"Bad memories: be yet welcomed...
you are my distant youth..."
The Army of Shadows
October 20, 1942
- Do you mind if we stop for a while?
- Not at all.
It won't take too long.
Just some shopping.
You have to sort it out for yourself
these days.
It's very understandable.
You will be alright in this camp.
The best camp in France!
This camp was for Germans.
I'm not sure I understand.
At the beginning of the war, we were
expecting a lot of german prisoners.
But of course there were none.
However, this camp is very useful now.
What good luck!
You said it!
Always the same; don't know who they
are, or how to treat them.
Some of them arrive without being charged
and stay forever.
Some, who committed crimes,
get out very quickly and become influential...
in the department,
or in the Vichy government.
Philippe Gerbier, 41 years old.
Engineer.
Vivid and independent mind.
Distant and ironic.
To subdue.
Seems to be influential.
To be treated gently.
Suspected of Gaullist thinking.
To subdue.
Set free by lack of evidence:
influential, to be treated gently.
The room you are going to
was for german officers.
I'm honored.
Certainly to be treated gently...
and certainly with caution.
Philippe Gerbier
Colonel Jarret Du Plessis
I don't know why you are here
but I'll tell you why I was arrested.
I said in a café that
Admiral Darlant was a bastard.
And Marechal Petain is a bastard also,
whose treatment of soldiers is reprehensible.
You, Colonel, have the chance
to suffer for your opinions.
Aubert, a druggist.
Do you know, Sir,
what a Mallert Shell is?
No.
It's a component of a
certain chemical reaction.
I am a chemist and I had to keep
a Mallert Shell.
I was censured for shell possession,
and no one would listen to any explications.
Octave Bonnafous.
Business man.
I unfortunately stumbled into
a Gaullist meeting...
No more laws!
Only bastards!
They took my pension away!
Where should I settle in?
As the room leader, allow me
to assign you this free mattress.
I am Legrain, communist.
Here's Armel, teacher and catholic.
Is he sleeping?
No, he's very sick.
No infirmary?
Already full.
Do you play dominos?
I'm afraid not.
We'll teach you.
Thank you, but I would rather not.
Excuse us then, but we must finish playing
before they turn off the light.
The Commandant is not as stupid as he looks.
He put me in with three idiots
and two lost children.
Going for a walk?
I'm working in the power station.
Well done!
I don't get paid,
but I like it and wish to practice.
See you later, comrade!
Are you communist?
No, but we're comrades all the same.
There are people here
from every country.
Russians.
Poles.
Algerians.
Jews from all over,
Gypsies.
Yugoslavians.
Romanian, Czech.
Germans against Nazism,
Italians against Fascism.
Spanish against Franco,
And some others,
arrested for smuggling.
You alright?
I managed the installation
of powerlines in Savoie.
You're an electrician?
- Just like you.
- Surely you're more qualified than I.
Maybe we could talk about it sometime.
Of course.
With pleasure.
The young teacher died one night,
silently.
The Algerians carried his body away.
I never heard him speak.
I'm not sad.
He's in a better place.
All debts will be paid one day.
Mister Gerbier.
I wish to speak with you tonight.
There are two obstacles to escape;
barbed wire and guards.
We can pass under the barbed wire,
and I can blind the guards
by turning off all the lights.
Why haven't you escaped yet?
I didn't want to escape alone,
and leave Armelle.
But I trust you.
Why are you telling me this?
I think you're needed on the outside.
Turn off the light and go to sleep.
Good night.
Secretly, between us,
the escape plan was taking shape.
Little by little.
Gerbier, come here.
Get ready.
Hurry please.
Please salute Legrain for me.
- There are the bastards.
- But...
Farewell, Sir.
Allow me, please.
Thanks.
There's just one chance.
I'll ask the soldier for something,
and then you'll cross the two gates.
Good luck.
Excuse me sir, do you have a cigarette?
What do you want?
I'd like a shave.
Marechal has said... Marechal has accomplished...
Marechal keeps his promises.
There you go.
I'll get your change.
- No wait...
- Wait for your change.
Take this.
Not very much, but it's all I have.
Thank you.
Paul Dounat received orders
from his organization.
He had to be in front of
the Marseilles courts
at noon, and wait there
for a friend he knew.
Police. Papers please.
All right.
But follow me anyway.
For a simple check.
Dirty job.
Felix, put on your hat.
No need in the car.
This is the guy who betrayed you.
I don't think there's any need to question you.
We should have refused him.
It's my fault.
So much to do,
and such little help.
Bison, faster please.
They'll notice us.
I'm also in a hurry.
I have to repair a radio,
and a young agent's bicycle.
And prepare tonight's reception.
Do you have the fake papers?
Yes, do you want them now?
The car must stay here.
It might be noticed.
- We'll take a walk.
- I'll come with you.
Not necessary.
Indeed.
I suppose not.
I'll pick you up later tonight.
One false move, and I shoot you.
Hell, when we rented this house,
the other one was empty!
Let's go anyway.
This way.
Is he the traitor that we're supposed to...
Yes, he is.
And are you the boss?
He is Claude LeMasque.
He's asked for harder assignments.
I came one hour earlier
to get everything ready...
and noticed that
some neighbors had arrived.
There was nobody yesterday!
I called immediately,
but you had already left.
It'll be alright.
We can begin the interrogating.
I prepared chairs, desk, paper...
This is not a trial.
Here's what it's about.
No way!
The neighbors will hear everything!
Listen...
The walls are paper-thin.
The English didn't deliver on
the silenced guns we requested.
Let's look for a better place.
How could you do it?
There's no better place.
The cellar won't work.
And neither will the attic.
We will need a good knife.
Bison has one.
A knife? Are you kidding?
I can't let you do that.
Felix! Go look for something
in the kitchen.
Please don't do this.
It's murder!
We are here to kill, regardless.
That's true, but not like this.
I know what you mean.
I swear I am not scared,
but this is my first time ...
This is our first time also,
can't you see?
I didn't find anything.
Maybe we could wait for Bison?
No, out of the question.
We must finish it now.
Bloody hell!
We can't just smash his head in, can we?
Gag him.
We must strangle him.
With our bare hands?
No.
There's a towel in the kitchen.
Enough!
You came here for this!
You wanted a harder assignment?
Here it is, so don't complain.
Make him sit down.
Felix, go behind.
I will hold his hands
and Masque will grab his legs.
I promise you won't suffer.
We're leaving.
I'm coming.
I could not imagine
this was possible.
Neither could I.
Get some cyanide pills.
And if you're arrested, eat them.
I will.
A glass of rum.
- Jean François!
- Felix!
It's been a long time.
Still young and handsome.
What are you doing in Marseilles?
I moved my workshop here from Paris.
And you?
Nothing special.
I have to go.
Can you walk a bit with me?
Alright, let's go.
Can you wait five minutes?
Five minutes.
Not my whole life.
Always lucky!
A bit risky to wear a pilot's jacket?
Fuck them.
- And then?
- And then what?
Just fuck them?
What else? Fight?
I know some more exciting things.
Really exciting?
Yes.
You'll have to get up early,
sleep on the train, on the road,
without reasons or explanations.
I'm interested.
Come and see me tomorrow,
here's my address.
No, don't write it down.
Just remember it.
And never tell a soul.
Of course.
Everyone says that...
but even a girlfriend...
I don't have one.
The girl in the bar?
I told her 5 minutes...
she'll have to wait a few more.
Parents you like to talk with...
They all died.
Just one brother,
who stayed in Paris.
I love him.
But would never confide in him.
Theater and Music Center.
Do you have an appointment?
With Mr. Russel.
This way, please.
I came as quickly as I could.
It's very urgent indeed.
How many people to board
for Gibraltar?
Two canadian officers,
from Dieppe commando,
three aviators from R.A.F.,
and also two Belgians
sentenced to death by Germans.
Eight including me.
Where will they wait for the submarine?
The doctor's clinic is under surveillance.
Couldn't we send them outside,
a few at a time?
No, too dangerous.
A Canadian officer will want to go into a café
and talk, forgetting his accent.
We will be informed of the submarine
arrival just one day in advance.
Everyone must go to the Viella farm.
Everyone?
It's not very safe...
We are not an insurance company.
On the contrary, indeed!
You must choose a real trustworthy man
to supervise everything.
I have this man.
You don't know him.
He did a very good job
on several recent missions.
He is now in Paris.
To deliver a new radio to Mathilde.
- When will he be back?
- Tomorrow morning.
Contact him immediately.
Everything must be ready by tomorrow night.
I'll be there at the last second.
And take a break.
When you will be gone.
No, now.
There'll be no time after that.
The luggages will be checked
inside the station.
Need some help?
Goodbye.
Open your case.
No smuggled goods?
No.
What is this?
Just a radio.
Okay, you can go.
Madam, please, luggage check.
Any trouble?
Not really. Stopped twice.
Tell Felix we need a new quartz.
The frequency has changed.
Alright. May I help you?
Certainly not.
The second radio is in the case.
Okay. Want something to eat?
No, thanks. I'm going to surprise someone...
Hello, Saint-Luc!
Ah, little Jean!
Still so many books around...
And the music instruments...
Nothing's changed.
The temperature has changed!
So I bought this,
in order to avoid freezing.
I stay there when I work at night
or when I eat.
But how did you get here?
Hope you have a permit.
Oh! Saint-Luc is back to earth.
He knows about the permit!
Of course I've got one.
And even...
...and I'm even very hungry.
We're going to eat.
Marie.
Yes, Mr. Luc.
What do we have on today's menu?
Some rutabaga like yesterday.
And?
Some unticketed cheese.
A little butter, but no bread.
I have tickets for bread,
and I can give all of them to you.
You're not resourceful.
You're still greedy.
So I am, but what can I do?
What about smuggling?
Marie is afraid of cops...
And I...
And you also...
It's becoming warmer.
I felt very warm this morning.
Twice.
So many people on the train or the metro...
I was wondering if Mathilde,
that I knew only a little bit...
was not closer to me than you,
my brother,
who I have so much love for,
but with whom I share so few things.
I went back to Marseilles the same day,
but today I had a very strange feeling.
Hello Mrs. Vialla.
Your home has become an hotel!
Hello!
- Hello!
- Good evening sir.
The fishing boat will await you
after midnight.
Maybe you can all sail together.
Mrs. Vialla's daughter
will lead you there, surreptitiously.
Perfect.
Am I leaving?
No. There's one more passenger.
Unexpected.
The big boss.
But he will not sail with us.
We're full.
You will board with him.
Somewhere else.
Bison will bring him.
You'll wait for my light signal.
Three short and one long.
Got it.
Madame, we will leave.
How much do I owe you?
You can pay later.
You already told me that before.
Yet you came back,
so you must like the welcome.
You will walk in single file.
Not too near,
but always keeping watch over each other.
Not a sound, not a word.
Keep quiet, I have a gun!
- What are you doing here at night?
- And you?
I'm Mrs. Vialla's brother-in-law.
The nurse?
I'm verifying that everything is alright.
And then?
It's okay, a police patrol has just departed.
Germans are too few and get lost.
So they trust the customs.
And the customs?
The customs? But I am the customs!
I am the only one in charge
in this area.
No kidding!
Get on board!
Good luck, boss.
So strange to think the big boss
looks like any other man.
Here in this boat, where base and
tip of the pyramid meet.
Strange.
I'll have to talk with Saint-Luc
about it after the war.
Watch your steps sir.
I'm so happy to be travelling with you.
I feel the same.
I cannot deliver you all the weapons
you asked me for.
The English don't believe too much in
the efficiency of the French resistance.
They want to keep as many planes
as possible to bomb Germany.
But we will improve
your transmission equipment.
So we'll send you some radio operators,
and we'll help your agents
to improve the landing place
Jardie invited me to the ceremony
just an hour in advance.
The war will be over for the French
when they can see this wonderful movie.
I heard Felix was arrested today.
Free France
I still had many things
to do in London,
but I decided to go back to France
that same day.
Never.
When your feet hit the ground,
don't try to stay upright.
Bend your knees and fall, understood?
I think so.
Mathilde moved to Lyon
during my absence.
She's a great leader.
I made her my assistant.
The boss already told me how
wonderful she was.
But I'm still surprised by her skill
in giving and receiving orders.
She studied the map of Gestapo
headquarters for hours.
She finally discovered where
Felix was imprisoned.
A jail for prisoners that they
absolutely need information from.
At first, she wanted to use a bomb.
Then she made another plan,
which required a disguise.
She arranged for me a new place
for my headquaters.
No place is more secure or pleasant.
My host is now the Baron de Ferte,
an ex-cavalry officer.
Before the war,
the Republic was my enemy.
With my tenant farmer, and my servant,
I had created a little army
equipped with guns and pikes...
to assault the prefecture
on horseback
in the case of royalist insurrection.
This militia still exists,
and is used to protect me now.
The Baron himself suggested use of
his field for landing and dropping.
We did as he wished and even more.
Strange carousel...
While the first airplane is landing...
the second one keeps on flying
at low altitude...
to cover up the sound of the
first plane's landing and take-off.
And then they switch.
This night, four men left for London,
and four men arrived from there.
Bison, Le Masque, Jean-François
et Mathilde were supervising.
Does your husband know
about your activities?
No he doesn't.
Nor does my daughter.
Here she is.
17 years old.
Don't keep it with you.
You're right. I won't.
Before anything else,
we must talk about Felix.
I know Felix doesn't have
prussic acid pills.
I'm not afraid of him talking,
but he has no way to escape torture.
The Gestapo will not give in.
And he will suffer for days, maybe weeks...
I know that.
There aren't many possibilities.
Did you find one?
Yes. Enter the Gestapo
and leave with Felix.
Mathilde, I want to rescue Felix.
But not at any cost.
I cannot sacrifice anyone.
I don't need many men.
With Le Masque, Jean-François,
Bison and me, I can make it.
No problem.
What is your plan?
Bison, can you get three
german officer's uniforms?
Of course.
Do it then.
The problem is how to contact
and inform Felix.
I haven't figured it out yet,
but I will.
Because he must be ready
when we will come.
I have tried to contact him
for a week now.
But that building is very
strictly guarded.
Yes, not so easy to enter.
- Careful it's warm.
- Thanks.
Mr. Gerbier
I don't have the courage of
Le Masque nor the strength of Bison.
Nor the skills of Mathilde.
I will not participate in this escape plan
But I'm sure that
my comrades will succeed.
Don't try to find out
what happened to me.
Mr. Dupont knows much of
the resistance movement.
How did you make it?
Well...
We will use only two uniforms.
I know, Mrs. Mathilde.
I won't let you do it without me.
And I won't let you go with us!
Remember what you said,
"I cannot sacrifice anyone."
Especially if "anyone" is you.
But Mathilde, why you instead of me?
Listen.
Two men won't be noticed.
But three men would.
When Jean-François was still there,
you asked for three uniforms.
But at least, I would have taken
only Le Masque and Le Bison.
Jean-François...
I trusted him.
Me too, that's not what I meant.
But... I could never imagine
he would leave us this way.
Who's that man?
He was denounced by an anonymous letter.
You can enter.
Naturally, is Dupont your real name?
Of course.
Which organization do you belong?
I don't know what you mean.
Do you understand the consequences?
You will be shot under this name
and no one will know what happened to you.
I decided to leave this place.
Perhaps a premonition?
Three days after, Baron de Ferte
and his men were arrested and shot.
We must take a man
named Felix Lepercq to Paris...
to the headquarters of
Oberstufuhrer Bolmerburg.
- Felix Lepercq?
- Yes, a terrorist.
Hurry up, it's urgent.
Get down.
One moment, please.
An ambulance from Paris Gestapo...
wants to take terrorist
Felix Lepercq.
Make an on-duty Doctor come and give
the transfer authorization.
Felix.
Felix can you hear me?
Mathilde, Le Bison and Le Masque
are here.
I will help you.
Are you in a lot of pain?
It's not possible.
He will suffer a lot,
until he dies.
Impossible. I can't let you
transfer a dying man. Sorry.
Okay, I will report this.
Felix.
I have several prussic acid pills.
Do you want one?
We could have saved Felix.
No.
No one and nothing could.
Not even you.
Besides, every policeman is looking for you.
You should disappear for awhile.
The next airplane is yours.
You're not serious?
Resistance organizations are rising
from everywhere.
We must unite them, train them,
supply them.
There's nobody to replace me now.
If you get arrested, we will
replace you however we can.
Police!
So, is the food good here?
You have meat at every meal,
and without tickets?
We will check all papers.
Hurry up, let's go.
I'll keep it, for later.
He says "Finish your smoke. They're
coming and I don't want trouble."
Everyone has his own troubles.
This time is the last one.
The word "Love" makes sense to me
only when I think of the boss.
He's more important to me
than anything.
More than everything.
But not more than life.
If Luc Jardie would die,
I would still like to live.
And I'm going to die.
And I'm not afraid.
How is that possible?
It's because I'm too narrow-minded
to believe it.
And if I don't believe it
until the last moment,
I will never die.
What a discovery!
The boss would like the idea.
I must explore this discovery.
I must...
You will turn your back to the
machine-gun and face the wall.
And then you will run
as fast as you can.
We will not shoot immediately.
We will give you a chance.
If you get to the wall, you'll
be shot in the next round instead.
We can try anyway.
Nothing to lose.
He knows about my legs.
He's waiting for the show.
And I feel more tied by his certainty
than by my chains.
Go!
I don't want to run.
I won't.
The most important thing was to time
it precisely. Mathilde did.
Oh, it was easy
with all the information we had.
And if I didn't run?
Something wrong?
Thinking about those who didn't run?
No, thinking about this officer,
was what convinced me to run.
Like a rabbit in panic!
Go on.
It's good to be safe.
Enough for one month.
There is drinking water, but I'll try
to bring you some wine.
No way, see you in a month.
All right.
I'm gonna leave.
Somebody could spot the car.
Okay.
Treat your arm and your leg.
It might get infected.
I put a shaver on the table.
I'm by myself for three weeks,
like a timid animal.
I write a long report for London,
and try to believe I'm still useful.
I haven't seen Mathilde
or anyone since.
I read the five books Luc Jardie
wrote before the war.
They keep me company.
At night, Jean-François'
disappearance haunts me.
Le Bison or Le Masque?
But it's ... you!
I have to talk to you.
When did you come back?
Four days ago.
Since Mathilde was arrested.
Mathilde?
We have to talk about her tonight.
We have to, Philippe.
They didn't hurt her.
She got in touch with us.
Gestapo found her real name
very quickly,
and where her family was living.
She had her daughter's picture,
and you can guess what happened...
That picture?
This was her only mistake.
The Germans quickly found her weakness.
Why did she keep the picture?
I told her!
Listen to this,
She begged the Germans to give her
the picture back.
What do you mean?
Mathilde sent us an S.O.S.
The Germans gave her two choices.
Tell everything she knows
about the organization,
or they will send her daughter
to Poland as a prostitute.
Now you know everything.
We have to find a solution.
Could she escape?
No, she can't escape,
nor commit suicide.
Mathilde will never give up
her daughter to the gestapo.
Can she stall time?
Until when?
It's not a solution.
Here comes Le Bison.
Don't tell him I'm here.
Go in that room.
Here are some new glasses.
Thanks.
Any news from Mathilde?
What's going on?
I know nothing.
What?
I don't. Here's a letter.
Mathilde was released yesterday.
And two comrades were arrested today.
Is it so?
If they say it is.
Le Masque, you knew this?
I'm not in charge of this report.
Mathilde is to be killed immediately.
I can't believe it.
I will never hurt Mrs. Mathilde.
I have been working with her.
She saved me once.
This is a great woman!
Men...as many as you want...
But Mrs. Mathilde, never!
We will not discuss about it.
She must disappear and she will.
You won't do it!
We have other killers.
If necessary, I will do it.
You won't.
You don't have the right.
You could have run as a champion...
you would be dead already
if not for Mrs. Mathilde.
You won't do it.
She can give me to the Gestapo,
she protected me, and you,
and now,
she's protecting her daughter.
Can we blame her?
Enough!
The decision is made.
If you're as cowardly as that,
I'll kill you first!
Stop it!
Shut your mouth! You were still a child
when I started commanding men...
What do you think?
Would I let you do that?
Have you gone crazy?
You, get out!
Or I'll kill you both!
You need a few cooler
heads in this room.
My friend, sit down.
Calm down and have a cigarette.
Don't you think, Gerbier?
You heard everything.
Yes, Mathilde is truly a great woman.
Even more than you know.
But we're going to kill her.
I can't believe you.
You will, listen my friend.
We will kill Mathilde,
because she asked us to.
She told you that?
No, but it's not difficult to guess.
Think of it like this,
If Mathilde only wanted to save
her daughter,
she just had to give names
and addresses.
In spite of this, Mathilde told them
we change our address every day,
she must contact some people...
whatever...
So that they set her free.
Clear, isn't it?
Imagine you were in her position.
Forced to betray comrades.
And suicide is not allowed.
I would like to be killed.
Do you find yourself braver
or better than Mathilde?
Please excuse me.
Take a german car. Le Masque will
drive. I'll come with you.
Are you mad?
I'm sure Mathilde would like
to see me.
Please, this is not your place.
This is an order.
You didn't have to do that, boss.
Do you really believe what you said?
I don't know.
Maybe this hypothesis is right.
Maybe she just wanted to see
her daughter again,
and now is finding it harder
to give it all up.
That's what I want to find out.
I had to come back to you
for the hardest job.
You, in this car, with killers!
Nothing's sacred now in this world.
February 23rd, 1943, Sunday.
Go.
Nov the 8th, 1943.
Le Masque had just time
to take his prussic acid pill.
Dec the 16th, 1943.
Le Bison was beheaded with an axe
in a German jail.
Jan the 22nd, 1944.
Luc Jardie died under torture,
after giving one name: his own.
Jan the 13rd, 1944.
Gerbier decided not to run this time...
André Dewavrin himself.
- Alias Colonel Passy.
From Joseph Kessel's book
"L'armée des ombres"