DEATH SHADOWS
Jitte-mai
Cast
Mariko Ishihara
Masanori Sera
Mari Natsuki
Mio Takagi
Akiko Kana Peter
Ken'ichi Kato
Nagare Hagiwara
Naoto Takenaka
Junji Takada
Eitaro Ozawa
Tsuruko Shofukutei Shoji Kobayashi
Ken'ichi Matsuno
Kyoichi Sato Sotaro Ibuki
Rikiya Yasuoka Ryuji Katagiri
Takeo Chii
Takuzo Kawatani
Tsunehiko Watase
Directed by
Hideo Gosha
North Ward Magistrate Office
Record of Criminal Cases
Otomatsu, a servant at the Ise-ya
store in Shinbaba-mae, Shiba.
Injured the store owner in an attempted
murder out of personal grudges.
Sentenced to death.
Kanpachi, a servant at the
Nabeshima Clan's Edo Mansion.
Robbed a house and committed murder.
Sentenced to death.
Yasuke, an assistant officer in Atago.
Knowingly aiding criminals and
extorted portions of their loot.
Sentenced to death.
You all have returned straight from hell.
It takes nothing to send you right back.
If you wish to live again and serve
society, take these truncheons.
If you do, they'll save your lives.
Listen - as clear as a bell,
this is your one last chance.
You only have two choices now:
To fall into hell again or
join the shadow police.
Two choices only. Which will you choose?
All right.
As of this moment, you're
human but not individuals.
You're the shadow police that'll vanquish
great evil from behind the scenes.
From now on, you have nothing
to do with the outside world.
I've got your voices in my hand now.
20 years later
Boss, look out! It's the shadow police!
Boss! Boss!
Damn you!
You... you're my daughter.
What a surprise.
We knew from our investigation
that major merchants...
like Hizen-ya and Mine-ya are associated
with that shadow organization.
But this is Limori Kansa, Advisor in
Edo of the 1000 koku Hinoki Clan.
There are also daimyo Tachibana
Sakyo-no-suke and Horiuchi Juroza'emon.
They won't be quiet about it.
They're the ones that'll be in
trouble if this case is exposed.
They're in cahoots with Denzo the Fang...
a major criminal who controls
appointed money exchangers...
for the Shogunate behind the scenes...
and schemed to make great profits
by disrupting the rice market.
Gonza the Badger.
Koda Denroku.
Matsu the Snake Neck.
That bastard was keeping a low
profile for a while since he broke jail.
I don't care about the small guys.
What's the story with Denzo?
Yes, well...
Yasuke the Viper - it's unlike him.
Please understand how I truly feel.
I want to talk with you.
What's that look on your face?
You run into your daughter for
the first time in 10 years...
and she's a member of
Denzo the Fang's gang.
Does that bother you so much?
You look exactly like your mom.
After all these years, you
want to rehash the past?
Well, just listen.
It was 20 years ago.
My vocal chords were cut and I lost
my voice in exchange for my life.
I became a shadow cop talking
only through sign language.
I was after a guy named Aioi
Kisaburo suspected to be...
the chief of all prostitution boat owners.
The bastard was the second
son of a 1000 koku daimyo...
untouchable by the town police.
I knew O'Saki was Kisaburo's lover...
but I had no idea how young she was.
I fell in love.
Frankly, I didn't care
about Kisaburo any longer.
I asked her not to sleep with
other men and be my girl only.
She wasn't doing it because
she wanted money.
My earnest plea moved her and
she told me where Kisaburo hid.
Looking back, it's laughable how a
shadow cop like me could act like that.
But I was simply ecstatic to
be with your mom O'Saki.
Time flies, and I completely
forgot that I was a shadow cop.
They told me Aioi Kisaburo brilliantly
escaped from the exile island.
He killed three guards.
It appears one of his men aided him.
He disappeared on a boat the man
rowed into the dark on a stormy night.
You know what he looks like
more than anybody else.
I got information they're hanging out
in the vicinity of Joshu. Go there.
I've got a wife and kid.
Their happiness is my priority.
Please understand.
For 10 years, I let you have a good dream.
Do you still want to
continue living an easy life?
Are you gonna come back to us?
Tell me you'll be back
someday. Promise me you will.
It's over. It's all over.
Our marriage is over.
My tie with our girl is over.
The happiest time of my life is over too.
Darling!
Darling...
I wish I could show you...
how mom lived after you abandoned us.
But don't worry.
She didn't suffer too long.
She died in less than a year.
I trained hard to become a killer.
I promised myself I'd avenge her death
by killing you by my own hands someday.
A young little girl managed to survive
with the hope of that one promise.
I'm sorry, O'Cho. Please get out of here.
You've gotta be kiddin'.
You're letting me go?
You abandoned me like a cat or a dog...
and this is the best you can do for me now?
I'm not gonna listen to you.
I want you to be happy.
Please leave here.
Listen, though I grew in the mud
I'm as pure as a lotus flower.
I've managed to lean on
my own shoulder so far.
I beg you, please leave.
We suffered... both mom and I.
I won't let you... I won't let you...
What's this?
Please understand.
Don't ask me any questions.
Just abandon me.
Please let me go.
Viper.
What happened?
You let Denzo the Fang escape, but
I suspect there's something else.
You know what'll happen
to you when you quit.
Death is the rule.
Yasuke, you want to end your life so much
that you're willing to abandon them?
I don't want to know what
happened in your personal life.
But remember you're a shadow cop.
Human yet not a person.
Turn your heart into a rock, Yasuke.
Finish off Denzo the Fang and his gang.
There's a major criminal hiding behind him.
Your cleaning job hasn't even started.
Ms. O'Cho, give him just a
moment. Right now, the boss is...
Ms. O'Cho.
What's that look on your face?
Stop it, already.
What on earth is going on here?
Are you letting back in the
sneaky thief you once kicked out?
She may be a thief but I
forgive her when she's back.
Especially when she brings with
her a special piece of information.
Information?
- Yeah.
I heard you're the only
daughter of Yasuke the Viper.
When I think about it...
it was a total mystery how on earth
the shadow cops learned about...
our meeting that day.
No way, I'd never betray you.
Don't make me laugh!
I was waiting for you, dad.
Oops, hold it, don't be impatient.
If you want your daughter to live...
listen, Viper, back then I was the
one who got a surprise attack...
but from now on, I've got a better hand.
I saw it with my own eyes.
You were negotiating with
her behind closed doors.
Come on, I want you to give up
those powerful black truncheons.
Drop them!
What do you think, Viper?
I came up with this trick.
Do you like it?
Your dear daughter is next.
Please save her.
She didn't betray you.
Torture me instead. You can
do anything you want to me.
What the heck is that? I have
no idea what you're saying.
Are they hand movements
in a dance or something?
Just save O'Cho.
All right, all right. No need to worry.
I'll kill you both, father and daughter. Right?
Look how helpless Yasuke the Viper is now.
All right, drag her down.
Dad...
Forgive me, dad.
From the bottom of my heart...
I ask for your forgiveness.
Forgive me, O'Cho, forgive me.
Dad...
Forgive me.
Forgive me, dad.
Dad...
Come and see this everyone...
This is O'Cho the Flower Storm,
the lover of Denzo the Fang who...
as the boss of the underworld, kept
the great city of Edo in turmoil.
Truly, truly it's this woman.
Look at her well and look at her again.
She's bound for execution.
She'll be tied to a stake,
decapitated in public...
then her head will be on public display.
This is her journey to hell!
I don't wanna die!
Spare me!
Spare me! Spare me!
How distasteful of her
to struggle at this point.
Stab her!
The woman named O'Cho the Flower
Storm was executed today as scheduled.
This truncheon is his memento.
You'll now carry on as a
shadow cop in Yasuke's place.
It's just as I killed my dad.
So why do you want me to do this?
Dad let a rotten child like me get away.
He warned me to leave Denzo.
Had I only listened to him,
he wouldn't have had to die.
But I... I...
He must've died full of regret.
He wasn't after a small
time criminal like Denzo...
but a high rank official in the
Shogunate that's behind it all.
He's such a major figure that even...
the Magistrate or Chief of
Justice can't touch him.
Unless they've got
concrete evidence, that is.
What do you say, O'Cho?
If you don't want to be a
shadow cop, that's fine.
But don't you want to finish
the job Yasuke started?
You'll understand what he went through.
You'll understand the pain of a man who...
gave up his wife and daughter
and lived his life as a shadow cop.
The same dark blood of
Yasuke runs in your body.
It's not easy to wipe the stain off.
Pick it up.
That's the only way...
only way left for you to
console your dad's spirit.
Now, let me tell you what plan I have for you.
The merchant Kano-ya Genshiro was once a
member of the 65,000 koku Hamada Clan.
He was an intelligent samurai who served...
as a counselor to chief of the
clan, named Mukai Genshiro.
The chief of the clan, Matsudaira
Suo-no-kami Yasutomo...
used a trivial mistake Genshiro
made as an excuse to outcast him...
and declared he no longer had
anything to do with the clan.
But in fact...
Suo-no-kami forged a trade license called
the inspection exemption license...
and gave it to Genshiro.
He ordered Genshiro to take on the
front of a trade merchant and...
engage in the crime of smuggling and
support the clan's finance unofficially.
That's right.
Sir Matsudaira Suo-no-kami is
the shogun's blood relation.
Four years ago, he ran up the promotional
ladder to join the Shogunate...
and in a blink of an eye became
Chief of Senior Advisors.
He's now the shogun of darkness.
With the enormous amount of
money earned through smuggling...
he ordered the appointed money
exchangers in Kuramae to buy up the rice...
in an attempt to turn the
rice market upside down.
O'Cho, you know well
about the scheme yourself.
Denzo the Fang worked for him.
The shogun of darkness
has no match in power.
There's only one thing that'll cause his fall...
a piece of concrete evidence.
We need to obtain the
inspection exemption license.
Do you understand, O'Cho?
There's no way to achieve
this by playing it straight.
A shadow cop's check mate, a
move Yasuke didn't get to make.
That's what you must accomplish.
Don't forget it, O'Cho,
your life is in my hands.
Mourning
Oh, the lady is dressed in
quite gorgeous clothes.
I'm certain she'll go
straight to heaven in peace.
Yes. Though she was our maid, we
loved her like our own daughter.
We were discussing her
marriage arrangements when...
a sudden illness fell upon her.
We felt so much for her that we wanted
to treat her in the best way we could.
So, we put on her the kimono and obi
I brought with me when I got married.
I see.
Well, well, it's quite a generous gesture.
I'll be sure to pray for her most thoroughly.
Idiot!
Did you give them the obi
and the obi fastener too?
Yes, she had no family.
I wanted to do for her the best
I could upon her departure.
I know I was on the road,
but without my consent...
What is it? Why so upset?
What is it about the kimono?
I don't care about the kimono.
It's the obi fastener.
In the fastener there was...
Get Sakichi here. Sakichi!
Yes.
You were right there and... how could you...
Idiot! Call a palanquin.
Yes.
Dismissed.
My dear, tell me what's going on.
Let go of me.
Before you interrogate me, be
ashamed of your own blunder.
Dear?
Dear!
Now, gentlemen...
They're silk embroideries.
The obi and its fastener are
woven with gold threads.
The lining is in crimson.
I'll have to set a higher price for this set.
3 ryo.
- 4 ryo.
5 ryo.
- 6 ryo.
Any more bids?
10 ryo.
Out of the way!
- What's wrong?
The gold-threaded obi and the
fastener that the dead girl wore...
Where is it?
Did someone buy it?
Yes, it was quite high quality.
Who did you sell it to? Tell me who bought it!
Hello.
Where are the silk
embroidered kimono and...
the gold-threaded obi and the fastener
that you bought from the priest?
Well, sorry, those items are...
We sure did purchase them but...
How much are they? Well,
the price doesn't matter.
I want to buy them back.
Twice the price? Three times?
Tell me how much you're
selling them for. Tell me.
Those items have already been...
Sold?
- Yes.
A singing teacher named
O'Chika in Hakusanshita...
had been asking for quality
material for a long time...
Sir? Sir!
Hey... come on.
Oh, don't woo me so persistently.
It makes me feel guilty.
I want you to be clear this is nothing serious.
Oh, you're so cold.
But that's what I hate and love about you.
Stop it now.
I'm not desperate enough to have
to play along an older lady's game.
What did you say?
I'm sick to the head from
the stink of your powder.
Don't you have the nerve.
What's that look?
You aren't so naïve that it
surprises you to hear it.
You're right.
I like it when you act bad like this.
I really like it.
You're suffocating me.
Let me kill you, okay?
I'm suffocating.
I'm gonna kill you.
I'll kill you, and then kill myself.
C'mon, I want you to kill me.
Let me die. Okay?
Hello.
Sorry to call on you so late,
but I have urgent business.
Please open up.
Sorry to call on you so late
but I have urgent business.
Please open up.
Ms. O'Chika. Ms. O'Chika?
I have urgent business.
Ms. O'Chika?
I'm not a criminal. I have
a favor to ask of you.
Please open up. Ms. O'Chika.
Someone help! Somebody!
Master, madam has... madam has...
Hanae...
Hanae!
What on earth happened?
After you left, she locked
herself up in her room.
We kept asking how she was
and there was no answer.
We got worried and looked in the
room, and found her this way.
Why did you, Sanosuke?
I'm not blind.
Why did you - no, need to kill her?
It's your own fault.
My fault?
You can't panic like that in front of
others, or eventually they might...
She... she didn't know anything.
Not yet.
But if she were alive...
She wouldn't have let up asking
you what it was that she did wrong.
And I know you'd have told her one day.
Sanosuke!
- Don't lose it, Genshiro.
We must take out any seed of trouble.
Completely.
It's all for the clan, for the survival
of the 65,000 koku Hamada Clan.
Wasn't that our mission?
Can't we get the obi fastener back?
It was a mistake.
It was a clever idea to hide it in the
fastener, but it wasn't well thought out.
If you'd just told me about it, you
wouldn't have lost your beloved wife.
Now that Denzo the Fang has been killed,
the police must be closing in on us.
If we leave things be...
- I know.
I promise to recover the
exemption license myself.
What time was it approximately
when you saw the man?
It was later than 11:30.
That's strange.
- What is?
Look.
It's not leaving an impression.
If she was killed later than 11:30...
pressing against her skin like this
would leave the spot discolored.
Which means she had died much earlier.
That's right.
But how could one kill
a sexy woman like this?
What a waste.
Damn you.
Sis... Sis, please forgive me.
Sis...
Sis, that woman was so persistent
I didn't know what to do. Sis...
I don't care what happened.
I wanted the obi fastener you
strangled her little neck with.
There was an incredible treasure beyond
your imagination buried inside it.
That's enough.
There's no use torturing
a little guy like him now.
The fastener is in the
Hacchobori Police's possession.
But, sir, that's no excuse to...
Hold on.
Genshiro is the only person who knows
what's inside the fastener besides us.
It's not too late.
We must take it back, no matter who
has it, and by all means necessary.
Hey, madam!
It's the Hacchobori Police.
I was told this is the House of Tricks.
Will you come out?
Is anybody home?
Are you the one they call O'Ren the Thistle?
I know you're a cop, but you can't invite
yourself into someone's private home.
Whoa.
Hidden behind the front of
a male prostitute house...
you run an illegal business as a tattooist.
I think I'm giving you plenty of slack here.
Hand over the brat named Sentaro to me.
Sentaro?
I know what happened.
A singing teacher named O'Chika,
who was murdered last night...
used to meet Sentaro here
to fool around with him.
Murdered? Do you mean to say Sentaro did it?
Yeah.
He strangled her with this.
What a waste.
She was a sexy woman.
Hand him over.
I'm short tempered.
Listen, it was a big mistake for him
to commit a crime in Hacchobori.
If you try to protect him in
anyway, you'll get it too.
I'm not protecting him.
He hasn't been around lately.
Is that right. Okay.
By the way, since you don't seem
to know, let me tell you something.
They call me Hell in this neighborhood.
Let me know if you find out where
Sentaro is. Sorry to have bothered you.
Don't just hide there and come out.
Sir...
I have a favor to ask of you.
A favor?
Oh, your wife's memento?
Yes.
It was something she'd always
cherished since we got married.
Then, while I was away in Osaka...
my servants didn't know.
Is that so?
I didn't know it was a
post-funeral recycle item.
Anyway, how did you find
out it was in my possession?
Yes, I asked the second-hand clothing
merchant who bought it. That's how.
Your story could bring
tears to someone's eyes.
I beg you please.
If money helps, I'm willing
to pay you any price.
Money?
Money sounds good.
I love it, I love it!
But you see, something's been
bothering me for quite a while.
After the singing teacher
in heat got strangled...
someone tried to take this
piece off her dead body.
Well, I'm not saying it's you.
But the maid who saw it told
me what the guy looked like...
and you seem to fit the description.
It looks like this piece has some
hidden value I'm not even aware of.
I wouldn't mind selling it to you...
but first I wanna find out what the
value is before I name the price.
Sir...
- Don't worry.
It's an important piece of
evidence of a murder case.
I'll wear it right next to my skin until then.
It looks like a shower.
I guess I'll borrow an umbrella somewhere.
Don't draw it!
I've got eyes on my back too!
You're a samurai, aren't you?
How dare you damage my best jacket.
Don't play me!
Sir!
I'd call it a draw due to an injury.