It's becoming more interesting.
Sir?
I know you're home.
I wanted to drink with you.
Well, come on in.
I located Sentaro.
I got him to tell me where.
Give me some credit, will you?
I won't buy it until I see his face.
You will soon.
So I thought, before you do...
Boss Hell, you know, don't you?
I've fallen for you.
You fell for me?
As you can see, I haven't had a woman lately.
I'll accept this treat.
Help me. Help me please.
A ladies' man's all messed up.
Save me. Sis, spare me.
I beg you.
- I will save you.
So you've gotta do what I tell you.
There.
You befriended that Hell boy, didn't you?
I know what's going on.
You wanna take over Denzo the Fang's job...
and reign as the boss of the underworld.
Even so, I don't think the
65,000 koku Hamada Clan...
would directly deal with someone like you.
There must be a go-between.
I wanna know who that is.
Say it!
Hell has what you're after.
If you want it so badly,
use your body to get it.
You see, I was honestly in love with Denzo.
Remember, I'll settle
accounts with you one day.
Was it you who wanted to see me?
Boss Hell, I presume?
Aren't you a foxy woman?
Ms. O'Ren sent me.
It's about Sentaro, isn't it?
Well, before we go further, there's
something I want to ask you.
What is it?
Once you catch Sentaro...
you won't need the obi
fastener any more, right?
It's about this again.
Well, won't you give it to me?
I see.
I bet it looks good on you.
But I can't.
Everybody wants it so much that
it makes me wanna hold on to it.
I knew you'd say that.
You're a tough one to get.
It makes me blush.
Look, there's the one
you're looking for - Sentaro.
You can take all the credit, Boss Hell.
You brat.
For real?
I'm not gonna die!
I don't die!
It hurts.
It hurts, it hurts.
Damn it! Don't be stupid!
Don't be so scared.
Hell's dead and is now a mere corpse.
Now, I don't need you anymore.
I'll spare your life.
Go wherever you wanna.
Who is it? Is it O'Ren?
I recognize the sword style.
You're Kano-ya, aren't you?
I decided to side with you because of her.
When you accomplish your
mission and get your reward...
please remember your
promise to give her half.
I'm worried about my blind girl's future.
They say love is blind, and that's true.
I'll even be your spy.
Please understand.
I'd gladly give my life for her.
By the way, who took the other half?
Kano-ya did. O'Ren's in the picture too.
Things are getting complicated.
Well, I can take care of O'Ren.
She doesn't yet know I'm working for you.
The bitch O'Cho has come out of hiding,
connected our business with Kano-ya.
She killed Boss Denzo.
We've gotta make a traitor
see what price she has to pay.
I know.
After Boss Denzo died...
we've all sworn to look up to you
as the boss of the underworld.
Tell us anything you want us to do.
Senzo, you got a problem?
Well, his speech is so sentimental.
I'm so not used to it that it tickles me.
What!?
A newcomer like you who drifted
from Aioi Kisaburo's family...
would never understand the
way we feel about Boss Denzo!
I see. Is that right?
Gin, didn't you get arrested for killing
a waitress in Shinagawa half a year ago?
So what?
Isn't that weird?
How did you come back out now?
Were the cops in Denma-cho
so impressed by your loyalty...
that they decided to dismiss
you with no charges?
Sis, I didn't do anything.
Please understand. The truth is I...
A spy must be punished.
You're a disgrace to Denzo's family.
Right, sis?
I don't even wanna see it. Get rid of him.
Yes!
I found it where Boss Kakizaki was killed.
This emblem is of Kano-ya, isn't it?
It sure is our emblem.
It belongs to the owner Genshiro.
That's the key.
Wait! That's why we
wanna negotiate with you.
We're willing to let things slide
depending on how you wanna play it.
Pack up 100.
We'll wait for you at
Kakinuki Temple at 6 tonight.
Don't act stupid.
Our men are standing by, ready for action
if anything happens to either of us.
Thanks for your time.
Don't underestimate me, Hanji from Osaka.
I feel bad about Boss Kakizaki...
but thanks to him, we've
come upon a money tree.
That's right.
We can drink 'til our bellies are full, and
sleep with women 'til we drop dead.
I feel bad about Boss Hell,
but we're going to paradise.
Thank Buddha, thank
Buddha... What a good fortune.
He really put his foot into it.
How could he lose the pill case?
Leave it to me.
I'm sheltering Genshiro at
the House of Tricks in Aoyagi.
You don't have to worry
about them ever finding him.
It's not his problem alone.
As the police investigation progresses...
this place will eventually be exposed.
By the way, are you gonna just
ignore the low rank cops who came?
I have no time to be bothered by them.
O'Ren...
Do you wanna run away with me?
It's stupid to bet one's life
on a future that's uncertain.
Before it's too late, we can take
all the money from the safe...
and together we'll...
Aikawa Sanosuke, I presume.
You're from the Hamada Clan.
It's Master's order!
Wait a minute. Wait a minute now.
I have nothing to do with it.
I'm just... He... he hired me for money.
Wait a minute! If you kill me, you'll
never get the exemption license back!
I have the paper... only half of it.
But I know who's got the other half.
I can get it for you.
So you killed this man...
but as long as the paper's floating around...
the clan will be in danger.
Am I not right?
Hire me.
I won't complain as long as I get paid when...
I get you both pieces of the paper.
I'm an underworld criminal who'll never
be able to walk in the sun anyway.
I'll shut up and vanish from your sight.
Welcome.
The flower card hanging from Sentaro's
neck had a butterfly on it, which means me.
The card was cut in half...
which means you wanted to negotiate
with me for the exemption license.
Denzo the Fang used to
use the riddle all the time.
You got it right.
C'mon, give me the license.
There's one question I
wanna ask you, though.
How did you know to cut a card
in half to mean the license?
How do you know it was cut in half?
That was a giveaway.
I want the half of the license you have.
How did you expect me to come
carrying the license with me like a fool?
You're quite dumb, aren't you?
We already know where you live.
We lured you out here.
What?
Yasu.
Save me, please.
If I die, O'Tami will be all alone.
I beg you please. Spare me.
Your beloved wife's probably
waiting for you in heaven by now.
O'Tami.
How pitiful.
We can do whatever we want with you now.
But it's no fun to kill you too quickly.
I'll show you what kind of
tricks this house comes with.
Have yourself a ball!
Squirm in pain and dry up like a mummy!
What is this?
As you see, it's the exemption
license you were dying to get.
Except, it's only half of it that O'Cho had.
Don't worry.
The other half has already
been in our possession.
When O'Cho killed the Hell Cop,
we took it in the nick of time.
O'Cho is dead now, probably fuming in hell.
Senior Advisor.
Kano-ya Genshiro...
We executed Aikawa Sanosuke by
the Master's order the other day.
Kano-ya no longer exists on earth.
You exploited your privilege as the
appointed merchant for the Hamada Clan...
engaged in illegal trade of smuggling,
and indulged in profiteering.
We know you're guilty. You
cannot make any excuses.
Did you hear that?
Now that the license has been recovered,
they have no more need for you.
I did it all for the clan, all for the clan.
Genshiro...
We must prove our innocence
to the Shogunate. You must die.
As you promised.
We have nothing to do with you anymore.
I'll shut up and disappear.
Do shut up.
What the hell are you doing?
I figured it'd turn out this way.
What?
Guys, come on out!
Sis!
C'mon, hurry!
Hanae!
O'Cho.
Be still. Don't let the wound open up.
Why?
Why did you?
Out of pity, or...?
I really don't know.
You served your master loyally,
putting your life at risk.
Yet he abandoned you like a dog.
I couldn't stand it.
What's that?
It's goodbye.
I may not come back.
Take it and leave town.
Where are you going?
It's none of your business where I go.
Your ties with the Hamada Clan are severed.
It isn't. The clan is all I've got.
You gotta be kiddin'.
They betrayed you. They abandoned you.
Shut up!
My entire life was devoted to the clan.
I even let my wife get killed for my loyalty.
If I lose the clan, what would I be?
If you try to obtain the license, I'll
stop you even if I had to risk my life!
Don't be stupid!
What did I save your life for then?
I couldn't watch you die.
I wanted you to start a new life.
O'Cho.
Stop me if you want.
You're no longer my enemy.
You're as good as dead now.
Wait, O'Cho.
Kill me before you go!
Kill me and you can go!
No matter how many samurai come...
they can't touch us 'til
they get the license back.
Here's the 3000 ryo as promised.
You made quite a mess
the other day, didn't you?
Don't underestimate us.
Listen...
We could use the license to suck the
blood out of the Hamada Clan if we want.
Do you mean to say you want to...
become the enemy of the
shogun's blood relations?
Yeah, you've guessed it.
That's a foolish act.
If we put our force together,
you're nothing to be afraid of.
You'd be better off taking the money
and handing over the license to us.
Really?
Since you're so puffed
up, we'll let you have it.
Here, take it.
Serves you right!
It's not about the money any more.
We wanna show you the
pride of Denzo's family.
Do it, Senzo!
Sis, our plan worked!
It was a good idea to get them
up on a boat. Serves them right!
That's right.
The Hamada Clan, my ass.
65,000 koku, my ass.
Burn, burn! Die in the flame, all of you!
Serves you right!
You'll all turn into ashes.
Senzo!
Sis, hurry!
Sis, hurry now!
I'm gonna kill you this time around.
Die!
Sis, hang in there.
Senzo... Senzo...
Sis...
Senzo, don't die...
Give me back the license.
If the Shogunate gets it, then
the Hamada Clan would...
Genshiro...
Give me back the license. Give it to me!
If you want it, kill me first.
You...
Genshiro.
It must have been hard for you.
I know how you felt.
Genshiro...
Now, now, now, it's a big scandal!
The underworld shogun and
Chief of Senior Advisors...
Sir Matsudaira Suo-no-kami, died
a happy death lying on top of...
Lady O'Yo's in his Kaji Mansion
in Shiba at midnight last night.
Good work, O'Cho.
It's over now, all of it.
Thank you, O'Cho.
I'll pay you as promised.
Don't fret.
O'Cho, you know too much now.
In order to protect the Shogunate,
to protect its security...
you'll have to lose either
your voice or your life.
I refuse either option.
I'm not some bug.
At last I've learned.
Finally...
Finally, I'm beginning to see the truth.
It's you who killed my dad.
And mom.
And O'Tami, and Genshiro.
You killed them all.
My real enemy...
is you!
Translated by
Ann Jiitsu
Subtitled and Mastered by
Cannibal King
www.KuroTokagi.com