"Unhappy memories!
Yet I welcome you...
You are my long-lost youth... "
ARMY OF SHADOWS
We're taking a little detour.
You're not in any hurry?
Not at all.
My partner's just gotta
pick up a few provisions.
You do what you can
in these lousy times.
Of course.
You'll be okay there.
It's the best camp in France.
A camp for Germans.
I don't understand.
During the Phony War,
we expected lots of prisoners.
Naturally,
we didn't take a single one.
But now the camp
comes in handy.
How lucky can you get.
You said it.
Same old story.
Who are they? How do we treat them?
Some are sent without trial
and kept here indefinitely.
Others are released quickly
and regain influence in the region,
or the prefecture,
when it's not in Vichy.
"Philippe Gerbier, 41,
eminent civil engineer.
Quick-witted.
Independent-minded.
Aloof, sarcastic manner. "
Use the stick.
"Possible connections. "
Use the carrot.
"Suspected of Gaullist sympathies. "
Use the stick.
"Released for lack of evidence. "
Influence.
Use the carrot.
I'm assigning you to a building
intended for German officers.
I appreciate the honor.
Use the carrot... indeed.
But use it with caution.
- Philippe Gerbier.
- Colonel Jarret du Plessis.
I don't know why you're here,
but I'll tell you why I am.
In a café, I called
Admiral Darlan a jackass.
Today I add
that Pétain is a jackass too
for letting the navy
bully the army!
At least you're here
for a good reason.
Aubert, pharmacist.
Know what a Mahler shell is?
It’s a cone-shaped container
for producing chemical reactions
under pressure.
I’m a chemist,
and naturally I had a Mahler shell.
I Was reported
for illegal possession,
but I never got a hearing.
Octave Bonnafous.
Traveling salesman.
I happened to be crossing a square
during a Gaullist demonstration.
No one's in charge.
They're all jackasses!
They cancelled my pension.
Where do I sleep?
As acting barracks officer,
I suggest you take
the corner mattress.
Legrain, communist.
His name's Armel.
A schoolteacher and a Catholic.
- He asleep?
- He’s very ill.
- No infirmary?
- Full up.
Do you play dominoes?
- Sorry, no.
- We can teach you.
Thanks,
but I’m not cut out for it.
Then excuse us.
We just have time to finish
our game before lights out.
The commander's not stupid.
He sandwiches me
between three fools and two lost souls.
Out walking so early?
I work at the power plant.
Good job?
Not even an extra crumb of bread.
But I work to keep in practice.
See you, comrade.
You a communist?
But I do have comrades.
There were all nations and races.
Russians.
Poles.
Kabyles.
Jews of every nation.
Gypsies.
Yugoslavs.
Romanians.
Czechs.
Anti-Nazi Germans.
Anti-Fascist Italians.
Anti-Franco Spaniards.
And black marketeers
who stood out from the rest.
Everything okay?
I once laid
a power line in Savoy.
- You an electrical engineer?
- Like yourself.
Oh, no, you must really
be somebody.
But we could talk shop
once in a while.
Sure.
The Catholic teacher
died one night
without a sound, as usual.
Some Kabyles removed his body.
I never even heard his voice.
I’m not sad.
Armel is better off this way.
The score will be settled.
Mr. Gerbier.
I have an idea.
I’ll tell you tonight.
Two things
make escape impossible:
the barbed wire and the sentries.
The ground
under the wire is uneven.
I can blind the sentries
long enough by cutting the power.
Why haven't you tried
to escape before?
I wouldn't go without Armel,
and I wouldn't do it alone.
You I can trust.
Why tell me all this?
They need you on the outside.
Turn off the light
and get some sleep.
Good night.
The communist and I
secretly worked out an escape plan.
We gradually eliminated obstacles.
Let's go, Gerbier.
Take your things.
Hurry up!
Tell Legrain good-bye for me.
But -
Jackasses.
Good-bye, gentlemen.
LINE OF DEMARCATION
Travel permit, please.
This is our chance.
I’ll get up
to ask the guard something.
You run through the two doors.
This one here
and the door to the street.
Good luck.
Excuse me, sir.
Could you spare a cigarette?
The mighty fortress, Europe,
is fighting bolshevism.
Marshal Stalin wants
to defend his city, Stalingrad.
What do you want?
But Stalingrad
will be taken and renamed.
A shave.
The Marshal said...
The Marshal did...
The Marshal keeps his promises.
All done.
I’ll get your change.
Take this.
It’s not very smart,
but it's all I have.
A note from the organization
Paul Dounat belonged to -
his name was now
Vincent Henry -
had instructed him to be
in Marseilles mid-afternoon
to meet a comrade he knew
outside the courthouse.
Dounat had been
at the appointed spot for a few minutes.
Police. Your papers.
Fine. But I must ask you to come along
for some simple fact checking.
A nasty job.
You may hate bowlers, Félix,
but you still have to wear one.
Only when we get out.
Look at him.
He sold you out,
along with Zephyr and the radioman.
There's no point
in providing any proof
or asking you questions.
We should have
dropped him long ago.
It’s my fault.
We're too few
for so many missions.
Le Bison, can't you step on it?
Not unless you want
to attract attention.
I’m in a hurry too.
I have to fix that old transmitter...
and repair
our delivery agent's bicycle.
And there's
a parachute drop tonight.
- Do you have my new papers?
- They're on me.
Want them now?
Driving up there
will attract attention.
We'll walk.
- I’ll come too.
- It’s not necessary.
Really it's not.
I agree.
I’ll be back after dark,
just in case...
One false move
and you're a dead man.
Christ! That place was empty
When we rented.
Keep moving anyway.
In the back room.
Is he the traitor we have to...?
Yes, that's him.
And you're the chief?
Claude Le Masque.
He’s been begging for a tough job.
I came early to prepare things
and discovered the neighbours.
They must've moved in
last night or this morning.
I phoned Félix at once,
but you were already on the way.
We'll manage somehow.
We can question him
in the attic.
I've set up a table
and some chairs.
We're not here for a trial.
We're here for this.
But you can't!
They'll hear everything next door.
Listen.
The walls are paper-thin.
The Brits could've sent
the silencers we asked for.
Let's try to find a better spot.
How could you do it?
Nothing doing.
The cellar connects
with the one next door.
The attic carries sound
even more.
We need a good knife.
Le Bison always carries one.
A knife?
You can't be serious!
I won't let you.
Félix...
check the dining room
or the kitchen.
You can't do this.
I’m begging you. This is murder.
In any case,
we're here to kill, correct?
Yes, but not like this.
We have to -
I know.
Do it the right way.
I’m not afraid.
I swear I’m not.
But it's my first time, you see?
It’s our first time too.
Isn't that obvious?
Nothing.
We could leave him here
till Le Bison gets back.
Out of the question.
We're all busy.
I want to tell the boss the job's done.
Damn it to hell!
We can't bash his head in
with a gun, can we?
Gag him.
Strangle him.
With our hands?
There's a towel in the kitchen.
Stop that!
Dounat has to die.
That's why you're here.
You wanted a tough job.
You got it. Don't complain.
Sit him up in the chair.
Félix, stand behind him.
I’ll hold his arms.
Le Masque will hold his legs.
I swear it won't hurt.
Let's go.
Coming.
I didn't think we could do it.
Neither did I.
Always carry
cyanide capsules on you.
If you're caught, use them.
I will.
Glass of rum.
Jean-François!
You haven’t changed.
Still young and handsome.
Neither have you.
What brings you to Marseilles?
I sold my garage outside Paris
and opened a bike shop here.
What are you up to?
Nothing at all.
I have an appointment.
Walk with me a bit?
Sure. I’ll be right out.
Wait for me five minutes?
Five minutes,
but not a lifetime.
Still on a lucky streak?
You got some nerve,
wearing that pilot's jacket.
Well, screw them!
Then what?
What?
Is that all you'd do to them?
As for the war,
if there's no sport in it -
What if I gave you some sport?
Real sport?
You'd have to get up early,
spend nights traveling,
and never ask questions.
Keep talking.
Come by my shop.
Here’s the address.
Nothing in writing.
Memorize it.
And not a word to anyone.
- You're crazy.
You say that,
but with a woman -
- I don't have one.
- And that girl?
I said five minutes,
but she'll wait a lifetime.
We always confide
in our parents.
Mine are dead.
My only brother's in Paris.
I worship him...
but there's no risk
of me telling him anything.
LYON TALENT AGENCY
Is the director expecting you?
No, Mr. Roussel.
Please come this way.
I came at once.
We have an emergency.
How many men
do you have for Gibraltar?
Two Canadian commandos
from Dieppe,
three RAF pilots
who were shot down,
and two Belgians sentenced
to death by the Germans.
With me, that makes eight.
Where will they wait for the sub?
They're watching the clinic.
Can't we scatter them around?
No. They'd do something stupid.
The Canadian colonel
goes to the café.
He thinks you can't detect
his accent.
We'll only know
when the sub arrives the day before.
Take them all to the Viellat farm.
All of them?
So much for total security.
We're not an insurance company.
In these conditions,
on the contrary.
It all depends on the man
in charge of them.
I have just the man.
You don't know him.
He did a few assignments for me.
He was just fine.
He’s in Paris delivering
a transmitter to Mathilde.
When's he due back?
Should be tomorrow morning.
Brief him right away, so everything
is ready by tomorrow night.
I’ll join them at the last minute.
And you get some rest.
- After you're gone.
- No, before.
You won't have time later.
We inform travelers
that all luggage will be inspected
at the exit.
Open the suitcase.
No black market goods?
What's that?
As you can see, a radio.
All right, move along.
No problems?
No problems.
Twice in a row.
Tell Félix the transmitters
need new crystals.
The wavelengths changed.
All right.
Can I help you?
Certainly not.
- The other radio's there.
- Okay. A bite to eat?
No, there's someone
I need to see.
Greetings, Saint Luc!
Little Jean.
All the books are in place.
As well as the harpsichord...
and the oboe.
Nothing's changed.
Oh, the temperature has.
No more coal.
So to keep from freezing,
I bought this.
For working at night
and for meals.
But say, how'd you get here?
I hope you have an Ausweiss.
Saint Luc has come down to earth!
Saint Luc knows what an Ausweiss is.
Yes, I have one.
And not only that -
Not only that, I’m starving.
We'll have lunch
right away. Marie!
Yes, Mr. Luc.
What's on the menu today?
Rutabagas,
like yesterday, Mr. Luc.
- What else?
- Unrationed cheese.
And there's some butter left,
but no more bread.
I’ve got loads of bread tickets.
I can let you have them.
You're doing badly.
You used to be a gourmand.
I still am,
but what's one to do?
What about the black market?
And resourcefulness?
Marie's scared of the police -
And so are you, Saint Luc.
I store up heat.
I felt the heat myself today.
Twice.
It’s those trains and crowded subways.
You can suffocate.
I wondered if Mathilde, whom
I'd only just met, wasn't closer to me
than you, dear brother,
whom I’d always loved,
whom I still love,
but with whom I share
nothing but memories.
I left for Marseilles that evening.
Much later, I recalled having felt
a sort of... foreboding.
So, Madame Viellat,
quite a hotel you run.
Good evening, sir.
Well?
The fisherman will be ready
at midnight.
He can take everyone
in a single trip.
Madeleine will show you the way
to avoid any patrols.
Fine.
- Do I go back?
- No.
There'll be an extra passenger.
It’s the big chief.
There are too many in our boat.
You'll take him in another boat.
Le Bison will bring him.
Wait for my signal once I’m aboard.
Three short lights and one long.
Got it.
We're in a hurry tonight,
so how much do I owe you?
I’ll do the bill another time.
You always say that.
You keep coming back,
so you must like it here.
Walk in single file.
Not too close,
but stay in sight of each other.
Not a sound, not a word.
No nonsense. I’m armed.
What're you doing here so late?
And you?
I’m Augustine Viellat's
brother-in-law.
The farmer's wife?
I’m checking
if the coast is clear.
- And?
- No problem.
The gendarmes
passed by up above.
The Germans don't know the area
and trust customs.
And customs?
That's a good one.
Customs is me!
I’m the officer
for the whole area.
That is a good one.
Time to board.
Good luck, chief.
Strange to think how the big chief
looks the same as anyone else.
In that boat, the apex and base
of the pyramid meet.
Odd geometry! I must ask
Saint Luc about it after the war.
So glad to travel with you.
Same here.
I can't send
all the arms you request.
As you know, the English have little
confidence in the French Resistance.
They want all available planes
for missions in Germany.
But I can increase
your transmissions.
I’ll send you some available
radio operators
and provide backup
to your agents
to improve the landing fields
for our Lysanders.
An hour before the ceremony,
Jardie asked me to attend.
The war will be over for the French
when they can see this great movie.
I heard about Félix
that same day.
I still had a lot to do in London,
but with his arrest,
I couldn't stay a minute longer.
I decided to return that night.
You've never jumped before?
No, never.
Be careful
when your feet hit the ground.
Don't try to avoid falling.
Bend your knees and roll.
Understand?
More or less.
In my absence and after Félix's arrest,
Mathilde had moved down to Lyon.
She proved herself
a first-rate organizer.
I made her my assistant.
The chief had told me
she was a remarkable woman,
but she still astonished me.
She knows both how to command
and how to carry out orders.
She is strong-willed,
methodical and patient.
She spent days studying the layout
of the Lyon military medical school,
now Gestapo HQ.
She learned Félix was in the cell
reserved for those to be tortured.
She wanted to breach
the walls with explosives.
She had to give up that plan
for another one
requiring various disguises.
She found a new hideout
for my command post.
She couldn't have found
a safer spot.
My new host
was Baron de Ferté Talloir.
Ex-cavalry officer,
needless to say.
Before the war,
I was a sworn enemy
of the Republic.
I organized my sharecroppers,
kennelmen and huntsmen
into a squadron armed
with hunting rifles and pistols.
I was ready
to lead a cavalry charge
against the local prefecture
in the event of a Royalist uprising.
His squadron, perfectly trained
and organized, still exists
and guarantees my security.
The baron invited me to use his grounds
as a drop point and landing strip.
His wishes came true
beyond all expectations.
What a strange carousel!
As one plane descended,
another one just like it
circled low over the field.
The steady drone of its motor
covered the landing and takeoff
of the first plane,
which then covered
for the other.
That night,
in two operations,
four men arrived from London
and four others returned.
Le Bison, Le Masque,
Jean-François and Mathilde
handled security
for the operation.
And your husband?
Does he know about your activities?
Certainly not.
Neither does my daughter.
That's her.
She's 17.
Don't carry it on you.
You're right.
I’ll get rid of it.
Before we get back to what
I don't dare call "routine" matters,
we have to take care of Félix.
He has no cyanide tablets on him.
I’m not worried
about him talking...
but he probably
can't escape torture.
The Gestapo won't let you
commit suicide.
We have to spare him the suffering
that could go on for days, even weeks.
I’ve given it some thought.
There are no two ways about it.
- You found a way?
We have to get into Gestapo HQ
and bring Félix out.
Mathilde, I want to save Félix,
but I can't commit a combat group
to such a desperate mission.
Who's talking
about a combat group?
With Le Masque, Jean-François,
and Le Bison, I should manage.
And how!
What's your plan?
Le Bison, can you get us
three German uniforms?
- Sure thing.
- Go to it.
Our first obstacle is to contact Félix
and let him know.
I haven't figured it out yet,
but I will.
Félix has to be ready
and waiting for us.
I’ve been trying
to reach him myself.
You'd think a German architect
built that medical school.
You can't get in.
- True, it won't be easy.
It’s hot.
Mr. Gerbier...
I have neither
Le Masque's courage...
nor Le Bison's strength...
nor Mathilde's daring.
I won't take part in this mission.
But I’m sure
that Mathilde
and my comrades will succeed.
Don't try to find me.
"Mr. Dupont, 6 rue du Boeuf.
Saint Jean knows lots of things
about the Resistance. "
How did you manage?
Oh...
We'll only use two uniforms,
Guillaume.
I know, Madame Mathilde.
NO ADMITTANCE
You're not doing this
without me.
We're certainly
not doing it with you.
Remember what you said.
"You have no right
to sacrifice anyone. "
Least of all when it's you.
But that goes
just as much for you.
Now, about Félix -
- May I?
Two men -
that looks normal.
But three would be too many.
When Jean-François was here,
you wanted three uniforms.
But at the last moment
I’d only have used
Le Masque and Le Bison.
Jean-François...
I trusted him.
Me too,
but that's not what I mean.
I just never thought
he'd leave us like that.
Who is this man?
The man denounced in the letter.
You can go in.
Naturally, Dupont is
the only name you have.
Naturally.
What organization are you with?
I don't understand.
You know the risk you're taking?
Being shot under a false name.
Your fate would remain a mystery.
I decided to leave that haven.
Maybe I felt it coming.
Three days later,
the baron and his men
were arrested
and shot without trial.
What is it?
We're to transfer
a certain Félix Lepercq to Paris
to the headquarters
of Obersturmführer Bömelburg.
Yes, a terrorist. Hurry up.
It’s urgent.
- Get out.
Wait here.
An ambulance
from the Paris Gestapo
is here for a terrorist,
Félix Lepercq.
Notify the doctor on duty.
Let him issue
the transfer permit.
Can you hear me?
Mathilde, Le Bison
and Le Masque are here.
I’ll help you.
Are you in a lot of pain?
It’s no use.
He’ll be in great pain...
right up to the end.
It’s impossible.
I can't let you transport
a dying man. I’m sorry.
Very well.
I’ll file a report.
I have some cyanide capsules.
Do you want one?
We could have saved Félix.
No one could.
Not even you.
Besides, you're wanted
by the police.
You'd better lie low for a while.
Take the next plane out.
You're not serious.
And the maquis groups
springing up all over?
They have to be organized,
trained and given supplies.
No one can replace me for now.
And if you're caught?
Then we'd have to replace you.
Police!
So Germaine serves good food?
Meat at every meal
without tickets?
Identity check for everyone!
Get a move on!
I’ll save it for later.
He says to smoke quickly.
They're coming for us.
He could get in trouble.
To each his own troubles.
This is it.
TRANSFINITE AND CONTINUUM
Love has meaning for me
only as it applies to the chief.
He means more to me
than anything.
More than anything
but less than life.
If Luc Jardie died,
I’d still want to live,
but I’m going to die,
and I’m not afraid.
It’s impossible
not to be afraid of dying.
But I’m too stubborn,
too much of an animal to believe it.
If I don't believe it to the very
last moment, the last split second,
I’ll never die.
What a revelation!
The chief would love it.
I’ve got to look into this
more deeply -
You will turn your backs
to the machine guns
and face the far wall.
You will run
as fast as you can.
We will not open fire at once.
We will give you a chance.
Whoever reaches the far wall
Will be shot later
With the next group
of condemned men.
We can always try.
There's nothing to lose.
He knows what my legs want.
He's ready for the show.
His confidence shackles me
more than my irons.
Go!
I won't run.
I won't!
It had to be timed perfectly.
Thank Mathilde for that.
We were well informed.
And what if I hadn't run?
Something wrong?
Thinking about the others?
No, about the officer
who was so sure I’d run too,
like a scared rabbit.
Step on it!
Isn’t safety great?
You have enough for a month.
The water's okay,
but I’ll bring some wine.
No, don't come back
for a month.
I’d better run.
The car mustn't be seen here.
Then run along.
See to your arm and thigh.
Don't let them get infected.
- All right, Guillaume.
You'll find a razor on the table.
For three weeks
I’ve been holed up alone
like a frightened animal.
I wrote a long report for London.
I kid myself
that I’m still of some use.
I haven't seen Mathilde
or anyone else.
ESSAY ON THE PROBLEM OF THE
FOUNDATIONS OF MATHEMATICS
NOTES ON THE DEVELOPMENT
OF ABSTRACT SET THEORY
ON LOGIC
AND THE THEORY OF SCIENCE
AXIOMATIC METHOD
AND FORMALISM
My only link
to the outside world
are the five books
Luc Jardie wrote before the war.
They keep me company.
At night, I’m haunted
by Jean-François' disappearance.
Le Bison? Or Le Masque?
Is that you?
It’s you?
We have to talk.
- When did you get back?
- Four days ago.
After Mathilde's arrest.
We have to talk about her.
We have to, Philippe.
Mathilde was arrested
on the 27th.
She wasn't hurt.
She found a way to let us know.
The Gestapo discovered
her real identity
and her family's address.
She was carrying
her daughter's photo on her.
You can guess the rest.
The photo?
Mathilde's only slipup.
The Germans sensed it was
that remarkable woman's weak point.
The photo...
How could she have kept it?
I warned her.
It’s extraordinary, Philippe.
She begged them
to give her back the photo.
What?
Mathilde sent us an SOS.
They've given her a choice:
Either she names all the agents
she knows in our network
or her daughter
is sent to a Polish whorehouse
for soldiers
from the Eastern Front.
Those are the givens
of the problem.
We must find a solution.
She can escape.
She can neither escape
nor kill herself.
The Gestapo is confident.
The daughter will answer for everything.
She can play for time.
How much time?
That doesn't solve the problem.
Here’s Le Bison.
Don't tell him I’m here.
Go into the back room.
I got you a new pair of glasses.
The same as before.
Any news from Mathilde?
Well?
- I don't know anything.
What?
I don't know anything.
It’s all in the letter.
She was released
yesterday morning.
Gerbonel and Arno
were arrested last night.
Is that right?
If that's what it says.
Le Masque...
you knew about this?
I’m not in charge of reports.
Mathilde is to be eliminated at once,
by any means.
You can't be serious!
I won't lay a finger
on Madame Mathilde.
I worked with her.
She saved my skin.
I watched her at Gestapo HQ.
She's a great woman!
If it was a man,
whenever you say.
As many as you want.
But not Madame Mathilde!
Over my dead body. Never!
No arguments, Guillaume.
She has to die and she will.
You can't do that.
We have other killers.
If need be, I’ll do it.
You wouldn't dare!
You have no right!
In the shooting range,
you could've run like mad,
but she saved your life
with those smoke grenades.
You mustn't do it.
Let her sell us all out
if she wants.
She protected me.
She protected you.
Now it's her daughter.
We can't judge her.
That'll do!
The matter is settled.
If you're coward enough to do it,
I’ll get you first.
Stop!
Get off me! You were still a kid
when I was in the Foreign Legion!
Think I’ll stand by
and let you do this?
Are you crazy?
Back off
before I kill you both!
What we need here is a man
who knows nothing about weapons.
Sit down, my friend.
Have a cigarette.
It'll do you good.
Right, Gerbier?
You heard it all?
You're right.
Mathilde is a marvellous woman,
more than you know.
But we're going to kill her.
- You can't.
We can, and here's why.
We're going to kill her
because she's begging us to.
She told you that?
No, but it's obvious.
Think for a moment.
If she just wanted
to save her daughter,
she'd only have to supply some names.
You know her memory.
Instead, she tells them
our agents keep moving around,
that she needs
to re-establish contacts.
So she gets herself released.
Isn’t that clear enough?
Now put yourself in her place,
forced to hand over your friends,
and unable to commit suicide.
I’d want to be killed.
You think you're any braver
or better than Mathilde?
- I’m sorry.
- Find a German car.
Le Masque will drive.
I’ll be in back with you.
Are you crazy?
I’m sure she'll want
to see me.
Don't! It’s no place for you.
It’s an order.
That wasn't necessary, chief.
You sure of what you claim
about Mathilde?
How should I know?
My theory might be correct.
Or she wanted to see her daughter again,
making it harder for her to die.
That's what I want to find out.
I have to be with you
for the hardest part.
You in a car full of killers!
Nothing's sacred anymore.
SUNDAY, FEBRUARY 23, 1943
Go!
Claude Ullmann, alias Le Masque,
had just enough time
to swallow his cyanide capsule
on November 8, 1943.
Guillaume Vermersch,
alias Le Bison,
was decapitated by ax in a German
prison on December 16, 1943.
Luc Jardie died under torture
on January 22, 1944,
after revealing one name:
his own.
And on February 13, 1944,
Philippe Gerbier decided
this time he wouldn't run.