Dear Ann,
l've come back to New York,
Some years ago you
asked me about myself,
''What are you doing,''
you asked
l didn't answer then
but l want to now,
When you've read this letter,
if you wanna come away with me
if you want me to take you
from here, tell Victor
you can trust him,
He'll find me,
I'll start somewhere
near the beginning,
William is not my name.
A few years before l met you
l was returning from a place
l'd always wanted to visit,
Japan, l was transferring in
San francisco to a flight home,
Once l was back on the plane l asked
if l could go back to the boarding area
because I had left
a book there.
By the time l found my book,
the gate had closed
so l sat and read my book until
the plane took off without me,
l decided to take the long bus
ride across the country to my home
in Connecticut,
just outside of New York,
Several hours into the trip
l heard on the radio that the plane
l missed had crashed into a mountain,
l closed my eyes and slept,
The next day l learned that they had
not been able to recover any bodies,
The plane and all the passengers
had been incinerated on impact,
l got off the bus in New York
and decided to stay for a while,
l realized that
for all anyone knew
l no longer existed,
for no particular reason
without really
thinking about it
l bought a passport
under the name
of William Vincent,
I took a class
and learned a trade
and got a job editing nature
videos for use in the schools.
I think that's what they're
used for, I'm not really sure.
l managed to find
an empty storefront to live in
in a neighborhood
in Chinatown not far from the East River.
Okay,
Yes.
from ''They can hover
in midair,''
They can hover in midair
by rapidly flapping
their wings
1 2 to 9O times per second,
They can fly backwards
and are the only group of birds
able to do so,
They can also stop in midair.
Hummingbirds are continuously
hours away from starving to death
and are able to store
just enough energy
to survive overnight,
Hummingbirds are capable of slowing
down their metabolism at night
or any other time food
is not readily available,
They enter
a hibernation-like state
known as torpor,
During torpor, the heart rate
and rate of breathing
are both slowed dramatically
the heart rate to roughly
5O to 18O beats per minute
reducing the need for food,
The most astonishing
quality of hummingbirds
is their ability
to broadcast color.
Hummin9birds radiate
like hot coals in the sun,
The color that reaches your eye
is created by pigment
which absorbs some
colors and rejects others,
Like soap bubbles
hummingbird's color
comes from iridescence, not pigment,
lt winks on and off
depending on the light source
and the angle of the viewer,
That's a nice dress.
Where'd you get it?
lt's a kimono.
l know it's a kimono.
l like it.
Change.
You know you don't
wanna fuck with me, ri9ht?
Of course l do.
Of course you do.
So he says, ''Hey,
you're right, but
''can we actually
do that, like
''who's in charge of this pro]ect,
you know
''and l'm like, listen
''if some noise needs to be
made, l will make the noise.
Okay? All right?''
And he says,
''Whoa, Jason, whoa.''
l'm like, whoa
what, Ted?
The problem with Ted is,
he doesn't get it.
He's like, pretty much like,
l can name off
three or four executives
in this company alone
who in a few months are gonna be
redoing their resume
and who do you think they're gonna
ask to take one of those offices?
But, l think that comes from ]'ve done a
]ot of meditation over the years, l have to,
You would think that in, like,
the cutthroat business that l'm in
when you're dealing with
derivatives it's all crazy.
lt's very chaotic,
But, you need to find
a time for peace,
When you're workin9
a ]ob ]ike that.
Because if you don't, you're
going to be chaotic yourself,
_'__ take it
one step further,
lf you really wanna know about financial
markets, Iet's talk about Per Bak
Right?
[scoffs]
Right.
Let's talk about,
Iet's talk about, uh
Kolmogorov.
[chuckles]
lf you wanna hear really
the theory of turbulence
order of chaos,
phase transition.
And that's where these guys
should be living right now
if they want
to survive.
But they don't, they
can't possibly grasp that.
Economic crisis, my ass. This
is an economic opportunity.
You should
-- You know what? You should check out a book
um, oh, what is
the name of that?
lt's, uh, Per Bak,
How Nature Wor--
-  I'll think of it.
-  Okay,
- You know,I'll be right back.
- Okay,
- And I'll think of it.
- Great,
l'll definitely remember it
before l get back, okay?
l can't wait,
Hi.
Do l know you?
Uh, no.
Sorry if my, uh,
staring bothered you.
lt's, uh, it's okay.
l don't mind.
l don't like
your friend.
Oh, you mean Jason?
Yeah. Do you
like him?
l don't know.
Why?
]ust asking.
Do you know him?
Hm-mm.
l'm Rebbecca.
Hi.
What's your name?
The scotch is--
You're very beautiful.
Wow.
Joseph?
Sorry.
l enjoyed tormenting
the man in the bar
and l think it was nice that l
might have made the woman happy,
Even for a moment. Even
if I didn't care about her.
There hadn't been many
that l had cared about,
Only two brothers
that l'd known
when l was a teenager back in the town
where I grew up.
l'd lost touch with the two
brothers, but l thought of them often
and saw them, in a way, in parks,
on the street, different places,
And l saw them
as l'd known them
as young boys, not as the
adults they would be now,
lt was a lovely thing to imagine, but
I knew it was just that, Imagined,
But l saw them as if
they were really there,
l wondered how they were,
where they were,
Anyway, wherever they are, it's
probably best that they don't know me
given the man l've become,
l knew them
when l was this age
the age l am now
in this shot, 16.
l'm 30 now, so the things l
remember are from a long time ago.
His name was Joseph
back then, not William.
He did some odd things,
but l think he was a nice person.
Maybe a little--
He could run very fast.
We used to race.
He was a beautiful runner.
Really beautiful runner.
I'd been lving as William Vincent
for three years before l met you,
ln that time, we might have passed
near to one another and not known it,
l wonder if either of us might
have felt something in the passing,
lf it happened,
for instance
l wonder if you were nearby
that night l saw
that man wearing
suspenders and a bow tie?
He's just kind of drifting down
the sidewalk Iooking at his phone,
What the fuck?
The man ]ust walked away
unaware that I had lifted
some things from his pocket,
Just a receipt and
a business card, Nothing,
But it seemed as if there was
something else in the air that night.
Something odd,
lt was an unusually
quiet, empty night.
But l felt as if something
had happened,
There was something wrong
that night but I didn't mind.
l might have
even liked it,
l went out to eat
still with the sense that there was
somewhere wrong in this city, somewhere,
Hi.
Hey.
What time is it?
lt's late.
What's the occasion?
Do l need an occasion?
You are an occasion.
This place sucks.
Watching what's going on,
You don't have to flatter
me, you know,
ls that
a good tip?
Excuse me?
ls that
a decent tip?
Yeah, it is.
He's just trying
to earn a living.
You're a fucking asshole.
Open the iris all the way
and bring the condenser up,
The subject now appears
against a dark background
]ust like aspen leaves
against a dark sky,
The color seen
in dark filled lighting
can give new information,
Dark filled lighting
is a good technique
for viewing the smallest
observable lifeforms.
And also helps us understand
that William
never meant any harm,
Nor did he mean any kindness,
He never meant anything,
We can take the risk if,
if we're able to--
Ri9ht.
l don't know that
we're able to
and l don't know that we
need to wait for everything--
Excuse me.
Excuse me.I think you might
have taken something of mine?
l don't think so.
Give me
my phone.
Like l said,
l don't think so.
l'm not fucking around.
Give me my phone.
Okay?
Does your friend have
a problem?
I don't know how I can
make this any clearer
l want you to give me
my phone, Right now!
This your phone?
What the fuck?
You little prick!
We'll, fuck you.
fuck you.
Go fuck yourself,
asshole.
Find out who he is.
William is standing
outside a door.
On the other side
of the door
a woman and a man
are having sex,
In a park, a child runs.
Another rides a bike.
A little girl reads.
A man walks under a tree.
No, A man walks past some
potted bushes on the street,
He enters a restaurant.
You remember me?
l'm Victor.
Uh-huh.
So, uh, listen, um--
Um--
So, anyway
this man l know
is very impressed with you
he saw the little thing you did
on the street a couple of days ago
with the phone
and a wallet, and uh
you know
l was there.
Um
uh, he would
like to meet you.
So
anyway this man, uh
l don't wanna-
l don't wanna be coy
or anything, but
this man has, uh
a lot of interests
that are
not aboveboard.
So--
Can l get you
something, sir?
No, thank you.
So like l said, he, he, he, he, he, he,
he would, he would like to meet you.
Uh-huh. And what
is not aboveboard?
Let's let him tell
you about that.
Okay.
And you, uh
and you're a part of this thing
that you're talking about?
Mm-hm.
So you're the muscle?
Yeah.
Are you muscling me?
You'd know
if l was.
Yeah, l guess
l would.
So this man
uh, l don't know
what this is about
who he thinks
you are, but
he thinks you can earn
him money.
Maybe you can,
maybe you can't
but he thinks you can
so he would
like to meet you.
Yeah?
Yeah.
lt's so weird.
Please?
What's in it for me?
That would be money.
You sound like
you're in a movie.
Yeah.
What if l say no?
Don't.
What if l do?
lt's my job to bring you to him.
Please don't make me do my job.
So if l say no, somebody's
gonna come and beat me up?
Hm. l don't know.
No?
See?
So?
l don't know, l'm just
trying to figure out
if l'm in trouble
here or
who you are,
or what-- You know.
Please, just come with
me. l'm saying please.
Okay.
Idon't know why
l went with him,
He seemed like a nice man, and maybe
his boss was interesting, I don't know.
As we drove to meet him
l thought of a photograph
l'd taken in Japan,
ln particular, a shaded area
in the corner of a frame
where l could barely
make out a woman,
l hadn't known she was there
when l took the picture,
I wanted to talk
to the brothers,
When we used
to come here
you guys would race
over there, by that pond.
Yeah, l remember.
You used to race, too.
You won.
Yeah, l was pretty
fast, wasn't l?
The fastest.
Remember?
l don't remember,
l was too young maybe.
You used to sit
over there.
No, l used, l used to
sit here with you guys.
Sometimes.
lt's nice to see
you again.
l told this woman
in a letter that
l thought it was better that
you guys don't know me now.
lt was better for you.
Why?
l'm not so nice now.
l never thought
you were nice.
You're nicer than
you think you are.
No, l'm not.
So how'd you
become a criminal?
l don't know.
Wait here.
This is William.
Hello, William.
Hi. Who are you?
A friend.
l liked you manner on
the street the other day.
Yeah, thanks
for stepping in.
What would have
happened if l hadn't?
l don't know.
Were you afraid?
No.
You didn't seem afraid,
l, l guess.
You're a secretive
one, huh?
Are you a tough guy?
No.
But you are secretive,
That's my
impression, anyway,
You know, l don't much
like people who aren't
who aren't like that.
Victor, would you
give us a minute?
Sure.
Actually,
give Ann a call,
would you?
ls she there?
Hang on a second,
Yeah, she's ready anytime,
Well, thank you for coming,
l wanted to meet you,
You're a film
editor, right?
Uh, yeah.
Why don't you
have any friends?
l do.
No, you don't.
Okay.
You know, there is someone
l'd like you to meet,
Victor will
take you to her.
She's a gift.
You're giving
me a woman?
No.
How could
l do that?
l don't know.
No, just
a friend
someone l'd like you to
meet, if you're willing.
A simple sign of respect which l'd
like to think that you'd reciprocate.
Uh, okay, great.
Great.
Victor.
No, uh, l don't,
l don't think so.
Not really my thing.
You'd be doing
me a favor.
Maybe some other time.
H i.
l'm Ann. Victor
told me to come here.
Oh, you mean,
Victor's boss.
Somebody.
It'd really be better for me
if you let me in.
Would you like
to take a seat?
Mm. Thanks.
So you're what
he gives away?
l wouldn't say that.
l'm sorry.
That was really rude,
Don't be. l can see how you
might think of it that way.
Anyway--
So who are you?
Um--
l can't really
offer you anything.
Um, do you
want some water?
Okay.
Here.
Would you like some?
l got lipstick
on the glass.
Anyway.
Here.
That's so pretty,
You think?
Yes.
You sure you
don't want any?
So this is home and
work, Victor said?
Yeah.
Movies?
Yeah, sort of.
Can l see?
Mm-hm.
Come on.
A 19th-century naturalist
called them little more
than organized water,
They were in our oceans
65O,OOO,OOO years ago
before sharks and dinosaurs.
They do not have
a central nervous system
a circulatory system
a respiratory system
or an osmoregulatory system,
So it's understandable
that Louis Agassiz
the great 1 9th-century
naturalist--
I should probab]y
get back to work,
Do you want me to leave?
Okay.
So, um
what is it
that you do?
Oh, things.
How's that?
lt's what l do.
So it's that.
Sounds okay.
ls it?
Why wouldn't it be?
l don't know.
l'm Ann.
William.
What can l do
for you, Victor?
There's a couple of things my
boss would, uh, like you to do.
l'll be your contact,
lt's really very
simple, you just
go to this address
deliver this
pick up a couple of envelopes
from the women there
and uh, l'll get
the envelopes from you,
Yeah, we__, uh
here's the thing, you,
uh, you get a lump sum
every week,
that look okay?
lt'd be okay if l
needed the money.
Then give it back.
There's a lot in here,
isn't there?
l think so,
All right.
Maybe l can find
a use for it.
So, Ann
what's the deal there?
She's a beautiful woman,
Yeah, so
what's the deal?
Pretty much
as you see it,
Care to elaborate?
You seem like
a nice boy.
This is not
a really nice group.
And, uh, you're
included in this group?
Yeah, me, too.
And Ann.
So, uh
anyway, uh
Ann
uh, she's, uh
uh
she's my boss's--
She owes him.
l suppose we all do.
Anyway, she's, uh
she's there for him when
he need, when he needs her
not so much for
himself anymore
but, you know, for others,
like yourself, as a favor,
Mm-hm.
So, uh, anyway, uh
she was asking
about you
uh, asking me, uh
she knows she's not
supposed to ask about you
that's none of my
business why she did.
But you need to know that
this is very dangerous for her.
And for you,
You're talking like
you're in a movie, Victor.
Like a gangster movie.
I'm not a violent
person, Are you?
l'm not a gangster.
You're not?
l don't think so.
No, I don't
think so either,
There anything l can
do for you, Victor?
No.
No, thanks.
Uh, yes, you can
keep your distance from Ann.
l'd rather not,
Please, William. For Ann.
When you need me
to do something
uh, you'll ask.
I assume that's
how this works,
And then, l'll either
say yes or no.
Uh, and the piece
you took?
The silver?
He, uh, he forgives
this because
you didn't know who he
is, but now you do, right?
l guess.
William?
Yeah.
H i.
Excuse me.
Can l get you
something to drink?
No, thanks.
You wanna sit down?
Juliette's got one
of these, too.
Okay.
l'll go see if l
can get her up.
Juliette?
Juliette's a little
out of it
right now.
Mm-hm.
Do you have
something for me?
Yeah.
Oh.
Thanks.
lt's heavy.
Oh.
Good morning.
You want some?
No.
Does she have
that envelope?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask her?
Juliette!
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
What's your name?
l'm William.
What's that?
William.
William?
Yeah.
Hi.
l'm sorry?
Do you want some?
No, he doesn't.
Did you already
ask him?
Mm-hm.
He really doesn't.
Do you have
an envelope for me?
Yeah.
Do you wanna
hang out with us
for a little bit?
William.
Come sit down,
Jesus Christ,
fucking 5 o'clock, Ann,
Thank you.
Put some clothes on,
Whatever.
We have a guest
in the house,
So, we'll see you
in like a week, right?
l don't know.
Bye.
Bye, William.
See you!
He's totally gay,
H i.
Hi.
l need
to pick up the money
you got
from the girls.
Oh. Did you talk to Victor?
Um, no, I will.
Don't you trust me?
Yeah, it's just
that l thought--
Oh, well, yes, usually
Victor gets it but
l was nearby so l
thought l would come.
Okay,
l like Victor.
l do, too.
He's a nice man.
ls he?
Well, who knows?
Maybe not by your standards.
l think he's nice enough.
What are my standards?
l know he's having
a hard time, you know
his wife is pretty sick.
l didn't know that.
Yeah, she is.
Where's the kimono?
Here.
This for me?
Can l try it on?
Sure.
Can l lie down?
M m-hm.
So you stole a wallet
and threw it away?
Yeah.
And that's how he--
What are you doing?
l know why l do
what l do.
You ought to stop,
Whatever you're doing,
Maybe l will.
You really ought to.
What about you?
Maybe we'll stop together,
Yeah.
Stranger things
have happened.
Yes.
Yes, you will?
Yes, l will.
Okay.
l guess.
There's the address.
It's this guy.
You nervous?
Yeah?
l'm here to pick
something up for Victor.
l don't know any Victor,
Yeah, you do. l'm just
here to pick it up.
Pick what up?
You know. Don't you have something
that doesn't belong to you?
Who are you?
What's Victor's
boss's name?
What?
You know Victor, right?
Yeah.
You know his boss?
What's his name?
Who are you again?
What's the boss's name?
l have no idea.
You know Ann?
Yeah.
You're such
a piece of shit.
l really need
to ask you to leave.
l'm only gonna ask
one more time.
Leave, asshole.
What's the boss's name?
Get the fuck
outta here,
Okay.
Oh!
fuck!
Ah.
My boss wants
to see you.
All right. Let's
go see him.
Victor, will you
give us a moment?
Sure.
That was quite a display you put
on at Russell's apartment yesterday.
Do you think
it was necessary?
Did you enjoy it?
No.
No? Not even
a little bit?
Are you a sadist?
l'm sorry?
A sadist.
Are you sadistic?
No. Are you?
A little respect, please,
75,OOO dollars.
lt's quite a bit more than
the occasion calls for, but--
l consider that
a lot of money.
l guess
you do, too.
What's it for?
lt's to thank you for the
work that you'll do for me.
Do you have
to think about it?
Because it might be
a problem if you do,
No, it's good.
Good,
Come,
Okay.
Victor will be in touch
at some point.
You like Victor,
right?
Yeah.
Also, you won't be doing any
more pickups or deliveries to Ann.
Okay.
ls that a problem?
No.
Good,
Because l don't want you and Ann
to ever see each other again.
lf you're wondering why
there's so much money in there
it's to thank you
for doing what l say.
Don't ever try
and see her again.
lsn't that partly
up to her?
lt's what she wants,
lt is?
More importantly,
it is what l want.
l see.
You do?
Yeah, l do.
Sorry.
Because light travels in waves
with specific wavelengths
with specific wavelengths, , ,
Objects become visible when they
are large enough to reflect light.
, , , uses an oil-immersion lens to
achieve a magnification of 1 , OOO
, , , immersion lens to achieve
a magnification of 1, OOO, , ,
Ugh!
Get outta here.
Okay.
Do you have money?
Yeah.
Okay, well,
then go.
Go, right now.
Come with me.
No, William,
No.
You remember William?
He's back,
That episode was
back then, but
like l said,
he's back, and
well, you know,
he's probably
tried to get
in touch with you.
Between us?
Of course.
He wrote me a letter.
And?
Come on, Ann, this is
really fucked up.
Don't worry, Victor.
l'm not going to be
a problem.
Promise?
Promise.
ls there anything you
want me to tell him?
No.
You know what
l have to do,
Yeah.
Nothing you want
me to tell him?
No.
So, uh--
l don't know,
l think, uh--
Don't think, Victor.
Hey, William.
You know what
l have to do?
No, l don't.
Yes, you do,
Where is Ann?
Will you get Ann?
Get Ann.
She wanted me to tell
you she's sorry.
And that she'll
always love you,
Please.