Whoo! Yee-ha!
Pass it by! Come on, pass it by!
- How you doin'?
- Good. Pass it by!
Come on! Pass it by!
Hey, Bennie.
Hey, Bennie. You got the loot?
The boys are waiting.
- I got the money. But you ain't coming with us.
- Aw, Bennie.
Hey, baby, I got the money.
I got the bread.
Twenty bucks.
- Hey, I got the 20. Wait a minute.
- Be careful!
Let go of my leg.
Let go of my hand.
Let go of my arm, man.
- Let me see that bill.
- Forward!
- Twenty bucks apiece.
- Twenty bucks.
- That's shocking.
- No, I'm gonna get you one.
- Look what we've got here.
- Dennis, you're in.
- I haven't seen him around, have you?
- Who cares?
Hey.
Get a load of him.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Been here long?
- Two or three days. Where have you been?
- Two or three days?
How come I haven't
been around before this?
I don't know. Your problem.
What do you do?
Nothing very much.
Well, I'm not gonna ask you
the story of your life.
- You seem nice.
- I wish you would.
Well, I'm making enough.
I got a nice cozy place.
- Well, I haven't had any better offers.
- What's to drink?
- Want to finish your drink?
- A little bit.
Good boy. Big boy.
- Tonight -
- What's the matter?
Well, uh...
I think I'm caught in this booth.
Come and get comfortable.
Oh, come on.
You come on.
What do you mean by "interesting"?
Huh?
What do you mean by
"come up to my apartment"?
That's a silly question
for a big girl like you.
What do you do?
I'm a musician.
Jazz musician.
I play trumpet.
You didn't bring
your instrument tonight, did you?
You guys are really something.
Well, what have you been
sitting here all night for?
Huh?
I thought you knew all the answers.
Well, you want to get
picked up, don't you?
Would you like that?
I'd like to take you.
- I'll bet you would.
- Have a great time.
What do you say?
All right? Please?
- Such a baby.
- What do you say?
I'm not kidding. I'm very serious.
Would you like it?
- Huh?
- All right.
- What's your name?
- Nancy.
- What's yours?
- Ben.
Hi.
#A real mad chick#
#Is like a lollipop#
#She'll keep you on the stick#
#If you don't play it cool#
#She'll play you for a fool#
#A lollipop, a lollipop
will never make you sick#
#A real mad chick#
#Is like an ice cream cone#
That's a lousy agreement.
I've been a singer
in this business for 10 years...
and I've never introduced
a girlie line in my life.
Well, I can't change you. Hughie -
It's not a question of the money.
It's just that my client feels
that it's beneath his dignity...
to have to introduce
a bunch of floozies.
I've got a few guys ready
right now to take your place.
- You aren't infallible, you know.
- #Is like a cherry pie#
#You'll never find the pit#
- Okay. All right, cut it.
- #Whether shower or sleet#
- Cut it! Cut it out.
- All right, all right.
Okay, okay.
- Okay, cut it. Cut it.
- #With every kiss#
- All right. All right.
- Okay, uh -
Now, there are 10 million people in
New York City. Half of them are girls.
And any one of them can sing this song
better than you broads. Any one of them.
"A real mad chick," right?
#A real mad chick#
And shake your bodies around!
Do something, will ya?
Now, let's try it once more.
- All right, if you want me to do it.
- Once more, girls. "A real mad chick".
But look, I'm going to feel like an awful
damn fool introducing those girlies.
You're an artist.
If you make up your mind
to do it, you can do it.
Look, I was an artist 10 years ago.
Now, that's when I was an artist.
How you doing?
You want to see me for a moment?
- You got a minute?
- Sure.
- Bennie -
- Wait a minute.
Let me see him for a moment, okay?
A moment, man. You know.
- What is it, Bennie?
- You got a minute?
Yeah, I got a minute.
Let me tell you something.
You know what these people
want to do to me?
It's bad enough working
in a third-rate nightclub...
packaged with the strippers and floozies
and playing second fiddle to them.
They want me
to introduce the girlie line.
Crazy.
- They can't even sing.
- Look, Hugh.
I need 20 bucks to pay a guy back
I borrowed from for a few beers.
- Are you ready for our deal now?
- We're still making up our mind about it.
- Where's your boy?
- He's over there talking to his brother.
I want to pay him back.
Have you got it?
Here's my offer now. You're gonna
play two nights. $35 a night. Yes or no?
We'll take it, Jack.
We've got no problems.
You've got to introduce the girls,
the whole line.
- We need the money, Hugh.
- You got it, 20 bucks for me?
What's it gonna be?
- Look, we haven't decided anything.
- We've decided, and he'll be there.
Look, man.
I'll see you later.
You're only a kid.
It's a lot of money for a kid.
Anything. Okay, excuse me.
Bennie.
Now, Mr. Ackerman.
There are no problems at all.
He's got a little trouble
with his kid brother.
And it's going to be taken care of
in just about another minute.
Now, as we agreed, we're going to be
there tonight in Philly right on time.
Bennie.
Look, Hugh.
We've gotta settle this thing.
What's the deal?
He wants to give us $35
a night and third billing.
And you introduce
the girlie line, Hughie.
We heard that part before.
- All right, what time do I leave?
- Just be in Philly in time for the show.
That's all I want from you.
#You'll never find the pit#
Rupe, you're a very lucky boy.
If you knew how many people
wanted this job.
You guys are both very lucky boys.
Well, I wouldn't say that
exactly, Mr. Ackerman.
#A real mad chick##
What's the matter?
Come on, what's the matter?
- I forgot your toothbrush.
- Look, I'll buy one.
Hey, how about moving up there?
- How you gonna get home?
- I thought I'd take a nice little walk.
No, look,
I want you to take a cab.
Oh, please, Hugh.
Don't start that again.
I'm 20 years old,
and I've lived in this city all my life.
- I think I can manage.
- Yeah, yeah, I know.
Look. You don't know everything,
and you're a baby.
I mean, all you have to do
is read the papers.
A girl can't walk safely
down the streets at night in any city...
without being hollered at and
called names and pinched and abused.
I don't want my baby sister being hurt
for a few pennies. Now, you take a cab.
Nothing ever happens to me
when I walk home.
Round trip to Philadelphia, please.
Look, nothing's gonna happen to me,
nothing ever does.
I love you.
Now, take care of yourself. Okay?
And do a good show.
And come on, let's go.
- And look-
- The suitcase.
- You're gonna be late.
- Look, take a cab, please. All right?
Get out of here.
You're gonna miss it!
- Where you been? You're never on time.
- Look, we'll make it.
Come on.
- No, we're gonna make it. Come on.
- Man, it's too late.
Look, he's stopping.
Come on, man, run.
After you.
Hey, Sam.
Thanks for letting us use this pad, man.
- How'd you like that date?
- Yeah, man, but everybody's gotta live.
Sure, sure. Fourth billing
and introduce the girlie act.
- Now, that really burns me.
- Forget it, will you?
What am I introducing a bunch of
dumb broads for? What's to introduce?
So they're dumb broads.
So they gotta live too.
That's the way I feel also.
That beats baked beans
with baked beans, buddy.
Sam. All right, I'm a singer.
And I sing a song.
Now, what am I gonna say about a bunch
of dumb broads with white ribbons...
going around singing "A Pretty Girl"?
Does that make sense?
Well, you just can't say that exactly.
I don't know, say a few nice words
about the audience...
like, uh, I don't know.
Just smile, be yourself, you know?
I'm a singer.
Nobody seems to get that.
And singers sing.
I mean, that's it. That's all, man.
Well, man. You can always
tell a couple of jokes.
Everybody likes jokes.
That makes people feel good.
Sam, what time is it?
You make them feel relaxed, at easy.
Like Steve Allen, you know.
Jokes? What jokes?
I don't know any jokes.
- Look, I don't even know my own name.
- Now, come on, baby. Let's go.
- Now, hold on a minute.
- To hell with jokes. You tell a joke.
Look, dummy,
don't let yourself go.
Tell us somejokes, man.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
How's that one
about the witch doctor?
Are you kidding?
They'd close the joint.
I was just thinking out loud.
I'll tell you one a little bit,
little bit more refined.
Uh, you like that one about
the rabbit in the tree?
I don't know that one.
That one about the rabbit that
fell on out of the tree and says...
"Man, that lovemaking's for the birds".
- That's great. That's cute.
- Don't you like it?
- Oh, man, come on.
- Wait a minute, man. What do you mean?
Look, man. Hold it.
That's cute. That's funny.
- Everybody likes jokes.
- That's right.
Man, you won't offend anybody.
You know, with dates?
- Do you really think that's funny?
- Yeah, come on. Give it a try, will ya?
- I do, man.
- I don't know. - Come on.
- Look, I can't.
- Try it, Hugh, once, will ya?
- Okay, okay.
- There you go.
Uh, ladies and gentlemen,
did you ever hear-
This is stupid, man.
I can't do this.
Try it, man. What's to lose with us?
Are we gonna kill you?
Look, if you're so smart,
you do it yourself.
Okay, I will.
It's easy though, you know.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
On my way over here this evening
a very funny thing happened to me.
Got it? I was walking down the street
looking up at this great big tree.
- And way up there on -
- Man. Say it out fast. Catch 'em off guard.
- No, you got to set 'em up, man.
- Set 'em up? You'll rock 'em to sleep.
- Man, who are you, Steve Allen?
- All I'm saying -
Wait. I got it. I got it. I got it.
I say, uh...
"Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
Well, you certainly look like
a refined audience we got here tonight...
and I have a couple
of refined jokes to tell".
- See? I play up the class.
- There you go.
Beautiful couple here,
ladies and gentlemen.
There's a couple celebrating
their third drink since 7:15.
Hey, that's pretty good, man!
You're beautiful.
You two married?
What are you asking if they're married for?
They're with a fella.
He's the lookout.
Here's the Andrew Sisters,
ladies and gentlemen...
Patty, Maxene and LaVerne.
- Are you two girls married?
- I just asked that.
Well, it got a laugh over there.
I figured it would get a laugh here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I want you to meet a singer-
We've got a singer right now
named Hughie Hurd.
He's a great singer. I want you all
to, like, take care ofhim.
Give him a lot of applause, please,
because he's new in town.
#Hello, baby#
#I had to call you on the phone#
#I said, hello, baby#
#'Cause your daddy is so lonesome#
#And daddy wants his baby home#
Man, he's putting them all to sleep.
#If you read my letter, baby##
- Kill him, man. Get him off.
- What?
What is this "bring the girls on"?
What kind of a place you running here?
Bring the girls on.
Bring them on out.
Call the girls, man.
Introduce the girls.
- Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
- Bring on the girls, will ya?
#A real mad chick#
#Is like a lollipop#
#She'll keep you on the stick#
#If you don't play it cool#
#She'll play you for a fool##
Well, is everybody going
to sit around here all day?
Dennis, stop that, will ya?
It makes me sick.
- What's the matter with you, Tom?
- I got a hangover. That's what's the matter.
That's what you get
for staying out all night.
Who takes care of your sister
when you stay out all night?
Man, I hire a babysitter. Don't I hire
a babysitter for you, sweetheart?
David's writing a new novel
all about you, Ben.
Better not be any of that
beat generation jazz like the last one.
Stop it, Dennis. It makes me sick.
Right in my coffee, Tom.
Yeah, take some Dramamine.
It helps sometimes.
- Dramamine? What's Dramamine?
- It's airsick medicine.
I'm not airsick. I'm ground sick.
But I'll take anything
if it'll help me with the way I feel.
Dennis, will you do me a favor
and get me some of that stuff?
- What is it?
- Will you get me some Dramamine, please?
Do me a favor, huh?
Dennis, I appreciate that very much.
Oh, Tom! Will you cut it out?
For crying out loud.
You guys.
You never break your pattern.
You'll never go anywhere with your lives.
- Tom, take this. Drink up.
- How many do I take?
Take just this one.
Why don't you do something,
learn something?
There are thousands of things to do
in New York City.
- Like what?
- Why don't you do something different?
Do you want to meet new people?
You wanna come to a literary
party I'm having tonight?
Don't invite them, David.
They won't even wear ties.
- Lelia's coming.
- What the hell is a literary party?
Just where people interested
in books and other literary efforts...
get together and discuss things.
Well, if they're coming,
I'm not going to be there...
because they're gonna just act awful,
and I'll be so embarrassed.
- Oh, it's all right.
- Oh, a tie. You kidding?
You can comejust as you are.
Do you want to come?
- Yeah, I'll read a poem.
- Don't get excited, honey.
Who wants to make
that fink party anyway?
All right, something else.
A concert or a museum?
A museum, I'm for it.
Ben, Tom?
I don't think you've ever even been
in a museum, any of you.
I? I've never been in a museum?
We've been in plenty of museums.
I bet you can't even spell it.
- Oh, will you stop teasing me?
- Here, Tom. Pick it up.
Lelia has a very bright mind, Bennie.
- She's developing very rapidly.
- Bull.
I don't want to sit around here and
be insulted by these creeps. Let's go.
Lelia, you should eat something
besides black coffee.
David, please.
Don't start lecturing me now.
Well?
- Come on, David. Let's go.
- Never mind. We're going.
What will it be, Dennis,
the Margarine or the Metropolitan?
Let's go to the Metropolitan.
They got mummies there and everything.
- What do you say?
- You guys kidding?
- No, man. Let's cut.
- Let's go.
- Let's go. Come on, Ben.
- Hey, Bennie.
Come on, Ben. Let's go.
Hey, Bennie, Dennis.
I don't know what you wanted
to come here for, Dennis.
This joint is nothing but a place
for a bunch of sexless women...
who don't have
any love in their life.
A lot of big deal professors.
A lot of creeps trying to show
off how much they know.
- You couldn't be wronger.
- I suppose professors don't come here?
Well, I didn't say that.
All right, Dennis. Look at that.
I suppose you can tell me
what he's about, huh, genius?
- He's a statue.
- I know he's a statue, Dennis.
What kind of a statue?
I know he's a statue.
- Well, Tom, I don't know everything.
- You know something, Dennis?
- You don't know nothing.
- Oh, yeah? What do you know?
- A lot more than you do, pal.
- Yeah?
What you come here for
if you know so much?
You have no respect for art,
no respect at all.
You listen to me, Dennis.
You're nothing but an ignorant slob,
Dennis, a little ignorant slob.
- I went to college, Dennis.
- You?
All I ever got out of it
was dissipation...
and a lot of early bells
disturbing my sleep.
A lot of supercilious professors...
slob professors shooting off
their mouth about something...
trying to teach me something they'd
already failed at in life themselves.
So don't tell me
I don't appreciate anything.
Tom, do you know what
I'm going to do with that?
I'm gonna put it on a Christmas card.
Just a mask on a card.
- Won't that be wild?
- Don't send one to me, pal.
Look, Tom, will you cool it?
You know what you're talking about?
I suppose you really understand
that thing, huh, Bennie?
It's not a question of understanding it.
If you feel it, you feel it, stupid.
That's what I been trying to tell you.
- Aw, shut up, Dennis.
- Aw, shut up, yourself.
- Say you're sorry.
- All right, I'm sorry. Okay, I'm sorry.
Hey, look at that one, now.
Look at that one, man.
- You're really sorry?
- Yeah, I'm really sorry.
- Okay. I apologize.
- Take it easy, guys, will you?
Hey, look at this.
Now, look.
Now, look at this cat.
He really had a sense of humor
when he made this.
That isn't supposed
to be humorous, Tom.
What are we supposed to do,
get serious with a can like that?
- I'm telling you right now, Tom.
- Don't get excited, Dennis.
I'm not going to hurt it.
It's made of iron.
A chick like that may destroy me.
What's the matter with Tom?
Is he crazy or something?
No, Dennis.
Someday you may marry a girl
that looks like that.
Oh, God forbid.
- It's not funny, Dennis.
- It's not funny.
This joint gives me the creeps, Bennie.
Let's go, come on.
- Where are you going?
- Let's get out of here.
Okay.
Lelia.
I'm not trying
to hurt your feelings.
But if you're going to write a story,
you have to do it professionally.
David, I don't want to be a writer.
I didn't want to do this.
You convinced me to do it.
And now all you can do is criticize.
I just want you to be honest.
Look, your story has some pretty good
things. But it's very hard to be honest.
I don't understand your viewpoint.
Jean-Paul Sartre has absolutely nothing
to do with existential psychoanalysis.
- Would you like a cigarette?
- No, thank you.
Well, it's all a bit vague.
Don't you think so, Joan?
I do not. The trouble with you is...
you suffer from self-induced hysteria
at the word existentialism.
- Are you aware of that?
- Can I fix you a drink?
- No, thank you.
- I assure you, I don't.
I know the article to which you refer.
I've read it three times.
I couldn't even find
the basic precepts.
- Which article was that?
- If you can explain it, I'd be delighted.
Well, it's perfectly obvious.
Man, in contrast to other animals...
is conscious of his own existence.
Therefore, conscious of
the possibility of non-existence.
Ergo, he has anxiety, right?
Right, absolutely.
I couldn't agree with you more.
Well, it figures.
Now this girl here...
she has no control over herself.
She's been deeply hurt.
And yet she goes on
as if nothing happened...
living her life the same as before.
It just doesn't make any sense.
Life takes more than imagination.
Well, the point is that
if you're yourself, you won't get hurt.
- Are you a writer too?
- Oh, no. Do I look like a writer?
Well, I can't tell anymore.
- I'm a dancer really.
- Oh, a dancer. Why, that's great.
- Are you a ballet dancer?
- Oh, no, exotic.
- Exotic?
- Oh, you don't know what that is, do you?
- Not exactly.
- It's, uh, sort of modern...
only more exotic.
That sounds terrific.
Listen, would you mind if I came
to see you perform sometime?
Oh, no. The very next time,
I'll invite you.
Great. When will that be?
Oh, I'm not dancing right now.
Oh, no? Why not?
I'm going to have a baby in March.
You're -
That's great.
You're going to have a baby.
A baby. That sounds terrific.
Congratulations. That's great news.
- We think so, don't we, honey?
- Huh?
Yeah, well, that's swell.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Listen, if it's okay...
I'll just excuse myself
and fix my drink a little bit.
You don't know what it is to be hurt.
You can't always see it coming.
Sometimes a person could ruin your life.
And yet, all he'd be able
to honestly say is "I'm sorry".
Hi, David.
Am I interrupting something?
Tony. Lelia Carruthers, Tony Russell.
- Hello.
I was just trying
to convince Lelia that...
writers today have got to be
realistic in their approach.
What he's trying to say is,
he hates my writing.
You be the judge, Tony.
You be the judge.
On her first day in New York this year...
Lelia's writing about
a walk down Fifth Avenue.
She sees a stranger standing
in the sunlight on a street corner...
and she walks up and kisses him,
this perfect stranger.
It's revolting on a Sunday afternoon.
It is not.
If I wanted to, I would.
Was that so bold?
I guess I have to
change sides, David.
David, would you go and get me
some more champagne?
It's even more revolting in real life.
Some more champagne.
I think you've had plenty.
- What did you say your name was?
- Lelia.
It's a lovely party, isn't it?
Do you know you're staring at me?
- I'm hypnotizing you.
- Thank you.
Who do you belong to, Lelia?
Why, I belong to me.
What about David?
- No more champagne, Lelia.
- David, I was just about to see Lelia home.
What do you mean?
I'm taking Lelia home.
Well, uh, you're both wrong...
because neither one of you
are taking me home.
I'm meeting Vickie and
she's spending the night at my house.
Oh. I guess my hypnotic spell is
a little rusty. What about tomorrow?
Tomorrow, Lelia and I
are going to the park.
- Oh, well, good, good. I'll come along.
- No.
- Oh.
- David, don't be so unfriendly.
Don't be such an old man, David.
- Hi, Moe.
- Moe-Moe.
Hey, baby.
Give me one of those.
- Hello, stranger. There's a stranger.
- Hi, Moe.
- Hello, Moe.
- How have you been?
- Lelia, come here.
- You sure look like you've got a hangover.
I've gotta go.
- What's the story here?
- I'll talk to you later about it.
I thought you and Lelia were making
the scene. Dave, wait a minute!
- I can't. I can't.
- Oh, wow.
I'm really not very happy.
I mean, I'm happy, but I'm not
as happy as everybody thinks I am.
- Why not?
- Oh...
because I feel that I should be
farther ahead than I am.
And everything
is passing me by, and -
- How old are you?
- Twenty.
- I'd never guess.
- Oh, stop. Don't laugh. I'm serious.
I have the feeling that
I'll never, you know, be smart...
and I'm never going
to get the things that I want.
And, uh - Oh -
What do you feel like?
Tell me what you feel like.
- I feel like I'm in a -
- In a cocoon and you can't get out?
That's right.
How did you know?
I didn't think boys were supposed to
understand things like that.
- You see, I am far behind.
- Behind who?
- Now you sound like David.
- I hope not.
Why not? David's one of the most
intelligent people I've met in my life.
But not very romantic.
No, he's not very romantic.
You know, I'm not a very nice person.
I mean,
I have very romantic inclinations.
Be forewarned that I'm not one
of these storybook characters...
that's supposed to be
all noble and righteous.
When I see someone I like...
and if she likes me,
we accept my romantic inclinations.
Do you happen to know
where we are right now?
No.
That's where I live,
right there, number seven.
Come on up for a drink.
You know you're beautiful?
Don't you move.
Don't move.
You've got the softest lips
I've ever felt.
Tony.
I love you, Lelia.
I don't want anything to drink.
All right, baby.
I love you, Lelia.
Love you, Lelia.
Baby, I love you.
So much.
Lelia.
Really, if I'd known
this was the first time for you...
I wouldn't have touched you.
I didn't know it could be so awful.
Don't be so upset, sweetheart.
Baby.
It'll be much easier next time.
There isn't going to be a next time.
Want a cigarette? Huh?
- Come on, have a cigarette.
- No.
I'm sorry if I disappointed you.
I guess I did.
I was so frightened.
I kept saying to myself,
"You mustn't cry.
If you love a man,
you shouldn't be so frightened".
It's only natural.
There isn't a girl in the world
that wouldn't feel the same way.
She's got to.
- What happens now?
- What happens?
Uh, what do you mean,
"What happens now"?
- I mean, do I stay with you?
- Stay with me?
Uh, stay with me?
Do you mean live with me?
Yes.
Do you want to?
No.
I want to go home.
Okay, baby.
I thought being with you
would be so important...
mean so much...
that afterwards two people would be
as close as it's possible to get.
But instead...
- we're just two strangers.
- Lelia.
- It's over.
I know that much about life.
Lelia, you can come stay with me.
I want you to.
But when I say
that you're close to me...
that's all I can say,
because that's the way I am.
But that does not mean that I don't feel
the same things that you feel.
Tony, please, please don't.
- Lelia, I love you.
- Please don't touch me.
Please don't touch me.
I want to go home.
- I want to get dressed now.
- Okay, sweetheart. Okay.
- Please leave me alone.
- Okay, sweetheart, I'll take you home.
Okay, sweetheart.
Sweetheart, it's okay.
- I'm with you.
- I want to go home.
I'll take you home.
Seventy-five, buddy.
Look, uh, why don't you just take
the taxi wherever you're gonna go?
Because I'm coming upstairs with you.
Look, folks. Come on,
it's my busy time. Let's go.
Yeah, yeah.
Just a second, huh?
Look, why don't we
just end it right here?
Make up your minds.
Because you don't want it that way,
and because I don't want it that way.
You go with her,
or end it and you stay.
But, uh, come on,
make up your mind.
- How much - How much on the clock?
- Seventy-five.
I'm coming upstairs with you, Lelia,
whether you like it or not.
- Please, don't make any scenes.
- I'll make the biggest scene you ever saw.
You're that important to me.
All right, all right. You can come up,
but just for a minute.
Okay, fine.
Ain't love grand?
Why don't you
mind your own business.
Keep it. Keep it.
#I love you truly, truly, dear##
- What's wild?
- Deuces wild.
- It's up to you, Dennis.
- Any kind of deuce?
Any kind of deuce. It's up to you,
Dennis. You open or what?
I open for 50.
Give me two cards, Ben.
Wait a minute.
Want me to call you, do you?
Tell you what
I'm gonna do, Dennis.
You need the money,
so I'm gonna let you have it.
I'm gonna let you have this hand
and bury my cards.
I don't wanna play anymore.
Let's call some girls.
- Come on, let's call a couple of chicks.
- Why not?
- Get on the phone, Bennie.
- Come on, Ben.
Who do you know, Ben?
You should know a lot of chicks.
You said you had something.
You've been bragging all day about it.
Ben, call Barbara.
Barbara Kennedy.
Twelve twenty-one, please.
Room 1221.
Uh, Anita.
I don't know her last name, just Anita.
Yeah, room 1221.
Yeah, hello, baby.
This is Clark.
I'm all through flying.
Anita? Yeah, Tom.
How about a couple of drinks?
Can you get that redhead
that works in the hat check room?
No, there's three of us.
I got two buddies.
Yeah, Bennie and Dennis.
We're feeling mighty low.
Can you get another girl?
All right, I'll meet you in about
20 minutes? Yeah, see you.
- Tell you, man?
- Come on, let's go.
Didn't I tell you the chicks would go?
You didn't believe me.
Let's go!
Come on, let's go.
Come on, Bennie.
#You are just a dream#
#And someday you'll disappear#
#Kiss me and make
this moment divine#
#Beautiful#
#Tell me you will always be mine#
#Forever is a long, long time#
#Spend it with your lips on mine#
#Beautiful#
#My beautiful you#
#My beautiful you##
Okay, let's break it up.
That's more like it.
How you been?
I'm fine. Uh, Tony Russell,
this is my brother, Hugh.
- Hi.
- And this is Rupert Crosse.
Glad to know you.
How are you?
Well, how did the thing go?
I mean, big crowds?
Fine. The only one bad spot
in the whole thing was...
this character here decides to--
he's gonna rewrite everything.
You ever hearJelly Roll
sung like an opera?
Come on. The song's notJelly Roll, man.
It's a ballad. It's a beautiful thing.
- You sing like a velvety-
- Of course, honey.
Oh, Lelia.
I have an appointment.
I have to go.
I told you.
- Where are you going?
- My appointment.
You didn't tell me about
an appointment earlier.
I just remembered about it
a couple of minutes ago.
Tony, I love you.
Doesn't that mean anything?
Look, Lelia.
We'll have lunch tomorrow, okay?
After lunch, we'll go to a movie
or something like that.
Maybe have some drinks.
Lelia.
Look.
I don't wanna fight with you.
I don't wanna argue with you.
- What's the matter?
- I want you to go.
Why?
I don't want you -
I don't want you to hurt my sister.
- I don't wanna hurt your sister.
- Look. Maybe I can make you understand.
- Lelia, I don't want to hurt you.
- Look, I want you to go!
Why? I don't understand that.
Look, I want you to go.
I mean, it's as simple as that.
- I don't want you around.
- Want to have dinner with us tomorrow?
I don't want nothing from you.
I'll take you and Rupe to dinner.
All of us will go.
I can't seem to
make it clear to you.
I don't want you around
hurting my sister.
I don't want you
to hurt anything of mine.
Now go.
Just get out!
- You're telling me to get out.
- Get out, man.
What do you want me to do now?
Just get out.
Remember, you told me to get out.
Look, would you leave?
Would you leave before I do something
I don't want to do right now.
Would you just get out of here.
Go ahead.
But you remember you told me
to get out of here!
Will you get out of the house!
- You got me, Bennie -
- I love you.
Okay. It's all right.
Oh, I love him so much.
You all right, baby?
Good night, baby.
Get some sleep, will you?
That water better be hot this morning or
I'm gonna wipe that superintendent out.
Excuse me.
Hey, how do you manage to get here
three minutes before I do?
What do you do, get up late at night
and watch the alarm or something?
- Too bad.
- Just don't slop it up in there, okay?
Well, some people like water on them.
Oh, go drown yourself.
Hey, baby. How you feeling?
- Fine.
- Great.
Looks like I'll have to go out
and buy you a whole field of tobacco.
How you feel now?
You feel like talking to me about it?
- Maybe it'll help you.
- No, Hugh.
There's not much to say.
Thanks anyway.
Is it just possible for somebody
to get a towel in this place?
Oh, I forgot to put them up.
I'll get you one.
No, don't drag it out.
It's probably someplace simple...
like in the hi-fi set.
Look, I better get it while it's hot.
Oh, Lelia. Look, I got some cats
coming up tonight.
And, uh, if you don't feel
up to it, we can cancel.
Oh, no, Hugh.
It's all right, really.
I'll even order some things.
It'll give me something to do.
Great, great. That's my baby.
Al.
Al told me a story yesterday about Bird.
Bird had this big limousine that had been
assessed by the Bureau of Internal Revenue...
and he was driving it all over town,
you know, like a block long.
And, uh, he was driving with
two other people in the car...
and Al was, like, the guy
in the center who, like, told me.
And the guy on the outside he didn't like
and they were going uptown.
And they were going down Broadway
and they had to make a left...
and another left to go uptown.
So as they stopped at the light...
Bird said...
"Man, would you mind getting out
of the car? I have to make a left turn".
So the guy said, "Okay, Bird,"
and got out of the car.
And Bird made his left turn
and went uptown without him.
- Isn't that sick?
- Yeah, very.
- Hey, Bennie, you got a towel for me?
- Yeah.
Thanks.
Maybe I'll just join
a small group in Vegas.
Bennie, what's this I hear
about you getting a job?
I mean, that really upsets me.
- You're kidding, aren't you?
- Very funny, very funny.
Lelia, can I get you
a cup of coffee or something?
No, Hugh.
What's the matter with you?
Are you sick?
You look awful. You ought
to get some rest at night.
Will you shut up!
What did I say?
Just forget it.
I won't forget it. What did I say?
- What's the matter with her?
- Nothing you'd be interested in.
Look, she's my sister too. I wanna know
what's the matter with her.
Nothing, baby. Just a little problem
that came up last night.
A little problem?
What is the little problem?
Look, Bennie. It's just a problem
with the races, that's all.
Like I said, Bennie,
nothing you'd be interested in.
Who all is coming
to this party tonight?
Oh, just some people.
You know what you need?
You need a guy to take care of you
and protect your values.
You need a home and security
and babies, honey.
That's what you need.
- Oh, look. There's DaveyJones. Davey!
- No, Vickie.
Meet Davey. He's wonderful.
You'll love him.
- Vickie, no.
- Davey! DaveyJones. Davey!
Davey, I want you to meet Lelia.
Lelia, this is Davey.
- Hello there.
- Hello.
Sit down for a second, Davey.
Davey went to the same school -
Your brother's school, Stuyvesant.
Vickie--
How long have you known Vickie?
What do you do all day?
- I paint.
- You're an artist.
Maybe I can drop by one afternoon.
Take in a movie or something.
I don't like the movies.
Well, there are other places to go.
Take you to a club then. How about that?
Or we'll go to an opera.
I might drop up one afternoon.
Maybe we can go for a walk
through the park or-
I don't like the park either.
Oh, give me a break.
Hi, Dave, daddy.
Hello, Rupert. How are you?
I'm not interrupting, am I?
Vickie, will you help me out, put in
a good word here or there somewhere?
Well.
- To talk to Lelia.
- Hi, baby. How are you doing?
Why don't you take her
to that wonderful painters' -
They're having some kind of thing
over at Cooper Union.
- She'd love that.
- I wouldn't dig that at all.
Well, that's the kind of thing
I enjoy, you see?
Well, we'll go then.
Lelia. Hello.
I'd like to see you
for a second, can I?
- Yeah, what?
- It's about Tony.
Say, uh, excuse me. Can I talk to Lelia
for just a second? It's something important.
- No, David. I'd rather not.
- Honey. It's okay.
No, please. David,
I don't want to discuss any of this.
- Please. Just come with me for a second.
- No, David, please!
He called me. He was very upset about
something that happened here the other day.
- And he got me upset about it.
- I know, David.
Yeah, but I feel I'm involved in it.
And I just want to tell you...
that I didn't know at all
what he was like, when, you know -
Hey, hey, Dave, Dave.
Come on, Dave.
Leave my sister alone.
Come on, man.
Come on and join the party.
Look, I have to go.
I'll see you later, all right?
- You're a very good dancer.
- I'm not such a good dancer.
Lelia, come on over here.
Come on over here.
Looks like you and her
are getting along real fine.
Well.
Look, why don't you just
come on and have a drink with us...
and join in the party
and forget about your mood for a while?
You know, I just don't understand.
I think you really
want to join in the party...
but maybe you don't know how.
You want to be coaxed a little bit.
You really feel that way?
I prefer to be coaxed.
But don't you coax me, okay?
There are other ways.
You want a drink?
Want me to get you a drink?
- No, thanks. I don't drink.
- You'll find it's good for what ails you.
Just pull yourself together, because
you're not kidding anybody but yourself.
You know, you have
your sense of values all mixed up.
So I can just -
No, don't touch me.
Come on, just a little taste.
- Let him go, let him go.
- You're crazy, baby.
- Let me go. Let me go.
- Hugh, come on.
Let me go!
What the hell is wrong with that guy?
What's wrong with you?
You don't have to get carried away.
He's always messing up the damn thing!
What's wrong with him?
This is a party! Stop it!
Mary had a little lamb,
its fleece was white as snow.
Everywhere that Mary went,
the lamb was sure to go.
- Gee, he's your brother, and I -
- I know.
I find it hard to believe
you can't talk to him.
I don't know, right now I'd just be satisfied
with a home and a few kids, you know.
- Simple things.
- I envy you.
He's a pretty unhappy kid, you know.
It's too bad you can't -
He's mixed up and for some reason,
I don't know...
he doesn't,
either doesn't want to, is afraid to -
Okay, Hugh.
Let her off the hook, will you?
The night's almost over.
Let's end it off with a little smile
rather than all this.
What's with this "Leave the girl alone"?
Why don't you leave me alone?
I was only attempting to remind you
that we invited her here...
to have a good time, that's all.
She obviously wants to hear
what I have to say.
- Maybe he doesn't wanna talk about it.
- She's not complaining.
Why don't you butt out,
mind your own business?
We want to kill each other,
that's my business.
Every time I turn around, it's you behind me
pushing me, interfering with me.
- You could be replaced.
- You sound pretty mad about it.
Okay, Hugh.
Let's knock it off, huh?
Hey, look.
I'm picking up your phrases.
The other day in Philadelphia
when I was singing...
you know,
I don't appreciate that at all.
- Oh, yeah.
- I'm getting ready to sing the song.
In the middle of the song...
for what reason I don't know
why you did it, you decided to change it.
This don't make sense.
Does that make any kind of sense?
No, I don't think it's fair to...
- sort of as a last minute sort of thing.
- Another little bright idea of his.
Without interfering with you...
I think what you feel more
is my attitude towards life.
Maybe that bugs you, but don't hold it
against me. That's the way I am, see.
How much longer you
planning on us staying here?
- I don't know. What time is it now?
- Five after 5:00.
- Here are your keys.
- Where the hell have you been?
- What the hell do you care?
- What do you mean, "What do I care"?
- There are your keys. Where's Lelia?
- She's out.
Don't mess with me.
I'm splitting. There are your keys.
- I want to talk to you.
- No. Get out of my way.
- I want to talk to you!
- Are you gonna stop it?
Take your hands off!
Look, Bennie, you're my brother.
What do you want me to do,
start the whole thing all over again?
Goddamn it, if I have to whip you,
I'm gonna tell you something!
- Look, wait a minute, will you?
- I'm going.
Bennie, will you listen? I love you.
What the hell am I supposed to say?
Bennie. Bennie, for God's--
Take the keys, please.
- Bennie.
- All right.
Are we friends?
Buddies? Brothers?
Huh?
- Hi. All ready?
- Well, hello.
No. Where's my flowers?
I was late, so I didn't have
a chance to - I just ran right over.
Well, I just don't think
that's very nice of you at all.
Don't you think you should bring a lady
something when you beg to take her out?
I can go back and get them
if you want me to.
No, just go make yourself comfortable.
There's drinks in there.
- Go, go.
- Will you be long?
I'll be as long as I am.
- Hi, there.
- Oh, hi.
I'm Davey. I'm taking Lelia
to the dance tonight.
Oh, good. Pleased to meet you.
Uh, why don't you go and have a drink
with my brother and Rupe?
- Thanks.
- Introduce yourself, why don't you?
Hi, fellas.
- Hi.
- It doesn't even make sense to be singing.
- I don't want to talk about -
- What?
- What's up?
What's up?
What do you mean, "What's up"?
- You want a drink?
- I'd love one.
- Good, get one over there.
- Yeah, drinks over there.
Over there, man. Drinks over there.
The whole song -
It would sound ridiculous
the other way, you know?
- I'd want to do it, you know -
- Lelia, let's -
I'm not ready, David.
David, I'm -
Do I look ready? No.
Therefore, wait.
Be comfortable and wait.
- Lelia, it's getting late.
- Well, wait.
I'm not gonna say I'm gonna sing
all the things like that.
- Were you just doing "Lucky Day"?
- Yeah.
I know that song.
I'm doing it in my nightclub act.
- Great, man. Great.
- Oh, boy. That's terrific.
No, but really.
I know it, and he's doing it wrong.
Oh, really?
You want to show him how to do it?
That's wrong, man. You're dragging it
through the middle. It's a up tune, man.
- It has to go and swing.
- You tell him, now.
- You know, you know.
- See? Now, that's the right idea.
Oh, wow. Isn't this -
- Hey, Bennie. Isn't this great?
- #I found a horseshoe#
#I couldn't go wrong#
- #And when you just happened along##
- Hey, Bennie. Isn't he a smash?
What do you think you're doing?
What do you think you're doing here?
I was explaining that song.
I didn't ask you to interrupt
my brother's business.
- He was singing it wrong.
- He makes the money, not you.
- You don't understand.
- What do you mean?
I didn't ask you to come in here
and disturb my relatives.
So please sit down and be quiet.
Did you hear that?
Wasn't it great?
Marvelous.
- Where is he?
- Are you kidding with this guy?
Rupe, I feel -
I'm a strange one.
Would you mind shaking it up, Lelia?
I've been waiting for exactly
two and a half hours.
Do you want to go out with a wreck,
or would you like me to look nice?
I want you to look good, but I want you
to shake it up. Do you mind?
You want to go to the dance with me?
- I wouldn't be here if I didn't want to.
- Then you'll wait. I'm not finished yet.
Hey, hey, what's with you two?
Lelia, do you have to
talk to him like that?
I'll talk-What do you mean,
"Do I have to talk to him that way"?
I wouldn't blame the fella
if he got up and left.
I don't know.
Sure wouldn't let anybody
talk to me like that.
You didn't tell me you had
such a tough sister, man.
- Does she carry on like that all the time?
- Look, I'm just happy to see her going out.
I'm done.
- How do I look?
- You look nice.
- You be a good boy. Be a good boy.
- Yeah, thank you.
- I'll see you. Write to me.
- I'll write, and I'll send the money.
Come on, I'm finished.
Come on, let's go.
My coat, sir.
Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- I wanted to talk to Lelia.
Well, you can't talk to Lelia.
I don't want you in here.
- Never mind, don't even talk. Just get out.
- Let me tell you -
I don't want to hear anything
you've got to say. Will you go, please?
- I don't want to hear anything.
- Please listen to me for a minute.
I don't want to listen to you.
Get out of the place!
- Hugh. Let me talk to him.
- Wait a minute.
- Wait a minute. This is my problem.
- This is our problem, our problem.
- Okay.
- So what do you want?
I just want you
to tell her that I'm sorry.
- All right. He's sorry, he's sorry.
- Okay. Okay.
- Will you tell her that?
- Yes, I will. Most definitely I will tell her.
Will you tell her that I realize now...
- there's no difference between us.
- Anything else?
She'll always mean a great deal to me.
- Just tell her that...
Tony said, "I'm sorry".
There's no difference
between you and Lelia.
She means a great deal to you.
And you're sorry.
Thank you.
You must like to fight or something, man.
You keep pushing people.
- See you.
- Okay.
What are you doing?
Getting ready to go to Chicago, buddy.
How about you?
Wait a minute. I'll pack,
and I'll be right with you.
Okay. So you meet me
down at the station.
- All right.
- Twenty minutes.
Twenty minutes.
#Lovely is the blue
of your eyes, beautiful#
- You're a very good dancer.
- Sure.
- You don't believe me?
- I believe you.
It's just that I know
I'm a good dancer.
Oh, wow. What an ego.
- Do you come here often?
- Yes.
I like this place. It swings.
Well, maybe you can
take me here next week.
But I didn't ask you.
Well, if I want to go,
I'm sure you'll take me.
Now, look, Lelia, where I come from,
the men do the asking.
- The girls just go yes or no.
- Well.
I guess I just don't fit into
that pattern, now, do I?
No, you don't. As a matter of fact,
you're just a little too much for me.
Well, then why don't you
take me home?
- Why did you ask me in the first place?
- Now, steady, girl.
Do you always shout down
your boyfriends that way?
- I never shout.
- Well, it would seem that way to me.
Look, do you always go around
embarrassing people in front of strangers?
I mean, laughing at them
in front of your family...
keeping them waiting for hours
just to show off how masculine you are.
Darling, I'm not masculine.
Well, it would seem that way to me.
Well, how do you want me to behave?
Look, just dance.
And be as lovely as you look.
Look, David, I am what I am,
and nobody tells me what to do.
Look, I don't know who
you think you're fighting.
You know, I saw the way
he looked at you back there.
And I also saw the way
he looked at me.
#Whisper, you make
this moment divine#
#Beautiful#
#Tell me you will
always be mine#
#Beautiful#
#Forever is a long, long time#
#Spend it with your lips
on mine, beautiful#
You know, despite
your horrible exterior...
it's you I like.
#My beautiful you##
- Hey!
- Come on.
- So you finally made it.
- No sweat, man.
- Hugh, I've got some bad news.
- The train move?
No.
No, I checked with
our telephone service and...
there's no point in us going to Cincinnati
because the job is closed out.
- What about Chicago?
- It's still there.
- So what happened?
- Ackerman.
Ackerman called Cincinnati
at his own expense...
and told them
you were being difficult.
- So?
- So that means no Cincinnati.
That means we go to Chicago for
a week's billing and come back here...
and maybe some cheap, mangy
club owner will give us a job...
- introducing the girlie line.
- Wait a minute, will you?
Or maybe you can sing
to a room full of drunks.
Look, we've been in this business
for a long time.
I'm supposed to be a manager.
You're supposed to be a singer. Right?
Now who have I ever managed
besides you? And what have you ever done?
- Rupe, wait a minute.
- The bestjob I've been able to get you...
is in the Black Rose
in Tucson, Arizona.
Rupe, wait a minute, baby. Wait.
No, no, I've had it
with this rat race. I've had it.
I'm busted. I'm busted.
I've been insulted by these pigs,
laughed at.
And what's in it for you or for me?
Look, if we've got to be failures...
let's do so in our own city
or get the hell out ofhere.
- Out of where, man?
- Here, the States.
We'll go to Paris, France, Africa.
I don't care.
It's going to be the same
no matter where we go.
- Look, I have had it.
- Rupert, wait a minute.
Do you believe in me?
Rupert, do you believe in me?
I don't mean what
those other people think of me.
I mean what we give each other.
You know, what comes out of both of us.
Your talent, my voice.
Man, when you're on time,
you're still not on time.
Rupe, do you believe this?
Because, Rupert...
I believe that you're
the greatest manager in the world.
And we're together.
Rupe, you're the greatest
manager in the world.
Come on, let's go.
Next week, Eastland's.
Move, will you? Come on.
Hey.
- You're gonna get us killed.
- Almost hit me, the dirty-
You ready?
Make the announcement.
Girls, the Happiness Boys
singing "Up On The Moonbeam".
Girls, the Happiness Boys.
#Up on the moonbeam#
- #Up on the moonbeam with you#
- #Up on the moonbeam#
- Hit it, boys.
- #What makes my head go round and round#
#While my heart stands still##
Hey, man!
Hey, Bennie.
- Hey. What's going on here?
- Take it easy. Leave him alone.
Get out of here.
We're with these girls.
- So what's the story?
- What are you guys doing here?
We just came in here,
and we're clowning around.
Go clown around somewhere else,
huh, buddy?
- Take it easy. We're only kidding.
- We're with these girls.
Shut up, punk.
- Wait a minute.
- What do you mean, "Take it easy"?
- I mean take it easy.
- Hands off, buddy.
Take your hands off me.
Let's see you imitate somebody now,
stool pigeon.
We're only kidding around, buddy.
All right, come on.
Come on, man. Don't get excited.
Listen for a second.
What you want to fight for?
Just get your hands off.
You want to tangle ass, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Take it easy, brother.
- You're gonna get yours, brother.
- Come on, mother. You for me.
- You're for me too, boy.
- You're just the guy I want.
- All right, let's go!
- Yeah? Come on!
My eye, my eye!
You -
I'll kill you!
- How about it, Jonathan? Tell him.
- Three beers.
- He wants to - He's all shook up.
- No more of this jazz for me, baby.
You can go home
for a week and cool it.
So what are you gonna do?
We went out to have a ball, didn't we?
- That's what we did.
- So you gotta pay the price, man.
If you get beat up, you get beat up.
I don't know why we do this, man.
- I mean, go around, try to pick up girls.
- Stupid broads.
You'd think we'd have girls of our own
like every normal type guy.
So?
So I'm not gonna do it anymore.
Want me to be corny and say
this has taught me a lesson?
- Well, it's taught me a lesson.
- Aw, just forget about it.
Okay, forget about it.
Uh. Yeah, okay.
Forget about it.
- I'm gonna shove off. Okay, Bennie?
- Okay.
- All right. I'll see you.
- So long.
I'll see you, Dennis.
Yeah, you too.
So long.
I gotta get a pack of cigarettes.