You wanted to see me, Sir?
You read the times this morning?
Avershays Press annouced the deal with Irving Gattinger.
Gattinger said he was done with writing.
Yes.
He hasn't written a book in 10 years.
It's a brilliant move.
Based on name recognition alone
it'll be an instant bestseller.
Yes.
What do you think about Weldon Parish?
Parish is one of my personal favorites.
Are you thinking of signing him?
The man hasn't written anything in 20 years.
Or more reason.
What do you know about him?
Um.. Weldon Parish.
He left Unites States in mid 1980s.
Moved to a small Italian village
and after his wife died,
he simply gave up writing.
He's become wreckless.
He doesn't even give interviews.
Mmm. We could sign Weldon Parish.
We woud set the publishing world on it's ears.
I want you to go to Italy and talk to him.
Mr. Benton, with all due respect,
and believe me, no one would like to see a
Weldon Parish novel more than myself,
It's just not going to happen.
That people have tried. The man is
just not interested in writing.
Well, I expect you to make him interested.
Have a nice trip. Goodbye Jeremy.
Hi,
"Aveti una stanza con una banio?"
All the rooms have a private bathroom.
Ah. You speak English.
Does it sound like English?
Yes?
There you go.
Great. Look, I have some bags and...
Excuse me?
I have a couple more bags in the car.
Well.
Thank you.
What? Are you kidding?
I carried the bags.
I opened the door.
You opened the door....ok.
Is everything ok?
Ugh yes.
The room itself is fine, but..
There is a hmm..
There is a couple next door of me and they are...
Screwing.
Yes.
They come here every chance they get for privacy.
Huh.. anyway. I am actually
in town looking for Weldon Parish.
You wouldn't by any chance know, would you?
No.
Well, any idea where he lives?
No?
No...
Really. He's up here for 20 years,
and you don't know him and you have no idea where he lives.
Yes.
Right.
Weldon Parish?
Excuse me.
Do you know where I can find Weldon Parish?
Weldon Parish?
( Italian )
Ok...
Hello Mr. Parish, my name is Jeremy Taylor.
Hello, Mr. Parish.
Hi, Mr. Parish, My name is Jeremy Taylor.
Pearce Learner Publishing.
Hi, Weldon. I am Jeremy.
He is not here.
I just thought I would tell you so you wouldn't
waste the whole day talking to the door.
Are you a reporter?
Me? No. Why?
Cause papa hates reporters.
He says they are the lowest form of human life.
My name is Jeremy Taylor. I am an
editor with Pearce Learner Publishing.
That's even worse. He says that editors
don't even qualify as human life.
Oh... Well, it can't hurt to talk to him, can it?
No, it could hurt very much.
The last editor who came here,
he chased him down to the water with an axe.
Ok. Well, I'll take my chances if you don't mind.
Ok. He is around the back. In the cellar.
Excuse me? I didn't catch your name.
Isabella.
Mr. Parish?
Mr. Parish. My name is Jeremy Taylor.
With Pearce Learner Publishing..
I have to say this is a great honor for me, sir.
(Foreign Language)
What?
Yes, I know he is here.
He is talking to me.
Can't you see he is talking to me?
Who are you talking to?
The King of the......
...
I am having Spam for lunch.
Do you like Spam?
I like mine with raisins.
Umm, you are Weldon Parish.
The writer.
They say I am.
Were you looking for someone else?
Yes, I think I was.
Ok, ok.
Hold on a second.
Did you find him?
Yes, I found him.
What happened to him?
No one really knows.
His mind just broke.
That's why everyone protects him.
Si.
That's just joyce.
Hmm, I want to check out in the morning
if that's ok?
He just came in. No.. he thinks
you are completely crazy, Weldon.
He is leaving tomorrow,ok?
Ciao, ciao.
That's a pretty elaborate plot
to get me to go away, don't you think?
Apparently that wasn't elaborate enough.
Mr. Parish, I came a long way to see you.
I didn't ask you to. See ya.
Do you know what "go away" means?
All I am asking for is
a few minutes of your time.
You are not going to go away, are you?
I am sorry to be so persistent,
but nobody ever got anyway by
taking "no" for an answer, right?
Alright. Make your pitch.
As I said before, I am with
Pearce Learner Publishing.
A place where we pride ourselves in
being able to work with creative individuals.
We believe in bringing the writer's
vision to the page.
And as a writer myself, I understand
how important that is.
What do you write?
Umm, well, I am actually still
working on my first novel.
I mean, I don't even know if it's any good, but
I have always dreamt of being a writer.
And being a writer you think you can understand me?
Well, Yes.
Well, you can't.
Actually, Mr. Parish, i think if you were to give me.....
Look...
You made your pitch.
I am not interested.
But I am not finished.
Yes. you are.
That's Bruno. Bruno dislikes
strangers more than I do.
Now would be a good time
to start running.
What?
Oh, Oh my god!
Hello?
Ah, Jeremy.
How is it going over there?
Oh sir, I'm...
Not well.
Well, did you meet him?
Oh yes.
Yes, I've met him.
What's he like?
The word "unstable" comes to mind.
Well, show me an artist who isn't, eh?
Well, I think I can say with
a great deal of confidence
that the man is not interested in writing.
Well, it is up to you to convenice him.
I am expecting results, Jeremy.
Jeremy?
Jeremy, are you there?
Yes, yes. I am sorry.
I am still here, but you know what?
Actually, I've got to run right now.
Can I call you back later?
Ok. Thank you. Bye.
Si. Si. Si....
Ciao.
Hi!
I heard about what happened this afternoon.
Dog... Yeah.
Yeah, your father is a very funny man.
I am so sorry. I tried to warn you.
So.. Where are you going?
I was actually just looking for a place to eat.
Oh, ok. there is only one place.
You would like that I take you?
Yes. Yes, I would.
Come.
Have you decided?
No, we haven't seen the menus yet.
There is no menu. Only specials.
Ok, then what are the specials?
Mix green salad and Spaghetti with Pesto.
Anything else?
No.
Perfect. Then can I have the mix green Salad
and some Speghetti with pesto?
Excellent choice. Isebella?
I've eaten.
Well.
You know..If you've eaten, you really
don't have to stay here with me.
No, people shouldn't eat alone.
I eat alone all the time so I am used to it.
You changed your hair.
It looks good.
Really?
Thank you.
So.. Isabella.
What is it that you do here?
I work with my horses,
I work with the vineyard.
That doesn't sound too bad to me.
Your father seems to have adapted well.
Well, my father is not an ordinary man.
Why do you want him to write so bad?
Well..
Honestly?
Mm.
When I was 12 years old,
I broke my collar bone.
So I was on the same bed for 5 weeks,
and I don't know if you have ever tried,
but it's not easy to keep a 12 years old
in bed for 5 weeks.
One day my hunt brings me a book.
"The Shadow Dancer" by Weldon Parish.
And.. as I am reading this book,
Something absolutely miraculous happens to me.
I am transported into a differnt world,
and everyday for 5 weeks,
I lived through those words.
And to have the talent to instill those kind of
feelings to other people is a gift. And...
It just should not be wasted.
You should have spoken to him like that.
Like what?
I see the passion that you have for his work.
You should have let him see it.
Well, I tried.
No, you tried to sell him.
And I know my father.
He reponds to honesty.
You should have tried using some.
If you want another chance.
He'll be at "Carina's letter". Umm,
It's a bar just outside of the home.
You wouldn't have the straight.
That, my dear friend. You'll have to pay to find out.
This is interesting. You are acting like you have it.
You are trying to make me believe you have it.
So?
So. In a way you are lying.
Prist shouldn't live, Giovanni.
There is no lying in poker.
There is only bluffing.
And God forgives bluffing.
What? I can't come have a drink at the bar?
You could have a drink at the hotel.
Well, I would have.
But there is no one there.
Why don't you let me buy you a drink?
Just so you know there is no hard feelings about today.
Thank you.
Salute!
Salute.
Ok. Why don't you ask me then you can go.
Ask what?
Question that's burning a hole in your little brain.
Why do I stop writing.
Ok. Why did you stop writing?
I didn't have anything else to say, Ollie.
Ok? It's that simple.
Now, you can go.
A writer always has something to say.
Oh.. Now you are an authority.
How the hell do you know
what I have to say?
No.. no.. no.. ha..  Mr. Parish.
Look. We say we'll have a drink.
I don't remember anything about a conversation.
Well, the mere act of accepting an
invitation to have a drink,
implies a certain degree of a conversation.
I hope you don't write like you talk.
Why? How do I talk?
Like an uptight jockstrap.
Ok.. Well, why were you upset?
Actually, I wouldn't upset anything.
I would have gotten the hint by not wanting to talk.
You are not one of those lampy pampy guy
unless there is a drink all night, are you?
Very Impressive.
Ok. Hasta la bye bye.
No, I bought this bottle of wine,
and I intend not to finishing it.
Eh?
See you guys tomorrow.
What do you mean,
"See you guys tomorrow"?
You said you were going back to London.
No. You said I was going back to London.
Hi, kid. You too.
You've had too much to drink.
Well just drive you back to the hotel.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
What's this?
You guys are going to rough me up a little bit?
Hay, Seriously. Hay, what's that?
What are you doing back there?
It's obvious that you just won't go away.
Hay. Wow.. Hay, Father.
You're just gonna stand by and let this happen?
This is God's will, my son.
I don't know why you can't understand.
I think I've gone a great length
to make myself clear.
God! I was just trying to do my job.
Well, now you are going to join the others.
What others? There are others in there?
They wouldn't go away, either.
Ok, but I will. I will go. I promise.
I don't believe you.
I think you'll just saying that so I'll let you go.
No, No.. I will abolutely go.
Tomorrow. As soon as I can.
I think he is telling the truth.
Yes. Listen to him.
I don't believe him.
No...
No.. Wow..There is no need for this.
La Reverende.
What does "go away" mean, Mr. Taylor?
It means "go away."
I'll expect you to do just that.
Lion.
I'm baptizing you in the name of father,
the son and the holy ghost.
What are you doing?
Baptizing you.
I am Jewish.
Not anymore.
Hay, Ciao.
Unbelieveable.
You've got balls, boy. I'll give you that.
And you've got my car keys.
There you go.
Is that all?
Yeap.
You know what? That's not it.
Because whatever reason you have
for not wanting to write,
I accept them being personal,
but that's still no excuse for you to be
such an unbelieveable asshole.
I guess I am not everyone.
You know,
I admit. I only came here because my boss sent me.
But underneath, I came here because
I have always wanted to meet you.
I thought that maybe if I could meet
the Great Weldon Parish,
Perhaps you can teach me how to be a better writer.
But I realize now that the only  things that you have
to teach me are bitterness,
and mistrust.
There goes the great business, Weldon?
What brings you to town, Ian?
I just finished my new novel and came back for a drink.
You remember that once you finished a book
way back,
when you still had so many to say.
I am sorry. Did I striken out?
It must be tough, being all dried out and said.
and having to live on the past glories.
At least he has past glories to live on.
and who might you be?
Jeremy Taylor.
Ian McBain.
Ian McBain, the novelist?
I know your work.
You are a fan?
No, I didn't say that.
Jeremy.
Actually, I would say that your themes are all the same.
That your narration lacks depth and imagination.
Jeremy.
Your prose struggles for wit.
Overall, you style is sluggish, at best.
And contains absolutely nothing that
your average Joe with a typewriter couldn't produce.
He punched me in the nose.
You'll live. I'll drive.
You...... shall carry us to.......
No..
Oh my god! Weldon.. Please.. Please.. No!
Weldon!
That was great, wasn't it?
You are completely out of your mind.
You know what, right?
Don't you feel it?
Feel what?
Oh God!
Life!
Would you sit down? You maniac! God!
Ok, I am serious. Stop now.
Break! Break! Wow!
Jesus!
I'm sorry about your car.
Oh. Shut up.
Look, I know maybe I was a little rough on you.
A little rough?
You think you were a little rough on me?
After you sit your dog on me,
Tight me up and threw me in the lake?
It was a pond.
Do you really think I am bitter?
Why do you care what I think?
I am just asking.
Everyone around here is afraid to tell me the truth.
Yes, I think you are bitter.
And, I think you are rude, insensitive,
dangerous, self-centered,..
Get the Idea.
Look at you.
You are in a jail, the both of you.
It was a matter of honor.
Come on dad, it was a manner of boredom
so you have to go and create trouble.
I don't care too much for your tone.
Remember who is the parent and who is the child.
I am a little confused about that myself.
So.. Why don't you remind me, huh?
Are you ok?
No.
I am gonna have some people up at the house. Tomorrow.
Why don't you come by?
I thought you didn't like me.
I don't. but I dislike you less than I did yesterday.
Ciao, Isabella. Weldon?
(Italian)
Hi!
Still mad?
Someone could have got killed yesterday.
In all fairness , it wasn't entirely your father's fault.
Exactly. He gets into enough trouble on his own.
He doesn't need help from anyone.
Ugh.. look, I am sorry, but
Ian McBain was saying that he is all dried out and
living on past glories.
I couldn't just stand there and let him say those things.
I love my father very much.
But tell me.
Which part of the statement isn't true?
-That's an aweful cruel thing to say about
your own father. Don't you think?
Really?
Well, yes.
None of my business.
No, I know what you see.
You see the great Weldon Parish.
A man's man.
A man who lives the life on his terms,
and others de damned.
But you don't have to pick up the pieces.
You don't have to watch a man
who was once strong and gentle,
Slowly destroying himself.
How long it's been like that?
Since the day he stops writing.
Are you saying you think he still wants to write?
Of course, he wants to write.
Then why doesn't he?
Because he is afraid.
He is afraid that what was once great
about him is gone.
He is afraid that Ian McBain is right.
Jeremy, these are my two other daughters,
Dinnie and Maura.
Pleasure to meet you both.
Jeremy Taylor.
Bon appetito. (Italian)
Appetito. Appetito. (Italian)
I didn't see you at the mass
this morning, Mr. Taylor.
Oh, are you Catholic?
No, I am not.
Be careful, he'll try to convert you.
I know. He's already tried, actually.
But does it matter what religion we are?
In the end, we all die.
There's this shocking defect that one day,
we will all be rotten corpses,
in the dark, demp, creek.
Cheers.
So, what is it you do? Mr. Taylor?
Why don't you all stop picking at him and let him eat?
He is a book editor.
Yes. He is a book editor.
I am sitting next to a book editor.
Please. Try to make a bribe, my son.
God gave you a tremendous talent.
It's true.
This... No, this time I can't tell you.
It's a secret. It's a secret.
Buon Giorno. (Good day.)
(Italian)
Jeremy, this is Amalia.
Pleasure to meet you.
How do you do.
Weldon.
That's the bill for my car repairs.
I noticed one of my cows was missing this morning.
You wouldn't know anything about it.
I've got it. for safe keeping.
So this is settled.
You stole my cow.
Call it collateral.
Excuses me.
Oh. Hello, Amalia.
Hello, Ian.
Oh, you are looking very beautiful today.
Can I speak to you in private for a moment?
I am busy.
Well, I just came by to ask if you'd... ugh..
If you'd like to go to the town party with me.
I can't. I am going with Weldon.
It's news to me.
One of these days you are gonna
push me too far, Weldon.
Yeah? Well, lets hope you are
standing by a cliff when I do.
What?
Get dressed.
Get dressed... Get dressed...
Seriously, what are we doing?
(....)
There you are sweetie.
Come to take you home from the bad man.
Weldon, I am not stealing a cow.
This is my cow.
I can't steal something I already own.
Then why do you need me here for?
You can be a litttle tempermental.
I'm gonna need you to get behind her
and give her a little push.
No, no way.
I understand that cow'd be Ian's?
What's this?
What does it look like?
No, I mean, that's it for?
For you to get rid of that computer.
Why? Computer makes it easier.
Writing is not supposed to be easy,
supposed to be hard.
Typewriters make you think about
the words you choose more carefully
because you can't erase them with the
push of a button.
Do you konw how?
I don't dance.
I'll teach you.
No... no.. no.. Look.
You don't want to write,
I don't want to dance, ok?
So if I would write, you would dance?
Maybe?
I don't wanna dance with you that bad.
Now, everybody has their price, Weldon,
and it has to be something you want.
What's your price? What would you do
to get me to write a book for you?
Well, for starters,
I could offer you a large advance.
I don't need money.
Ok, but there has to be
something that you want.
I want you to kiss my ass.
No, seriously.
I am serious.
I am going to drop my drawers.
And if you kiss my ass in front of everybody,
I'll sign the contract.
OK.
Oh my god. Wow. Wow. Wow.
No, not okey. Not okey at all.
Don't say I didn't give you a chance.
I wouldn't call that much of a chance.
All you had to do was use your imagination.
Pretend I was a beautiful woman.
1/3 of a second.
We all would have known how much you wanted it.
OK, fine. I'll do it.
Huh, too late.
What?
Too late.
Life is about seizing the moment,
and you just let this book slit by.
That was a shady trick you pulled on me back there.
You know what your problem is?
you are too anal.
I am not the one who asked you to kiss my ass.
You knew I wouldn't do it, didn't you?
Of course.
You are far too concerned with what
a room full of strangers might think of you,
to do anything foolish or spontaneous.
Well, that's called restrained.
Boring.
Perhaps. But it's better than
being a lunatic.
Everybody needs a lunacy.
It's what frees us from
the pain in this world.
There is a wild man inside you, Jeremy.
I can see him in your eyes.
Why don't you let him out?
You might like him.
If he's anything like you,
I'll think I'll keep him locked up. Thanks.
Look, would you mind trying to putting on your pants?
I am not really comfortable
standing next to a naked man.
Ha. Ha. Ha. Ha.
I used to come here with my wife.
She loved this place.
She'd spend hours just....shhhh.
Back then I never had time for the little things.
I was always so afraid I....
wouldn't get a thought down
or I'd forget a line of dialogue.
when the police came to tell me that her car had...
After that nothing mattered.
And now I wish I could go back.
Just for one day.
Time is a precious thing, Jeremy.
And the years teach much was today's living new.
Jeremy.
Oh.. Hi.
Weldon told me tell you
to be at this place at five.
Um... What? Five?
Five.
OK. Fine. Five.
She is beautiful, isn't she?
Who?
That's a good one.
Are you still mad at me?
No.
My father told me it wasn't your fault.
That's right. It really wasn't.
Who?
What's that?
I have no idea.
Would you care to take a seat?
Sure. OK.
OK.
You are writing.
Well, trying.
Well, that's say..
I am looking for inspiration.
You.. finding anything?
Em... Yes.
I think I am starting to.
Are you missing London?
No.
Actually, No. I am not, really.
Your family?
Well, I don't have too much family left.
Both of my parents died when I was 16 years old,
and I moved to London to live with my aunt,
but she passed 3 years ago.
I am so sorry.
Eh, well, you didn't know.
Thank you.
You have a girlfriend?
No.
I did, but you know...
Those things go. Didn't work out.
Come on, that's not fair.
You don't speak any Italian, huh?
No, not a word.
No.
Well, if I can ever help you...
Well, actually, since you've offered. There are
a couple of words i've been meaning to learn.
For instance, beautiful.
"Bello."
Mm.
Okey.
And, lips.
"Labbia."
Right.
Now, just a kiss.
That's enough Italian for one day, huh?
Okey. Okey.
I'll see you later.
Oh, yeah.
Describe it to me.
Now?
What you're looking at.
Describe it to me.
Well, it's sun setting.. huh..
green the hills, and..
No, describe it to me as if you are writing it.
The sun.. droppin in behind a...
The sun dropped?
English is your first language, isn't it?
I can't think on the spot like this.
Jeremy, anyone can use words.
It's called talking,
but writers arrange them in a way so that
they'll take on that beauty in their form.
Think of words as... colors.
and paper is the canvas.
Alright. Well, if it's really that easy,
why don't you try painting it?
Sorry. I realized you don't want to do that.
You are right.
What if I... did do it..
I'd probably say something like...
The sunset...
slowly
igniting the sky and fiery shades of reded orange.
In the distance, dark clouds rolled over the horizen,
riding the summer winds.
Soon, day will give away to night,
and with it will come..
the sun as that washes over everything.
"Italian"
For my size.
Gracie. (Thank you.).
And this?
No. No. (Italian.)
OK. OK.
Perfect.
(Italian)
I was wondering if you were coming.
When have I ever missed the monday night.
What is this?
Karaoke night.
What do you think?
You guys actually do this?
Yeah.
And so do you.
Oh, no. No way.
You'll be fine.
No, no. Seriously, I won't do it.
You just need a couple of drinks.
I don't care how many drinks you put in me,
I am not getting up and singing.
(Italian)
Jeremy, is that you?
Yes, sir. It's me.
Any progress in this Parish affair?
A little, yeah.
Well, what seems to be the problem?
Well, he seems to think that he doesn't
want to write, but I think that he does.
Do you think he genuinely like you?
Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
Good. Use it. Anything is possible.
Get him to see that his writing
is in everyone's best interest.
Well, what if writing really
isn't in his best interest?
Jeremy, the funtion of business
is to get things done.
That is what you are there for.
To get things done.
Now, do it.
Ok, well. I understand what you are saying
that writing comes from experience.
But even after you've experienced something,
you still got to get it down on a page.
That's called talent.
Weldon. The other day, when you
describe the sunset, that was great.
No, it was. That was great.
And I gotta tell you, I think it would really..
It would be helpful for me
if you could... I don't know...
Throw something like that down on a page and,
and just... just let me see it, you know?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
We had a deal, remember?
We would talk about writing.
Not about me writing.
Right. No, I just wanna...
I know what you want.
What do you think I am, an idiot?
You don't think I know what it would
do for your career if you sign me?
That's not why I am doing this.
Alright., we were talking about experience.
If you were writing a fight scene,
It helps if you've been in a fight.
Have you ever been in a fight?
Me? Yeah.
The closest I ever came was getting
punched in the nose the other day.
That's pathetic. If you were writing a character
who got.. punched in the stomach.
How would you describe that?
Just use my imagination.
OK. Go ahead. Tell me what you feel like.
I'll double over in pain,
I'll be gasping for breath.
Ugh.. What else?
Well, I don't know.
Ok, now.
You got the doubling over and
gasping for air part right.
But it's also that breath sensation you got.
The pounding in your head,
the weak legs and tearing eyes.
Oh, notice this snot hanging out of your nose.
There is a feeling that you'll never
gonna breath again and then...
you lung is filled with cool fresh air.
That's experience.
Stop trying to manipulate me.
Father, am I disturbing you?
No. No. No, my son.
I, I was just preparing the sacraments
for the evening prayer.
I, I've been expecting you.
You have?
yes.
I am a priest, and part of my job
is to help those who need it.
You wish to speak about Weldon and writing.
So. How do I reach him?
Do you believe in fate?
I'm... father.. I don't know.
I do.
I believe that each of us are
predestined to walk a path in life.
Along this path, we meet others.
And through knowing them,
we changed their lives.
Ok, but...what does that have to do with
Weldon and writing?
There's an old story about a bird
who loved to fly.
One day, while it was high up in the air,
it began to rain. And its
feathers became so heavy
that when it tried to land, it broke its wing.
Time past, and the bird became better.
It wanted to fly, but
no matter how hard it tried,
Something inside stopped
it from leaving the ground.
Day after day, it tried.
And day after day.
it's fear, held it down.
Then one day, a strong wind came,
and lifted high into the sky.
It opened its wings, and
realized that it could fly.
I got. I do.
Weldon is the bird and he
is afriad to fly, right?
No, Jeremy. Weldon is the bird,
and you are the wind.
That is the path, fate's chosen for you.
Hi.
Hello.
Father Moretti tells me you had
a nice little chat today.
Obviously, I didn't punch you
in the stomach hard enough.
I need to apologize for earlier.
Look, I only went to speak
with Father Moretti
because I... I didn't understand what happ....
This is my manuel script.
I know.
Where did you get this?
I went to the hotel and told Gustav
you wanted me to get it for you.
You had no right to do that, Weldon.
You've got talent, Jeremy.
You are a good writer.
The problem is you don't
trust your talent.
You don't believe you could find that
part of you that has something to say.
But... how do I know when I found it?
What do you mean?
There is no mistake in it.
I know there is a lot of time
and effort put into those pages.
Have enough faith in yourself to let them go.
Take what you've learned from
them and start again.
Ciao.
"Italian"
I have abosutely no idea what
you just said, but sounds good.
Want some company?
Sure, come.
Rid the horses, ha?
Uhuh.
Jesus, I am gonna die.
When was the last time you were on a horse?
That's see... Last time I was on a horse was...
That would be never.
Never?
Yes, never.
Why did you come?
Well, it's a new experience. ...
I think I've no experiences lately.
Ooh... Wow...
So how was the writing go?
Um... I don't know actually.
I am really starting to question
wheather or not I have what it takes.
Oh, yes. Self-doubt.
It is a common theme with creative people.
Do you find a lot of creative people are...
Crazy?
Yes, crazy.
Of course they are crazy.
There are thousands of writers, artists.
For most of them, the dreams were never come true.
You have to be crazy.
Well, thanks, Weldon. That's very encouraging.
No.. that's the reality, Jeremy.
Art is not something you choose to do.
It's something that chooses you.
Why did you want to become a writer?
Because... I think that I..
No, it's not something you think.
It's something you know.
Tell me when you know the answer.
It's amazing how much she lives like her mother.
Sometimes I walk into her room
and for a moment I'd think...
Describe her to me.
Come on, not this again.
Just do it, will you?
Sun light frames her body and
golden glow of honey light.
All the wind dances gently
through the long strands of her hair.
Her face is strong, proud,
With eyes that don't easily away their secrets.
It's a face that doesn't call out,
with softly beckons.
How was that?
You tell me.
By the way,
How long have you been
in love with my daughter?
"Italian"
Ciao, Weldon.
Ciao.
What?
You two are the couple next door?
Are you ready for the party?
Yeah.
I was not stealing.
I was accepting charity.
Weldon. It's going to be a late night.
Why don't you all stay at the hotel?
Half price, of course.
Ok, free.
You were gone when I woke up this morning.
You had a dream.
That's funny cause it felt pretty real to me.
Yes, but last night was last night.
What exactly does that mean?
Means I wanted to see how I felt with you.
And how did you feel?
Jeremy....
We live in different worlds, ha?
There is no reason why you
couldn't come and live in my world.
Do I look like I belong in London?
My life is here, with my
family and my horses.
Isabella, I don't want to just
let this slip away.
I know...
I am sorry. I...
I just wanted to share something with you.
It is a god damn pitty, Weldon.
Your daughter is a wonderful girl.
Yes, she is.
Yeah, she is.
What was god thinking
when he created women?
He was probably trying to
make up for creating us.
You think?
True. I mean most of us are smelly, hairy morons,
with one foot out of the cave.
But women, that's where god outdid himself.
Yes, he certainly did.
I mean, of all the things he created,
what could be more perfect than a woman?
Nothings come to mind.
The curve of their necks,
the small of their backs,
softness of the skin,
breasts of the multitude of
the shapes and sizes.
I tell you, Jeremy. If I were
a woman, I'd be a lesbian.
Now, there is a good idea.
Me, too. I think I'll be a lesbian, too.
Is that ok? Can I be a lesbian?
Sure. Sure.
You Wanna know what my problem really is?
I am afraid.
Of what?
Of life, of love. Everything.
I won't mind the vila, Weldon.
one grow grapes and write great novels.
So what's stopping you.
Fear.
Fears. I mean, I have built this whole
for myself in London. I..
I don't think I can just change.
Well, Jeremy.
Most people are perfectly content,
living in their dreary little worlds.
They just clinch to the edge of the toilet bowl,
trying to keep their heads above water
hoping some fool will come along
to pull the chain.
It's only when you hear that flushing sound
and begin to sly down into the abyss
that they'd start taking stock at their lives.
What about the people who are so
comfortable in their suffering?
They don't even know that the chain has been pulled.
I know that you wanna write, Weldon.
You just can't leave it alone, can you?
No. No, I can't.
But tell me I am wrong.
Weldon, look me in the eye,
and tell me that you don't want to write.
I don't want to write.
You know what I think?
I think that you miss it.
No.
I think that all the drinking,
and all the crazniess,
is just your way of covering it up
what's missing in your life.
Right.
And everybody knows it, Weldon. everybody.
Your daughters know it;
Father Moretti knows it;
Gustavo knows it; I know it;
but what's worse, is you know it.
Tell me, hot shot.
You think knowing me a couple of weeks,
and living 25 years of a sheltered
existances gives you a right
to tell me how to live my life?
25 years or 25 minutes.
The truth is still the truth.
My life is fine the way it is!
I do what I want when I want.
I pick a few grapes once a year.
That's all I have to do.
I was just a writer, for god's sake.
That's all I was.
I didn't cure a cancer,
I didn't walk on the moon.
The world isn't gonna stop spinning
if there isn't a Weldon Parish's novel.
You are right, it won't.
But maybe yours will start again.
And you are a writer, Weldon;
is what you are, and you are
a great one at that.
A great writer knows when
he is not a great writer anymore.
So what? He just gives up?
I didn't give anything up.
20 years ago I lost something,
something more important than my writing.
How can I explain it to you?
I can't explain it to myself.
Stop it. Just stop.
Stop what?
If you don't want to write, that's fine.
But stop blaming it on your dead wife.
What do you want from me?
You want to prove I am miserable.
I  rarely see you don't want to write, Weldon.
You write every single day.
You just stopped putting the
pen to the page.
Sometimes I've tortured you
this way, that way,
and you find yourself a place you live...
imaging you being...
If we have realized it...
it's too late to go back.
No, it's never too late.
I don't have anything left.
I don't believe you, Weldon.
I can't do it.
And it's bullshit. You knot it.
I can't.
Why?
Because...
Because why?
Because I am afraid.
But Weldon, you are not afraid of writing,
you are afraid of failing.
We all fail.
Courage is in the trying.
Are you alright?
You should have seen me today, Father.
You would have been proud.
I was very clever.
What happened?
I forced Weldon done a road
hitting when I go.
And I am a little afraid of what
he's gonna find at the end of it.
Sometimes it's you messed up something now,
in order to make the something now.
Did it ever occur to you that
maybe the great Weldon Parish,
just simply does that have anything left to say?
You don't really belive that, do you?
I know that you think I am a
salvation, but I am not.
I am just not.
Everynight, I go home and
I struggle to write one paragraph
that tells me that I have something,
anything important to say.
And there is a man, who can do it
standing on his head,
and he chooses not to.
He chooses that.
And I am supposed to feel sorry for him?
Well, I am sorry. I don't.
and I know life is dump dump.
but life dumps on all of us, father.
And we move on, we get pass it.
At least most of us do.
Look, I am not responsible for Weldon Parish.
I only did what I was sent here to do.
And I told him that right from the very beginning.
It's not like I lied to him.
If that's true, why are you so upset?
Maura, where is everybody?
Still sleeping.
What are you all gawking at? You acted
as if you've never seen me writed before.
You could stay.
And do what?
Write?
Besides, I don't think I'd be
the only sad to see you go.
I don't know about that.
Jeremy, what have you got to go back to?
My life, my job.
I can't just pull up stakes
and move out here, Weldon.
Why not?
I...
I just can't.
Well.
What about the contracts?
What about them?
I can't sign if you don't give them to me.
You know? why don't you just see how it goes?
Uh?
I want you to write the book for yourself.
There is no need for you to have to deal
with the pressures of editors and publishers.
And if you like what you've written;
Then believe me, we will be
happy to publish it.
( Italian )
Bye.
Ciao, Jeremy.
Ciao.
Goodbye, my son.
Ciao, Jeremy.
Isabella?
In Italy we say a good friend is someone who
is there through with the good and the bad.
Si.
Yeah?
And it's because I can't imagine
doing anything else.
What?
That's why I wanna be a writer.
Because I can't imagine doing anything else.
Okey.
Bye, everybody.
Ciao.
Ciao, Jeremy.
(Italian)
You broke his wing.
No fly...
Uh.. no fly. no fly.
Fly.
Graci, mama.
( Italian )
Si, mama.