[Dog Barking]
[Exhaling,
Clearing Throat]
Hey, uh,
is Juanita in?
No, she's not,
but she'll be back in...
in a while.
[Delilah] So you gonna stand
out there or you comin' in?
[Chuckles]
I'll come on in.
Girl, check you out.
I thought you were going
over to the Communists.
Ah, nah. Not me.
Well, dig, if you were smart,
that's what you would've done.
What?
[Scoffs] Man.
You don't know what the hell
you're talkin' about, girl.
Nah, it's cool. It's not your fault
you've been brainwashed by America.
- [Snickers]
- I mean,
at least you
made it back alive, right?
You know, "Hello.
How ya doin'?"
That would've been real nice before you
got off into all this political shit.
Welcome home.
And welcome
to the revolution.
- So, uh, this is Sarah's?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, wow.
So is she a smart baby?
- Oh...
- [Keys Jangling]
Why don't you find out
for yourself?
[Door Opening]
Hey, y'all.
Sorry I'm late.
Traffic on the Cross Bronx
was a mess.
Oh. All righty.
There we go.
There you go.
Go play with your blocks.
[Sniffles]
Hey.
Oh, no. Look, Juanita,
I'm in one piece.
[Sighs]
Hey, I got somebody
I want you to meet.
- Come here, Sarah. Come to Mommy.
- [Baby Talk]
Good girl. Come here.
Look at that.
That's Daddy.
Say hi.
- Hi.
- This is Sarah Marie Curtis.
- Hello. [Nervous Chuckle]
Well, hold her, silly.
She's yours.
Ohh!
Hey.
[Man] ¡ Oye!
What's goin' on, my brothers?
[Sighs]
So this is it, huh?
Yep. This is home.
Dig it. Dig it.
[Anthony]
Check out Sleeping Beauty back there.
Boy, I still can't get over
how gorgeous she is.
- Well, she got that from her mama.
- Oh. Okay.
[Siren Wailing
In The Distance]
You know, Juanita,
I just wanna let you know
l... I did miss you.
- A lot.
- Don't you think I know that, Anthony?
It's not important anyway. The important
thing is that you're here now.
Shh. Come here.
Ooh.
Hey, baby girl.
Hey, Cutty.
Came by to see you a little earlier,
but you weren't home.
Oh, you know,
I had class tonight after work,
and then I stopped over by my mother's.
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
It's Saturday.
[Juanita]
Yeah.
- I see my little girl's
sleepin' back there, huh?
- Yeah.
She's all played out.
- Cutty, I wanted you to meet, um...
- Look here.
I got a little somethin'
for Sarah.
[Cutty]
Buy her somethin' real nice.
? Smilin' faces sometimes
Hey?
Cutty, I told you.
Stop spoilin' her like this.
? Smilin' faces?
- [Chuckles]
- ? Smilin' faces tell lies?
- Somebody's gotta do it.
- ? And I got proof?
- ? Beware??
- Cutty, I want you to meet Anthony.
[Tyres Screeching]
[Juanita]
Okay. All right.
Let me just put her to bed.
You come on in.
You make yourself at home.
Come on in.
- Okay. Can I get you
something to drink?
- Look, Juanita, uh...
- I think I better go.
- But you just got here.
Who knows? You could
be expectin' company or somethin'.
Nobody's comin' here,
Anthony.
I think I still should go.
I used to see Cutty.
Is that what you wanna hear?
Blood made that
very clear to me.
- So, then what's the problem?
- "Problem"?
[Chuckles]
Man throw two yards in your car.
You askin' me
what's the problem?
Shit.
Obviously nothin'.
Don't come up in here
judgin' me.
What the fuck, man.
You got a pimp around my daughter?
Oh, he is not a pimp.
And besides, if you cared anything
about havin' a daughter,
you'd have wrote me back
after I sent you her picture.
But don't jump on me
for havin' a life.
You didn't want one
with me.
So now what?
Are you gonna leave?
- Some bullshit.
- [Scoffs]
[Scoffs]
[Sighs]
Come here.
Come on. Come here.
? Hey?
- ? Ya gotta
Ya gotta pay back?
- ? Payback?
- Damn!
- ? Revenge?
- ? A man?
- ? The big payback?
? Got to get back?
Cleanup time, Cowboy.
Say, man, why the fuck you
always gotta talk some shit?
? Payback
Right there?
See, that's why I kicked his fuckin' ass
when he was a little kid.
- Always gettin' smart and shit.
- ? A man?
? Get down
with my girlfriend?
? That ain't right?
Now you gonna play
this marine war hero.
You know what I think?
I think y'all
was some goddam fools,
goin' over there,
fightin' that white man's war.
That's right.
What you got when you
get back here, huh?
Not a goddam thing.
'Course, you do got
that fine ass Juanita. [Chuckles]
Man, what the fuck you lookin' at me
like that for, man?
I'm just complimenting you
on your taste.
'Course, you know, uh, baddest
motherfucker this side of Nicky Barnes,
my boss man, Cutty.
? Gettin' ready
for the big payback?
I thought that might
ring a bell.
? The big payback?
He used to tap that ass while you
was over in the 'Nam. [Chuckling]
- ? The big payback?
- Motherfucker!
Goddamn!
You do some fuckin' talkin', don't you,
goddamn it! Try this on, motherfucker!
- No, no, no. He needs his ass whipped.
- What you mean "no"?
- [Cowboy Grunting]
- [Anthony Shouting]
- ? Get ready?
- Talk shit now, huh, motherfucker?
Shut the fuck up!
Come on! Come on! Fuck you!
You wanna fuck with me or what?
I'm gonna fuckin' kill your ass.
- Say somethin' now, motherfucker.
- That's enough, youngblood.
- Pull out your goddam knife!
- That's enough. I said that's enough.
- Come on! That's enough!
- I'm gonna kill this motherfucker!
I'll kill that mother and
everybody in his motherfuckin'...
- Come on!
- Let me go, Kirby. Let me go!
- [Kirby]
He's already beat up. Come on now.
- Oh, shit.
Come on. Let's go
get some air.
Don't need no fuckin' air!
Let me go.
- ? Lemme hit him, Hit him, hit him??
- That's game.
- [Crashing]
- Shit!
Gonna have
the aeroplane corn bread.
- Here we go. [Gasps]
- [Juanita] Ugh.
- You're gonna spoil that girl.
- Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna spoil that one
in your belly too.
I don't need
no spoiled kids.
Hey, why not?
Not enough black babies
are spoiled.
Ain't that right,
Sarah? Hmm?
- You got a point there.
- [Grunting] Come on.
Sit on down.
Big girl. Come here.
Come here!
[Laughing]
Look at you.
Fat girl.
[Chuckles]
Let's see what
we got ourselves here.
Oh, you know what? I think we
gonna have ourselves a little boy.
Ha! Yeah, come on, man.
You got to be a boy.
Boy, boy. Mm-mm-mm.
Ant Junior.
See? It's the power
of the mind.
We will ourselves
a little boy.
Then can you will yourself
a better job?
Can you will yourself
to stop drinkin' so much?
Come on, Juanita. Don't even start
that shit, all right?
Thought we supposed to be
havin' a nice time here.
[Sighs]
Look, Juanita.
I'm gonna get myself
a good job.
You know how long you been singin'
that same old song now, Anthony?
I mean, in case you haven't noticed,
this here's the real world.
Ain't no free meals here
like in the marines.
Hey, let me
tell you somethin'.
Wasn't nothin' free
in the marines.
I earned every meal and every
fuckin' dollar, all right?
Look, everything's
gonna be cool.
You know I'll be
five months next week.
You're five months pregnant,
you can't be no nurse's aide.
I said we'll be all right.
Hey, um... [Clears Throat]
Anybody want some speed?
Get the fuck outta here
with that shit.
[Anthony] Why don't you cut
the bullshit, Joe?
Can't you clear your mind
for one sec, man?
Now, you sure that they
pick up cash money?
Hey, cash money, bro.
Like clockwork,
once a month.
Then they stop by the post
office before they make their
final run to Washington, man.
All the way to Washington, D.C.,
where they burn the money.
Can you believe that shit?
[Jose] Old bills, man.
Sometimes a couple million.
- How many guards?
- Four.
Two in the front and one
in the back carry revolvers.
The other one, [lmitates Gun Cocking]
12-gauge shotgun, man.
You think we can take 'em?
I can't say, man.
I mean, [Clears Throat]
four guards, and all of 'em packin'?
I put up the guns.
I get the money together
to get the plans goin'.
But you got to be the master planner.
[Jose] You got medals for blowin'
motherfuckers up out there.
- I heard you were like John Wayne.
- Well, then that's the deal.
Yeah,
all that money.
Ah, man.
Anthony. You down?
? The look?
- ? Of love?
- Let's drink on it anyway.
? Is in your eyes?
- ? A look?
- Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh.
- ? Your heart?
- Say, man...
- Shhh.
- ? Can't disguise??
Put the goddam thing away.
Get your little pyromaniac ass.
- You gonna be walkin' in a minute.
- Aw, cool out, Kirby, man.
I'm not gonna burn your car.
Not yet, at least. [Giggles]
Look, forget it, Juanita.
Come on.
Watch out there.
[Sighs]
What's the problem, Anthony?
What is it? I mean, is it
because I'm pregnant?
[Scoffs]
Come on. Now don't be silly.
So, then what's the problem?
Come on.
Talk to me. What is it?
[Thunderclap]
[Juanita Scoffs] I told you.
You need to leave that alcohol alone.
[Thunderclap]
[Body Parts Thudding]
[Growling]
- No! No!
- Anthony! Anthony, baby!
Come here. It's me.
It's me. It's all right.
- It's all right. Come here.
- [Panting]
Shh. Shh. Shh.
It's just another dream.
- It's just another dream.
- [Sobbing]
This is my best cut,
Mrs Stein. Enjoy.
Thank you
very much, Saul.
[Mrs Stein]
He's such a nice man.
[Man]
What did he give you?
- We need to talk.
- Oh. All right.
[Man, Mrs Stein
Chattering]
- So what's happenin'?
- You're a good man.
Aw, come on, Saul.
I ain't got time to kibitz with ya.
I got a whole lot
of meat to cut.
I'm closing down the shop.
Should've told you sooner,
but I thought maybe...
business, you know,
pick up a little.
Sorry.
- Here.
- Oh, no, look, Saul...
- No, I can't.
- What am I gonna do with it?
I have to get rid of it.
Come on.
? Now I know?
? We have great respect?
? For the sister
and mother?
? It's even better yet?
? But there's the joker
in the street?
Here you go, brother.
Don't let the bullshit get to you.
[Chuckles]
I'm tryin', man.
- I'm tryin'.
- You wanna get the man's
foot off your neck?
Come check us out.
Take care of yourself, brother.
Live righteous.
Here you go, brother.
Here you go.
Take care of yourself, brother.
Come see us now.
? Don't let us
hang around this town?
? And let what others say
come true??
Brothers and sisters,
here you go.
Heh, heh, heh, heh, hey.
Hey, youngblood.
[Chuckling]
Bringin' in the groceries, huh?
Lord, have mercy.
Man, I remember
when I was married.
I used to love to bring home
the groceries.
Made me feel real good.
Like a man.
Know what I mean?
[Chuckles]
Hey, listen, youngblood.
Uh, I just dropped by
to see Juanita and Sarah.
- You know, lay a little
somethin' on 'em.
- Stopped by to see my baby?
Is that right?
You know, youngblood, I took
care of your woman and your baby
when you were in the war.
Now, a man oughta get a little respect
for somethin' like that.
Now, I ain't
gonna lie to you.
I care about Juanita.
I care about her a whole lot.
But you back now,
and I'm gone.
So from this point on, you should
consider me like a friend of the family.
Find yourself in a jam and shit,
need a little cash,
you come see me,
I'll front you.
- Keep your shit.
- Listen, brother.
I know about pride.
But you got mouths to feed.
Now I laid a little cash
on Juanita.
Stay the fuck away
from my family.
What did you say?
You heard me, goddamn it.
I said, "Stay the fuck away
from my family."
See, I ain't the enemy,
youngblood.
I don't want no trouble.
Shit.
See, I tried to be
a friend, motherfucker.
Surprise, nigger.
[Chuckles]
Big bad marine.
Look at you now.
Does she suck you?
Fuck you?
Make you feel like a man?
Make you feel
real good?
Huh, boy?
Now, she wasn't doin' it
like that before you went
to the war, now was she?
[Chuckles] Now you gettin'
all that good lovin',
and you can't even put food
on your fuckin' table.
Come on, Santa Claus.
Open your mouth and suck this.
Come on. I got a present
for you. Suck it!
Suck it, nigger!
Kill me, motherfucker.
Shoot me right now.
What you gonna do,
shoot me?
You lucky
this is personal, nigger.
I ain't gonna kill you
over no woman.
Don't you ever...
in your fuckin' life...
bite the hand
that feeds you, nigger.
See ya, Santa Claus.
- [Sighs] I'm all right.
- Hold still.
- No, I'm all right. Damn!
You givin' him
that money back.
He won't take it back.
What the fuck you talkin'...
You better give his shit back to him.
Even if I wanted to give it back to him,
he wouldn't take it back.
W-W-W-Wait. What the fuck you talkin'
about, "if you wanted to give it back"?
No, no, no, no.
Fuck that shit.
Have you forgotten
you just lost your damn job?
- We need that fuckin' money.
- We don't need his money.
Yeah, well, Anthony,
I'll tell you what.
You start bringin' some real
money in here, like a real man,
and then I'll think about
givin' it back to him.
Until then, I don't
wanna hear shit.
You need to get your tight ass together,
that's what you need to do,
and stop feelin' sorry
for your damn self.
Sometimes it's like you ain't even
the same man I knew before the war.
That's who I was in love with. That's
who I thought showed the fuck back up.
I don't know who
the fuck you are.
So, what? You just suck his
dick so good, he just start
throwin' money at you, right?
[Scoffs]
What is with you?
Why you so damn paranoid?
I ain't fuckin' him.
Not at this moment,
you ain't. No.
But the motherfucker
ain't sniffin' around here,
tossin' money in your motherfuckin'
face for nothin'!
Yeah, well, I sleep with you
every night, don't I?
You know, Juanita,
that's a damn good question.
Come on. Go ahead.
Admit this shit, man.
Be honest.
- You fuckin' him, right?
- Is that what you wanna hear, Anthony?
- Uh-huh. Yeah.
- Fine.
I'm fuckin' him.
So, uh,
whose baby is that?
D-Don't even answer that shit.
No, you right.
I ain't gonna answer it.
I mean, you Anthony. You the
big marine man with no damn job.
You know
every fuckin' thing.
Answer this for me: If you think
I'm jivin' you so much, Anthony,
why the hell
you with me, huh?
Why the fuck you with me?
Do you think I need you?
Do you think I need this shit?
Fuck. You can't get a decent job,
you won't fuck me.
The only time I get to hold you
is when you're havin' one of
them silly-ass nightmares...
Shut the fuck up!
You don't know, girl.
You really don't know.
- Don't you fuckin' walk away from...
- You better get the fuck off of me!
- Don't walk away from me, Anthony.
- Let me go.
- Don't you... What about Sarah?
- I'll fuckin' kill you, girl!
Don't you ever run up on me!
Ever! Ever run up on me again!
I'll fuckin' kill you, Juanita!
Get the fuck off me!
Bunch of shit!
[Sobbing]
[Shouting Gibberish]
[Man #1]
That's right. You can't trust them!
[Man #2]
Pretty cool, wasn't it?
[Audience Murmuring
In Agreement]
[Female Speaker]
Now, they send our men off to Vietnam...
to fight for this
so-called democracy.
- Right, right.
- That's right. Yeah!
But when they get back down
to the South Bronx,
and to Bed-Stuy and Harlem
and Watts, etc., etc.,
shit is worse than ever.
[Audience Shouting
In Agreement]
- There is something...
very sick about that.
- He's a devil.
That's right,
he's the devil.
[Shouts Of Affirmation]
- Power to the people!
- In 'n' out.
- ? I'm never gonna give you up?
? I'm never, ever
gonna stop?
? Not the way
I feel about you?
- ? Girl, I just can't live without you?
- There you go.
? I'm never, ever
gonna quit??
So like I was sayin',
I ran into this brother,
and he, uh, gave me
this flyer.
I figured I'd go over
and check it out.
And there you were, up there talkin'
that ol' righteous shit.
I'm just a college student tryin' to do
her part to rally the people together.
But, dig, we need more
than talk. It's time to do.
- Do what?
- Revolution.
Oh, wait a minute. See.
Y'all a little outta my league now.
Is that what you're gonna say
when the revolution comes?
When it's time
to pick up a gun?
[Snickers]
What you know about weapons?
I'm qualified
to handle a.45,
an M-16 rifle,
a.38-calibre pistol...
and a Russian AK-47.
An AK-47?
[Chuckles]
[Sighs]
Why don't you join us?
A lot of brothers
from the war have.
Baby, I got enough
heavy shit to deal with.
- [Waitress] I got you, brother.
- Relax.
[Sighs]
You're so uptight.
Damn, I got to make
some fuckin' bread.
I'm through
with your sister, but...
I still got to take care
of my baby girl, Sarah.
[Chuckles]
Shit, and the one that's on the way.
Damn!
Look, anyway, uh, I got
this plan to make some money.
I want you to keep
this shit to yourself.
[Anthony] At 6:15 a.m., the truck
pulls outta the post office...
at 149th and Grand Concourse.
Now, it makes one stop
before it goes to D.C.,
which is a mail drop-off
at First Federal Loan and Savings,
which is on Noble Street
and West.
Now, Kirby,
you're gonna position yourself
in a getaway car...
at the end of the corner,
where you can see everything.
Jose. Me and you are gonna position
ourselves behind the bank,
underneath the left and the right side
of the loadin' dock.
[Sighs] Delilah, you're gonna
position yourself inside the Dumpster,
which is located directly across
from the loadin' dock.
Now, Skippy, I want you
to position yourself...
approximately ten feet
from the alleyway.
There, you post
a lookout.
[Anthony Exhales] We all know
what to do at the point of attack...
because we've gone
over that shit enough.
If anybody gets caught, you shut the
fuck up, and we'll keep your money.
Shh! Fuck that shit, man.
I'm telling you right now,
if I get caught...
[Spins, Clicks Pistol Chamber
Into Place]
- I'm shooting my fuckin' way out.
- Put that shit down.
I think we need another man
on the street with Skip.
[Kirby]
Someone to cover the other side.
- I agree.
- Oh, man! Hell, no!
We don't need no 'nother man.
Shit, I can see.
- Besides, we got too many
motherfuckers anyway.
- Fuck that shit, Kirby, man.
[Jose] Everybody trusts
everybody here, right?
I can get somebody
from our organization.
Oh, no, no, no, no. I don't want none
of them revolutionary niggers involved.
You can cut your eye at me
all you want to.
I ain't too keen on havin'
that broad up in here neither.
You the one talkin' about we need
another man. Make up your goddam mind.
You have somebody in mind,
Anthony?
We might as well put
a motherfuckin' ad in the paper.
Then we gonna get everybody.
Shit, ain't gonna be
no money left for a nigger.
- ?? [Organ]
- [Congregation Murmuring In Agreement]
Oh, yes! You all didn't know
your reverend was a gamblin' man?
- A sinnin' man?
- [Congregation] No!
I was a man who maimed!
Now see here.
I was a man who killed!
[Congregation Shouting
In Affirmation]
We all know it was done
in the name of the wicked one.
- [Congregation Shouting
In Affirmation]
- The one that was...
cast down from heaven.
- [Man] Hallelujah!
- [Woman] Amen! Yes!
I said... you all know
who I'm talkin' about!
Can I get a "hallelujah"
in this house of God?
[Congregation]
Hallelujah!
Look here, man. Skip is
in. Period. All right?
I stand a lot to lose
if this thing blows up in my face.
The last time I saw him,
he was shooting poison in his veins.
Yeah, I know. Well, you know,
he's tryin' to shake that shit, man.
- He's still on drugs.
- And I still trust him
with my life, Cleon.
Remember that last battle?
He froze up.
For a minute.
Then h-he broke out of it.
And when he "broke out of it,"
Dugan was dead.
Come on, Cleon. You know that could've
happened to any of us.
Now either you in
or you out. Which one?
How much money
did you say was in that truck?
[Grunts]
Shh.
[Panting]
[Wind Whistling]
[Engine Stops]
We still got
about 15 minutes.
I tell ya, I could've
used another cup of coffee.
Let's make this quick.
- [Buzzer]
- [Guard #1] Bank security.
- How ya doin' today?
- Good.
- Mornin'.
- Good mornin'.
[Flips Open, Clicks
Cigarette Lighter]
[Snaps Lighter Closed]
Oh, f...
You waitin' on
the number 11 bus?
Yes.
I don't think
she runs this early.
I caught it the other morning,
uh, at this same time.
You sure about that?
Uh-huh.
- Let me check for you.
- No need to go to any trouble, Officer.
No, no, no.
No trouble at all, brother.
I see by that patch on your jacket
you were in recon.
I was a 5th marine. Always willin'
to help out a fellow leatherneck.
Brown on patrol.
Requesting off-hour route check
on number 11.
Dispatch to Brown.
Hold for schedule.
[Officer Brown]
That's a copy.
Do somethin', Cleon.
- Ambush! Ambush!
- Drop it, motherfucker!
Aaah!
[Groaning]
What the hell?
Shit!
[Truck Engine Cranking]
Joe! Come on.
Let's move.
[Engine Cranking, Starting]
Oh, goddamn it!
[Panting]
Huh?
Fuck! Shit!
Oh, shit!
Anthony!
[Groaning]
[Clicking]
[Laughing]
- Did you see that shit, man?
- What the fuck's wrong with you?
- See the way the fuckin' doors
blew off, man?
- No, motherfucker!
Motherfuckin' Joe, you blew
the whole motherfuckin'
truck up, motherfucker!
- It blew up like that!
- That's how you fucked
your hand up last time!
You... And the money... You fucked up.
I'm gonna kick your motherfuckin' ass!
Grab what you can, motherfucker,
before the whole thing burns!
[Jose] Anthony and Delilah
gotta see this shit, man.
I'm gonna go get 'em!
Hey, Anthony!
[Laughing]
You gotta see the shit I did, man.
I blew that shit up, man!
You gotta see it, man!
You gotta see the shit I did!
[Anthony Talks Softly]
Let's get outta here.
Put the gun down. Put the gun down.
Come on, Delilah. Let's get up.
Up. Let's go.
Come on, bro.
- [Siren Wailing In The Distance]
- We gotta go, man.
I can't...
I can't leave her.
[Jose]
You ain't gotta leave her, bro,
'cause she's already gone.
- [Woman Screaming]
- Get up here! Go on!
[Tyres Screeching]
[Police Dispatcher,
Transmission Indistinct]
[Engine Revving]
- [Dispatcher] Unit 1004, do you copy?
- [Groaning]
Please respond.
Do you require assistance?
Do you copy?
[Dispatcher] Any available units
in the vicinity of Noble Street.
Two-eleven in progress.
Code three. Repeat.
Code three.
[Siren Wailing
In The Distance]
God's not gonna
forgive me for this one.
I'll tell you what, Reverend.
With this kind of money,
you can buy your way into heaven.
That's where you're wrong, brother.
We done bought our way into hell.
The plain fact is that I promised
the Lord I would never sin like this.
To tell you the truth, I'm not sure
I even want any of this dirty money.
Well, I'll tell you what,
Reverend.
We'll find somethin'
to do with your share.
- Amen to that shit.
- [Cleon] No. No, no, no, no.
- I'll take the money.
- You lyin' sack o' shit.
I'm sure the Lord will find
another way for me to do my penance.
Just tell me
one thing, Cleon.
Why the fuck
you didn't grab the cop?
You killed him.
A young brother.
You wouldn't have froze up
like a bitch, maybe I wouldn't
have had to do that shit.
Would you all
shut the fuck up?
Man, Delilah. Shit.
Radio said they got
Joe's stupid ass.
[Anthony]
Fucked it up.
The whole plan was fucked up.
We ain't do shit right
out there, man. Shit.
Y'all make sure that Jose's share
goes to Marisol and his kids.
Done.
Your junkie ass really
messed up out there.
Don't blame me
for your fuck-ups.
I told Anthony I didn't want nothin' to
do with a crazy, devil-filled junkie!
- What?
- You listenin' to me? Look at him.
- Oh, shit!
- Now say some more shit!
I'll knock your ass
right back down.
Fake-ass wanna-be preacher,
no-members-havin' motherfucker!
Why don't you all stop actin'
like some fuckin' clowns?
You know, you niggers
sure is silly.
Now, you're standin' here
fightin',
and we got over $300,000 of
cold, hard, unmarked U.S. cash
to split up five ways.
Let me tell ya somethin'.
You make me lose count again,
I'm gonna shoot me a motherfucker.
Then we gonna be splittin'
this thing up four ways, hear?
Man, I can't believe this.
They was gonna burn all this shit.
All this shit, and a nigger
can't even find a job.
Well, that's Uncle Sam
for you, baby.
[Sniffing]
Money to burn.
[Radio Announcer]
Police have issued an all-points
bulletin for the remaining...
...Reserve Bank
on Noble Street.
Faces painted skeleton white.
[Anthony Hears Chopper Pilot]
Cobra, request your status. Over.
- [Radio Announcer]
Five federal security guards...
- [Delilah] Anthony!
- [Jose] She's already gone.
- [D'Ambrosio] Do it.
[Radio Announcer]
The bloody shootout erupted...
an armoured truck... explosives...
[Skip] No, motherfuckin' Joe.
You blew the whole motherfuckin'
truck up, motherfucker!
[Radio Announcer]
...the deaths of nine people.
[Skip Thinking]
Heroin ain't never did nothin' to me.
[Announcer]... killed moments
away from the scene of the
crime... Robbery turned bloody...
[Skip Thinking] Had some shit done
to me over there, man.
[Announcer]
...crushed to death by...
? Rudolph
the red-nosed reindeer?
- ? Had a very shiny nose?
- [Children Shouting]
- ? And if you ever saw it?
- [Skip] What you slowin' down for?
- [Anthony] Be cool. Be cool.
- [Skip] What you doin'?
- Come on. Come on.
- What the fuck, man? Aw, shit!
- ? All of the other reindeer?
- What the fuck we doin' over here?
[Anthony]
Say, man, check out all these kids.
Man, let's go to the liquor store
and go to the club.
Look, man, I'm gonna take care of you.
We're gonna go down to the club.
- We don't know them motherfuckers!
- That's the whole point.
Come on. Get in the spirit.
Hey, y'all come on over here!
- We gonna get robbed.
- Be cool, nigger.
Y'all come on over here.
[Anthony]
Be cool, man. Damn.
- ? Rudolph, with your nose so bright?
- [Children Shouting]
[Anthony]
Y'all gonna get some. All right.
- Merry Christmas!
- What, motherfu...
Yeah, man. Merry Christmas,
motherfucker. Go on. Leave me alone.
Say, Skippy.
Hey, man, why don't you bring your ass
over here and quit that jivin'.
Come on. Yeah, yeah.
Y'all take all the toys. All right.
Get one.
See what I'm sayin'?
- I'm not kiddin'. We givin' it away.
- All right. Yeah.
Santa Claus don't wanna come
'round here 'cause he's scared
he's gonna get shot or robbed.
Just one. Hey, give me this, man.
Get a... Get a toy.
- [Children Shouting]
- Come on, come on, come on.
Why you stealin'?
You ain't gotta steal.
Santa's never gonna come 'round
here unless he's got police protection.
Last year, one of y'all niggers stole
one of his reindeer.
Oh, no. I say let's just go up there
and kill that motherfucker.
Man, me and Anthony gave out
a couple of things, but that was it.
You gave toys and turkeys to people.
Then you got the hell outta Dodge.
Y'all sayin' my man is goin' around
handin' out $100 bills...
and sayin' that
God Almighty gave it to him?
My cousin lives up there
in Mount Vernon.
He says Cleon's up there actin'
the goddam fool.
That ol' high-profile ass
nigger.
Bought a brand-new Caddy.
Folk know he can't afford it.
- I'm gonna go over there
and talk to him.
- No, no, no. Fuck the talk!
I'm drivin' up there, and I'm gonna
take him out before he rats us out.
Look, Kirby. I'll handle everything,
all right?
- I'll straighten this shit out.
- All right.
But if you don't take care of this,
Anthony, I promise you, I will.
I told you we didn't
need another man.
That's y'all's motherfuckin'
punk-ass friend!
? People runnin'
from their worries?
? While the judge
and his juries?
? They take the law
that's part of the flaw?
[Anthony]
No. Oh, shit, Cleon!
Damn!
? The feelin' now
is killin'?
? For peace no one
is willin'?
? And to make it
get that feelin'?
[No Audible Dialogue]
? Everybody's startin'?
? Use the pill and the dope?
? Educated fools?
? From an educated school??
Right now we'd like to bring on
a young man who believes in
doing things his own way.
Based on the way he kinda get next to
all of the folks who've seen him work,
his way has gotta be
pretty hip.
So let's lay some noise
on the mighty Al Green.
[Audience Applauds]
Apartment 13!
? I'm so tired
of bein' alone?
? I'm so tied up
on my own?
? Won't you help me, girl?
? Just as soon as you can?
Don't move, mister!
? I been wantin' to get
next to you, baby?
? You see, sometime
I fold my arms, I say?
[Backup Singers]
? Ooo-ooo?
? Whoa-oh-oh?
? Oh, baby, hey?
? Needing you
has proven to me?
? To be my greatest dream
Yeah?
? Oh, I'm so tired, baby??
- Here's the rest of the fifties.
- Put it in there.
You know, I still feel fucked-up about
this whole situation.
Look, feelin' fucked-up
don't help a goddam thing,
and it ain't gonna
bring nobody back.
- Shit!
- Just worry about yourself.
We gotta get outta here.
- Come on.
- Say, man, you got everything?
Yeah, grab that bag.
This is a bitch.
This is it, man.
This is it.
All we got to do, boy,
is make it to Mexico.
We'll be fine.
We'll get us a villa, see?
And buy a boat and sail
all around the gulf.
Everything will be fine.
We just gotta get the fuck outta here.
Yeah, maybe I can send
for Sarah once we get down there.
Well, anything's possible.
Come on.
Wait a minute.
Run, Anthony! Hyah!
Y'all get back! Get away
right there! Get off me!
Shit!
- ? You pity fool?
- Fuck!
? You better have
some sympathy?
? 'Cause there's
educated people?
? Runnin' the lives
of our society?
? Makin' up the rules??
Mr Curtis,
you have been lawfully tried in this
court and found guilty on all charges.
Do you have anything to say on your own
behalf before I pronounce sentence?
Uh,
no, ain't nothin' I say
gonna get me out of this.
But things were
gettin' bad for me, and...
I had to do what I had to do
to s... to survive.
Maybe it was wrong, but l... I certainly
didn't mean for anybody to be hurt.
Uh, Your Honour, please consider
before sentencing...
that my client served his country proud
in the Marine Corps.
As a matter of fact, he was
a member of an elite unit,
a sergeant, decorated
with many medals.
In fact, one of those medals was the,
uh, Silver Star, for valour.
I realize that my client had
a difficult time adjusting when he...
Excuse me, counsel.
l, too, was a marine,
and I served my country proudly
in World War Il, a real war, I may add.
- Yes, Your Hon...
- I'm not finished yet, please.
I received the Purple Heart
at Guadalcanal.
Now this young man
has obviously forgotten...
some very fundamental things
like decency and dedication and honour...
everything the corps
taught us.
He is a disgrace to everyone
that has ever put on that uniform,
and I will not permit you or him to use
the Vietnam War as a cop-out here.
Anthony Curtis, for your
participation in this crime,
a crime that took the lives
of several innocent people,
I do hereby sentence you
to the custody of the Attorney
General of the United States...
for a period
of 15 years to life.
Oh, my God.
These proceedings are concluded.
- This court is adjourned.
- "Life"?
What the fuck he mean, "life"?
After all the shit I did
for this motherfuckin' country?
What the fuck he talkin' about, "life"?
Man, fuck you! Fuck you!
- Hey!
- Oh, Anthony!
After all the shit I did for this
motherfuckin' country?
R-Remove the prisoner
from the courtroom. You hear me?
- Fuck you! Fuck you!
- Get him out of here!
- [Anthony Yelling]
- Let the record show...
Let the record show that a chair
was thrown at the judge.
? Whoa, whoa?
? If you see me
walkin' down the street?
? And I start to cry?
? Each time we meet?
? Then walk on by?
? Walk on by?
? Make believe?
? That you don't see
the tears?
? You just let me grieve
in private?
? 'Cause each time
I see you?
? I break, I break?
? I break down and cry?
? Oh, baby?
? Walk on by?
? Hmm-mmm-mmm?
? I just can't get over
losing you?
? So if I seem?
? Broken in two?
? Please walk on by?
? Walk on by?
? Foolish pride?
? Is all that I have left?
? So let me hide?
? The tears and the sadness
you gave me?
? You put the hurt on me?
? You socked it to me, mama?
? When you said goodbye?
? So, please, walk on by?
? Make believe you never see
the tears I cry?
? So do me a favour?
? And walk on by?
? So I'm beggin' you to?
? Walk on by?
? Oh, yeah?
? And make believe you never see
the tears I cry?
? So I'm beggin' you
I'm beggin' you?
? To walk on by?
? Make believe you never see
the tears I cry?
? Oh?
? There's no dust in my eye?
? Oh, no?
? Smoke ain't makin' me cry?
? No, no, no?
? It's the hurt
you put on me, yeah?
? I don't want you
to see this man cry??
? Where is the love?
? Ooh, yeah, yeah?
? You said you'd give to me?
? Soon as you were free?
? Will it ever be?
? Where is the love?
? You told me that you
didn't love him?
? And you were gonna
say goodbye?
? But if you really
didn't mean it?
? Why did you have to lie?
? Where is the love?
? You said was mine
all mine?
? Till the end of time?
? Was it just a lie?
? Where is the love?
? If you have had a sudden
change of heart?
? I wish that you
would tell me so?
? Don't leave me hangin'
on these promises?
? You gotta let me know?
? Oh-ohh?
? Do-do do-do?
? Do-do do-do-do??