Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Man, what's takin' you so long?
It's cold as a motherfucker out here.
I had to get the last stop.
Quiet, punk.
- I'll shut your hairy ass up, man.
- Come on, man. I'm freezin' my fuckin' nuts out here!
Mush, motherfucker, mush!
Ant, Juanita gave you
some of that pussy yet?
- Man, get out of here, man.
- What?
Man, I thought we was homies, man.
I'm just askin'.
Well, why you gotta be
askin' me all that? I mean...
I'm just lookin' out for you.
All I'm sayin', man, fine as she is,
she should be giving you something.
I bet you ain't even
smelled the pussy, eh?
You two realize that soon
we're gonna be out of school, right?
- Oh, sure.
- After four long years of that shit, man.
I can't fuckin' wait to get out. That's
all I've been thinkin' about, man.
You know? I just be thinkin' about like
what am I gonna do afterwards, right?
You know, I can dig some travelling.
Nigger, you sound like
you rich or somethin'.
Hear this nigger?
He ain't even got a fuckin' job.
- I know.
- Man, you better take your ass off to college, man, I'm tellin' you...
before Uncle Sam grab your ass like
he gonna do this stupid motherfucker.
Oh, bullshit, Skip, man.
Ain't nobody gonna grab me.
Jose, a recruiter
can see your dumb ass a mile away.
Look at you.
You're a recruiter's dream. You a 1-A.
A one-way ticket to motherfuckin'
Vietnam if I ever saw one.
That's why I'm goin' to Hunter College.
You goddam right.
I ain't fightin'
no white man's war. Shit.
Them Vietcongs, chongs, whatever
the fuck, ain't done shit to me.
I don't even know
them motherfuckers, man.
And I ain't afraid of no war.
Man, what the fuck you been smokin'?
Look, y'all might think
I'm crazy, but...
I just wanna do somethin'
that's different.
Yeah, well, gettin' your
fuckin' head blown off is different.
Hey, man, turn that shit down!
And slow this motherfucker down!
- Ain't nobody in a hurry to go to school.
- Man, leave that shit up.
You know I fucked Monica, right? Her
mama came in, caught us the other day.
Came in, seen my dick,
jumped in the bed too.
- Later on, you chump suckers.
- Ah, fuck you.
- Your mama!
- Punk ass, jivin' around.
- Hey, this is for you, Anthony, right here.
- Close this motherfuckin' door.
It's cold as hell out here.
Sit your nasty ass down.
Oh, hey. How you doin'?
You up kinda early.
Um, I heard your truck.
Seems like you hear my truck
every mornin'.
Well, uh, morning
is the best time to study, so...
You should, uh, try workin'
on your first boyfriend.
I'm too busy studyin'
to be worryin' about boys.
Your sister up?
Uh, Sleeping Beauty?
Yeah.
Look, uh, tell her I said hey.
See ya.
- Good morning, Anthony.
- Oh, hey.
- I thought you were sleeping.
- You woke me up.
- Uh, so you goin' to school today?
- Mmm.
I could lay in bed all mornin'.
Oh. See, now...
Now that'd be real nice.
- Don't even think about it.
- Well, look, uh...
I'm gonna get on out of here.
I'll talk to you later.
- Okay.
- See ya.
Keep on pushin'
- I'll be down there later on.
- Got to keep on pushin'
I can't stop now
Hard shoe.
Come here, hard shoe.
Come here, man.
What's up? What's up?
Listen, I want you...
I want you to tell Kirby I want 645.
- Straight, now. Listen. And, uh...
- Straight.
- We've been rollin' here.
- Come on, man. I ain't got time.
- Let me get the money.
- I want you to be back here tonight...
- Man, straighten your hat out.
- With my money, you little motherfucker.
- What's goin' on, baby? - All right,
baby. - All right, cat daddy. All right.
- Hey, Anthony. How you doin'?
- Hey.
You know, you brought me luck the other
day. So look, ten of that's for you.
- See? Now, that's how it goes.
- Hey, now.
- L-I'm gonna use the same number too.
- Don't forget me, man.
What's goin' on?
Hey, what's goin' on?
Hey there, Jellybean.
What's goin' on?
Hey, what's goin' on?
How you been?
Kirby back there?
All right. Cool.
- Go on, get that shot. Get that shot.
- All right, thanks, youngblood.
Hey there, Peanut! What's goin' on?
What's up there? What...
Blood.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Kirby's back there in the back, man.
Put that in Brooklyn
and get ahold of that fuckin' Spyder.
- Okay, man.
- Hey, brother.
- Aw, man, take them.
- Yeah, yeah.
Here's the numbers and the cash.
- We got five.
- Hubba hubba!
Ain't you supposed to be
duck huntin' with your daddy?
Oh, yeah.
We gonna go next weekend.
- Aw, shit!
- Oh, man, Kirby.
Made me miss my shot.
You know these motherfuckers down South.
I wonder if half the time
they believe what they be sayin'.
What's a nigger gonna do?
We got blood in this land
from slaves.
Been to war. Spilt our blood.
Shit, I been to war. I spilt blood.
Ha! That's right.
Tell 'em, Kirby.
You over there fightin' in Korea.
That's how I got this plastic-ass leg.
Nicky, fix me a drink.
Ko-motherfuckin'- rea.
Damn! Mmm!
Never gonna give you up
That's why I had to leave that
motherfucker, because if I'd have...
If I'd have still been down there,
I'd have killed me a motherfucker.
Man, shit ain't gonna change.
What make you think shit gonna change?
Nigger, what's your little
narrow ass doin' up in here, man?
Leave that boy alone
and let him shoot.
Aw, Kirby, man, you know he too
goddam young to be up in here, man.
He can outshoot you.
Oh, shit.
Oh, I know you out
your motherfuckin' mind, man.
Put your money
where your mouth is.
I take your money.
Rack 'em, boy.
- Uh, huh, huh, huh
- Watch this.
I got the feelin'
Baby, baby, I got the feelin'
- Yes!
- You don't know
You got my two dollars?
Game ain't over yet, man.
Got the eight ball,
corner pocket.
Oh, man!
Don't run out of here without payin' me
after that boy whup you.
Yeah, at least I will
run out of this, motherfucker.
People that owe me money don't pay me,
I take care of 'em.
Man, will you get the fuck off
my motherfuckin' table, please?
- Baby-baby-baby, baby-baby-baby
- Chicken-haired motherfucker.
Ain't no goddam business
bein' here in the first place.
Ooh, missed it by that much.
- Cleanup time.
- You don't never play with me.
Eight ball, corner pocket.
Oh! Yes! Game.
Hey, that's a good game, Cowboy.
You're a lucky motherfucker,
you know that?
Aw, I wouldn't say luck,
but, you know.
- Just know how to play a little bit.
- Here's the money.
- Give that to Kirby.
- All right.
Uh, wait, wait.
This is two dollars.
See, uh, you bet me, so that means,
uh, you owe me some money too.
Man, fuck you.
Why you gotta cheat?
Man, who the fuck you think
you talkin' to, man?
You know what? I'm gonna tell
everybody around here...
when it comes to playin' pool,
Cowboy likes to cheat.
Nigger, I'll kick
your little monkey ass, man.
Oh, man.
Shut your motherfuckin' mouth, man.
I oughta cut you.
Little motherfucker. Yeah.
It hurt, don't it?
What the fuck?
What the fuck are you doin'?
Get the fuck off of me, man!
Kirby, what the fuck you doin', man?
- What the fuck are you doin'?
- What the fuck are you doin', man?
- Get on out of here!
- You a bad motherfucker!
- And don't you come back in here unless you come correct.
- Fuck you!
- You all right, kid?
- Oh, yeah.
Just a little cut, you know.
It's all right.
Yep. You do a real good job
for me with them numbers.
Well, you know, I try.
But, uh, you better be cool.
Don't let your mom and pop find out.
Oh, no way.
I won't do that.
It's for you.
Oh, man. Whoa!
- Hey, thanks, Kirby.
- Ain't nothin' to thank me for.
- You earned it.
- Oh. Twenties.
Hey, kid, you wanna take
a little run with me?
Yeah, I'll take
a little run with you.
Say, uh, Kirby, where we goin'?
Like I told you,
just a little run.
A run. Okay. All right.
- Wanna drive, kid?
- Who, me?
No, not "me. "
You, motherfucker.
Well, Kirby,
I don't have my licence yet.
Aw, shit. Fuck the dumb shit.
You wanna drive or what?
Yeah. All right, I'll drive.
Yeah.
- Pull over here.
- All right.
Come on. Come on.
What you call her, Nellie?
Come on, Nellie.
I call this bitch
whatever I wanna call her.
Listen here.
Keep that motor runnin'.
- I'll just be a minute here.
- Yeah, all right.
- Stop messin' with my gold! - Wait a
minute! - How many times I gotta tell you?
I ain't no motherfuckin'
play toy! I'll kick your ass!
- Get the fuck up!
- You get the fuck up off of Spyder!
No.
You got more heart than
your punk-ass old man. Come here.
- Oh, man, Kirby!
- Oh, what the...
Give me my fuckin' leg,
you stupid son-of-a-bitch!
You grabbed the wrong leg,
you stupid cocksucker. Come here!
- Get on back in here now, Spyder.
- You asshole!
- I want my motherfuckin' money, hear?
- Easy, Kirby.
- Now! - Easy, man!
- Dumb son-of-a...
Give me my fuckin' leg,
you stupid cocksucker.
- I'll fuck you up.
- Get on back down there.
- They gonna call the police.
- I got 15 miles to go now
- Come on. Come on!
- And I can hear my baby callin' my name
Floor this motherfucker.
Floor it.
Now I'll be so glad
to see my baby
And hold her in my arms
one more time
Now when I kiss her lips
- I'll turn a backward flip
- You did good, kid.
You're almost as good
a getaway driver as me.
Uh, thanks. Say, uh...
So you were a getaway driver, huh?
- Son-of-a-bitch!
- What? Wh-What's wrong?
- I oughta go back there and kill that bastard.
- Why? What happened?
Motherfucker made me lose
a whole pack of cigarettes.
A pack of cigarettes?
I thought maybe you should be
worried about your leg or somethin'.
- Oh, that shit's funny to you, huh?
- No, no, it's not funny.
I tell you what. The next time
the motherfucker grabs me by...
the wrong leg, I'm gonna use it to kick
his ass between his shoulder blades.
- Hey, man, you really did that sucker.
- Yeah, everybody in town...
know I got one leg, and that
motherfucker grab the wrong one.
Me and Kirby, baby. Yeah.
- This is wonderful news, Edward.
- Thank you.
All right, all right.
You see, Anthony?
You be thankful you can go to City
College on the financial aid programme.
Yeah, in four years,
you can be just like me.
Just like you?
You can graduate and maybe even
go to graduate school too.
Well, I'll tell y'all one thing.
My mama sure would've been proud.
Never would've believed
I got two college graduates.
You think about what
you're gonna major in, baby?
The Marine Corps.
Uh, Dad, could you pass the salt?
What'd you say?
Thanks. I said
the, uh, Marine Corps.
- I'm... I'm joinin'.
- Marine Corps?
- Yeah.
- Now that's original.
What you talkin' about, Anthony?
I'm talkin' about
I wanna do somethin' else.
I don't wanna go to college.
I'm sick of school.
I mean, I don't know why everybody
got this strange look on their face.
- It's my life.
- Yeah.
It's your life.
Looks like to me
you're tryin' to ruin it, baby.
You're an idiot.
You know that?
Dad, I don't wanna go to college.
I'm just not ready for no college.
You always said the marines and fightin'
over in Korea made a man out of you.
I figure I be, you know,
livin' my own life.
I'll talk to your mama.
When your baby and you are tight
and everything is right
- And you is mellow
- Give me that.
There you go.
Now, drink some wine.
You keep everything all right
And you know that
you're the only fellow
Ain't that a groove
Told your little ass
you couldn't drink with me.
- Ain't that a groove
- Hey, James. Want some of this?
- Now, lookee here, fella
- Yeah! Whoo!
Girls like to be in the mood
whenever they think their man is yellow
- Whoo! Yeah!
- Hit me, baby
Say, Skeeter, I still can't
believe you graduated, man.
- Man, shut up.
- Glad we out of school, man.
I'm sick of these
stupid-ass brothers.
I'm about to get
my pimp thing on started.
You know, I got so many ho's now, man,
I gotta get an assistant pimp...
just to keep in track of 'em, you know,
make sure they on the right streets and shit.
Say, Skippy, why... why you always talkin'
about this pimp stuff, man? What's happenin'?
'Cause it's real, man. I'm a pimp.
Pimpin' run in my family.
My great-great granddaddy was a slave,
and he was a pimp.
He used to have his ho's pick his cotton
in the field. He didn't have to do shit.
You better be careful, man. You're
gonna catch something, Skip. Watch.
That's all right, motherfucker. I was
born by the pussy, I'll die by the pussy.
Don't worry about
what the fuck I do.
Hey, Skip, do you
believe in superstition?
Hell, no.
Well, you should, man.
Your stupid ass jinxed me.
- What the fuck you talkin' about?
- Uncle Sam, man.
Dropped a motherfuckin' 1-A on me.
I told you, didn't I?
Didn't I tell you?
- Say, when did that happen?
- Last week, Anthony, man.
Yeah, right, motherfucker.
Pass the joint.
- Anthony, man.
- What?
You know that, um,
that me and Marisol, we tight, man.
Yeah, man, y'all are...
Y'all pretty down.
- You would say I love her?
- I don't know.
I could say that you love her.
- I'm thinkin' about marrying her, man.
- Oh, wait a minute.
- Hey, don't do that shit.
- Hey, man, you might be goin' a little too fast now.
Hey, I love her, man, and did you see
how she looks today at that party, man?
- She looks good enough to marry.
- I'm glad to hear you want me.
What you over here
talkin' about, Anthony?
- Why you standin' over here?
- Shut up, Skippy. - Shut up.
Anthony, I know you ain't gonna stay over
here talkin' to Skip while my song's playin'.
Not if they expect to be
with us tonight.
- Look here, Skippy, we gonna have to cut on out, bro.
- Uh, yeah.
- Man, where y'all goin'?
- Uh, we gonna go hang on out.
- Look it, have some chicken. - I thought we
was hangin', man. - Have some chicken, man.
I told you about them broads,
old punk-ass.
And anyway, Skip,
Brenda lookin' for you.
I don't give a fuck. You tell her I'm
at where I at and I'll be where I be.
Motherfuckin' pimp. If I gotta go where
every ho want me to be, I be confused.
Motherfucker. Tell her
don't make me hurt my hand again.
If you want a do-right all day
Woman
You gotta be a do-right
All night
Jose, I love you.
I love you too, mama.
If you give my pussy away
to somebody else...
while I'm gone...
I'm gonna come back
and blow that motherfucker up.
I got this itch
I need to be scratched.
S- S-S-So... So you're sayin'
that y-your, your mama...
is workin' a night shift tonight?
Mm-hmm.
And you know what else?
You could scratch it
all night long if you want to.
You know I'm the nigger. I'm the nigger.
You swear Big Bertha
won't get off work early?
She's not gonna get off
from work early.
- You scared?
- No, I ain't scared. I just don't...
You act like you're scared.
Come on. Shut up.
- Where Delilah at?
- She in her room. Come on!
- Say it loud
- I'm black and I'm proud
- Get out.
- Say it loud
- I'm black and I'm proud
- Go to your own room.
- Say it loud
- I'm black and I'm proud
Once upon a time
I almost lost my mind
I was lonely
So lonely
Once upon a time
Oh, Juanita.
Look, it's okay.
It's all right.
It's okay.
- Okay. Okay.
- Let me get your bra.
- Okay.
- Let me get it.
- Ow. Just unhook it. Just unhook the...
- I can't. I can't.
I'll get it.
I'll do it. I'll do it.
- Okay. Okay.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't peek. Don't look at...
Don't look at me. Okay.
Okay. Okay.
- Oh!
- What?
That's not it.
Up, up, up, up. Higher. Ow.
- That's too high. Wait. Down, down.
- Okay, wait.
- Right there? Okay.
- Yeah.
- Okay. Okay.
- All right.
- It's okay.
- Uh-oh. Wait.
Okay. Easy. Ow!
Ah!
Oh, shit. Wait, wait, wait.
- Oh, shit.
- Okay.
- Baby.
You know, Marisol and Jose
goin' down to city hall tomorrow.
Oh, yeah? What for?
To get married.
- Is that right?
- What you think about that?
Nothin', I guess.
So I guess you don't want me
to wait for you either.
Look, Juanita,
I didn't say that.
So then you're gonna marry me
when you get back?
I mean, if you
ain't got somebody else.
I don't want nobody else.
Juanita, have you
ever thought maybe...
maybe I might get hurt out there
and never come back?
You know, I don't want
you waitin' for nothin'.
You're not scared of losing me?
I didn't say that either.
I'm scared of losing you.
So, do you think we could probably
do it one more time before I go?
Uh-huh.
Oh, no.
- It's Ma!
- Shh! But it's just 6:30!
- She just pulled up.
- Well, go stall her. And close my door!
- Shoot! Shoot! Shoot!
- Oh, man.
I shouldn't have never messed around
with you in the first place.
- Right. - You know Bertha
gonna kill us. - Wait a minute.
- Uh-uh. Ain't gonna wait no minute.
Would you move? - Wait a minute!
Come on. Let me help you
with them packages.
- Delilah!
- I got it.
Girl, you got my good groceries
all on the ground.
Pick those up.
Since I work, the least you girls
could do is keep this place clean.
You know I'm gonna
wait for you, Anthony.
Juanita, I gotta go.
I gotta go, Juanita.
- Nigger, get out of my yard!
- Fuck you!
Shut up!
What's your status? Over.
Shit.
Head for the rally point!
Get back to the rally point!
Get the fuck outta here!
Let's go! Pick it up!
Pick it up! Come on! Come on!
Come on! Move!
Move! Let's go!
Load 'em up! Load 'em up!
Oh, fuck!
I'm out of ammo!
- Devaughn! Cover me!
- Stay down!
I got him! Hurry up!
Don't check out on us, Martin. You're gonna
be all right. You're gonna be all right.
- I got him!
- Cover fire!
Goddam it! They got us pinned down!
We'll never make the rally point!
Dugan!
You think it's time we get these
fucking dinks off our asses? Huh?
- Relax.
- Fuck you!
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you!
Radio, up!
God don't like dinks.
- How's he doin', Curtis?
- Thanks. Thanks for not leavin' me, man.
- Where the fuck is that radio? Get that radio up here!
- No, no, no, no, no.
Radio comin'! Radio comin'!
Get that cover fire, Ferguson.
You wanna die, boy?
Sir, sir! Lieutenant!
Arty freak!
Hammerhead, Hammerhead. Recon Cobra.
Emergency fire mission. Over.
Hold on, brother. Come on.
Come on, come on.
You gonna make it, dude.
You only got a little longer.
- You gonna make it.
- Grid five, seven, one-niner.
- Tell my mama...
- No, no, I don't...
Gooks in the bush.
Request firecracker salvo. Will adjust.
How copy? Over.
Roger. Solid copy.
Firecracker shot out.
Incoming!
Down! Down! Down!
Curtis, get down!
Out-fucking-standing job.
Saddle up. Let's get to the rally point,
take that whirlybird home.
- We got some beer to drink.
- We goin' to the rally point now?
The mission's been compromised.
We're goin' to site 37.
It ain't compromised no more.
They're dead.
Now this is Sneaky Pete.
Reconnaissance.
Some of them dead gooks...
they could have important
intelligence papers on their bodies.
All right.
- Move 'em out.
- Move out!
Hammerhead, Hammerhead.
Cobra on site of your mission now.
I count ten... say again, ten...
November-Victor-Alpha-Kilo-India-Alpha.
- How copy? Over.
- I copy, one-zero. Good job.
Hammerhead, Cobra. Solid copy.
Good job. Cobra out.
Aw, shit, man! What you doin'?
He already dead.
Motherfucker.
Looks like we nailed us
an officer.
You lucky bastard. You get back to C.P.,
you name your own price, sir.
No way, D'Ambrosio.
I'm keepin' this one.
Been lookin' for one of these
since Cleon and I got here in '66.
Ain't that right, Cleon?
I walked right by that guy.
You gotta keep your eyes open.
Oh, man, what the fuck?
You hungry or somethin', Cleon?
Just like you, sir.
I'm collectin' me a souvenir.
Saddle up. We're movin' out.
That's all he's gonna say? You ain't got
nothin' to tell this fuckin' shit, man?
- Man, that nigger Cleon crazy.
- Yeah.
- Did you see that shit?
- I saw it.
- Nigger, did you see that shit?
- Yes.
I heard that nigger's supposed
to be a preacher's son and shit.
He cuttin' off motherfucker's
heads for souvenirs and shit.
Now, if you hadn't flunked out
of Hunter College, pimp daddy Skippy...
you would've missed all this
good shit down in Vietnam.
Kiss my ass, nigger. You the reason
why I'm at this motherfucker anyway.
You didn't tell me 'bout
this recon shit.
- That's 'cause you didn't ask me when you were writin' me.
- Nigger, I didn't have to.
- Shit, I figured it was better than being a grunt.
- It is.
Ant, motherfucker,
we out in the woods all day.
Them motherfuckin' gooks jumpin' out
like Indians every five minutes.
- Man, a nigger ain't made for this shit.
- You thought this was a skate.
Nigger, ain't nothin'
wrong with no skate.
You could just call me
a skatin' motherfucker.
I skate my ass right out of here,
they give me a chance to.
- Ain't no shitbirds on my squad.
- Man, what you jivin' about?
Hey. Hey.
Ant. To the Bronx.
Yeah, uh...
to the youngblood
who couldn't be with us today.
- Lance Corporal Martin.
- To Lance Corporal Martin.
- Yes.
- Yo, Ant, man.
What they be puttin'
in your head out here, man?
I mean, you done got into this shit
a little bit too deep, don't you think?
You're in recon now, Skip.
You in deep too.
Man, fuck this shit, man.
- Oh, come on, man.
- Man, this ain't our war, man.
Shit, our black ass should be
back in the Bronx where we belong.
Joe-ass got lucky. They sent him
home, gettin' wounded and shit.
Heard he wounded his hand
pretty bad, man.
Shit, that's all right, though.
He got out of this shit.
I rather be home with a fucked-up hand
up in some pussy than to be out here...
healthier than
a motherfucker without it.
- Shit.
- Same old Skip. Boy, you ain't changed.
That's right.
You heard from Juanita?
She used to write me a lot
during my first tour.
We got a package for ya!
Turns out, man, before I left,
fucked around and got her pregnant.
- Man, you bullshittin'.
- No, I ain't.
- No shit?
- Dead serious, man. Got a little girl back at home.
Oh, man, that's groovy, man. That's
groovy. I can dig it. That's cool.
Hey, dig, man, I know
you got a picture, man.
- Let me see her picture. Shit.
- Can't even look at her, man.
Man, what the fuck
you mean, bro?
That's your little girl, man.
That's your baby.
You know how I survived
26 months in the bush?
Because I don't think about the world,
Skip. That shit don't exist to me.
I don't give a fuck about anything
or anyone in it...
because the minute I do, I'm a dead man
out here, and you remember that shit.
We'll talk about the world
when we get back.
Yeah, whatever, man.
I'm gonna go get high.
I mean real high. And I'm gonna
get my dick sucked too.
Big dick. Big.
Very, very big.
Can you handle it?
"Hey there, Kirby.
What's happenin' back in the world?
If you hadn't heard,
doin' my second tour. "
- Fire in the hole!
"We spend most of our time
livin' in the bush.
Kind of numb to
everything out here.
Tryin' to keep
my head clear.
Our lieutenant is this crazy
white boy named Dugan from Ohio.
He's good at gettin' us
out of crazy situations.
We got this one wild-ass
brother out here named Cleon. "
Gook fuck.
"His daddy's this big-time preacher, but
you'd never know from his crazy son. "
Now you're good.
Now Jesus loves you.
"He's from Mount Vernon.
Oh, yeah. You won't believe it...
but Skip volunteered
for my unit.
I don't think he's
cut out for recon.
He's always gettin' high and shit,
tryin' to keep his mind off things.
Me, I'm just tryin' to take it one day
at a time and do what's right...
whatever that is.
See you when I get
back to the Bronx.
Anthony. "
That fuckin' shit stinks.
I don't wanna pull rank, Cleon, but if
you don't get rid of that fuckin' head...
I don't hear nobody else
complainin' but you.
Well, maybe you should
listen to your team.
Medical advice, Cleon:
You dump that shit.
Hey, Doc, shut the fuck up.
You don't know shit.
Fuck you, man. It stinks like
a sack full of assholes.
Ain't a one of us got as much
as a splinter in his finger...
since I cut this head off.
This head is our
good-luck charm.
Nah, this here's
our good-luck charm.
If you don't mind, Sergeant, I...
My vote is to get rid of it.
Man, Cleon, you need to get the fuck on
with that bullshit, man.
- That head smell like shit.
- Bottom line, Staff Sergeant.
You either get rid of that fuckin' head
A.S.A. fuckin' P., or I'm gonna...
have your ass court-martialed
when we get back to the rear.
We clear?
Cobra, Cobra, Delta six. Over.
Delta six, Delta six, Cobra.
Copy. Over.
Cobra, Delta six.
Execute Charlie, Michael...
We're in a world of shit now.
I just buried our luck.
Listen up. Change of mission.
A patrol from 25 has found...
a shitload of weapons in a vill
about a klik and a half to our whisky.
Platoon commander wants us
to interrogate on the spot.
Betancourt, you're the closest one in
the area that speaks that gook shit.
So that's where we're headin'.
All right, saddle up. We're movin' out.
- So now where's D'Ambrosio?
- He went to go take a shit.
- When?
- When Cleon was diggin' the hole.
- Why the hell didn't you go with him?
- You know how he is.
- He don't like nobody around when he's shittin'.
- Oh, man.
Grab his shit.
Let's find him.
Aww.
Fuck! Doc.
- 360!
- D'Ambrosio, what'd they do?
You'll be all right.
Doc's gonna take care of you, okay?
This morphine is all
I can do for him right now.
Here, Doc. You can use mine
if that's not enough.
Are you crazy? Another one of those
would kill him right now.
What the fuck
you got there, Curtis?
Somethin' about
"Black men, go home.
This isn't your war. "
You get rid of that cocksucking
commie bullshit right now.
- Yeah. Right.
- Hey, Curtis.
- Apply some pressure here.
- We gotta hump this man back to the rally point.
Oh, shit.
Save me, Curtis.
Look, Adam, you don't
worry 'bout nothin'.
We're a team,
okay, brother?
- We gonna take care of you.
- Please.
Yeah. It's not much longer.
We're almost there.
Kill me.
Kill me!
I would do it
for you.
for you, Curtis.
Buttermilk 17.
Cobra, over.
Cobra, Cobra. Buttermilk 17. Inbound
your buzz. Contact on your visual.
- Shh.
- Buttermilk 17. Cobra.
Hey, you gonna be all right.
The medevac will be here
in a minute.
Do it.
You think
I don't mean it?
I can't go home like this.
- Hey, what's he saying?
- He's delirious, man.
- Please.
- Uh, Cobra, Buttermilk.
- Hooking direct to your 12. Stand by.
- Cobra standing by. Over.
Shh-shh-shh.
Uh, Cobra, Buttermilk 17.
Roger your visual. Pop smoke. Over.
Buttermilk 17, Cobra.
Smoke. Over.
Pop the smoke.
Get that man ready for medevac!
- When'd he go?
- A few minutes ago.
It's better to check out
than go home all fucked up.
No shit.
Oh, shit!
Get down!
Fuckin' assholes!
- Stay down! Stay down!
- I'm gonna get these motherfuckers!
Return fire! Fire!
Get these motherfuckers!
- Skip! Return some fire!
- Shoot them motherfuckers!
Mission aborted! We get the fuck
out of Dodge, back to the rally point!
Ferguson! Get some
fuckin' rounds goin'!
Skip! Cover me!
- Dugan!
- Dugan, wait!
Dugan!
Skip! Skip!
Snap out of that shit. Go!
- Fuck this, man. Let's bug out, Cleon!
- Cobra, move the fuck out!
- Get up! Come on!
- Move it! Move it!
Move! Get up!
Get up! Come on!
- What are you doin'?
- What is this, man?
- Slow down, man.
- Fuckin' grunts!
- Say, get a special shot for Skip. My man's
goin' home today. - Count of three: 1-2-3.
All right. Good.
Now come on, now. Skip, come on, now.
Let's see a dap, man.
- All right!
- Get one like this. Get one like this.
Come on, now.
Everybody, come on. Get closer.
- Ah, man!
- This is Cobra, baby.
- Recon Cobra!
- It's Cobra. Hey, hey!
Team Cobra, ready?
Come on
Come along, come on
and get up and get down too
- Get down, get up
- Say, h-h-hold on a sec.
- Keep the metre running.
- Get down, get up and move your feet
Come on and rise, rise, rise
Shake your get-up
Straighten up there, marine!
He a friend of yours?
Friend of yours and
I'll give a discount, marine.
No, man.
Oh, shit.
Man, look who's back
in the motherfuckin' world.
Dig this motherfucker
right here, man.
Look at you, man. That's a mackin'
outfit if I've ever seen one.
- Look, with all the stripes and shit. What, you a captain now?
- No, man.
Look, man, you wear that motherfucker for about
a month, this nigger get all the pussy, man.
Check this motherfucker out, man.
Well, look, man... Yeah,
you go get me some squares, man.
I gotta take care of a couple things,
baby. I'll get back with you. All right?
You stay up now, all right?
What's happening, blood?
Hey, man, I'm back.
My nigger!
Come on and get down
Hey, Luther!
Tell your sister I'm gonna
be over there later on.
Hey, fuck you!
Man, the neighbourhood is changin'.
Aw, it's still a good place.
White people movin' out, though.
Oh, dig. I saw Juanita
the other day, man.
Man, she finer than a motherfucker.
Is that right?
You need to go check her out, man.
Go see your little daughter.
Remember them big-ass ears
you had when you was young?
She got 'em, just like you.
That's how I know it was yours.
So, what's up with Joe, man?
Is he, uh... Is he workin' or what?
Aw, post office, you know.
Three-quarter gig, part-time.
He gotta do what he gotta do.
He got mouths to feed, you know.
What about you, man?
How you doin'?
- Who, me?
- Yeah.
I'm cool, baby. I'm Skippy, baby.
I'm still pimpin'.
Need any money
or anything, you know?
Man, I got over like a fat rat
when I got out, man.
Dig, I got my school money comin'
from the government once a month.
I got my veteran's cheque
comin' once a month.
I got my fifty percent medical cheque
comin' to me for the rest of my life.
I ain't gotta do a goddam thing else
but go to the mailbox, you dig?
Hey, man, how the hell you pull
a fifty percent medical?
Nigger, you ain't disabled.
Man, some shit got
into me over there, man.
What?
All I know is my blood cells
are all fucked up.
Some nights I wake up
in cold sweats and shit.
Don't look at me like that, man.
It ain't the heroin.
The heroin ain't never did nothin' to me.
A lot of vets comin' down with this shit.
- And they don't know what it is?
- Square biz.
Damn. Look, man, you wanna
come on in the crib or somethin', man?
Nah, man. I'm cool, baby.
Hey, I'm gonna split.
But you here, baby. You home.
We got plenty of time to do our thing.
You know what I'm sayin'?
- Brother.
- Brother. Go see your mama.
- Right on. I'm gonna check her out.
- With her fine ass.
You know, I been takin' care
of your mama while you been gone.
Boy, I'll kick your head in.
Don't talk like that.
Mmm.
You all right?
Yeah.
Well, can't you look me in my eyes?
I ain't seen you in four years.
Well, what'd you do over there?
What was it like?
Look, uh, I'd rather not
talk about that right now.
Well, Anthony, you gonna have
to tell us something.
Now, you know a lot of them boys went over there
and got hooked on them drugs and stuff. You know.
Look, I was in a special unit
out there...
and bad habits could've cost us
our lives.
Well, that's what I'm talkin' about,
them bad habits, honey.
Now, if you picked up some of them things,
there's a lot of places you can go and get help.
No bad habits, Ma.
'Cept a little killin'.
For my country, of course.
Hey. Let me give you some more
of these collards.
- Yeah.
- Baby, this sure is good.
Oh, shit. Look who back.
Look at this motherfuckin' man.
- Hey, what's happenin', youngblood?
- What's goin' on, cool breeze?
- Long time, no see.
- All right now, Pops. What's happenin'?
Hey there. What's goin' on, blood?
Ain't seen you in a long time, man.
- Boy just got back. -
Hey, blood. - All right.
- Cheers. My man. Drink!
- All right. How you feel? All right.
Hey, what's goin' on?
Hey, I got next game.
- You know that's my table.
- You call that a break?
- I got the thing made
- Hold up there, now. It's my shot.
Say, chump.
Don't I know you from somewhere?
- Ha-ha!
- My man, Joe! What's happenin'?
- Oh, look at you!
- How you doin', man?
- Good, man. What's goin' on, man?
- Jesus Christ, man.
- I can't believe it's you! You cool, man!
- What's goin' on, man?
Say, man,
I heard you got wounded out there.
Yeah, man. I was in demolitions
and my fuckin' hand gets blown off, man.
- Oh, man. Shit.
- Yeah, man. But hey...
motherfuckers told me everything there
is to know about explosives, man!
- That right?
- Check you out, Pappy. You got all those kids now.
Man, hey. You gotta check out Kirby,
man. He's over in the back room.
Yeah. Let's go on back.
He's still back here, huh?
- All right. Dig it.
- Hey. Abre la puerta! Hey! Hey!
Doin' all right. You know, Kirby just
all hangin' in there, you know?
- Who the fuck is it?
- It's me.
Blood! What's up, blood?
- Hey, Nicky. What's happenin', man?
- Skin!
Kirby back there, man.
That boy looked at me,
he say, "Kirby...
when she pulled off them drawers,
I thought I'd never stop seein' ass!"
- What's happenin', Captain?
- Who the fuck is that?
- Youngblood?
- Yeah, it's me!
Youngblood! Come on, boy!
- How you doin'? Come on in the back here, boy. Come on.
- Oh, boy. All right.
Man, I been everywhere
lookin' for a gig.
Aw, motherfuckers forget about you
gettin' your ass almost blown off...
or whatever the fuck.
Yeah. Look, uh, Kirby, uh...
I was thinkin', man.
Maybe, uh, come back and work for you.
What? Work for me?
Yeah. You know. Runnin' numbers.
Like we used to do.
Shh. Fuckin' pigs run me
out of business.
How... How the pigs run you outta
business, man? You had 'em on the payroll.
Pigs are greedy.
And you gotta remember I'm dealing
with the NYPD...
greediest, most corrupt pigs
on the face of the earth.
So I got the fuck out.
I told that motherfucker I'd rather
eat cat shit with a knittin' needle.
I wasn't gonna bust my ass sendin'
some cop kids to college. Shit.
I dig it.
This place ain't never
made much money.
So I'm just hustlin' here and there.
Tryin' to get over,
just like everybody else.
It's gonna be all right, kid.
Here's to gettin' over.
I hope, man. Hope. Shit.
- You afraid of blood?
- Uh, that's all I been around for the past three years.
Anthony Curtis.
You related to Tony?
The actor?
N- No. Not...
Oh! The act... No, no, no.
- Different colour, right?
- Yeah! He's a white cat. Yeah.
And his name was Schwartz.
Schwartz, not Curtis.
- Okay.
- Know anything about butchering?
Uh, I'm a fast learner.
Here, put that on.
- Here. Take this.
- Need some help, man!
All right.
Hey, uh, is Juanita in?
No, she's not,
but she'll be back in a...
in a while.
So you gonna stand out there,
or you comin' in?
I'm gonna come on in.
Girl, check you out.
I thought you were goin' over
to the communists.
Ah. Nah. Not me.
Now, dig, if you were smart,
that's what you would've done.
What?
Man, you don't know what the hell
you talkin' about, girl.
No, it's cool. I mean it's not your
fault you been brainwashed by America.
I mean, at least you made it back
alive, right?
You know, "Hello, how you doin'?"
That would've been real nice...
before you got off
onto all this political shit.
Welcome home.
And welcome to the revolution.
- So, this is Sarah's?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, wow.
- So, is she a smart baby?
- Ahh.
Why don't you find out for yourself?
Hey, y'all. Sorry I'm late.
Traffic on the Cross Bronx was a mess.
Oh. All righty.
There we go.
There you go.
Go play with your blocks.
Hey.
Oh, no. Look, Juanita.
I'm in one piece.
Hey, I got somebody
I want you to meet.
Come here, Sarah.
Come to Mommy.
Good girl. Come here.
Look at that.
- That's Daddy. Say hi.
- Hi.
This is Sarah Marie Curtis.
- Hello.
Hold her, silly. She's yours.
Oh.
Hey. Mmm.
Hey, um...
Oh, yeah. Be advised.
What's goin' on, my brothers?
- This is it, huh?
- Yeah. This is home.
Dig it. Dig it.
Check out Sleepin' Beauty
back there.
Boy, I still can't get over
how gorgeous she is.
Oh, she got that from her mama.
Oh. Okay.
You know, Juanita...
I wanna let you know I...
I did miss you. A lot.
Don't you think I know that, Anthony?
It's not important anyway. The important
thing is that you're here now.
Shh. Come here.
Oh.
Hey, baby girl.
Hey, Cutty.
Came by to see you a little earlier,
but you weren't home.
Oh, you know I had class tonight
after work...
and then I stopped over by my mother's.
- Oh, yeah. I forgot. It's Saturday.
- Yeah.
I see my little girl's sleepin'
back there, huh?
Yeah. She's all played out.
- Cutty, I wanted you to meet, um...
- Look here.
- Got a little somethin' for Sarah.
- Smiling faces
- Buy her something real nice.
- Smiling faces sometimes
Hey, Cutty, I told you
to stop spoilin' her like this.
Smiling faces
Smiling faces tell lies
- Somebody's gotta do it.
- And I got proof
- Beware
- Cutty, I want you to meet Anthony.
Okay. All right.
Let me just put her to bed. You come on
in and make yourself at home.
Come on in.
Okay. Can I get you something
to drink, or...
Look, Juanita.
Uh, I think I better go.
But you just got here.
Who knows, you could be
expectin' company or something.
Nobody's comin' here, Anthony.
I think I still should go.
Anthony.
I used to see Cutty.
Is that what you wanna hear?
Oh. Blood made that very clear to me.
So then, what's the problem?
Problem?
Why, man throwed two yards on your car.
You askin' me what's the problem?
Shit. Obviously nothin'.
Don't come up in here judgin' me.
What the fuck, man?
You got a pimp around my daughter?
Oh, he is not a pimp.
And besides, if you cared anything
about havin' a daughter...
you'd have wrote me back
after I sent you our picture.
But don't jump on me
for havin' a life.
You didn't want one with me.
So now what?
Are you gonna leave?
Some bullshit.
Come here.
Come on. Come here.
Ooh, hey
Ya gotta, gotta payback
Payback
- Damn!
- Revenge
A man
The big payback
Got to get back
Cleanup time, Cowboy.
See, man, why the fuck
you always gotta talk some shit?
Payback
Right there
- See, that's why I kicked his fuckin' ass when he was a little kid, man.
- Payback
- Always gettin' smart and shit.
- A man
Get down with my girlfriend
That ain't right
Now you gonna play this marine
war hero.
Out of touch
You know what I think?
- I think y'all was some goddam fools goin' over there...
- Gonna fight
fightin' that white man's war.
- That's right.
- Payback everything you got to see
- What you got when you get back here, huh?
- Yeah
- Never do any damn thing
- Not a goddam thing.
Course, you do got
that fine-ass Juanita.
- Throw me out
- Now, what the fuck you lookin' at me like that for, man?
I'm just complimentin' you
on your taste.
Throw me away
You had all the rage
- You had me down
- Course you know...
- That's the facts
- Baddest motherfucker this side of Nicky Barnes...
- Now, you punk
- My boss man Cutty...
Gettin' ready for the big payback
I thought that might ring a bell.
The big payback
That's where I learned
He used to tap that ass
while you was over in Nam.
- The big payback
- Motherfucker!
- Goddam!
- You do some fuckin' talkin', don't you, goddam it!
Try this on, motherfucker.
- No, no, no. He needs his ass whipped.
- What you mean "no"?
Get the fuck outta here!
Talk shit now, huh, motherfucker?
- Shut the fuck up. Come on. Come on. Motherfucker. Now what?
- I'm ready to be respected
You wanna fuck with me or what?
I'm gonna fuckin' kill your ass!
- Say somethin' now, motherfucker.
- That's enough, youngblood.
- Pull out your goddam knife!
- No! That's enough. Come on!
- I gonna kill this motherfucker!
- That's enough!
That mother! I'm gonna kill
this motherfucker!
- Let me go, Kirby! Let me go!
- No. He's already beat up. Come on now.
- Oh, shit.
- Come on. Let's go get some air.
Don't need no fuckin' air!
Let me go!
- Let me hit him, hit him, hit him
- That's game.
Shit.
Gonna have the aeroplane corn bread.
Here we go.
Ooh!
- You gonna spoil that girl.
- Mm-hmm.
Gonna spoil that one in your belly too.
I don't need no spoiled kids.
Hey, why not?
Not enough black babies are spoiled.
Ain't that right, Sarah, hmm?
You got a point there.
Come on. Sit on down.
Big girl. Come here.
Come here.
Look at you.
Fat girl.
See what we got ourselves here.
Oh, you know what? I think we're gonna
have ourselves a little boy.
Yeah, come on, man.
You got to be a boy.
Boy, boy, boy. Mm.
Ant Junior.
See, it's the power of the mind.
We will ourselves a little boy.
Then can you will yourself
a better job?
Can you will yourself to stop
drinkin' so much?
Come on, honey.
Don't even start that shit, all right?
I thought we supposed to be havin'
a nice time here.
Look, Juanita.
I- I'm gonna get myself
a... a good job.
You know how long you been singin'
that same old song now, Anthony?
I mean, in case you haven't noticed,
this here's the real world.
Ain't no free meals here
like in the marines.
Say, let me tell you somethin'.
Wasn't nothin' free in the marines.
I earned every meal
and every fuckin' dollar, all right?
Look, everything's gonna be cool.
You know I'll be
five months next week.
You're five months pregnant,
you can't be no nurse's aide.
I said we'll be all right.
Hey, um... Anybody want some speed?
Get the fuck outta here
with that shit.
Say, why don't you
cut the bullshit, Joe?
Can't you clear your mind
for one sec, man?
Now, you sure that they
pick up cash money?
Hey, cash money, bro.
Like clockwork, once a month.
Then they stop by the post office...
before they make their final run
to Washington, man.
All the way to Washington, D.C.,
where they burn the money.
Can you believe that shit?
Old bills, man.
Sometimes a couple million.
- How many guards?
- Four.
Two in the front
and one in the back carry revolvers.
The other one, 12-gauge shotgun, man.
You think we can take 'em?
I can't say, man.
I mean...
four guards, and all of 'em
packin'?
I put up the guns. I get the money
together to get the plans goin'.
But you got to be the master planner.
You got medals for blowin'
motherfuckers up out there.
- Man, I heard you were like John Wayne.
- Well, then that's the deal.
Yeah, all that money.
Ah, man.
Anthony. You down?
- Ahh.
- The look
- Of love
- Let's drink on it anyway.
- Is in your eyes
- Mmm.
- Ahh.
- A look
- Ooh, ooh, ooh.
- Your heart
- Say, man. Shhh. -
Can't disguise - Hmm?
Put the goddam thing away.
Get your little pyromaniac ass...
- You gonna be walkin' in a minute.
- Aw, cool out, Kirby, man.
I'm not gonna burn your car.
Not yet, at least.
Don't go
Forget it, Juanita.
Come on. Watch out there.
The look of love
What's the problem, Anthony?
What is it? I mean,
is it because I'm pregnant?
Shh. Come on.
Now, don't be silly.
So, then what's the problem?
Come on. Talk to me.
What is it?
I told you. You need to
leave that alcohol alone.
- No! No!
- Anthony! Anthony, baby!
It's me.
It's me. It's all right.
It's all right.
Come here.
Shh. Shh. Shh.
It's just another dream.
This is my best cut,
Mrs Stein. Enjoy.
Thank you very much, Saul.
- He's such a nice man.
- What did he give you?
- We need to talk.
- Oh.
- So what's happenin'?
- You're a good man.
Aw, come on, Saul. I ain't got time to kibitz
with ya. I got a whole lot of meat to cut.
I'm closing down the shop.
Should've told you sooner,
but I thought maybe...
business, you know,
pick up a little.
Sorry.
- Here.
- Oh, no, look, Saul... No. I can't.
What am I gonna do with it?
I have to get rid of it.
Come on.
Now I know
We have great respect
For the sister and mother
It's even better yet
But there's the joker in the street
Here you go, brother.
Don't let the bullshit get to you.
I'm tryin', man. I'm tryin'.
You wanna get the man's foot
off your neck?
Come check us out.
Take care of yourself, brother.
Live righteous.
Here you go, brother.
Here you go.
Take care of yourself, brother.
Come see us now.
Don't let us hang around this town
- Here you go, sister.
- And let what others say come true
Brothers and sisters, here you go.
Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh.
Hey, youngblood.
Bringin' in the groceries, huh?
Lord, have mercy.
Man, I remember
when I was married.
I used to love
to bring home the groceries.
Made me feel real good.
Like a man. Know what I mean?
Hey, listen, youngblood. Uh...
I just dropped by
to see Juanita and Sarah.
- You know, lay a little somethin' on 'em.
- Stopped by to see my baby?
Is that right?
You know, youngblood...
I took care of your woman and your baby
when you were in the war.
Now, a man oughta get a little respect
for somethin' like that.
Now, I ain't gonna lie to you.
I care about Juanita.
I care about her a whole lot.
But you back now, and I'm gone.
So from this point on, you should
consider me like a friend of the family.
Find yourself in a jam and shit,
need a little cash...
you come see me,
I'll front you.
- Keep your shit.
- Listen, brother.
I know about pride.
But you got mouths to feed.
Now, I laid a little cash
on Juanita.
Say, man, stay the fuck
away from my family.
What did you say?
You heard me, goddam it.
I said, "Stay the fuck away
from my family. "
See, I ain't the enemy, youngblood.
I don't want no trouble.
Shit.
See, I tried to be a friend,
motherfucker.
Surprise, nigger.
Big bad marines.
Look at you now.
Does she suck you?
Fuck you?
Make you feel like a man?
Make you feel real good?
Huh, boy?
Now, she wasn't doin' it like that
before you went to the war, now was she?
Now you gettin'
all that good lovin'...
and you can't even put food
on your fuckin' table.
Come on, Santa Claus.
Open your mouth and suck this.
Come on. I got a present for you.
Suck it!
- Suck it, nigger!
- Kill me, motherfucker.
Shoot me right now.
What you gonna do, shoot me?
You lucky this is personal, nigger.
I ain't gonna kill you
over no woman.
Don't you ever...
in your fuckin' life...
bite the hand
that feeds you, nigger.
See ya, Santa Claus.
- Hold still now.
- I'm all right.
- Hold still.
- No, I'm all right. Damn!
You givin' him that money back.
He won't take it back.
What the fuck you talkin'...
You better get his shit back to him!
Even if I wanted to give it back to him,
Anthony, he wouldn't take it back.
W- W-W-Wait. What the fuck you talkin'
about, "if you wanted to give it back"?
No, no, no, no.
Fuck that shit.
Have you forgotten you just lost your
damn job? We need that fuckin' money.
- We don't need his money.
- Yeah, well, Anthony, I'll tell you what.
You start bringin' some real money in here, like a real
man, and then I'll think about givin' it back to him.
Until then, I don't wanna hear shit.
You need to get your tight ass together, that's what you
need to do, and stop feelin' sorry for your damn self.
Sometimes it's like you ain't even
the same man I knew before the war.
That's who I was in love with. That's who
I thought showed the fuck back up here.
I don't know who the fuck you are.
So, what? You just, uh,
suck his dick so good...
he just start
throwin' money at you, right?
What is with you?
Why you so damn paranoid?
I ain't fuckin' him.
Not at this moment, you ain't. No.
But the motherfucker
ain't sniffin' around here...
tossin' money in your
motherfuckin' face for nothin'!
Yeah, well, I sleep with you
every night, don't I?
You know, Juanita,
that's a damn good question.
Come on. Go ahead.
Admit this shit, man. Be honest.
You fuckin' him, right?
- Is that what you wanna hear, Anthony? That's
what you wanna hear? - Uh-huh. Yeah. Yeah.
Fine. I'm fuckin' him.
So, uh, whose baby is that?
D- Don't even answer that shit.
No, you right. I ain't gonna answer it.
I mean, shit. You Anthony.
You the big marine man with no damn job.
You know every fuckin' thing.
Answer this for me: If you think I'm jivin' you
so much, Anthony, why the hell you with me? Huh?
Why the fuck you with me? What, you think
I need you? Do you think I need this shit?
Fuck. You can't get a decent job,
you won't fuck me.
The only time I get to hold you is when you're
havin' one of them silly-ass nightmares...
Shut the fuck up!
You don't know, girl.
You really don't know.
- Don't you fuckin' walk away from...
- You better get the fuck off of me!
- Don't walk away from me, Anthony.
- Let me go.
- Don't you... What about Sarah?
- I'll fuckin' kill you, girl!
Don't you ever run up on me! Ever!
Ever run up on me again!
I'll fuckin' kill you, Juanita!
Get the fuck off me!
Bunch of shit!
- Yeah!
- That's right. You can't trust them!
- Now, they send our men off to Vietnam...
- That's what they do.
to fight for this
so-called democracy.
- That's right. Preach, sister.
- Yeah! Yeah!
But when they get back down
to the South Bronx...
and to Bed-Stuy and Harlem
and Watts, etc., etc...
shit is worse than ever.
- There is something very sick about that.
- He's a devil.
That's right,
he's the devil.
That's right!
Go, sister! Go on!
- Power to the people!
- In 'n' out.
- Never, never gonna give you up
I'm never, ever gonna stop
Not the way
I feel about you
- Girl, I just can't live without you
- There you go.
- I'm never, ever gonna quit
- What can I get you, baby?
Anyway, so like I was sayin',
I ran into this brother...
and he, uh, gave me
this flyer.
So I figured I'd go over
and check it out.
And there you were, up there
talkin' that ol' righteous shit.
I'm just a college student tryin' to do
her part to rally the people together.
But, dig, we need more
than talk. It's... It's time to do.
- Do what?
- Revolution.
Oh, wait a minute. See.
Y'all a little outta my league now.
Is that what you're gonna say
when the revolution comes?
W- When it's time
to pick up a gun?
What you know
about weapons?
I'm qualified
to handle a. 45...
an M-16 rifle,
a. 38-calibre pistol...
and a Russian AK-47.
An AK-47?
Why don't you join us?
A lot of brothers
from the war have.
Baby, I got enough
heavy shit to deal with.
- I got you, brother.
- Relax.
You're so uptight.
Damn, I got to make
some fuckin' bread.
I'm through
with your sister, but...
I still got to take care
of my baby girl, Sarah.
Shit, and the one
that's on the way.
Damn!
Look, anyway, uh, I got
this plan to make some money.
I want you to keep
this shit to yourself.
At 6:15 a. m., the truck
pulls outta the post office...
at 149th and Grand Concourse.
Now, it makes one stop
before it goes to D. C...
which is a mail drop-off
at First Federal Loan and Savings...
which is on Noble Street
and West.
Now, Kirby...
you're gonna position yourself
in a getaway car...
at the end of the corner,
where you can see everything.
Jose. Me and you gonna
position ourselves behind the bank...
underneath the left
and the right side of the loadin' dock.
Delilah, you're gonna position
yourself inside the Dumpster...
which is located directly across
from the loadin' dock.
Now, Skippy, I want you
to position yourself...
approximately ten feet
from the alleyway.
There, you post
a lookout.
We all know what to do
at the point of attack...
because we've gone
over that shit enough.
If anybody gets caught, you shut
the fuck up, and we'll keep your money.
Shh! Fuck that shit, man.
I'm telling you right now,
if I get caught...
- I'm shooting my fuckin' way out.
- Nigger, put that shit down.
I think we need another man
on the street with Skip.
Someone to cover
the other side.
- I agree.
- Oh, man! Hell, no!
We don't need no 'nother man.
Shit, I can see.
- Besides, we got too many motherfuckers anyway.
- Fuck that shit, Kirby, man.
Everybody trusts
everybody here, right?
I can get somebody
from our organization.
Oh, no, no, no, no. I don't want none
of them revolutionary niggers involved.
You can cut your eye at me
all you want to.
I ain't too keen on havin'
that broad up in here neither.
Well, you the one talkin' about we need
another man. Make up your goddam mind.
You have somebody in mind,
Anthony?
We might as well put a motherfuckin' ad
in the paper. Then we gonna get everybody.
Shit, ain't gonna be
no money left for a nigger.
Oh, yes! Y'all didn't know
your reverend was a gamblin' man?
A sinnin' man?
I was a man who maimed!
I was a man who killed!
We all know it was done
in the name of the wicked one.
The one that was
cast down from heaven.
- Hallelujah!
- Amen!
I said y'all know
who I'm talkin' about!
Can I get a "hallelujah"
in this house of God?
Hallelujah!
Well, look here, man.
Skip is in. Period. All right?
I stand a lot to lose
if this thing blows up in my face.
The last time I saw him, he was
shooting poison in his veins.
Yeah, I know. Well, you know,
he's tryin' to shake that shit, man.
- He's still on drugs.
- And I still trust him with my life, Cleon.
Remember that last battle?
He froze up.
For a minute.
Then h-he broke out of it.
And when he "broke out of it,"
Dugan was dead.
Come on, Cleon. You know that
could've happened to any of us.
Now either you in
or you out. Which one?
How much money did you say
was in that truck?
We still got
about 15 minutes.
I tell ya, I could've
used another cup of coffee.
Let's make this quick.
Bank security.
- How ya doin'?
- Good.
- Mornin'.
- Good mornin'.
Oh, f...
You waitin' on
the number 11 bus?
Yes.
I don't think
she runs this early.
I caught it the other morning,
uh, at this same time.
You sure about that?
Uh-huh.
- Let me check for you.
- No need to go to any trouble, Officer.
No, no, no.
No trouble at all, brother.
I see by that patch
on your jacket you were in recon.
I was a 5th marine. Always willin'
to help out a fellow leatherneck.
Brown on patrol.
Requesting off-hour route check
on number 11.
Dispatch to Brown.
Hold for schedule.
That's a copy.
Do somethin', Cleon.
- Ambush! Ambush!
- Drop it, motherfucker!
What the hell?
Shit!
Joe! Come on. Let's move.
Oh, goddam it!
Fuck! Shit!
Oh, shit!
Anthony!
- Did you see that shit, man?
- Hey, what the fuck wrong with you?
- See the way the fuckin' doors blew off, man?
- No, motherfucker!
Motherfuckin' Joe, you blew the whole
motherfuckin' truck up, motherfucker!
- It blew up like that, man!
- That's how you fucked your hand up last time!
You... And the money... You fucked up.
I'm gonna kick your motherfuckin' ass!
Grab what you can, motherfucker,
before the whole thing burns!
Hey, Anthony and Delilah
gotta see this shit, man.
I'm gonna go get 'em!
Hey, Anthony!
You gotta see the shit I did, man.
I blew that shit up, man!
You gotta see it, man!
You gotta see the shit I did!
Let's get outta here.
Put the gun down. Put the gun down.
Come on, Delilah.
Let's get up. Up. Let's go.
Come on, bro.
We gotta go, man.
I can't...
I can't leave her.
You ain't gotta
leave her, bro...
'cause she's already gone.
Get up here!
Go on!
Unit 1004, do you copy?
Please respond.
Do you require assistance?
Do you copy?
Any available units
in the vicinity of Noble Street.
Two-eleven in progress.
Code three. Repeat.
Code three.
God's not gonna
forgive me for this one.
I'll tell you what, Reverend. With this kind
of money, you can buy your way into heaven.
That's where you're wrong, brother.
We done bought our way into hell.
The plain fact is that I promised
the Lord I would never sin like this.
To tell you the truth, I'm not sure
I even want any of this dirty money.
Well, I'll tell you what,
Reverend.
We'll find somethin'
to do with your share.
- Amen to that shit.
- No. No, no, no, no.
- I'll take the money.
- You lyin' sack o' shit.
I'm sure the Lord will find
another way for me to do my penance.
Just tell me
one thing, Cleon.
Why the fuck
you didn't grab the cop?
You killed him.
A young brother.
If you wouldn't have froze up like a bitch, maybe
I wouldn't have had to do that shit, now wouldn't I?
Would y'all
shut the fuck up?
Man, Delilah. Shit.
Man, radio said they got
Joe's stupid ass.
Fucked it up.
The whole plan was fucked up.
We ain't do shit right
out there, man. Shit.
Y'all make sure that Jose's share
goes to Marisol and his kids.
- Walk on by
- Done.
Your junkie ass really
messed up out there.
Don't blame me
for your fuck-ups.
I told Anthony I didn't want nothin' to
do with a crazy, devil-filled junkie!
- What?
- You listenin' to me? Look at him.
- Oh, shit!
- Now say some more shit!
I'll knock your ass
right back down.
Fake-ass wanna-be preacher,
no-members-havin' motherfucker!
Why don't y'all stop actin'
like some fuckin' clowns?
You know, you niggers
sure is silly.
Now, you're standin' here fightin',
and we got over $300,000...
of cold, hard, unmarked U.S. cash
to split up five ways.
Let me tell ya somethin'. You make me lose
count again, I'm gonna shoot me a motherfucker...
and then we gonna be splittin'
this thing up four ways, hear?
Man, I can't believe this.
They was gonna burn all this shit.
All this shit, and a nigger
can't even find a job.
Well, that's Uncle Sam
for you, baby.
Money to burn.
Police have issued an all-points
bulletin for the remaining...
...Reserve Bank
on Noble Street.
Faces painted skeleton white.
Cobra, request your status.
Over.
- Five federal security guards...
- Anthony!
- She's already gone.
- Do it. Kill me.
The bloody shootout erupted...
an armoured truck... explosives...
No, motherfuckin' Joe. You blew the whole
motherfuckin' truck up, motherfucker!
...the deaths of nine people.
The heroin ain't never
did nothin' to me.
...just moments away from the scene
of the crime... Robbery turned bloody...
- Had some shit got into me over there, man.
- Crushed to death by...
Rudolph the red-nosed reindeer
Had a very shiny nose
- And if you ever saw it
- What you slowin' down for?
- Be cool. Be cool.
- What you doin'?
- Come on. Come on.
- What the fuck, man? Aw, shit!
- All of the other reindeer
- What the fuck we doin' over here?
- Say, man, check out all these kids.
- Man!
Hey, let's go to the liquor store
and go to the club.
Look, man, I'm gonna take care of you.
We're gonna go down to the club.
- We don't know them motherfuckers!
- That's the whole point, baby.
Come on. Get in the spirit.
Hey, y'all come on over here!
- Nigger, we gonna get robbed.
- Hey, be cool, nigger. Y'all come on over here.
- Be cool, man. Damn.
- Rudolph, with your nose so bright
All of y'all gonna get some.
All right. All right.
- Merry Christmas! Merry Christmas!
- What, motherfu...
Yeah, man. Merry Christmas,
motherfucker. Go on. Leave me alone.
Say, say, Skippy. Hey, man, why don't you
bring your ass over here and quit that jivin'.
Come on. Yeah, yeah. Y'all take
all the toys. All right. Get one.
- See what I'm sayin'? I ain't kiddin'. We givin' it away.
- All right. All right. Yeah.
That's why Santa Claus don't wanna come 'round here
'cause he's scared he's gonna get shot or robbed.
All right. Just one. Hey, hey, hey. Give
me this, man. Get a... Get a... Get a toy.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Why you stealin'? You ain't gotta steal.
- All right, all right, all right.
- Funky little brothers. I talked to him.
He says he ain't never gonna come down
here unless he's got police protection.
Last year, one of y'all niggers
stole one of his reindeer.
No, no. I say let's just go up there
and kill that motherfucker.
Man, me and Anthony gave out
a couple of things, but that was it.
You gave toys and turkeys to people.
Then you got the hell outta Dodge.
Man. Y'all sayin' my man is
goin' around handin' out $100 bills...
and sayin' that
God Almighty gave it to him?
My cousin lives up there in Mount Vernon. He
says that Cleon's up there actin' a goddam fool.
That ol' high-profile ass
nigger.
Bought a brand-new Caddy.
Folk know he can't afford it.
- Look, man, I'm gonna go over there and talk to him.
- No, no, no. Fuck the talk!
I'm drivin' up there, and I'm gonna
take him out before he rats us out.
Look, Kirby.
I'm gonna handle everything, all right?
- I'm gonna straighten this shit out.
- All right.
But if you don't take care of this,
Anthony, I promise you, I will.
I told you we didn't
need another man.
That's y'all's motherfuckin'
punk-ass friend!
People runnin' from their worries
While the judge and his juries
They take the law
that's part of the flaw
No. Oh, shit, Cleon!
Love, fallin', fussin' and a-cussin'
Damn!
The feelin' now is killin'
For peace no one is willin'
Kinda make you get that feelin'
Everybody's startin'
Use the pill and the dope
Educated fools
From uneducated schools
Right now we'd like to bring on a young man
who believes in doing things his own way.
And based on the way he kinda get next to
all of the folks who've seen him work...
his way has gotta be
pretty hip.
So let's lay some noise
on the mighty Al Green.
Apartment 13!
I'm so tired of bein' alone
I'm so tied up on my own
Won't you help me, girl
Just as soon as you can
Don't move, mister!
I been wantin' to get
next to you, baby
You see, sometime
I fold my arms, I say
- Ooo-ooo
- Mmm-hmm-mmm
Whoa-oh-oh
Oh, baby, hey
Needing you has proven to be
To be my greatest dream
Yeah
- I'm so tired of being alone
- Oh, tired, baby
- Here's the rest of the fifties.
- Put it in there.
You know, I still feel fucked-up
about this whole situation.
Look, feelin' fucked-up don't help a goddam
thing and it ain't gonna bring nobody back.
- Shit!
- So, just worry about yourself. We just gotta get outta here.
- Come on.
- Say, man, you got everything?
Yeah, grab that bag.
This is a bitch.
This is it, man.
This is it.
All we got to do, boy,
is make it to Mexico.
We'll be fine.
We'll get us a villa, see?
And then, and buy a boat
and sail all around the gulf.
Everything will be fine.
We just gotta get the fuck outta here.
Yeah, maybe I can send
for Sarah once we get down there.
Well, anything's possible.
Come on.
Wait a minute.
Run, Anthony! Hyah!
Y'all get back!
Get away right there! Get off me!
Shit!
- You pity fool, you pity fool
- Fuck!
You better have some sympathy
Yeah
'Cause there's educated people
Runnin' the lives of our society
Makin' up the rules
Mr Curtis, you have been
lawfully tried in this court...
and found guilty on all charges.
Do you have anything to say on your own
behalf before I pronounce sentence?
Uh...
no, ain't nothin' I say
gonna get me out of this.
But things were gettin' bad
for me, and...
I had to do what I had to do
to s... to survive.
Maybe it was wrong, but I...
I certainly didn't mean
for anybody to be hurt.
Uh, Your Honour,
please consider before sentencing...
that my client served his country proud
in the Marine Corps.
As a matter of fact, he was
a member of an elite unit...
a sergeant,
decorated with many medals.
In fact, one of those medals
was the, uh, Silver Star, for valour.
I realize that my client had
a difficult time adjusting when he...
Excuse me, Counsel.
I, too, was a marine...
and I served my country proudly
in World War Il, a real war, I may add.
- Yes, Your Honor...
- I'm not finished yet, please.
I received the Purple Heart
at Guadalcanal.
Now, this young man has obviously
forgotten some very...
fundamental things like decency
and dedication and honor...
everything the corps taught us.
He is a disgrace to everyone
that has ever put on that uniform...
and I will not permit you or him to use
the Vietnam War as a cop-out here.
Anthony Curtis, for your
participation in this crime...
a crime that took the lives of several
innocent people, I do hereby...
sentence you to the custody of the
Attorney General of the United States...
for a period of 15 years to life.
Oh, my God.
These proceedings are concluded.
This court is adjourned.
"Life"? What the fuck
he mean "life"?
After all the shit I did
for this motherfuckin' country?
What the fuck he talkin' about, "life"?
Man, fuck you! Fuck you!
- Hey!
- Oh, Anthony!
After all the shit I did
for this motherfuckin' country?
You, remove the prisoner
from the court!
- You hear me? - Fuck you! Fuck
you! - Restrain the prisoner!
Get him outta here! Let the record
show... Let the record show...
that a chair was thrown
at the judge.
Whoa, whoa
If you see me
walkin' down the street
And I start to cry
Each time we meet
Then walk on by
Walk on by
Make believe
That you don't see the tears
You just let me grieve
in private
'Cause each time I see you
I just can't help myself
I think about how tight we used to be
I break down and cry
Oh, baby
Walk on by
Hmm-mmm-mmm
I just can't get over
losing you
So if I seem
Broken in two
Please walk on by
Walk on by
Foolish pride
Is all that I have left
So let me hide
The tears and the sadness
you gave me
You put the hurt on me
You socked it to me, mama
When you said goodbye
So, please, walk on by
Make believe you never see
the tears I cry
So do me a favour
And walk on by
So I'm beggin' you to
Walk on by
Oh, yeah
And make believe you never see
the tears I cry
So I'm beggin' you
I'm beggin' you
To walk on by
Make believe you never see
the tears I cry
Oh
There's no dust in my eye
Oh, no
Smoke ain't makin' me cry
No, no, no
It's the hurt
you put on me, yeah
I don't want you
to see this man cry
Where is the love
Ooh, yeah, yeah
You said you'd give to me
Soon as you were free
Will it ever be
Where is the love
You told me that you
didn't love him
And you were gonna say goodbye
But if you really
didn't mean it
Why did you have to lie
Where is the love
You said was mine
all mine
Till the end of time
Was it just a lie
Where is the love
If you had had a sudden
change of heart
I wish that you
would tell me so
Don't leave me hangin'
on these promises
You've gotta let me know
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player