One Piece The Movie
Episode of Chopper +
The Miraculous Cherry Blossoms, Blooming in Winter
This is a battle during the search for One Piece,
the one great treasure left behind by the legendary Pirate King, Gol D. Roger.
Countless pirates have raised their flags and set sail for the Grand Line.
This is the Great Pirate Era.
From these intrepid crews have risen pirates with immense power,
the most feared of whom are those with the supernatural powers...
granted by eating a Devil Fruit:
The Devil Fruit users.
Among them is the boy who ate the Gomu Gomu fruit and aspires to be the next Pirate King: Monkey D. Luffy.
He is the captain of the Straw Hat Pirates.
An absolutely essential member of a crew like this is a doctor.
At the moment, however, this ship does not have one.
Why?
Because this is the story of an encounter...
Daily... training...
This is the best way to become a great swordsman.
Well then...
Alright!  Lemme try catching a Sea King or something with this!
What?!  Hey, Luffy, where'd you find that thing?!
It was just lying over there.
Hey, hey, Captain!
I can make you whatever you want, if you just ask me.
I'm the shipwright after all.
Franky!
No, no matter how you look at it, you can't catch a Sea King...
If you need to catch something, shouldn't you leave it to me, the great sniper, Usopp-sama?
Hey, you guys!  Do you know what happened to my weights?
Hey, those are mine, dammit!
Oh, crap!  Zoro's mad!
Straw Hat!  Hurry up and throw it away!
Destroy the evidence!
Good idea!  Here, catch!
You're too slow!
Give it back, dammit!
They sure are noisy.
Nami-swan!
Robin-chwan!
Would you like to taste this afternoon's relaxing snack, petits fours?
Thank you.
My pride as the ship's cook, as well as my heart and soul, went into making this.
Please enjoy...
Faint, blushing cheeks... wavering eyes...
This is the look of a maiden in love!
Who could those eyes be looking at?  Could it be...
me?!
The air has changed...
A huge gust of wind is coming.
Hurry, haul in the sails!
Shift our heading southward!
Franky!  Prepare the cola barrels!
We'll blast away with a Burst!
Sure!  Leave it to me!
Everyone ready?!
Yeah!
Let's go!
The power of the Burst is as awesome as always!
But what's going on?
I'm not questioning Nami or anything, but still...
Why'd we change our course all of a sudden?
What is that?!
A cyclone!
It's right where our ship was headed a minute ago!
If we'd stayed on course we'd have run straight into it!
They say that cyclones in the Grand Line are impossible to predict...
that they come without warning...
I'd expect no less from you, Nami.
Everyone, this is bad!  Come quickly!
Nami-chan has a terrible fever!
What?!  A fever?  That's bad!
Ith Nami-than going to be awlight?
Ith thhe, Wobin-tan?
She'll recover if she eats some meat!  Meat!  Meat!
You idiot!  In times like this, you need some refreshing cola!
Can't you two be a little more concerned?!
Be quiet!
Sorry...
So high... Her temperature's 41 degrees!
Is that bad?
Dunno... I've never been sick before.
Me neither.
What's going on, Robin?
Well, archeology is my specialty, not medicine...
But I know that this kind of temperature isn't normal.
We should get her to a doctor as soon as possible.
A doctor?  We don't have one on this ship.
Yeah, a ship doctor would be useful.
This could be a fatal disease!
Nami's gonna die?!
Nami-dan, pweade do't die!
Be quiet!
Full speed toward the nearest doctor!
We're gonna save Nami!
A pirate ship?
Get lost, damn pirates!
This ain't no place for you!
Hurry up and get out of here!
One of our crewmates is sick.
We're looking for a doctor.
Please tell us where we can find one.
Think we'd fall for that?!
You're just a bunch of dirty pirates!
What's going on here?
What do we care if you die or not?
Dalton-san.  Some pirates are here.
Then can you bring the doctor here?  Please!
She's suffering from a serious illness!  Please help her!
Quit screwing around!
Why, you...  Don't you dare...
Straw Hat!
Hey!  What if you'd killed him?!  He was unarmed!
Well, I just...
I'm begging you.
Luffy, you-!
Please call a doctor.
Please, help my friend!
I'll take you to our village.
Follow me.
Thank you.
This place sure is cold!
The climate on the Grand Line varies from island to island.
This must be a Winter Island.
A Winter Island?  So that's why there's so much snow.
I love the white snow!
We do have summers on this island, but the snow never melts.
Living in a kingdom of snow is harsh,
but we can't just leave our homeland.
I might be a bit late in introducing myself, but my name is Dalton.
I'm the island's protector.
I apologize for the hostile welcome.
Don't worry about it.
We're pirates; we're used to it.
But, you there.  I'm sure I saw you get hit by that bullet earlier...
Oh, guns don't work on me.
This guy ate the Gomu Gomu Fruit.  He's a rubber-man.
I see.  You too have eaten a Devil Fruit.
But despite the abilities you might gain by doing so,
you must never let yourself become an actual Devil!
What?
Oh, no.  I wasn't referring to you people.
This island had...
Oh, a reindeer!
A reindeer?!
A raccoon dog?
A mole?
A cuckoo?
Wrong!
Oh, now that I look at it, that's gotta be a stuffed deer!
Yeah, now that you mention it...
If it were anything else, it'd be a monster!
Monster?!
It talked!
I'm dead.
That's the Hiking Bear.  It's harmless.
Just mind your manners.
I'm freezing...
I guess I'll go take a bath.
This is our village, Bighorn.
First, why don't you come to my house?
Are you sure, Dalton-san?  They're pirates, you know!
They mean us no harm.  They just happened to drift by here.
We can trust them.
Oh, okay.
I'll leave it to you.
Her temperature is 42 degrees?!
Yes... Please hurry and call a doctor!
This village has one, right?!
We've only got one doctor on this island.  A witch.
Witch?
You see the mountains outside the window, right?
Yeah... Umm...
Hey!
This is Hyper Snowman-san!
This is the Snow Monster Shirora!
Yeah, yeah, yay!
I'm gonna kick the crap out of you two!
What's wrong?
It's the Hiking Bear!
Deep bow.
Hey.
At the top of the highest mountain lies a castle.
Right now, it's a castle without a king.
A castle?
The only doctor on this island, the one people call a witch,
Doctor Kureha, lives there alone.
What?  Then please call her down here now!
I'd like to, but we have no way to contact her.
Huh?
There used to be a ropeway to the castle, but it was taken down.
Yet she still calls herself a doctor?!
What kind of person is she?
She's definitely skilled, but she is a rather eccentric old lady.
She's close to one hundred forty years old.
Really?  Is she alright?
How do people around here deal with diseases and injuries?
She comes down from the mountain every now and then.
She looks for patients, treats them,
and takes whatever she wants from their houses as payment.
She doesn't sound like a very nice lady.
Hey, hey.  She's almost like a pirate.
But how does that old lady get down from the mountain?
This is just a rumor,
but people say they've seen her silhouetted by the moon, flying down in a sleigh.
That's why they call her a witch.
A... A witch who flies through the sky?
Other people claim they've seen her with a strange creature unlike anything they've seen before.
The... The Abominable Snow Man?!
I knew he existed... It's the Abominable Snow Man!
Damn it.
It's bizarre for this island to have just one doctor.
She must be dangerous to be with the Abominable Snow Man.
Aah!  I've got the "I-Shouldn't-Go-To-The-Mountain" sickness!
And an old lady at that!
Hey!  What are you doing?!
Hey, Nami!  Nami!  Can you hear me?
Oh, she's awake!
We've gotta climb the mountain to get to the doctor, so we're climbing the mountain.
Don't be so reckless!  What're you gonna do with Nami-san?!
It's fine.  I'll carry her.
No, that's gonna be too dangerous!
Why?  It's best to get her there as soon as possible, right?
We don't know when that doctor will be coming down anyway...
Nami-san's condition is too serious!
Nami-san?
Nami?
I'm counting on you!
That's what I wanted to hear!
Leave it to me!
You guys are crazy.
Right!  I'll go too!
Then so will I.
No, we've gotta hurry.
It's better if just a few of us go.
Right!  Off you go, you two!
I'll wait here with Robin!
I won't stop you if you're serious about this,
but you might run into a Lapahn herd on the way.
They're brutal, flesh-eating rabbits.
If you get attacked by a herd of them, you won't survive it.
Rabbits?  That's no problem, right?
Sure.  I'll just kick 'em!
Then let's get going!  Before Nami dies!
Don't say such ominous things, you damn bastard!
Will they be alright?
As long as it's those two.
I hope they can get Nami all the way there...
There's no point standing out here and worrying.
Please, come inside.
Nah.  I want to stay outside.
As do I.
I see.
In that case, I will keep you company.
We had them once, you know.
Huh?
Doctors.
There was a time when our country was renowned for its medical knowledge.
But half a year ago, the country fell...
because of a pirate attack.
We were attacked by Blackbeard and his crew.
Against their terrifying power, the kingdom was crushed.
So that's why you were so hostile toward us.
But many think it made the country a better place.
There's no way that could be!  How?!
Because the kingdom was under tyranny!
We were known as a country of advanced medical science,
but only twenty doctors were allowed to stay in the country.
The rest had been culled in the Doctor Hunt and banished from the country.
Why would they do that?
To give the king complete control over the country's medical facilities!
With no other doctors, the citizens were forced to plead the king for help.
Holding every sick person in the kingdom hostage...
It was criminal!
The king's name was Wapol.
He had eaten the Baku Baku Fruit and gained the power to devour anything.
He was absolutely the worst kind of king!
But that guy was killed by the pirates, wasn't he?
In that case...
Once Wapol realized the strength of the pirates,
he took the doctors and was the first to flee the kingdom!
He didn't even try to fight back.
He simply abandoned the entire kingdom!
How awful.
Then the "witch" who lives in that castle...
Doctor Kureha is the only doctor who escaped the Doctor Hunt.
Doctorine!  Pirates have landed!
They might come here, too...
Indeed.  There are definitely a lot of pirate ships down there.
Seems like this is gonna be a busy day, Chopper.
A lot?
H-How can this be?!
We've gotta warn the village!
Right!
Don't let them set foot on land!
We've gotta stop them any way we can!
What?
Awesome!
I can't just sit around here!
We've reached the Drum Kingdom, Bro-chan!
Covered in snow, as always!
It's gotten colder...
The wind picked up.
Why're you barefoot anyway?
It hurts just to look at you.
This is just my stylus!
What do you mean "stylus"?  Don't you mean "style"?
Doesn't really matter, does it?
Yes it does!  They mean completely different things.
What's "stylus" then?
You're the one who said it!
Besides...
this has been getting on my nerves for a while now!
What was with that guy?
What was that ship?  We're real lucky here!
I'm in super condition this week!
Why'd I have to come along?
That's only because you fell asleep in here!
Besides, didn't you say you were gonna take a bath?
I got lost.
On the ship?!
I don't know how to find anything on that ship.
Why, you!  You got a problem with my design?!
What's going on?!
Are they picking a fight with us?!
White bears?
Nah, they're rabbits.
But there sure are a lot of 'em...
Listen up, Luffy.  You mustn't attack these guys, no matter what!
Why?
The shock from your punches will hurt Nami-san too!
If you do that, she really will die!
I-I got it!  I won't fight!
It jumped at us!
How'd it move so fast?!
I can't kick properly in all this snow...
What?
They're all coming at once!
Run into the forest!
All these trees ought to slow 'em down!
Or not...
Why, you...!
Stop!
Moron!  Just leave this to me!
Sorry!
We've gotta shake 'em off!
If we try to fight all these guys, we'll be here all day!
Why, you...!
You bastard!
You guys!  You have a long way to go before you can really give us a fight!
A-Amazing...
Who are these guys?
Hey!
You alright?
P-Pretty much...  You guys saved us...
Who are they?
They're causing quite a lot of trouble.  Still, it's okay.
They're nothing compared to Wapol-sama.
Besides, we've got a powerful ally.
We've got Wapol-sama's older brother, Mushroo-sama.
This is quite an impressive ship.
I gotta fix it later.
Hey.  What're you doing?
I found a rather interesting vehicle here...
What're those?
How do you use them?
As always, you eat some pretty awful stuff.
Don't say that, Bro-chan...
You damn maroon!  I told you to call me "Big Brother"!
Sorry, Bro-chan, but you know...
What?
Even though I finally freed you and all,
are we really gonna rebuild the kingdom?
Who the hell do you think I am?
There's nothing the great Mushroo-sama can't do!
Just as I'd expect from you, Bro-chan!
Still, I gotta say, it's a shame that
Blackbeard-guy left.  I wanted to beat him myself.
I want to have a bit of fun for myself too...
Wapol-sama!  This is awful!
What's up?
Doctor Kureha has taken up residence in Drum Castle!
What's that?!
That ancient hag is living in my castle?!
In that case, how 'bout we shoot her down to teach her a lesson?
Using these.
But the castle is too far away...
Just as I'd expect from you, Bro-chan!
That's perfect for striking a bit of fear into the citizens!
Very well!  Let's chomp on!
Yes, Sir!
You damn maroon!
I told you to call me "Big Brother"!
After all this time?
Sorry, Bro-chan!
As long as you get it, it's fine.
It's terrible!  Everybody!  Run!
He's... They've returned!
They're coming here right now!
Him?!
You can't mean...?!
It's Wapol!  Everybody!  Run away!
Wapol?!
They're not chasing us...
No way...
We've gotta get away, Luffy!
G-Get away?  Where to?
Anywhere will do!  Just somewhere far away!
It's an avalanche!
Is this...?
Everyone!  We've got to get out of the village!  Hurry!
The village is gonna be buried!
Hey!  You two...
Huh?
Listen up, Luffy!  Your first priority is Nami-san, your second priority is Nami-san!
Third and fourth priority, Nami-san, fifth priority is also Nami-san!
Protect her even if it kills you!
Understood!
But how?
Over there!
Get on top of that cliff!  We gotta get as high as possible!
Right!
Here it comes!
We made it!
We're not high enough!
That was close!
We're safe...
But if this keeps up, we'll end up at the bottom of the mountain!
You're kidding!  After getting all the way up here...
Oh, crap!  It's a boulder!
We're gonna crash!
No way!
Ladies must be treated with delicate care.
Sanji!
Sanji!!!
We're done for!
Over here!
What a sight to behold!
Right, let's march on!
Yes, Sir!  All troops, advance!
I'll definitely get you there!
Don't die, you two!
Damn... That was a little too close.
What kind of guy drives straight into an avalanche?!
The coastline is in that direction, right?
What?  We've been climbing higher into the mountains!
None of this would have happened if you hadn't suggested we "take this for a little ride"!
That doesn't mean that you had to drive it so carelessly!
We've completely lost track of where we are!
Whatever.  Let's just look for the village that Luffy and the others went to.
It'll be easy to get to the ship from there.
Guess you're right.
Looks like I was carried a fair distance.
Where am I?
Here...
I can't...
see the top.
Julie!  Rosario!  Where are you?!
Please, answer!
How could he?!
Delicious!
The houses in this village taste absolutely fantastic!
Ah, this is boring!
Oh!  What's up, Bro-chan?
You damn maroon!  I keep telling you to call me "Big Brother"!
Sorry.  I won't call you that any more.
This is such a letdown.
I thought that something more impressive would happen.  We only buried one village!
In that case, Bro-chan...
How about we try using that?
We'll take that device we were gonna use on Blackbeard and launch it at the citizens!
Oh no!  They're gonna use that on the citizens?!
Just look at those hateful eyes.
It'd be better to wipe out everyone who might defy me, the king of this country!
Not a bad idea at all.
Launching the bomb I've been carrying in here might be pretty fun too.
Right, Bro-chan?
But how're we gonna launch it?
We've only got one shot.
And I doubt those cannons will do the job...
Well... Ah, I know!
There's a huge cannon up in the castle.
And while we're at it, the old hag is up there too.  So it's perfect!
I got you.
Right, men!  We're gonna resume our advance on the castle!
Yeah!
Everyone, prepare yourselves!
Man, you saved me!
I'm so glad to be alive!  Thanks, Robin.
Still, am I imagining things, or is my face swollen?
It's frostbite.
Really?
Yes.
So, you're safe?
Oh, Dalton.
I see you're safe too.
You're...
Oh, Usopp-kun.
Hey, what's with the long pause?!
It's the village!
Yay!
Mom!
Thank God!
What's going on?
There sure are a lot of people gathered here...
Hey, what's happening?
The Twenty Doctors have appeared!
Huh?  Who're they?
The doctors who surrendered to Wapol's authority.
But what are they doing here?
Please!  We've come to tell you something important!
Don't mess with us!
That's right!  No way we'd trust you guys!
Just hurry back to that damn Wapol!
We have no place to return to.
We escaped from Wapol.  We were prepared to die trying!
We are doctors, after all!
Even though we had to bow to his might,
we only continued our work for the sake of the people!
It was because a certain quack doctor told us to never give up.
This foolish man told us... that all was not lost.
Everyone, please listen calmly to what we're about to tell you.
We have no time to waste.
Wapol intends to launch Mushroo's Spore Bomb from the castle...
and cover the entire island in poison gas!
What?!
Did you say Mushroo?!
Poison?!
Oh, no!  Luffy and the others are in trouble!
Wait, so are we!  We've gotta do something!
We've no choice but to run!  This island is done for!
No!  We're gonna stop them, one way or another!
Even if it costs us our lives!
Dalton-san...
But we don't have any decent weapons...
Besides, how are we gonna get to the castle?
What are you doing here, Twenty Doctors?
You betrayed us, didn't you?!
Can we climb the mountain with that?
Yeah.
Why, you...
Please wait, you three!
If you must go, then take this with you!
I'm sure it'll be useful!
What's that?
It's an antidote.
It's made from ingredients that are unavailable on this island, so there's only a small amount...
but we'll give it to you.
It's the result of our continued research and hard work.
Right, I understand.  Thank you.
Doctor... Doctor... Doctor!
Sanji!
That was close!
Hang in there... We're almost there!
Wapol-sama, is this really okay?
If you use the Spore Bomb-
You don't get it, do you?
Why do you think I went out of my way to save my brother?
Wasn't it to stop Blackbeard?
Well, that too, but this country needs to be ruled by striking fear into the people.
For that, my brother is the perfect choice.
Can't this damn hippo run any faster?!
That's it!  Get going!
Go, go!
I'm glad we have that stupid brother of mine...
Thanks to him, everything will go just as I've planned.
If I make everyone beg for the antidote, I can easily control the population.
Whether they opposed me or supported me before.
What?!  They're not here anymore?
That's right.  Two of them left, carrying the sick one with them,
and then the other two left, just a little while ago.
Where were they going?
Up there.
The mountain?
Will they really be alright up there?
Hey.
Yeah.
Oh, that's right!  You two had better run away as soon as possible!
Something terrible is about to- Huh?
Don't you die now!
Hang on for just a little longer!
What a beautiful... castle.
D-Doctor...
This guy's got frostbite all over.
This one's covered in blood.
Six broken ribs and a damaged spine...
Mind if I treat him?
Sure, do whatever you want, Chopper.
Anyway, the worst case is this girl...
She's on the verge of death.
What?
You got something to say?
They're my friends...
Friends?
What... is that?
Ya happy?
Your fever's starting to go down, girl.
38 degrees... We're getting there...
Who are you?
I'm a doctor.  Name's Doctor Kureha.
Call me Doctorine.
Doctor?  Then, were you the one who...
You wanna know the secret behind my youth?
No, I wasn't asking about that...
I just treated you, 's all.
It was that youngster who carried you all the way here.
Oh, how are the two of them doing?
They're sleeping in the next room.  They sure are a tough pair.
I see.
You sleep too.  You're not completely healed yet.
Thank you.
But my fever's gone, so...
Take a look.
What's this?
This is the culprit.  You were bitten by a Keschia bug.
They call it the Five-Day Illness.
Once its saliva enters your body,
you're subjected to hellish suffering for five days.
Judging by the rash,
I'd say you were bitten about three days ago.
Of course, after five days, you wouldn't have suffered any more.
Huh?
If those five days had passed without treatment,
you'd be dead.
You understand now?
If you do, then you should get back to sleep.
At the very least, you have to stay here for two more days.
Um, can I ask you one more question?
How long does it take for a Log to set on this island?
A Log?
Oh, is that what you call it?
Why do you want to know?
We weren't planning to come to this island,
so I'd rather not lose our way to the next one.
I see.  I'd guess it takes about a day.
What?!  Then we've got to set sail at once!
The only time I release a patient of mine...
is when they've recovered, or when they die.
I won't let you leave.
No way...
Wait up, meat!
Don't eat him yet, Luffy!
I'll cook him up!
Cut it out, humans!
I said don't eat him!
Wait up, you!
The deer from before, it's talking!
What a surprise.  They can move around already?
They were just on the brink of death.
What is that?  That walking stuffed animal thing?
Oh, him?  His name's Chopper.
Chopper?
He's just a blue-nosed reindeer who ate the Hito Hito Fruit and gained human abilities.
A reindeer?
He's a doctor, too.
I've taught Chopper everything I know about medicine.
Gotcha!
Right!
You two, that's...
Oh, Nami!  You're all better, huh?
What a relief, Nami-san!
I'm just about to cook you some revitalizing food.
I'm...
not food!
He took human form!
Hey... He's...
A monster.
He's a talking reindeer...
And he was so small, then he turned huge...
He's a monster.
Awesome!
Damn kids!
You plannin' to make a mess of this entire room?!
Granny?
I'm still a healthy 139-year-old!
Die, ya damn brats!
Wait!  I ain't lettin' ya get away!
Sanji!  H-Hey, Sanji!
Yeah?
I've decided!
On what?
That reindeer is a cool guy!
Let's have him join our crew!
Chopper.
Are you trying to hide... behind that wall?
Too slow.  Besides, you're not really hidden at all.
Shut up, pirate!
Oh, and is your fever alright?
Huh?  Yeah, it's pretty much gone.
Still, you have to stay in bed.
Doctorine's medicine works really well, so the fever goes down quickly,
but the infection is still in your body.
You have to take the antibiotics and relax, or...
Thank you.
You've been taking care of me, right?
Shut up!
I don't want gratitude from a stinking human, you jerk!
Are you kidding me?!
You really can't hide your emotions at all, huh?
You people are pirates, right?
Yes.
Real pirates?
Yes, we're real.
You've been out on adventures and stuff?
Pretty much.
Y-You're strong?
Are you interested in pirates?
I'm not!
I'm not, you idiot!
Alright, I get it.  Sorry!
Still...
Then...
Wanna come with us?
To the sea!  Won't you come with us?
If you became our ship's doctor, it'd help us now.
I'd like to get out of here before the Log changes direction...
Don't be ridiculous!  I'm a reindeer, you know!
Think I can go with you humans?!
Because you're a reindeer?
Besides, doesn't looking at me...
scare you?
I'm a reindeer, yet I'm standing on two legs...
I can talk, too...
You want to scare me?
and I've got a blue nose.
So that's where you were, reindeer!
Wait!  Join our crew, monster!
Monster!
I wish they'd just calm down for a little while.
You're not very grateful, are you, little girl?
You planning to steal my reindeer while I'm not around?
Oh?  I need permission to seduce the little guy?
Ya don't say...
Nah, ya don't need my permission.
If ya wanna take him along, then go ahead.
But it won't be easy to convince him.
He has a wound in his heart.
A grievous wound that even I can't heal.
From the moment he was born into this world,
his parents told him that he was a disgrace...
Huh?
It was because of his blue nose.
He always had to walk by himself at the very back of the herd.
And he was just a newborn baby, too...
Then, one day, he ate the Hito Hito Fruit and everyone treated him like a monster.
The other reindeer drove him away by force.
Still, he wanted friends,
so he went down to the village in human form...
W-What is that creature?!
It creeps me out!  It's gotta be the Abominable Snow Man!
Get your guns!  Shoot it down!
It's working!
Damn monster!
Shoot!  Kill it!
He didn't know what he'd done wrong.
Nor did he know who was to blame.
He simply wanted friends, yet they only called him a monster.
He was neither a reindeer nor a human.
He just lived on by himself like that.
Can you heal his heart?
There was one person, though.
Huh?
He opened his heart to one man, long ago.
His name was Doctor Hiluluk...
The quack doctor who gave him the name "Chopper" and treated him like his own son.
Hey!  He ran this way!
He's unbelievable, that Doctor Hiluluk!
Can you believe that guy?!
Just barging into the patient's house and forcing him to take some weird injection!
We were gonna have the Twenty Doctors take a look at him, too!
Found him!  He's over here!
Wait, Hiluluk!
Capture him!
Ya happy, young one?
Ya gonna put me to sleep?  How's that gonna help ya?
That's a sedation gun, ain't it?
There's nothing scarier than an incompetent doctor.
How many people are afraid of the common cold because of you callin' yourself a doctor?
Hmph!  I don't wanna hear that from some heartless doctor who barely looks at her patients,
before snatching away their money...
That's just my style.
Oh, and did you hear?
Apparently this country has no doctors left except you, me, and the Twenty Doctors.
I won't be caught by the Doctor Hunt.
Just watch, my medical research will save this country!
Oh, really?  Sure you don't actually mean that it'll destroy the country?
There's someone on the bridge!
Did the Abominable Snow Man from earlier come back?!
Shoot it down right now!
There's nobody here...
Where'd it go?  Find it!
Who're you?
Were you shot by a pistol?
If we don't stop your bleeding soon, you're gonna die.
Don't look at me like that.  It's alright, I'll help you.
Still, what are you?
You don't look human...
Oh, I see.  You're that Abominable Snow Man they were talking about.
Monster!
Shoot!  Kill it!
I got it!
Not yet!  It's still breathing!
Damn bastard... Don't mess with me!
Who the hell do you think I am?!
Hey!  Wait!
I would...
never shoot you!
My name is Doctor Hiluluk!
I'm a doctor!
Y-You can talk?!
Why'd you stay silent for three whole days?
I thought you'd hate me if I spoke.
When I try to talk to people, they shoot at me.
So what if you can talk?!
Don't brag about something like that!
I can talk too, you know!  A lot better than you, too!
Run away, Chopper!
Chopper?
It's gonna explode!
That was close!  I failed again, huh?
Hey, Chopper!  Are you alright?
Why are you calling me Chopper?
Tony Tony Chopper.
You're a reindeer, and those horns of yours look like they can chop down trees.
It's a nice name, right?
That's what I'm gonna call you.
Chopper...
Well then, I want to start the experiment again, but I suppose we gotta clean up first!
Give me a hand, Chopper!
Sure!
Still, what can I say?
You're an outcast, just like I am.
But you shouldn't hate humans.
This kingdom is sick.
The hearts of the people are ailing.
Society might claim that there's no such thing as a sick country,
but they're wrong.
Listen up, Chopper!
There's a tale that goes like this...
In a kingdom far off to the west, there was a great burglar!
He was suffering from a terrible heart condition.
He used his stolen money to be treated by the best doctors, but even so...
not a single one could cure him.
It was an incurable disease.
The man believed that he would soon die and wandered off in turmoil...
After a long while, he reached a mountain where he beheld a wondrous sight.
What do you think he saw?
Cherry blossoms!
He saw an entire mountain of brilliant cherry blossoms.
Three months later, he went to see the doctors, and they were shocked.
This is what they told him:
"You're completely healthy!"
That's right!  He'd been healed!
He had recovered from an incurable disease!
It was a miracle... No, that's not all!
There's no doubt that it was a miracle,
but seeing the cherry blossoms must have triggered a sort of change in the man's heart!
This is an excellent medicine!
It cured a supposedly incurable disease!
Amazing, right?
That means there's no such thing in this world as an incurable disease!
I will save this kingdom as a doctor!
That's why I've raised this skull against every disease there is!
Skull?
That's right!
This is a symbol of conviction that defies the impossible!
With this flag raised, I will fight like a pirate!
Pirate?
That's right!  A pirate!
Chopper, you should rest back in the house.
You're still injured.
It won't be my fault if your wounds reopen.
They won't reopen!
The wounds will decide for themselves whether they're gonna reopen or not.
I'm alright!
I'm not so sure...
Dad!
Get lost, quack!
Damn, another failure!  I thought for sure that lizard-eyes would work!
I'll be taking these!
Hiluluk stole my money!
Don't be so greedy, damn snob!
It's the soldiers!
Chopper, we're gonna use a decoy strategy!
What do you mean?
There!
Take care!
Get real!
I told you that you couldn't come with me!
What kind of doctor would kick his own patient, you jerk?!
I could've died!
Go ahead and die, you damn blue-nosed freak!
Don't insult my nose!
Shut up!
You were just going to die before anyway!
What kind of doctor are you?!
Doctor...
That was the first time I've fought anyone.
I suppose so.  You'd need an opponent in order to fight someone.
Then I guess it'll be your first time for this, too.
A present... to make it up to you.
What, you're gonna cry again, reindeer freak?
No way I'd cry!
It's unfair if you turn big!
Take a look, Chopper!  A magnificent sea!
It's huge!
That's right!
This vast sea is filled with the pirates worthy of traversing it!
You should go out to sea someday, too!
If you go out to sea, you'll realize just how insignificant your own troubles are!
Really?
Yeah, it's true!
Compared to the rest of the world, the island you were born on is as small as this!
Really?!
No, smaller!  This one country is as small as this !
Really!
What a wonderful story.
I don't know about that...
Huh?
It's taken a year, but your treatment is finally complete.
Yeah.  Thanks, Doctor!
Then, stay well.
Congratulations on your recovery.
Your wounds have healed.
I don't have to look out for you anymore.
From now on, you should just go wherever you want.
Now, get out!  I've got research to do.
Doctor!
I definitely won't cause any more trouble, so let me in!
I'll make you tea every day, and I'll take care of the cleaning, so please let me stay!
I don't have any friends!  I don't have anywhere to go!
Doctor... Doctor!!!
Look, Doctor!  I'm hurt!
Why, Doctor?
Your wounds have healed!
Get going!  Go out to sea or something!
Never come back here!
Please forgive me, Chopper!
I'm gonna die, aren't I?
Yeah, you're gonna die.
Is there nothing you can do to delay my death?
You still have worldly regrets?
Why don't you just accept the inevitable?  It'd be easier for you.
I still have work that needs to be done.
I only need a little more time.  I want to finish my thirty years of research.
If ya wanna live that badly, why don'tcha go to that kingdom far off in the west?
Just go see those so-called "miraculous cherry blossoms" that saved you back when you were a burglar.
There's no need.
I'm gonna make cherry blossoms bloom in this country.
What a fool.
This is a Winter Island, you know.
There's no way you can make cherry blossoms bloom.
They will bloom!
The medicine I've developed at great cost to my life... will prove that things like that do exist in this world!
Then I should be able to save every human living in this world!
I want to do it here, in the land where I was born.
I'm almost done!
I just need a little more time.
You just don't know when to give up.
By the way, what's with that weird monster following you around?
What?  He followed me?
Yeah.  I think he was trying to hide over there.
I'm the one and only friend he's ever met.
If I were to die right before his very eyes,
what do you think would happen to him?
Do you want him to endure more despair?
So you drove him away all of a sudden, after being with him for a full year?
We're alike.
That's why I'll be sure to tell him in the end,
"There's nothing you can't do!"
I'll tell him by making the cherry blossoms bloom!
Listen up.  I don't have a miracle cure; I can't heal you...
But I can probably trick your body so that it stays alive for another ten days or so.
But unfortunately for you...
you'd have to pay me a fortune for it.
Just hurry up and treat me!
Think you're gonna trick me with this tranquilizer gun?
It's true, you two are just like each other.
You're both so clumsy.
Fine.  I'll treat you.
Then you can show me exactly what kind of change you're gonna bring this country as a doctor.
What happened to the rest of the guards?
Well, they were asked by the Twenty Doctors to look for a mushroom.
A mushroom?
Yeah.  Apparently it's a mushroom that can cure any disease in the world.
Mushroom?
What's that?
Is that...
Yeah, it's the monster who was with the quack doctor.
Get going!  Go out to sea or something!
Never come back here!
Hey!  Wait!
I would never shoot you!
I've done something terrible, huh?
Chopper...
You should at least see my cherry blossoms!
My final work!
Damn you!  I don't have any more time!
Nothing is impossible to a man who flies the skull and crossbones!
That's what I taught you, right, Chopper?
There it is!  Amiudake!
That's it!
But...
How am I gonna get to it?
It's been six days...
Damn it all...
Nothing's come close to the reaction I was hoping for!
Chopper!  You...
What happened to your body?!
Mushroom...
That's an Amiudake, isn't it?!
Please survive, Doctor...
I wanna become a doctor...
Did you...
get that for me?
Teach me how to become one...
I'm a reindeer, but do you think I can do it?
Of course you can, Chopper!
You're so kind, after all!
Hey!  What's going on?!
You're telling me every single one of the Twenty Doctors is sick?!
Please!  My kid has a fever!
Don't complain to us!  Even doctors get sick, you know!
At least hand out some medicine!
You're gonna ignore the patients?!
Don't be a fool.
Give us the Twenty Doctors!
Is the Amiudake soup good?
Awful!
Medicine is supposed to taste bad!  It's the proof that it's working!
I can feel my strength coming back!
Thank you, Chopper!
Doctor...
Listen up.  I'm going out for a while, you should just stay here and sleep.
You're in worse condition than I am right now, after all.
Got it.
Well, see you later.  I'm off.
Doctor was happy.
I cured a sick person.
Hey, Chopper.
You're gonna make a fine doctor.
I guarantee it!
I'm gonna make a fine doctor!
Did you hear, Kureha?  The entire country is in an uproar.
Yeah.  That whole thing about the Twenty Doctors all being sick,
and no one around to treat them, right?
How ridiculous.
Just ignore it, and it'll all calm down.
So what did you come for today?
Actually, I wanted to ask you a favor.
What's this?
That's...
This is it!
I've been waiting for this reaction!
I waited for thirty years!
I did it, Chopper!  My research is a success!
That's thirty years of my life.
It's the research that I finally managed to complete!
A miracle cure that can heal the ailing hearts of the people!
So you've wasted thirty years of your life.
Why are you giving this to me?
It's not enough, and I'm out of time.
I want you to make the cherry blossoms bloom in my place.
Don't be ridiculous!  Why would I do that?!
And one more thing!
Please teach medicine to Chopper!
He wants to be a doctor!
Get real!
There's a limit to how insolent one can get!
He'll definitely become a great doctor!
He's a good guy, and he's got a kind heart!
He risked his life to make medicine for me!
I'm begging you!
Pass your skills on to him and make him a doctor!
You want me to take over your stupid research and that bizarre pet of yours?!
So what if you're about to die?
You should know I'm not about to start feeling sorry for you over that!
Get out!
Yeah, I know.
We've known each other for a long time.
I know perfectly well...
that doctors are all nice people who save people's lives.
Please take care of Chopper.
My medical research will eventually save this country!
You seemed so desperate... That isn't like you.
For you to give up...
I'm out of time.
Did you hear, Kureha?  The entire country is in an uproar.
That idiot!  Don't tell me...
Where's Hiluluk?
You don't have to run away.  I already know about you.
Doctor left a while ago.
He got better, so he's probably headed to town...
He got better?!
There's no medicine that can cure that disease of his!
You heard that back at my house too, right?!
But...
Look! He drank this, so he's alright now!
Is that... Don't tell me that's Amiudake?!
Yeah, it's a miracle cure!
Doctor's going to teach me about medicine!
He'll definitely become a great doctor!
He's a good guy, and he's got a kind heart!
You stupid reindeer!
Listen, reindeer, that mushroom...
It's a deadly poison!
If you eat it, you won't even last half a day!
That can't be true.
I checked the books.
This is a symbol of conviction that defies the impossible!
That's why I've raised this skull against every disease there is!
I mean...
There was a skull drawn next to this mushroom!
Doctor said it himself.  He'd gotten better!
There's no way he'd die... You're a liar!
He was happy about the way you felt...
But that skull...
is a symbol of poison!
That's a lie!
It's not.
There's no medicine in this world that can cure all diseases.
That's why we've got doctors!
Do you understand?  Kindness alone isn't enough to save someone!
If you want to save someone, you've got to acquire the proper knowledge and medical skill!
You can't save anyone if you don't know how!
Did you... get that for me?
Thank you, Chopper!
What a fool you are.
Hey!
Doctor Hiluluk!
Now, prepare the ropeway!  Take me to the castle!
I don't have much time, so hurry!
Every second counts.  Hurry!
Hiluluk will never come back here.
He's decided to make the castle his grave.
I'll continue trying to relieve people's suffering until I die!
Because I'm a doctor!
Wapol-sama!  Hiluluk is coming!
So he fell for the trap?
What a hippo!
That can't be... Why?!
Why would he?!
There he is!  It's Doctor Hiluluk!
Take me to the patients!
I've come to save the Twenty Doctors!
Wh-
What's going on here?!
You hippo!  This is a trap!
As you can see, the Twenty Doctors are doing just fine!
You just came here to die!
You've eluded the Doctor Hunt for long enough!
Defying the king is a horrible sin!
I hereby sentence you to death!  Guards, take aim!
What?!
What a relief... So nobody's sick?
I really thought the country was in danger.
But you were just deceiving me?
If the country really was in danger, I wouldn't want help from someone like you, you damn hippo!
Shoot the rebel!
Drop it.  You people can't kill me.
What?
When do you think people die?
When they're shot through the heart with a pistol?
No...
When they are struck by an incurable disease?
No.
When they drink soup made from a poisonous mushroom?
No!
People die...
when they are forgotten.
Even after I'm gone, my dream will come true.
The ailing hearts of the people will definitely be cured.
Why are you crying, Dalton-kun?
Do you think that works for a kingdom as well?
Sure, as long as someone inherits your will.
A monster will be coming here soon.
He's my son.  Don't hurt him!
Don't worry, Chopper.
Your mushroom won't kill me.
This has truly been a great life!
So long, quack doctor.
Thank you, Chopper.
You're gonna make a fine...
That hippo!  He went and blew himself up!
What a crazy guy!
Wapol-sama!  It's a monster!
Kill it!
Wait!
Get him, Dalton-san!
Kill it!
Leave this place!
If you're mad because he laughed at Hiluluk's death, then I apologize!
But if you don't have the strength to make them see reason, you'll just die in vain!
Please don't...
become another sacrifice for the country!  I'm begging you!
Why so courteous, Dalton?
If you disobey the king's orders...
Silence!
You still don't get it?!
The one and only person who tried to save this messed-up country just died!
So what if that wannabe-doctor just killed himself?
I've realized the path this country is on!
The path to destruction!
What?!
No matter how far our medical research progresses...
Even if we keep researching medicine forever...
There is no medicine that can cure stupidity!
You've said too much, you damned hippo!
You know what happens if you make me angry!
Don't you, Dalton?
Please...
make me a doctor!
I'm gonna become the miracle cure!
I'll become a doctor who can cure any disease!
Because...
Because there's...
no disease in this world that can't be cured!
Please... Please make me a doctor!
Call me Doctorine.
Hey!  Reindeer!
Not in here either, huh?
Where'd that guy go?
A pirate flag?
Doctorine!  Wapol has returned!
I know.  Like I said, today'll be a busy day.
Well, we're here!  This is the first step in rebuilding the Drum Kingdom!
What happened to my servants?
The way up to the castle is tough to travel.
They probably couldn't keep up with us.
I'm sure they'll be here soon.
Wapol-sama!  There's a weird flag flying on the roof of the castle!
What is that?  What happened to the Drum Kingdom's emblem?
I burned that thing.
So, you're here?!  Doctor Kureha, the last survivor of the Doctor Hunt!
You've got a lot of nerve, moving into my castle during my absence!
Absence?  You abandoned the kingdom and ran away!
What was that?!
You see, I've made this castle into Hiluluk's grave.
Get out of this country!
The Drum Kingdom has fallen!
That dumbass doctor's grave, you say?
Don't make me laugh!
Hey!  Hurry up and dispose of this half-dead old hag!
Yes, Sir!
Not happening!
Take this!
Doctorine!
Hey, hey, hey, Afroman!
Launching your afro at a lady... What kind of soul brother are you?
Who the hell're you?!
Just an ordinary pirate.
What the... I can't get it off!
What's with this afro?  Static electricity?
Exactly.  And there's more where that came from!
Hey, reindeer!  Don't just stand there and watch!  Help me!
Uh, alright!
Ugh, this is gross.
It's stuck to me!
You can have it back.
No, don't give it back, dammit!
You could at least take one!
No way!
What're you guys doing?
I should mention that those static moss balls are highly flammable!
Oh, crap!  He's gonna ignite the afros!
We're gonna use a decoy strategy!
Oh, I see, a decoy...
Wait, I'm the decoy?!
Checkmate!
Why, you!
Chopper!
Wapol-sama!
Dammit!
Oh, Sanji!  Did you find the reindeer?
Luffy!  Grab on to my leg from there!
Leg?  Right!
Like this?
Don't you let go now!
I'll try adding some spin, too!
Nasty, nasty...
He's got an injured spine... what did he expect?
Thank you.  You people sure are incredible.
Man, he's tough!
Wapol-sama, are you alright?
Those damn pirates have really done it now!
Huh?  There's some weird guy there...
Hey, Wapol.  Should I lend you a hand?
No... I can't rely on you all the time, Bro-chan.
I'll kill those damn hippos!
I'll show them the true power of the Baku Baku Fruit!
He's up to something!
Don't let your guard down.
If those guys were that weak,
the people would have stopped them from doing something ridiculous like getting rid of the doctors.
Besides, that guy... Wapol's older brother Mushroo...
He's got the power of the Noko Noko Fruit.  He's dangerous.
Noko Noko?  A mushroom fruit?!
Twenty years ago,
when Mushroo was 13 years old,
the king had to leave the country for a World Peace conference...
He detonated a bomb from the castle, just like he's planning to do now,
and killed a lot of people.
He wanted to test his powers because he was bored.
That was the only reason.
When the king returned, he apologized to the people and had Mushroo banished from the kingdom.
After that, Drum established itself as a country of advanced medical science.
But how could one explosion cause all that?
Because of the Noko Noko Fruit.  A horrible power.
A Fatal Bomb.
He's able to release the poison spores stored in his stomach once every 10 years...
And he fired that?
I suppose we were lucky...
Even though the wind was strong, and the poison spread quickly, we were able to survive.
But it's been twenty years since that day.
If he uses his power now...
the explosion will probably be even bigger than the last one.
But he does have one weakness.
I asked the king where he had sent him.
The king told me:
"We couldn't allow him to cause trouble in another country,
so I sent him to the Kingdom of Fire, where his power would be halved,
and asked the king there to restrain him."
The Kingdom of Fire?
Everything I eat becomes part of my body.
Awesome!
First law of the Drum Kingdom:
Anyone who defies the king's will dies.
That law means everything to this country.
After all, this country is my country.
This castle is my castle!
And then...
you had to go and place that wannabe doctor's flag up there!
It's defiling my castle!
The pirate flag...
Hey, reindeer.  Is that flag...
Doctor...
Serves you right!  What's wrong?  You got a problem with that?
What are you doing to the skull mark?!
What's that supposed to mean?
Hey!  Hippo-face!
You understand what it means to shoot a flag, don't you?
What?
He's...
Think I give a damn about such a stupid decoration?
Didn't I tell you?  This is my country!
I'll shoot that thing as many times as I want!
Watch out!  It's dangerous!
Someone like you can't destroy this flag!
The skull mark...
is a symbol of conviction!
That was a direct hit!
You hippo!
See?  It's still whole.
Impossible!  He's crazy!
I dunno who you are, or whose pirate flag this is...
But this is a flag that you pledge your life to!
You don't raise it as decoration!
It's not a flag that someone like you can just laugh at or destroy!!!
So this is a pirate?
Amazing!
Chess!  Eliminate these guys!
Yes, Sir!
Now, just wait a minute.
Wapol.  Go ahead and get things ready.
I'm gonna have myself a bit of fun.
Luffy!
Are you alright, Straw Hat?!
I'm fine.  'Cause I'm made of rubber.
Rubber?  What's that supposed to mean?
To put it simply...
He's a monster.
Look out!
Go!
Get him!
Too bad.
You can't move!
What's this?!
You guys...
Those are...
Poison spores.
You're kidding!
Luffy!
Sheesh.  As soon as we launch that bomb, this'll all be over...
It sure is noisy here... What's going on?
Chopper!
Too easy.
You're late, you damn maroons!
Mushroo-sama, that's...
You know what it is?
A monster who once scared the villagers.
We've got ourselves a pretty weird creature here.
I know how you feel.  Seems you're the same as I am.
Nobody would accept you, and you had no choice but to live your life alone!
What?  You still plannin' to fight?
What're you gonna do, all on your own?
I'm a doctor.  I've sworn on Doctor's flag...
that I'd save the people... Save this country...
Even though I don't have any friends...
You do have friends!
I'm your friend!
You...
I'm impressed that you can still move after inhaling my poison.
It'd be easier for you to just fall over like these morons.
Chess-sama!
Even Kuromarimo-sama...
What're you goin' to do in that state?
I'm sure it takes everything you got just to stand up right now.
Guess there's no choice.  I'll just put you out of your misery!
Stop it!
Go to Hell!
Robin-chwan!
Don't ignore me!
Wait!
Dalton!
Dalton-san...
You still don't get it, do you?
What do you think you should do for this country right now?
There once was a man who only thought of what was best for the kingdom and then died, right here!
You saw it too, right?!
The time of oppression is over!
We can't allow Wapol and the others to stay in this country!
Damn!  How could he do that to me?!
Good thing the snow was there to save me.
You damn maroons!
Alright!
Seems the antidote worked.
Amazing!
Great!
Get him!
W-What?
Nami-san!
That came from inside the castle...
Damn!  Wapol's gone!
Nami-san!
Nami, you alright?
Yes, I'm fine.  I was just surprised.
Thank God!  You've gotten better?
Where is he?
That weird guy went up there...
He said something about a cannon.
What's he planning to do?
It can't be!
You've still got some poison left in you, right?!
Bro-chan!
We're finally here!
You sure they're here?
Beats me.  Anyway, let's head toward that building.
Such a pretty castle.  What's that damage up there?
I wanna fix it!
What're you talking about?
Behold!  This is the miraculous combination of three great powers!
Thought so!
What're you gonna do with that thing?
I'll tell you.  I'm gonna cause a poison explosion like the one twenty years ago...
No, even stronger than that one!  I'm launching a Fatal Bomb!
A Fatal Bomb?!
Drop the ridiculous act!  If you do that-
Yeah, that's right!  I'll kill every single citizen and purify the country!
What?!
Don't act like the death of those people is such a huge deal.
All that matters is that the country will be mine again!
As long as we have our advanced medical system, sick people will always come here, so replacing the citizens will be easy!
Stop it!
Too late!
Such insolence.
So that's it, huh?!
It's released!
Yeah!  Leave it to me!
They did it!
Right!  Everything went according to my plan!
As if.
Someone like you, without any resolve...
has no right to touch someone else's skull mark!
Gomu Gomu no...
No, wait!  I'll give you a title and medals!
Oh, crap!  Everyone, run!
Gomu Gomu no...
Then, you can be the vice-king!
Doctorine... The Drum Kingdom...
This country was defeated by the skull and crossbones.
Reindeer!
Hey!  Reindeer!
Where'd you go?
Don't be ridiculous!
Please!  The Log will reset if we don't leave this island soon!
No can do.  You've gotta rest here for another two days.
As a doctor, I simply can't let you leave.
Can't we work this out?
What's this?
The antidote for the Fatal Bomb.
As a doctor, you couldn't just let someone take it away from here, am I right?
Listen up, girl.  There's a coat hanging in my room,
and I fixed up that youngster's spine. He's lying in the next room.
Don't you dare run away!
So she's telling me to take the coat and run away now?
Hey!  Reindeer!
Let's be pirates together!
So it's a full moon tonight...
Reindeer!
Come out!
I wonder what Doctor would say about this?
Reindeer!
Hey, Luffy, just give up already.
No matter how much you yell or look for him, he's not coming.
He doesn't want to be a pirate.
That's wrong!  I wanna take him along!
That's just what you want!
Reindeer!
Oh, reindeer!  Hey!  Let's be pirates together!
I can't.
Sure you can!  It'll be fun!
You don't get it, do you?
I'm... grateful to you guys.
But I'm a reindeer.
I've got horns and hooves...
And a blue nose...
Can you heal his heart?
Sure, I do want to be a pirate, but...
I can't join a crew of humans!
I'm a monster!
I can't join your crew!
So I've just come to thank you...
Thank you... for inviting me...
I'm staying here, but...
If you ever feel like it...
then feel free to come visit us...
Shut up!
Let's go!!!
Hey, could you give me a hand?
I've got some hard work to do.
We're gonna carry the cannons out from the armory.
Don't just stand there.  Hurry up!
Oh, right...
Doctorine!
I need to talk to you.
Chopper, where'd you go?
Go help carry out the cannons.
Listen, Doctorine!  I'm gonna be a pirate!
I'm gonna go out to sea with those guys and see the world!
Don't be ridiculous!
Who taught you how to be a doctor?
Are you saying you're not grateful to me at all?!
That's not true!  I'm really grateful!
I love this place, where I met you and Doctor!
Then why don't you stay here?!
Being a pirate ain't all fun and games, you know!
You could end up dead at any moment!
I don't mind!
Don't be ridiculous!  Who's ever heard of a reindeer sailing the seas?!
Yeah, I'm a reindeer!
But I'm a man, too!
Good for you...
but I'll never allow it!
If you leave, it'll be over my dead body!
Doctorine... Please understand...
A crybaby like you, calling himself a man?!
I won't let you just do whatever you want!
I won't let you get away!
What the?
I'm sorry, Doctorine.  But I want to see the world!
What would someone like you do, if you did go to sea?!
You gonna live in a fantasy world like Hiluluk did?!
You're wrong!  It wasn't just a fantasy!
Doctor completed his research!
Everyone, get in the sleigh!  We're getting off this mountain!
Wait!
Hurry!  Everyone, get on!
What's wrong?
Look!
The witch's sleigh?
That was great!
There was a rope here?
I guess we couldn't see it because it's white.
Where are we?
Finally awake, huh?
You're annoying.  Go back to sleep.
What was that, damn you?!
Calm down!  I'll fall off!
This is it!
I've been waiting for this reaction!
I waited for thirty years!
Doctor... It wasn't just a fantasy, was it?
Your research was complete, right?
Or was that just another lie?
I did it, Chopper!  My research is a success!
Did you just say that because I'd be sad if you died without saying it?
Nothing is impossible for a man who flies the skull and crossbones...
Say it again, Doctor!
A pet of mine ran away, that's all.
I hate sentimental partings.
We're gonna send him off in style!
Ya ready, youngsters?!
Yes!
Fire!
Whazzat?
Did the old lady snap?
It's coming from the castle.
No way!  Did Wapol win?!
Is he bombing us?!
No, wait.  This is...
Doctor Kureha!  We've launched them all!
Light up!
Listen, Kureha!  This dust is the miracle cure that will heal the ailing hearts of the people!
I decided to use it like this.  Ya got a problem with that?
Doctor...
Doctorine...
Amazing.
Yeah...
Beautiful.
This is the result of my thirty years of research!
You just can't comprehend the thought process of a fool.
Listen, this red powder isn't just ordinary powder!
Once this mixes with the white snow in the atmosphere,
it will cause brilliant...
pink snow to fall!
Now, get lost, my stupid son!