Look at this!
Hey, look!
Voice of the dead.
This is gold.
Gold... Gold...
Oaks!
Get me water...
Water...
Gold...
There is gold for everyone.
Down the river...
Come on this side.
Better not waste time, boys,
go on and give me a hand.
Let's get this down.
It sure is heavy.
Man...
This will make life a lot easier
for all of us.
The answer to everyone's problems
is gold, and we've got plenty.
Secret... in the right moment.
This time we really hit the jackpot.
Oaks! Mind if I butt in your conversation
you're having with yourself.
Let me hang onto it...
I want to cross the border, we've got
to be in Mexico before dark.
I was talking to myself because we
have a lot of gold to talk about.
We sure do. We've each got
a good share coming.
We worked hard for it. What's more,
it's pleasing work.
Lot's of gold, lot's of pleasure,
but now it's time to divide it up.
I don't feel like dividing.
Do you hear that?
He says he don't feel like dividing.
I can't believe my ears.
I'll say it again. I don't feel like dividing.
I've come too far, done too much,
to let anyone else touch this gold.
I've had to put up with the
stinkiest skins.
I don't divide my gold with no
Motherless Mexicans.
Hands up!
What's going on?
Hands up, you two.
Don't let him get away.
Shoot him down.
Tough luck, half-breed.
Guns don't shoot
with no bullets inside.
Dig it wide, dig it deep.
Hey boys, that's a beautiful grave.
Ain't seen one bigger.
You're gonna be real comfortable.
Ain't that right boss?
We work for you, you're going to kill us
without giving us one drop of tequila.
You'll be able to say your prayers
in Spanish, as you lie down to die.
And Gringo won't forbid it.
Have a nice discussion with the devil.
How about your half-breed prayers,
in English or Spanish?
I don't have to pray for salvation,
after I've been killed.
You do, you're a murderer.
I'm pleased to call you my friend, since
you're going to give me your gold.
What is he doing? Quick, shoot him.
Don't let him get away!
You can't leave without horses.
Manchiana, we've got to do something
to stop him. Save the horses.
You won't be going nowhere without
horses, Oaks!
You're scaring the horses away.
Hold your fire.
I must say, you've done a brilliant job.
You won't get away with this, Oaks.
Fire!
With gold bullets.
It is your gold. The gold you died for.
Bullets made of gold are better
than lead. They go deeper.
For you who's seen the flame of death,
gold can be useful to burn your killers.
We stay with you, be your companions.
But, you tell us the hunting grounds
you've seen...
...on the other side of the River of Light.
You who have seen
the land of the dead...
...must give us the wisdom learned
from the mouths of the great gods.
Each thing you remember,
you must tell us these things.
We will serve you and follow you.
No, Uncle! No, Daddy!
No, don't. I'll bite you.
Sure don't look like paradise!
Better than the desert though.
Don't like the looks of it.
Even God wouldn't stay here.
Where would you suggest we go?
It's hot out here and I need a drink.
I'm hungry, fellows, and
when I'm hungry, like I'm hungry...
...I'm not scared of a thing.
You can bet your life on it.
He's right. One town is the same
as the next.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Who's afraid? Nobody's a coward.
I just said I don't fancy the looks of it.
Why don't you shut up!
We ain't got no choice.
And I'm hungry, too.
You stay here with the horses,
and I mean stay.
You go to the store.
You two come with me.
Good morning to all you gentlemen.
First time in these parts.
Great little town you've got here.
You can see it right away.
It's real friendly here.
Are you interested in selling a few
horses? We're heading north.
There's work waiting for us up there.
Most of our horses are head up
with accidents.
They kept getting dizzy from the heat!
So, I said, "Get off"...
...so here we are.
Waiting to throw the cards?
Here you go. Double pair of aces.
I don't see how someone without
a horse can be laughing.
Stop throwing darts, Evan!
Ain't no lack of horses down here,
just money.
No problem there, mister.
We're in the sails of a lot of money.
We're prepared to pay.
Whisky on the run.
You heard him!
The best!
From the looks of it,
you had yourself a long walk.
It's worth a long walk to find work,
if it pays well.
It's real nice to find some people
who work like you, mister.
It's enough to take
one good look at you.
You can see from your expression
you're hard-working and honest.
You're all covered in white dust.
I guess you crossed the desert.
You took the toughest way to get to
an old, lonely town.
Best thing for you.
Hey, now you can sell your horses.
You talk like a businessman.
Well, how about it?
We ain't got time to lose.
I told you, "Horses cost money here".
This is better than money.
That's how I'll pay you.
How many horses do you need?
Nine.
Have you got more of this,
to pay for the rest?
Sure!
I'll do my best to get them for you.
Hey, Richie. Why don't you play
some music for our guest?
Lori, Lori! What are you waiting for?
Come on down. We've got
gentlemen to be entertained.
Let them hear one of your songs.
- Pretty girl
- Real pretty.
And a real voice, too.
Do you want anything else?
No. No, that will do.
Now, let's just see what we've got.
It seems you want a lot of things.
Yeah, we've got a mighty long ride
ahead of us.
We're heading for the north,
getting work.
Beef jerky, sugar, beans, and
2 cases of...
And we're going to need at least
10 boxes of carbon cartridges.
10 boxes! You wouldn't find that much
to hunt in these parts.
Please excuse me. I won't be long.
They're a bandit gang.
You should see the gold they've got.
Hurry up, we've got everything.
Give me a moment!
Don't you get the impression
it's kind of black in here? Unnatural.
That's stupid.
It's just the desert.
We're used to the sun.
Don't move. You're still weak.
I feel a lot better.
I'm stronger than I look.
Can't you make this horse get moving?
He moves more slowly now
because he's old.
How do you ever expect to get there?
The men we're following don't have
water and few horses to carry them.
They will stop in a small town
on the hill.
How much further is it?
Not far. It lies in the next valley,
at the edge of the desert.
What's the name of it?
I don't know what the White man calls it.
The people of the Indian tribes call it
The Unhappy Place.
Hurry, this way.
Follow me. Hurry, come on.
- Come on. Can't let them get away!
- Get moving.
Go on.
Let's go, don't let them get away.
Go! Go!
Watch out!
We got him!
Very good. Don't let him go. Hold him.
Don't let him go!
Help!
- This way.
- Get him!
I got him!
A rope!
Your days are numbered.
Hang him! Hang him!
- Where do we hang him?
- Over there!
He's still alive,
what are you waiting for?
Hold him still, until I get the rope
around his neck.
- Get that rope up there.
- Come on.
- Killer!
- Your career is over!
- Hurry up!
- Take him there, with the others.
Take it and show it to him.
Do a good job.
You won't be scaring
honest people anymore.
God forgive you all.
They'll hang you for this.
Are you ready?
Let's do it together.
There's plenty of spare rope
in this town.
Now, you're supposed to be
hanging these men. Get on with it.
Stop! That's enough!
Look at the blood.
He's dripping like a pig.
They're still moving.
Thieves, murderers...
there's no salvation for you.
Pray for forgiveness to God Almighty.
Hey, one's still alive.
He's cornered.
You'll never get out of that house alive,
Oaks, as long as I'm here.
What's wrong with you?
Ain't there someone with
a bit of courage?
I offer 500 dollars to the man
who gets him out.
Be careful!
I killed him!
What're you doing, stranger?
Do you want to be killed?
200 dollars!
My eyes must be playing tricks.
Watch it, stranger.
It isn't him. It can't be.
Who is it?
Who are you?
How did you get here?
I have to know.
Go on, fire.
You're all supposed to be dead.
Come out from behind there.
Oh my God! He's full of holes,
but he's still alive!
Don't leave him there.
String him up with the rest of them.
Wait. What's going on?
He has some information I want.
There is plenty of time for hanging.
Why wait, Mr. Sorrow? You know
darn well we're going to hang the man.
Pancho.
Yes sir. What is it, Mr. Sorrow?
Get those bullets out of him, and
make sure you bring him to me alive.
Come on, men.
Help me get him out of here.
I didn't know pity was
part of your nature.
You know better than that, Oldeman.
There are a few things I want to find
out concerning those men.
They're a bunch of killers,
murdering outlaws.
We felt that's what had to be done.
But you don't know what I heard.
They couldn't hide much from me.
We got them into justice.
You can have all the justice you like.
I've got to know something...
something more important.
Come on? I've got a little talking and
a little listening to do.
Who have you chosen, Mr. Sorrow?
We can help.
Now, let's see what miracle
that bunch can perform.
We want to know something.
Are you going to stay here or
are you going to move on?
I guess I'll stay.
Take this. Make him drink.
Drink this, it's good for your hair.
Pancho, you have to save him.
He won't do me any good as a corpse.
I'll do my best, sir.
Go on. Do the surgery.
Enough with your screaming.
This is nothing! Keep going, Pancho.
We'll get him back on his feet again...
...and he'll be glad to tell us
his life story.
A horrible story about
crimes and priests.
I don't want to hear it,
I'm leaving.
But I love to hear people's stories.
I'll listen eagerly.
I hope we honorable citizens
turn out to be...
...better than that lying criminal.
No, I'll have my usual raspberry syrup.
Good, Pancho!
You caught it!
He's as good as a doctor.
This is gold!
- Gold?
- Gold!
- Get it!!
Stop it! What's going on?
Get back! I said, get back!
What have you done, you idiot!
You killed him?
I'm sorry, all my life I've been searching
for gold, and this man is full of it.
This bullet is solid gold.
I don't like the kind of games
you're playing.
It's no game.
Gold is a sure way to kill a man.
It's a game, all right...
...and I'd say a very expensive one
for a gunman.
30 dollars a shot.
It sure was an investment.
You're going to give me
those 500 dollars, ain't ya'?
Ah, you're going to pay 500 dollars.
Since when did he get so generous?
It isn't for me.
It is for the public good.
It is worth paying any price for justice.
I wouldn't count on seeing that
money, stranger, if I were you.
It's only gold, isn't it!
All right, stranger, here is your
500 dollars.
That's why you came here...
to collect!
Well, all right. I need a bed.
Pay me tomorrow.
No need to hurry.
Have you got a room for me, boy?
Yes, sir. Right away.
He seems to come from far away,
like every drifter.
What do we do with this?
Listen to me, Templer.
Nobody in this place
gets away with anything.
You were in too much of a hurry
to hang these guys.
The young stranger helped you out.
Now, this one's dead,
and no one can talk.
These outlaws were too dangerous.
No point in waiting to kill them.
I don't care about those gringos...
...only about what they had...
...a whole lot of gold.
That is what I'm talking about.
A saddle full of gold,
not those gold bullets.
Go and get it and bring it to me.
I don't know what they've been
telling you...
...but if there was any of it,
someone has escaped with it.
I'll keep my cowboys wide awake,
as if this were my own land...
...and nobody gets through without
me hearing about it.
Oldeman here is wicked.
Ain't you?
It's not me, but the Lord in heaven
will show us the way.
I'll find it, whatever it is.
Don't you worry about that.
Come on, boys, let's go.
Look, here it is.
Just like I said.
He signs his name with a cross.
I don't understand why
you didn't give him the money.
He didn't want it.
He just wanted to sleep here.
Listen.
Sleeping is very good.
He isn't going to get the chance
to sleep late.
Tomorrow, he can take his dollars
and get out.
I should have known you would give
him the money. You saved it for him.
What about all the things we planned
together?
Don't worry about that.
Finally, you'll marry me?
I don't like being just "your woman".
Sure, Lori, I'll marry you.
You mean it?
Sure! We're getting married
as soon as we can.
Listen. That man just stopped walking.
Be fair. I earned at least
twice your cut.
You must be crazy, Templer.
I was the one who found it.
How would you have hid it,
if I hadn't helped you?
I could have gotten someone else.
Is that so! Who lent you money
all these years...
...that you never paid back?
Listen, Oldeman...
...I've made investments that will be
useful for the whole community.
It is your money,
but what did you do with it?
I spent it building this town,
making it prosperous.
I've paid my interest, and plenty of it.
No man can say
I was anything but honest.
I've always defended the morals
of the folks here.
I was never afraid to teach justice
and the fear of God.
I taught half of them how to pray.
Now, we must divide this gold,
splitting it equally...
...or do you want to cause trouble
and attract Sorrow's attention?
That's your kind of justice, Oldeman.
That's just what I expected from you,
swindler.
You can't fool me,
you low-down chiseler.
Keep your voice down.
This is not enough!
It ain't all yours. This gold is going to
be divided equally.
We'll see about that!
Are you threatening me?
- You're not going anywhere with that!
- You can't stop me taking my share.
- We've already decided what's fair.
- That's mine. I want my fair share.
Either I get my share
or I'm taking all of it.
Who's there?
Mind if I speak with you, sir?
What do you want?
I want to ask a favor of you.
You woke me up.
Is it very late?
Yes, it is, sir.
Well, what do you want?
Speak up.
I want you to take me with you.
With me? Where to?
Anywhere.
That just reminded me.
I have to go somewhere, myself.
You're a brave man...
braver than anyone here.
Take me with you, sir.
Being brave is not important.
Why do you want to leave?
It's awful to be in this wicked town.
I won't spent another night here!
There must be a better place
in this world!
Yeah, I've seen better places, boy.
So, you will take me with you?
I'm not leaving. I'm staying right here.
You better make other plans.
What's your name, boy?
Evan!
Evan! Evan!
What's going on?
Look at what Evan did to
my beautiful clothing.
All the beautiful things
you brought from Denver.
You're son is a monster.
He'll be hanging from a tree like
one of those dirty bandits out there.
Calm down. I'll buy you other clothing.
Not even if you're dead.
You know the same thing would happen.
I wish you wouldn't blame him.
You know it isn't his fault.
Not his fault?
How about when he hit me?
Calm yourself. I'll punish him.
Evan. Evan...
Evan, come here.
Help me cut them down!
We'll help you do your duty.
In this village full of outlaws...
...they have to go free.
They have the entire night to get away.
The desert cools down at sunset
and the nights are cold.
Now, will you tell us?
Tell you what?
What is death like?
We heard there are
many wild beasts to hunt.
We heard the pastures are
full of white buffalo...
...the land is green and fertile.
Hey you! Who told you to cut
those men down?
We want those outlaw killers
to hang there...
...to remind strangers not to even
attempt to break the law.
You'd be warned by that, right?
Did you hear that!
Be careful, so nothing happens to you.
Take this advice, stranger.
Here's your 500 dollars. Take it.
Now, get out of town. Around here,
we don't like folks we don't know.
Make it easy on yourself, stranger.
Get out, while you still can.
Everybody here is a family man,
and we want to keep it that way.
- So you have to go!
- We're talking to you!
My friend, you see there are problems.
You're even helping them!
Are you in need of a horse?
Run, run!
Get it!
No, no. Let me go, please.
Hold him tight!
Hold the boy!
- Shit!
- Stop him!
Leave him alone.
Hey, stranger, get over here.
Don't you know it's dangerous to put
your nose in other peoples' business?
It looked like fun, so I joined in.
Fun is just what they were having.
He was just invited to a party,
and he's the guest of honor.
It'll be a family party.
He doesn't look anxious to
go to your party.
That's exactly the reason
why we invited him.
Why don't you come, too?
I like the tip of your trigger finger.
Isn't it a pity that every time you shoot
a man, you're wasting gold?
Don't you save it for special occasions?
Listen, I've got a proposal for you.
On my ranch, I have living quarters
for a man like you.
Come work for me.
Maybe. It depends on what work
you need done.
Tie him up tight!
Don't be afraid that you'll hurt him.
- Pedro!
- Yes, boss.
Take one of my fastest horses and
visit his father.
Tell him we want all the gold he found
on the outlaws they hung...
...or we'll kill his son.
Also tell him I want all of it soon.
I'm anxious to close this deal.
Sure thing, boss. Right away.
Boys, there will be gold for all of you.
What are your thoughts, my friend?
I myself believe fathers have a
strong love for their sons.
While we're all waiting, let's entertain
our handsome, young guest.
Guarnito! Hurry! We're waiting to
begin the party.
Why not sit down? Go on, sit there.
Make yourself at home, next to me.
Don't my boys have a good time here?
Why don't you join in the fun?
Come on. Drink up. Eat something.
Before you know it, you'll feel
like one of us.
The place, the food, and the drink
satisfy man's basic needs...
...and even more refined sensations,
like crying, for instance.
This doesn't seem right.
You, holding the kid hostage.
I didn't know you were a model citizen.
Come on, you must have broken the
law at some time in your life.
You handle a gun noticeably well,
stranger.
Yeah. I have good reason to practice.
It is unlikely you got all that practice
being an honest, law abiding man.
You'll enjoy being
a member of my gang.
It should be quite obvious.
Mirami, my boys are hard workers...
...so I give them the best of everything.
See for yourself.
I taught them well, to enjoy good things.
If I have to pay the ransom
for my son's life...
...you should help, too.
Why should I?
He's your son.
You pay with your share of the gold.
We're partners.
We share the same secret.
You pay your ransom, not me.
My share is not enough.
They'll kill him.
Don't you see they're determined
to get all of the gold back?
Not my share. That stays with me.
The kid is not my responsibility.
I thought you were my partner.
I am your partner, Templer, but
the boy is yours.
My God, you're scum.
Let me go or I'll shoot.
I'll make you pay.
Where are you? Can't you make up
your mind quickly about the gold?
Take it easy, there.
Help yourself as much as you want.
Tell them they've got 5 minutes
to make up their lousy minds.
- Did he agree?
- No.
He wouldn't give it to you?
No. I couldn't make him understand.
That was our chance to
get our hands on all of it.
You mean, to sacrifice my son?
Can't you see it's only a bluff?
They're just trying to scare you...
I'm not going to take that risk.
The trouble is, you're weak as water.
You'd be a fool, telling them you've
managed to get all the gold.
Deny it! Deny it!
Make them think you don't have it.
Here he comes.
It's no good. He says he doesn't
have the gold.
He asked you to let the boy go.
I have a job for you, stranger.
Carry this kid's corpse
back to his father.
Max! You know what to do.
Wait a minute.
I have an idea how
he can be of use to us.
I'll get your gold.
You want to save the boy,
don't you?
Guess I'm getting old.
All right.
You must first shoot
that rope there...
...the one that ties him to the wall.
I know you're an excellent shot,
so it should be easy for you.
But not so easy after
drinking the rest of this whisky.
How about that?
I want to see if you're a good drinker.
He can get drunk.
Silence! Drinking is like playing.
You need concentration.
Now we'll see what kind of
man you really are.
Pablo.
Stop.
I'll handle this.
Very smart.
You surprised me, friend.
But you should know better...
The boy is still tied up.
I'll give him to you anyway.
Cut that cord!
Hurry up! His life has been saved.
Cheer up, boy, if you want to
please your father.
You should start praying for death...
...because now your life is worth less
than the gold or the sand in the desert.
What's this? A funeral?
Get on with the party.
Who fired a gun?
- I don't know.
- It was a gunshot.
- Where did the shot come from?
- From the stable.
What happened? It was an accident.
He was playing with my gun.
He was looking for trouble.
I know how you must feel, stranger,
after you did your best to save him.
He didn't want to be a man.
What do you mean?
A man must take on responsibility.
A man does what he must do,
and accepts the consequences.
I'd say he died like a man.
My offer is still open to you,
if you want to accept it.
Take him back to town, to his father,
and get all the gold he's hidden.
If he doesn't cooperate,
he'll have visitors.
I'll go, but I don't think
it will do any good now.
I think it depends on you.
Pablo, saddle up that horse.
- You see anyone?
- Not yet.
Why don't they come?
What is it?
The stranger is bringing him in now.
What happened? How is he?
You better prepare yourself,
Templer. It doesn't look good.
Here they are.
Come on, take him.
Take him.
Help me with him.
Come on, move away from the table.
My poor boy, what did they do?
Are you mad?
He was disgusted of a father like you.
Hold him.
What's wrong with him?
He must be out of his mind...
...to have no respect for the feelings
of a father for his son.
Kick him out of here, once and for all.
You'd better give up that gold, Templer.
Or they'll come and get you.
Are you going to just let him
walk out of here?
No, not now.
There is too much wickedness.
They don't know you still have
many gold bullets in your gun.
Son, you must have a lot of faith.
When you finish all your bullets,
you must leave.
We have a common enemy.
You know who I mean.
You must be very careful
of a man like Templer.
He has always threatened me with
violence.
He's come into my house,
where I live.
I didn't think any house in this town
would welcome a guest.
Mine's different. If a stranger comes to
my door, tired and hungry...
...he's always welcome.
Come on, stranger.
Why are you so generous?
Because I'm scared.
I've been threatened.
You can protect us.
I must have protection.
I'll pay you.
I do everything myself.
I don't have any servants.
I don't trust them. They steal and,
there are too many nice things here.
Eat up. I'm sure you're hungry.
You'll get special treatment,
if you'll just stay here.
You won't believe this,
but I treat everybody specially.
An honest person can't sleep well
in this town.
Are you afraid to live alone?
Yes, I am afraid...
...and I've been unfortunate.
I saw a woman up in that window.
You've already seen her?
She's my wife.
But she might as well not exist.
She's unbalanced.
The girl is insane.
I had to lock her up in her room,
poor creature.
She wouldn't harm anyone.
She has the mind of a child.
If anything happened to me...
...Sorrow's men would come around.
What if Templer came here. A man with
no religious principles or morals.
That's why the Lord struck down
his son.
He lives with that woman openly
and they're not married.
Everybody talks about that scandal.
Please say you'll protect us.
I want to go out.
She always does it.
She is always like this.
There is nothing I can do.
We better find that stranger
and kill him before it gets dark.
And see about those 2 Indian men.
We have a fine reason to beat them.
Do whatever you want, but be sure
he's as dead as a doornail tomorrow.
All right, boss, leave it to me.
It's a good bed...
But you don't want to fall asleep.
What's that?
Like this, don't turn it out.
I want you to rest, but stay awake.
I'm exhausted.
You can't stop me from sleeping.
I'm getting up early and hitting the road.
Good night.
I said, "Good night!"
I knew I'd find you in here.
I heard voices and somebody
moving about.
Don't you recognize me?
Sure. I saw you in the window.
You didn't understand the signs
I was making to you.
What were you trying to tell me?
To get out of here. You're in danger.
You don't know what
people are like here.
You're different from them.
You must not stay here.
I've got to save you.
Why do you think I'm in danger?
They are trying to murder you.
Life in this place is worth nothing.
Look at me.
What's your name?
Elizabeth.
Your husband says you are crazy.
He's evil.
He wants me to think I'm mad.
He nearly succeeded.
Why does he want to do that?
Because I fell in love with someone...
I've been locked up ever since.
Then you're not really mad.
I don't know.
What's the matter?
It's just...
There must be someone to love me.
He left your door unlocked?
Why did he do that?
Because he wants me to make sure
you stay to defend his house.
Where's the gun?
Get out of here while there is time.
You haven't kissed me yet.
My love! My love!
What's going on?
It's Sorrow's men!
Arm yourself. Wait at the window.
But don't shoot!
Templer, open up.
We've got to do something.
Hide the gold.
- I know where to hide it.
- Where?
Templer, you can't stop us.
Do you hear?
We're not playing around.
We're coming in.
All right boys, break the door.
You take care of the horses...
...the rest of you get up there
and break that door down.
Go for it!
Have you no respect for the dead?!
The saloon is closed.
We're in mourning here.
Listen to that,
anybody will think it's true.
You know what to do.
Cover every corner of the house.
Templer, either you tell us
where you hid it...
...or we're going to kill you.
You've searched this place from
top to bottom.
You see, the gold ain't here.
It's been taken by that dirty rat,
Oldeman. You'll find it at his house.
If you're lying, watch out.
Quick! They're here. Save me.
Look, they're here!
No! Get away from the window.
Do something. That's why you're here...
to protect me.
Am I suppose to protect
your house...
...your reputation or your wife?
Do you have anything of greater value?
There is light over there.
We'll have fun.
The house is this one.
Oldeman! Oldeman!
We're coming for the gold.
Here it is. Take it. Give it to them,
before they harm you.
You're mad.
Leave her alone.
Come on, Oldeman, open up!
We don't like waiting.
Open!
- Somebody is there.
- Open the door.
Give us the gold!
Don't waste our time.
He's not him, Willy.
It's the gold!
It's the stranger! Kill him.
Get the horses and let's go.
Don't be afraid. It's all over.
She betrayed me...
a servant in my house...
...no better than that.
Damn that half-breed.
I'll show them both...
...together they'll know who I am.
I know I can't help you.
You should try to forget it.
Don't be so sad. You know I love you.
I'm sure I can help.
I can't love you.
I've got to finish what I've started.
I know.
I've always known
that would be your answer.
You'd leave me.
Where is my gun?
I have given you the power to
walk upon serpents and scorpions...
...to withstand the light of adversary,
whoever they may be.
If who so ever among you say,
"I shall be great", shall be small.
Who so ever shall say,
"I shall be first", shall be last.
For the son of God came
among you, not to be served...
...but to serve you.
He gave his life so that you may live.
Amen.
What a day!
Give me a drink.
Rotten thief, now you know what
it costs to double-cross me.
That will fix you and him
at the same time.
He must have taken it
while we were sleeping.
I want to know why.
I better go find him.
What are you going to do when the
others come back to get the gold?
If you want, I'll stay.
No, they'll kill you.
Don't worry.
Go now, and some day
come back for me.
If you don't, I shall die.
- Sure filled him full of holes.
- A good job.
Left his gun behind.
The chamber is empty.
I know this gun. I'm sure I do.
Hey! Wait a minute.
This bullet is solid gold.
It's the stranger! He murdered Templer.
Go and get him.
What are you waiting for?
Lori. Where the devil is Lori?
I haven't seen her.
She's a bad woman.
I'm sure she's got
something to do with this.
Better get going.
Take your guns.
Yes, let's go. Come on!
Hey, mister. Hey, you!
Come here.
Listen, I'm terrified.
I want you to help me.
They're going to kill me.
Oldeman has killed Templer.
It was awful.
I managed to get away. I saw him do it.
I saw him kill Templer.
Where did he do it?
In the saloon.
We just came from the funeral.
Now he wants to kill me.
I'm in danger because I saw him do it.
I don't stand a chance in hell
against Oldeman.
He's a highly respected citizen.
He can kill me and
make it look perfectly legal.
Would you like to be rich?
What do you mean by that?
Exactly what do you want me to do?
I know where he hid
all of Templer's gold.
If you help me get it, we'll split it.
Where is it?
At the cemetery. In Evan's coffin.
I don't have the courage to
get it myself...
...but there is enough gold down
there to do things that...
Listen here. If anyone tries to
open that boy's coffin...
...I'll make sure he's shot.
Haven't you done enough?
That gold belongs to Evan.
But we need it to leave this place.
We've got to get out of here
before they kill us.
Your life is in danger as well as mine.
What do you think of this baby?
All right, are you ready? Let's go.
Come on, hurry up!
Now we'll see some action.
You heard him. Get going.
If you want to sleep in your beds,
then find those two.
Make sure they won't do any more
harm in our town.
Let's get rid of him.
Search everywhere.
Let's stay together.
Look everywhere.
Hey, his friends are here.
Oh, those Indians... they always hang
around with him.
There they are!
Those dirty Indians!
They'll know where he is.
They always do.
Let's make them talk.
Let me get my hands on them.
Kill him.
Don't shoot him. It's a sin.
I always wanted the scalp.
A perfect job!
A perfect hairdresser.
Well done.
It was so easy.
They're coming to get you.
You must hide.
How many of them are there?
The whole town!
Let's go!
Hold it, stranger.
You can't get away this time.
Come on, Willy, stop.
This man is ours.
Now you'll have to answer to
Mr. Sorrow.
Where is he? What have you done?
Your precious lover?
Sorrow's man took him away and
tortured him to death.
I thought you'd be pleased.
I'll deal with you later.
Come here.
You'll never get out of here alive.
Hold it. We don't want him unconscious.
You're very stupid...
...when you could have taken
advantage of my offer...
...to become one of my boys.
We could be friends, but you prefer
to go your own way, don't you?
You are going to tell me
where that gold is.
You made a mistake.
An elementary mistake.
Now, you're gonna have to pay.
Mr. Sorrow doesn't like to be cheated.
You'll tell me even if
I cut your tongue out.
Carlos, go and prepare our
persuasive little pets.
We'll have to get going,
but you won't be lonely.
I'm going to make sure
you have nice company.
Do you like the company of snakes
or blood-sucking vampire bats?
Rats can also be good company.
You won't be lonely.
Carlos, let's wish him a good night.
Come on.
It's useless, Sorrow.
You can't scare me.
You don't know me.
We'll see. We'll see.
I've made stronger men than you
tell me everything.
You'll change your ideas soon.
Come on, Carlos.
Sleep easy.
Willie, Canada, Carlos.
Come on, all of you.
We can get going!
Our prisoner has been
persuaded to talk.
We know where
the gold has been hidden.
Search everywhere.
Go now. Go!
The cemetery... the cemetery.
Having a good time with your friends?
Interesting, isn't it?
It's better than any party.
The cemetery...
If everything goes as planned,
they should be back before dawn.
Don't you want a drink?
How did you get here?
You don't believe that this is just
for playing music?
That's right, corporal.
A drink! A drink!
All right, you dirty, old drunk!
It's a pity you don't understand
what my boys mean to me.
They make me so happy
in their black uniforms.
Drink, you feathered sponge.
You'll like it.
Damn it. There's no gold in there.
We've been tricked.
It must have been here.
We've got to find that gold!
Go on. What are you waiting for?
Open every grave. Get going.
Dig! Dig!
Dig, damn it.
We've got to find that gold.
Dig! We'll find that gold if we have to
tear up every grave in this cemetery.
Give me the explosives.
Take as much as you can.
Come on, let's go.
Here, take this.
Here they come. Go, go.
It's the Boss's horse. Get him.
Stop him.
Go the other way.
Get him.
Something's wrong.
I finally got him.
Damn you.
What have you done, maniac?
It's burning. It's the upper floor.
Everything is burning.
How did it happen?
I hope no one is inside.
You'd better come out quick.
Move yourself, come on.
We must pray. Can any of you get
down on their knees and pray?
I've never seen a fire like this.
What a shame.
It was a beautiful place.
He was proud of it, wasn't he?
There's no point in letting a house
burn down like this.
I won't give you 2 bits for it.
Did you hear the screams?
You can't get close.
Fortunately it's isolated.
Or the whole town could've burnt down.
Let's get out of here.
It's too dangerous.
It can collapse any moment.
Look at me!