Hey.
Look at this.
Look.
It is the voice of the dead.
This is gold.
Oaks.
You won't get away with this, Oaks!
Give me water.
Water.
Gold.
There's gold for everyone.
Gold...
Down at the river.
It's cold as anything in here!
Sure, it's cold as anything.
Get your pants on.
Hell, come on this side.
It's deep here!
Come on in!
That feels nice and fresh!
You need a bath.
This side is deeper.
Come over here and see.
Hey, run for cover!
Take cover! Take cover!
Get down!
Come on, hurry up!
Get out of the way!
They're all around us!
How many are there?
We better not waste time, boys.
Come on, give me a hand.
Let's get this down.
Sure is heavy.
Let's have a look.
Yahoo!
This'll make life a lot easier for all of us.
The answer to anyone's troubles is gold,
and we got plenty of it.
The secret is knowing the right moment.
This time we really hit the jackpot, huh?
Oaks, mind if I butt in
on the conversation you're having...
...with yourself?
Let me in on it.
I want to cross the border.
We've gotta be in Mexico before dark.
I was talking to myself because I've
got a lot of gold to talk about.
We sure do.
We each got a good share coming.
We worked hard for it.
What's more, it's pleasing work.
Lots of gold and lots of pleasure,
but now it's time to divide it up.
Well?
Don't we?
I don't feel like dividing.
You hear that?
Says he don't feel like dividing.
I don't think I can believe my ears.
I'll say it again.
I don't feel like dividing.
I've come too far,
done too much...
...to let anyone else
get their hands on this gold.
I've had to put up
with the stink of your skins.
I don't divide my gold
with no motherless Mexicans.
Qué pasa?
Hands up, you two.
Shoot! Shoot! Don't let him get away!
Shoot him down!
Tough luck, half-breed.
Guns don't shoot with no bullets inside.
Dig it wide. Dig it deep.
Hey, boys, that's a beautiful grave.
Ain't seen one bigger.
You're gonna be real comfortable.
Ain't that right, boss?
We work for you...
...and now you are going to kill us
without giving us one drop of tequila.
You'll be able to say your prayers in Spanish...
...as you lie down to die.
How 'bout your half-breed prayers, huh?
In English or Spanish?
I don't have to pray for salvation
once I've been killed.
You do.
You're a murderer.
I'm pleased to call you my friend,
since you're gonna give me your gold.
Hey!
Catch that man!
Don't let him get away!
Kill him!
What's he doing?
Quick, shoot him down!
Don't let him get away!
They can't leave without horses.
Jack! Montana! You gotta do something
to stop him! Save the horses!
You won't be goin' no place without horses, Oaks.
The horses are getting away!
You're scaring the horses away!
Hold your fire.
I must say, you've done a brilliant job.
You won't get away with this, Oaks!
Fire!
With gold-made bullets.
It is your gold.
The gold you died for.
Gold bullets better than lead.
Go deeper.
For you who have seen
the ﬂame of death...
...gold can be useful
to fire at your killers.
We stay with you.
Be your companions.
But you tell us
of happy hunting grounds you've seen...
...on other side of river of life.
You who have seen the land of the dead...
...must give us the wisdom you have learned
from the mouths of the great gods.
If you remember and tell us these things...
...we will serve you and follow you.
Give up? Give up!
No, please, Uncle Max!
No, don't! I'll bite you.
I'll bite you!
Sure don't look like heaven.
It's better than the desert though.
You're not aimin' to stay here?
Don't like the looks of it.
And where do you suggest we go, Collins?
It's hot out here and I need a drink.
I'm hungry, fellas, and when I'm hungry
like I'm hungry, I ain't afraid of a thing.
You can bet your life I'm not.
He's right. One town's the same as the next.
There's nothin' to be afraid of, Collins.
Who's afraid?
Nobody here's a coward.
I just said I -
I don't fancy the looks of it.
Why don't you shut up?
We ain't got no choice.
I'm hungry too.
You stay here with the horses,
and I mean stay with 'em.
You go to the store.
You two come with me.
Make them horses drink slow,
Charley, if you don't want 'em to bust.
Good morning to all you gentlemen.
Great little town you got here.
First time in these parts.
You can see right away
it's real friendly here.
Any one of you interested
in selling a few horses?
We're headed north. There's work waitin' for
us up there, but we can't walk all the way.
Most of our horses met with accidents.
Kept gettin' dizzy from the heat.
So I said crawl or hop.
So here we are.
Stop throwin' darts, Evan.
Come on, put 'em down.
Let's see what you got.
No, no. First put up your money.
Ain't no lack of horse meat here.
just that they cost money.
No problem there, mister.
We earned ourselves a lot of money,
and we're prepared to pay.
Whiskey all around.
You heard him.
The best.
From the look of you,
you had yourself a long walk.
It's worth a long walk
to find yourself work to do...
...if it pays well.
It's real nice to meet some people
who work like you, mister.
It's enough to take one good look at you.
You can see from your expression
that you're hardworking and honest.
You're all covered in white dust.
I guess you must have crossed the desert.
You took the toughest way
to get to my old hometown, huh?
Best way for you, huh?
Now you can sell your horses.
You talk like a businessman.
Well, how about it?
We ain't got time to lose.
I told you, horses cost money here.
This is better than money.
That's what I'll pay you with.
Well, how many horses
do you have to have?
Nine.
You got more of this to pay for the rest?
Sure.
I'll do my best to get them for you.
Hey, Richie, why don't you play
some music for our guests, huh?
Florie. Florie!
What are you waitin' for?
Come on down.
We got gentlemen here to be entertained.
Let 'em hear one of your songs.
♪ My town is so nice ♪
♪ My town, my town ♪
♪ There ain't no other;
♪ On the map ♪
How about that?
She's a pretty girl. Real pretty.
A pretty voice too.
Uh-huh.
♪ I want to tell you, stranger ♪
♪ 'Cause you're new on the scene ♪
♪ I want to tell you ♪
♪ That this town ♪
♪ Is the best thing around ♪
♪ My town is so nice ♪
♪ My town is the best ♪
Do you want anything else?
No, no. That'll do.
Now let's just see what we got.
It seems you want a lot of vittles.
Yeah, we got a mighty long ride ahead of us.
We're makin' for the north
to begin work there.
Dried salt beef, sugar...
...beans, two cases of...
And we're gonna need at least
10 boxes of carbine cartridges.
Ten boxes?
If you went hunting you wouldn't find
that much to shoot in these parts.
Please excuse me.
Won't be long.
Hello, Alderman.
And good day.
You should see the gold they got.
They're a bandit gang.
Hmm.
Huh?
♪ My town is so nice ♪
♪ My town ♪
♪ I know you'll be staying on forever;
♪ Tell you once ♪
♪ And remember ♪
♪ That your time ♪
♪ May be limited ♪
♪ My town ♪
♪ ls so nice ♪
♪ My town, my town ♪♪
Don't you get the impression
it's kind of black in here?
Sure don't seem natural.
That's stupid.
It's just the desert.
We've become used to the sun.
Don't move. You are still weak.
But I feel a lot better.
I'm stronger than I look.
Can't you make this horse
get a move on?
He move more slowly now because he is old.
How do you ever expect to get there?
The men we follow have no meat or water,
and few horses to carry them.
They will stop in small town over hill.
How much further is it?
Not far.
It lies in next valley at edge of desert.
But what's the name of it?
I not know what white man call it.
The people of the Indian tribes
call it the Unhappy Place.
Hurry. This way. Follow me.
Come on, hurry!
Can't let 'em get away.
What are you waiting for?
Get 'em!
We can't let them get away!
Hold him. Hold him.
Keep him down!
Hold him!
Hurry up!
Stop him! Stop him!
Hold him still while I get
this rope around his neck.
Get that rope around there.
Come on.
Come on, get a move on.
Mother of God forgive you all.
May they hang you for this.
There's plenty of rope to spare
in this town, and little else.
Now you're supposed to be hanging
these men, so get on with it!
Thieves, murderers-
There's no salvation for men like you.
Pray for forgiveness to Almighty God.
That one there is starting to dance.
Get out your harmonica, Slim.
He looks like a fish out of water!
Hey! There's one still alive.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Yeah, what are you waiting for?
He's getting away!
He's gone around the corner!
Go this way!
Go around the other side!
Get down over there!
Come on!
Get under cover.
Get down!
He's cornered.
You'll never get out of that house alive, Oaks,
long as I'm here.
What's wrong with you?
Ain't there someone here
with a bit of courage?
I'll offer $500 for the man who'll get him out.
My eyes must be playin' tricks.
It isn't him.
It can't be.
Who is it?
Who are you?
How have you got here?
I have to know!
You've come back from hell!
Go on, fire!
You're all supposed to be dead!
Why don't you come on out
from behind there?
My leg. My leg!
Don't leave him there.
String him up with the rest of'em.
Wait.
What's goin' on?
It's Sorrow.
Wait, I said. Put him down.
You heard me.
This man interests me.
I want him alive.
He has some information I want.
There's plenty of time for hanging.
Why wait, Mr. Sorrow? You know darn
well we're gonna hang the man anyway.
Pancho!
Yes, sir.
What is it, Mr. Sorrow?
Get those bullets out of him,
and make sure you bring him to me alive.
Come on, men.
Help me get him out of here.
I didn't know pity was part of your nature.
You know better than that, Alderman.
There are a few things I want to
find out concerning those men.
They're a bunch of killers-murdering outlaws...
...and we done what we felt had to be done.
But you don't know what it is I heard.
We just brought them to justice.
They couldn't hide much from me, Mr Sorrow.
By God, you can have all the justice you like.
I got an eye skinned for something
much more important.
Come on, Willy.
I got a little talkin'
and a little listening to do.
Do as you choose, Mr. Sorrow.
We can help.
That's wise of you.
Now let's see what miracles Pancho can perform.
We want to know something.
Are you going to stay here or move on?
I guess I'll stay.
Here. You won't feel a thing.
Go on, do it.
Stop yelling, you coward.
Keep going, Pancho. Hurry up.
He'll be better in no time, right?
And he'll be eager to tell us his life story.
A horrific story full of crime and murder.
I refuse to listen.
I love autobiographical memoirs.
I can't wait to hear them.
I hope our word of good citizens will carry a
lot more weight than the lies of a criminal.
No, Tern pier.
I'll have my usual raspberry syrup drink.
Good for you, Pancho. You got it.
He's as good as a real doctor.
But this is gold. Gold!
Gold?
What are you doing? Stand back!
Back!
Pancho, you idiot!
You didn't have to kill him, did you?
I'm sorry, sir, but all my life
I've searched for gold...
...and this man is full of it.
Bah!
Ahh.
This bullet's solid gold.
Yeah, they shot him full of gold, Mr. Sorrow.
I don't like these kind of games you're playing.
It's no game.
Gold is a sure way to kill a man.
It's a game, all right...
...and I'd say a very expensive one for a gunman.
Thirty dollars a shot.
Sure. It was an investment.
You're, uh, gonna give me that $500,
aren't you mister?
Since when did he get so generous?
You're gonna pay $500?
It's not for me, Mr. Sorrow,
but for the public good.
Justice is worth paying any price for.
I wouldn't count a lot on seeing
that money, stranger, if I were you.
It's only gold, isn't it?
All right, stranger.
Here's your $500.
That's what you came in here to collect.
Well, right now what I need's a bed.
Pay me tomorrow.
There's no hurry.
You got a room for me, boy?
Yes, sir. Right away.
Listen to me, Templer.
Nobody in this place
gives anything away for nothing.
You can be sure of that.
You were in a little bit too much
of a hurry to hang those guys.
And that young stranger helped you out.
Now this one's dead,  and no one can talk.
Those outlaws were much too dangerous.
No point in waiting to be killed.
I don't care about them gringos.
Only what they had.
A load of gold- that's what I'm
talking about and what I want.
Saddlebags full of gold.
Not those gold bullets either.
Go get it and bring it to me.
I don't know what they've been telling you...
...but if there was any,
someone has escaped with it.
I keep my cowboys wide awake...
...and since this is my own land, nobody goes
through it without my hearing about it.
Alderman here is a witness.
Aren't you?
It's not me that's the witness,
but the Lord in heaven who showed us the way.
We'll find it, whatever it is.
Don't you worry about that.
Come on, boys! Let's go.
Look. Here it is.
Just like I said.
He signed his name with a cross.
Bill, I don't understand why
you didn't give him the money.
He didn't want it.
Just wanted to sleep here.
Listen.
Not sleeping very good.
Well, he's not gonna get the chance
to sleep late.
Tomorrow he can take his dollars and get out.
I knew it. I suppose you're gonna
give all the money we saved to him.
How about all those things
we planned together?
Don't you worry yourself about that.
You mean you'll marry me? I don't
like being just your woman.
Sure, Florie. I'll marry you.
You mean it, Bill, don't you?
Sure. You know I do.
Soon as we can.
Listen. That man stopped walking.
Be fair. I ought to have
at least twice your cut.
You must be crazy, Templer.
Well, I was the one who found it.
Uh-huh. How would you have hidden
it if I hadn't helped you?
I could have gotten
someone else to do that.
Is that so? And who's lent
you money all these years...
...that you never paid back?
Listen, Alderman.
I made investments that could be
useful to the whole community.
It's your money, but what did you do with it?
I spent it improving this town, making it prosper.
I paid you my interest, and plenty of that.
No man can say I was anything but honest.
I've defended the morals
of the folk here always.
I've never been afraid to teach the
way of justice and the fear of God.
I taught half of them to pray.
Now we must divide this gold,
split it equally.
Or do you want to cause trouble
that will attract the attention of Sorrow?
Is that your kind of justice?
That's just what I expected, you swindler.
You can't fool me,
you low-down chiseler!
Keep your voice down, Templer.
It's not enough.
It's all you'll get.
This gold is going to be divided equally.
We'll see about that.
Are you threatening me?
You're not goin' nowhere with that.
I'm taking my share.
We decided what that is.
Half! That's what it is.
Stay where you are.
Get out of my way.
It's mine! I warned you.
Leave it where it is.
You can't stop me taking my share.
Nothin'! That's your share.
My share is half. Half!
Do you hear?
Who's there?
Mind if I talk to you, sir?
What do you want?
I want to ask you a favor.
You woke me up.
Is it very late?
Yeah, it is, sir.
Well? What do you want?
Come on, speak up.
I wanted to ask you to take me with you, sir.
With me?
Where to?
Doesn't matter where.
That reminds me.
I've gotta go somewhere too.
You're a brave man.
Brave as anyone here.
Take me with you, sir.
Being brave's not important.
What makes you want to get out of here?
It's awful being in this wicked town.
I won't spend another night here.
There must be someplace better
in this world.
I've seen better places, boy.
Then it's all right?
You'll take me with you?
I'm not leaving.
I'm staying right here.
You better make other plans.
I'm sorry.
- What's your name, boy?
- Evan!
Evan!
Evan! Evan!
What's goin' on?
Just look what Evan did
to my beautiful clothes!
Your son just ruined all the beautiful
things you got me in Denver.
Your son, he is a monster.
He'll end up hanging from a tree,
like those dead bandits out in front.
Calm down.
I'll buy you lots of new clothes.
No, even if you did, you know
the same thing would happen.
I wish you wouldn't blame Evan.
You know it isn't his fault.
Not his fault? He hates me
and I can't make you see it!
Calm yourself. I'll punish him for it.
Evan. Evan!
Evan!
Come here. Come here.
Help me cut 'em down.
We'll help you do your duty.
The spirits of these outlaws have to go free.
They have waited all through the night.
The desert cools after sundown,
and the nights are cold.
Now will you tell us?
Tell you what?
How is death.
We heard that there are
a great many wild beasts to hunt.
They tell us the pastures are full of
buffalo and the land is green and fertile.
Hey, you!
Who told you to cut those men down?
Did you hear that?
We want those outlaw killers to hang there...
...as a reminder to strangers
not to try and disobey our orders.
You be warned by that.
Did you hear that?
Better be careful,
and nothing will happen to you.
Take his advice, stranger!
Here's your $500. Take it.
Now get out of town.
We don't like folks we don't know here.
Make things easy, stranger.
Go while the going's good.
Um, you see, we got problems, my friend.
Uh, even up in... heaven.
So you are in need of a horse.
Quick! Catch the black one!
No. No, no. The brown.
Go with the wind!
No! No!
Let me go. Please!
Please!
No.
- Oh, no!
You're hurting me!
Leave him alone!
Hey, you, stranger.
Come over here.
Do you know it's dangerous to stick your nose
in other people's business around here?
But it looked like fun,
so I thought I'd join in.
Fun's exactly what they were having.
They were just inviting him to a party
He's guest of honor.
He doesn't look anxious to go to your party.
That's the reason we asked him to come to it.
Why don't you come too?
I admire you for your gun play.
Though it's a pity you waste all that
gold every time you shoot somebody.
It's only on special occasions I use 'em.
How about listening
to a proposition I'll make you?
On my ranch there's room for a man like you.
Do you want to work for me?
Maybe I do.
Depends what you want done.
Tie him up tight.
There ain't no need
to be afraid of hurting him, Max.
- Pedro.
- Yeah, boss?
Take one of my fastest horses.
Pay a visit to his father.
Tell that idiot we want all the gold they
found on those outlaws that they hanged.
I am bargaining for the life of his son.
And you can tell him, Pedro,
I want it all soon.
I am anxious to make this deal.
Sure thing, boss.
Right away.
Boys, there'll be gold for all of you.
What do you think, my friend?
I am a great believer
in the affections of a father.
But while we're all waiting,
it'll be amusing...
...to entertain our handsome young guest.
Juanito!
Johnny, we are waiting to begin the party.
Yes, señor I'm bringing
Put it over here.
Why not sit down?
Go on, sit there.
Make yourself at home next to me, won't you?
You see what a good time
my boys have here?
Why don't you join them
in their entertainment?
Larry had a big piece. Get outta the way!
Let me at it!
Pick it off of the table, will ya?
Come on, drink up, eat something, and before
you know it, you'll feel you're one of us.
The pleasures of food and drink
satisfy men's baser senses...
...and open the way
to more refined sensation...
...like crime, for instance.
It don't seem right to me...
...you holdin' that kid here as a hostage.
I'd never have suspected you were a moralist.
You must have broken the law sometime.
You handle a gun too good, stranger.
I have good reason to practice.
It's most unlikely
you got that kind of practice...
...being an honest, law-abiding man.
You'll have fun being a member of my gang.
It should be quite obvious.
Mira, amigo.
My muchachos are hardworking,
yet look what I give them...
...the best of everything, amigo.
You can see for yourself.
I taught them well to enjoy good things.
Tastes good.
If I have to pay the ransom for my son's life,
I think you should pay it too!
What have I got to do with it?
He's your son.
You'll pay with your share of the gold.
We're partners in
this, share the same secret.
You'll pay the ransom, not me.
My share is not enough.
They'll kill him.
Don't you see?
They're determined to get all of it.
Not my share of the gold.
That stays here.
The kid's not my responsibility.
I thought you were my partner.
I am your partner, Templer,
but the boy is yours.
My God, you're a rat.
You leave me be,
or I'll shoot you.
I'll make you pay.
Where are you?
Can't you make your
minds up quick about the gold?
Take it easy there.
What's your big hurry?
Help yourself
to as much as you want.
You can tell them they got five minutes...
...to m-make... their lousy minds up.
Did he agree?
No.
Wouldn't he give it you?
I couldn't make him see reason.
It was our chance
to get our hands on all of it, Bill.
You mean you'd let them kill the kid?
Bill, can't you see it's only a trick?
That's all!
They're just trying to scare you
into giving in to them.
I'm not going to risk that.
The trouble with you is,
you're weak as water.
You're being fooled into telling them you
managed to find the gold. Deny it, deny it!
Make them think
you don't have it, Bill.
Here's Pedro.
It's no good.
He says he doesn't have the gold.
He asked you to let the boy go!
I have a job for you, stranger.
You can carry this kid's corpse
back to his father.
Lex! You know what to do.
Uh,wait a minute.
I have an idea how he can be useful to us.
I'll get your gold.
You want to save the boy, don't you?
For the gold.
All right.
But you gotta win him.
You must first shoot that rope there,
the one that ties him to the wall.
I know you are an excellent shot,
so it should be easy for you.
But not so easy after you have drunk
what's left of this whiskey, mmm?
What about it?
Now let's see, shall we,
just what kind of a man you are.
I'll handle this.
Very smart.
You surprise me, amigo!
Very smart indeed.
But you certainly should know better.
The boy is still tied.
I'll give him to you anyway.
Cut that cord!
Cheer up, boy.
If you want to please your father,
you should start playing at being dead.
Now your life is worth less
than the golden sand in the desert.
Well, what is this? A funeral?
Get on with the party.
Evan!
Evan.
Who fired a gun?
On your feet!
He committed suicide
'cause there was no one standing guard.
Kid must have taken my gun.
Damn fool to do a thing like that.
I know how you must feel, stranger,
after you did your best to save his life.
He didn't want to be a man.
What do you mean?
A man who can take on responsibilities...
...a man who does what he must and accepts it.
I'd say he died a lot like a man.
My offer is still open to you, if you'll accept it.
Take him into town and get that father of his
to give me all the gold he's got hidden.
If he won't, he'll have visitors.
I'll go, but I don't think
it'll do any good anyway.
I think it will. It depends on you.
Pablo, saddle up a horse.
You see anyone?
Not yet.
Why don't they come?
Templer!
Well, what is it?
The stranger is bringing him in now.
What happened?
How is he?
You'd better prepare yourself, Templer.
It doesn't look good.
Florie!
Here they are.
Oh, my God.
Here. Come here.
Evan.
Take him.
Help me with him.
Come on.
Move away from that table.
Evan.Evan.
Evan, my son. Oh, God.
My poor boy.
What did they do to you?
Are you mad?
Get your hands off me!
What's up with him?
He must have gone out of his head not to
respect the feelings of a father for his son.
We gotta kick him out of here once and for all.
You've gotta give up that gold, Templer.
Or they'll come and get it.
You're letting him just walk out of here?
No, not now.
There are too many witnesses.
They do not know that you still have many
golden bullets to shoot from your gun.
Son, you must have much hate.
When you have finished all your bullets,
you will leave here.
We have an enemy in common,
you and I.
You know who I mean.
Templer is a man to beware of.
Be careful.
He's already threatened me with violence.
Say, come into my house.
This is where I live.
I didn't know there was a house in this town
where they welcomed guests.
My house is different.
If a stranger comes by, tired and
hungry, he's always welcome here.
Come on in, stranger.
How come you're so generous?
Because I'm scared.
I've been threatened.
You can protect us.
I must have protection.
I'll pay you.
I do everything myself.
I have no servants.
I don't trust them.
They steal things.
Too many good things here.
Eat up. I'm sure you're hungry.
I'll treat you special if you stay here.
You won't believe this,
but I treat everybody special.
You appear to live alone.
I feel like I do.
I've been unfortunate.
I almost wish I did.
I've seen a woman at the upstairs window.
You've seen her already?
Yeah.
She's my wife.
But she might as well not exist.
She's unbalanced.
You understand?
The girl is insane.
I've had to lock her in room, poor creature.
She wouldn't harm anyone.
She has the mind of a child.
If anything should happen to me...
Sorrow's men might come around,
and they're dangerous.
And imagine if Templer were to come here.
He's a man with
no religious principles whatsoever...
...a man without scruples or morals.
That's why the Lord struck down his son.
He lives with that woman openly
and they're not married.
It's a scandal everyone talks about.
Please say you'll protect us.
She is always like this.
There's nothing I can do.
We'd better find that stranger
and have him killed.
And find him before dawn.
And see about those two Indian men.
We'll have to find a reason to beat them up.
Do whatever you want, but I must be sure
he's dead as a doornail by tomorrow.
All right, boss, leave it to me.
I'll do it.
It's a good bed, this.
But you're not to fall asleep.
What's that?
Like this.
Don't turn it out.
I want you to rest, but stay awake.
I'm exhausted.
You can't stop me from going to sleep.
I'm getting up early tomorrow
morning and hitting the road.
Good night.
I said good night.
Hmm?
I knew I'd find you in here.
I heard voices and someone moving about.
Don't you recognize me?
Sure. I saw you at the window.
You didn't understand the signs I made to you.
What were you trying to tell me?
To get out. You're in danger.
You don't know
what the people are like here.
You're different from the others.
You mustn't stay here in this place.
I must try to save you.
What makes you think I'm in danger?
They'll try to murder you, I'm sure.
Life in this place is worth nothing.
Look at me.
Uh, what's your name?
Elizabeth.
He says you're crazy.
He's evil.
He wants me to think I'm mad...
...and he's nearly succeeded.
Why does he want to do that?
Because I fell in love...
...with someone fine...
...and I've been locked away here ever since.
Then you're not really mad.
I don't know.
What's the matter?
It's just...
...that I must have someone to love me.
He left your door unlocked.
Why did he do that?
Seems odd.
Because he wants me to make sure
you stay awake to defend his house.
Where's he gone?
Get out of here while there's time.
You haven't kissed me yet.
My love.
What's going on?
It's Sorrow's men!
Arm yourselves, all of you.
And wait at the windows. But don't shoot!
Open up, Templer!
Templer, if you don't open up this door,
we'll break it down!
We've got to do something.
Hide the gold.
I know where to hide it.
Where?
Templer, you can't stop us!
Can you hear me, Templer?
We're not playing around. We're coming in!
All right, boys, break the door down!
You take care of the horses.
The rest of you, get up there
and break that door down.
Templer, we're coming in!
Have you no respect for the dead?
The saloon is closed.
We're in mourning here.
Listen to that.
Anybody’s think it was true.
You know what to do.
Search every corner of the house.
Well, Templer...
...are you gonna tell us
where you've hidden it...
...or do we kill you?
You're searching this place from top to bottom...
...and you can see the gold just ain't here.
It's been taken away.
It's been taken away
by that dirty rat Alderman.
You'll find it in his house.
If you're lying, Templer, watch out!
Quick! They're here! Save me.
Look. There they are.
Get away from the window.
Do something. That's why
you're here- to protect me.
What am I supposed to protect...
...your house, your reputation
or your poor wife?
Isn't there anything of greater value?
That's the house, all right.
Alderman, we're coming for the gold!
Your friend Templer gave you away.
We know you've got it, so let's have it
before we burn your house down.
Here it is. Take it. Give it to them,
my love, before they harm you.
You give that here!
You're mad!
Leave her alone!
Come on, Alderman! We know
you've got it in there! Open up!
Come on, Alderman!
There's somebody in the window.
We don't like waiting, Alderman!
Give us the gold!
It's the stranger!
Shoot him! Go on! Fire!
Get back.
Fire at that man!
Kill him!
Kill the stranger!
Get to the horses! Quick!
Get on your horses!
Come on!
Back off! Get on the horses!
Don't be afraid.
It's all over.
It's all right.
She's betrayed me.
A servant in my house.
No better than that damned half-breed.
I'll throw them both out together.
Then they'll find out who I am.
Can't I help you?
You should try to forget it.
Don't be so sad.
You know I love you.
I'm sure I can help.
Nobody can help me.
I've got to finish what I started.
I know.
I've always known that'd be your answer.
You'll leave me.
Where's my gun?
“I have given you the power...
...to walk upon serpents and scorpions...
...and to withstand the might of your
adversaries, whoever they may be.
Whosoever among you
shall say I am great, he shall be small...
...and whosoever among you shall say
I am the first, he shall be the last.
For the Son of God came among you
not to be served, but to serve you...
...and he gave his life that you may live.”
All right, lower the coffin.
What a day.
Give me a drink, huh?
It's so hot.
Rotten thief.
Now you know what it costs to double-cross me.
That'll fix you and him at the same time.
He must have taken it while we were sleeping.
I want to know why.
I've gotta go find him.
What are you going to do
if the others come back to get the gold?
If you like...
I'll stay.
No. They'll kill you.
Don't worry.
Go.
And one day come back for me.
If you don't, I shall die.
Sure filled him full of holes.
Did a good job.
The stranger left his gun behind.
The chamber is empty.
I know this gun.
I'm sure I do.
Hey, wait a minute.
This bullet's solid gold.
It's the stranger's.
He murdered Templer.
Go get him.
Well, what are you waiting here for?
Florie. Where the devil is Florie?
Haven't seen her.
She's always been a bad woman.
I'm sure she's got something to do with this.
Better get going. And don't forget your guns.
Yeah, let's go. Come on!
Hey, mister! Hey!
You! Come here!
Listen.
I'm terrified.
I want you to help me.
They're gonna try to kill me.
Alderman has killed Bill.
It was awful.
But I managed to get away.
I saw him do it.
I saw him kill Bill Templer.
Where'd he do it?
In the saloon.
We'd just come back from the funeral.
N-Now he wants to kill me.
I'm in danger because I saw him do it.
I don't stand a chance in hell against Alderman.
He's a highly respected citizen.
He'll have me killed
and make it seem legal.
Would you like to get rich?
What do you mean by that?
Just exactly what do you want me to do?
I know where he hid the gold.
All- All of Templer's.
If you'll help me to get it, we can split it.
Where is it?
At the cemetery.
In Evan's coffin.
I haven't the courage to get it myself,
...but there's enough gold in there
to do things that-
Listen here. If anyone tries to open
that boy's coffin, I'll see they get shot.
Haven't you done enough?
That gold belongs to Evan.
But we have to have it to leave this place.
And we've got to get out
before they kill us.
Your life's in danger as well as mine.
What do you think of this baby?
Not bad!
Looks like Alderman's getting anxious.
All right.
If you're ready, let's go.
Come on!
Now we'll see some action!
You heard him.
Get going.
If you want to sleep safe in your beds,
find those two...
...and make sure they do no more harm in our town.
Hey, there's
a friend of his here.
Who? The stranger?
Oh, those Indians.
They always hang around with him.
Hey. Anyone knows where he is,
they ought to.
Let's make them talk.
Come on, huh?
Let me get my hands on them.
Well, come on.
On your knees! You dog!
Don't shoot.
It would be a shame.
I've always wanted a scalp.
Done!
A perfect success!
Well done. Aren't I
a good hairdresser?
- You're a real pro!
- I heard him go “plop”!
Hurry! They're looking for you.
They want to kill you.
Where's your friend?
They killed him.
Give me that rifle!
Hold it, stranger!
You can't get away this time!
Now you'll have to answer to Mr. Sorrow.
Where is he?
What have you done?
Your precious lover boy is dead.
Sorrow's men took him away
and tortured him to death.
I thought you'd be pleased to hear that.
I'll deal with you later.
Get in.
You'll never get out of there alive.
Hold it!
We don't want him unconscious.
I'm gonna tell you something.
You've been very stupid
not to take advantage of my offer...
...to make you one of my muchachos.
We could have been amigos.
But you preferred to go
your own way, didn't you?
You're gonna tell me
where that gold's hidden.
You'll tell me,
if I have to cut your tongue out.
You made a mistake.
How could you?
How could you make a mistake
as elementary as all that?
Now you're gonna have to pay.
Mr. Sorrow doesn't like to be cheated.
Carlos, go prepare our persuasive little pets.
We have to get going,
but you won't find it lonely.
I'm gonna make sure
you have nice company.
What do you like, the company of snakes...
...or blood-sucking vampire bats?
Rats can also be good company.
You won't feel lonely.
Now I'll wish you good night.
Come on.
It's useless, Sorrow.
You can't scare me.
You'll never get me to tell you.
You don't know me.
We'll see. We'll see.
I've made stronger men than you
tell me everything.
You'll change your ideas soon.
Come on, Carlos.
Sleep easy.
Carlos! Willy! Nico! Miguel!
You can get going!
We know now
where the gold has been hidden.
Our prisoner has at last
been persuaded to talk.
The cemetery.
The cemetery. The cemetery.
Having a good time with your friends, amigo?
Interesting, ain't it?
It's better than any party.
The cemetery.
Don't you want a drink?
If everything goes according to plan,
they'll be back before dawn.
How did you get in here?
You don't think
this is just for playing music.
That's right, Corporal.
Go for the throat!
Gimme a drink!
A drink!
All right, you dirty old drunk!
It's a pity you don't understand
what my muchachos mean to me.
They make me so happy
in their black uniforms.
Drink, you feathered sponge!
You like.
More! I want more!
Damn it, there's nothing in here!
We've been tricked!
But it must be here.
We've got to find that gold!
Go on.
What are you waiting for?
Open up every grave!
Get going.
Dig, damn it, dig!
We've got to find it! If we have to,
tear up every grave in this cemetery!
Dig, damn it!
Hurry up! Find that gold!
Get your backs into it!
Hurry up!
Come on! Let's go!
We need explosives.
Here.
Take as much as you can carry.
Come on. Hurry up.
♪♪ Here. Take this.
They're coming back.
Come on. Let's go.
Here they come! Go!
Hyah! Hyah! Hah!
Hey, that's Sorrow's horse!
Where?
Come on!
Get outta here! Come on!
The time has come, Sorrow!
It's time! it's time!
The time has come!
Too late!
Too late. Too late.
Damn you.
Missed me! Missed me!
Elizabeth!
Whole darned building's in ﬂames!
It's gone too far.
We can't stop this now.
I hope there's no one inside!
If there is, we'd better get 'em out quick.
Move yourself!
Come on!
We must pray!
Get down, all of you, and pray!
Can't you?
What a shame.
It was a beautiful place.
Proud of it, wasn't he?
He sure was.
But there ain't no point
in having a house that burns like this is.
I wouldn't give you two bits for it.
Look there! It's all gold!
I'm uglier than you!