lf you don't break your ropes
while you're alive,
Do you think ghosts will do it after?
Lee Jong-hyuk, So li-hyun
Kim Young-joon,
Choi Seong-min, Lee Ye-won
Park Choong-sun
DARK FOREST
The three suspects arrested and
taken into custody last March
for the murder of the writer Yoo ll-han
were transferred to the National
Mental Hospital yesterday afternoon
The court' ...
l'm sorry Jeong-ah.
l promised Mother that l won't
pass on this cursed gift to you.
Listen to me, Jeong-ah.
From now on, you'll be seeing
a lot of things you don't want to see.
Sometimes, even the deaths of
people you love.
What are you talking about?
But it can't be helped.
This is the only way to save you.
What' going on, Seon-ah?
One day,
when you're in my shoes,
you'll understand.
l just hope that will never happen.
What are you doing!
A bad dream?
Yes...
Did you know...
...that the last thing a person sees
before he dies becomes
his whole memory?
ls that so?
Then my memory will be of you.
Now, we'll be meeting our climbing team.
First up is Mr. JEONG Woo-jin,
the captain of this team.
Don't you have anything
to say for our viewers?
Who me?
Ah, nice to meet you.
l'm Woo-jin.
BlG BROTHER Woo-jin
Uh, actually l'm the chauffeur,
not the captain
Well, our captain' sense of humor
doesn't do justice to his good looks.
Now, Ms. KlM Jeong-ah,
our number one female member.
Hey,
WlTCH Jeong-ah
leave me out of this.
Smile for the fans!
Now! Our one and only ladies man
Mr. LEE Jun-hu
This is Jun-hu,
TOMCAT Jun-hu
waiting for
all you lonely ladies out there.
l mean really,
that' sooo cheesy.
What do you mean?
This is all a part of a grand scheme
Scheme? What scheme?
Scheme to break girls hearts?
Me? l didn't mean that...
For your viewing comfort,
we'll skip to the next team member
LONELY Seung-heon
Mr. JEONG Seung-heon is so shy
that he' refusing to talk to us.
Well, that' it for our climbing team.
TWlNKlE Se-eun
This has been OH Se-eun reporting
from Hangyeryeong.
- Seung-heon?
- Yeah?
Don't l look like a real TV reporter?
Sure.
Here.
You keep saying you'll quit...
l know...
Since it' no smoking in the forest,
l'm really going to quit this time.
This is the last one.
Really.
- l have your word.
- Yeah.
What are you writing?
You'll know
when you use them all up.
Keep smoking if you're curious.
Then l guess.
l'll just have to keep on smoking.
You are hopeless.
Hey, haven't we spent too much time
on the road?
Yeah, let' hurry up.
What do we do?
Hey, this isn't the only way in,
you know.
Yeah? Where else?
The entrance by the stone pagodas.
l thought they closed it off
last year after the forest fire.
No, from what l've heard,
they just sealed off the entrance.
You wanna bet?
What shall we do?
Let' ... just go back.
Go back my ass
Come and see for yourself.
There' another car besides ours.
l told you so.
What' up?
Can you see anything?
You surprised me!
Hey, Miss Reporter!
How about carrying some of the bags?
You won't need it unless you get lost
so don't look so touched.
You... You want me to get lost?
l know you're only here because
Jeong-ah asked you to, so cut it out.
Stop making others uncomfortable.
You are the only one who
finds me uncomfortable.
Hey but still...
We need at least two bottles
for all of us...
You are a raging alcoholic!
All right, all right.
l was just going to take one anyway.
Hey, be careful.
Be careful.
We are just getting started.
Keep up.
Wow nice! Turn the angle around
a bit and it'll look great.
- Shit!
- No? Then never mind.
Hey, look, stone pagodas.
Yes, right.
Hey, 10,000 won for anyone
who can hit it with a stone.
- OK?
- l'm in!
Okay.
Se-eun...
what?
Don't ...
You can't just throw things for fun at
what might be someone' ardent wish.
Like anybody would care.
Shall we go?
Hey, let' do it.
Yeah!
Nice...
You...
Jun-hu, about Jeong-ah,
what' up with her?
Oh, typical PTSD. You know,
the post-traumatic stress disorder.
After losing her sister in a car crash,
she hallucinates from the shock.
What about that freaky incident
l've heard about?
Well,
Jeong-ah thinks that was a divination,
not a hallucination.
As a matter of fact, Jeong-ah' sister
was a famous medium.
Then is she... possessed?
Possessed?
l don't know about that.
But after her sister died, Jeong-ah does
say some extraordinary things.
You know, the other day...
How are you holding up?
l'm fine...
Look at your shoes.
lt makes you look silly.
Well, you know...
lt' good to be out in the nature
lt' refreshing and feels great.
How about you, Seung-heon?
Huh?
Yeah, sure.
We should come more often.
Whatever you say.
l know it' hard but try to keep up.
Yeah, l'm fine.
- Ow!
- Se-eun!
- Are you okay?
My ankle...
l don't think it' serious but l don't think
she can keep going either.
l can carry her down on my back.
That' even more dangerous.
We can't go down, and we can't go up.
Bear with me, okay?
This isn't just for show, you know.
l guess we'll just have to camp around
here tonight.
What?
You... you want to camp here?
That' the only thing to do
in this situation.
Fresh air...
Glad you joined us?
Well, yeah, sort of...
Happy birthday!
You got me a birthday present?
Yeah, they say a knife brings good luck.
Good luck...
But... but... how did you know
it was my birthday?
Woo-jin told me, of course.
He shouldn't have...
Thanks for the present anyway.
Anyway, Jeong-ah.
What do you like most
about my brother?
Well, l like him for who he is,
not for a specific reason.
For who he is... Yeah, me too.
You like him for who he is,
not because he' your brother.
What are you talking about?
You liar!
Did you know that you touch
your eyebrows when you are lying?
Eye, eyebrow?
l don't touch my eyebrows, never.
One thing' for sure, he really cares
about you and he really loves you.
Did you guys know that
you can set vodka on fire?
Yeah, whatever.
l mean it, you wanna bet?
Stop betting, you never win anyway.
That' just who l am.
Hey, isn't it strange?
You know the forest fire last year
was supposed to be one of the worst.
lt burnt for three days straight.
Yeah, the forest must have grown
back really fast.
The trees and the plants look
more lush than ever.
That' right.
lt' as if the forest is
saying that 'you can never kill me.
Oooh... you're right.
lt' a bit spooky.
This forest lost its soul to the fire.
Lost its soul?
They say that the souls
of people who die
in forests are doomed
to wander forever.
That' bullshit.
What do you think, Jeong-ah?
Sometimes, unexplainable things happen
in this world.
Do you think
l'm too hard on Seung-heon?
l don't mean to
but l'm not sure...
l shouldn't interfere,
but maybe
you should try to understand him more.
He could be so much more,
but l think he' intimidated by you.
l thought he was going to
get some water.
What' keeping him?
He should be back soon.
What' wrong, Jeong-ah?
lt' Jun-hu, oh my god, Jun-hu.
What' wrong with Jun-hu?
Man, that was embarrassing.
Woo-jin.
Jun-hu' in danger.
What do you mean he' in danger?
l think...
Something' happened to him.
Jeong-ah, what are you saying?
That kind of things don't happen.
You still don't believe me.
lt' not a question of believing
or not.
You don't have to believe me.
Let' go find him anyway, please?
Let' go.
Be careful.
Where is everybody?
This isn't fun. l'm bored
What' happened to him?
Jun-hu! Jun-hu!
Jun-hu...
Jeong-ah, are you okay?
What' wrong?
Oh no, l think we're too late.
Too late for what?
l think Jun-hu...
he' had an accident.
Jeong-ah, please,
that' your imagination
running away again.
No, no...
Se-eun!
Se-eun, Se-eun' also in danger!
Se-eun?
That' it for our climbing team.
This has been OH Se-eun reporting
from Hangyeryeong
What is that?
This has been OH Se-eun...
Who is it?
ls it you Seung-heon?
Jun-hu?
Stop playing around.
Right now, l'm ...
Seung-heon.
What do we do?
Seung-heon is...
What' up?
Where have you been?
Where' Se-eun?
ln her tent, probably.
What, what' going on?
l don't know...
Jun-hu' gone too.
What do you mean he' gone?
Get your stuff together.
What are you going to do?
We have to find Se-eun
and Jun-hu.
Would, wouldn't it be better if...
lf we just went and
called the police?
No, we can't leave
without Se-eun and Jun-hu.
What?
But... but you saw it too.
Someone else' here...
All right.
Then you go down and get help.
l'll go look for Se-eun.
l, how can l go alone?
Seung-heon, please!
Seung-heon, we'll leave after
we search for them, okay?
Yes, Seung-heon,
we'll search for a while
and if we can't find them,
we'll go, okay?
Se-eun!
- Se-eun!
OH Se-eun!
Se-eun!
Who...?
l heard her voice.
This way!
Who are you?
Help!
Jun-hu?
Hey, it' me. Se-eun.
What' wrong?
What... what are you doing?
l've lost her.
Woo-jin...
Can we go now?
Seung-heon, l know you're tired but
let' look for them a little longer okay?
l... l'm scared.
When will you grow up?
Woo-jin?
Why do l have to do
everything for you?
What? l... l never asked you to!
Then try to act like an adult!
All right, from now on,
l won't say anything
so you don't have to worry about me.
Seung-heon! Slow down!
Mind your own business!
What the hell' matter with him?
Woo-jin...
Did you hear that?
l can hear something
Woo-jin, can't you hear me?
Seung-heon, l said slow down!
Woo-jin, l said this way,
where are you going?
Woo-jin!
Where the hell did he go?
Seung-heon!
- Seung-heon!
Woo-jin, l'm sorry.
Woo-jin!
Where are you?
Seung-heon!
Are you okay?
Seung-heon! Seung-heon!
Jeong-ah... Seung-heon
my little brother...
lt' weird, Woo-jin...
l don't feel anything.
What' wrong Jeong-ah? l'll believe,
l'll believe anything you say.
What' going on?
What happened to Seung-heon?
l think Seung-heon...
he' still alive.
Yeah, he can't be dead right?
Let' look for him.
He can't have gone far.
- Seung-heon!
- Jung seung-heon!
You want to rest a little?
lt' all my fault.
Woo-jin...
Seung-heon is fine...
Don't give up.
When we were little...
You know the boy scouts?
l used to envy the big boys wearing
cool uniforms
and camping in forests...
So l went into a forest one night
with Seung-heon.
But on the way back,
Seung-heon hurt his leg
l had to go get help
So l left him alone
Once l came out,
l got scared.
What if Seung-heon died?
What should l tell Mom?
My parents asked me
where Seung-heon was,
but l couldn't say anything.
Seung-heon came home on his own
the next afternoon.
l see...
But the problem didn't stop there.
Seung-heon must have understood
my situation so he never said anything.
lt was me who pushed him away
and made him a loner.
Jeong-ah,
how can l make it up to him?
Who is it?
Se-eun?
Se-eun...
You, you killed her!
No, l saved that thing.
What?
What did you do with Seung-heon
and Jun-hu?
This is the gratitude l get
for saving you?
You saw for yourself.
Your friends...
They're no longer living.
What bullshit are you talking about?
Yes, it' bullshit...
But unexplainable things happen
in this world.
l see that you haven't shed any blood,
fortunately.
What?
When l first arrived here
with my wife and children
l never dreamed this would happen.
Let' go.
Okay.
So nice and refreshing, right?
And l set the forest on fire.
What? You expect me to believe you?
Whether you believe me or not
is your choice.
But if you turn into one of them.
l'm going to kill you
without any hesitation.
You bastard...
The same goes for you too.
lf l turn into one of them,
you have to kill me.
lf you don't break your ropes while
you're alive,
do you think ghosts will do it after?
lt' a poem by Kabir
An lndian poet.
What the hell
are you talking about?
l still have a rope to break.
So don't waste you
time and energy
and leave the forest immediately.
Keep in mind.
Do Not Bleed.
lf you meet your friends on the way
Kill them.
Cut their heads off or
burn them
Until they stop moving.
That' the only way you can live...
Shut up, you murderer!
Damn it!
No, this can't be.
Woo-jin...
lt' okay Jeong-ah.
What happened to him?
l don't know, l think he' gone.
Woo-jin, l...
l saw Jun-hu.
He was dead but he looked
as if he was still alive.
l'll call the police as soon as
my cellphone finds signal.
Wait,
no signal.
Jeong-ah, Seung-heon is alive!
Seung-heon!
Seung-heon,
it' me, your big brother.
Woo-jin...
He' alive.
He' alive!
You remembered... the boy scouts.
Of course, the boy scouts!
This? lt hurt like hell
in the beginning
but l think l'm numb now.
What happened?
The thing is, l don't know.
Someone came up from behind...
Who...
Anyway,
l guess this has brought good luck.
Yeah, l'm glad you're safe.
Let' go now.
We're still in danger.
Woo-jin...
Over there...
This won't do...
Run!
That way!
Seung-heon, we're nearly there.
Woo-jin, this sound...
- Seung-heon
- This sound... l don't want to hear...
Woo-jin, this sound...
Woo-jin, it hurts really bad.
Seung-heon, we're nearly there...
Hang on...
Yes, it' just ahead of us
Calm down, Jeong-ah.
Your fear' making you see things.
Woo-jin.
What will you do if l turn into
one of them, like Se-eun?
What the hell
are you talking about?
That will never happen.
l... l'm just saying... what if...
lt' never going to happen, okay?
What if it does...
What if you turn into one of them
and try to hurt me and Jeong-ah.
Then what should l do?
Woo-jin, l've never...
l've never blamed you for anything.
So...
lf l do turn into one of them,
l want you to finish me off.
Stop it, Seung-heon...
That will never, ever happen.
We are... already... lost...
Just like that time
when we were playing boy scouts...
l'm keeping my word this time.
l'll do everything to find help
so take care of
Seung-heon for me, okay?
Won't it be dangerous alone?
Don't worry, we'll be safe as long as
we keep away from the forest.
You see...
Now, get in and lock the door
Be careful, Woo-jin.
Don't worry about me.
What is this place?
Seung-heon...
ls that you Jun-hu?
Dammit.
Hey, wake up!
What' going on,
you don't remember me?
lf l turn into one of them,
you have to kill me.
Wait... wait...
Wait!
Seung-heon, please,
come back to your senses...
Please, it' me.
Please!
lf l'm to blame
for your transformation.
l hope this sets everything right.
Seung-heon!
Where' Jeong-ah?
You haven't ...
Seung-heon!
You can't have...
Talk to me!
Tell me you haven't
you bastard!
You...
Wake up!
lt' all my fault so please...
Get hold of yourself,
JEONG Seung-heon!
l'm your brother.
Yes,
it' me, Seung-heon.
Seung-heon, please...
Woo-jin?
Please.
Jeong-ah!
Woo-jin...
Are you okay, Jeong-ah?
Yeah, lm fine...
Seung-heon...
l'm sorry, Woo-jin...
l'm sorry...
l'm sorry, Seung-heon...
So sorry...
Woo-jin, l...
Seung-heon... l promised that
l will never leave you alone again.
Woo-jin, l'm sorry...
l...
No, l'm the one who' sorry.
l didn't even carry out his last wish.
Woo-jin...
Jeong-ah, you set him free.
Now it' my turn.
Get in the trunk, Jeong-ah.
What will you do on your own?
l have an idea.
- But Woo-jin...
- Please, Jeong-ah!
l can't lose you.
Promise me that you'll live.
That you won't die...
l promise, l promise.
Hurry... now...
Woo-jin...
l'm sorry Jun-hu.
l think... you won the bet this time.
lt' all over.
Woo-jin.
Thanks for staying alive.
What' wrong Jeong-ah?
Nothing... Nothing...
Jeong-ah...
Remember
what Seung-heon said before?
What? Sorry, Jeong-ah,
l didn't catch that.
lf l turn into one of them,
like Seung-heon,
can you kill,
no, set me free?
Jeong-ah... lt' all over.
So answer me.
l should have, if l loved that person,
like Seung-heon.
You mean that?
Yes, even you.
No... if it happened to you.
l'm not sure if l could.
lf you don't break your ropes
while you're alive,
Do you think ghosts will do it after?
So this is how it should have been
all along...
Jeong-ah.
Woo-jin, please don't come near me.
l don't know why,
but this isn't over yet.
l... l saw you die.
What?
And the vision of me killing you.
But l...
lf you turn into one of them,
l don't think l can set you free.
Jeong-ah, that...
Don't come near me.
What do you think you're doing?
Jeong-ah...
This is the only way to save you.
What are you doing?
My sister saw my death.
That' why she killed herself
instead of me.
And passed on this cursed gift to me.
What?
Now l know...
From now on, you will also see
a lot of things that you don't want to see.
Jeong-ah...
what are you talking about?
This is my last wish so please...
Please.
Please break my rope
while l'm still alive.
No matter how l die here,
l'll turn into that horrible thing.
Jeong-ah...
l would rather...
that you kill me.
Set me free with your own hands.
Woo-jin, l can hear it.
Jeong-ah!
What shall l do?
Woo-jin, please...
- Woo-jin!
- Jeong-ah!
Jeong-ah!
Woo-jin,
Please...
Woo-jin, please...
Shouldn't you quit?
Thank you for becoming
my whole memory.
Now, let' see
Ooh, not bad...
Good!
Slow down, what' the hurry?
Cheon-hye! Se-ah!
l still have a rope to break.
Wow... nice...
What are you doing?
Hurry up!
We should be safe here, right?
They wouldn't chase us
all the way up here.
lt' over, at last...
What are you saying?
This is just the beginning
The three suspects previously in custody
at the National Mental Hospital
for the murder of the writer Yoo ll-han
escaped this morning around 2 a.m.
They reportedly killed
more than ten wardens
and police officers
during their escape,
but the actual number of casualties
is yet to be confirmed.
This is breaking news.
The three suspects
who killed 18 people
During their escape
from the National Mental Hospital...
...are still on the loose
but the police
have found the car they used
for their escape...
...in a forest
in Chungcheongbuk-do Province
The police also found two other cars
one belonging to the PARK family
who went missing in 2004
and the other to a Mr. JEONG,
who disappeared in 2005.
The police are focusing on finding out
the relationship between the two cases.
Detail news will be on 8 p.m. tonight...