[Heartbeat]
[Heartbeat stops]
[Woman moans]
[Moans louder]
[Screams]
OH, GOD!
IT WAS A BRILLIANT
LECTURE, DOCTOR.
YEAH. THE BEST
OF THE YEAR.
CAREFUL, ALL THESE BRAVOS WILL
GO TO AN OLD Ph.D.'s HEAD.
AND NOW, IF YOU'LL TAKE
THE  NECRONOMICON
AND RETURN IT
TO THE LIBRARY,
I'LL MEET YOU THERE
AS SOON AS I CAN.
DOCTOR, DON'T FORGET WE'RE
PICKING YOU UP FOR DINNER.
I'LL BE THERE.
AND YOU TAKE GOOD CARE
OF THAT BOOK.
YOU KNOW, SOME OF
THAT STUFF HE SAID
SORT OF GOT TO ME.
[Laughs]
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
NO, NO. I KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN.
ESPECIALLY THOSE
CREEPY PEOPLE
AND SOME OF THE
THINGS THEY DID.
CAN YOU LIFT THAT?
COULD I SEE THAT
BEFORE YOU PUT IT AWAY?
DO YOU ALWAYS SNEAK UP
ON PEOPLE LIKE THAT?
OH, MY, YOU SCARE EASILY.
I'D REALLY LIKE TO GLANCE
THROUGH THAT BOOK,
THE  NECRONOMICON.
WELL, THAT'S
IMPOSSIBLE.
I'VE TRAVELED A LONG WAY.
THE LIBRARY IS CLOSING.
COME ON.
GIVE ME 5 MINUTES.
ABSOLUTELY NOT!
WAIT A MINUTE.
I DON'T SUPPOSE
IT WOULD DO ANY HARM.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
UH, WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE IT IN THERE?
THANK YOU.
YOU MUST BE
INSANE.
OH, IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
HE'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
HE'LL TAKE CARE OF IT?
THAT BOOK IS PRICELESS.
OH, STOP WORRYING
ABOUT THE BOOK.
DID YOU NOTICE HIS EYES?
HE'S REALLY GOT GREAT EYES.
NANCY, WHAT DO YOU DO?
YOU'RE GIVING
HIS RAREST BOOK
TO THE FIRST KOOK
THAT COMES ALONG.
WELL, UH...
I--I TRUST HIM.
"YOG-SOTHOTH...
"IT IS THE GATE WHEREBY
THE SPHERES MEET.
"ONLY THEM FROM BEYOND CAN
MAKE IT MULTIPLY AND WORK.
"YOG-SOTHOTH
IS THE KEY.
"AND WITH THE GATE OPEN,
THE OLD ONES SHALL BE...
"PAST, PRESENT, FUTURE...
ALL ARE ONE.
"THE OLD ONES WALK
SERENE AND PRIMAL...
"UNDIMENSIONED AND UNSEEN...
"THE OLD ONES BROKE THROUGH
OF OLD...
"AND THEY SHALL
BREAK THROUGH--"
[Armitage]
THE BOOK, PLEASE.
OH, THERE'S NO NEED
TO BE UPSET.
I WAS ONLY READING IT.
HAVE YOU ANY IDEA
WHAT THIS VOLUME IS WORTH?
IT'S ONE OF A KIND.
OF COURSE,
A GENERATION AGO,
THERE WAS
ANOTHER COPY...
40 MILES FROM HERE.
YOUNG MAN, I AM FAMILIAR
WITH DUNWICH.
I KNOW.
YOU'VE READ MY PAPER
ON OLIVER WHATELEY?
HE WAS A GREAT MAN.
THEY HANGED HIM.
THEY WERE FOOLS.
WHO'S TO SAY?
I'M WILBUR WHATELEY,
OLIVER'S GREAT-GRANDSON.
THEN YOU KNOW WHO I AM.
DR. HENRY ARMITAGE.
YES. IT'S A PLEASURE
TO MEET A WHATELEY.
THANK YOU.
[Nancy] DOCTOR?
OH, IT'S EASY TO SEE
WHY YOU 2 GIRLS WERE
SO EFFECTIVELY CHARMED.
I'M VERY GLAD TO HAVE
MET THIS YOUNG MAN.
WE SHARE A MUTUAL INTEREST.
IN FACT, I'D LIKE TO TALK
FURTHER WITH YOU.
[Armitage] WE MIGHT LEARN
A GREAT DEAL FROM EACH OTHER,
DON'T YOU THINK?
ABOUT DUNWICH, PERHAPS?
DUNWICH, DR. ARMITAGE,
MIGHT APPEAR TO YOU
AS JUST ANOTHER SMALL TOWN.
THE PEOPLE OF DUNWICH ARE
JUST LIKE EVERYONE ELSE.
THEY'RE JUST MORE HONEST
ABOUT IT.
YOU SEE MAN AS A RATHER
DISMAL CREATURE.
YES. WHY NOT?
LOOK AROUND.
YOU'LL SEE WHAT'S THERE.
FEAR, AND FRIGHTENED
PEOPLE WHO KILL
WHAT THEY CAN'T UNDERSTAND.
IT'S LATE.
I SHOULD BE GOING.
DR. ARMITAGE,
I'D LIKE PERMISSION
TO STUDY
THE  NECRONOMICON.
FOR WHAT REASON,
MR. WHATELEY?
WELL, I'M A STUDENT
OF THE OCCULT.
AND THAT BOOK IS
LIKE A BIBLE.
A RATHER ODIOUS COMPARISON.
UH, NO, NOT REALLY.
IT'S NOT ENOUGH TO SAY
THE BOOK IS IRREPLACEABLE?
NO. YOU'RE AFRAID.
AFRAID? POSSIBLY.
IN ANCIENT TIMES,
THAT BOOK WAS SAID
TO UNLOCK THE GATES
TO ANOTHER DIMENSION,
TO ANOTHER RACE
OF BEINGS.
I DO NOT SHARE
THOSE BELIEFS,
NOR DO I FULLY
UNDERSTAND THEM.
HOWEVER, I KNOW ENOUGH
ABOUT STRANGE THINGS
NOT TO LAUGH AT THEM.
I DON'T HAVE TO TELL YOU
I'D TAKE GOOD CARE OF IT.
I'M SORRY,
I COULDN'T POSSIBLY
LET THE BOOK
OUT OF MY HANDS.
I NEED IT IN MY OWN
FIELD OF STUDY.
DR. ARMITAGE, WILL YOU
LEND ME THE BOOK?
I WILL NOT.
THAT'S YOUR LAST WORD?
YES.
LET ME GET
PART OF THAT.
OH, NONSENSE.
NANCY'S CAR
IS HERE.
I'LL TAKE YOU
TO THE HOTEL.
THANK YOU.
GOOD NIGHT.
MR. WHATELEY.
MAYBE WE'LL MEET AGAIN.
PERHAPS.
I GUESS I KIND OF PUT
THE DAMPER ON A NICE EVENING,
BUT I CAN'T STAND POMPOSITY.
I THINK YOU'VE MADE
YOUR POINT QUITE CLEAR.
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH LONGER
HE'S GONNA BE IN TOWN?
UH, HIS LAST LECTURE'S
NEXT MONDAY.
MONDAY.
THAT'S ONLY 3 DAYS.
I WANTED TO HEAR
ONE OF HIS LECTURES.
YOU WON'T BE HERE
THAT LONG?
NO. I HAVE TO GO BACK
TO DUNWICH TONIGHT.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I SHOULD GET MOVING,
OR I'LL MISS MY BUS.
WHAT TIME'S YOUR BUS?
9:15.
9:15?
YOU JUST MISSED IT.
DAMMIT.
THERE ISN'T ANOTHER BUS
UNTIL TOMORROW MORNING.
WELL, UH,
I COULD DRIVE YOU.
OH, IT'S TOO LATE.
I COULDN'T LET YOU DO THAT.
NO, NO, REALLY.
I MEAN, I'D LIKE TO.
OH, FINE.
IT'S ONLY A COUPLE
MORE MILES, NANCY.
I HOPE SO. WE'RE
ALMOST OUT OF GAS.
OH, SAVED.
IT'S PAST
CLOSING TIME.
OH, COULDN'T I HAVE
A LITTLE GAS?
OK. HOW MUCH?
CAN YOU FILL IT UP,
PLEASE?
SERVICE
WITH A SMILE.
SAY, HOW FAR
IS THE TOWN?
OH, IT'S DOWN THAT WAY.
BUT WE TURN OFF
RIGHT UP HERE.
I'M SORRY.
I WANTED TO SEE DUNWICH.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THERE'S NOT MUCH
TO SEE AT NIGHT.
BESIDES, EVERYTHING IN TOWN
CLOSES UP PRETTY EARLY.
$1!
$1? I ASKED YOU
TO FILL IT UP.
$1!
AREN'T YOU GONNA FINISH
THE WINDOW?
[Nancy] BOY, I COULD NEVER GET
USED TO TREATMENT LIKE THAT.
[Whateley] THEY'VE
TREATED ME THAT WAY
SINCE THE DAY
I WAS BORN.
THEY NEVER CHANGE.
THEY'RE STILL
THE SAME FRIGHTENED,
SUPERSTITIOUS FOOLS.
THAT'S EVEN CRAZIER
THAN YOU SAID.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO COME IN
AND SEE THE INSIDE?
OH, NO, NO.
I'D LIKE TO,
BUT REALLY,
I SHOULD START BACK.
JUST HAVE A DRINK...
OR CUP OF TEA.
I REALLY SHOULDN'T.
PLEASE.
OK.
[Nervous laugh]
WELL?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
[Nervous laugh]
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO THINK.
I'M GLAD YOU FIND IT
INTERESTING.
WOULD YOU LIKE
A CUP OF TEA?
PLEASE.
FINE.
IT'S BEEN A LONG RIDE.
IF YOU FEEL
LIKE FRESHENING UP,
THERE'S A BATHROOM
RIGHT THROUGH THAT DOOR.
THANK YOU.
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
[Kettle whistles]
[Strange noises like wind]
WILBUR!
THIS IS MY GRANDFATHER.
I WANT TO SPEAK TO YOU.
WE WERE JUST GOING
TO HAVE SOME TEA.
I'LL SEE YOU
WHEN WE'RE FINISHED.
I'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU.
SORRY.
SIT DOWN, NANCY.
I THOUGHT YOU
LIVED ALONE.
GEE, I'M SORRY
HE FRIGHTENED YOU.
DO YOU WANT
SUGAR OR CREAM?
NO, THANK YOU.
TELL YOU THE TRUTH, I DIDN'T
THINK HE'D BE UP THIS LATE.
OH, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S JUST THAT
HE STARTLED ME.
WILBUR, WHEN YOU
WERE IN THE KITCHEN,
I HEARD STRANGE SOUNDS.
OH? WHAT KIND OF SOUNDS?
I'M NOT SURE.
I MEAN,
IT SOUNDED LIKE WIND...
OR THE OCEAN.
THAT'S WHAT IT WAS.
THIS PLACE IS SO OLD.
WHEN THE WIND BLOWS,
EVERYTHING KIND OF CREAKS.
OH, WILBUR,
I'M SORRY.
I DROPPED
SOMETHING BEFORE.
OH?
THE...GLASS.
OH. [Chuckles]
THAT'S NOTHING.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WELL...
I GUESS I'D
BETTER START BACK.
FINISH YOUR TEA.
NO, REALLY, NO.
IT'S LATE. I MUST GO.
I UNDERSTAND.
WELL, YOU COME BACK AND
VISIT SOON, WILL YOU?
WE'LL SEE EACH OTHER AGAIN.
[Engine sputtering]
WHAT'S WRONG?
HELL, I DON'T KNOW.
I WISH I COULD HELP, BUT I
DON'T KNOW MUCH ABOUT CARS.
[Sighs] I DON'T THINK
THIS THING'S GONNA START.
MAYBE WE OUGHT
TO PHONE A GARAGE.
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE IT,
BUT I DON'T
HAVE A TELEPHONE.
WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
NOW WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
[Chuckles] I DON'T KNOW.
[Nervous laugh]
YOU-YOU KNOW,
THIS IS REALLY
A GOOD IDEA.
I'M COMPLETELY
WIPED OUT.
I--I DON'T EVEN
THINK I COULD DRIVE
IF I HAD TO.
I'M SURE YOU'LL FEEL
BETTER IN THE MORNING.
OH, YES. YES.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THIS ROOM,
BUT IT HASN'T BEEN USED
FOR YEARS AND YEARS.
OH, NO, NO.
DON'T APOLOGIZE.
IT'S FINE, FINE.
UH...LET'S SEE.
HERE'S A NIGHTGOWN
YOU CAN PUT ON IF YOU LIKE.
THANK YOU.
[Sighs] WILBUR...
GOOD NIGHT.
WHO IS SHE?
JUST A GIRL.
SHE GAVE ME A RIDE HOME.
DOES ANYONE KNOW
SHE'S OUT HERE?
NO.
SUPPOSE SHE GOES UP THERE?
SHE WON'T.
SHE HAS NO REASON TO.
[Rattling]
¶ [Strange music]
[Laughing]
[Screaming]
[Cackling]
[Panting]
[Elizabeth] SHE DIDN'T
COME HOME LAST NIGHT.
SHE MUST'VE DRIVEN
THAT BOY HOME.
I COULD SEE SHE WAS
ATTRACTED TO HIM,
BUT I DON'T THINK
GOING OUT THERE
WAS SUCH A GOOD IDEA.
WELL, DIDN'T YOU
TRY TO TELEPHONE?
I COULDN'T
GET A LISTING.
OH.
IT'S NOT LIKE HER
NOT TO HAVE CALLED ME.
NOW, IF HE WERE
A STRAIGHT GUY,
I WOULDN'T BE WORRIED.
[Nancy] I CAN'T REMEMBER
MUCH MORE.
EXCEPT IT WAS THE WEIRDEST
DREAM I'VE EVER HAD.
SOUNDS KIND OF SEXUAL TO ME.
[Laughs]
OK, DR. FREUD, TELL ME
WHAT IT ALL MEANS.
WELL, THIS IS
OUR FIRST SESSION.
IT'S A LITTLE HARD TO TELL.
ARE YOU PREPARED
TO ANSWER SOME QUESTIONS?
ASK ME ANYTHING.
ALL RIGHT. HOW DO YOU
FEEL ABOUT SEX?
I THINK IT'S GREAT.
SO DO I, NANCY.
WELL, I MEAN, I THINK
IT'S GREAT IF IT'S
AT THE RIGHT TIME
AND THE RIGHT PLACE.
YOU'VE LED A STRANGE
LIFE HERE, WILBUR.
I WAS RAISED
BY MY GRANDFATHER,
AND HE TAUGHT ME
ALL THE THINGS HE KNOWS.
I HAD TO WORK HARDER
THAN MOST KIDS,
BUT IT HASN'T
BEEN SO BAD.
WELL, I COME
FROM THE CITY AND--
WELL, I JUST--I DON'T
KNOW, I NEVER FELT
SO RELAXED OR HAD
SUCH PEACE OF MIND.
I THINK THE COUNTRY
DOES THAT FOR PEOPLE.
NANCY, WHY DON'T YOU
STAY THE WEEKEND?
WELL, I'D
LIKE TO, WILBUR,
BUT I--I COULDN'T.
BUT YOU'D
LIKE TO, THOUGH, HUH?
HER CAR'S THERE.
SHE'S GOTTA BE
AROUND SOMEWHERE.
[Knocking]
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
PARDON US.
WE'RE LOOKING
FOR OUR FRIEND...
NANCY WAGNER.
I'M DR. ARMITAGE
AND THIS IS
ELIZABETH HAMILTON.
WE MET YOUR GRANDSON
WILBUR YESTERDAY
IN THE UNIVERSITY.
ARMITAGE?
WHAT WOULD MY GRANDSON
WANT WITH YOU?
HE CAME TO SEE ME
ABOUT A BOOK I OWN,
THE  NECRONOMICON.
LOOK, IS MY
GIRLFRIEND HERE
OR ISN'T SHE?
NO! GO AWAY!
GO AWAY!
WERE YOU LOOKING
FOR US, DOCTOR?
NANCY!
ARE YOU
ALL RIGHT?
I WAS WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
OF COURSE
SHE'S ALL RIGHT.
SHE'S NOT A CHILD.
SHE DROVE ME HOME
LAST NIGHT
AND THEN SHE DECIDED
TO STAY THE WEEKEND.
DIDN'T YOU, NANCY?
YES. YES,
I DID.
SO IF THAT'S WHAT YOU CAME
TO SEE ABOUT, DOCTOR,
I GUESS WE'LL BE
SAYING GOODBYE.
[Elizabeth]
NANCY, WAIT
A SECOND.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE DOING?
OF COURSE I KNOW
WHAT I'M DOING.
I'M STAYING
WITH WILBUR.
NANCY--
BYE, ELIZABETH.
BOY, I REALLY
CAN'T BELIEVE
SHE DRAGGED
DR. ARMITAGE
ALL THE WAY UP HERE.
[Chuckling] I MEAN,
THAT'S SOMETHING I--
I EXPECT
FROM MY MOTHER.
DOESN'T MATTER.
WOULD YOU LIKE
SOME MORE TEA?
PLEASE.
YOU TIRED, OR IS IT
THE COMPANY?
OH, NO, NO, NO.
I DON'T KNOW,
I'M KINDA SLEEPY.
WELL, WE DID TAKE
A LONG WALK TODAY.
YEAH.
MAYBE YOU COULD
USE A LITTLE NAP.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S
NOT A BAD IDEA.
UM, WE ARE GOING
TO TOWN, AREN'T WE?
SURE. BUT I THINK YOU'LL
ENJOY YOURSELF MORE
IF YOU CAN KEEP
YOUR EYES OPEN.
[Embarrassed laugh]
UM, I'LL BE
ALL RIGHT.
YOU LIED TO ME.
NOW TELL ME
THE TRUTH!
KEEP YOUR VOICE
DOWN, WILL YOU?
WHY IS SHE HERE?
I TOLD YOU, HER CAR
BROKE DOWN.
WHAT ABOUT THIS?
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
AND THOSE
PEOPLE.
YOU TOLD ME NO ONE
KNEW SHE WAS HERE.
THEY DON'T MATTER.
THAT MAN ARMITAGE WROTE
THE PAPER ON MY FATHER.
HE KNOWS ALL ABOUT US.
I DON'T HAVE
TO ANSWER TO YOU.
I DO WHAT I WANT.
COME BACK HERE!
LET THE BOOK BE!
[Machinery drowning out
conversation]
YOU KNOW,
IT HAPPENED
25 YEARS AGO.
THEY WERE
A STRANGE FAMILY.
I JUST HOPE THERE'S
SOMETHING IN THERE.
THIS USED TO BE
THE TOWN BANK, YOU KNOW.
AH, HERE IT IS.
THIS IS THE ONE.
LET'S GET IT
OUT IN THE LIGHT.
AH, HERE IT IS
JUST LIKE I TOLD YOU.
"MOTHER NAMED LAVINIA,
FATHER UNKNOWN.
"CHILD CALLED WILBUR."
I SET THAT TYPE MYSELF
25 YEARS AGO.
WHO WAS THE DELIVERING
PHYSICIAN?
SAME OLD DOC
THAT DELIVERS
ALL OF THEM
AROUND HERE...
DOC CORY.
THANK YOU,
MR. FULLER.
ELIZABETH--
DR. ARMITAGE!
IF I WERE YOU, I'D STAY
AWAY FROM THE WHATELEYS.
ELIZABETH.
THAT WAS THE ORIGINAL
TOWN SQUARE.
70 YEARS AGO,
THERE WAS A BIG
OAK TREE RIGHT THERE
IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE STREET.
THAT'S WHERE THE
PEOPLE OF DUNWICH
LYNCHED MY
GREAT-GRANDFATHER.
THEY JUST LET HIM
HANG THERE
FOR DAYS AND DAYS
AND DAYS AND DAYS.
THEN THEY BURNED
THE TREE DOWN
TO THE GROUND.
WILBUR, STOP IT.
IT'S JUST HISTORY.
WHY DID THEY DO IT?
BECAUSE HE
DIDN'T BELIEVE
IN WHAT
THEY BELIEVED.
BECAUSE HE WASN'T
AFRAID OF THEIR GOD
OR THEIR DEVIL EITHER,
FOR THAT MATTER.
IN FACT, HE THOUGHT
THEY WERE PRETTY
MUCH ALIKE.
WHAT DID HE BELIEVE IN?
IN ANOTHER
RACE OF BEINGS
FROM A DIFFERENT
DIMENSION.
AN EARLIER RACE,
SUPERIOR TO MAN.
AND HE BELIEVED
THEY COULD BE
BROUGHT BACK.
YOU MEAN THEY
HANGED HIM FOR THAT?
YES.
THEY TRUMPED UP
A MURDER CHARGE
TO COVER IT UP.
A GIRL HAD
DISAPPEARED AND--
THEN WITHOUT
A SHRED OF EVIDENCE,
THEY WENT AFTER HIM.
THEY CLAIMED HE USED HER
IN SOME SORT OF SACRIFICE.
YOU MUST BE
WORRIED, TOO,
TO GO TO ALL
OF THIS TROUBLE.
OK, THE DOCTOR
WILL SEE YOU NOW.
THANK YOU.
I WON'T BE LONG.
DR. CORY?
YES?
I'M HENRY ARMITAGE,
DOCTOR OF PHILOSOPHY.
I'M LECTURING
AT THE UNIVERSITY
IN ARKHAM.
OH, YES, YES,
WELL...
WHAT CAN I DO
FOR YOU, DOCTOR?
I'M...NOT SURE.
I HAVE A RATHER
STRANGE REQUEST.
WELL, A COUNTRY
DOCTOR'S
USED TO THEM.
PLEASE, SIT DOWN.
THANK YOU.
WELL, NOW...
PLEASE GO AHEAD.
I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU
SOME QUESTIONS
ABOUT THE WHATELEY FAMILY.
WELL, THAT'S AN ODD
BIRD OF AN AILMENT,
BUT IT FLARES UP
NOW AND AGAIN
IN THESE PARTS.
HAVEN'T YOU
EVER BEEN THERE?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I WOULDN'T GO
NEAR THAT PLACE.
WHY?
OH, THAT PLACE
GIVES ME
THE CREEPS.
BUT WHY?
WELL...SOME SAY
THAT OLD
WHATELEY
AND WILBUR
AREN'T ALONE...
THAT THERE'S
SOMETHING ELSE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
"SOMETHING ELSE"?
I--I DON'T KNOW
EXACTLY, BUT, UH...
WHEN I WAS
A LITTLE KID,
THE OTHER
CHILDREN AND I,
WE THOUGHT THE OLD
WHATELEY HOUSE
WAS HAUNTED.
OF COURSE, I DON'T
BELIEVE THAT ANYMORE,
BUT I KEEP AWAY
AND SO DOES
EVERYONE ELSE.
ANYWAY, THE OLD MAN
AND WILBUR,
THEY HAVEN'T
ALLOWED
ANYONE ON THE PLACE
IN YEARS.
OH.
WELL, A FRIEND OF MINE
IS OUT THERE RIGHT NOW.
WHAT?
YEAH.
SHE'S OUT THERE
WITH WILBUR.
WILBUR WHATELEY
HAS A GIRLFRIEND?
OH, I DON'T
BELIEVE IT!
WELL, HASN'T IT EVER
HAPPENED BEFORE?
NOT WITH ANY GIRL
AROUND HERE.
I SAW YOUR NAME
ON THE BIRTH RECORDS.
WELL...
YOU HAVE ME
IN AN AWKWARD
POSITION, DOCTOR.
AND BEFORE
I CAN REVEAL
ANYTHING TO YOU,
I MUST KNOW THE PURPOSE
OF YOUR INQUIRY.
OF COURSE. DR. CORY,
THIS WILL SOUND
QUITE FANTASTIC,
BUT I ASK
YOUR INDULGENCE.
PLEASE BEAR WITH ME
AND THEN DECIDE
FOR YOURSELF.
WHERE THE WHATELEYS
ARE CONCERNED,
THERE IS VERY LITTLE
THAT IS NOT FANTASTIC.
I WONDER WHAT'S GOING ON.
LOOK...
I DON'T WANT
TO WORRY YOU,
BUT IF I
HAD A FRIEND
DOWN AT WEIRD
WILBUR'S,
I'D GET HER
OUT OF THERE.
LET ME PUT IT
THIS WAY, DOCTOR.
THE LEGEND OF
THE  NECRONOMICON
HAS IT THAT
LONG AGO
THE EARTH WAS INHABITED
BY A SPECIES
FROM ANOTHER DIMENSION.
WITH CERTAIN CHANTS
FROM THE BOOK,
COUPLED WITH ANCIENT
RITES AND SACRIFICES,
THIS RACE, THE OLD ONES,
CAN BE BROUGHT BACK.
AND MANKIND?
DESTROYED.
AND FROM WHAT
YOU'VE SEEN
OF YOUNG
WHATELEY,
YOU THINK IT'S
ACTUALLY POSSIBLE
THAT HE MIGHT
BELIEVE THAT?
THE BOOK, THE GIRL...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO THINK.
IF HE DOES BELIEVE
THE LEGEND,
FROM MY IMPRESSION
OF WILBUR,
HE'D BE CAPABLE
OF ANYTHING.
IF HE DOES ATTEMPT
ONE OF THOSE
RITUALS,
THAT GIRL IS IN
GRAVE DANGER.
WELL, IT'S HARD
TO ACCEPT.
BUT THEN, IT WOULDN'T
BE THE FIRST TIME
THAT SOMEONE ELSE
PAID THE PENALTY
FOR WHATELEY FANATICISM.
OH?
YES, YOU SEE...
IT WASN'T I
WHO DELIVERED
YOUNG WHATELEY.
IT WAS HIS
GRANDFATHER.
IT'S BEEN
25 YEARS,
BUT I'LL NEVER
FORGET THAT DAY
AS LONG
AS I LIVE.
[Dr. Cory]  I WAS IN
OSBORNE'S STORE,
JUST CHATTING WITH
A FEW OF THE LOCALS.
OLD WHATELEY
CAME RUNNING IN
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
ALL WILD-EYED
AND CRAZIER THAN EVER.
BUT NOBODY
EVER SAW MUCH
OF THE WHATELEYS
IN TOWN,
SO IT WAS A SURPRISE
RIGHT OFF.
HE ALWAYS TOOK
A LOT OF JEERING
FROM THE TOWNSFOLK.
WELL, THEY DIDN'T
WASTE A MINUTE'S TIME
BEFORE THEY STARTED
IN ON HIM.
[Whateley]  I DON'T CARE WHAT
YOU FOLKS SAY.
IF LAVINIA'S BOY
LOOKED LIKE HIS PA,
HE'D WOULDN'T LOOK
LIKE NOTHING
YOU EXPECT.
YOU NEEDN'T THINK
THAT THE ONLY FOLKS
ARE THE FOLKS
HEREABOUTS.
LAVINIA'S READ SOME
AND HAS SEEN
SOME THINGS
THAT MOST OF YOU CAN
ONLY TELL ABOUT.
SOME DAY,
YOU FOLKS'LL HEAR
A CHILD OF LAVINIA'S
CALLING HIS
FATHER'S NAME
FROM THE TOP
OF SENTINEL HILL.
AND THEN
YOU'LL KNOW!
AND YOU'LL WISH
TO GOD YOU DIDN'T!
ALL RIGHT, FELLAS,
THAT'S IT.
[Dr. Cory]  AS I ENTERED
THE BEDROOM,
THERE WERE 2
ELDERLY ALBINO WOMEN,
ROBED ENTIRELY
IN BLACK,
STANDING WATCHFULLY
OVER HER.
SHE WAS BURNING UP
WITH FEVER
AND SOAKING WET.
GOD ONLY KNOWS
WHAT WENT ON
OUT THERE THAT DAY.
IT WAS PLAIN TO SEE
SHE'D BEEN OUT
IN THE RAIN.
THEY TOLD ME
THAT SHE'D HAD TWINS.
ONE OF THEM
WAS STILLBORN.
THOUGH I NEVER
SAW THE BODY.
AND SINCE OLD WHATELEY'S
NOT ALLOWED
ANYONE OUT THERE SINCE,
IT'S POSSIBLE THAT BABY
MAY HAVE LIVED.
IT'S A MIRACLE
THAT WILBUR
CAME THROUGH IT
ALL RIGHT.
LAVINIA'S INSIDES
WERE ALL TORN UP.
WELL, I DID EVERYTHING
I COULD FOR HER.
SHE WAS SO FAR GONE,
I WAS LUCKY
TO SAVE HER LIFE.
HER MIND WAS GONE FOREVER.
OF COURSE, WE NEVER DID
FIND OUT WHO THE FATHER WAS.
AND THE 2 OLD WOMEN?
I DON'T KNOW.
NEVER SAW THEM AROUND HERE
BEFORE OR SINCE.
WHERE'S LAVINIA NOW?
[Muttering]
INCREDIBLE.
IT IS HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT SHE'S ONLY
45 YEARS OLD.
SHE'S BEEN HERE NOW
FOR MORE THAN 20 YEARS.
THERE'S BEEN NO
APPRECIABLE CHANGE.
[Lavinia] WALK UNSEEN
IN LONELY PLACES...
OLD ONES...
OH, MY SONS,
OPEN THE GATE,
MY SONS!
[Sobbing]
[Screams]
COULD I GO IN
AND TALK TO HER?
[Doctor] I'M AFRAID NOT.
SHE'S VIOLENT.
AT TIMES, EXTREMELY SO.
I'D LIKE TO TRY.
IT WOULDN'T DO ANY GOOD.
LAVINIA?
I WANT TO TALK
TO YOU.
KILL THEM ALL!
LET THEM IN!
[Giggles]
DO YOU THINK YOU'VE
HAD ENOUGH TO EAT?
OH, PLENTY.
WELL, LET'S TAKE A WALK.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANT TO SHOW YOU.
OKAY.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH. I'M JUST
A LITTLE DIZZY.
I'LL HELP YOU.
IT'S NOT FAR.
I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
[Gasping]
IT'S NOT MUCH FURTHER.
WHAT'S IN
THE PACKAGE?
LOOK.
IT'S JUST FANTASTIC.
WHAT IS IT?
NO ONE KNOWS EXACTLY.
LEGEND HAS IT THAT IT'S
BEEN HERE FOREVER.
IT'S CALLED
THE DEVIL'S HOPYARD.
FERTILITY RITES
WERE PRACTICED HERE,
SO THEY SAY.
IS THIS AN ALTAR?
YES.
BUT WHAT WAS IT
USED FOR?
WHEN THE SEASONS
AND THE CYCLES
OF THE MOON WERE RIPE,
THEN THEY CAME
ONE BY ONE
AND GATHERED
AMONG THESE STONES.
AND THEY SELECTED
A BEAUTIFUL GIRL LIKE YOU.
DO YOU REMEMBER WHAT WE
TALKED ABOUT THIS MORNING?
YES.
WHEN YOU ASKED ME
THAT QUESTION
ABOUT SEX?
YES?
I LIED.
I KNOW.
THEN THEY PLACED
THE GIRL'S VIRGINAL BODY
UPON THE ALTAR,
NAKED TO THE ELEMENTS.
AND THEIR BLACK ROBES
BLENDING INTO THE NIGHT,
THEY LIGHTED CANDLES
AND GATHERED ROUND
TO OBSERVE AND TO RELISH
HER NAKEDNESS.
AND THEN THEY WAITED.
THEY WAITED
FOR THE MOMENT
WHEN SHE WOULD ALLOW
THE POWER OF DARKNESS
TO ENTER HER.
THE MOMENT WHEN
THE GATE WOULD OPEN
AND THE OLD ONES
WOULD COME THROUGH.
AND A STRANGE CHANT
ECHOED IN THE NIGHT.
YOG-SOTHOTH...
YOG-SOTHOTH!
[Moaning]
[Hooting]
HELLO! IS ANYBODY
HERE?
HELLO!
[Gasps]
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TO STAY AWAY FROM HERE.
I'M NOT STAYING AWAY
FROM ANYWHERE.
I'M LOOKING FOR
MY GIRLFRIEND,
AND I WANNA SEE HER NOW.
SHE'S NOT HERE!
NOW GET OFF MY LAND!
I'M GOING INSIDE!
NO, YOU'RE--
DON'T TOUCH ME!
NANCY?
NANCY, IT'S
ELIZABETH!
[Distant rattle]
NANCY?
[Heartbeat]
STOP!
NANCY?
WHERE ARE YOU?
[Screaming]
NO!
[Panting]
[Door opens]
THERE'S A CAR
OUTSIDE. WHO'S HERE?
SHE CAME LOOKING
FOR HER FRIEND.
MAKE SENSE,
WILL YOU?
WHO'S HERE?
SHE WENT UP
THOSE STAIRS.
ELIZABETH.
WILBUR, WHERE'S ELIZABETH?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE KNOWS.
SHUT UP,
YOU OLD FOOL!
YOU'RE THE FOOL!
I KNOW YOUR PLAN!
YOU CAN'T SUCCEED!
YOU DISGUST ME.
YOU'VE TAKEN
THEIR ABUSE,
AND YOU'VE GIVEN UP.
THEY'VE BROKEN YOU.
BUT THE OLD ONES
ARE COMING BACK.
I'M GOING TO LET
THEM THROUGH.
NO! I TRIED
AND I DESTROYED
YOUR MOTHER.
YOU'LL FAIL, TOO.
YOU'LL DESTROY
HER!
OLIVER HAD THE BOOK.
IT DIDN'T HELP.
HE HAD
THE WRONG GIRL.
SHE RESISTED
AND SHE DIED.
NOW YOU LISTEN
TO ME.
I'M GOING TO SUCCEED
WHERE YOU FAILED.
I'LL STOP YOU!
[Birds screeching]
STOP...HIM...
[Birds stop screeching]
WILBUR...THOSE BIRDS...
WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
THEY WERE TRYING
TO CAPTURE HIS SOUL
AS IT LEFT HIS BODY.
BUT THEY'RE
QUIET NOW.
THEY DIDN'T GET HIM.
HE'S FREE.
[Wilbur]  DARKNESS LEADS
UNTO DARKNESS.
LET THIS SOUL TRANSCEND
THE BOUNDS OF EARTH
AND BE DELIVERED
TO THE SPIRIT OF DARKNESS.
DEATH SHALL BE
THE CARRIAGE OF THIS SOUL.
[Speaking ancient,
cryptic language]
LET THE CRY OF THE BIRDS
TRANSPORT THE SPIRIT.
YOG-SOTHOTH...
ACCEPT THIS MAN INTO
THE DEATH OF DARKNESS.
HEAR ME, OLD ONES,
FOR YOUR TIME IS COMING.
THIS DEATH SHALL MARK
THE BEGINNING
OF YOUR JOURNEY.
YOG-SOTHOTH.
[Trucks approaching]
SEE? I TOLD YOU
HE WAS HERE.
HE'S BURYING
THE OLD MAN.
LIKE HELL,
HE IS!
FROM DARKNESS WE CAME--
[Man] ALL RIGHT, HOLD IT!
WE BURY OUR TRASH
AT THE COUNTY DUMP,
NOT HERE!
THIS IS A CHRISTIAN
CEMETERY.
NO PLACE HERE
FOR YOUR KIND.
FROM DARKNESS
WE CAME--
I SAID HOLD IT!
GIVE ME THAT BOOK.
NOW, YOU GET OUT HERE.
YOU TAKE YOUR
GARBAGE WITH YOU!
WHEN I'M FINISHED.
YOU'RE FINISHED NOW!
ALL RIGHT, HOLD ON!
HOLD ON, YOU TWO!
WHAT IN HELL ARE YOU
TRYING TO DO?
I WAS TRYING TO BURY
MY GRANDFATHER.
WE GOT FAMILY
BURIED HERE.
WE DON'T WANT
NO WHATELEYS
AMONG THEM.
WE OWN THIS PLOT,
AND I HAVE THE RIGHT
TO USE IT.
[Crowd jeering]
NO ONE'S GETTING
BURIED JUST YET.
THERE'S BEEN NO
DEATH CERTIFICATE
ISSUED ON THIS BODY.
WE'LL HAVE
TO TAKE IT BACK
TILL IT'S ALL
STRAIGHTENED OUT LEGALLY.
COME ON, NANCY.
NOW, NANCY,
YOU'LL WAIT
RIGHT HERE, WON'T YOU?
I'LL WAIT.
PUT IT BACK.
[Drops book]
PICK IT UP.
[Telephone dialing]
UNH!
[Telephone rings]
HELLO?
UH, CORY HERE.
RASKIN JUST TELEPHONED
ME FROM THE ASYLUM.
I THOUGHT
YOU'D WANT TO KNOW.
LAVINIA IS DYING.
FROM WHAT?
WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, I'M NOT SURE,
BUT IT SOUNDS AS IF
ALL HELL'S
BREAKING LOOSE.
WELL, CAN WE GO
OVER THERE?
I'LL PICK YOU UP.
NO, IT'LL BE FASTER
IF I MEET YOU THERE.
OH, DO YOU REMEMBER THE GIRL
THAT WAS WITH ME YESTERDAY?
YES.
I STILL HAVEN'T BEEN
ABLE TO REACH HER.
IT JUST OCCURRED TO ME.
SHE WAS TALKING
WITH YOUR NURSE.
WELL, CORA'S RIGHT HERE,
I'LL ASK HER.
CORA, THE GIRL
WITH DR. ARMITAGE,
SHE DIDN'T
HAPPEN TO SAY
WHERE SHE
WAS GOING,
DID SHE?
WHY NO, DOCTOR.
WELL, I'M SORRY,
ARMITAGE,
YOU'RE OUT OF LUCK.
I'LL SEE YOU
AT THE ASYLUM.
ALL RIGHT. OK.
NOW, CORA, I WON'T
BE BACK TONIGHT,
SO WHY DON'T YOU
LEAVE ALL THAT WORK
TILL THE MORNING?
NO, I'D RATHER GET IT DONE
THIS EVENING, DOCTOR.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, SUIT YOURSELF.
AND BE SURE YOU--
BE SURE YOU
LOCK UP, WON'T YOU?
GOOD NIGHT.
[Moaning]
[Heavy breathing]
[Doctor] WE'VE DONE
EVERYTHING WE CAN.
BLOOD PRESSURE, PULSE,
RESPIRATION--
EVERYTHING IS SKY-HIGH.
SO IT CAN'T LAST
MUCH LONGER.
[Panting]
[Armitage]
WHAT CAUSED IT?
[Doctor]
I WISH I KNEW.
[Moaning]
[Armitage]
LISTEN.
[Birds shrieking]
[Cory] THE BIRDS ARE
IN RHYTHM WITH HER BREATHING.
[Moaning]
LISTEN!
[Lavinia] YES...MY SON.
[Panting]
[Birds shrieking]
SHE'S FINISHED.
THEY'VE STOPPED.
WHAT WAS SHE MUTTERING?
THE BIRDS.
THAT CHANT.
THE  NECRONOMICON.
DR. CORY,
I'VE GOT TO GET TO
THE LIBRARY RIGHT AWAY.
[Thunder]
LAND OF LIGHT...
THE ARMY OF DARKNESS
SHALL SWEEP DOWN.
THEY ARE GATHERED LIKE
A HORDE OF AVENGERS,
LIFE WITHIN LIFE,
THE POWER THAT SUMMONS.
COME BACK, OLD ONES...
PRINCES OF DARKNESS,
AND REPOSSESS THE EARTH.
[Inaudible]
[Speaking ancient,
cryptic language]
YOG-SOTHOTH.
[Speaking ancient,
cryptic language]
[With echo]  I SUMMON YOU.
COME, BROTHER OF DARKNESS.
LEAVE YOUR PRISON
AND HELP ME
BRING THE OLD ONES THROUGH.
BROTHER OF MY BLOOD,
MY SOUL, I SUMMON YOU.
THE TIME HAS ARRIVED.
NOW WE WAIT NO LONGER.
WE MUST ACT.
UPON THIS SACRIFICE,
SHALL THE JOURNEY BEGIN.
[Heartbeat]
[Whateley]
"YOG-O-OTH. YOG-O-OTH.
"JOIN THE CIRCLE,
COMPLETE THE CHAIN.
"YOG-SOTHOTH IS THE GATE
"WHEREBY THE SPHERES MEET.
"AND WITH THE GATE OPEN,
"THE OLD ONES SHALL BE.
"MAN RULES NOW
WHERE THEY RULED ONCE.
"THEY WAIT,
PATIENT AND POTENT,
"FOR HERE THEY SHALL
REIGN AGAIN,
"AND RULE WHERE THEY
ONCE WALKED.
"THE OLD ONES
BROKE THROUGH OF OLD,
"AND THEY SHALL
BREAK THROUGH AGAIN."
YOG-SOTHOTH!
[Woman]
WE THANK THEE, O LORD,
FOR THE FOOD WE ARE
ABOUT TO TAKE
FOR THE NOURISHMENT
OF OUR BODIES.
AMEN.
[Growling]
SOMETHING'S
BOTHERING RUSTY.
BEEN ACTING STRANGE,
ALL RIGHT.
[Dog barking]
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
BABY LAMB?
[Growls]
[Neighs]
[Whining]
[Growls]
[Growling]
[Barking]
[Horse neighs]
[Heartbeat]
[Gunshot]
[Neighs]
[Bellows]
[Bellowing]
[Ringing]
PLEASE...
LUCILLE?
[Crashing]
[Heartbeat]
AH!
[Inaudible]
[Thunder]
THE GATE IS
OPENING NOW.
WE DON'T HAVE
LONG TO WAIT.
YOU'RE ONE OF US NOW.
[Thunder]
IT'S TIME.
YOU SAW WHAT WILBUR DID
TO GET THE BOOK.
HE'S GOING TO TRY TO LET
THE OLD ONES THROUGH.
WHETHER THEY EXIST OR NOT
DOESN'T MATTER.
HE'S NOT RESPONSIBLE
FOR HIS ACTIONS.
IF YOU'RE RIGHT, HOW ARE
WE GOING TO HANDLE IT?
WHAT? SOMETHING'S
GOING ON.
WELL, THAT'S
THE COLE PLACE.
[Dr. Cory]
HARRISON.
[Sheriff] I TRIED TO
CALL YOU, DOC.
WHAT'S HAPPENED?
ALL HELL'S
BUSTED LOOSE.
[Reeger]
DAMN WHATELEYS.
NO MAN WOULD HAVE MUTILATED
THE BODIES THAT WAY.
I DON'T SAY
THE WHATELEYS DID IT,
BUT DAMN IT,
THEY'RE RESPONSIBLE.
SETTLE DOWN, REEGER.
SETTLE DOWN? THERE'RE
DEAD PEOPLE IN THERE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
SETTLE DOWN?
REEGER'S RIGHT.
[Crowd clamors]
LET'S GO
GET THEM!
YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
YOU STOP THEM,
REEGER, OR I WILL.
[Man] WELL, LET'S GO!
MY FAMILY'S NOT GONNA--
COME ON,
LET'S GO!
STOP! STOP, YOU CAN'T
KILL WILBUR WHATELEY.
HE DIDN'T DO THIS,
BUT HE MAY BE
THE ONLY MAN
WHO CAN SAVE US
FROM WHAT DID.
[Man] WHY SHOULD
WE LISTEN TO YOU?
WELL, YOU ALL KNOW ME.
I DELIVERED
MOST OF YOU.
I'M TELLING YOU
TO LISTEN TO THIS MAN.
HE'S THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN HELP US.
[Man] WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO DO?
[Clamoring]
GET IN YOUR CARS,
AND MEET US AT
THE WHATELEY PLACE.
COME ON.
[Heartbeat]
[Wind howling]
AH!
[Groans]
[Heartbeat]
AH!
[Cracking]
LISTEN!
[Heartbeat]
[Wind howling]
WHAT IN GOD'S NAME
IS THAT?
I'VE NEVER HEARD
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
HENRY, IT'S REALLY
HAPPENING, ISN'T IT?
IT'S MOVING
TOWARD THE HILL.
THE DEVIL'S
HOPYARD.
WE'VE GOT
TO GET UP THERE.
[Moaning]
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
LET'S ALL SPREAD OUT,
AND ALL OF YOU,
STAY ON YOUR TOES.
[Man] HURRY UP,
LET'S GO.
[Man] START UP THAT WAY.
YOU ALL RIGHT,
REEGER?
YEAH.
GO ON,
I'LL CATCH UP.
I JAMMED
THE DAMN RIFLE.
[Man] YOU FIND
ANYTHING?
[Heartbeat]
[Wind howling]
[Growling]
[Gunshot]
AH!
[Reeger]
[Growling]
AH!
[Loud growling]
[Reeger]
AH!
[Speaking ancient,
cryptic language]
[Moaning]
[Thunder]
MY GOD,
WHAT'S HE DOING?
[Moaning]
[Speaking ancient,
cryptic language]
[Thunder]
YOG-SOTHOTH.
[Speaking ancient,
cryptic language]
YOG-SOTHOTH.
[Thunder]
YOG-SOTHOTH!
[Speaking ancient,
cryptic language]
[Thunder]
[Speaking ancient,
cryptic language]
AH!
[Roaring]
NO.
OH, NO. NO.
I'M SORRY, NANCY.
THERE WERE 2 CHILDREN
BORN THAT NIGHT
25 YEARS AGO.
DR. CORY WAS TOLD
THE OTHER ONE DIED,
BUT IT DIDN'T.
IT WAS CAUGHT BETWEEN
THIS WORLD AND ANOTHER.
WILBUR'S TWIN
TOOK AFTER THE FATHER.
AND THE FATHER?
NOT OF THIS EARTH.
IT'S ALL OVER NOW.
THE LAST OF
THE WHATELEYS IS DEAD.
[Heartbeat]