We spent last summer training
at our grandfather's cabin.
Grandpa wanted to give
us the ultimate test.
We just got too good for him.
-Your level is ninja daycare.
-No, yours is!
Grow up, you two.
Grandpa said we still
had lots to learn.
Come on!
Why'd you get in my way, Colt?
I had him.
You didn't even get near him, Tum Tum.
I did too. Didn't l, Rocky?
Looks like grandpa wins again.
Keep your eyes on the target.
Wipe all thoughts from your mind...
...and keep your energy focused
on the target.
Watch the bull's-eye grow in front
of your eyes.
And when it gets as big as a melon....
I want you to look within yourself.
And remember, all ninjas...
...heart...
...mind and body!
And spirit.
Now I've taught you all I know.
And it's time for you
to go and study...
...with a teacher far greater
than myself.
Japan, Japan, Japan!
We get to go to Japan?
All right. Quiet, quiet.
I must go next week...
...to my hometown in Koga.
And I have arranged for you...
...to come with me to study
with the Grand Master!
All right! Grand Master!
-I never knew that was there.
-That's the point.
Fifty years ago...
...I was just about your age.
I fought for the honour
of receiving this dagger.
There was a legend about the dagger
and a samurai sword.
They could open the door
to a cave of gold...
-...Iaden with riches!
-Like a key?
Exactly.
The old master told me
the whole legend...
...when the dagger was passed along.
Many believed the story.
Koga, the boy who I defeated...
... was one of them.
When he lost, he tried to steal
the dagger from me.
What happened to that kid
who tried to steal your dagger?
Who knows?
Just little boys playing
a long time ago. But now...
...I must take this dagger...
...and present it to the winner
of the Ninja Tournament.
What about the cave of gold, Grandpa?
Can we visit it when we go to Japan?
Weren't you listening, twerp?
You need the sword too.
-Bigger twerp.
-Biggest.
-Bigger-est.
-Boys, boys.
It's just a legend.
There is no cave of gold.
And the sword....
Who knows where it is?
I waited 50 years
for my revenge...
...Mori Shintaro.
Before you go to Japan...
...you will be tested
on the field of battle.
Now remember what I have taught you:
Control.
Restraint.
Concentration.
Unity.
Four strands of rope.
Now, separately you will snap.
But together you'll be strong.
Now get out there and kick butt!
All right. Get it up, son.
Michael, where are you?
Two, please.
One with the bun, one without.
-It's on me.
-Thanks.
-When does the ice cream guy get here?
-ln a half-hour.
Hi, Lisa DiMarino.
Bye, Lisa!
Don't they look adorable
in their uniforms?
Welcome to the league championship
playoffs.
This game will determine who goes home
proudly with the championship trophy:
The Dragons...
...or the Mustangs.
Play ball!
Batter up!
-Safe!
-Michael!
You're playing baseball!
Catch the ball, not the weenie!
Hey, come on, break it up. Back off.
Don't dig so deep. You'll only
be here for one more pitch.
Hey, batter!
Couldn't hit with a telephone pole.
Little Pony couldn't hit a full moon.
Rocky! Concentration!
Heart.
Mind.
Body.
Lisa?
You're home! Safe! Here's the ball.
Stepping up to the plate for the
Mustangs, number 11, Gerald Thomas.
He doesn't come alive very often.
But when he does, he really lets go.
It's a long drive.
It's back, back, back!
And it's out of here!
It's on the parkway!
At bat for the Dragons, number 14,
Jeffrey Douglas!
Batter's got time.
Remember the bull's-eye!
Time!
Get your shoe here, son.
Two down. Let's go.
Strength in restraint! Control!
Shall we play ball, boys?
Stop!
Don't do it, Jeffrey!
Scramble!
Thank you.
This is the most disgraceful display
I have ever seen in baseball history!
You're supposed to learn how to be
citizens and sportsmen, not hooligans!
I am suspending this game for one week
to give you a chance to cool down!
The game starts over next Sunday.
That is if, by then,
any of you decide to grow up!
We're not going to Japan.
What?
-I want to go.
-I want to play.
Stop it! "l want, I want."
What's the matter with you guys?
I was embarrassed and ashamed of your
behaviour, and you should be too.
How can I pay attention with Grandpa
pestering me from the stands?
-That's embarrassing.
-Enough.
Just what were you looking at
when you were supposed to be pitching?
Lisa DiMarino, Lisa DiMarino....
And Jeffrey, fighting like that.
What have I said about your temper?
You have to learn to control it.
Well, I wonder where he gets it from.
You see what this ninja stuff does?
All they want to do is fight.
Does this mean no Japan?
It may mean no to a lot of things
until all of you decide to grow up.
This sucks.
What are you doing dreaming
about Lisa DiMarino on the plate?
Four strands.
Hey! I didn't do that!
That was-- And Rocky!
I think the rope is unravelling.
One, two, three-- Three....
-Four!
Who?
Stop!
Somebody pull the plug!
What's the name of your band?
-Tough Noogies.
-Alien Vomit.
Get behind the bar.
The rest of you clowns...
...get out of my club!
There's a phone call for you.
Thank you.
Hey, Uncle!
How's the weather in Japan?
My idiot nephew, forget the weather.
Did you get the pictures?
Oh, yeah.
Cool knife.
I will pay you well...
...to perform this task for me.
We'll take it!
The tickets are for Tokyo, Japan.
How many tickets, boys?
All right, huddle up.
It's Japan. How often do you get this
chance? Are you gonna throw it away?
What about the championship?
You want to throw that away?
-I want to go.
-Your vote doesn't count.
It does too.
You could pitch the winning game.
What do you think Lisa would think?
I can't wait all day.
We voted...
...we're gonna play baseball.
Just one ticket.
I'll come pick it up. Thanks.
I voted to go, Grandpa.
Thank you, Tum Tum, for wanting
to continue your ninja training.
Ninja? I really wanted to go there
to learn how to be a sumo wrestler.
You know how much those guys get
to eat every day?
Don't burn dinner, and clean
up the mess afterwards.
By the time you get back,
dinner will be on the table.
I think that's him.
The guy who we're
trying to steal this from.
No wonder your uncle's offering
20 grand.
He's gone.
That means the cabin's empty.
Rock 'n' roll!
Someone's coming.
Robbers.
Or maybe somebody's lost.
A ninja must always be prepared
for battle. Or to give directions.
We should also steal some VCRs....
-Directions?
-I don't think so.
Let's murder-lize them!
Let's see what we have here
for our guests.
Eggs, old pie....
Let me have a taste of it.
I'll keep watch, you two go in.
-I'll flatten you!
-Focus!
What are you hitting me for?
I gotta do all the work around here.
Piece of cake. Okay. On three.
Wait. Wait.
Is that the one after two?
One...
...two....
--three!
Get off of me!
Look, a desk!
If you were gonna hide
a letter opener...
...wouldn't you hide it in a desk?
I found it.
See? Let's go.
Were you hatched from a moron egg?
Does that look like this?
Get a better scent.
You sniff around down here.
I'll go upstairs.
Who's there?
How hard can it be
to find a little dagger?
Slam?
Slam, man. You find it?
-Lemon meringue.
-Banana cream, bozo!
Nice try.
Vinnie!
Come on, cheesehead!
Was that a yes?
I don't think the house is empty.
There's nobody here.
You're right.
There's somebody here.
I'm tired of playing with you--
That's it, you runts! You're mine!
Please, Mr. Man, don't hurt us.
Come on!
Get over here!
Who are you, teenage mutant wannabes?
We're the Three Ninjas!
-Let's go while we're still standing.
-I'm with that.
Out of my way, Slam. I'm out of here!
I'm working with idiots.
Oh, yeah? Come on. Try and get me.
Come on, come on.
Let's get him!
Watch the tree! Watch the tree!
Chickens.
Come on. Go, go, go.
-Vinnie!
-What are you doing?
Now, if I was a dagger,
where would I hi--?
Will you hurry?
I did it!
Come see us again!
I thought it was supposed to be empty.
It was supposed to be an easy job.
-Stop!
-Glam said it was empty.
We forgot Glam!
He's here. Drive!
-Wasn't that great?
-That was awesome.
I can't believe the oil trick
worked twice.
What?
I thought you'd have dinner ready.
What's this mess?
-Three guys--
-Tried to rob the cabin!
What did they want to rob?
-TVs and stuff. We heard them.
-But we got rid of them.
They finally gave up and ran away.
We used what you taught us.
We were great.
A true ninja never brags
about his skills.
The next time, call the police.
There were these...security guards.
-And....
-Watchdogs!
-I got close to it. I saw it.
-Do you have the dagger?
No, I don't have it. It's not like
it's exactly in my hands.
I want the dagger in my hands tomorrow.
Understand? Tomorrow!
Get the dagger and be at my office
here in Tokyo...
...or you will receive no pay.
Love you.
We're dropping Dad at the airport.
He's disappointed they aren't going.
Everything they need to know
they can learn from baseball, like me.
Don't forget your dad
was a kid once too.
I thought he was born full-grown
with a briefcase.
That's enough.
When I was a kid, I played
like a member of the team.
The way you'll play next week, right?
Michael, come on!
Hey! Who ate my Good & Plenty?
This should protect my bag.
Mousetrap.
I almost forgot
the most important thing.
They're taking the dagger.
Wait, wait, wait.
-Which bags are yours?
-The one without the sticker.
Which one?
Oh, here it is.
Goodbye. Wish you
were coming with me.
Me too, Grandpa.
There he goes!
-Bye, Dad.
-Bye, Grandpa.
Vacation time!
This is terrible. I'm so sorry.
I'm just a stupid American.
Very sorry. Sorry, sir. Sorry.
Get in! Get in! Get in!
Greetings, Uncle!
I was expecting you earlier.
Don't touch me!
Uncle, we did your bidding,
and we got the goods right here.
-Quiet, fool.
-Give it to me!
-Give it to him!
Hey, nice vase.
Behold! The dagger of doom.
-I can explain this.
-You have failed!
Ishikawa! Show them
how we deal with fools!
Hey, that's our lead singer, you!
We can do instrumentals.
We don't need lyrics.
Can we talk about this?
Nephew, I am much dissatisfied.
But I am prepared to give you...
...another chance.
You say Mori Shintaro is in Japan.
Keep an eye on him.
Listen to every word he says.
And bring back that dagger to me!
My fortune says,
"Love appears on a journey."
You blew that one for us.
-You voted to stay too.
-I know.
But I wish I hadn't.
Besides, all love fortunes
are for Rocky.
That means you got mine.
What's it say?
Put them on. Grandpa says you
make it worse when you squint.
Put them on, Rocky.
We won't make fun of you.
The four-eyed beast!
Mine says I have an insect for a
brother, and I should squash him!
Help me!
-He's right.
-Yeah.
You do look like a four-eyed beast.
Only I can call my brother that.
What do you call him? My Little Pony?
Kick their butts, Colt.
I'd love to see you try. Come on.
Let's go. Let's go inside.
-Now!
-You're not my boss.
I said, now!
Yeah, go inside. The Strike Out Kid.
See you Sunday, Dragons!
You're acting like Grandpa.
You should have murder-lized them.
You made me look like a wimp
in front of those guys.
Chill, it's Grandpa.
Well, hello, boys! I'm all right.
I'm in a hospital.
What's wrong?
Oh, I was in a tiny car accident.
A few bruises.
I'm at the mercy of a nurse
that doesn't speak English.
Actually, she's a witch
posing as a nurse.
Do you mind?
I'm talking to my grandson.
I had all my luggage stolen.
They took everything.
Even the dagger.
They stole the dagger.
You vampire!
I saw this weird Japanese guy
with long, white hair running away.
-Don't tell your mom and dad.
-We won't.
I'm in Tokyo General.
Oh, it's a fine hospital.
Except for this wicked nurse
with a face like a dragon's butt.
Some people here do understand
English, Mr. Shintaro!
Hope you feel better soon. Bye.
-Who hit him?
-A Japanese guy with white hair.
Like the jerko at the cabin?
-Oh, no!
-Those guys are in Japan!
This isn't my bag.
This is Grandpa's bag. Look.
They were after the dagger.
We gotta go there.
We gotta help Grandpa.
What about the baseball game?
-That's a game. This is Grandpa.
-But where are my Ding Dongs?
Forget your Ding Dongs.
We gotta work fast.
First, I'll take care of the tickets.
Okay, so that's three
children's fares to Tokyo.
-We're almost grown-up.
-The name on the card?
Mori Shintaro. He's my grandfather.
We'll need his authorization.
Can I talk to him?
Sure. Colt, do you have Grandpa's
message from the answering machine?
-Hello.
-Hello, Mr. Shintaro? How are you?
I'm all right.
That's nice. I just took
a reservation from--
-My grandson.
-Yes, that's what he said.
Three seats this afternoon to....
-Tokyo.
-Yes!
I have your authorization for three
first-class children's tickets...
...to Tokyo, totalling $1 1,364?
I'm sorry?
Is this amount okay with you?
-Yes, everything, you vampire!
-Really, sir! I don't set the prices.
I just work here.
I'll run this through.
They can pick
the tickets up at the airport.
Ugly witch.
Yeah? Well, you know what you are?
Goodbye.
All right, we got a lot to do.
I'll write a note to Mom and Dad.
Colt, find money,
and, Tum Tum, call a shuttle.
We'll be packed on time.
How will we do all that
before Mom and Dad get home?
You've heard of ingenuity, right?
Well, this is "ninja-nuity."
-Tum Tum!
-I don't want to leave Mom and Dad.
Tum Tum, it's for Grandpa.
Happy?
-How fast can you get us to LAX?
-Buckle up.
Colt?
Tum Tum?
Rocky?
It's okay. We'll stick together.
Rocky, catch.
You're out!
She thank you. Want to repay you.
Could you take us
to Tokyo General Hospital?
She want to know, are you sick?
We're fine.
But our grandpa's there.
-Mori Shintaro. Do you know him?
-No, but it will be our pleasure.
Can't you do that more gently?
Really, Mr. Shintaro! My grandkids
behave better than you do.
My grandchildren can drive you
out of town with their ninja sticks.
-He's right! We could!
-That's right, Tum Tum....
Boys! What are you doing here?
Grandpa, we missed you!
Nurse Hino, these are my three ninjas!
Rocky, Colt and Tum Tum.
Would you get that--?
Get out of here!
Well, boys. Colt, what
about the baseball game?
You're more important, Grandpa.
-We think you're in danger.
-What kind of danger?
You know the Japanese guy with
the white hair who stole your luggage?
He tried to rob the cabin.
How do you know?
Did he look like he was trying
to be a grunge-rock stud?
-The guy with the ugly white hair.
-The troll hair!
You know, a real wannabe type.
Oh, yeah.
Will you shut up, please?
I think they were after the dagger.
Well, they have it now.
-Rocky, how?
-You took Tum Tum's bag by mistake.
And they got my Ding Dongs.
Did you hear that?
Those kids got it!
So you came all this way because
you thought I needed your help.
What'd you tell your parents?
Well....
Oh, no.
We left them a note.
We have to call them
and tell them what's going on.
Meanwhile, we'd better make plans
about the dagger.
Hello, Jessica!
How's everything? How's the weather?
She's pissed.
Hi, Mom.
Jessica, it's not their fault.
I missed them and I sent for them.
Here, you talk to Tum Tum.
Hi, Mom. No.
Hey, boys.
The tournament is going on
right now in Koga.
I want you to take this dagger...
...and present it to the winner
of the competition.
-What about you?
-I'll meet you in Koga.
What? Oh, Ma.
Now do this for me.
Set the beeper on your watch.
Call us every day
at 2 p.m., Tokyo time.
Okay, Mom, okay, got it. 2 p.m.
Mom wants to say goodbye!
-Bye.
-Bye, Mom.
Nurse Hino, I thought I told you
to go away!
Do you know how I deal
with troublesome patients?
Nurse Hino, can I make a deal
with you?
I'll let you use me
as a pin cushion...
...if you see to it that my boys
get on the train to Koga.
I'll be glad to help.
-It's the end of my shift anyway.
-Thank God.
Nurse Shibuya will be taking my place.
I hope we make it there in time.
-I hope we see some great ninjas.
-I hope there's food.
Is this what Grandpa
wanted us to learn?
The next level of screaming?
This guy's good.
I could take him.
Hey, Colt. If number 16 wins this
one, he'll be in the finals.
I'll be right back.
Hey, that guy's not bad.
He's kind of wild, like Colt.
Colt!
Come on, he'll get his
brains splattered.
Stay here. Maybe it's the lesson
Grandpa had in mind.
Yes!
Ow!
A girl?
I'm such a spaz.
Rocky?
If she's the winner,
does that mean we give her this?
Let's go ask Mr. Big over there.
I'm sorry, you're going too fast.
Perhaps I can help.
I speak some English.
Tell him we bring this
from our grandfather, Mori Shintaro.
Whoa! Look at those feet!
He say he know everything. He spoke
with your grandfather from Tokyo.
Bet he's ticklish.
He says ceremony can wait a few
days, until Mori Shintaro arrive.
We must uphold the tradition.
What shall we do with this?
Grand Master say if your grandfather
trusted you with it, so does he.
Colt got beat by a girl!
-I'm still better than you.
-Shut up, spaz!
You are worthy opponent, Spaz.
Oh, no. It's Colt.
This is Rocky and Tum Tum.
I am Miyo. This is my mother.
I would love to hear about America.
You live near Bart Simpson?
-No.
-Were do you stay in Koga?
We didn't plan anything.
Then you come home with us.
We'd be honoured. But we must hurry.
One more important place to go.
Every year she is the only girl
to try out.
Hey, who lives in that castle over
there? The evil umpire?
Castle Hikone. No one live there.
Very, very old.
-Maybe she should stick to ninja.
-Shut up.
He tell me to come back
when I learn to catch.
He say because of ninja I am
good at swinging butt.
What?
You know, swing my butt.
You mean your "bat."
Yes. My butt.
Hey, I got an idea.
-You teach us ninja.
-And we'll teach you baseball.
Yes!
Grand Master's house. Run!
-Greetings, Uncle!
-Where have you been?
Doing your bidding, my dearest blood
of my blood. Listen to this.
Rock 'n' roll!
Stop! Why are you wasting my time?
Relax, san. What's the big deal?
Wrong tape.
Here, go on.
Just a second.
The tournament is going on
right now in Koga.
So I want you to take this dagger
and present it...
-... to the winner of the competition.
-That is his plan.
Return the dagger to the Grand Master.
Perfection.
I will be ready for him.
Ishikawa, prepare for our journey.
What about our dough?
I asked for a dagger,
you bring me a tape.
Two tapes.
No payment!
You have failed me.
Take care of them!
This is great. Rocky...
...tell Miyo's mother how
good this is.
-Thank you.
-We know my brother's a picky eater.
Your Japanese is getting good, Rocky.
You should say something
to the Grand Master.
Like, "Clip your toenails."
I have an idea to help.
Come, I will show you.
This book helps me learn
your language.
See?
I don't read Japanese.
You can teach me a few words.
No, it's half in English.
Don't you see?
Well, why don't you just read it
to me? You're better at this.
Just go ahead. Just sound it out.
"Hello."
"Nice to meet you."
Ow!
Rocky loves Miyo!
Grand Master say he will start
your training today too.
We're ready for him.
You were a great help, Miyo.
I wish I could go with you.
-Well, good luck.
-Thanks.
We'll do great. See you later.
-Bye, Miyo!
Bye, Miyo. My little chicken pot pie.
So...
...you are the grandsons
of Mori Shintaro.
Hey, how come you didn't speak English
to us at the tournament?
In front of the other people?
They would not understand us.
It would be rude.
Did you bring the dagger
your grandfather gave you?
I thought you wanted to wait
till he arrived.
I changed my mind.
I want it now.
Weren't you shorter the other day?
Rocky! Colt! Tum Tum!
He's a fake!
Scramble!
You gonna talk us to death?
Oh, no. Mom!
Rocky!
-Give me the phone!
-Sure.
Catch.
It's about time. You're late.
Hey, Mom. It's me.
What's going on?
Not much.
You know, it's just
a small town in Japan.
Colt, Mom wants to talk to you.
Coming down!
Hi, Mom. Dad!
I thought there wasn't gonna
be any ninja stuff.
We're not. We're seeing
the sights and meeting the people.
When you get home, we're having
a long talk about responsibility.
Fine. I'll set aside a month.
Don't be a smart kid.
I'm not being a smart kid.
Rocky wants to talk to you.
Hi, Dad. The noise? What noise?
It's the TV. It's a kung fu movie.
Tum Tum, turn it down!
Hang on a sec.
Grandpa? He's out fishing
with friends.
Yeah, gotta go. Bye.
Come on, Rocky!
Rocky!
All right, Miyo!
Where have you guys been?
So that's where you were?
Quickly, but be careful.
This way, secret passageway
to outside.
You said this was a secret.
This is my ninja compound.
My army trains here.
Don't even think of escaping.
Let me go, you big hairy ape!
Did I say ape? Forget it.
It's not fair to the other apes.
I just knew it was a bad idea
coming to Japan.
What? You voted for it
in the first place.
I just wish I was home.
I want to see Mom and Dad.
I want to be in my own house.
I want to eat a real cheeseburger
with real cheese.
I knew this would come to food.
What is a ninja?
Rocky, stop being like Grandpa.
A body. A spirit. A mind.
Tum Tum?
A heart.
Pretty quiet around here without
the team, huh, coach?
They don't even seem to care
what I think anymore.
They listen to their Grandpa
more than me.
They listen to their Grandpa because
their Grandpa listens to them.
I wish they could behave more like....
-Like what? Like you?
-Yeah.
They can't. They're not you.
They're Samuel and Jeffrey
and Michael.
-No, they're not.
-They're not?
They're Rocky and Colt and Tum Tum.
-I just wish they'd come home.
-Yeah.
I will give you one last chance.
I have the dagger and the samurai
sword, but they tell me nothing.
Only one man knows their secret...
...and that is Mori Shintaro.
Are you capable of kidnapping
an old man?
-Uncle.
-A hospitalized old man?
I've a marvellous idea.
This is stupid. I feel ridiculous.
Quiet, you.
The phone was ringing.
I thought it was for me.
Straighten up.
Good day, ladies. Hello.
Hello.
-That was him!
-That was him?
Yo, sir! Excuse me, we have--
-Yes?
-Your therapy.
I had my physical therapy today.
-I don't mean therapy.
-We're discharging you.
Oh, I see.
I never saw you lovely
young ladies before.
Oh, that's because we've
been on holiday.
I'm getting tired of this!
You're on the wrong floor, girls.
Mine!
Bye, girls.
Oh, my leg, my foot, my ankle!
Oh, Vinnie!
Say something! What kind of
leader are you?
-Surgery preparation.
-Yeah, surgery.
Vinnie! Glam!
No surgery, we're fine! We're fine!
Why have you brought me here?
Why have you put me in
these clothes? Why?
Leave us.
Who are you?
A boy from your childhood.
Koga!
-Boys!
-Grandpa!
Are you all right?
We're okay, Grandpa.
What about you?
Are they hurting you?
Grandpa, get us out of here.
Please?
I'll try my best.
Who's in there with you?
Rocky's girlfriend.
She's not my girlfriend.
Well, I mean....
Remember: four strands of rope.
The cave. Where is the cave?
According to legend...
...the cave is beneath Castle Hikone.
The dagger. The dagger.
The sword and the dagger are the keys.
Now let my grandchildren go!
You have someplace else to go first.
Castle Hikone.
A ninja must use everything around him
to his advantage.
But there's nothing here we can use.
I still have a ninja ball.
I don't even
have my jellybeans anymore.
Forget it. There's no way to escape.
We don't have to.
We just have to
make it look like we did.
Don't you just hate us?
They must be on their way
to Castle Hikone.
-My bag!
-Where's that?
I know where it is.
-What do we do?
-Let's kick their butts!
-Light up their eyes!
-Let's light these fat boys up.
Colt! Get him off me!
How are we gonna get there?
On the wings of eagles.
I don't want to fly!
Come on! It's just like
a roller coaster.
I hate roller coasters!
I want to go down!
The entrance is down an old well.
Over there.
Ah, here it is!
Watch where you're going!
I am watching.
-Look out for that tree!
-What tree?
There's the door.
The sword.
The dagger!
The gate to my cave of gold.
Ishikawa, wait here.
Look! The dagger and the sword.
-Maybe you should leave it there.
-No, we might need it.
I don't like the look of this place.
It's sealed shut.
Nice job, spaz.
What is this place?
It's creepy, that's what it is.
Four strands of rope.
These are ancient samurai warriors!
Your riches are nothing
but skulls and bones!
You're chasing fairy tales...
...and I'm not gonna be
buried here for your greed!
There is no cave of gold.
No!
A fairy tale?
It is a cave of gold!
The legend was true!
Yes. It is true.
I-- I beg of you.
The brave warrior,
begging for his life.
Goodbye, Mori Shintaro.
I beat you once, Koga.
That was a long time ago, Grandpa.
Behind you!
Excuse me, Mr. Man.
This way!
Colt!
We're coming!
I will win, because you
are controlled by your greed!
-Don't move.
-Fifty years ago...
...I accidentally scarred your face.
What has happened to your soul,
that I truly regret.
No more talking.
Your fate is to be buried here.
Let's go!
You mean, "Scramble!"
Koga, it's not worth it.
Come with me.
Come on!
Tum Tum, watch out behind you.
Here comes the bag.
-Hurry up!
-Come on!
I'm trying!
I want to find it!
-Please!
-Tum Tum!
I found it!
-Let's go!
-Hurry!
-Go!
-Please hurry!
I found my Ding Dongs.
A true ninja is free from all desire.
It took me a long time
to understand that, Mori Shintaro.
From our days in Koga...
...until this moment.
Slow learner.
You are all very brave ninjas.
All of you.
Grandpa, this is Miyo.
Champion of the Koga Dojo.
You? A young lady?
As this was presented to me
by a ninja master...
...I pass this to you.
You have achieved...
...ninja level at the
highest mastery of mind....
-Body.
-Spirit.
And heart.
Keep this dagger...
...till the day you will present it...
...to a young ninja.
This is better
than winning World Cereals.
I think you mean "Series."
What I said, "Cereals."
It's too bad we missed our game.
I thought it wasn't till Sunday.
-lt is Sunday.
-Not in America. It's Saturday.
-lf we catch a plane today....
-We can make it!
What are you gonna do?
You can't play with only six players.
-The rest of them are off on vacation.
-What are you gonna do?
I guess we have no choice.
I forfeit.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm sorry to say...
...due to a shortage of players,
the Dragons have announced--
Play ball!
Oh, this is great timing!
This is great. Let's play ball, huh?
You heard him!
Play ball!
-I missed you so much.
-And the boys.
The big question on our mind is:
Will this be a baseball game
or a wrestling match?
-Out!
-Two down, everybody.
Dragons down by one.
Two strikes, runners at
second and third. Here we go.
Come on, Colt! Bring me home!
Thanks for the
air-conditioning, horsy.
Now batting, number 10,
Gerald Thomas.
It's a bloop single to left.
Runner digging for third base.
That's hitting below the belt.
I hope the Mustangs won't turn
this into a wrestling match.
Replacing number 25
for the Dragons is number 21.
That player doesn't seem
to be on the roster.
Top of the 7th, Mustangs up 4 to 2.
Bases are loaded, they have a chance
to blow it wide open. And the pitch.
Long drive, deep centre field.
The centre fielder going back,
back to the wall.
Leaping!
A great catch!
By a girl!
Great! That was a great catch.
Everybody gather around.
All right, listen up.
It's our last three at bat.
Let's just go out there
and do our best, all right?
-All right.
-Okay!
Boys, come here.
Look, win or lose...
...I just wanted to tell you...
...that I'm really very proud of you.
You're real sportsmen out there.
You see? You learn
about life through baseball.
With a little bit
of ninja thrown in, huh?
I'm really glad to have you home, men.
Dad?
Four strands of rope.
Let's murder-lize them!
Yeah!
Bottom of the 7th. Last chance.
The Dragons need three runs
to win this championship.
Strike!
Goes to bunt.
Swings away!
Whoa, almost hit
the third baseman's head off!
-A base hit.
-Come on, Rocky!
All right, Colt!
Hey, Strikeout Kid!
Come on, ninja-nuity!
All right, Colt! You can hit now!
Come on, horsy.
Bet you can't hit this one.
Come on, Darren!
Strike!
And another one!
Two strikes, two outs. One more strike
and the Mustangs win the championship.
And the pitch.
It's a long drive,
deep left field. Way back!
Way back!
Dragons could win the championship!
It's headed towards the foul pole.
Twisting, turning, spinning.
-Foul ball!
-Oh, no!
It's a foul ball! A foul ball.
Colt.
Here. Use my butt.
I carved my name for luck,
strength and control.
Ninja-nuity.
Come on, son! Come on, you can do it!
Go get them!
Long foul ball. Bet you can't
hit it again, loser.
Batter up!
Throw at this batter one more time,
you're gonna forfeit the game, coach.
Play ball!
Watch the bull's-eye grow
in front of your eyes.
And when it gets as big as a melon....
The Dragons win the league
championship! The Dragons win!
This game ain't over yet.
Extra innings in the parking lot.
Come on, fellas.
You'll show them
when you get back to Koga.
Yes. I tell them how I kicked bat.
I think you mean-- Oh, never mind.
You won the first round,
but the game ain't over yet.
I can handle it.
Tell you what. One on one.
Your best guy. You can pick
any one of us to fight against.
Okay.
I pick you.
You ruined my home run, girl.
Oh, come on. She's just a girl.
Hey, you play on a guys' team,
you play by guys' rules.
She's just visiting.
Pick me. I'll fight you.
Come here.
Well, I tried.
I said, come here!
What? Where'd she go?
I hope there's more food
in our next adventure.
See you next time. Bye!
Subtitles by
SDl Media Group