Free Movies Downloads
http://bon99.com
Spring - 1649
So, even though you're a whore,
you refuse me?
If I don't like someone...
then I don't like him.
And I don't like you.
What?
You are persistent!...
I am a prostitute
because I like it.
But I won't sleep with someone
who disgusts me.
You rude bitch!
Are you going to kill me?
Well, then do your best.
I'd like to see it.
Don't get involved!
If she doesn't like you...
just leave.
Bastard!
We won't forget this!
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Don't give up your life
so easily.
Excuse me... what is your name?
My name isn't important.
Maybe we'll meet again
under better times.
My name is Kyara...
come visit anytime.
I hope I see him again.
FEMALE NINJAS MAGIC CHRONICLES 2
Kunoichi Ninpo-cho ll: Seishojo no Hiho
Religious Census Magistrate's Office
Okay, next!
*Somon Bugyo: Baba Samemasa*
My Christ...
I can't step on him.
You are a secret Christian!
Take her to the prison!
Yes! Right away!
In the 17th century, the Shogunate
tried to wipe out Christianity.
Innocent people were persecuted
for their religious beliefs.
Many were forced to practice
their religion in secrecy.
I am innocent of any crime!
You are a monster!
I'll discover your deepest secrets.
You are wearing a bell.
I hear it inside your body.
I have no bell.
Yes, you do. The bell of Christ
is inside your body.
The bell is jingling because
I'm holding this cross near.
Matsudaira Izu-no-Kami's Mansion
Oh? So you found it, Chuo...
It wasn't just idle gossip,
nor a made-up story...
Tenth year
Christian Lord, Otomo Sorin
and four other Christians
asked for help.
*Roju Matsudaira Izu-no-kami Nobutsuna*
The Vatican sent money.
* Roju Matsudaira Izu-no-kami Nobutsuna *
They want to establish their religion in Japan,
so they sent a shipment of 100,000 gold coins.
100,000 coins?... That would be
over a million ryo!
The money was hidden
somewhere near Shinagawa,
and it will remain hidden until
the Christians are ready to act.
The key to its whereabouts
lies with this cross.
We found the first of the five bells
inside the girl.
Once we get them all, we'll know
the location of the fortune.
Most likely, the bell is
hidden in the girl's vagina.
Now, I'll show you how to remove
it without touching her...
Look at this! Just as we heard!
There's a message on the bell.
Saint and Salt water
What does this mean? The two
words don't mean anything.
No. Remember... there
are five bells altogether
Each of them are hidden inside
a Christian female...
Females who have pledged
obedience to Princess Maria Ten.
She holds the ultimate answer.
Princess Maria Ten.
She is the granddaughter of the
Christian Daimyo Otomo Sorin...
The princess is protected by
5 Catholic female ninjas.
It's frightening to comprehend...
A religion that would hide a
bell inside a girl's vagina!
But...
Regardless... I can't let
the money slip away.
Contact Amakusa Seiichiro.
I must see him immediately.
Oh! Christian slut...
you're awake.
Are you thirsty?
Do you want something?
I'm praying for salvation.
And I'm taking you with me.
Salvation? You mean 'death'?
I'm not going with you.
I curse you with my magic...
The Cross!
What have you done?
The cross in your eye
will never go away!
Princess Maria Ten!
Let her divine curse fill you!
Okyo!
Sisters! I'm going to my
salvation! Goodbye sisters!
Otomo Magic
The Cross
Okyo.
What are you doing here?
I'm not doing anything.
I saw you make the sign
of the cross. Are you Christian?
Young Noble, he's one of Otomo's
ninjas... Mikaeru Sukezo.
Seiichiro...
I want you to locate the Roman
treasure and claim it for us!
Yes, I'll accept with honor.
I'll do my best.
Mmmm. Very good. I'm happy.
You're the best and most trusted.
Your family will be rewarded
by the Shogunate.
Thank you, my lord.
For 60 years my family has known
poverty and unhappiness...
This is a grand opportunity
for my Amakusa Family.
Tell me your ideas... How will
you compromise the Christians?
I've collected the best ninja
army possible...
I'm Mahiru Kyonen.
My name is Uguisu Donin.
Hata Manjimaru.
Soga Mokubei.
Thank you for coming...
Army of Seiichiro! Do a good job!
Yes!
Seiichiro... please demonstrate
some of your ninja magic.
Yes...
My lord... try to attack me.
Are you sure?
- Yes -
Strike me as hard as you can...
This is my Echo Trick.
What did you do?
I'm sorry. This is a trick...
When you hit me...
Like an echo...
it returns to you.
This is very good magic.
Use it against the harlots.
It's a trick of my eyes...
As long as I can see...
I can use it.
Seiichiro... you are the perfect
Tokugawa warrior.
And now, like a good warrior,
it's time to fight!...
Do your best against
the bitches!
Religious Census Magistrate
Government Office
Thank you for accepting...
here is money from the Lord.
If you need anything more, just ask.
Thank you.
Prepare for a most ambitious job.
- I know that.
The Princess and the 4 remaining
girls are related to Lord Otomo.
They are very dangerous.
Do not underestimate them.
I understand they're well protected in Edo...
But I plan a direct approach.
I'll challenge them rationally.
I see.
Excuse me.
My daughter...
This is Amakusa Seiichiro.
I'm Shino.
- Nice to meet you.
I've heard much about you.
You're the samurai from the
Amakusa famlly.
She's not impressed with the
power and plight of our country.
She doesn't even respect
my political position.
Father...
Why do you feel that way?
His job is very important.
I don't like it.
Killing Christians is awful!...
They don't hurt anybody.
I apologize for her political views.
Excuse me, gentleman.
What is that?
Rufina.
Francesca.
Justa.
Savina.
Okyo is dead. But she killed the
man who stole her bell.
The Tokugawa family knows about
the bells and their secret.
Seiichiro the ninja has been
hired to find and kill you.
Sukezo... is Princess Maria Ten
in danger?
The Princess is safe for now.
But these are dangerous times
for Catholics.
Our treasure must remain
a secret.
I taught the ninja magic to you
for times like this.
You must be prepared to protect
the bells with your lives.
The others risked their lives to
protect their own bells.
No waiting or loyalty is necessary in battle.
Trust in God. Everything
will work out.
Yes.
Guard this place.
And be careful.
Go with God.
Amen.
I want the bells...
I don't want to kill them.
I can't allow that!
I'll protect them
with my life.
Do you value your life
so little? I'm ready!
Echo Magic! Now!
Otomo magic!
Blow darts!
Your eyes will never open!
You won't be able to use the
Echo Trick again... without eyes!
Can we stop?
- Yes.
Samurai!
You're burning up with fever!
Be strong! Strong!
Samurai! You're awake!
Who are you?
I'm Kyara. The whore you
helped once before.
Kyara!
Yes. I work in the brothel.
You helped me once.
Don't try to get up.
You can stay here until
you feel better.
But that's not a good idea...
it'd be bad for your business.
Don't worry. I can
do what I want...
But, tell me, what happened
to your eyes?...
There must be some reason...
perhaps because of this bell?
Give the bell back to me!
Give it to me! Give it!
Here.
I wouldn't care if you decided
to stay here forever... forever!
Come everyone! Look at these
incredible eggs.
They aren't the usual farm-eggs
you've been eating.
These are the eggs from
giant frogs.
And their taste is...
Get away! Move!
Merchant! Who gave you permission
to conduct business here?
Pay me your rent money
if you wish to continue!
Your tone doesn't match
your pretty face.
Pay me the money,
forget the flattery.
I'd like to pay you...
but I have no money.
Perhaps I could pay you with
some loving tonight?
What the hell are you doing?
- Is that how you treat a lady?
Stop the violence! Everyone has
to pay rent around here.
Mmmm? Who are you?
Me? I'm the one who has this...
What! But it's...
I took it from a samurai.
This is the rent money!
You!
... wait! wait!
Where are you, woman?
Come out!
I knew you would come for me.
Woman! It seems you know the
meaning of that bell...
You're a secret Christian!
My name is Okai!
Rufina Okai!
This bell is mine! And now I'll
take another one from your body!
Cherry Blossom Trick!...
Your body will get very hot
soon.
Hotter! Even hotter!...
Where is the bell?
Where?
I found it.
I have it!
I won!
You want more?
I understand.
Otomo magic!
Serpent tongue!
Otomo Magic - Serpent Tongue
Rufina Okai prays to meet God...
Amen.
Festival...
Treasure
Mahiru Kyonen died very quickly.
That's a strange name...
Who is he? Your partner? Friend?
You never answer my questions.
Kyara...
- What?
I need to find all five bells.
Five of them? Why?
I can't tell you why, but...
I'll find the bells
even though I'm blind...
I dedicate my life to the bells.
Very good! And I'll help you...
I've fallen in love with you...
Ask anything of me...
I'll keep them for you...
I'd never lose them.
Samurai...
That's fine.
Madam Kyara...?
What is it?
There is someone here
to see you. Someone named Shino.
Shino?
Oh, it's a visitor for me.
You have a lady visiting you?
That's not good.
Thank you for coming.
Do your eyes hurt?
It's inconvenient...
but there's no pain.
You are Seiichiro the ninja!
How did this happen?
It is embarrassing, but...
I lost a challenge.
will you take a message to
the Lord, Shino?...
So far, I have two bells...
- Two bells?
You don't need to tell him
anything more.
Kyara... come out.
I know you're hiding over there.
So you discovered me?
Well, I'm just curious.
This is Kyara. She nursed me
back to health.
Oh, she's very beautiful!
My name's Shino. I came to visit
him on behalf of my father.
How nice of you!
Kyara, did you hear a daughter of
Huchira died at Tomyo-ji Temple?
I knew about that.
Let's go to Hakone right away
There's a natural spring...
the water would help your eyes.
Well, let's go!
Kyara!
Hakone
It feels quite good.
I'm happy with you.
I feel like I'm in a dream.
Because you're with me,
You should always be with me.
When I'm with you...
I forget all the bad things.
You're lying. You never stop
thinking about the damn bells.
Well...
Don't worry. If you stay with me,
we'll find the bells.
Spring God...
make his eyes better.
Hot!
It's not good to sneak up
on people.
Young Noble, I heard you had an
unfortunate accident.
What did he call you?
My eyes won't affect anything.
Good. I feel much better now.
Mokubei and Manjimaru are coming.
I see.
Who is this man?
I'm sorry. I didn't introduce
myself... Uguisu Donin.
Uguisu? Like the bird?
This is a special place...
It's especially refreshing to
see such a pretty nude lady...
I must pray now...
He's too strange!
Ouch! It's hot!
I'm so surprised... Samurai,
you're from such a good family,
You're right. He is from a good
family...
Certainly above your level.
Don't fight.
Fine! So what if I'm just
a whore?!
Stop, Kyara. 'Young Noble' is only a
name...
In truth, I don't have anything...
No house, no money...
Only this band of ninjas.
Oh? Is that right?
And I have you, Kyara.
Sweetheart.
I'll get some more sake.
Young Noble, can you trust Kyara?
What do you mean?
She could be one of the
secret Christians.
Mokubei, how dare you!
I just saying... sometimes it's
safer to think that way.
Be wary of anyone who wants to
get close to you.
There's no way she would've
helped me...
if she were a Christian.
I guess she wouldn't have given
you the bells...
if she were a Christian.
Kyara doesn't have a bell
in her body...
And she's definitely not
a virgin!
When I think about Kyara the
darkness in my eyes gets bright...
but I haven't forgotten my training.
I'll recover the bells.
Somehow I'll get them.
And she'll continue to help me.
Goodnight, samurai.
Come over here.
Samurai!
I want to be close to you
tonight.
Samurai! I'm so happy.
So happy!
Well, well. I'm surprised to find you up
so early in the morning.
I'm a woman... with things to do...
do you play that lute?
Would you like to hear
'Bateren no Goeika'?
Please stop!
I hate that song!
That's good... most Christians
I've met love that song.
Stop playing! I simply have a
headache... from lack of sleep.
Oh? You haven't been
sleeping well?
Young Noble, I have information
for you.
There's talk about a stranger
living on the outskirts of town.
The townspeople say
she's a hermit.
She doesn't want people to see
her face.
And she says weird prayers.
Prayers?
You don't think she's saying
Christian prayers?
Uguisu went to investigate.
We should go, too.
Mokubei, you carry this.
Yes, Young Noble.
I'm sorry sweet Christ...
I'm wearing these clothes to
protect myself... and the bell.
Do you like this?
Eh, Christian girl?...
Your body is going to sing...
with my Lute Trick!
The string is made from an
enforced spider's web.
You can't lift your hands
from it.
Now... I'm going to investigate.
No! Please stop!
I'm going to enter you!
Prepare!
Give me the bell...
Give it to me!
River - Descent
I'll kill you!
Otomo magic moon water bubble!
Otomo Magic
Moon Water Bubble
Be strong!
I've been poisoned!
- Uguisu! Uguisu!
Young Noble, good luck. I hope your
family regains its power.
Uguisu!
- Uguisu!
Princess Maria Ten!
Francesca Oyu is coming
coming to salvation.
Amen.
Young Noble, I'll find the next bell
with this...
Be careful!
The cross is mine.
Mokubei... after her!
Do it now!
Umbrella Trick!
I'll go ahead.
Tell me! Are you Princess Maria?
You're my enemy!
I don't know if you're Otomo's
granddaughter... but you'll die!
Princess Maria Ten...
Justa Ofue is coming to see God.
Ofue... I'll take your bell.
Sink - Under
Otomo magic
Dead Eyes Portrait.
I thought you were alive.
Otomo Magic Dead Eyes Portrait
That was a great trick...
I saw the face of your attacker.
Justa, die quietly now...
Salvation awaits.
We have four bells, but we've
lost many brave fighters.
You can't have weak emotions
over this.
Remember your goal...
the plight of your family.
True. But after all this...
we still don't know the secret.
Samurai, I think I know how
to read the eight symbols.
I think this is it...
Saint - Treasure...
Salt water - Under - Sink
River - Descent - Festival
I don't know what that means.
The first part 'Saint Treasure
Under Salt water'
is about the Catholic treasure
probably under the ocean.
And the second part... traveling
down a river to the right spot.
Does that make sense?
Yes. That's very good. But
what about 'festival'?
Plus an ocean is unpredictable...
with the tides moving in and out.
The treasure must be moving
around.
Young Noble... we can't figure it out
from only 8 characters.
There must be another symbol
which gives the answer.
The secret of time. The word
'festival' seems out of place.
We need to find the 5th bell.
I can't believe how easily they
accept their death...
They look so relaxed as they
go to their salvation.
I wonder if I will die
with the same ease...
I don't like it
when you talk of death.
I don't plan to die soon, Kyara.
Are you telling me the truth?
Promise me.
What will you do when you find
the treasure?
The treasure belongs to our
emperor.
The Emperor? But you're risking
your life for it!
The Amakusa Family will gain
respect again through my success.
I forgot. You're from a good family.
You are important.
You live in the clouds.
Kyara!
I wanted to be with you,
but it's only a dream!
I won't leave you.
Oh, will you marry me?
Yes.
There's no way it could happen...
not in this world.
When my family regains strength...
I can do whatever I want.
Samurai! Even if it's a lie...
I love hearing talk like that.
I'm telling the truth.
Samurai!
What is it?
The crickets stopped.
Do you think someone is there?
I don't see anybody.
Kyara, get the cross.
I don't hear anything.
Our enemy wants to steal
this cross and the 4 bells.
They will come after us
to get these things.
We won't have to look for
the fifth bell. It will come.
Edo
The fifth bell?
Move! Out of the way!
Kyara! I accuse you of being
a secret Christian!
That's absurd!
How could I be a Christian?
Shut up! This cross will tell us
everything we need to know!
Take her!
Let me go!
I'm not a Christian...
Help! Samurai!
The cross which Kyara had
was the key to finding the bells.
She can't be a Christian.
There's no way!
I'm sorry. She was accused
of being a Christian.
We apologize.
Who? Who made the accusation?
- I can't say.
I did. I knew you would come
if she was arrested.
Shino...
Shino!
You've been spying on us,
haven't you?
I am a Christian.
No! Shino! What are you saying?
Father, I was hiding it from you.
I've been a Christian
since I was a little girl.
I've carried mother's beliefs
ever since she died.
This can't be!
Shino! Are you also the
Princess Maria Ten?
Will you kill me?...
If you kill me, my followers
have instructions to beat Kyara.
Kyara!
I have four bells in my hand.
Before I can add the fifth bell...
I must kill your family.
Father, what is your response?
Will you destroy your only
daughter? Or kill Seiichiro?
Guards! Somebody!
Seiichiro is a Christian!
Throw him in jail!
Samurai!
Kyara!
I've been looking for you.
You're the one who stole
the bell from Justa.
So you are also a Christian?
My ninja magic...
Silk Worm Finger!
Die!
Otomo magic...
Double shadow.
The one you killed
was merely my reflection.
You little bitch!
Go to Hell, warrior!
I lost to a Christian!
Justa... I killed him for you.
What's going to happen to us?
I'm going to be killed.
- I won't let them!
I want to help you.
You must stay alive.
I feel guilty for involving
you in this!
It's too late... I already
know the secret.
They won't let me live.
I'm not afraid...
if I'm with you.
Maybe it would be best
if we died together.
We know who has the fifth bell
but we can't do anything.
There's still something else
I want to do...
I want to meet
Princess Maria Ten.
Come out...
Monika Okyo, Rufina Okai, Francesca Oyu, Justa Ofue.
God rest your souls.
Kneel down.
Shino. You smell of death.
What have you done?
I killed your last ninja.
I killed him for Justa.
You murdered Mokubei...
I'll kill you too.
And what about Kyara?
I must kill everyone associated
with the enemy.
Is that the wish of
Princess Maria Ten?
I don't know what Princess Ten
wants anymore.
I don't know why she has allowed
all the bells to be discovered.
It seems the Princess has
betrayed the Christians...
I can't support that.
I'd say the Princess has stopped
taking an interest in you.
So be it!
Princess Maria Ten!
I, Savina Oshino, am coming to
my salvation! Amen.
Kyara... can I ask a question?
What is it?
Shino tried to kill you
as her enemy.
It's like she was trying to
say something...
Perhaps you are the
Princess Ten.
That's impossible!
Don't you think?
That's true. There's no way
you could be Princess Ten.
The fifth bell reads:
Virgin - Birth
Do you know what it means?
Saint-Treasure-Salt Water-Under-Shinagawa
Virgin-Birth-Descent-Festival
'Virgin Birth Descent FestivaI'
That's the Christian's holiday.
Christmas time.
The 25th of December.
Probably the treasure will be
there in the water.
Samurai! You did it!
I see. Finally, Seiichiro solved
the secret of the bells.
Now there's nothing to keep us
from getting the treasure.
So... like you promised...
will you reinstate the
Amakusa family?
Don't be a fool. We need the
fortune for the Tokugawa Shogunate...
But I don't have any room for
the Amakusa Family.
I'll kill them and
keep the money.
That's the true meaning
of Christmas.
You are a powerful Lord.
Shinagawa
December 25th
The Christians probably
calculated the weight of the box,
and the movement of the tide.
Everything is on schedule for today.
We should wait for
the tide to go out.
Today is the day.
If we find the treasure...
my family's future will be secure.
Samurai, do you still want to
see Princess Ten?
Yes. If possible... I'd like
to see her... at least once.
I understand.
But the real person I want to
see is you, Kyara.
That's all I want.
You want to see me more
than anyone else?
Yes, only you.
Ninja echo trick.
I understand... I can
open your eyes.
Kyara.
Open your eyes.
Do it.
I can see! I see you Kyara!
Kyara! You are...
I am Princess Ten...
Maria Ten
Are you going to kill me?
I didn't know then... but now
I understand what Shino said.
The reason she wanted to kill you...
I don't know why she has allowed
all the bells to be discovered.
It seems the Princess has
betrayed the Christians...
What Shino said
was exactly correct.
My plan changed.
The girls became insignificant.
My goal is now to recover the
money and use it as a barter.
I decided to use the Christians
to eliminate my enemies.
No matter who died, I was still
ahead...
And now the money will secure
my own reign.
It was easy to use the religion
of these Christians...
They are so gullible and eager.
I have no intention
of letting you keep the money...
Seiichiro... it won't be turned over to
the Tokugawa Shogunate.
Kyara!
I am Princess Maria Ten.
What?
Seiichiro, why don't you try
the Echo Trick?
Can't your open eyes secure me
as I just did to you?
Kyara, I won't even try. I refuse
to use magic on my loved one.
Kyara!
Samurai.
I'm going to give up my plan
for Amakusa family's recovery.
I want to live with you.
Only you.
You can't. It's impossible.
Besides, I don't want to be
trapped in the weakness of woman.
Do you understand?
Kyara!
Thank you, Samurai.
I'm so in love with you.
I wish I could be only one person.
As Kyara, I could love you,
but I am Princess Maria Ten.
I have to go into the ocean...
and open the lock...
This cross is the key.
I must do it.
Kyara! Don't go!
No, Princess Maria Ten must do it.
Now is the time.
If there is a God, protect me.
Amen.
Kyara! Stop!
Come back!...
Kyara! Please stay with me!
Princess Ten... you are an
enemy I can't destroy.
Kyara. Thank you for the dream.
We'll be together in Heaven.
My final magic...
The Echo Trick!
The souls of Kyara and Seiichiro have
ascended to Heaven.
Two souls, which were never meant to be
united in this life, can finally be together.
No one knows the whereabouts
of the 1 million ryo in gold.
Produced by
KADOKAWA Yuji
Planning/Producer
AKASHI Wataru
OriginaI Story by
YAMADA Futaro
Screenplay by
ISHIKAWA Takato
Cast
SUMIDA Yuki as Kyara
YAMAGUCHI Kenji as AMAKUSA Seiichiro
ITAYA Yumiko as Savina Oshino
Mizuno Miki as Justa Ofue, Arai Mieko as Francesca Oyu
Yano Kazumi as Rufina Okai
SHIOJI Akira
MAKI Fuyukichi as MIKAERU Sukezo
Free Movies Downloads
http://bon99.com
SpeciaI Appearance by
ENDO Tatsuo as MATSUDAIRA Izu-no-kami
Free Movies Downloads
http://bon99.com
HAYAMA Reiko as Monika Okyo
Free Movies Downloads
http://bon99.com
Produced in Cooperation with KYOTO
MOVIE CO, LTD. SHOCHIKU GEINO CO, LTD.
Free Movies Downloads
http://bon99.com
Directed by
TSUSHIMA Masaru
Free Movies Downloads
http://bon99.com
Produced by SUMIKAWA
FILM ARTS TOHO KUSHINSHA
Free Movies Downloads
http://bon99.com
Translation and subtitles by
Amy Asai and Thomas Weisser
Free Movies Downloads
http://bon99.com
Extra translation and transcribing by Chanbara.
Special thanks to Zen for extra translation.
Free Movies Downloads
http://bon99.com
Subtitled by
Marukomu
Free Movies Downloads
http://bon99.com