Movie motifs from the story of Gogol's "Howl"
close your eyes
and pray
fearing the sight of
Vee, the ancient god,
that lurks in the eternal darkness underground
His eyelids are
sprouted roots to the ground
if you look him in the eyes
, it will instantly die
elders say so .. .
so they said and their ancestors...
From the beginning, when the earth was still young
, and the gods were teenagers...
this ancient tradition has lived
souls of the Slavs...
long ago adopted the Christian faith...
These are current beliefs and ancient customs
...
as customs and beliefs,
when young girls
placed wreaths on the water with burning candles.
if someone teenager take the crown...
It was believed that it was his destiny...
and swim jets of fire burning in the darkness...
and this is no end...
sis where are you?
Translation by ear and timing:
Venelin Atanasov -  venkobul
I wish you pleasant viewing
Vee
sin came to our land
what happened...
My sin is not dead
So tell December
again occurred of
"Ivan Cup" Freaks...
Tonight someone is missing...
Daughter...
Who did this?
Who did this?...
I told you
deal with indecent
share of demons...
wants to confess
To none  go to read prayers over me
Send now and bring bursaka Homa Brutus.
... Let's pray for my soul
wrong three nights...
he knows...
daughter...
what is it?...
Here. cried .. trouble...
And that deprive them of reason...
you're good, holy man
known bogougodnige affairs...
and maybe she heard about you.
Who, me?
God is with you pan Sotnik, what are you saying?
Looks like a foregone
although it is improper to say I went to
furnadzhiykata against itself Maundy Thursday.
Even today I have to start deeds
I told you about
You need a decent deacon or acolyte at least.
I, even my voice is not so
myself do not know what...
forgive me Lord.
I will do everything
left me my dove.
You know what a leather whip?
In bulk is something neiztarpimo
do its job
Do not you end up, you can not stand,
and they finish her 1000 gold pieces.
What the hell...
Nothing to be afraid...
man can not get out of here...
You do not got nothing holy sir
lady, her old home is transmitted sin
a miserable teacher
I am a courtier of the King
'm Not just a teacher
Bachelor've Geography
and Cartography
not have to play with words charlatan
dumber half of Europe with its apples
Daddy, I love it
Love him?
This crook shoe indecent trousers
I have big plans,
that will bring me glory in the future
realizing them when you marry my daughter?
No.
What it means - not?
Of course I intend to marry,
but not now and in the near future.
I think you can
have no future.
Get him!
Jonathan, run!
Jonathan Run, run!
Late mother in the future.
Let the dogs after him!
Honey, I love you!
I love you baby, trust me!
Do not forget the birds.
Dear Miss Dadling
pray profound apology
For my little premature departure.
How my
severe to admit it,
but your dad is right, Lord Dudley
I actually lost his entire fortune
But I threw it in the wind, as many believe
,
and I put him in his invention
With his help I can commit
turn in cartography
And to show people the real
shape our world.
Starting this great endeavor
I decided right here
our kind Greenwich,
I took in their dimensions
starting point.
Once our quiet little town will be glorified
worldwide
in all corners of the earth
on it will columnists time.
This is my dream.
Dream that will come true
Only if you believe in me.
And his adventures
will try
periodically to inform you letters
encrypted by the method of Leonardo da Vinci
not to be read by those
Which were not designed.
I love you and do not want to make light
hunters information
I will prove to everyone that this is not so!
I know will fly to you
with pigeons.
This will feel your closeness,
that in difficult moments of trial
will warm my heart.
...
Known for his holiness and godly deeds...
and your entire church wisdom
About it after church
look at whether Homa done everything right.
This you best understand it.
Dorothy is better than bursaka.
Here are the 1000 coins, take...
Thank...
I believe all can build a monastery.
Will say "amen"
Go, go... prepare for memorial service
Hurry
What?
Bury young mistress...
third day have no effect
Course I trace lord...
but when the witch brought him.
Phew... Paisij...
What is this?... For Homa.
That such and I am not held hands even...
key
Get out of here...
This place is cursed...
confounded God's sanctuary...
here can no longer serve
nailed the windows and doors
yes. .. witch...
This place is cursed...
Well being cursed...
Split them... equally...
Do not come here
is cursed ..
should not go there pan Sotnik
cursed place...
cursed...
I do not understand what you mean
Do not go there
About unless you mean
For people think!
It was there beheaded.
Do not take sin of the soul.
Where to go now
As you listen, I tell you to leave.
Do you have a conscience ...
Do you mother...
Kill him...
In the name of Father, Son...
holy spirit...
son Christ
will close the circle
not to crawl iniquities
in our homes...
Must suffer and pray...
Lord, help to protect you from the wicked,
children
they believe,
closed that old church...
will be a miracle.
Help me...
Show them what will happen to them...
if we listen.
This is the first day of April.
Probably occurs in spring Greenwich
Imagine your window
before you extend a flourishing garden
Spring sun caress your hair.
Thank you, nurse.
How can he do that.
What a witch...
Galabova mail, right?
Daddy, look at me
My God...
I'll kill him!
It's been exactly one year
Since the beginning of my journey.
Luck, who accompanied me left me.
I guess I strayed from the path.
I have not eaten for several days
Finished  funds to be able to continue the journey
.
Do not shoot...
What are you?
Bursaki...
foods, do you?
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry.
So you were saying...
Feast upon ...
hiding?
Who Am I?
Yes from me!...
Stay!
What... what?
This is not eating, it's breakfast...
Here...
dating.
So the gentleman is a scholar.
Yes, yes... a scientist.
We're scientists.
I, for one, am orator Gorobetz...
and this is Halyava theologian.
Where is the city?
There are near here
Hutar.
Hutar
But I do not even enemy I
advised to go there.
Why?
Around that same Hutar
killed our friend.
Scientist Do?
To Scientist...
philosopher Homa Brutus.
A year ago I Homa and Holyava
returns to the place of the bursa...
Because the dawn mist you...
or the devil we visit her...
gone astray.
Where Panas
Excuse me Taras
but service is service...
... a sign?
... A sign we are not drunk!
... For the soul!
Who's there?
Let us  grandmother to lodge.
When I was full of people,
where to put you.
Well,
you go.
Look Babka
by God in my stomach like that
someone driving a cart.
Lie what you want?
I do not .
Do you remember your soul decent,
... buy pods...
is a slut this Page
nose and it is not pretty.
And her hands are not clean.
All grandmothers are witches.
A market are accurate witches.
And  fatigue are asleep...
Hear grandmother...
now fasting...
I'm not that guy,
that 1000 gold pieces will be vile.
Do not Ow outdated, obsolete.
old woman turned out that
young mistress,
because she was a witch.
I already know that for sure.
My teacher Isaac Newton
discovered the law of gravity
That free flight is absolutely impossible.
Here, free fall...
as you like.
What we lie to you?
Fact colleagues.
Well, I blew
right here
Funny you
is that after this time
Homma never saw him again.
Homma allow yourself to Satan
witch etc. iniquities.
So perished
that in this world...
Died...
Do not lie, he died.
Hey God, died.
Pour
A? This is the best.
How is it?
Not bad!
A Hutar started in such a diabolical besotiya,
that my seemingly God.
He said Homa scared.
Lie
And here that do not lie
long I think about them...
Properly say,
scared of the witch and killed.
We can go back in Hutar, huh?
Where are you going?
I know why he died.
Because  scared.
If it was not, nothing will happen to him.
Wait
had only to cross himself,
and spit tail
and that's it
Then nothing would have.
I already know that.
However  glorious man was Homa.
Noble man was.
A vanished...
Dirty power... Satan...
God... what do...
strange sound
thing is that it is strange
And you say that this is the monster?
And there are nine horns?
Seven horns... seven.
Get up, get up.
You go ahead,
but we can there.
Hey, colleagues
funny stories.
What are you doing?
What was that guys?
Repent.
Here's the sign
devil Ambassador penetrated the circle.
Ambassador What is he,
when his feet muddy.
It does not seem Ambassador.
Trouble
Ambassador from hell.
Jonathan Green
Jonathan Green to me.
I am Jonathan Green.
Scientist, cartographer,
I citizen of her majesty
Queen of England.
Welcome you
Everything swim to our shores
still has splinters.
I turned my telescope
there, where I saw the fire.
And could well make out
frenzied movements of the savages.
I was confident that these fires
they were roasting their terrible lunch
from human flesh.
What are you reading?
Last bestseller Mr. Dafoe,
adventure of Robinson Crusoe.
Of all great writers you
a passion right in it?
Reply what is this lady?
Father, please give it to me.
This is it, right?
I asked you to drop the
all relations with him.
Insist in my home
nothing reminds of that person.
Quiet Dad,
forget that this person
is the father of my child
And maybe this minute it
threatens grave danger.
Surrounding savages and pirates
on a desert island.
Divaci? Island?...
What island
This is the largest continent on earth
And your  null Cartographer Jonathan Green
is at its very center.
Continent?
Think Island...
Excuse me, sir...
very important
wheel
bike?
To
Here  such mechanisms makes blacksmith.
Let's go.
He crafted the such apparatus
burners, clean as a whistle,
but if you drink of course.
I already know what the burners
This mechanism.
nonsense...
no, do not drink...
year since not drink
Since then his daughter was speechless
stands at the forge,
masters something
It all life Koval swords.
Swords?
Swords
I Carras
Foreign guests have.
Guests?
This is the alien clunkers.
Myself walking alone and manage.
We also know how something.
No, no, no...
this is the Dutch master
Dutch saying...
And that what you like Pan scientist?
The aircraft of Leonardo da Vinci.
I do not know what you mean, but
how to fly already know
How to land?
E pan Scientists,
please exit
Free  where there sat
not take off your coach.
I have not cried about it
will soon be a year since
flew us
splendid me.
Let
tomorrow to do a memorial service in the old church.
I'll have the boys
and they will clear the way for a moment.
You did not say anything...
I have not heard...
and I forget about it.
9 days I waited, waited 40 days...
will soon become old, how can I?
Do not need to wait
and pray hard.
One thing makes me boil
What he saw there as a year ago?
Petros, Petros.
Yes  Sotnik pan.
Say what you wrote here?
This is a map of the area.
Call this... this... teachings.
But quietly.
Excuse me, do you speak English?
What is your name?
It is not.
Who  devil led him
so gentle at first,
may scrub your back.
How I love this job,
Your brother Scientists.
On far you decided to fly?
Scientists pan.
What's the problem?
Pan Sotnik you shout at him.
Only, quietly.
Nastusya... Nastusya
I love you, and you tormenting me
You know I was serious if
not see you for an hour
Year and you already torturing me...
... I saw the manes of horses burning
I suddenly thought...
everything at us... so much fear...
repent.
My bike
Spirit, you hear?
All  grandmothers witches...
In water path is shorter.
Clean as a whistle.
Sotnik Pan...
Teachings...
Hey Cartography, do you believe in god?
How to tell
I'm a scientist
So in the devil you do not.
I do not believe.
I thought.
It's going to happen that
church and all my lands
bear.
Map?
But to me it takes time.
1000 coins.
What does pan Sotnik?
For  damn place questioning.
This is an old song.
Says his boys...
once will clear the way...
I want to see those guys,
who will go to the cursed place.
No such heroes...
here advance
I need and helper.
'll Have help.
Start with the old church,
but anyone anything.
Pan Sotnik must hurry.
Give Pan scientist...
Excuse him,
What happened?
Ever since his daughter died,
is not himself.
People thought that
young lady is a witch...
soul wanders in these marshes
And can not calm down,
this resulted in Homa Hutar
and locked in the circle,
should not pass it impure force.
From there only the brave Cossacks
can not go.
Come on... go... go!
I need facts.
Do not tell anyone about this,
you were at Pan sotnik.
If he's right Paisij...
Now we will check...
Where is the learning?
Here.
Guys... to be... all right.
How a scientist?
I know those observed stars.
What kind of science is.
The ones I'm talking about...
watch the stars through the glass.
There was one with us.
Also learned...
philosopher.
Homa Brutus
... You pan scientist, how do you know him?
I've already heard,
all know it.
Whom you do not know
celebrity...
Our cry then pan Sotnik in itself,
and ordered to take you
Homa Brutus at bursatsite.
Vain you think...
not here shantak could quickly escape.
Ah, wonderful place...
Here to run, to catch fish.
Hunting weapon...
However, I think in these forests
there are many birds...
fruit can dry
and sell in the city,
and more well if you boil them vodka.
Because  no beer
can not be compared to fruit vodka.
Why pan Sotnik chose
Negi. Oh for such an important job?
There was no stand any kind of
This is acknowledged
If she takes a notion panels
then most
literate person would understand.
And we brought in Hama in the church.
Let me boys
remember that dogs were barking.
Cossack  What I am after is afraid.
Smell a little tobacco.
Nice tobacco.
This terrible sparkling beauty.
Where is this church?
What for you this pan scientist?
Nothing.
Most needed thing in our Hutar,
draw him round
and the devil do not be afraid.
And even from a witch.
They say that every witch has a small tail.
Where your daughter again to swamp you?
I tell you, do not go.
This is actually the tales and prejudices.
Maybe to you, in Europe and no witches
A country, in Kiev, all grandmothers are.
Seen that the teachings pan is not understood.
Young mistress
get involved with the devil and became a witch.
Yavtuh You do not drink?
You can propiesh craftsmanship.
Enough...
What were you started to chat...
Hey, scientist panel well,
No offense guys to sit, drink.
What about Homa, facts
evidence.
Here they are, my evidence.
I only have one eye.
And hear on...
It is scary just his fabulous time
first time not too scary.
It already is not scary.
Must sanctify the whole church so,
can be seen during the day.
It is under the table
I think that hurts the ear
help me
wants to escape
I can not see
Do not let him take the chalk, turn
Do not let him take it
= I do not see =
where is it?
Where are you?
Call  Vee, Vee!
Raise my lids!
Here it is, now it's yours!
Save your soul and
leave alive!
See how many?
They live and people everywhere.
you can protect
through cross them?
Only that in you will cross
Slightly you to cleanly dressed
a lifetime to inside the circle.
A lady chosen names you.
Called  itself Vee to get out of the circle.
Looking into his eyes I survived.
You have a strong heart,
so and help you find peace.
I Help
O Pan Scientists pan Sotnik be angry
Took the money, but...
's time to go.
What?
Where is the highest place?
The old church.
What?
Come on Peter.
Well, what a scientist?
Grabbed their belongings and ran away.
Devil's work
sand begins to disappear from the circle.
Lord, what will happen to us now?
Go and pick up people.
... And pan Sotnik asks for it.
not you see there money...
1000 pennies, which I gave to Homa?
I saw everything I saw.
Then, in the church.
'll Take that secret confession.
You know what you want as
, but I'm here.
Is this cursed place?
Hold the rope.
Peter, hold on tight.
I go to the swamp and you
around the cursed place.
I'll buy a new saddle.
A coins, we have enough of everything.
Do you see how?
Peter, hold on tight rope.
I got it I got it...
... pick up my instruments.
You heard right, Teachings drank all
blood in Petros cursed place,
and got someone else.
Collect people, Father
Paisij you cry sermon.
Pull up old devil...
Guess that undergone by me
tension in recent days and my tiredness,
story became my first impressions.
Reminded me of pirates, buccaneers these
Without honor and conscience, which is
end his life,
hanged under
exhilarating delight of admiring audience.
I scared you not, my dear,
appearance sometimes lie.
... Until you look here,
teachings in the old church.
What you still hiding pittance?
Failed.
We see,
cursed place, and exercises standing on the dome
and Petros with him.
Nothing Averki stay there if something happens,
teachings will die that night.
Tell me what to do next.
'll Find pan Sotnik, people believed in me,
and is ready to punish the infidels.
Pan  Sotnik wants to
memorial service for her daughter.
Stay here, I'll need you.
You do not stand in front of a pastor,
entitled to sue you,
front of you is a slave and worm,
whom you can spit,
But I urge you,
not try to understand the reasons
or when there is no reason...
They say it's darkness and ignorance. Let.
Expel yourself from those who
carry the light of knowledge.
Where are you going...  Sotnik pan?
Do not feel love
flock to Christ?
Where?
That we have a herd, it is so.
Pan  Sotnik abandon us... and all the blame
is it stretched her veil and these scientists,
which I doubt that they are omniscient.
Ah... my gold should
better to hide it.
You have nowhere to go from here learning.
Fear newcomer.
I see after it comes satanic army.
Expel the devil away, so
earth burn beneath his feet...
My tools were there.
Petros, pick me up.
What was that Peter? I do not understand.
Pan Scientists tell you that this place is cursed
should run.
Get to Sotnik...
What did you see there?
Devil's work.
And you're here.
You have not been there.
Curse noticed in relationships
Training and then not grumble!
Go...
not understand...
Go on, make your work.
Do not you okay you can not get up.
Tomorrow I'll go there.
... Dorothy...
You say you will not drop it from the top...
he returned from there.
And went to Sotnik.
Who?
Teachings
Bring him here.
Who?
Petros
I asked them to fix it, and you smashed it.
No.
Not good, you exercise, you know...
Give it here
What are you, Dorothy?
What are you doing?
Close  mouth, Dorothy,
will raise around Hutar.
No, otherwise.
Do not. Father Paisij,
joked and long.
Come on.
What are you doing this scientist?
Pan Sotnik send it there
And promised him 1000 gold coins that you have forsaken in
cursed place.
Bravo... bravo.
Will now report to me
for all you know.
Put ??it that people do not see.
'll Leave, but will not serve ever.
... But this time do not miss teaching,
and I am going to gather people.
Good.
Where did you go mate?
Mills.
Scientists pan ... Paisij sent Cossacks.
Need to run.
I'll come with you, but I have one condition.
What?
Nastosya'll take with you.
Nastosya, get ready, I came for you. Do not take anything superfluous.
I have a biscuit... I'll survive somehow.
You might not agree. Can you hear me?
Then get kidnapped, by God!
Behold, I have prepared and rope, but will not
tie you and it will come, right Nastosya?
So, no.
Then you will go.
'll Go... and you will not see me.
Maybe then you'll cry for me. Farewell.
Nastosya, my love, come with me.
Come on.
We are waiting for you in the boat.
Averki Averki... Where are you... my friend...
What's the matter?
I'll kill you.
Where are you hiding  groshes me, huh?
What is it, you just mind its
pittance.
You took them.
Well, what can you say
whatever you want, huh?
Where is my pipe?
Nastusya, Nastusya here we are.
Petros, where?
Averki, how many times have we saved lives
each other. Now what?
Nastusya...
Nastusya
Forget  malice will go to the Pan Sotnik,
remember Cossack freedom... oh spree.
Nice pipe you got no one else has one.
At start.
Friend
Vee Vee... out there in the swamp.
Vee, horned monster.
Behold, the time has come that the word of God with
fire and sword to punish the devil's spawn.
Why so little?
There are... It is better that you will not.
Come, come with me.
Not kill.
Here it is... a witch.
Paisij Father, if it is not Nastusya
and unclean, I myself saw it.
Paisij Father, I saw it!
With seven horns. This is not Nastusya.
What I did.
Keep it
Judah
Will not escape me.
Map
You, you do not need a map.
You wanted to find out what happened to your daughter.
What do I know?
I know what happened.
You knew who?
Get him
All course animal...
Find me will not spare any money.
Condition for me to save and
Nastosya to ensure my safety.
Now we will fix that.
satanic deeds do here?
Run Nastusya!
This girl hewed two
Dorothy in front of me and me...
What are you talking about, asshole.
Witch...
Open!
Can.
What?
Unable . Is not allowed.
Who is not allowed?
From me.
I would have kept
her tongue.
Now the people do not dwell on.
Here, Satan's seed.
Get him!
Keep it
Do not!
Throw him into the dungeon to the witch.
And then interrogate him
not run away from here.
Learning is light.
Let's see what it says this scam.
My dear Miss Dudley
so
Wings locals
closely resemble the wings of a flying type mice.
In breadth they reach more than three meters.
What?
Felt their fetid breath so close
if I reach out to touch their skin.
They also have copies.
Hear that?
Remember  legged sailor whom he met in London
port
He showed us a huge octopus.
Why are you crying?
So long I did not get any letter
it.
Forget about it, it
is not cause for tears.
Dad, please.
So there's squid, ten times bigger than him...
has 6 eyes and call Vee.
Yes. Completely crazy.
If you go back, look at me
cursed place.
O God, make it so that it
is true.
Do not worry, I will not do anything.
All is well.
Swamp monster... ...
long you feed him?
Month... year?
This is a map,
work of my whole life.
Can not be lost without a trace.
Wait, that's not my bookmarks.
This is an escape plan.
why the hell can not sit.
I want power, ex pittance.
Pittance are the temple.
Have to decide, she saw everything.
I want to perform the ritual of the marsh,
So that all be
bloodstained i
Clever invented it.
I want to know, what are these leather items.
Go.
Ha ha ha... what... a witch.
There prepare conspiracy.
Nastosya  Run, run...
Where you goin fool foreign
grief to behold.
Go...
Where, sit down!
Old Devil.
Witch.
Now there is no escape.
And they say all the trouble comes from knowledge.
What are you doing here?
Just a great fit.
What miracles?
From the holy water of Paissii,...
Paisij cast spells she is still human.
A lie, lie Yavtuh.
Dog lie.
You want the truth?
Because you become like a woman Yavtuh.
Do you hear? When released into the water witch
it will fly.
Can not you stay and keep it for me?
No no.
Come Yavtuh  grandfather. Anyway
nothing to do...
'll stay and watch for a while,
only that you do not delay...
Hello pan Scientists.
Peter has prepared your fire escape to there.
Go to the swamp. Stole two horses. You here this
hand, do not do anything, so you'll stay alive.
Paisij... Paisij and Averki... conspiracy.
Beware of them.
Realized run.
Thank you.
It is possible this woman is a witch.
Paisij said take all stones.
... And will test it in the water...
If you swim, it's a witch.
Brothers and sisters, punishment will overtake
anyone who does not listen.
That's all...
adventures.
Peter, Peter...
Get out.
Undone...
What are you talking about. Are you dead?
What does that mean.
This means now I'm gone.
Do not know where he was buried.
There was nothing, nothing to bury.
Here's what  hear me Peter,
have an opportunity to save Nastosya.
I know who you saw.
Who?
Sheepskin horn...
Dress skin Distract them.
They will chase you understand?
I understand... I .
Get up and do it.
Led them to the cursed place.
I do not know such a disgrace.
Pity for the people.
Now all come to
to face God's judgment.
Vee.
Watch  fell and fell.
Stop, stop...
Get it.
What you were looking for?
Homa Brutus.
Wants to kill me, right?
Taking my cards and avoid punishment.
We need your facts. Here's the facts.
Young lady like you a lot.
Understanding that u can not be equal,
you abused her and left her to die.
It is believed that three days you will read
prayers over her. Will repent.
But you turned out to be cruel.
He knows who... This is
last words before death.
It's just a skin. You scared the whole entire year
Hutar.
I'll show people. Become!
What do you want from me?
Tired, that's all.
Whatever. Will not believe.
Where did you get this...
I have got out of the swamp and
unhook the bag.
Here I am, because I knew that
will not believe.
And what is your card?
It was the only way of salvation.
Where can I wear?
Bursa? Not everyone can grasp how to leave this world.
Or you can accept me for the lady-killer.
Dirty power.
Guys, it's me, Homa.
You sic Averki and Dorothy?
Their greed  destroy them.
Wait, how do you explain then that Miss
chosen names you.
A year ago, I Vorobets and
Halyava gone astray in these parts.
What's your name, boy?
Homa  - philosophy.
Come to my philosophy.
Homa-a. Do not be afraid, I will not eat.
At the first meeting I...
So, our fate was
one to meet.
Nastosya would have thought that it
I have done so wearing the skin.
She saw me, but only in the face of a monster.
I live here all year and pray for the salvation of the soul
Miss.
Terrible was the first three nights.
What horrible not experienced.
During the third night quite debilitating.
When only sing the first roosters come from.
Who, who is it?
This is it!
So what, are not you tired little devil?
Now recognized me Homa? How do you
without her?... She seduced me.
I was hoping you were dead, but you're alive.
I want to scare them, dress leather horns.
tempt me... how
gleaming black and devilish eyes.
But I do not sin. It has been said is not wrong
one who is tempted,
and that which tempts and do not know what
find pleasure in playing.
cause me disgust.
Help me.
Whatever. Nobody will help you.
Where you...
What you ask?
Drop it!
'll Have to part with
cloak with his head.
Base  fleeing.
People want a miracle and I will give it.
Many years ago I went to a missionary in Europe
and know how to create a new religion
, clean without miracles,
by using your inventions.
I'm the new prophet!
And you will die.
As a priest, I can not let
without repentance.
Read your prayers.
Nastusya!
Nastusya...
Nastusya.
I want to know that your life is
is not in the hands of God
and mine.
I decide who lives and who dies.
Be damned!
Freedom.
Little Daniel, um. Forgive me.
I'm ashamed to admit, but cruel
I lied about your father.
Trust me, he's a great, good man.
This is his letters from him to your mother.
Which I intend to publish.
I want the whole world to know what was wrong
judge a man so foolish as me.
Are unfortunate Bruno burned in the fire,
then realized
that the earth is round.
Now  letters are in your hands, yes.
Now they are in you.
Jonathan!
Ah, another dove. Now we know
with you how this story ends.
Yavtuh, where are you going?
Here.
Is not you afraid?
Cossack  must not be afraid of anything.
To know that your life is not
in the hands of God, and mine.
I decide who lives and who dies.
Paisij cries while
fire everywhere heard.
cursed!
Mother.
A miracle.
Felt the breath of god
and his touch that changed my destiny.
Never before or since I have not experienced anything like that.
All my previous life flashed before me.
I thought I
who will continue after my death.
Honey, I want you to have a child.
What you need to know what
were friends with your landlord.
Quiet!
Evil was punished and I got a fee.
Here are the coins of Sotnik.
Peter.
Body and soul of the ladies found
rest and father and received mental balance.
A Homa, perhaps with his mistrust of
scientist, something like this seminarian.
If fate has chosen me and that is a
resulted in this God-forsaken place,
to finish the story he read in January
This is a magic lantern
miracle created by the genius of humanity
That can build or destroy, in
depending on what hands fall.
Once the images will come to life, and we will see
wonderful city and wonderful people.
Paisij you found?
No, I never saw it anywhere.
Is Dead
Two unusual rat with an unnatural size,
came, sniffed, sniffed and passed.
All grandmothers are witches.
those who are older,
even bigger witches.
Hell.
What is it?
Scientists pan, one for the road?
Drank.
For Lent?
Memento pan Scientists?
I'm not drinking.
This is a Cossack.
Spirit.
Pick up, pick up.
I never really knew where to put
gear.
Now, when the country went out and my mind cold
progressive researcher
Again  possessed feelings
I can ascertain,
all fantastic events of recent days,
appear as the fruit of the imagination of the human brain
Which is a little more
studied by modern science.