Billie.
Hello, my sweet.
Oh, my God.
Chet?
The very same.
Wh--am I asleep?
Am I dreaming right now?
You tell me.
Oh, my God.
You're so warm.
I've had my hands
in my pockets.
Are you a ghost?
Yes, 'tis I,
the ghost of Chet.
What are you doing here?
I've come to see you,
my precious.
Oh, God, you look so alive.
Go ahead,
you can touch me.
God, this feels so real.
It feels so right.
- What are we...
- Shh.
Okay.
O.M. gosh.
Stop, I'm gonna throw up.
Way to go, Brett.
This was supposed to be like
a "Scare Tactics" level prank.
Now you're, like, making love
to her--it's embarrassing.
What--what's going on?
That's not Chet.
That's Chet's brother, Brett.
Yeah, like Brett Butler,
"Grace under Fire."
ABC Wednesday nights,
9:30/8:30 Central.
They're twins.
Identical.
Except I don't have a lisp.
But...
I mean, I don't have one.
Ha ha!
Yeah, I'm in town
for a couple days.
Thinking about investing
in a rock company.
- I like rock music.
- No, it's just rocks.
Well, that's cool
that you're stopping by.
- Yeah.
- Any brother of Chet's
is a new Chet to me,
you know?
New Chet Brett.
Welcome to CLANGENE.
You know, I'm pretty stoked
that you're into "Halo."
You must be a beast, sister.
I've killed a few stay-at-home
dads in my day.
There's this one guy--
oh, he's a total dickbutt.
He spams me every time
I get a great weapon.
Did somebody say "dickbutt"?
Dang it, Kerry!
Get out of here!
Who's your friend?
Is he ready to watch me
pwn your ass?
I'm Brett,
like Brett Butler but--
Pwn your own butt, Kerry!
The point of the game
is to kill.
Maybe you need to get
your video game GED too.
Is that a thing?
Well, guess what, Kerry.
I'm about to take you
to school.
The school of--
No!
What did you do?
It's time for class.
That is the meanest thing
that has ever happened
in the history of meanest things
ever to happen.
I think the Potato Famine
of '45
and bird flu
would disagree with that.
That sounds
totally made up.
Those are real things that you
would know if you went to class.
I don't care about
stupid potatoes and sick birds!
If I have to do
all this high school stuff,
I should get to do
the fun stuff too.
We just did Macbeth
with British accents.
"Is this a dagger I see before me?"
I'm talking
about the fun high school stuff,
like... prom or...
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, you're a genius.
I want to do the prom stuff.
- I didn't say--
- Yes! I love that suggestion.
- Prom!
- No, I didn't give that--
- I should totally have a prom.
- Yeah.
You're the only student.
I'll ask other GED students.
It's already happening.
Brett, are you there?
- I'm in.
- You don't need a prom, okay?
Gene, I didn't go to my prom,
and I turned out...
I think a prom would do you good.
Okay? Maybe you get
a little over-the-dress action?
- Or under the dress.
Excuse me?
I'm not the one
who almost sucked face
with a ghost last night.
How you doing?
Okay.
You don't need a prom.
I'll play you for it.
You want to play "Halo"
against me?
- Yeah.
- I'm sort of a pro.
Damn, Gina,
you are good at this.
Yeah, I've got hands
on a rocket launcher.
Good job, Billie.
Yeah, I won a tournament
two years ago.
Best New Year's Eve ever!
Look alive.
Kerry just logged on.
Why don't you fart-breathers
do yourselves a favor
and log off?
Because CLANGENE breathes
farts wherever we want!
I'm tea-bagging your friend.
She likes it!
Where are the tea bags?
I don't see the tea bags.
Billie.
- He killed me.
- No!
Not again!
My rocket launcher!
Is mine.
My rocket launcher.
Gene, relax,
it's just a game.
A game?
A game? Just a game?
Do you remember
what killed Chet?
A game, Billie, a game.
We can play again
in a couple minutes.
What's the point?
He already has all my weapons.
What else does he want?
My soul? My mouth?
My brain and also my mouth?
No.
Something has to be done about this.
Gene, why are you talking
like that?
Yeah, stop petting your hands.
And I know
exactly what to do.
First step--
Oh, man, poor Gene.
I know.
I'm worried about her.
No.
Okay, and hopefully
he's wearing a purple T-shirt.
Get him on the stage.
- What are you doing?
- What?
My revenge plot.
My prom plan. Nothing.
"First step:
Invite Kerry to prom."
Kerry the "Halo" bully?
Why would you invite him
to a prom?
Which you're not having.
Because, step two,
when he arrives,
we treat him like a prince.
Or better yet, a king.
A prom king, Billie.
Then, when he least expects it,
step three.
And you know what step three is?
I honestly have no idea.
Yeah, you do.
- You don't know what it is?
- Uh-uh.
We dump a bucket
of pig's blood on his head,
just like in that movie
"Carrie."
Okay, it sounded crazy
either way you said it
'cause your plan is basically
to invite your online nemesis,
who you've never met before...
- Mm-hmm.
- To a fake prom...
- Right.
Dump a bucket of animal blood
on his head
just because his name
sounds like the name
of a fictional horror movie
character/book character
that that happens to.
You know what?
Now that I'm hearing it
out loud,
yes, perfect plan!
Ha ha!
Okay.
You're not having a prom.
Is that permanent marker?
What? No.
Whiteboard's broken.
Why would something so bulky
be up so high?
Let me help you with that.
Oh.
There you go.
Oh, thank you.
I need this to advertise
the flavors
at my frozen yogurt shop.
Oh.
Peanut butter,
vanilla, green tea.
I don't--I don't own
a frozen yogurt shop.
- Who does anymore? I'm Hank.
- Oh.
"Hank" you for this.
Sorry.
I'm--I'm Billie.
Okay, so you don't own
a fro-yo shop.
No, I'm--I'm a teacher--
I'm a tutor.
I'm a tutor too.
No way.
Hand on a Bible.
Yeah.
Is it just me, or is everyone
like, "You're a what?"
Okay, can you get that Bible
back out here?
'Cause if another person asks
me, "Why aren't you a teacher?
Why are you just a tutor?"
I swear to God,
I'm gonna, like...
do something,
I don't--
- Preach!
- Okay.
They don't understand
that not every mind
thrives on
traditional education.
- Uh-huh.
- Can I get an "amen"?
You can get an "amen"
and then some.
I mean, my student,
she's like an adult,
but then she's also
like a little kid.
You're describing Atticus
to a tee.
She actually wanted me
to throw her a homeschool prom,
which is like, ugh--
- That's a great idea.
A great idea,
is what I said.
- Well, Atticus would love that.
- Oh.
And if you need a date,
I am clearly writing down
my phone number.
If you're free.
Oh, well, I ain't cheap.
Preach!
- Hallelujah.
- Oh, yeah.
Glory be to God!
- I'm not religious, by the way.
- Neither am I.
Okay, good, 'cause, yeah,
we're shouting in the store...
- Yeah, yeah.
- About Jesus.
"Hank" you.
Okay, so I posted the invite
on my GED chatroom,
Joy's gonna get the streamers,
and I'm thinking no band,
just my voice.
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey, prom
I think we should get a band
for sure.
- That's so rude.
- I mean, your voice is great--
- Hey, Brett. Hey, Gene.
- Shoot. Hide it.
Oh, Gene.
Oh. Hey.
What's up? No?
I was thinking
about that whole prom thing.
Maybe it's not such a bad idea.
Really?
Yeah. I mean,
you've been working...
hard, and yeah,
you deserve it.
We already started making
a disco ball.
Brett!
Well, I'm a little upset
that you broke
most of the mirrors
in the house,
and this is very dangerous,
but points for creativity, so...
- Yes, point!
- Point!
Both: Point, point!
You don't actually
get points--
This is so great, Billie.
Prom's gonna be next level.
I'm talking, like, "babies left
in the dumpster" level.
Well, that's really upsetting.
No, that sucks.
Who thought of that?
And none of the pig's blood
stuff too, right?
Just--just a prom.
Yeah. I mean, totally.
Oh, my gosh, that was, like,
first draft ideas.
- Okay.
- Final draft is just like
me wanting to cut loose with
my GED brothers and sisters.
Oh, yeah, like,
Yeah. Cut it--
with my brothers and sisters,
Billie, now that we have prom
on the books and everything,
I'd like to ask you something.
Okay.
Will you--
Gene, can you get me a Band-Aid
really quick?
- I'll get a Band-Aid.
- Band-Aid?
- I'll get some Band-Aids.
- Will you, um--
No, no,
your knees are gross.
- No, it's fine.
- Brett, you okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- You need something?
Yeah, maybe a couple slices
of brie
and some light crackers
and grapes,
just your basic
wine country lunch.
You want me to go to prom
with you?
Okay, I'm holding an L with
my fingers on my forehead--
you can't see it--
but, you know, for "loser."
Okay, got it. No, I don't
want you to be my date,
but I would like you to come.
Sort of a promotion
from enemy to frenemy.
You and I,
actually hanging out in real L?
Am I getting
"To Catch a Predator'd"?
Tell him he's getting Sissy Spacek'd.
Shh, stop!
Hemming and hawing.
Are you in or you not?
I'm in.
Shaft-deep in your mom.
But seriously,
what time is your stupid prom?
- So--so what time is it?
- Oh, sorry, 8:00.
Mm-hmm.
- Billie!
What are you doing?
First and foremost,
that teeth brushing song
should be on top
of the pop charts.
On a more pertinent note,
I'm here to finish the query
that was disrupted
by my unfortunately timed
knee accident.
Billie Brown, will you go
to prom with me?
Get out of my shower!
- Is that a yes?
- No!
No, it was?
Get out!
Faster.
I love your body.
So Billie gets
on the stage, right?
She announces
prom king and queen.
We get Kerry on the X.
I'm gonna do this:
"Drop the blood!"
And that's your cue to drop
the blood, got it?
Yeah, I agree.
Billie is rude and insensitive.
Are you not even listening
to me right now?
No, I don't even know
why I'm going anymore.
New Chet Brett,
you are my trigger man, okay?
You have the most important job,
so snap out of it.
Prom is not about being sad
and in love.
It's about revenge and shame.
Tonight, my enemy tastes blood.
Tonight, a war begins.
[dramatic music]
- Okay, well, that looks terrible.
- Not good.
- Can't go to prom like that.
- Here.
Come on, everybody!
Get behind me
or in front of me.
It's not a conga line if you are
not behind or in front of me.
- Not enjoying the festivities?
No, those people look like
they live under a bridge.
Looks like your date
didn't show.
He's coming.
God, I hope his student
isn't too buttoned up.
These people are just so ugh--
Brett, don't touch me!
It'd be fun
to take a picture later.
Where is Gene?
Oh.
Gene, you're not in slo-mo.
Stop it.
There's no fan
blowing your hair.
A breeze.
Don't talk like--
You're not in slo-mo.
- Maybe I was.
- You're not.
Did you ever think I was
for a second?
No, I didn't.
I said it right away.
- You thought it, right? Yes!
- All right, he's here.
He's here. Go, go, go, go, go.
Leave, leave, leave.
Okay, let me just fix
something 'cause there's a mess.
- Oh, what's wrong?
- Just rip your boobs out.
- Don't touch me. Go, go, go.
- Free 'em for prom.
Please, leave.
Go, go, go, go, go.
- Hank!
- Hey.
And you must be Atticus.
You are a young boy, wow!
I like to think that I have
an old spirit.
Okay.
- Uh, yeah.
- Oh, sure.
Come on in.
All right.
So where is this student
of yours?
Oh, um, the party
is in the backyard.
Great.
So should we head back?
- No.
- I mean, why would you say that?
- Yeah, why, Atty?
I thought you wanted to have
some fun with kids your age.
I brought your gluten-free
cookies and your inhaler,
so you're all set.
I don't want to go back there
right now.
Look, we drove
all the way out here
to this beautiful home that this
beautiful woman invited us to,
so what if she gave us a tour?
That'd be better--
I mean, good.
- That'd be great.
- Yeah. What do you say, bud?
- Okay.
- Yes!
Look at us,
like we're a little family.
I'm just kidding. That's a joke.
Although we could be.
Just--all going up
to our separate bedrooms.
Except for us.
We'd have the same bedroom.
Whoo!
We're gonna live forever!
Or a few good solid years.
Yeah?
Mm. Boo.
Who requested
lame "fall in love" music?
It's for chumps.
Gene!
Huh?
It's me, dickhole.
It's Kerry.
Kerry?
You're here.
And that is what you look like.
Hey.
And last but not least,
this is Gene's room.
Awesome, "Halo"!
Oh.
Don't you want to go down
and meet everyone at the party?
You know what? Let him play
for a little of bit.
- Really?
- Yeah, we can just, uh,
"Hank" out on the bed.
Sorry, last one.
- Thanks, Billie.
- No, "Hank" you.
- Okay, that's plenty, really.
- Okay.
Hey, so, great party.
Everyone seems
real bombed or...
blitzed.
Yeah, there's alcohol
available here.
Right.
Cool pizza.
We got that.
We bought it.
- Chill.
- Yeah.
[sighs]
I'm sorry
I'm so awkward.
No, I'm sorry
I'm so pretty.
But you are.
What?
Why are you being
so nice to me?
You're, like, so mean to me
in game.
I know. I'm sorry, I probably
a little too hard on girls...
- Sexist.
- That I like.
- Sexy.
- Dance with me?
Aren't we already?
I mean, he doesn't hang out
one-on-one
with anyone besides me.
In hindsight, this might have
been too much too soon.
Well, if it makes you
feel better,
I'd rather be up here with you
than down there with those...
teenaged people with their memes
and their hashtags
and Drake--Drakes.
Well, uh, maybe next time
it can just be us.
Can I get an "amen"?
Amen.
Okay.
You can get a kiss too.
Oh, wait.
Where's Atticus?
Oh, this is awesome.
He must have gone
down to the party.
We should spy on him.
Come on.
No! I mean, nah.
Uh, you know what?
We don't want to compromise--
If he sees you,
it could ruin his sociali--
I'll go and spy on him.
You stay up here.
And I will report back
to headquarters,
- Mrs. Moneypenny.
- James Bond style.
- Yeah.
This is actually really fun.
I'm--I'm having a time.
People usually say, like,
"good" or "great"
in front of the word "time."
That too.
- Could I see you again?
- What?
I'm sorry,
that was probably really abrupt.
Like I said, I'm not too good
at this kind of situ--
Shh.
That's boob for "yes."
You hear me?
Loud and clear.
Squeeze if you can hear me.
Yeah.
I hear you too.
Atticus, what are you doing?
I thought you said you were shy!
Tammy, right?
Billie.
Yeah, **** off.
You're drunk.
Don't do that.
Wait, what is this?
This is the prom?
Who are these people?
O... kay, I think there's been
a little miscommunication.
What's this in your hand?
Did you eat gluten?
Unbelievable!
Oh!
Oh, you vomited
on her pregnancy.
Don't make out with her
after you vomit.
Oh, no, stop.
Stop.
She's pregnant, by the way.
That's not just beer bloat.
- What's that for?
A bucket of... confetti.
You know what?
I think the night is over.
I thought you were
someone else.
No, no, no. I'm a tutor.
Fro-yo shop, preach!
No, I'm not doing
any more church bits with you.
Would it be
too crazy romantical
if I just kissed you
right now?
Does this answer
your question?
- Oh, you have blood.
- What?
- Blood?
- Uh-huh.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
This is really embarrassing.
It happens
when I get too excited.
No, that's okay.
Confetti really makes it
a party, no?
I don't have time
for this conversation right now.
It's just
a little bit of blood.
Blood, blood.
NCB, abort the mission!
- Not now, Gene.
- Yeah, not ever!
What's that?
What's what?
- Hold on.
- No.
- Okay, but--
- Come on, Atty, come on.
Excuse me, sir.
I think you need
to calm your roll
when speaking to a lady
of such physical beauty.
- Brett, please don't.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
What, son?
You want some of this?
Let me tell you something,
friend.
I Krav Maga daily.
I'm confused.
Am I your son or your friend?
We're out of here!
Come on, Atticus.
- Let's get your EpiPen. Come on.
- Doesn't make any sense.
- Later, bitch.
- Bitch?
At least I can digest
wheat flour, son.
Well, that's what I get
for listening to Gene,
a backyard full of weirdos
and the guy that I like leaving,
thinking I'm pathetic, which...
I totally am.
I don't think
you're pathetic.
Thanks, Brett.
That guy might though.
Okay, well,
I guess that's my cue
that the evening is over,
so...
Wait, aren't you gonna
announce the king and queen?
Are they still doing that?
Yes.
Did anyone vote?
No.
Cool.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Good-bye.
And the winner is
Gene and Kerry.
Confetti!
No!
What the ****?
Is it blood?
It's blood?
My bangs is blood!
My bangs blood!
I am so, so, so, so sorry.
Brett, what did you do?
Why did you drop the blood?
- Drop the blood?
- No!
Ah.
Why did you have
an extra bucket?
I got a deal.
You guys look like
that "Carrie" movie.
Which movie, Kerry?
The blood one.
Throw a plasma grenade
on the ground,
another one in front of it.
Basically you have
a grenade launcher.
Oh, my gosh, you're so much
better as a frenemy.
Maybe I could be
your boyfrienemy.
What?
Hey, Billie,
even though
I poured blood all over you
and I saw you naked
and you probably hate me,
this is the best date
I've ever had.
Me too.
Really?
If I'm being honest, no.
Oh, my God, is that pig's blood
that I got on your knees?
Nah, I just got
super duper sweaty,
and my Band-Aids fell off.