Too much on the arms.
What the
are you doing?
I'm getting a suntan.
Got my bikini on.
I got the afternoon off.
I thought you had, like,
a date with a mom or something.
I have a date
that my mom set up.
There's a big difference.
Did I miss any?
Yeah, in your anus hole.
Okay, Gene.
You can't get cancer up there
from sitting in the sun.
Sunburn in rectum.
Possible?
Searching.
"Requiem for a Dream."
Rectum. Rectum.
Searching.
"Requiem for a Dream."
Not requiem. Rectum.
Oh, I'm shouting.
Oh, nice,
you made me some popcorn.
Your dad's
been looking for you.
- What'd you tell him?
- I found Gene!
- What are you doing?
- I told him I'd do that.
Gene, come on!
Tanzy's opening
her Mother's Day gifts!
Why does he do
this every year?
Maybe he feels bad
that you don't have a mom.
Also, Tanzy loves gifts.
Well, this just in: I don't
give a [bleep]. You know?
- Can you move?
- Oh, sorry.
Oh, the production
value's so bad.
Do you actually like this?
I--I'm sorry, I just can't get
over the production value.
This one--this is from Gene.
You can tell because it's
got Grumpy Bat on it.
Not from me.
I don't give a [bleep].
Ooh, leen-ger-ee!
Thanks, Gene.
Got it.
Okay, wait. Say "You're
welcome" to your mom, Gene.
I will,
if I ever see her.
Mom burn.
Good one, Gene.
I might have to return
it 'cause it's for a fat person.
That's fine.
- What?
- Hi, Gene.
I'm your mom.
♪ We're too gangsta for TV
♪ That's why
you don't see us ♪
♪ But they still
wanna be us ♪
Ha ha!
Oh, my God.
We can play
dirty hooker later.
Whoo! Yay.
Dad, there's a man
who says he's a mom?
- Yeah.
- Is that like a manny?
Diane.
- It's Dan now.
- Oh.
I'm sorry, who are you?
Well,
I'm--I'm Gene's mom.
Oh!
Well, happy Mother's Day!
Would you like a Mom-mosa?
It's like a mimosa,
only it's champagne.
- Tanzy, don't. Just--
- I'm sorry.
Maybe I--I should've called
before I came over.
- Oh, well--
- You can use our phone.
No. Tanzy, don't.
All right?
You--you--I got to...
just--I--just gonna--
- Daddy, are you okay?
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
- This is so Diane.
- It's Dan.
Oh, okay, Dan.
You are being
so Diane right now.
What's going on?
I was Kent's first wife,
Diane.
Yeah, and you left
without warning,
and now you show up
the same way.
How dare you?
Are you okay, Gene?
No, she's not all right.
I mean, she--she's trying
to process something.
All right,
I tell you what.
I think you should leave.
Yep, I think you should go,
because as you can see, we are
celebrating Mother's Day here.
Just so it's clear,
I'm not Gene's mother.
I hope it's not too late for
us to have a real relationship.
I'm on Facebook now
and Linkedln, if you'd like
a more a professional,
somewhat useless connection.
Well, good-bye.
Let's open my presents!
Come on, Gene.
Wait!
- What's up?
- What?
- What did you want?
- You told me to wait.
Oh, right.
Oh, now I remember.
My dad was just joking about the
whole "you have to leave" stuff.
- He doesn't really mean it.
- Honey, your dad meant it.
We don't exactly
have the best history.
He said you could
come back in and, like,
hang out if you wanted to,
so you should.
Or I don't know.
Like, also
who cares or whatever.
- What did you say?
- What?
Start walking.
♪♪
Sorry I'm late.
Name's Pony.
I was at the strip club.
I've never been to Canada,
and I have pierced nipples.
Oh, looks painful.
Yeah, this one's a little
infected.
I don't know why
you think I need to know
either of those things.
Total honesty.
That's my policy.
I'm sorry. Are--
you're the dental hygienist?
You're my mom's travel
agent's son?
I don't know
why anyone has a travel agent,
but that's who you are?
Guilty as charged.
- That's my bag.
- Hey!
- What are you do--
- You got something to hide?
No.
All right.
Oh, three deodorants.
- That's weird.
- I get nervous, and I like...
different smells
for different events.
Individually wrapped
condiments.
That's some old lady [bleep]
right there.
- I like flavor.
- Ooh, compact.
Thank you very much.
I'm gonna take that.
Why?
Hey. Jerk off lotion.
That's not jerk--
it's just normal lotion.
I have--
- We're both adults here.
A book.
- Who brings a book on a date?
- I don't know.
Someone who's nervous
their date might be terrible.
This book's terrible.
You read "The Decameron?"
Yeah. Totally blows.
Everybody dies at the end.
So sort of a spoiler,
but I'm really impressed
you read "The Decameron."
I can barely get through it.
All the--
You know what?
You seem nice.
You got hair and the cans
and everything, decent face,
but, listen,
I don't think it's gonna work.
And besides,
my bros are having a bonfire
down at their RV park,
so, uh...
So, uh...
what are we...
waiting for?
♪
Jesus, your head is small.
Yes.
My mom drank in the womb.
- Let's go.
- All right. Do you want--
Just leave it.
- Mind if I take these knives?
- Yeah, take it.
This is my door.
This is my carpet
and some of my clothes.
Oh.
That's, like,
a little dinosaur,
and he's screaming out
something.
I like to think he's like,
"Language," 'cause
I use curse words a lot.
That's my blanket
I use it to block out the sun
'cause the sun
[bleep] sucks.
These are my beanbag chairs.
I like to sit in them.
Hmm.
Excuse me.
Ooh.
Well, I didn't say
sit in my beanbag chair.
Can I sit on the floor?
Yeah, sit on the floor. Yeah.
I just don't know if there's
anything on your butt.
Like to keep 'em clean.
Do you have any hobbies?
Yeah,
ice-skating and singing.
Do you have a favorite group?
Selena?
Oh, the--the dead lady?
Yeah, she's good.
I saw that TV movie about her.
Do you ever have that thing
happen where, like,
you're going to the bathroom
and your legs fall asleep?
- Yeah.
- It happens to you too?
Sometimes
I'm on the toilet so long
that I pretend that I'm on a talk show.
That's cool, *** it go?
Hello, I'm Dan and I welcome here
very interesting young lady.
Very pretty lady with curly hair
sitting next to me.
Hello, Gene.
Hi, it's nice to be here.
What are you doing
dear today in the bathroom?
I just go to the bathroom, man.
- Me too.
Got any TP?
Yeah, let me pass it to you.
Oh.
It's too many... I'll pause the game.
So, did you ever, um--
did you ever
think about me all these years?
Pass the gummy bears.
I thought about you
constantly.
Like, when you were
pooping and stuff?
- Sometimes.
- Gross.
I have to say that I thought
that giving birth to a child
would kick
in my maternal instincts.
Did they?
Well, this is the first time
we've been talking in 20 years.
So jury's still out?
It took me a long time
to figure out
that I could be
both a man and a mom.
Same. I'm, like, a really,
really, really good dancer,
but I'm also super pretty.
- You are very pretty, Gene.
- Whatever.
So glad you didn't get
my dead chicken eyes.
- Oh, no, I got 'em.
- A little bit.
- You see it?
- A little bit. For me?
Eat, eat.
- You're skin and bones.
- Bon appétit.
- Mm.
- You like it?
It's really good.
Oh.
That was so violent
and awesome.
Ugh.
Looks like we're early.
Want to go around back?
Give you a little cat bath,
little butt stuff?
You can't just say stuff
to people like that.
Well, you know,
I'm sorry, all right?
But that's the kind
of guy I am.
I give little to no thought
to the things that I do or say.
I just--it's off the top
of my head, you know?
South Dakota.
Cinnamon buns. Tawny Kitaen.
Did not think
about those words at all.
Salmon.
"Mamma Mia." English.
Lick.
Lick, lick, lick.
Lick, lick my.
I didn't mean the last part.
Ooh, no, no, no.
That was my favorite part.
- Nice foot kick, Ma.
- Thanks.
What else should you know
about me?
Well, I have a fear
of spiders and Pierce Brosnan.
Same.
Oh, but I like spiders.
Oh, yeah?
What's your favorite TV show?
"Transparent"
and "Vanderpump Rules."
- I love Vanderpump Rules.
- Isn't it fun?
- Yeah.
- Whoa, hey.
What the hell, Diane?
I asked you to leave.
Don't yell at him.
My name is Dan,
and you know that.
Your name is Kent.
I hate that name.
- I always have.
- Ah.
And how the hell
did you not see
- that I have been here all day?
- Don't yell at him.
I have an extremely big house.
Now answer my question.
Gene told me that you said
that I could come back.
I never said that.
Gene, why did you say that?
Don't yell at my daughter.
It's my extremely big
house too!
Fine. What-what do you
want, Dan? Huh? Joint custody?
You remember
what happened with Teriyaki.
Don't you bring up Teriyaki.
Ah.
We shared a terrier mix,
and then I lost our custody.
- Yeah.
- To a coyote.
- I'm so sorry.
- Yeah, that's correct.
Dan, I want you to...
- Stay in Billie's guesthouse?
- Leave.
I didn't know you had
that kind of aggression in you.
- Well...
- You used to be so passive.
Well, I guess
we've both changed.
Good-bye, Gene.
Wait, no.
Why do you make
all the moms go away?
Why do you make them go away?
- God, I hope she gets it once.
- Mm-hmm.
Ah!
I hate my life!
It sucks!
It's a sucky, sucky life,
and I'm gonna kill myself!
Shh!
I've got to do something
to make this better.
I totally messed it up.
I got to get my family
back together again.
- Shh!
- Oh, sorry.
They must really
hate each other.
Whoa, now they're,
like, in love?
What is the plot of this?
Oh, my God.
I get it now.
Love and hate
are one and the same.
Where there is heat,
there is a flame.
What's happening
to your face?
A plan.
This is absolutely
fascinating.
I don't know anything
about this subculture.
Do you mind if I take notes?
Nah, go ahead.
Thank you. There we go.
I got a little notebook
just in case I saw something
I didn't know yet.
Another round of homebrew?
Oh, hell yeah, Joker.
Oh, when.
Save some for yourself.
Can't, I got
a long drive home.
Well, have you
ever made non-alcoholic?
I heard it's a bitch.
Oh, it really isn't.
Yeah, you brew it the same,
but then you heat it to 175
for 20 minutes
before you add your yeasts
- and your sugars.
- Are you for real?
'Cause that's some--that's
real strange knowledge to have.
Oh, yes.
In high school, I threw a party,
and I didn't want
anyone to get in trouble,
so I homebrewed some NA.
No one ended up coming, but--
You two swing?
Do we swing?
You mean sexually do we swing?
Yeah. Joker here's
very gentle for his size.
Well, now I know
how you got your nickname, Jocker.
Do we swing?
I wasn't joking about swing.
Okay.
Guess who passed
the friend test, right?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Just happy.
- Oh.
Okay, 'cause your mouth
wasn't moving, you're
breathing sort of
look paintfool.
Ah. Again.
- Why are you here?
- Let's see.
It's my house,
and this is my backyard.
Why are you here?
Because your daughter said she
wanted to meet me here privately
and to be here at Steven,
which I assume means 7:00.
Well, I'm supposed
to be here at Steven, too.
- Ah.
- Oh.
Well, she really went to town
with the Christmas light
thingies.
Actually look kind of nice.
I think she hacked
the Spotify playlist
of mine called "No Safe Word."
She also uncorked
a 1921 Château D'Prive Magnum,
which I will try
not to let ruin the evening.
- Shall we?
- If you insist.
Mm. No.
It isn't romantic enough.
Put more romance.
That's good.
Very good, Joy.
What are you doing?
Not casting a spell.
Mind your business.
- I'm just gonna say it.
- Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry that I didn't call
before I came over.
Okay, that's good.
That--is that just
for now or for the time before
or the time before that
or the time before that?
Okay.
It was for every time.
I'd really like
to be part of Gene's life now.
It was wrong of me not to
include you in the conversation.
Well,
I appreciate the apology.
Do you still enjoy travel?
Travel remains a passion
of mine, yeah.
Do you still
enjoy listening to music?
I do. I like music.
- It's music.
- Mm-hmm.
Damn it. How do they spice
it up in telenovelas?
A third party.
- Is that, like, another person?
- Yeah.
Can I confess something?
If I say no, you're probably
gonna tell me anyway, so...
When our moms sets us up,
I was sure you were just
some dental hygienist.
I am.
I am a dental hygienist.
Yeah, but you're so much more
than that, you know?
You're spontaneous
and you're clever and real.
I thought
this was some put-on,
but it's--it's not,
and it's awesome.
Sorry, I'm embarrassing you.
I just--this is--this is
really great. That's all.
♪
I want you to have this.
Oh... ly cow.
Does this mean we're,
like, going--going steady?
No, it means I
gave you a jacket.
Okay.
You want to see something cool?
Uh-huh.
- Oh, wow.
- I'm not done!
"I have these shoes.
♪ MothersDay."
Hey, Tanz-manian devil,
how's it going? Cool response.
Look,
I just wanted to warn you--
How do I put this eloquently?
Your man is downstairs
about to go downstairs
on another man.
What? Dan's back?
I know, girlfriend.
I feel you, but sometimes
people get back together.
It's like everyone
always said to me, you know,
"When you turn 25, Gene,
you're gonna
start wanting a family."
And guess what?
I do.
I want my OG mom and my OG dad
to live that OG lifestyle.
OG stands for "Only Gene."
- I will not let this happen.
Oh, no.
I-I didn't want you
to get upset and go downstairs
and add a little spice
to the scene downstairs, no.
I'm sorry, Gene,
but I'm getting my man back.
Good!
I mean, or boo.
Or do whatever.
The hell is he doing?
I think he's gonna jump
over the fire.
I'm in love,
and her name's Millie.
- Billie!
- You bet.
That's me. I'm Billie.
This is for me.
Go!
Pony, no!
- Don't be upset.
- Come on.
You remember that--
you remember that trip to Italy?
It was so amazing.
- Amazing times.
- It was so amazing.
Do you remember the thing you
kept doing in Naples?
You don't?
I don't remember anything
about Naples.
Come on.
You kept calling
Naples "nipples" the whole time.
You know, it really
wasn't all that funny at first,
but you just kept doing it!
- More, please.
- Oh, [bleep], that's good.
Where the hell is Tanzy?
It looks
like you don't need her.
You're right, Joy.
I need to take matters
into my own hands.
I didn't want to have
to do this,
but it's not
like I wasn't prepared.
Wish me luck.
You are all right,
Mr. and Mrs. Good.
- You're all right.
- You are good.
Hey, Mom and Dad,
how 'bout a tune.
♪ Let's get--
You want this?
Is this what you want?
You want me to be a man?
- You want my husband, don't you?
- No.
Well back off!
'Cause he's mine, bitch!
- Ow!
- Tanzy!
- You apologize this instant!
- No, it's okay.
We're all grown-ups here.
- We can handle this like adults.
- All right.
♪
- Stop! Stop it! Stop it!
- Get off of her!
- That's it.
- No biting! No biting!
- You're crazy!
- And what? And what? And what?
Take her inside!
Take her--take her inside.
- Don't talk like that.
- I'm gonna kill you.
Oh, my God.
- Are you okay, Mom?
- Okay.
I should probably go now.
I have overstayed my welcome.
And I tried
to head-butt a woman.
So I've got to go home.
Wait!
Oh, I forgot
why I said that.
I'm so sorry
you had to see me like that.
No, I'm pissed
I didn't, like, Vine it.
That was, like,
"Vanderpump Rules" type [bleep].
Kent, would you
walk me to the car?
I'd like to remain alive
at least until then.
I--I got you.
Come on, Dan. Come on.
Wait!
I remembered.
Oh.
This is not a good-bye, okay?
I love you, Mom.
I love you, too.
All right, come on. Come on.
Wait, are you guys
back together?
No.
Yeah, they're back together.
How was your date?
Um,
He died.
Hmm.
Who was that man?
My mom.
- Well, good night.
- Good night.