You're not my father. Just leave me be.
Tomorrow I'd be obliged if you
found yourself new lodgings.
She's useless, this one is.
I am never... leaving you.
That promise is unbreakable.
That fella they call the prince.
There's a secret going on there.
My uncle has control of my money.
Marry me, we'll secure a future.
I thought you were leaving tonight.
I can't go back home. Not yet.
But here's as good a place as any to wait.
Say what you want to
say. You don't like her.
I don't like that she
treated you so bad before.
Things are different between us.
This is business. Nothing more.
Look on the bright side. She
might jilt me all over again.
Too late. Here she comes. Missed
your chance to talk me out of it
I had to endure a lecture.
My uncle seems to think
the pair of us are fools.
I had to endure the same lecture.
From my housekeeper, no less.
- And? What did you say?
- I told her this was business.
- Thru'pence.
- What?
- For that measly little bag?
- Do you want it or not? There's folks waiting.
- Well, there must be cheaper.
- None to be had.
Got us over a barrel with these prices.
Charge what they like for it.
Listen here. All of you - listen!
Market's closed. All
trading here ends today.
- You can't just order us to leave.
- I'm the agent here.
You need licences.
And I'm no longer giving 'em.
Anyone found trading will
be in breach of the law.
- And what law's that, then?
- Mine.
You want to sell your goods,
you bring them to my door.
I will give you a fair price for them.
- And then I'll sell them on.
- What gives you the right?!
Mr Blackwood.
He's given me the authority to
run this town. I'm not gonna let
you waggoners run up
the prices any longer.
Who the hell do you think you are?
You put your hands on me?
That's gonna cost you.
How's your lad doing? I hope
things have settled down for him.
It's hard to know what's
going on in his head.
I only wish I could turn
the clock back for him.
I miss seeing him around.
I miss all of you.
'Appen I could come to call?
Upon the whole family, like?
- I'm only recently widowed, Johnny.
- I didn't mean...
I only meant...
There's plenty more needs doing!
Get to work!
Go on. Ganger's calling.
How about The Riviera for your honeymoon?
Or erm... Venice perhaps.
Not too hot in late spring.
Well, we've neither the time nor the
money for a grand tour, I'm afraid.
- There's work to be done. Right here.
- We need you to draw up
a contract for us, an equal partnership.
We're making a tender for the viaduct.
Buying up all the
remaining stock between us.
You'll be taking on huge debts.
Well, I'm due an inheritance...
now that I'm married.
- Charles? How will you raise your half?
- I'll borrow against the house.
- I'll have the papers drawn up.
- We'll need them by the end of the day.
The money will run out
if we don't act now.
Well... congratulations.
We haven't signed yet.
No! Not the company.
The other matter!
Your wedding!
Should we perhaps shake hands?
Or maybe a kiss, even.
I've no romantic illusions, Charles.
I just want us to be friends.
And to say we achieved something.
Romance we can leave to
the rest of the world.
Whoa! Whoa, there!
Go on!
I've seen worse shit-holes.
Not many, mind.
A ha'penny of tea.
All right. How much do I owe you?
Er...
- Pound of flour, bacon joint, ha'penny of tea and a ball of twine!
A shilling fourpence.
Top at arithmetic in my class at school.
Whatever the lad says.
Thank you.
Got twice the brain of
that great ox, you have.
Two sacks of flour to shift.
Have to make your living elsewhere.
My stock's as good as anyone's.
Why won't you take it?
There's people I like and there's
people I don't like, see?
Get on your wagon and
don't ever come back again.
I see you, Ralph Coates.
Acting like you own this town.
You're no better than the rest of us.
Keep your hands off me!
You're not in charge here.
And you never will be.
All right, all right!
I'll break your supply
line. I'll see to it.
Get off me! You're a strangler!
What's going on here?! Stop!
- The lad's all mixed up!
- 3lb of loin. Same wi' t'beef.
He's charged me too much.
The boy's right, Hawk. Give
him the money he's owed.
Now be on your way.
I need a sharper mind than
yours to keep this job.
You got quite a head on
your shoulders there, boy.
I need a new grocery clerk. How about it?
- No.
Sir, I don't think she'd let me.
Give her this. Call it an advance.
Who's next?
- Thank you.
- Grand opening tonight!
Now we've got music.
I am a fair maiden
My story is sad
For once I was courted...
What's the matter? Why have you stopped?
Oh, I'm awful fond of this glassware
Mum?!
But now he has left me
And gone far away...
Martha? Come over here, lass.
Sing summat for us, will you?
Oh, I... I don't sing so good.
Nonsense. Come on.
I am a fair maiden...
Reckon she can entertain the
folks in here. Don't you?
You're kidding.
- That bony little nothing?
- Finish making tea, lass, will you?
I kept my love's company
By night and by day
But now he has left me
And gone far away
Oh!
Oh! We'll advertise it proper.
Martha Quainton - the nightingale.
We could make a little stage from some of the crates.
- Oh, no. Please, no.
It'll be worth an extra sixpence in your wages.
- Aye.
Oh, ta.
Uh...
I can see why you're so keen.
I'll be earning my own wages
and bringing 'em home.
- Please let me.
- I hope to get you back in school.
I can keep up with my reading.
I've seen them children
running wild on the moor.
I don't want you running with them.
- At least this way -
- Can I go tell him?
Martha?
What's the matter?
- Tell her, lass. Tell her what you did!
- It were a joke.
That's all. Just a silly joke.
She tried to poison me.
She's a demon... she is.
- Ooh! Martha!
- Are you all right?
- What have you done to her?!
- She's making a fuss, she is.
It were only cleaning soda.
My throat burns something awful.
I'll go to the river,
fetch some water for you.
I want that little beast out of here!
What's the matter? Are
you all right, Annie?
- Where's the Partridge lad?
- Over here.
We need to get him to his mam.
What's the matter with him?
His neck's all swollen. 'Appen
there's fever in this town.
Oh, God!
No, no, no, no.
Oh, she has a bad fever, sure.
- And her neck's swollen.
- Rose Partridge's boy's the same.
I've seen summat like it before.
Folks call it strangling angel.
- Please tell me she'll recover.
- I can't help her, Annie. She needs a doctor.
There's a fella in town.
He's not cheap, mind.
I'll pay anything I have to.
Annie. I'll go.
You need to be with her.
Erm... begging your pardon, sir.
- Will Mrs Blackwood be returning soon?
- She's at her uncle's house.
- She'll be arriving tomorrow.
- You'll be wanting a room prepared?
Aye. She can have the Blue Room.
I meant... for the two of you.
You must've... discussed it between you.
I'll make up two rooms, then.
The fever is infectious. Reckon she
caught it from the Partridge lad.
She needs a doctor. They both do.
Someone needs to ride to town. The cart doesn't leave till morning.
- Take my cart.
You're a puzzle, Prince.
Always eager to play the hero.
I still can't figure you out.
I can't figure you out myself.
Why does a man who built railroads in
America need to cross the seas to get work?
Makes me wonder what
you're leaving behind there.
You know horses? Hm?
Did you ever see a stallion
drive another from the herd?
He gets a sense of who
his strongest rival is.
I'm not your rival, Mr Coates.
Now, excuse me, would you?
Any jobs going?
Is there?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- What's going on in there?
- The Partridge lad.
He died.
Please.
I'm not ready.
What?
What is it, my sweetheart? I'm here.
Leaves...
.. and orange blossom.
I'm not ready to die.
They're gonna ride me through the village.
That's right, my darling.
You'll be married in lace.
You'll look beautiful.
And you can tall Ralph Coates...
he doesn't own this valley!
And his supplies aren't getting through!
This remote place...
with no-one to take care of you.
I wanted my girl to have everything.
Please... Martha.
Please be strong for me.
Oh, thank God you're back!
How's Martha? How's she doing?
Where's the Doctor?
You never made it into town.
- Some Laggan men are blocking the road. I couldn't get past.
I don't think she'll make
it through the night.
What about the Blackwood house?
- Johnny!
- Aye.
Aye, you're right.
They're the only ones who can help us.
I'm going to need you
to spend the night here.
I'll watch over him, Mrs Quainton.
Why can't I just come with you?
Because I don't want you getting sick.
It's your first night on your own.
It's a new adventure.
Eh?
Ya!
Mortgage papers. Sign here and here.
I'll deliver it to the
bank in the morning.
Let me in, Charles, please.
I've got a girl who's
dangerously ill here.
In the name of God, Charles,
I'm begging you to help us!
What's going on?
Annie, this is my brother.
Her neck's all swollen. It
seems she can't breathe proper.
- Strangling angel, the shanty folk call it.
- Bring her in and lay her down.
- Here we are.
- Hey.
I tried to fetch her a doctor,
but there's trouble on t'road.
There's no way we can get through.
I'll... send Easter to fetch Dr Crick.
He shouldn't be on the road alone.
I swore to myself if you ever came back
here - - The girl needs tending, Charles.
Fast as you can, Easter.
- What's going on out there?
- Just some navvies from the shanty town.
I need that wage money. Deliver these
immediately, will you, so we can raise the capital.
Are you all right sleeping down there?
The takings from today.
We made a proper fortune here.
The people that live out here have
nothing but what the traders bring.
But he who controls the flow of
trade, that man would be king.
What are you doing?
Well, the king has to
be bountiful sometimes.
I'm making a food parcel for Mrs Laggan.
Her husband died in the uh... explosion.
Hey, that fella they call the prince.
- I see him hanging around your ma.
- You mean Johnny?
Mm.
I thought they might...
I thought they might be together.
- 'Appen Polly's in?
- She had to go out.
Is it urgent?
You a friend of Polly's?
Anything I can help you with?
I come and see her regular, like.
Why don't you come and see me?
You might prefer it.
I'd do you for a shilling six.
Sixpence cheaper than her.
Does she know you're undercutting her?
What she doesn't know won't hurt her.
- Seems I don't know you after all.
- I never said nothing to you that were a lie.
Why is your brother so
angry with you, Johnny?
He reckons I turned my
back on this family.
And did you?
I brought a tonic for her.
Good girl.
Alma. What are you doing?
I were stupid! I were jealous.
What are you talking about?
Martha Quainton.
They say that she's at death's door.
No! Don't try and stop me!
I need to do this.
I need to do all of the chores. It's
the least I can do to make amends.
You've not heard, then?
It's nowt to do with you. She's got fever.
Well, I must've caused it.
Partridge boy had it worse.
- You didn't do nowt to him, did you?
- She said it were me.
My mam. She said I were
the one what had done it.
I've been scrubbing this
place from top to bottom.
- She probably wanted her floors washing.
- Oh, damn her!
The girl's up at the house. But
she needs a doctor bad, sir.
Mr Blackwood took the girl
in, did he? Imagine that.
Some men have blocked the road.
I'll need help getting through.
There's navvies here are
broad enough to see them off.
I'll appoint someone
to come along with you.
All quiet around here, then?
Aye. Not much doing. No trade.
You did say... all vittles are shared.
As soon as I make some
clink, I'll pay my way.
Trade's been slow, has it?
You get one chance.
Don't try and make a fool out of me.
I've been in this game a long time.
Pretend this never
happened, then, shall we?
I'm sorry.
Things have been bad.
Place I worked in before,
fella who owned it...
- .. used to get drunk and...
- Knock you about, did he?
Just been used to taking care
of myself and no-one else.
Well, we take care of each other.
Here.
Start paying your way with the next one.
They'll be armed with just cudgels, so...
.. no match for you with this.
A girl's life depends on you.
- Find that doctor. Bring him back to us.
- Why are you putting me in charge?
You're a decent man. Honest...
strong. Go along with this gentleman.
You can be our watchman.
I thought maybe you were dead.
I was working in Africa a while.
- And Father tracked me down there.
- He told you he was sick?
You're too late for him!
Aye. I know.
I'm sorry for it.
The girl - she's taken a bad turn.
Come on! Come on.
Lovely girl, come on.
She's barely breathing.
- I don't know what to do.
- The poison makes a canker in her throat.
- There must be something we can do!
- Martha, can you hear me?
Martha!
Somebody do something! Please!
I'll need a knife from the kitchen.
- What?
I saw my mother save a
child on the plantation.
Reckon I can save her.
But I'll need a knife.
Wait. What are you going to do to her?
It will be easier... if you're not here.
- What's going on, Mr Coates?
- There's trouble in the valley tonight.
But you're safe in here, son.
Don't you worry about nothing.
Davey! Davey!
I'll cut you down like a hare!
I grew up in this house.
I sat on these stairs some nights,
watching the light from my father's study.
I still remember the
creak of that banister.
She's out of danger.
Thank you, sir!
- I see you broke the blockade, then.
- The other fella fled across t'dales.
I'll take him back to Jericho,
lock him up and fetch a magistrate.
No, no, no. You head on over to the
scaffold. I'll take him from here.
I reckon we owe you a debt.
Any man can be anything he wants here.
Just you remember that.
How long are you planning to stay?
Already you're anxious to be rid of me?
Let's not pretend we have any
appetite for this reunion.
You wanted no part of this family. Fine.
Get back out on the road.
What's the matter? Lost
something, have you?
No wonder you tried to hide it, Charles.
John James Blackwood -
deceased. You declared me dead!
Missing for more than seven years...
a man's death can be made legal.
That's what my lawyers advised me.
I didn't know when you would
come home... or even if!
I see. So you thought you'd just...
hasten that day along a little.
The terms of his will!
He left everything to you and not to me.
That's why he wanted you here. No matter
that you'd turned your back on him.
He still forgave you everything.
Didn't matter what I did.
Nursed him through his dying days!
He still left Blackwood House to you!
Can you imagine how that feels?!
I just assumed...
I thought he'd cut me
off without a shilling.
Charles.
I didn't come here... just
to claim an inheritance.
There's none to claim.
The house is all we have left, John.
This viaduct...
It's almost bled me dry.
I need to borrow money against the house.
Otherwise, everything I've
built here will vanish.
So, if you're to have your money,
you want me to just walk away.
If he was willing to forgive me...
if he wanted me to be here...
.. then why can't you do the same?
Oh, don't play the dutiful son.
It doesn't convince me.
You never truly cared for him.
You never cared for anyone.
You stand between me
and everything I want.
Only John Blackwood...
would have the arrogance to ruin
people's dreams and not give a damn!
Enjoying this, are you
Can't pretend I'm not
happy seeing you like this.
That is true.
- What are you doing? You letting me loose?
- Don't want no magistrates poking their nose in.
This town is mine.
- What are you gonna tell 'em?
- Tell 'em you escaped.
Jumped me when I stopped
to get you some water.
That's why you chose that dumb lad.
Why you put that gun in his hand.
Sweet-natured fella... like him.
Means you can control him like a dog.
They will arrest you if you show up again.
Maybe you can pay me back sometime
She'll remain with us. No question.
Mm.
Hey.
You - rest easy.
You've got the whole Blackwood
family waiting on you.
I must go see George. I'll be back soon.
I were bringing these flowers for
Martha, Mrs Quainton. How is she?
Well, I came to say... I'm proper sorry.
And I were hoping... maybe...
she and I could be friends, or summat.
You didn't bring those flowers for Martha.
You brought them to stop
people from thinking ill of you.
You're right. Weren't my idea.
Well... I suppose you can
tell folk it's all made up now.
Aye, there's a few girls here.
But... you won't find one
as fun as me, though.
How old are you, girl?
18, 19, hm?
How old do you want me to be?
Pardon me, ma'am.
I prefer someone with a
little more schooling.
You seem in good spirits.
- Smile on your face.
- Oh, it's been a good day.
Young girl didn't take your fancy?
You know, girls that age...
they ain't got no discretion.
I need you to forget
what you're gonna see.
What's that there on your skin?
An injustice.
Something you should know.
Your brother got wed.
- Who is she?
- Miss Lambton.
Do you remember her?
Finally persuaded her, did he?
I know why you truly fled this place.
Your brother doesn't
know anything about it.
If you set foot in here again,
I will spill it!
I can't believe he came back.
I didn't expect this.
He can't stay here!
- He can't be a part of our lives, Charles.
- There's something I have to tell you.
The estate belongs to him.
What?!
- It's fine. He says he wants no part of it.
But if you can't prove it's yours, we're
no longer free to raise the money on it.
My uncle, he only agreed
to my having my inheritance
on the understanding that
you would match the money.
So you're telling me we
haven't got a farthing?
Annie?
What's wrong?
I'm grateful for what you did for Martha.
But I'm sorry, I can't let you in.
What is it? What's the matter?
I can't be with a man who lies to me,
Johnny! I don't know who you are!
I came here to see my father afore he died.
- Really?
Then you tell me plain. Why have
you been hiding in this valley?
My brother and I... we find it
hard to act civil round each other.
No, that's not an answer, Johnny.
That's your family home.
That's your own kin. And
you've not even been near!
Annie, please!
You're the reason...
I've stayed here so long.
And just because I'm a Blackwood...
George!