- We need somewhere we can go.
- This job's going.
Culverdale way. They're building
a great bridge out there.
A viaduct,
making this country one nation.
- I'm Johnny Jackson.
- Tobias Farrelly.
Folks call me Skinny.
There's a space on my gang...
Your Highness
Aagh!
You're a dead man, Prince.
I swear you are!
- Someone help me!
- Jack!
Has anybody seen my husband?
Looks like it was sabotage
killed these men.
Name's Bamford. I'm a detective.
Someone's made a copy of that?
Any of your men missing?
Red Killeen.
- Get back!
- No!
George killed a man.
We have to bury the body.
I have an inheritance.
And I want to put it to use.
- After everything that's happened between us?
- This is business.
I need you to take over in the
valley. You're the best man we have.
- What can I get you, Mister?
- I'm not here for your poor man's ale.
Red Killeen!
I've reason to believe
he had a grudge in this town.
Caused the explosion.
I've ridden east to west...
Churchtown to Morwenstow...
No sign of him.
Vanished into the wind, he has.
Someone here knows summat.
Somebody's got a story to tell.
This here is for information.
Half stays in my pocket
till I can check the truth of it.
'Appen I'll have that drink now.
This here's Dagger. He's er...
looking for a place to stay.
14 shillings a week,
three meals and a mattress.
How about if I pay you less
and maybe have smaller portions
That smile works with the ladies,
does it?
Aye. I've had some success with it.
Not put off by
a wedding ring neither.
Not married. Just impervious.
Dictionary up there.
Help yourself
Thank you.
I've just given this chap
the welcome speech.
He can give it you. And mind you
keep these curtains closed.
I've a daughter.
Should have enough
to pay a week's rent.
And have money to put by, an' all.
How long will it take to get home?
Oh, nose to the grindstone,
should be back in a month or two.
You're lying to me.
Martha.
- Where's George?
- He's busy with his books.
Mam? What's going on?
George?
That secret...
Our secret... the one that
we agreed never to speak about.
- You haven't told no-one?
- What's this about?
- Promise me that you haven't let on!
- Johnny, stop it!
Why do you want to remind him?
It's better if he forgot.
- I haven't said nothing to no-one.
- Course you haven't.
We'll never... talk about that again,
any of us.
You're not my father.
Just leave me be.
That detective's back in town.
If George says anything,
we're finished.
He keeps remembering.
It doesn't help
having you under this roof.
- What does that mean?
- - I want you gone.
- Annie, you can't blame me.
- I'm not blaming you.
You moved heaven and earth to help us
but he needs to put this in the past.
Right.
Tomorrow I'd be obliged if
you found yourself new lodgings.
Come.
Hands in.
This is my kingdom.
You're a guest here.
Don't forget it now.
That scaffold needs rebuilding
from the ground up.
It was badly damaged in the blast,
sir.
Lumber isn't cheap.
And it takes time to acquire.
We can't just have the men all sitting idle.
What about building from
the other side of the valley?
- Begging your pardon, sir... are you suggesting...
- Another gang.
Blasting from the east whilst
the west is being dismantled.
It ain't never been done.
Still,
don't mean it ain't worth trying.
You're a good man, Coates.
Tell me. Where do you hail from?
Vermont, sir.
North-eastern part of America.
Family of blacksmiths.
Led me to work on the railways.
Crossed the seas to get away from
that damn civil war.
I see. England's a haven, then.
Of sorts.
Sir, the erm...
That detective's back down in
the valley. He's unsettling the men.
My viaduct has been sabotaged,
Coates.
Whoever did this,
we can't let them get away with it.
Mr Thornhill.
I...I need a job, Mr Coates.
I need to find work in this valley.
I can't get a job...
after what happened.
If you're not too proud
to skivvy for me...
you can collect the rents.
Morning.
Tell me, now.
Either of you gentlemen
hear talk of Red Killeen?
You're his friends, aren't you?
Least, that's what I've been hearing.
Be sure and come at closing time
Great at clearing the place, you is!
I've spoken to my lawyers, Charles.
Take me on as a partner...
and your problems will be over.
We'll put up half the capital each.
I've got my inheritance and you...
can borrow against this estate.
I assume you have control of it.
I'm the only one to inherit.
Sunday is Whitsun.
The men deserve some celebration -
a couple of kegs.
A hog roast. Maybe dancing.
A Whit Fair,
like any proper village.
'If thou of fortune be bereft,
and in thy store
there be but left two loaves,
sell one and, with the dole,
buy hyacinths to feed thy soul.'
Are you suggesting poetry evenings?
I'm suggesting we make this valley
somewhere they want to live and work.
Another Eden.
- It's not near enough.
- I know. And I'm sorry for it.
Can't do you no special favours.
Coates has paid me to collect rents.
- Not listen to folks' sad stories.
- Jack saved some, but it were less than I reckoned.
You'd better get out of them
smart clothes and start earning.
It's less than a week since he died.
Are you telling me
I've no more time to mourn?
My poor Jack.
Poor Jack would sooner you didn't
get booted out of your home.
I didn't know it were you.
I mean,
that's been leaving them flowers.
You knew him, Tobias?
He lodged with me for a while.
How are you holding up?
I'm not sure how to make a go of it.
It's a hard town for women.
You have to scratch
to find your place.
Reckon they'll always be willing to
pay for a plate and a mattress.
Me, I've got no spare rooms.
I'll have to find
some other employment.
Something you want to say?
Begging your pardon, sir, I...
don't like speaking out of turn.
All evidence to the contrary
these past 30 years.
What do you wish to scold me for?
I was with you
every day you grew up, Charlie.
I feel like I raised you.
And I saw...
what she did to you before.
And how she... broke you.
It's different now.
She's offering to invest her fortune.
But you can't just
shut your heart away.
That'll be all, Epiphany. Thank you.
- I see you've got t'sign up in t'window.
- Johnny left this morning.
You're the man of the house now.
I feel bad for him.
It's not your fault.
I were speaking badly to him.
He were just trying to help us out.
George, it's safer this way.
No-one'll find out what happened.
Ma'am. Your sign says lodgings.
- Where did the prince end up?
- Found himself other lodgings.
I can smell a quarrel
You can lose that smirk
before you come for supper.
Morning to you, ma'am.
Morning.
George,
go out and fetch some water in.
George?
Fine children you've got there.
Will you be staying long?
As long as it takes to find one man.
I could have been a collier
working down a mine
I could have been a sailor
a-sailing on the brine, but...
I'm a navvy, I'm a navvy,
working on the line
working on the line...
That detective fella, he's gone out.
You know why he's come here,
don't you?
Remember your dad
took you fishing one time?
He said I were no good for it.
I wouldn't stay still.
Scared them fishes away, I did.
I need you...
to be a fisherman for me.
I need you to remain quite... still.
Day or two... he'll be gone.
Navvies are all
cut from t'same cloth.
They all wear the same,
walk the same,
cuss the same -
easy to lose yourself in a crowd.
So you think Killeen
has slipped the net.
There is a chance he'd make for port.
- Find a berth overseas.
- Easy way to be sure.
Telegraph port authorities.
Liverpool.
She's a real marvel, that Annie.
What happened... twixt the two of you?
She's not my sweetheart. Never was.
You're better off.
With two children
hanging off her apron...
It's better to be a free agent
in a town like this.
Found yourself a new friend, Prince?
He ain't no navvy.
Looks like a pretty lass, he does.
'Appen the prince wants to
get in his trousers
Leave it. He wants someone to rag.
Don't start nothing, Dagger.
Take your ease.
- No-one's gonna curse me to my face.
- Come on, lad. You be smart now.
Whoa!
You're a dead man. You know that?
Oh! It takes two of you now,
does it
'Ey, Prince.
What do you reckon to this, then?
It takes two of them
to beat just one of us.
Get off him! Get off him!
- Break it up!
- Get off him! Get off him!
Get off! Next person who raises
his hand leaves this town! I mean it!
We'll finish 'em sometime,
you and me.
What's going on here?
The prince and his mate got into it with
Hawker and Shay. It's just a bit of sport.
All right, you men. Back to work!
- I was just looking! Let me go!
- Why should I?
- It's the birch for you.
- I'll tell you something true.
Red had a fight down by the river.
Good fighter the other fella was too.
Did you see his face?
Do you know his name?
Tell me before I let you go.
No, I just heard talk of it.
Happened over near waterfall.
Hey, son. Fetch me that.
Ever seen a man fight wi' a knife?
You'll dispatch a man with one stroke
if you know where to hit right.
The Killeens of the Earth.
Maybe somebody finished him off.
What do you think?
Well, I can't pretend
you're not welcome.
There's more than enough work going.
Tell me true.
Do you think you'll manage it?
Hm?
Have some stranger
put his paws over you?
I need two bob by t'week's end.
Do you reckon one customer
would do it?
One jig'll give you what you need.
It's fast money.
Usually, half a minute.
Please, God, my Jack'll forgive me
for making this my living.
Where's the money gone?
Someone's been in here,
taken everything.
- Where were you?
- Washing pots. You can't blame me.
I were only gone a minute. And how would
they even know the money was there?
Oh, the fool.
The little fool!
- What's happened?
- George has run away from here. - Why? What's gone on?
He did something.
It's best you don't know about it.
I need to go after him.
You serve supper.
- If anyone asks, I'm sick.
- Where are you going to find him?
I know exactly where he's headed.
I've telegraphed
the port authorities.
Expect a reply within a day.
Post rider will deliver
directly to me.
We'll find out
if Killeen's fled abroad.
Still... I reckon there might be
another answer, maybe.
Killeen was involved in a fight
just before he disappeared.
And... you think...
I think navvies are proud men.
They won't let a slight
go unpunished.
I think he might be under the soil.
So.
- We're looking for the man who beat him.
- Aye.
A fighter. And a good'un.
What if we held a competition at
your Whitsun fair, a sporting match?
We set the men against each other.
All the good fighters will declare.
And the man you're after,
he's sure to be amongst them.
- So... have you ever worked a tavern before?
- No.
We're saving. I'm... trying
to help my ma the best I can.
Be in in a half hour. Best frock.
Alma. This is Martha.
She'll be working alongside you.
- What do you reckon?
- What's that?
Have you heard about the wrestling
match at the Whitsun Fair?
You and me.
We can challenge Hawker and Shay.
Something about you
is far too reckless.
But I reckon that's how I like it.
I need to know about
them bruises on your skin, lad.
I'm looking for a navvy
who's been brawling.
- Shouldn't have more than 30 or 40
men to choose from - Turn around.
- What?
- I'm looking for knife marks.
A navvy's skin's
a catalogue of violence.
No. You're not the man.
Now. Make him wash his self.
And he's paying for a jig,
not a mattress.
He falls asleep and snores, you
kick him out of bed. Do you hear?
Right, fella. She's waiting for you.
Mrs Laggan.
You might as well keep 'em.
They're going back into your pocket.
I...I'm sorry. No, missus.
I don't reckon how
I'm eager to do this.
What's the matter? Don't you like me?
Oh, aye. I like you right enough.
Two bob. That's all I need
to settle my bill for t'week.
Stay.
- Please.
- Erm...
I...I'll take this for rent, then.
But I won't lay a finger on you.
Well, I haven't done nowt to earn it.
We've talked some.
I bought your company with it.
How's that for you?
I don't know what we are,
Mrs Laggan.
We're not townsfolk,
we're not countrymen neither.
But I surely know that...
...we're not savages.
This... can be
our little arrangement.
Oh, look who it is.
'Ey! Any of you likely lads
wanna try your hand?
Whit Fair wrestling.
You can earn yoursen 10 shilling.
Put your name down, Hawker.
You'll make us all rich!
Them two think the money's
as good as won.
They'll have to get past
Dagger and me.
- Call yourself a wrestler?
- More like a big old.
By name but not by nature eh
I swear I never touched 'em.
Must've knocked 'em with
your sleeve. You - get sweeping.
- Everything all right?
- She's useless, this one.
George?
I knew you'd come here.
You can't make me go back there.
You don't have any choice.
This isn't your home any more.
You can't pretend the last few days
haven't happened.
Where's the money?
How much is missing?
- I hitched a ride. I had to pay.
- So that's half my savings.
- Now you hate me.
- Don't ever say that.
Come back.
I promise I'll look after you.
- I won't let anything happen to you.
- You're a liar.
- No-one can promise that.
- George.
This is about your dad.
He left us wi' nothing.
He did.
But I am never... leaving you.
That promise is unbreakable.
Saw you coming across the moors.
Are you bringing Mr Bamford
a telegram?
- Aye, sir.
- I'm the agent here. - I'll take it off your hands.
If you make it worth my while
What brings you out here,
Mr Bamford?
I don't recall giving you permission
to open my telegram.
Killeen's not in the passenger log,
is he?
You know where he is, though,
don't you?
Would you believe
I'm ignorant of his whereabouts?
You won yourself quite a promotion
after the explosion happened.
You paid Killeen to do it,
didn't you?
This town was run by a drunk.
Thornhill had no place here.
So you let some crazy man loose
with a barrel load of powder
just to win this mile of track
from him?
Ever fought in a war?
Ever marched behind
a general who's inept?
One bullet in the general's back
can save a whole army.
So. It's for the good of the rest.
Anything else to say
before I march you off in irons?
You're not gonna lift a finger,
except to shake my hand.
And maybe...
...count out some of this money.
There's a price
to every man's loyalty.
What's yours, sir?
Whatever Blackwood's paying you,
I'll double it.
Come and place your money.
Place your money.
- Yes, sir. What can I do for you? Can I place a bet?
- Yes.
That one.
Didn't wanna go watch?
I want to stay by you.
Come on!
I get to do what I should've done
before. Bury your face in t'dirt!
Bamford's still here, then,
sniffing round.
You're lucky. You don't have to
share a bunk with him.
He's staying at Annie's wi' us.
All right. The rules are simple.
One man in the ring at a time.
Fighters can swap out.
All it takes is a handshake.
All right? Fighters, step in!
Dagger, shake!
Shake!
One man in the ring at a time!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey! Hey!
Up you get! Up you get, pretty boy!
Here we go! Come on!
Come on! Let's have it, please!
Get out of it!
What's the matter? What's happened?
I can't watch. It's... it's Johnny.
He's being ground into t'dirt.
Come on, lads! Come on, lads!
Johnny!
- Wrestle!
- Come on, Johnny!
Wrestle!
And fight!
- Come on, Johnny!
- Ten...
nine, eight, seven...
six, five...
four, three, two, one!
Come on!
Hawker and Shay are the winners!
Yes!
Come on, lad.
It was my fault. I distracted you.
No, you made it easier,
losing for real.
We bet against ourselves.
Reckon we'll have cleaned up here.
There's your winnings.
- What will you do with it?
- Probably keep Polly occupied a while.
What about you, Prince?
I'll see you at the tavern, lads.
Come here.
- What's this?
- It ain't enough for you to set up home again in t'village.
But it's enough to get the lad
away from Bamford.
Take the children and leave here.
I've not that many friends
that I'll forget the best of them.
Thank you.
Oh!
Sir.
I've been waiting for you,
Mrs Quaintain.
I've come to tell you...
...I'll be leaving.
Killeen is overseas.
He won't be crossing my path again.
Much obliged.
Where's my wandering boy tonight?
The boy of my tenderest care
The boy who was once
my joy and light
- Excuse me.
- The child of my love and prayer?
Got the telegram from Liverpool.
Killeen was in the passenger log.
He'll be halfway round the world
by now.
- Are you certain he acted alone?
- Aye, sir.
Reckon that's what happened.
Oh, where is my boy tonight?
I reckon I owe you, sir.
You... you owe me nowt, ma'am.
- I paid for a portion of your time.
- I owe you.
I owe you one dance.
Thank you.
Something's wrong.
What is it?
I'm afraid women
aren't much welcome in business.
My uncle has control of my money.
He's refusing to let me invest it.
But... I thought...
- You led me to believe...
- Oh, don't fret, Charles. All's not lost.
I'm committed to this enterprise.
And the money is due to me
the second I'm married.
Oh, fine. So I just have to wait for you to find
a suitable husband and we can be business partners
We could always hasten
that day along, of course.
We're a pair... you and I.
Both passionate about the work here.
Marry me. We'll secure a future.
I'm in the unique position
of having tried that once already.
I've been paying all my life
for that one mistake I made.
You have too.
Can't this be the moment
that we begin again?
- He bought the story. He thinks Killeen has fled.
- Good.
You'd better hope
he is in the ground.
Who do you think
would've put him there?
That fella they call the prince.
There's a secret going on there.
I've seen navvies fight
a hundred times.
Never seen a navvy
shake hands before a fight.
Whoever he is, he's a gentleman.
I thought you were leaving tonight.
I thought I'd never see you again.
I can't go back home. Not yet.
But here's as good
a place as any to wait.