Whole thing was an accident.
Nobody's going to find out.
You'll make sure,
they'll only dig so far?
This ground is soft,
there's something else.
- There's another body.
- I have nothing new to tell you.
We didn't have a body back then.
With a blanket, this is a direct
link to someone from your house.
I saw you, tear out something from
his body.
Could be of some use,
might even point to who did it.
Take this.
It's a proud moment, when a man
receives his first ever wage.
No matter how he comes by it.
The world is full of men like
Rory McCleod.
It's the ones that love you, even
when you give them reason not to.
That's a real man.
That's your Davey.
John and Isabella were together?
Is that what you're telling me?
- It's you that I care about.
- Then aren't I lucky to have you?
- You can't go on the run.
- Annie, I have to.
Coates. He won't let this lie.
Perhaps Coates understands exactly
the type of man you are.
A liar, a cheat. Is it unreasonable
to assume a murderer too?
Mam?
Yes, love?
What's gonna happen to Johnny?
I don't know.
But it were my fault.
I can't let him take t'blame for it.
We'll sort it.
Now try and get some sleep.
I need to own up, Mam.
- I better tell them that it were me.
- No, you don't.
You get that idea out of your head
right now. And keep your voice down.
How the heck are you gonna sort it?
What's happening?
Nothing, love.
You go back to sleep.
Your brother's dreaming, is all.
I was only saying.
You've been "only saying" all
morning.
Just give it a rest, will you?
Mark my words, the law takes on a
different meaning when you're a gentleman.
We'll see no justice here.
Red was murdered in cold blood and
thrown in the ground like an animal.
Now his body's sitting there
rotting,
while Johnny Blackwood
kisses the backsides of his cronies.
Look, everybody says Red were
responsible for the explosion.
It seems to me he were an animal!
There's no proof Johnny did owt.
But if he did, I reckon
he was doing us all a favour.
You two have always been special
friends, haven't you?
Hey, hey. Leave it! Leave it!
Leave it!
Get back to work, you two.
And no more trouble.
Forgive me for intruding,
Mr Blackwood.
But with you being his brother,
you'll know he's not to blame.
I can't help you, Mrs Quaintain.
Coates is dealing with the matter.
He must take my brother before the
magistrate, same as any man.
But you have sway, sir...
...influence.
And I know you're a good man.
The way you took my daughter in,
saved her life.
You know Johnny could never hurt
anyone.
Justice is blind to family loyalty.
I can't get involved.
So you're happy to entrust his life
to another?
And you're sure Mr Coates is the
right man?
I'm sorry, Mrs Quaintain.
You can't just abandon him!
Your food, Mr Blackwood.
I trust you slept well.
I need to see my brother.
I need to talk to him.
No, it's best you stay right here
for now.
Red has friends on the gang
and there've been rumblings.
I've sent for the magistrate,
but until then,
you're safer under lock and key.
And whatever's happened between us,
sir,
I'll see that you're dealt with
fairly.
Mr Coates?
The workers are not happy, sir.
They want answers.
As do we all.
We need to get t'magistrate down
here quick time to avoid trouble.
It's a day's ride into town. I ain't
leaving that prisoner with no protection.
And I ain't taking him with me,
neither.
You yourself know, anything can
happen up on those moors.
No, we stay right here until things
quieten down.
This is our town.
Our turf, and Red was one of our own,
not some gent dressed up in navvy's clothes.
Johnny needs to pay for what he did
to him.
Gentlemen, gentlemen.
I can assure you, justice will be
served. You have my word.
What's your promise count for in a room full
of gentlemen who think we're nowt but scum?
You run this town. Do something!
- All right.
- Do it now before we do.
Let's talk about it.
See if maybe we can come to a
solution between ourselves.
Capstick's.
- Joe?
- Yeah?
A barrel of ale if you will.
- A barrel?
- That's right.
If you please.
We've got important matters to
discuss.
I'll roll one out.
What are you doing? What is it?
Davey, please, I need to see him.
It ain't safe here.
Imagine it were Alma,
begging to see you.
I have to talk to him.
All right.
But if Mr Coates catches you,
or me, for that matter...
Thank you.
Annie.
What are we gonna do?
I'm helpless, trapped in here.
I'll think of something.
In the meantime, we keep quiet.
We give them nothing.
Maybe Charles will see sense.
No, we're on our own,
he won't help us.
I went to him, asked him to help.
He straight out refused,
won't use his position, anything.
No, listen to me,
it'll be all right.
I'll do everything I can
to get Coates off your back,
clear your name,
I don't know how but I will.
Annie, be careful.
Coates is gunning for me.
He'll stop at nothing to be rid of
me.
Then let him do his worst.
He's got nothing on you,
no evidence.
You didn't kill Red.
Drink up, gentlemen.
If you'll excuse me a moment,
I've got business to attend to.
What's Coates playing at,
filling their bellies with ale?
Surely it'll inflame things?
I don't know, but it's the fastest
grasp of silver we've had in a while.
Mr Quaintain?
Whoa, whoa.
It's all right.
This trouble's got us all on edge.
Yes, sir.
Your mother too, huh?
Especially since your pa's gone
and Johnny's locked up.
- She's scared, sir.
- Well, it's an upsetting business.
It must be tough on you,
living in that house.
You know, uh...
sometimes a man needs another man's
counsel.
Come and take a walk with me.
Sometimes you just need to share the
weight.
You know?
Take another man's view on the
world.
I guess you had Johnny until now.
You were beginning to trust him...
...seek his advice.
I do listen to him.
And me mam.
Just happen they're not always right.
I mean... how can I let another man
take on something that's my doing?
George, what's on your mind?
I promised me mam that I'd take it to
t'grave.
I feel so ashamed.
I can't stop thinking about it.
It's there every day when I wake up.
He had nowt to do with it.
It had nothing to do with Johnny.
He were just trying to help.
I didn't mean him no harm.
I wanted to get away from him.
Are you telling me...
...that Red's death was down to you?
Johnny tried to cover it up.
I can't let him pay for it, I can't.
I'm scared.
Come here, son. Aww.
We can handle this between us.
You mustn't say a thing about this.
Not another word about it to
anybody.
Aye, of course.
Now we're for it.
These lot won't rest until they've
lynched him.
Aye, I think you're right.
Coates has made fools of us all.
Thinking he can quieten us down
with a bellyful of ale?
It's time Johnny Blackwood
learnt the meaning of justice.
Open the door, Davey!
Look, I can't do that.
Calm down, Shay.
Get out of me way!
Blackwood!
Come on out to me, Blackwood!
Let me out, Davey!
- Come out here!
- Get back, Shay.
Come on, get back!
Everybody, get back!
Calm down.
Calm down! Get back!
Gentlemen! Gentlemen!
Gentlemen!
Everybody, calm down!
I know you all want actions.
But let's go back to the tavern.
And you can give voice to your
concerns there in a civilised way.
What, while he's hiding in there?
- Give me the keys.
- What about the magistrate?
There's no time.
Get back.
I've nothing to hide!
If each of you has a voice, it's only
right that Johnny Blackwood has one too.
I hope you have a good story worked
out.
Get him out of there! Come on!
Get him out of there!
- Where's George?
- I'm not sure.
I need to find him.
I don't want you wandering
about alone out there.
Mam, what is going on?
Hello, love. I'm just after
a quick word with your mam.
Come in.
I thought you might need a friend
with all that's going on.
You two, wait out there.
But don't think about stepping off
that porch.
Can I count on you,
Polly, as a friend?
In the truest sense of the word?
I need you to do something for me.
Without asking questions.
We all know that Johnny and Red
came to blows once.
Navvies are always scrapping.
And it's a fact that Red's body was
found in Annie Quaintain's blanket.
Now, Annie Quaintain is not strong
enough to kill a man of Red's stature.
But Johnny Blackwood was living in her hut
and could have easily taken that blanket.
Mr Coates, it's a bunkhouse!
Any number of fellas
could have snatched that blanket.
What I know that you don't know,
is that Mr Blackwood was determined
to exhume those bodies by himself.
That's not true.
You're a liar, Mr Coates.
It's not a job that any man would
relish,
unless he had something to hide,
perhaps.
How about we cut his throat and
sling him in the same dirty hole?
- Quiet, please.
- You don't know what you're talking about.
Quieten down!
He went missing just after Red was
dug up!
You don't know what you're talking
about!
He was trying to flee! And, look,
he's lied to us from the start!
What posh gent would want to live
down here unless he was hiding summat?
What's he got to hide?
Quiet, please!
This is not gonna work if we all
speak at once.
Now, if you want to say your
piece...
Give me this. Bring this on out.
If you've got something to say...
you stand on this.
If you ain't standing right there,
then you ain't got the right to talk.
- Agreed?
- Aye.
The whole town's turning out.
Mam, why have you changed your
dress?
- That's your mourning gown, in't it?
- Yes, it is.
Reckon it'll do no harm to remind them we've
had enough heartache for one lifetime.
Right, Martha, you're to accompany
your mam.
George, me and you are gonna keep an
eye on that stew pot.
Why can't George come?
It's no place for young eyes nor
ears.
Aye, all right.
You look after your mam.
So what if Johnny fought with Red?
It don't make him guilty of murder.
Oh, oh, Dagger! Happen you're in on it,
mate, you're always trying to protect him.
All navvies fight from time to time!
Me too!
And you... you... and you.
And no one's accusing us of killing
Red.
You've got nothing on him.
Well said, Dagger!
You can't prove anything!
Quiet, quiet.
Who's next to step up and speak?
I reckon I've got summat to
tell you.
I were taking a walk late the other
night.
I stopped for a breather,
a short moment to myself.
Were you on your own?
And I overheard Annie and Johnny
talking.
At first, I thought they
were having a private moment.
I mean, Annie's got two kids.
It can't be easy for sweethearts,
even at their age.
They were whispering secrets...
about something terrible that had
happened.
And you could see it by the look on
their faces.
What did I tell you? He's guilty!
Quieten down, everybody!
Let the girl speak!
What's she playing at?
She don't know nothing about it!
Don't bet on it. Where there's
trouble, Alma'll find it.
- You're right there, Joe.
- Aye.
All I ever hear talk of is your
mam's cooking.
What's the big secret,
then, eh, George?
Secret? What do you mean?
The ingredient.
Oh, erm... dunno. Salt?
Too busy with your books to worry
about owt like cooking, aren't you?
Then how come you've not turned
a single page since I got here?
Have you ever played faro?
Eh?
Johnny and Red were avowed enemies!
What happened was more than scrapping. Jack
had to break them apart and warn Red off.
Sadly, Jack is not here to speak for
himself.
Hatty...
...is there something you can help us
with?
No.
But your husband might have said
something.
No one's opinion was more trusted
than Jack's.
It would mean a lot to us all if we
knew how he felt about the matter.
Speak up, lass.
Jack did tell me about a fight
between Johnny and Red.
Aye, every man saw it.
She doesn't need to account for it.
No, not the fight at the viaduct.
They fought another time as well.
It was down at the river,
it ended with Red pulling a knife.
Jack had no option but to fire him.
Red vowed to pay Johnny out.
Well, happen Johnny got there first!
No, I'm not saying there was any kind of
vendetta between them, I'm not saying that.
I can't deny there were bad blood.
Jack did the right thing banishing
Red.
And Red paid him out with that
explosion.
I say Red Killeen got what he
deserved!
Dead and buried in an unmarked
grave! I'm glad of it!
Me mam don't let us play cards in
t'house.
Me and me dad used to but she
stopped us.
Oh, yeah? Why's that, then?
She said it were a game for cheats
and drunks.
Hey, your bet were on t'other card
before.
Happen your mam was right.
You're getting there. It only took two
rounds before you noticed this time.
How long do you reckon they're gonna
be?
You're fond of Johnny, then?
Well, aye.
Then there's Johnny's feud with his
brother.
And the reason he hid his name.
Who's to say that Johnny
didn't cause that explosion...
...trying to sabotage his brother's
business?
Is this the fair hearing that you
promised me?
You set me up from the start.
What more do we need to hear?
Johnny had cause. He has a history of
violence, he's got a history of lying.
So what are we gonna do with the
guilty man?
We've no prison.
We banish him across our borders,
he walks away a free man.
Call for the magistrate!
As far as I can see...
...there is only one solution.
Take that, you dirty scum!
Leave him alone! Don't touch him!
Everybody, step back!
Mr Coates, sir.
- What about the tin?
- What's that?
The one you took from Red's corpse.
You said it was evidence.
Evidence that's not gonna help him.
That tin had money in and it ended up in
your pocket. I heard how you spent it.
It was a pretty girl, huh?
Don't let anything happen to him.
I need to go to the Blackwood house,
Mr Blackwood needs to know what's happening.
I'm begging you,
don't let them touch him.
Come on!
You have to come, Mr Blackwood!
It's John, he's in bad trouble.
The shanty folk are taking justice
into their own hands.
At least, they're about to.
what about the magistrate?
Mr Coates, he didn't send for him!
Some of the men are talking vengeance
and demanding that Johnny pay in kind.
I think they might hang him.
Oh, Lord, have mercy.
Got you.
You need to do it with more
confidence.
I could see your hand shaking.
I've got my work cut out with you.
What's going on?
Your mam told me to tell you to go
with Polly.
Says it's important.
You've all heard about the violent
altercation between Johnny and Red.
He hasn't denied it, to his credit.
But what about his movements
around the time Red was murdered?
Annie Quaintain?
You're best placed to help us with
that.
Hold on tight, George.
You ever driven an horse before?
We're going too fast!
By heck!
George, love, what are you doing?
Sit down before you fall down!
I need to get off.
Whoa!
Whoa, Bessie!
I need to go back there!
George, love, what's the matter all
of a sudden?
George!
You're quite fond of Johnny,
Miss Quaintain?
I don't see how my opinion on him
has any bearing here, Mr Coates.
The two of you are close,
we all know that.
He's a good man.
Are you two close enough to conceal
a crime, perhaps?
He's no crime to conceal.
Of course he has! She knows more
than she's letting on!
And you have no idea who took that
blanket?
No.
There wasn't one fella in particular who
complained about being cold that night?
Hey, that's enough! Leave her be!
Cheap jibes won't get you any closer
to the truth, Mr Coates.
You and Johnny are close.
Is that why I can't see a wedding
ring on your finger?
Or is it because you and the man
who stands here are lovers?
Do you two share a lovers' secret,
a secret that you would do anything
to conceal?
Tell the truth, woman!
You're right, Mr Coates!
We do have a secret.
Johnny and I are lovers.
Oh, now we're getting
somewhere!
See, ladies and gentlemen,
what I've been telling you?
And we were together... alone...
the night that Red Killeen was
murdered.
That's how I know he has no crime to
conceal.
So, no, I don't wear my wedding ring
any more. I don't even know where it is!
So you want us to believe
that you were in a deep clinch,
a passionate embrace with this man,
the moment that Red Killeen
was being murdered?
Yes, I do, because it's true!
You want us to believe that while
you stand here in your mourning clothes?
Who are you, Annie? Huh?
The grieving widow who's struggling
to protect her children,
or a woman who just throws
her wedding ring away
so that she can
lay with a handsome young navvy,
just moments after the tragic death
of two of his friends?
Mr Coates! Mr Coates!
I reckon I can tell you
t'whereabouts of that wedding ring.
She sold it me...
in return for taking her to Settle.
She were going after her boy.
He'd run away.
It's in a shop there.
I pawned it.
Why was her lad running away?
Happen he knows summat.
George Quaintain, where is he?
No, no!
No, you don't need the boy.
You don't need George.
You can't put a boy on the stand,
it ain't fair.
Oh, look who's turned up to save the
day!
Just in time, Mr Blackwood, just in
time to witness Jericho justice.
You can't create a monster
and then expect it not to roar!
You're to tell me how you did it,
exactly.
They're like a pack of animals.
Mam is taking a hiding in there, so
you're to tell me so I can help her.
And you.
George!
I just wanted to get away from him.
He had me trapped on t'scaffold.
I took this tanner's knife...
just to protect myself with.
To scare him off.
I didn't mean to cut him.
You're to go home.
Go home and stay there.
No... Johnny.
He'll get blamed for it, they'll
hang him. It's my doing.
It's all right.
Trust me, I know what to do.
Please just go.
Hey!
You've got to do something!
I'm not sure I can. They're not gonna let me
just walk Johnny out of here. There'll be a riot!
I've something to say.
Johnny Blackwood is guilty,
I know so.
Johnny killed Red.
There were a fight between him and
Johnny up on t'scaffold.
Johnny cut Red with a tanner's blade.
There was a weapon buried next to
the body.
A tanner's blade.
- She's right!
- A tanner's blade! What do you say to that?
- George.
- Where is he?
George!
George.
- Get that boy down!
- Martha is lying.
Get down, George!
She's just trying to protect
me!
Johnny Blackwood's innocent.
I killed Red Killeen.
Let the boy speak!
Look, I had no intention of hurting
him!
No reason to!
But he chased me up t'scaffold.
I grabbed t'tanner's blade
to protect meself with, that's all.
I nicked him once on t'neck
when I were trying to fight him off.
Then... he fell back off t'scaffold.
It were him or me.
Look, Johnny did nothing wrong.
He were just trying to help me and
me mam.
But it were wrong.
Wrong of me to let him.
Wrong of me not to own up.
Cos when a man's at fault,
he should face t'consequences.
Why was Red so set on killing you?
What had passed between you?
I knew what he'd done.
I saw him stealing from t'explosives
hut.
Red caused the explosion.
He killed Skinny and Jack.
Calm down, everybody.
Quieten down.
I think it's time to release me.
- Annie, bring the boy up.
- No...
He's confessed like a man,
let him face the consequences.
George is just a boy!
George Quaintain has...
bravely admitted the killing of Red.
It were an accident!
Now it's up to us to decide his
fate.
You can't do owt to him, Mr Coates.
Let the boy be, Mr Coates.
What say you, Mr Blackwood?
Surely he was doing all he could
to save himself.
- Aye.
- He was that.
It'll be my recommendation to the magistrate
that Red Killeen's death was accidental.
Red Killeen murdered one of ours.
And he's not here today to talk
about that.
But some might say that today,
justice was done.
We'll shake on it, Mr Coates.
Come on, son.
You kept your cards close to your
chest.
I am so proud of you, Davey Sharpe.
You were summat else today.
What were you doing out walking so
late to overhear what you did?
Like I said, I were taking a moment
for meself.
I couldn't sleep.
I were thinking of you.
It's as though this trouble...
all this hurt caused for George,
Johnny, Annie...
...all started with lies.
Folk being afraid of telling the
truth.
- I don't want to live like that.
- You won't have to.
Not if you're with me.
Not once we're married.
Let's set a date, Davey.
Make me an honest woman.
Charles, wait.
Words can't express our relief,
John.
Will you not stay for a drink?
Toast my freedom and George's.
I don't think so.
Home, Easter, if you please.
Oh, come on, Charles, why not?
There's been more than one secret
unearthed here in the past two days.
I know what happened between you.
Oh, Charles, I...
It was a long time ago.
I'm so sorry.
Drive on.
Aye, you best run like a rat.
You've got no place here.
You'll be seeing me again,
Dagger Wilkins.
I ain't finished here.
Why didn't you tell me what had happened
instead of lying to me all this time?
- Didn't you trust me?
- I couldn't put you through it, Martha.
The lies, the fear...
Look, it's over now.
We can start again.
No more secrets.
Come on.
What was it you once said to me?
You'd either see a stallion drive
another from the herd.
You've been desperate to get rid of me
since we first clapped eyes on each other.
I had to give this town its justice.
And serve yourself into the bargain.
You've got a week to work out your
notice.
And then I want you gone.