It's time for you to come home.
I'm staying here.
Mr Coates needs me.
- This is about your dad.
- He left us with nothing.
George killed a man.
We have to bury the body.
We'll take him up onto the moors.
It's the only way.
It seems whatever I do,
my life gets tangled up with yours.
- Is that so terrible?
- It's not what I had planned.
- What's that there on your skin?
- An injustice.
Shanty folk don't want me.
Not me family neither.
Coates has been asking questions.
Wants to know all about you.
This is my estate.
You're on my land.
Charles needs your help.
He needs you
to bequeath Blackwood House
to him in its entirety.
- Beg him to sign the deeds away.
- I'm not going on my knees to him.
I offered you my help, Charles,
and you threw it back in my face.
All you've done is bring this town
one day nearer to disaster.
Pay day, lads!
Look at him.
Fast as muck off a shovel.
With nothin' but a taste for ale
on his lips.
- Pay day. What do you expect?
- Whatever's not thrown down his neck
- will end up in Polly's purse.
- Aye. She's set to retire on wages
Dagger puts her way.
It's from my uncle.
He's still refusing to help us.
There's no money, Charles.
I'm sorry, it's not much
of a business partnership.
Whatever happens,
we'll get through it together.
We can't pay the men their wages.
You have to go and tell Mr Coates.
I miss you.
The place is quiet without you.
It's not been right peaceful down
at Steam Truck.
And Martha.
Reckons she's got double the chores.
I could come back, help her out.
It's only right.
Can move back in tonight...
if you'd like.
We're content enough here,
aren't we?
Though it's the last place
I'd have thought to bring you.
- I'll come back with the others.
- No, you're all right.
Best get fed before rush.
How is it?
What's keepin' Coates?
Ale isn't going to sup itself.
A slight administrative oversight,
that's all,
but resolved easily enough.
The men won't take kindly
to late wages.
A simple explanation
is all it takes, Mr Coates.
I think it's best
they hear that from you.
- Thank you all for your patience.
- What choice?
- Aye.
- As you might be aware...
What I mean is that...
certain issues have arisen and...
- Speak up, man!
- Enough.
Certain issues have arisen
which will lead to a delay
in wages being paid.
Just for today, that's all.
Just a day... or so.
But I can assure you
that it is temporary
and will be rectified
as soon as possible.
It's no use looking to me.
- I know as much as all you do.
- So you'd say?
- If you knew something?
- Aye.
But I don't. Trust me.
Like we're supposed to trust
your brother?
Dagger.
We're good for the money, as soon
as Blackwood gives us what's owed.
- Only those with cash.
- But none of us have been paid.
Well, I'm sorry,
but we're not runnin' this place
- for the good of our health.
- Oh, come on, Lizzie.
Your Joe is happy
to slip some a beer.
Joe Capstick,
are you givin' away free drink?
We can't deny the men their ale.
There'd be a riot.
Perhaps that's what's needed.
If Blackwood is green enough
to think all's well without wages.
Read what it says.
Well, what's it say, then?
'No money no ale'.
It's house rules.
This isn't right. None of us
should have to suffer this.
I kept them all out for you,
exactly as you left them.
You know, I remember
when he give me it, my dad.
I've been thinking about him
a lot recently.
I ought to be getting on.
What's the matter?
Are you not in any hurry, then?
Maybe we could just talk some.
It's been a tough day.
I worked on the rail road
for 30 years across America.
Civil war came
and I fought for the North.
My regiment was blown apart
at the Battle of Bull Run.
I escaped.
Tried to make my way back home.
Went renegade.
Burned my uniform.
Somethin' happened.
I was mistaken for a runaway slave.
They captured me,
put me to work on a plantation.
Branded me there.
I swore then
I would never be made a slave again
by any man.
The plantations
had their own way of working.
There's this great divide
between the masters and the men.
I never trust a man
who tries to straddle both worlds.
They make out they're on your side,
but they're only out for themselves.
Something about Johnny Blackwood
has always made me feel uneasy.
And ever since I heard him say
he owns this estate,
I reckon he wants to be master here.
'And the bride and groom are
expecting to take up residence
in their new home after
a short honeymoon in the Highlands'.
Did you hear that, Davey?
A brand new house.
Oh, can you imagine that?
A scullery, your own privy...
I'd like that
when we get a place of us own.
Why waste money on a place
for ourselves
- when there's room enough here?
- It's time to behave
like you've got expectations.
Moving up like you deserve.
Who knows where it might take us?
- Nowhere. We're going nowhere.
- I beg your pardon?
How long do you think viaduct
is going to take?
There's work here
for a good few years.
Years?
You want me to live on the edge
of a bog-soaked moor for years?
Why flit elsewhere when
there's regular wages to be had?
Wages? Nobody's had any wages.
- That's what all this upset has been.
- Exactly.
Why pay rent for elsewhere
with money we don't have?
Martha,
I doubt there's a need, love.
But there's there's kegs
to get ready and glasses to wash.
I know, love, but situation's bad.
We can't afford to pay for a shift
this evening
if men aren't spending on ale.
Aye. We'll give you a shout
the minute owt changes.
The men aren't happy.
They've rent to pay, food to buy.
They work, are paid,
money gets spent, then skint again.
Week in, week out. No savings.
So a delay in wages
might seem nothing to you,
but to folk down here,
- it's everything.
- I built this place from nothing.
You dare to stand there
and tell me how to manage things?
You think 'manage'
is what you're doing?
The whole place can see
what a crisis you're in.
Money will be here in a day or two.
We both know
that's not entirely true, is it?
No work tomorrow onwards
till wages are paid.
We're not doing owt
till our pockets are filled.
What's the use
in making matters worse?
- There's no need for this.
- Wages will be here soon enough.
Mr Blackwood won't let you down.
He's right.
You have my word on this.
And how much is that worth to you?
Cos it equals nowt to us.
Till there are coins in the palm
of my hand, no graft gets done.
No man lifts a finger!
It's only a day or so
before the money comes good,
isn't that right?
In the meantime...
I'll work with you.
Come back!
I'm ordering you.
What about your loyalty, huh?
Is it to these men
or to your family, as a Blackwood?
Your biggest fear realised,
Charles.
A Blackwood folly.
And I don't say
that to humiliate you,
but to encourage you.
Take Johnny's money from the house
and let him stay in the valley
as long as he wants.
He doesn't need to be part
of our lives up here.
Mr Coates is here to see you.
Have the men decided
to go back to work?
No. And not likely, I'm afraid.
But there may be a way through this.
Navvies work hard,
then march on their stomachs
from the scaffold to the tavern.
That all comes to a halt
without money in their pockets.
If you're here just to repeat
my brother's words...
Your word isn't good enough.
It's gonna take
some kind of guarantee.
Written, not spoken.
Charles?
What do you have in mind?
- We're just after our money.
- All right. - Calm down.
- Step back.
- Stay back.
For those men who are willing
to work, I have these.
Guarantees. Each docket
initialled and stamped by me.
Currency until wages are paid.
It's nowt but scraps of paper.
They're as good
as any coins in your hand.
Which can be exchanged
for goods and services.
Food, beverage, rent.
And I assure you, this is temporary.
And as extra good will on my part,
a bonus next pay day.
Line 'em up, Davey.
Mr McCleod. Shall we get started?
There's about three good land sites
from where you could quarry
the stone to build your viaduct.
It's... er... not going to be cheap,
but will save you in the long term.
You left that in the steam truck.
Thought you might be missing it.
It must be nice to be back here.
You mind if I have a word
with your ma in private?
So, it seems like
he's reconciled with you.
- It appears so.
- Come around to you and Johnny, huh?
We're not together.
He doesn't even live here.
Have you ever asked Johnny
how old he is?
I reckon he's not yet
two score years.
He is the older brother,
that's plain as day.
Is that why you came here?
To quiz me about him?
It is, isn't it?
Charlie Blackwood,
he ain't got no money
and that's why we're all
in the mess we're in right now.
I reckon
he thought he had a fortune,
but then his brother rolled back
into town
claiming that this is all his land.
You think Johnny's planning
on being the master here?
Thank you for stopping by,
Mr Coates.
Good day to you.
Good day, ma'am.
- Annie, don't accept these.
- What?
There's no value to 'em.
You'll get no money to back 'em up.
My brother's word counts
for nothing.
The whole town is thick with them.
They're the only reason
work carries on at all.
- Johnny, you have to tell people.
- What, and let all hell loose?
Johnny, if you want folk
to think you're on their side,
you've no choice.
Listen.
These are worth nothing here
or anywhere else.
I knew it!
Let's go and see Blackwood.
I've seen a few places in my time.
China, South America...
Well, welcome to Yorkshire.
- Can't promise anything exotic.
- Oh, I don't know.
Just scores of grubby navvies.
You'll soon have scores more.
I'm here to plan the quarry
for the other side of the viaduct.
Mmm. Pa will be pleased.
More thirsty workers
to fill his pockets.
Pretty face
and a publican for a father?
This town's looking up already.
Actually,
I'm looking for a room to rent.
We're not usually in the business
for accommodation...
...but exceptions can be made.
Mr McCleod here
is looking for a room to rent.
- You must be Alma's sister.
- Oh, that line's old as the moors
and I've twice the wits she has.
If it's a room you're after,
a shillin' a night.
Two up front in case of breakages.
And eyes off my daughter,
else her intended
might have summat to say.
- What's happened to you?
- Blackwood's dockets.
The word is we won't see a penny
off the back of them.
What's... er...
- What's that all about?
- Just something and nothing.
You're a liar, Mr Blackwood!
The shop won't take 'em,
the canteen or the tavern
- because they're worthless.
- I don't understand.
Your brother told us you don't have
the money to honour 'em.
Please. I understand the confusion -
You've given us nowt
but a dead promise.
He's made right fools of us.
Are we to be left without jobs?
What are we supposed to do?
- So what now, Mr Blackwood?
- Clear out the way, please!
Leave here
with not a care for the rest of us?
- I'm sorry.
- Sorry's not good enough!
- There's no use in this trouble.
- And there's no use defending him.
Is there no work for you
at Capsticks?
I don't know
how we're going to manage.
Same as we always have.
We'll get by, the three of us.
George?
What's this doing here?
I took it from fireplace
when I ran back t'house that time.
We never speak of him no more.
You know why I don't say anything.
Cos you hate him.
- Cos he left us wi' nothin'.
- George.
It's because I don't want
to say unkind things about him.
Things that might hurt you.
Easter, I know Charles
doesn't have a penny left.
The guarantees,
they're nothing but scraps of paper.
What choice did he have? He's
fighting for this place on his own.
Something your father
never intended.
He wanted you back here
alongside your brother.
Have you ever been to his grave?
This land is in your bones.
All he wanted
was his family back together.
So do what you need to do
to make that happen.
Folk have no idea what's going on.
Best to sit tight.
But you would tell me, would you,
if I had to do otherwise?
No point in losing our heads.
Most are saying
Blackwoods are bankrupt.
I wouldn't bet on that.
Not until each of them
has declared their hand.
You've done your best.
You've shown the men
you're on their side.
- There's nothing else you can do.
- There is.
This whole estate,
the viaduct and the land,
was left to me in my father's will.
But it's debt-ridden.
There's not a penny left.
I didn't know until recently
because my brother took it.
But it's now worth nothing.
So that's it?
This whole town
is to pack up and move on?
There's the family house.
If I borrow money against that,
we can pay the men.
It might give Jericho a chance
at least.
Well, then do it.
It's what my father
would have expected.
It seems you can't fight
who you really are.
When you told me
you were a Blackwood,
I knew this day would come.
This doesn't have to change things.
With the best will in the world,
Johnny, it does.
If you go through with this,
it'll separate you
from the rest of the men.
You can't drink with them
at the tavern
or wash alongside at the river
because you'll be in charge.
And what about us?
Annie.
I rent bunks to navvies and
I sell stew from the back of a hut.
It's a world away from
what you're walking back into.
Then I won't do it.
Not if it means that me and you -
And sacrifice people's homes
and livelihoods? No.
It's the right thing to do.
We both know it.
Go.
Tell people
you'll find a way out of this.
But this could be our chance.
No.
Go forward in this together
and we can put the past behind us.
Agree to my partnership
and everything that
you've worked for can be saved.
And I'm supposed to be grateful
for that?
Welcome your offer with open arms?
It's what our father
would have wanted.
It's what he intended.
It's my home as well as yours.
Since when did that mean anything
to you?
This is the only way
to do what's right by folk.
- As far as you're concerned.
- No, it's a fact.
Because if you don't, there's
nothing to stop me taking over.
- You wouldn't.
- What choice do you leave me?
None.
- Not if you still want some control.
- Charles, look.
Johnny as a part of this
was something we never discussed.
- Charles.
- Don't you think I understand that?
But if we do as he asks, all of
our immediate problems are solved.
Doesn't that count for something?
It'll buy time for us.
There's nowt of value left in this
tommy shop except muck and timber.
I've nothin'
but the clothes on my back.
Blackwood should pay for this.
It's time we take what's ours.
Could help you move them to bed
if you want.
Ah, best leave them be.
All chaos outside
and they take refuge in a bottle.
Imagine mess if we did same.
Asleep. Dribblin' like a baby.
You could do worse, love.
And that's the best to hope for,
is it?
He loves you, Alma.
He can't believe his luck.
In't that enough?
Trouble is, life can't be
all lightning in a bottle.
Sometimes you just have to make do.
Here, we'll take everything
from Blackwood's house.
No. It... It isn't right.
- Thieving's not the way to go.
- He's stolen from us.
We're only takin' a share
of what's rightfully ours.
Look, I could lend some money.
To see you move on.
- We could go together.
- Got enough for the rest of us?
I couldn't take your money.
And Blackwood's gettin'
no more than he deserves.
Well, I'm sorry.
I can't have no part in it.
A word to anyone about this
and I'll slice you open.
- How many of them?
- Five. Six, maybe.
- Dagger included.
- We have to stop them.
No. Stay out of it, Annie.
Hawker had a knife.
I'd like to believe all of this
was for the benefit of your brother.
- It is.
- And you get something in return.
Well, that's only fair.
What isn't is taking what's mine
and asking me to disappear again.
If you did,
I'd see you weren't left penniless.
You can't honestly believe
that you becoming part
of this venture is a good idea.
Why not?
You forget everything
that went on between us?
Listen, there's nothing
to be gained from bringing that up.
It was one night together years ago.
One night?
We talked about running away.
Isabella, we were younger.
Foolish.
Yes, I was...
to believe anything you had to say.
Why should I now?
Because I'm a different person.
And from where I'm standing,
so are you.
If we leave right now,
we can try and warn them.
- We can't just do nothing.
- So you come to me for help, huh?
- I'd thought you'd go get Johnny.
- He's already at the house.
Trying to solve this mess.
So it's true.
I was right about him all along.
He is in danger, Mr Coates,
and one of the men had a knife.
You expect a toast?
There's no harm in doing something
to mark our new business situation.
One based on a threat.
Charles,
take out the past ten years,
was it really so bad between us?
There's nothing to stop us
making this work.
Dagger, you go first.
- What are you waiting for?
- Maybe Sam was right.
Happen this isn't the way to go.
No, I'm not a thief.
I never have been, so...
We are not leaving here
empty-handed.
We'll hurt them if we have to.
Where are you lot going?
Argh!
No! Please, please, no!
No, no, no! I don't mean any harm.
It was...
It wasn't my idea to come here.
Mr Blackwood, sir.
- What's going on, Dagger?
- I never meant any of this, Johnny.
We just wanted what was owed.
Isabella!
This is nowt to do wi' you, Prince.
It's your brother
- we've got grievance with.
- We're family.
You make trouble for him,
it's with me too.
Thought as much. Blood thicker
than water. No worry to us.
If you harm her - - Back off!
It's over, Hawker! It's just us two
making trouble for ourselves.
I'll cut you up, Prince.
I should have done this
first time I clapped eyes on you.
- Johnny!
- Hawker, don't be a fool.
- I'll be out of here soon enough.
- You think it ends there?
One word to the law,
they'll track you down.
- Back off!
- Hawker, please.
- Annie.
- I understand your frustration,
but don't make one mistake
on top of another.
It'll live with you.
A death on your conscience,
day after day
for the rest of your life.
I'm all right.
Don't you look nice.
Girl does her best
with what she's got.
The only thing a man can do
when a girl looks at him like that.
Once the men are paid
and the others are punished,
hopefully this is the end
of any unrest.
I can do that... if you've
other business to take care of.
It's usually Coates
who takes care of the wages.
I'm sure Mr Blackwood
is more than up to the task.
Coates, we should find Mr McCleod.
I'd like to continue
with his thoughts on the quarry.
I'll need a moment
with Mr Coates first.
Bring your keys.
I meant no harm.
One thing led to another.
I never intended...
There's no use you being here.
Go on.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Let him go.
Your brother agreed
they should be punished.
It's his lies
over the money that led to this.
Then I'll get authority
from your brother.
You have mine.
You need to make room for me.
We start with this, understand?
A knife held to my throat
isn't something I easily forget.
There's no place for you here
any more.
Your father...
used to take you on walks.
He'd have Martha by the hand
and you up on his shoulders.
All the way up to Castleberg Crag.
Oh, he could turn a Sunday walk
through the Dales
into a right adventure.
Do you remember?
He once made a den out of sticks
and he called it a castle.
I don't want you to lose
those precious memories...
...but there's all sorts of things
about him that you don't know.
And if you really want
to learn the truth,
then there's some things
you should hear.
Now,
you know he gambled away our money.
- I couldn't stop him.
- Aye, whole village knew about that.
Well, he was very unhappy.
He had mountains of debt.
They say that...
he threw himself
off Castleberg Crag.
I thought you didn't know.
Lads at school
used to talk about it.
I never believed them.
Oh, George, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
My boy.
I can't understand
why he did what he did.
I know, love.
There's no explaining it.
But he loved you more than anything.
Don't ever doubt that.
So, Johnny Blackwood, eh?
He seems like a decent man.
I know that he likes you.
It'd be nice to see you smile again.
You giving me permission
to take up with him, are you?
Mr Coates, the Blackwoods are
grateful to you for helping us.
Is that so?
Because from where I stand,
I'm nothing but a stooge
between brothers
and no man
should have to tolerate that.
Charging up to the house like that.
I don't know if it makes you
the bravest woman I know...
or the most stupid.
Bit of both?
Reckon you need somewhere to stay.
You offering me bed and board again,
Annie Quaintain?
There's things
we need to talk about.
It's not your business.
Charles still doesn't know
about you and Johnny.
Wouldn't want anything
to come between them again.
You might be married to Charlie now,
but you are the reason
that John left in the first place.
It's ancient history.
But with John back around the table,
matters you think dead and buried
when he left
might still cause upset.
Charles will hear nothing from me.
I trust you to do the same.
Three options for your quarry.
All require expensive excavation.
The best and the cheapest access
site to quarry the stone is...
...over there.