Did you buy them an' all?
Go get 'em, will you?
They're in that back room.
- Let's be done with this.
- All right.
Get a move on here!
- Why's this down here?
- How much did you say was for the book down here?
- Fetch us an extra one for a cart sale.
- Are they from upstairs?
Just a couple of chairs.
I think so, aye.
- I've got it.
- There's nowhere else to put it.
Excuse me, would ya?
There's a poorhouse in Settle.
They'll take your children.
I'm not being parted from them.
I think you'd better talk to him.
This house isn't ours, not anymore.
It's just a house.
We'll be together.
I can't stand everyone
knowing, that's all.
We're going to walk out of
here with our heads held high.
Come on.
Worth a shilling, maybe.
Sold everything to pay his debts.
You said we could come to you.
I'm sorry, Annie,
I've been sick of late.
That's fine.
Forget I came here.
Ma'am...
.. what's going on?
Annie?
I'm sorry.
We need somewhere we can go,
somewhere I can at least earn a
wage. It'll get dark in a few hours.
- (We can't sleep out on the streets.)
- There's jobs going, Culverdale railway.
They're building a great bridge out there.
- That's 15 miles.
- I'll find a train that'll take you.
Where are we headed?
An adventure.
- Why have we stopped?
- You have to change trains.
It's the end of the line. There's
a different railway yonder.
All change! This is the end of the line.
Connecting train across the valley.
All change, please!
Here.
- Take my hand.
- Thank you.
- Here. The steps... Ooh!
- We're headed for Culverdale.
- It's this valley right here.
Here, let me help you, lad.
There we are.
- No, there's no need to carry our things.
- It's no bother, ma'am.
Happen if you don't want to talk to
me I can walk a little way in front.
- Step down here.
- Steady.
I suppose this is where we
part. I'm walking further west.
You should head over that ridge.
- Good luck to you and your family.
- Thank you for your help.
Happen I'll come to call
when you get settled.
I look forward to all
the lively conversation.
It's the ends of the earth.
See you later.
Go left a bit. No, no, no,
come back to the right.
That's it, that's great.
That's great. Look at that.
Oh, it should be an
"S". There's two of us.
- Capsticks.
- It's beer they want, woman, not a grammar lesson.
Ned Shaw, I'm the engineer.
You all work for me now.
I pay a fair wage for a fair day's work.
Put your mark in the book,
you'll be assigned a work gang.
Your bunting's in the dirt, my fine lady.
How about a smile?
Everything's barter here. A
smile for my arm, a fair trade.
- Can you tell me where there's work to be had?
- Boss's office over yonder.
- How about a kiss instead, then?
- How about I smack you with this suitcase?
Shaw & Blackwood pay
me to look after t'men.
Make sure they're fed,
they've got a roof over them.
They're mostly villains,
rough ends.
You don't belong here.
Nowhere else to go?
What are you going to do to earn
a living out here on t'moors?
I don't yet know.
I just need a place of my own.
Are those for rent, those huts?
I need somewhere to sleep tonight.
Forty shillings a week,
it beds enough for six.
Is there anywhere cheaper, perhaps?
You could take in lodgers,
no shortage of men here.
I'll give you two days' grace
on rent to set yourself up.
Who are you, then?
Ralph Coates, the new foreman.
Hired to work the next mile of the
branch line, east of the valley.
I learnt my trade on the
Baltimore-Ohio Railway.
Joseph Thornhill.
This here minor track's
mine. I'm the agent.
Senior foreman here on the viaduct build.
Nice berth you've got. Can you
tell me where I can bunk down?
The flophouse is cheapest, across the way.
If you're staying, you'd
better go with this gentleman.
There's a vacant hut round
the back of the flophouse.
All right?
Good day.
How long since he died?
Your husband?
Who told you that?
I'm a railway foreman, ma'am.
Two things I make my business.
The railways... and the
folks that work 'em.
Excuse me asking, where's the line?
- Have you just arrived in town?
- I rode in on the goods train.
I'm Johnny Jackson.
I'm looking for work.
Look for the office that says
Shaw & Blackwood. Ask there.
- I'm obliged to you.
- Aye, manners.
Never heard the like.
There's a space on my gang, Your Highness.
George, have you got ink and paper?
We need to make more than just the rent.
We need to buy our way back home again.
- Come on, George.
- Mornin'.
I bought you some rations.
- I can't possibly take your food.
- I can.
George?
Every mouthful a banquet.
There's really no need, sir.
We're just on our way to market.
Ma'am, you can't survive without
a favour every now and then.
Maybe someday you can pay me back again.
Thank you.
I did my best with what I could find.
I married you for your
kissing, not your sandwiches.
I have a theory about navvy boys.
Born fighters. In their nature.
But if you're on my gang, the
only thing you'll be fighting
- is that bedrock. Do you hear me, navvy?
- Aye.
- Tiger?
- Aye, Jack.
- Davie Boy?
- Walker?
- Aye, Jack.
- Shay?
- Aye, Jack. - Red? - Aye, Jack.
- Skinny?
- Aye, Jack. - And what do I call you?
His Royal Highness The Prince.
All right, let's get
some work done. Come on.
The London line ends there, and
then the Midland line begins.
Two networks, two locomotives.
And just your estate
between them, eh, Blackwood?
And that spells opportunity. Yes, sir.
A viaduct linking the networks,
making this country one nation.
And you need money to finish it,
hence this rather fine luncheon.
What would your father have thought
about all these... squatters on his land?
He traded in sugar. Sugar's the past,
railways are our future.
Ah, see, here's Mr Shaw, the engineer.
- We set up this venture together.
- So, how are you faring?
It's going to take some persuasion
before they open their wallets.
- Gentlemen. - Mr Shaw. - Mr
Shaw. - How are you doing?
- Away!
- Clear!
Drag it back now and stow it tight.
Take that with powder tomorrow.
It saves the digging of a hundred men.
Aye.
Who let that thing off its pegs?!
- That new man, he were careless.
- It wasn't me.
- I saw you.
- You couldn't see nothing with so much drink inside you.
Whoa, whoa!
- The Prince is a boxer as well, look.
- Red, you lose a day's clink.
Now move yourselves!
Right.
Someone's been in that bag and
they've taken half my things.
Must've happened when we
left the bags outside.
- I hate this place. Why have we come here?
- Hey, don't say that.
At least we've got a roof
... and we're together.
So we've really gotta stay in this crate,
side by side with a bunch of strangers?
Look, this here's the parlour.
The kitchen and the scullery
are over in the west wing.
- What about the billiard room?
- Of course.
Every respectable family
needs to entertain.
Over here we can have the music room.
A grand piano for when we
have recitals in the evening.
Oh, out there is the kitchen/garden,
with formal lawns leading down
to a tennis court. Is that
grand enough for you, Duchess?
You're mad sometimes.
Wherever you two lay your heads,
that's my dream home.
And if it all goes to plan,
I think we can promise you
a very healthy return on your investments.
Oh, I have absolute confidence.
Gentlemen.
- So sorry to keep you.
- My niece, Miss Lambton.
Let me introduce you.
Mr Shaw, the engineer.
Ma'am.
And you know his partner,
of course, Mr Blackwood.
Hello, Charles.
Please, gentlemen, don't
let me disturb you.
Another chair, please, Easter.
I'm glad you can join us, Miss Lambton.
I'm very glad to be here.
She asked if she could come.
Sorry, I should've warned you.
- Charles or myself will be more than happy to answer that.
- It's an extraordinary venture.
Come here!
Look at all them fine things she owns.
- Don't gawp.
- All my good clothes were taken, Ma.
Oi. Don't forget them boots, will ya?
Cheers, Polly. See you next payday.
- I like your lace.
- Thank you.
It's pretty, in't it?
Hey, go on.
Have you just moved in?
Lace Polly they call me.
Annie.
I'd... best get on.
So where are you from, Skinny?
I live down Plymouth way.
Daughter, too. Three years in September.
How can you stand to be away?
I just go when the work whistles.
Send back all the spare money I have.
Better than a shipyard, this.
No-one to tell you how to live.
What about you, then? You don't
talk about yourself much, do you?
Aargh!
- Argh!
- You men!
Argh! Argh!
Get your pack. I don't want to
see you this side of the mountain.
You're a dead man,
Prince, I swear you are!
We need to find new lodgings
- before we wake up with our throats cut.
- Yeah.
Your sign says lodgings.
It's 14 shillings a week.
You get three meals,
a mattress and your laundry.
Start on about kissing me again,
I will kick you out of doors.
We've already had the pleasure.
I said I'd come to call
when you got settled.
So...
.. here I am.
What are you doing, boy?
Just getting firewood.
You ain't seen me.
Do you hear?
Oh.
- Which part of the track are you working on, then?
- Your side.
Not as grand as here.
Do you get a cut of
what those traders earn?
- Aye, I do.
- Reckon I'm just gonna have to steal your pass then.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Well, this is a banquet.
- A man works harder on hot vittles than he does on cold.
- Mmm.
Right.
Skinny?
Now you're staying here as my
guests, these are my house rules.
The room at the end is
for family, this parlour
- is the only place we meet.
- What do we get in exchange for all these rules?
We're the only lodgings with fine china.
You get to live a cut above the others.
- All right.
- A knife and fork there.
Alma, stop your dreaming,
get out here, help serve.
I've only just got up.
A navvy drinks beer any time of
t'day. If we want to make a living,
it means we're open.
Alma.
- Good morning to ya.
- Morning.
What's the matter? Can't bear
to share the water with me?
I've a daughter.
She's...
I understand.
Don't worry, I won't bother
you for the time of day.
Now you and me, our
linen's the same colour.
The only friends you'll have
around here are the ones you make.
He's telling everyone, boasting about it.
- I never kissed Jackie Blackburn.
- He says you're sweet on him, he brung you presents.
I can't help who dreams about me, can I?
- Why are you following me, Davey?
- I want to talk.
- I mean here, this navvy town.
- You...
You kissed me up in Scarborough.
You don't run halfway around the
world cos someone kisses you.
What's that under your skirt?
Well, Davey, if you don't
know, my kiss were wasted.
No, I mean that lace. Well,
that's what he brung ya?
He saved up half his wages.
- Who are you staring at?
- That petticoat is mine.
- Whoever gave it you, they stole it.
- Alma, give it back.
You lay a finger on me and
I will smack you so hard
your teeth with rattle.
Agh!
You fool, you little fool!
There. Now neither of us can have it.
Uh!
He didn't save up no wages,
your new admirer. He filched it.
I'm afraid they're about to start blasting.
It's not safe to go into the valley today.
- Oh, are we to be prisoners, then?
- You're free to wander my grounds.
- There's good shooting on the moors.
- Perhaps Blackwood can entertain your niece whilst we're gone?
It would be an honour.
Davey boy, get the agent
to give you powder.
Take the new man with you,
show him how it's done.
We need 20 ounces of the black
stuff to shift this bedrock.
I said I'd escort you.
Your uncle's gone off for a few hours.
The prospect delights you, obviously.
You don't need to nursemaid me, Charles.
I wanted to see you. I heard
about your grand scheme.
You didn't think it might be awkward?
I'm sorry.
I thought... things might mend.
It's been eight years.
Perhaps I was wrong.
Perhaps we won't ever be friends.
All men back behind the crow line.
Clear the pit while I plug the fuse.
.. my fine daughter
Step it up, Mary, if you can
Step it up, Mary, my fine daughter
Show your legs to the countryman...
Show your legs to the countryman
There's some powder missing.
A barrel's gone.
Step it up, Mary, my fine daughter
Step it up, Mary, if you can
Step it up, Mary...
Oh, God...
Oh, sweet Jesus, no.
Someone help me!
Help! Get me out of here!
There's gunpowder everywhere!
Please, get me out!
- It's everywhere!
- Jack!
Argh! Aargh! Aargh!
Help them, lads, they're over there.
- Argh! Argh!
- Get down!
- Argh!
Here we are.
He was up at the scaffold when
it happened. Open the door.
We need to bind these
wounds with something.
Here we are, gently. There
we are, there you are.
- I'll be back.
- Where are you going?
There may be others.
I don't know how to tend to it.
Martha, go and find a doctor.
Martha, go and find
someone who can help us!
Has anybody seen my husband?
Anybody seen Jack Laggan?
Davey?
Davey...
I'm sorry. He... wouldn't
have known nothing.
No!
No! Davey...
Jack! Jack...
Jack. Jack!
JAAACK!
- I sent for a doctor.
- There isn't one to be had.
I'll need a spoon.
Have you got flour and
salt to make a poultice?
Go, quickly.
There, there.
Have you seen my lad anywhere?
Sit down there.
Oi!
Hey!
Talk to him, lass.
Say something to make him smile.
You're going to get better.
We're looking out for you.
Mr Blackwood? Sir? Sir?
There's a navvy lad in that
hut, burnt bad in the explosion.
- We need to get him to a
hospital. - Show me. - This way.
Get him up. Pull him down.
- Let me give you something for what you've done for him.
- No, I can't accept nowt, sir.
No, not just for Christian kindness.
Drive on.
I wanted to see Mr Thornhill.
Crawled into a bottle.
He'll be leaving here.
Someone has to answer for this tragedy.
- Remind me, what's your experience?
- Oh.
Thirty years on the railway, sir,
across the northern United States.
I want you to take over in the valley.
Jack Laggan, the ganger who was killed,
- you need to find a man to replace him. Who's his second?
- A young man named Sharpe. Davey Sharpe.
Find him, will you,
Coates, and promote him.
- You're in charge now.
- Why, thank you, sir.
We need more blankets for the wounded.
I'll take them over with the
water as soon as it's boiled.
What are you doing?
Someone ought to write,
he has a wife and child.
Well, won't Mrs Shaw or...
Mr Blackwood see to it?
I don't think those men
care about any of us.
I should go back to the
site and find his pack.
If the worst happens we
have to send her his wages.
Davey Sharpe?
Mr Shaw's looking for a new ganger.
I told you're his man.
It wouldn't be right, sir,
with Jack not even in the earth.
Someone's gotta keep this ship afloat.
Would you rather I gave it to another man?
Well?
I'm in debt to you, sir.
Agh!
- Come 'ere!
- Argh!
Argh!
You saw me take powder out of
yonder blast cart, didn't you?
And you know what powder
does, don't you, boy? Hmm?!
Shh, shh, shh.
Argh!
Come on, come here!
Right!
Argh!
Red was thrown off the gang.
He was trying to pay us back.
George saw him do it,
steal the powder.
- Well, we have to tell the agent.
- Annie, no.
George, wait out the front. Go.
Go on.
Thornhill's a decent man.
- He's been booted out, and there's no law here.
- George was defending himself. - We can't prove it.
George killed a man,
that's all they'll see.
They'll come for him.
God help him if the navvies
take t'law into their own hands.
I don't know what to do.
We have to bury the body.
What?
- No-one will know. Red was ordered to leave here.
- That's insane.
They'll think he just skipped town.
It's the only way.
Why are you helping us?
Because I can.
Because I'm... here.
And you're alone.
Bring a blanket to wrap him in,
and we'll take him up onto the moors.
- (What's he doing?)
- (I don't know.)
Where are we putting him?
They've already dug a grave for
Jack. We'll bury him underneath.
No-one will dig there, ever.
Here.
Turn him over.
What's he doing with all this money?
- That's more than just his wages.
- I reckon someone paid him to do it.
We should bury it with him.
Jack's job?
Ganger's job?
Aye.
The agent come and told me right away.
So,
what do you say?
I say it's high time you
asked me to marry you.
What?
- Do you mean it?
- Yeah, of course I mean it.
I've always been sweet on you, Davey.
W...
I don't want you saying this
just cos I get more wages.
Kiss me.
Make it a proper bargain.
Mr Blackwood has sent me.
The man that got burned
up in that there fire?
You mean Skinny.
He died before we got him to t'doctor.
Mr Charles?
A man died tonight.
Died on the cart,
right in front of me.
The investors, I need
to speak to them myself,
- to reassure them.
- Charlie,
they took a carriage back to town.
They didn't wanna spend the night here.
All right, now.
Here we are.
'And the Lord said to Joshua,
"See, I have given thee rich land
called Jericho into your hands,
with its great king
and its mighty men of valour
who toil there each day."'
I've been thinking today
Of that beautiful land
I shall meet when the sun goes down
At the glorious gates
With my governor I stand
Will there be any stars in my crown?
Will there be any stars,
any stars in my crown?
When at evening the sun goeth down
When I wake with the blessed
In the mansions of rest
Listen here, all of you!
Looks like it was
sabotage killed these men.
The name's Bamford.
I'm a detective.
Mr Blackwood's hired me to investigate.
Anyone knows anything,
you come and tell me.
Tell me what happened with Shaw.
I've just seen him leaving, Charles.
I don't see it's any of your business.
My uncle withdrew all his capital.
The scheme has made him near bankrupt.
Shaw rode over here to
tell you that the viaduct
is finished.
Why did you come back here today?
To tell you that my uncle is a fool.
This viaduct could make you all a fortune.
It's all academic. I've no more to invest.
But I do.
I have an inheritance...
and I want to put it to use.
- You... are not serious?
- I'm offering you a way out of this.
- After everything that's happened between us?
- I have money,
- you have a vision.
- We were going to be married.
This is different,
Charles. This is business.
No,
I'm sorry, no.
You've put every penny
you have into this scheme.
The well is dry, no-one else will
invest in you after this accident.
If you don't take my money, you're ruined.
And he reckons some of
the powder was missing.
That doesn't make much sense, sir.
Mr Thornhill seemed to be the kind of man
to keep that key on him at all times.
No-one could've got
into that gunpowder cart.
Look at that,
the stains on it. Someone's
made a copy of that,
pressed it into some wax or something.
They took it while he slept.
Any of the men missing?
Red Killeen was fired two days ago.
They say he had a score to settle.
He could have had a copy made of that key,
broke into t'cart, stole t'powder.
He'll be on t'road. I'll
run him to ground, I will.
Hey.
Gentlemen... Gentlemen!
I'm Ralph Coates,
and I've been hired to
replace Mr Thornhill.
Now I know you got questions
as to why a Negro from America
has been put in charge over here.
Well, let me tell you.
In this business, it's not about
the colour of a man's skin,
it's about what he knows,
what he's worth.
I've done 30 years on
the rails across America
and I got the papers to prove it.
And I promise you,
you do right by me,
I will do right by you,
and we'll get this job done.
I was a schoolmaster's wife.
I sang to the Lord each Sunday.
My husband, he died,
left us debts.
That's what brought me out here.
I hate you, Johnny Jackson,
for making me do what you did.
Still, I know you saved my son for me.
I reckon I owe you everything.
I've been waiting for you, Mrs Quaintain.
That detective's back. If George
says anything, we're finished.
There's a price to every man's
love. What's yours, son?
I can't watch. It's Johnny.
- He's been ground into t'dirt.
- I am never leaving you,
that promise is unbreakable.
That fella they call The Prince,
there's a secret going on there.
I thought you were leaving tonight,
I thought I'd never see you again.