I'm due an inheritance
now that I'm married.
And money will run out
if we don't act now.
I didn't expect this. I
can't believe he came back.
- Let me in Charles, please.
- What's going on?
Annie, this is my brother.
That fella they call the Prince, I've seen him hangin'
around your ma. I think they might be together.
John James Blackwood.
Deceased. You declared me dead.
You're a puzzle, Prince. I
still can't figure you out.
I can't figure you out myself.
Rest easy. You've got the whole
Blackwood family waiting on you.
He left everything to you and not to me.
My uncle, he only agreed
to my having my inheritance
on the understanding that
you would match the money.
So you're telling me we
haven't got a farthing?
- Why have you been hiding in this valley?
- You're the reason I've stayed here so long.
George!
Hey, up, George.
- George.
- George. - George.
Right, got your shirt, your boots and
the tobacco from the gang, Mr Coates.
- What you doin' here?
- I've come to find you.
- It's time for you to come home.
- No, I'm staying here.
Mr Coates needs me.
Could you give us a moment
alone, please, Mr Coates?
- I'm someone important here.
- You're someone important to me.
When I'm here... I get
treated like I'm a proper man.
Proper wages and everything.
I'm sorry you saw me with Johnny,
but, honestly, it was nothing.
I always lay a place
for you at the table...
.. any time you feel ready.
Stubborn little boy. Just
give him a little time.
No harm if he has to stay a while longer.
I'm grateful, Mr Coates.
But he belongs with me. I'm his mother.
You have a fight with her?
She told me a lie.
She's gone and got herself a new man.
Yeah... you mean the
Prince, Johnny Jackson?
That's not even his real
name. It's Johnny Blackwood.
As far as the world is concerned,
John James Blackwood is a dead man.
The papers are lodged with the
bank. The money can still be ours.
And? When the truth comes to light?
By then, it'll be too late. The money will
be in our hands and the viaduct will be saved.
Do we even know where he's gone?
I suppose he must be back in the valley.
We'll never keep it a secret
amongst the shanty folk.
Charles, the estate is
no longer your property.
You need to go to your brother now.
- Beg him to sign the deeds away.
- I'm not going on my knees to him.
A week from today, there'll
be nothing to pay the workers.
Then we need to find a
saviour... you and I.
No, no, no, no. No more, thank you.
But it'll go to waste. I made too much.
I'm already fit to
burst. - Really? - Aye.
How's your lass getting
on, up at the house?
Oh, fine linen sheets. I expect she'll be sorry to come home.
- Aye.
What about your lad? They say
he's working over at Coates' place.
He should be here with me.
It's just the other side of the street.
It feels like the other
side of the world to me.
Methodist Society. Eager
to save the navvies' souls.
They're having a service today in Jericho.
And what makes you so keen to worship?
Jonas Sorsby is giving the sermon.
For the Lord planted a garden,
and out of the ground
he made his glory shine!
- Praise be to God. Amen.
- Amen.
So how long will the navvy
folk be living here?
Six years, until the work is complete.
Six years shall ye sow the
land and gather in its yield.
Mr Sorsby, I know you to be a
highly successful businessman.
A chain of Drapers' stores. And
two cotton mills in Bradford.
A railway viaduct may be
something of a departure,
but I was wondering whether
you'd be willing to invest in us.
You could buy shares in the promised land.
A ladle taste better than
a silver spoon, does it?
The Quaintain boy told me.
You know, these navvies won't
stomach being made fools of.
It's none of your business.
Why you hanging round
here, hmm? Mr Blackwood?
Your family has money.
What's the deal between
you and your brother?
Mr Coates?
And just how long do you think
you can keep this a secret?
Hello, John.
Hello.
Mistress of Blackwood Estate,
how long's it taken you?
Eight years. How patient you've been.
That's cruel, John. I don't
remember you being cruel.
Eight years... since you left
this place. Walked out on everyone.
And is this the great
future you had planned?
Well, now who's the one being cruel?
You caused a great deal
of pain when you left.
Left a lot of questions unanswered.
Well, it's better that they stay
that way... for the sake of everyone.
I've been able to atone for my mistakes.
It's time that you do it,
too. Charles needs your help.
He needs you to bequeath Blackwood
House to him, in its entirety.
Why didn't he come to me himself?
You already know the answer.
Well, he's welcome to it. I
didn't come here for money.
I came here to pay my
respects to my father.
I need you to come back to the house.
Sign a deed. Make it legal.
You owe him that.
We both owe him.
Just seen your lad about.
Running errands for Coates.
I want him home. I'd rather
he was working with me.
Somehow, I've got to find a way to
stitch this family back together.
- Hey, you! Leave her alone!
- She's a dirty navvy!
My pa said this town ain't worth spit.
Hang on, I know you. I've
seen you in the village.
I'm George Quaintain's
mam. I know your mother.
- What you doing out here, missus?
- This is MY home now.
Go on! There's navvies here
with fists the size of boulders.
Don't be around here when the
siren goes. Go on, quickly!
Imagine coming all this way
on't cart just to gawp and sneer.
What's up with you?
"Home". It's the first time I've said it.
Happen I'm putting roots down here.
What did I tell you? You
are never to come here.
Charles needs my help. He
needs something from me.
As soon as he returns,
I'll be gone from here.
A canteen?
Serving food to the men. Just
to make some money on the side.
You need a licence to trade in this town.
I don't have much money put by.
Well, not so much a
licence, as a nod from me.
Well, I'd be grateful if you'd
nod your head, then... sir.
- Where would you like these?
- Just up against that wall, please.
Thank you.
And that comes in there.
Yeah, put it in by the stove.
- Sir, I need to talk to you.
- Just a moment, Epiphany.
And in here, gentlemen, you can
see a glimpse of our vision.
Bear with me, please, gentlemen.
- May I take your hats?
- Most kind of you.
- You went to him behind my back?
- I'm a partner in this business.
I don't need your permission to act.
I told you, I'm not going to
beg him, not for anything.
Charles, you listen to me!
You're not children fighting over toys.
Gentlemen, would you excuse us just a moment?
- Certainly.
This is what you wanted from me.
Blackwood House, the estate and grounds,
is hereby bequeathed to Charles
Blackwood in its entirety.
And now I want you to leave this valley.
You don't get my freedom into the bargain.
You think you belong down
there, amongst those men?
This valley is my home. I
took my very first breath here.
You're not the master of where I go.
This piece of paper means nothing
to me as I have an investor now.
Gentlemen, so sorry to keep you.
Sorry.
John. Wait... please...
My, my, a restaurant at
the end of our street.
Will erm...
Will folk be expected to dress
for dinner, if they come to call?
Folk can wear what they want,
as long as their money's good.
Hey, what you doing?
What do you think? I'm
giving you a helping hand.
- No, there's no need.
- Don't be daft.
Actually, it'll make a change
to do some work standing.
Come on, then. What's all this about?
George looks up to Coates.
Coates isn't the only one who
can build a little empire.
I'm going to give him a run for his money.
Hold up.
- I think I envy you.
- Oh... - The way you run your show.
Oh. So, are we, er...
Are we becoming friends now, Annie Quaintain?
- It appears so.
- Are you ready?
- Come on, then.
I reckon there's enough
here for... a week... or two.
You say there's more coming soon?
We've got entertainment for tonight...
.. and I reckon it
should be pretty decent.
I've got five extra barrels in,
and I've written a bill of entertainments.
Let's see!
Oh, who's "Quick-Fingered Jack"?
Ah, it's Dagger Wilkins. He
knows a card trick or two.
Who's "The Blooming Rose of Jericho"?
Er...
Alma.
She... She wanted to sing a ditty.
Oh, don't tell me you said yes, Joe.
- Aye.
What you doing, dressed like that?
It's my costume for tonight's show.
Costume? It looks like you've
forgotten to put your frock on.
All the music hall stars
wear this style, look.
What will I call myself?
Every star at the Alhambra's got a name.
What's wrong with Alma?
- I like Alma.
- Oh, Davey... you've no imagination.
I've spent 19 years being dragged
from navvy town to navvy town.
I don't see much excitement.
But tonight... Tonight
is gonna change all that.
Folk heard you talking
to that woman who came.
They're saying as how you're a Blackwood.
I'm the same fella I was before.
A name don't make no difference.
This valley was my home long
before any of you came here!
'Scuse me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Here, here!
Let me help you with that. Don't
you soil your precious hands.
Don't you struggle with it,
sir. Let me take that for you.
I didn't come here to deceive
you, that was never the plan.
I just came here for an honest
day's work, same as any man.
You made us look a right bunch of fools.
He didn't have to try too
hard with you, did he?
You've been arm in arm with
him since he came here.
Oh...
Get in there!
Hit me. If I were any other navvy,
you'd knock me to the ground.
Begging your pardon, sir.
Reckon that was MY fault.
Hey...
We don't want you here.
I'd like you to see the
progress up at the scaffold.
Perhaps later.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
The Blooming Rose of Jericho!
Evening to you.
Navvies like their pleasures,
sir. Hard to deny them.
Mr Sorsby. Sir? Best not stray too far.
Stripping down to tie my garter
Tie is just a little bit, above my knee
If your hand should
slip a little further...
Cleanse your hands, ye sinners.
The triumph of the wicked is short-lived.
And he said...
Mr Blackwood, forgive me. I
cannot agree to be a partner here.
If I'm playing in your garden
Plucking blossoms wet with dew...
There's things here that
make you uneasy, sir?
"Uneasy"?
You've made nothing less
than Sodom and Gomorrah here!
Hey!
The stage is here.
Try to appease him, Charles. We need him.
Mr Sorsby, sir!
I'm determined we should
do business together.
Well, you'll need to clean
up this town, then, sir.
Before I'm back tomorrow.
Afraid I don't have
sixpence. Just a penny.
- Is there... owt I can do?
- You pay me what you can afford.
As long as I hear something
rattle, that'll do.
All the while he's living here,
he's not who he's claimed to be.
It's like something out of a penny
novel, rich man in a pauper's coat.
Who are you two discussing?
The Prince. He's Blackwood's brother.
And I don't want to be
friends with him no longer.
Are you not gonna serve me?
The sign says all welcome.
No?
Why should you be any
different from these folk here?
What do you let him stay for?
Because he works hard and he's hungry.
Just like all of you.
Tell her to wash it in yonder well
Parsley, sage, rosemary and thyme
Where never sprung
water or rain never fell
Then she'll be the true love of mine
You must be joking, sir.
What's a tavern if there ain't no beer?
That's the price of business, Joe.
We've got to make some changes here.
I'm not a learned man, sir.
But I know Jesus took wine.
Not for breakfast, dinner and tea.
Maybe... find yourself a dairy herd.
And drain those barrels dry.
Oh, and tell your girl she's NOT
to go up on that stage any more.
You try telling her anything.
Hang on, hang on. It'll keep.
It's a fine day's work.
I'll be wanting supplies for tomorrow.
You'll struggle to keep up with me.
Can you have your young grocery clerk
deliver first thing in the morning?
I need a shin of beef.
Shall we say... seven shillings?
A shilling more than yesterday?
You putting up prices already?
You want to be at the front
of the line, you have to pay.
Mr Coates, why do I get the feeling
you're determined to get your cut from me?
I'll make other arrangements.
You'll have to deal with me or no-one.
Well, we'll see about that, won't we?
Mrs Quaintain, why do I get the feeling
you're issuing a challenge to me?
I will not be at the beck and
call of a man again. Ever.
What are you two still hanging around for?
The cart doesn't leave for a while.
And I suppose you need feeding.
Come with me, I'll find you summat...
.. and I've got a job for you.
- Do you like stew?
- Yeah.
Mabel?
Are you with someone, are you?
Oh, no...
Work, for the night is coming
Work through the sunny noon
Fill brightest hours with labour...
He weren't joking about that dairy herd.
I'll tell you, plain... I'm not staying.
I'm not running no milk parlour,
just because Jesus is expected
to pop in now and again.
Young Blackwood, what's he thinking?
Selling this town out to Methodist folk.
Reckons how he needs their money.
Oh, he needs a happy town. And
he ain't gonna have one soon.
I only got to sing one song! And
Pa says I ain't to sing no more!
Oh, don't LOOK at me with them cow eyes!
I wanted to be someone!
Well, you're someone
to me. You're my Alma.
Oh, you don't... understand!
I hate it... here. I hate
the SMELL of the beer!
I hate the way that every
man always has dirt on him!
This was my one chance
to be somebody better,
and it's been taken away from me!
I reckon you're not
used to being waited on.
I told you, any man
could be anything here.
Regardless of colour.
- You make a decent wage at that estate?
- We don't get paid money.
No, we're treated as family.
In return, we tend to
the house and grounds.
Unusual terms of employment.
I've seen that in America,
before the Civil War.
Our families, in Antigua,
they were slaves.
My sister raised me. She
worked on a plantation.
I've been in Yorkshire since I was a baby.
So you're grateful for what
you've been given, huh?
What did you mean... when you
said a man can be anything?
I can find you paid
employment in the valley.
How's that suit you?
Good!
Tell me... how well do you know
those Blackwood brothers, huh?
- I shouldn't be talking about the family.
- No, of course.
Your loyalty is admirable.
I-I'm sorry, I embarrassed
you. I didn't mean to.
Stay, please.
Finish your coffee.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
All right. Well, let me
know, won't you, Alice?
Well, look at this empire of yours.
It's growing bigger every day.
You'll be running this town soon.
What you after, lad?
- I was wondering if Mabel's in?
- No, she not working today.
You'll have to keep it
buttoned up till Tuesday.
What's the matter with Mabel?
She's not got that fever, has she?
Ah, you don't know how
we live, Annie Quaintain.
And you don't want to, either. Trust me.
What do you mean? Don't want to know what?
Some fella visited her last
night, smacked her around.
- Do you know who it was?
- Nah, she won't tell me, poor lass.
Should get the law on
to him, whoever he is.
That's the woman from the village talking.
You're a navvy now. Law don't trouble us.
Just as you asked, sir,
the tavern will now be a temperance bar.
Like sheep, we've all gone astray.
God loves a sinner come home.
Perhaps we can now start
to think about a contract?
What about those women?
They have no place in your town.
See that they're gone.
Mabel?
Sorry to bother you. I
brought you some vittles.
Oh... Look at you.
Happen it looks worse than it
is. It'll mend in a day or two.
You must tell people his name.
He told me he'd hurt
me again if I said owt.
There's people here who'll look after you.
They won't be able to do nothing.
Why not? No-one's beyond the law.
Some folk are beyond our laws.
You're telling me he's a gentleman.
How long you planning to live like this?
No-one else would know this place.
Shanty folk don't want me.
Nor my family, neither.
Look at you! Come here.
I was always the captain.
How far did we travel,
eh? Australia? America?
Not much further than
the edge of the garden.
Where've you been these last few years?
I've seen a lot of the world.
Carved a great canal across the desert.
Further than the end of the garden, then?
Listen, I need to tell ya.
Coates has been asking questions.
Wants to know all about you.
Get that wagon filled.
You, stack it with those
ones. Get the rest.
What's going on here?
You two, those baskets. Get rid.
I want these women out of here.
- What are you doing?
- Keep out of our way, ma'am.
They're making us leave. New
investor wants rid of us.
Go away, will you?! What's
the matter with you?!
Get that wagon filled!
Put it in the back.
Mabel... what are you staring at?
It's him. That fella, there. He's the one.
You! You're no man of God.
You're a damned hypocrite!
- Annie? What's going on?!
- He's the one who hurt Mabel.
Well, no wonder he's so
keen to see you out of here!
You'd better keep your mouth shut.
Or what? You'll do the same
to me as you did to her?
- Take your hands off me!
- Ooh!
You'll answer to the law for that.
I know you don't owe me no favours.
Your visits to me, that's all business,
and I don't wish to take advantage
of your fondness for me.
Why do I feel there's a 'but'
coming in this sentence?
Annie Quaintain struck a
man in the street just now.
Locked herself in her hut.
There's gonna be trouble.
And it's your job to protect her. Come on.
'Railway Agent', painted in
big, black letters outside.
That's supposed to mean something.
George!
Get up to the scaffold, there's
empty pitchers to be collected.
All right. I'm just going to finish
off doing this - - George, I said get!
It's best he ain't here.
Begging your pardon, sir. Ma'am.
- I need to speak with you.
- What is it, Coates?
A woman came to me and complained...
about yonder gentleman.
He's already told us what occurred.
The woman who struck me is
trying to fleece money from me.
Said she'd spread some damned
lies if I didn't pay her!
She's saying he assaulted a woman here.
- You're not serious?
- This is preposterous!
A woman who works over at the brothel hut.
- And you believe her lies?
- I'm obliged to, sir.
It's my job to take care of these people.
Now you listen to me, Coates. We're not just
any folk. We have a reputation in this county.
You're not going to take
her word over mine, surely?
I will drag her out of that hut.
And I will march her towards a constable!
Don't let him do that, sir. Don't
let him bring the law on her.
You must do as he asks. We
need to appease him, Coates.
You can either have this town on your
side or his money in your pocket.
Let me talk to her!
Miss Quaintain, it's Ralph Coates.
You're needed up at the office.
I'll see that you're treated well.
You have my word on it.
I sent him out. He ain't here.
Mrs Quaintain, would you mind telling us
what happened with Mr Sorsby?
No doubt you've heard.
He hurt Mabel.
A shanty town prostitute.
Who are you to make judgments on us? Your
son's the one that's been carrying on with her!
She was trying to extort money
from me! This is all a lie.
Just the word of two navvy women.
Against that of a gentleman.
Surely this lady's word
counts for something.
Tell your wife not to
take against us, Charles.
Tell her yourself, she's
standing right beside you.
Wives be subject to your
husbands, says the book.
And what does it say about priggish
men with inflated opinions?
Are you really gonna
be silent here, Charles?
Well, he has to. He knows
what's best for the townsfolk.
Now I've heard about
these navvy towns before.
There's little respect for the law.
But there is no question in
my mind what happened here!
- No, wait! Where are you taking me?
- You can't take her away like that.
You have no authority over me, Agent.
You're coming with me to see a constable!
What about my son and daughter?
Annie, I'll look after 'em till
all this is sorted. Don't worry.
He's there. He's coming, Mam.
- What's going on here?
- What's it to you?
This is my estate. You're on my land.
This woman is being taken to
the police for extorting money.
- On what evidence?
- The word of a gentleman.
Well, I'm a gentleman, too.
I don't believe that my
word is any better than hers.
But if that's what it takes to
convince you, I'll vouch for her.
- You're all swagger, aren't you?
- Take a look at that sign, there.
It's my name that's on it, not yours.
You have no authority here.
If you want any of my investment,
you'll not stand in my way.
No amount of money is worth letting
you harm these folk. You hear me?
You really want to start a
war with these shanty folk?
What you do to one... a hundred
others will know by tomorrow.
Sir, perhaps we can escort
you to your carriage?
Aye, sir. Reckon it's
time you were leaving.
Thank you.
You'll not see a penny of my money!
Well, I'll go and uncork those
four barrels I kept hidden.
Come on, you lot, you heard what he said!
Seems whatever I do,
my life gets tangled up with
yours... Johnny Blackwood.
Is that so terrible?
It's not what I had planned.
Come for supper again. I
won't charge you sixpence.
I did what I had to do
to keep Jericho alive.
All you've done is bring this
town one day nearer to disaster.
I offered you my help, Charles.
You threw it back in my face.
I wouldn't accept your help!
Not if my whole future depended on it!
You shame yourself.
Staying silent... when you should speak.