¶
>>> LIVE IN THE SHADOW OF THE
HOLLYWOOD SIGN, WELCOME TO THE
DOLBY THEATRE, AND THE OSCARS.
>> START PROCEEDING WITH THE
COUNTDOWN.
>> STRAP IN.
>> TEN.
NINE.
EIGHT.
SEVEN.
>> HANG ON.
>> FIVE.
FOUR.
THREE.
TWO.
ONE.
>> EACH PERSON YOU SPEAK TO HAS
HAD A DAY.
SOME OF THE DAYS HAVE BEEN GOOD.
SOME BAD.
WHAT IS IT TO BE HUMAN?
WHAT IS IT TO BE ALIVE?
>> TELL ME WHY IT'S SO IMPORTANT
FOR IT TO SAY HELLO?
>> NO ONE SAID THE JOB'S
SUPPOSED TO BE EASY.
>> NO ONE SAID IT'S SUPPOSED TO
BE THAT HARD, EITHER.
>> WE'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
>> WE'LL USE THE FORCE.
>> THAT'S NOT HOW THE FORCE
WORKS!
>> I BLEW MYSELF UP.
>> WOO!
>> BECAUSE I'M STUPID.
>> THAT'S NOT STUPIDITY.
THAT'S FRAUD.
>> TELL ME THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN STUPID AND ILLEGAL AND
I'LL HAVE MY WIFE'S BROTHER
ARRESTED.
>> BE CAREFUL WITH THAT.
>> IT'S OKAY.
IT'S NOT LOADED.
>> WHAT IF YOU HAD THE CHANCE TO
FIND OUT HOW BIG WE COULD REALLY
BE?
>> I GOT SOMETHING TO SAY.
>> IS THAT THE BEST YOU CAN DO?
>> WHAT A LOVELY DAY!
>> DO YOU HAVE YOUR SEAT BELT
ON?
>> YOU'RE ASKING ME THAT NOW?
>> SORRY ABOUT THAT.
NEEDED TO LET OFF A LITTLE
STEAM.
>> THEY'RE ALL LOOKING AT YOU.
>> BELIEVE ME.
THEY'RE ALL LOOKING AT YOU.
>> YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE WHO SEES
THE WORLD IN THE SAME WAY I DO.
>> NO ONE SEES THE WORLD THE
SAME WAY YOU DO.
>> YOU SEE THIS GUY HERE STARING
BACK AT YOU?
THAT'S YOUR TOUGHEST OPPONENT.
I BELIEVE THAT IN BOXING AND I
DO BELIEVE THAT IN LIFE.
>> I CAN DO THIS.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE IT.
>> WHAT?
>> THE WORLD.
>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, PLEASE
WELCOME YOUR HOST, CHRIS ROCK!
>> THANK YOU!
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU!
WOO!
MAN, I COUNTED AT LEAST 15 BLACK
PEOPLE ON THAT MONTAGE.
HEY!
WELL, I'M HERE AT THE ACADEMY
AWARDS.
OTHERWISE KNOWN AS THE WHITE
PEOPLE'S CHOICE AWARDS.
YOU REALIZE IF THEY NOMINATED
HOSTS, I WOULDN'T EVEN GET THIS
JOB.
Y'ALL BE WATCHING NEIL PATRICK
HARRIS RIGHT NOW.
BUT THIS IS -- THIS IS THE
WILDEST, CRAZIEST OSCARS TO EVER
HOST, BECAUSE YOU HAVE ALL THIS
CONTROVERSY, THE NO -- NO BLACK
NOMINEES, YOU KNOW?
AND PEOPLE ARE LIKE, CHRIS, YOU
SHOULD BOYCOTT, CHRIS, YOU
SHOULD QUIT, YOU SHOULD QUIT.
YOU KNOW, HOW COME IT'S ONLY
UNEMPLOYED PEOPLE THAT TELL YOU
TO QUIT SOMETHING, YOU KNOW?
NO ONE WITH A JOB EVER TELLS YOU
TO QUIT.
SO, I THOUGHT ABOUT QUITTING.
I THOUGHT ABOUT IT REAL HARD.
BUT I REALIZED, THEY'RE GOING TO
HAVE THE OSCARS ANYWAY.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO CANCEL THE
OSCARS BECAUSE I QUIT.
YOU KNOW?
AND THE LAST THING I NEED IS TO
LOSE ANOTHER JOB TO KEVIN HART,
OKAY?
I DON'T NEED THAT.
KEV -- KEV RIGHT THERE.
KEV MAKE MOVIES FAST.
EVERY MONTH.
PORNO STARS DON'T MAKE MOVIES
THAT FAST.
NOW, THE THING IS, WHY ARE WE
PROTESTING -- THE BIG QUESTION,
WHY THIS OSCARS?
WHY THIS OSCARS, YOU KNOW?
IT'S THE 88th ACADEMY AWARDS.
IT'S THE 88th ACADEMY AWARDS,
WHICH MEANS -- THIS WHOLE NO
BLACK NOMINEES THING HAS
HAPPENED AT LEAST 71 OTHER
TIMES.
OKAY?
YOU GOT TO FIGURE THAT IT
HAPPENED IN THE '50s, IN THE
'60s.
YOU KNOW, IN THE '60s, ONE OF
THOSE YEARS, SIDNEY DIDN'T PUT
OUT A MOVIE.
I'M SURE -- I'M SURE THERE WERE
NO BLACK NOMINEES, SOME OF THOSE
YEARS.
SAY 62 OR 63 AND BLACK PEOPLE
DID NOT PROTEST.
WHY?
BECAUSE WE HAVE REAL THINGS TO
PROTEST AT THE TIME.
YOU KNOW?
WE HAVE REAL THINGS TO PROTEST.
TOO BUSY BEING RAPED AND LYNCHED
TO CARE ABOUT WHO WON BEST
CINEMATOGRAPHER.
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU -- WHEN YOUR
GRANDMOTHER'S SWINGING FROM A
TREE, IT'S REALLY HARD TO CARE
ABOUT BEST DOCUMENTARY FOREIGN
SHORT.
BUT WHAT HAPPENED THIS YEAR?
WHAT HAPPENED?
PEOPLE WENT MAD, YOU KNOW?
SPIKE GOT MAD AND JADA WENT MAD
AND WILL AND EVERYBODY WENT MAD,
YOU KNOW?
LIKE -- JADA GOT MAD, JADA SAYS
SHE'S NOT COMING, PROTESTING,
I'M LIKE -- DOESN'T SHE HAVE A
TV SHOW?
JADA BOYCOTTING THE OSCARS IS
LIKE ME BOYCOTTING RIHANNA'S
PANTIES.
I WASN'T INVITED.
OH, THAT'S -- IT'S NOT AN
INVITATION I WOULD TURN DOWN.
BUT I UNDERSTAND, I -- I'M NOT
HATING.
I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE MAD.
JAD A IS MAD.
HER MAN WAS NOT NOMINATED.
I GET IT.
YOU GET MAD.
SAID IT'S NOT FAIR THAT WILL WAS
THIS GOOD AND DOESN'T GET
NOMINATED.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS ALSO NOT FAIR THAT WILL
WAS PAID $20 MILLION FOR "WILD
WILD WEST," OKAY?
OKAY?
YOU KNOW, THIS YEAR, THE OSCARS,
THINGS ARE GOING TO BE A LITTLE
DIFFERENT.
DIFFERENT AT THE OSCARS.
THIS YEAR, IN THE IN MEMORIUM
PACKAGE, IT'S JUST GOING TO BE
BLACK PEOPLE THAT WERE SHOT ON
THEIR WAY TO THE MOVIES.
YES.
I SAID IT.
ALL RIGHT?
HEY, IF YOU WANT BLACK NOMINEES
EVERY YEAR, YOU NEED TO JUST
HAVE BLACK CATEGORIES.
THAT'S WHAT YOU NEED.
YOU NEED TO HAVE BLACK
CATEGORIES.
YOU ALREADY DO IT WITH MEN AND
WOMEN.
THINK ABOUT IT.
THERE'S NO REAL REASON FOR THERE
TO BE A MAN AND A WOMAN CATEGORY
IN ACTING.
IT'S -- COME ON!
THERE'S NO REASON!
IT'S NOT TRACK AND FIELD.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SEPARATE THEM.
YOU KNOW, ROBERT DE NIRO'S NEVER
SAID, I BETTER SLOW THIS ACTING
DOWN SO MERYL STREEP CAN CATCH
UP.
NO.
NOT AT ALL, MAN.
IF YOU WANT BLACK PEOPLE EVERY
YEAR AT THE OSCARS, JUST HAVE
BLACK CATEGORIES, LIKE BEST
BLACK FRIEND.
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND THE WINNER FOR THE 18th YEAR
IN A ROW IS WANDA SIKES.
THIS IS WANDA'S 18th BLACK
OSCAR.
BUT HERE'S THE REAL QUESTION.
THE REAL QUESTION EVERYBODY
WANTS TO KNOW, EVERYBODY WANTS
TO KNOW, IN THE WORLD, IS
HOLLYWOOD RACIST?
IS HOLLYWOOD RACIST?
YOU KNOW, THAT'S -- THAT'S A --
YOU KNOW, YOU GOT TO GO AT THAT
AT THE RIGHT WAY.
IS IT BURNING CROSS RACIST?
NO.
IS IT FETCH ME SOME LEMONADE
RACIST?
NO, NO.
IT'S A DIFFERENT TYPE OF RACIST.
NOW, I REMEMBER ONE NIGHT I WAS
AT A FUND-RAISER FOR PRESIDENT
OBAMA, A LOT OF YOU WERE THERE,
AND, YOU KNOW, IT'S ME AND ALL
OF HOLLYWOOD.
AND ALL THE, YOU KNOW, IT'S ALL
OF US THERE AND THERE'S ABOUT
FOUR BLACK PEOPLE THERE, ME,
LET'S SEE, QUINCY JONES, RUSSELL
SIMMONS, QUEST LOVE, YOU KNOW,
THE USUAL SUSPECTS, RIGHT?
AND EVERY BLACK ACTOR THAT
WASN'T WORKING.
NEEDLESS TO SAY, KEV HART WAS
NOT THERE, OKAY?
SO, AT SOME POINT, YOU GET TO
TAKE A PICTURE WITH THE
PRESIDENT.
AND AS THEY'RE SETTING UP THE
PICTURE, YOU GET A LITTLE MOMENT
WITH THE PRESIDENT, I'M LIKE,
MR. PRESIDENT, YOU SEE ALL THESE
WRITERS AND PRODUCERS AND
ACTORS?
THEY DON'T HIRE BLACK PEOPLE.
AND THEY'RE THE NICEST WHITE
PEOPLE ON EARTH.
THEY'RE LIBERALS.
CHEESE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
IS HOLLYWOOD RACIST?
YOU'RE DAMN RIGHT HOLLYWOOD'S
RACIST.
BUT IT ISN'T THE RACIST YOU'VE
GROWN ACCUSTOMED TO.
HOLLYWOOD IS SORORITY RACIST.
IT'S LIKE -- WE LIKE YOU,
RHONDA, BUT YOU'RE NOT A CAPPA.
THAT'S HOW HOLLYWOOD IS.
BUT THINGS ARE CHANGING.
THINGS ARE CHANGING.
YEAH, WE GOT A BLACK ROCKY THIS
YEAR.
SOME PEOPLE CALL IT "CREED," I
CALL IT BLACK ROCKY.
AND THAT'S A BIG -- THAT'S AN
UNBELIEVABLE STATEMENT, I MEAN,
BECAUSE ROCKY TAKES PLACE IN A
WORLD WHERE WHITE ATHLETES ARE
AS GOOD AS BLACK ATHLETES.
ROCKY'S A SCIENCE FICTION MOVIE.
THERE ARE THINGS THAT HAPPENED
IN "STAR WARS" THAT ARE MORE
BELIEVABLE THAN THINGS THAT
HAPPENED IN "ROCKY."
WE'RE HERE TO HONOR ACTORS.
WE'RE HERE TO HONOR FILM.
AND THERE'S A LOT OF SNUBS.
A LOT OF SNUBS.
ONE OF THE BIGGEST SNUBS NO
ONE'S TALKING ABOUT, MY FAVORITE
ACTOR IN THE WORLD IS PAUL GEE
M
GIAMATI.
I BELIEVE HE'S THE GREATEST
ACTOR IN THE WORLD.
THINK ABOUT WHAT HE'S DONE.
LAST YEAR, HE'S IN "12 YEARS A
SLAVE," HATES BLACK PEOPLE.
THIS YEAR, HE'S IN "STRAIGHT
OUTTA COMPTON," LOVES BLACK
PEOPLE.
LAST YEAR, HE'S WHOOPING LUPITA,
THIS YEAR, HE'S CRYING AND
EASY-E'S FUNERAL.
THAT'S RANGE.
BEN AFFLECK CAN'T DO THAT.
BUT WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY IS,
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT ABOUT
BOYCOTTING ANYTHING, IT'S JUST,
WE WANT OPPORTUNITY.
WE WANT THE BLACK ACTORS TO GET
THE SAME OPPORTUNITIES AS WHITE
ACTORS.
THAT'S IT.
YOU KNOW?
JUST -- YOU KNOW, NOT JUST ONCE,
LEO GETS A GREAT PART EVERY
YEAR.
AND, YOU KNOW, AND --
EVERYBODY -- ALL YOU GUYS GET
GREAT PARTS ALL THE TIME.
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE BLACK ACTORS?
LOOK AT JAMIE FOXX.
JAMIE FOXX, ONE OF THE BEST
ACTORS IN THE WORLD, MAN.
JAMIE FOXX -- HE IS.
JAMIE FOXX WAS SO GOOD IN "RAY,"
THAT THEY WENT TO THE HOSPITAL
AND UNPLUGGED THE REAL RAY
CHARLES, LIKE, WE DON'T NEED TWO
OF THESE.
NO, MAN.
BUT THE BIG -- YOU KNOW,
EVERYTHING IS NOT ABOUT RACE,
MAN.
ANOTHER BIG THING TONIGHT IS,
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED -- SOMEBODY
TOLD ME THIS, YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO ASK WOMEN WHAT THEY'RE
WEARING ANYMORE.
IT'S A WHOLE THING.
YOU KNOW, ASK HER MORE.
YOU HAVE TO ASK HER MORE.
NOW -- YOU KNOW, LIKE, YOU ASK
THE MEN MORE.
HEY, EVERYTHING'S NOT SEXISM,
EVERYTHING'S NOT RACISM.
THEY ASK THE MEN MORE, BECAUSE
THE MEN ARE ALL WEARING THE SAME
OUTFITS, OKAY?
EVERY GUY IS WEARING THE EXACT
SAME THING.
YOU KNOW, IF GEORGE CLOONEY
SHOWED UP WITH A LIME GREEN TUX
ON AND A SWAN COMING OUT HIS
ASS, SOMEBODY WOULD GO, WHAT YOU
WEARING, GEORGE?
HEY, WELCOME TO THE 88th OSCARS!
ACADEMY AWARDS.
YES.
THANK YOU.
YOU WANT DIVERSITY, WE GOT
DIVERSITY!
PLEASE WELCOME EMILY BLUNT AND
SOMEBODY WHITER, CHARLIZE
THERON.
>> TONIGHT'S OSCARS CEREMONY
WILL FOLLOW A PARTICULAR ORDER
THAT TRACKS THE FILMMAKING
PROCESS ITSELF.
SO, WE BEGIN OUR PRESENTATION AT
THE PLACE WHERE EVERY GREAT
MOVIE BEGINS, WITH A STORY THAT
SIMPLY HAD TO BE TOLD.
>> WRITERS, WE KNOW THAT YOU'RE
THE TRUE BACKBONE OF THE
INDUSTRY AND WE LOVE YOU FOR IT.
WE ALSO THINK YOU'RE ALL
EXTREMELY HOT.
A WRITER WROTE THAT.
>> HERE ARE THIS YEAR'S HIGHLY
ORIGINAL NOMINEES FOR BEST
ORIGINAL SCREENPLAY.
"STRAIGHT OUTTA COMPTON,"
SCREENPLAY BY JONATHAN HERMAN
AND ANDREA BERLOFF.
STORY BY S. LEIGH SAVIDGE, ALAN
WENKUS AND ANDREA BERLOFF.
>> SO, WHAT'S A GUY FROM COMPTON
DO WHEN HE STARTS MAKING REAL
MONEY FROM THAT?
>> LAFLTER FROM THE ASSEMBLED,
NOT FROM CUBE.
SILENCE, THEN?
>> CUBE?
>> BUY RAIDER GEAR AND CURL
ACTIVATOR.
>> "BRIDGE OF SPIES," WRITTEN BY
MATT CHARMAN AND ETHAN COEN AND
JOEL COEN.
DONOVAN PACES IN A DETENTION
ROOM.
HE TURNS TO SEE ABLE STANDING
JUST INSIDE THE DOOR.
DONOVAN --
>> THE DEATH SENTENCE IS NOT A
FOREGONE CONCLUSION.
DON'T WORRY.
>> I'M NOT AFRAID TO DIE, MR.
DONOVAN.
>> "EX MACHINA," WRITTEN BY ALEX
GARLAND.
THEY EXCHANGE A LOOK, THEN AVA
RESTS A HAND.
THEN, THE POWER DIES.
CALEB --
>> DON'T TALK.
JUST LISTEN.
YOU WERE RIGHT ABOUT NATHAN.
EVERYTHING YOU SAID.
>> WHAT IS HE GOING TO DO TO ME?
>> HE'S GOING TO REPROGRAM YOUR
A.I.
>> "SPOTLIGHT," WRITTEN BY JOSH
SINGER AND TOM McCARTHY.
>> IT'S FROM '93.
>> ROBBIE LOOKS DOWN.
WE SEE THE CLIP.
LAWYER FOR PORTER VICTIMS SAY 20
OTHER PIECES IN THE AREA ARE
ACCUSED.
ROBBIE'S FACE CHANGES, SASHA
WAITS, EXPECTING A RESPONSE.
ROBBIE?
>> THAT IT?
>> ROBBIE'S TONE CATCHES SASHA
BY SURPRISE.
>> YEAH, YEAH, THAT'S IT.
>> "INSIDE OUT," SCREENPLAY BY
PETE DOCTER, MEG LEFAUVE AND
JOSH COOLEY.
ORIGINAL STORY BY PETE DOCTER,
RONNIE DEL CARMEN.
>> ALL RIGHT, HERE YOU GO.
YOUR NEW EXPANDED CONSOLE IS UP
AND RUNNING.
>> THE NEW CONSOLE LIGHTS UP.
>> COOL, UPGRADE.
>> FEAR LEANS ON THE CONSOLE.
>> DID I JUST DO THAT?
>> GUYS, WHAT'S PUBERTY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
PROBABLY NOT IMPORTANT.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
"SPOTLIGHT."
JOSH SINGER AND TOM McCARTHY.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR FOR
THIS IS THE THIRD NOMINATION FOR
TOM McCARTHY, WHO IS ALSO
NOMINATED FOR DIRECTING
"SPOTLIGHT."
>> WE'VE GOT TO THANK OPEN ROAD,
WE'VE GOT TO THANK PARTICIPANT.
WE HAVE TO THANK OUR WONDERFUL
PRODUCERS, MICHAEL SUGAR, STEVE
GOLIN.
WE HAVE TO THANK OUR WONDERFUL
CAST AND CREW FROM BOSTON AND
TORONTO.
MY WIFE, WHO MAKES ME A BETTER
WRITER EVERYMAKES ME A
BETTER HUMAN EVERY DAY.
AND MY FATHER, BRUCE SINGER, WHO
TAUGHT ME HOW TO DREAM.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WE MADE THIS FILM FOR ALL THE
JOURNALISTS WHO HAVE AND
CONTINUE TO HOLD THE POWERFUL
ACCOUNTABLE AND FOR THE
SURVIVORS WHOSE COURAGE AND WILL
TO OVERCOME IS REALLY AN
INSPIRATION.
WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE THIS NEVER
HAPPENS AGAIN.
TO RHONDA PRICE, TO MY BEAUTIFUL
WIFE WENDY, NORA, VIVIAN, MY
FAMILY AND ALL OUR FRIENDS, WE
THANK YOU.
THIS ONE'S FOR YOU, GENO.
WE LOVE YOU.
LOVE YOU, MOM AND DAD.
>> Announcer: NOW, PLEASE
WELCOME OSCAR NOMINEE RYAN
GOSLING AND OSCAR WINNER RUSSELL
CROWE.
>> GOOD EVENING, FOLKS.
WE'RE HERE TO PRESENT THE
AWARD FOR BEST ADAPTED
SCREENPLAY.
>> NOT TO GET TOO
TECHNICAL, THAT'S THE SCREENPLAY
THAT WAS THE VERY BEST AT
ADAPTING TO WHATEVER HARSH
CONDITIONS AND OBSTACLES WERE
THROWN IN ITS WAY.
>> NO, IT'S A SCREENPLAY ADAPTED
FROM ANOTHER SOURCE SUCH AS A
NOVEL, PLAY, SHORT STORY OR TV
SHOW.
>> AGREE TO DISAGREE.
OKAY?
>> AGREE THAT YOU'RE WRONG.
>> LOOK, LET'S NOT FIGHT.
I MEAN, MY GOD.
WE HAVE TWO ACADEMY AWARDS
BETWEEN US.
THIS IS BENEATH US.
>> DID YOU WIN AN OSCAR?
>> NOT WHEN YOU PUT IT LIKE
THAT, BUT YOU HAVE TWO, SO,
THERE'S TECHNICALLY TWO BETWEEN
US.
>> I HAVE ONE.
>> YOU HAVE TWO.
>> AGREE TO DISAGREE.
CAN WE GO ON AND GIVE OUT THIS
AWARD SO MORE PEOPLE CAN HAVE
OSCARS LIKE WE DO?
>> LISTEN, MATE.
YOU CAN'T JUST GO AROUND
SAYING --
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
BEST ADAPTED SCREENPLAY.
CHARLES RANDOLPH AND ADAM McKAY
FOR "THE BIG SHORT," BASED ON
THE BOOK BY MICHAEL LEWIS.
MICHAEL SITS BEHIND DRUMS AND
PLAYING TO PANTERA.
FINALLY, HE BREAKS THE STICKS
FROM PLAYING TOO HARD.
WE HEAR HIS WIFE FROM UPSTAIRS.
WIFE?
>> MICHAEL?
MICHAEL?
>> YES.
>> IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
>> YES, HONEY.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> YEAH, BABY.
>> NICK HORNBY FOR "BROOKLYN,"
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY COLM
TOIBIN.
HE SEES HER AND HIS FACE BREAKS
OUT INTO A RADIANT AND RELIEVED
SMILE.
SHE SMILES BACK AND WALKS DOWN
THE REMAINS STEPS TOWARDS HIM.
TONY?
>> ALL I WANT TO DO IS TRAVEL
HOME WITH YOU, NO FOOD, NO
DRINK, NO NOTHING.
I KNOW YOU GOT TO STUDY AND GET
SOME SLEEP, I'LL TAKE YOU TO
YOUR HOUSE AND SAY GOOD NIGHT.
OTHERWISE --
BASED ON THE NOVEL "THE PRICE OF
SALT" BY PATRICIA HIGHSMITH.
>> WOULD YOU LIKE TO COME VISIT
ME THIS SUNDAY?
>> CAROL WAITS FOR THE ANSWER.
>> YES.
>> WHAT A STRANGE GURL YOU ARE.
>> WHY?
>> FLUNG OUT OF SPACE.
>> SHE FEELS HERSELF BLUSH AND
LOOKS AWAY FROM CAROL.
SHE TRIES TO ATTEND TO HER LUNCH
AND MARTINI.
DREW GODDARD FOR "THE MARTIAN,"
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY ANDY
WE'RE.
>> HITS THE GROUND LIKE A WET
RAG.
MARK TALKS TO CAMERA.
HIS CLOTHES ARE SCORCHED.
HIS HAIR IS SINGED IN PATCHES.
MARK --
>> SO, YEAH.
I BLEW MYSELF UP.
>> EMMA DONOGHUE FOR "ROOM,"
BASED ON HER NOVEL.
>> HE TOLDS HIS TRUCK UP TO THE
VENT SO IT CAN DJOIN IN.
JACK?
>> WHY DO THE ALIENS NEVER
SCREAM BACK?
>> I GUESS THEY STILL CAN'T HEAR
US.
>> WE'LL DO IT LOUDER, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
>> CHARLES RANDOLPH AND ADAM
McKAY, "THE BIG SHORT."
>> THIS IS THE FIRST WIN FOR
ADAM McKAY, WHO IS ALSO
NOMINATED FOR DIRECTING "THE BIG
SHORT" THIS YEAR.
>> AH -- THANK YOU SO MUCH TO
THE ACADEMY.
ALSO, THANK YOU TO MICHAEL
LEWIS, FOR WRITING AN AMAZING
BOOK.
IT INSPIRED CHARLES AND I SO
MUCH.
THANK YOU TO PARAMOUNT FOR
TAKING A RISK ON A MOVIE THAT'S
ABOUT FINANCIAL ESOTERICA.
THANK YOU TO MY BEAUTIFUL WIFE
AND MY CHILDREN, LILY ROSE, MY
TWO DAUGHTER, LILY ROSE AND
PEARL, I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
MOST OF ALL, IF YOU DON'T WANT
BIG MONEY TO CONTROL GOVERNMENT,
DON'T VOTE FOR CANDIDATES THAT
TAKE MONEY FROM BIG BANKS, OIL
OR WEIRDO BILLIONAIRES.
STOP.
GO, SORRY.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH, PLAN B.
THIS VERY MUCH TO PARAMOUNT, TO
MY WIFE.
TO MY KIDS, I AM SO HAPPY TO BE
YOUR FATHER.
THANK YOU.
>> Announcer: SOME OF
HOLLYWOOD'S MOST EXCITING STARS
ARE COMING UP.
PLUS, MORE FROM CHRIS ROCK,
NEXT.
¶
>>> AS YOU KNOW, FOR THE SECOND
YEAR IN A ROW, ALL THE ACTING
NOMINEES ARE WHITE.
BUT WORST THAN THAT, IF YOU ARE
A BLACK ACTOR, JUST GETTING AN
OPPORTUNITY TO BE IN A MOVIE CAN
BE A STRUGGLE.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> SORRY.
>> YOU'RE JOY.
>> I'M JOY?
>> COME ON.
GO.
>> UM --
>> IT'S NOT ROCKET SCIENCE.
IT'S A MOP.
>> JUST SAY SOMETHING.
>> SORRY.
THESE LIGHTS ARE SO BRIGHT.
UM --
>> OH, MY GOD.
TELL HER TO SAY SOMETHING ABOUT
THE MOP.
>> TALK ABOUT THE MOP.
>> SAY SOMETHING!
MAYBE ONE DAY THEY'LL MAKE A
MOVIE ABOUT A SKINNY WHITE LADY
THAT MADE A MOP.
A BLACK GIRL WOULD HAVE TO
INVENT THE CURE FOR CANCER
BEFORE THEY GIVE HER A TV MOVIE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> BUT HEY, I'M NOT MAD.
BECAUSE I KNOW HOW TO PLAY THE
GAME.
JOY.
>> AHH!
>> THERE ARE NO ACTRESSES IN
THIS MOVIE!
MY AGENT CALLED YOU TWICE.
THEN I CALLED YOU 16 TIMES.
YOU SHOULD HAVE CALLED ME BACK.
>> LOOK AT ME.
I'M A BLACK THESE BEE YAN,
STARRING IN HIS FIRST DRAMATIC
ROLE.
AH!
>> HELLO?
>> I'M THE DANISH GIRL!
THESE DANISHES IS GOOD, GIRL!
NAILED IT.
>> GUYS, I'M -- I'M HERE.
>> OH, IS HE STILL UP THERE?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> SHOULD WE GET HIM?
>> YEAH, YOU SHOULD GET ME.
>> DON'T WORRY, BLACK ASTRONAUT,
WE WILL.
>> IT WILL COST $2,500.
>> OH, THAT'S A LOT.
CAN WE JUST LEAVE HIM UP THERE?
>> AH.
>> GUYS, I CAN HEAR YOU.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
>> HI.
YEAH, MIGHT BE A PR PROBLEM.
>> I'LL TELL YOU WHAT'S A PR
PROBLEM.
SPENDING 2,500 WHITE DOLLARS TO
SAVE ONE BLACK ASTRONAUT.
WE'LL ALL BE OUT OF JOBS.
>> WHAT?
WHITE DOLLARS?
>> YEAH, BUT I DON'T REALLY SEE
A BLACK ASTRONAUT.
DO YOU SEE A BLACK ASTRONAUT
ANYWHERE?
>> I DON'T SEE A BLACK
ASTRONAUT.
>> I'M RIGHT HERE [ BLEEP ]!
>> OH, GOSH.
YOU WANT TO GET LUNCH?
>> OH, YEAH.
WHAT ABOUT SOME PHO?
>> I HAVEN'T EATEN SINCE JUNE.
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> SEE.
TOLD YOU THEY WEREN'T GOING TO
BRING YOU BACK.
>> CAN YOU HELP ME?
>> KISS MY ASS.
>> NO!
>> IT'S HARD TO GET A JOB.
BUT LET ME TELL YOU SOME GOOD
NEWS.
THE ACADEMY HAS TAKEN STEPS TO
FIX THIS PROBLEM.
THAT'S WHY IT IS MY HONOR TO
INTRODUCE THE NEW DIRECTOR OF
OUR MINORITY OUTREACH PROGRAM.
PLEASE WELCOME MISS STACEY DASH.
>> I CANNOT WAIT TO HELP MY
PEOPLE OUT.
HAPPY BLACK HISTORY MONTH!
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
BUT ENOUGH ABOUT BLACK PEOPLE.
LET'S BRING OUT SARAH SILVERMAN.
>> I'M HERE TO INTRODUCE THE
FIRST OF TONIGHT'S NOMINEES FOR
BEST ORIGINAL SONG, "WRITING'S
ON THE WALL."
IT'S FROM "SPECTRE," THE LATEST
JAMES BOND FILM, WHICH I DID NOT
SEE.
I GUESS -- I GUESS I WAS A BOND
GIRL, IN THAT I HAD SEXUAL
INTERCOURSE WITH JAMES BOND
FOLLOWED BY NEVER HEARING FROM
HIM AGAIN EVER.
LIKE, NEVER, LIKE, NOT EVEN A
TEXT.
AND I KNOW HE HAS A CELL
PHONE -- HE HAS FOUR OF THEM.
IT'S TUNE.
WHATEVER.
MAYBE HE LIKES SLEEPING WITH
VULNERABLE WOMEN WITH HEAVY
JEWISH BOOBS AND THEN NEVER
CONTACTING THEM AGAIN.
MAYBE THAT'S HIS THING.
KNOW WHAT MY THING IS?
BEING IN FRONT OF 80 MILLION
PEOPLE ON LIVE TV AND SAYING
WHATEVER COMES INTO MY MIND.
OH, HERE'S SOMETHING.
JAMES BOND, NOT A GROWER OR A
SHOW-ER.
I DON'T WANT TO SAY HE'S
TERRIBLE AT SEX, BUT HE DID
SLEEP WITH 55 WOMEN IN 24 MOVIES
AND MOST OF THEM TRIED TO KILL
HIM AFTERWARDS.
AND IN MY OPINION, I DON'T THINK
HE'S STREET ENOUGH.
BUT MY PERSONAL MISHIGAS ASIDE,
I'M HERE TO INTRODUCE AN ARTIST
WHO, THROUGH NO FAULT OF HIS
OWN, SANG THE LATEST BOND THEME
SONG.
SINGING "WRITING'S ON THE WALL,"
HERE IS THE BRILLIANT SAM SMITH.
¶
¶ I'VE BEEN HERE BEFORE
BUT ALWAYS HIT THE FLOOR ¶
¶ I'VE SPENT A LIFETIME RUNNING
AND I ALWAYS GET AWAY ¶
¶ BUT WITH YOU I'M FEELING
SOMETHING
THAT MAKES ME WANT TO STAY ¶
¶ IF I RISK IT ALL
COULD YOU BREAK MY FALL? ¶
¶ HOW DO I LIVE?
HOW DO I BREATHE? ¶
¶ WHEN YOU'RE NOT HERE
I'M SUFFOCATING ¶
¶ I WANT TO FEEL LOVE
RUN THROUGH MY BLOOD ¶
¶ TELL ME IS THIS WHERE I GIVE
IT ALL UP ¶
¶ FOR YOU ¶
¶ I HAVE TO RISK IT ALL ¶
¶ CAUSE THE WRITING'S ON THE
WALL ¶
¶ A MILLION SHARDS OF GLASS
THAT HAUNT ME FROM MY PAST ¶
¶ AS THE STARS BEGIN TO GATHER
AND THE LIGHT BEGINS TO FADE ¶
¶ WHEN ALL HOPE BEGINS TO
SHATTER
KNOW THAT I WON'T BE AFRAID ¶
¶ IF I RISK IT ALL
COULD YOU BREAK OUR FALL? ¶
¶ HOW DO I LIVE?
HOW DO I BREATHE? ¶
¶ WHEN YOU'RE NOT HERE
I'M SUFFOCATING ¶
¶ I WANT TO FEEL LOVE
RUN THROUGH MY BLOOD ¶
¶ TELL ME IS THIS WHERE I GIVE
IT ALL UP ¶
¶ FOR YOU I HAVE TO RISK IT
ALL ¶
¶ CAUSE THE WRITING'S ON THE
WALL ¶
>> YEAH!
AMAZING.
NO, HEY, HEY.
MY FAVORITE SONG IS "FATHER
FIGURE."
ALL RIGHT.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, PLEASE
WELCOME KERRY WASHINGTON AND
SUPERMAN HIMSELF, HENRY CAVILL.
>> TONIGHT, WE'RE GOING TO SEE
HIGHLIGHTS FROM THE MOVIES
NOMINATED FOR BEST PICTURE.
THE FIRST IS A SCI-FI EPIC WITH
HEART, A CLASSIC ADVENTURE SAGA
THAT'S AS BIG AS AN ENTIRE
PLANET AND YET OCCURS AT THE
SMALLEST POSSIBLE HUMAN SCALE --
THAT OF ONE MAN ALONE.
HERE IS "THE MARTIAN."
>> THIS IS SPACE.
IT DOES NOT COOPERATE.
>> TURNS OUT HE'S ALIVE AND WE
LEFT HIM ON MARS.
>> HE'S GOING TO STARVE TO
DEATH.
>> AT SOME POINT, EVERYTHING IS
GOING TO GO SOUTH AND YOU'RE
GOING TO SAY, THIS IS IT.
THIS IS HOW I END.
NOW, YOU CAN EITHER ACCEPT THAT
OR YOU CANAN GET TO WORK.
>> MISSION CONTROL, WE ARE GO
FOR LAUNCH.
>> LET'S GO GET OUR BOY.
>> YOU SOLVE ONE PROBLEM AND YOU
SOLVE THE NEXT ONE AND IF YOU
SOLVE ENOUGH PROBLEMS, YOU GET
TO COME HOME.
>> OUR NEXT NOMINEE FOR BEST
PICTURE CONFRONTS THE
QUESTION -- HOW CAN YOU
UNDERSTAND SOMETHING THAT
AFFECTED MILLIONS OF PEOPLE
AROUND THE WORLD, WHICH BUT
CONFOUNDED US ALL?
THANKS TO SOME BRILLIANT WRITING
AND DIRECTING, INNOVATIVE
EDITING AND A FANTASTIC ENSEMBLE
CAST, "THE BIG SHORT"
ACCOMPLISHED THAT REMARKABLE
FEAT, FINDING HUMOR AND PATHOS
ALONG THE WAY.
HERE IS "THE BIG SHORT."
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> THAT'S AMERICA'S HOUSING
MARKET.
WHILE THE WHOLE WORLD WAS HAVING
A BIG PARTY, A FEW SAW SOMETHING
BY DOING SOMETHING THE REST OF
THE SUCKERS NEVER THOUGHT TO DO.
THEY LOOKED.
>> IF WE'RE RIGHT, PEOPLE LOSE
HOMES.
PEOPLE LOSE JOBS.
PEOPLE LOSE PENSIONS.
>> THE HOUSING MARKET IS ROCK
SOLID.
>> IT'S A TIME BOMB.
>> I FIND HOUSES.
>> YOU GUYS SAID YOU WANT TO GET
RICH, NOW YOU'RE RICH.
>> IN THE YEARS THAT FOLLOWED,
HUNDREDS OF BANK EXECUTIVES WENT
TO JAIL.
JUST KIDDING.
>> Announcer: AND NOW, LAST
YEAR'S OSCAR-WINNING SUPPORTING
ACTOR, J.K. SIMMONS.
>> THE FIVE WOMEN NOMINATED FOR
BEST SUPPORTING ACTRESS THIS
YEAR DEVELOPED REMARKABLY
ROUNDED AND CONVINCING
CHARACTERS -- A MURDEROUS
FUGITIVE WITH A PRICE ON HER
HEAD, A YOUNG WOMAN DRAWN INTO A
FORBIDDEN RELATIONSHIP IN THE
1950s, AN INTREPID REPORTER
SEARCHING FOR TRUTH, AN ARTIST
WHOSE SPOUSE UNDERGOES
PIONEERING GENDER CONFIRMATION
SURGERY AND THE PLAIN-SPOKEN
MARKETING CHIEF WHO GOES
TOE-TO-TOE WITH STEVE JOBS.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
PERFORMANCE BY AN ACTRESS IN A
SUPPORTING ROLE.
JENNIFER JASON LEIGH, "THE
HATEFUL EIGHT."
>> YOU'RE MAKING THE BIGGEST
MISTAKE OF YOUR LIFE.
WHEN OUR BOYS GET HERE IN A
COUPLE OF DAYS, THEY'RE GOING TO
CUT YOUR NUTS OFF AND THERE
WON'T BE A STICK LEFT IN THAT
TOWN UNBURNED.
>> WELL, I GUESS I SHOULD BE
PLUM SCARED RIGHT NOW, HUH?
>> IF YOU HAD ANY BRAUNBRAINS,
WOULD BE.
>> ROONEY MARA, "CAROL."
>> WHAT AM I THINKING?
I'M THINKING THAT I'M UTTERLY
SELFISH --
>> DON'T DO THIS.
YOU HAD NO IDEA.
HOW WOULD YOU HAVE KNOWN?
>> AND I SHOULD HAVE SAID NO TO
YOU, BUT I NEVER SAY NO.
AND IT'S SELFISH, BECAUSE --
BECAUSE I JUST TAKE EVERYTHING
AND I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING AND I
DON'T KNOW WHAT I WANT AND HOW
COULD I WHEN ALL I EVER DO IS
SAY YES TO EVERYTHING?
>> RACHEL McADAMS, "SPOTLIGHT."
>> YOU ADMIT TO MOLESTING BOYS
AT ST. JOHN THE BAPTIST?
>> YES, YES, BUT -- AS I SAID, I
NEVER GOT ANY PLEASURE FROM IT.
THAT'S IMPORTANT TO UNDERSTAND.
>> RIGHT.
BUT -- CAN YOU TELL ME WHERE AND
HOW YOU FOOLED AROUND WITH THESE
BOYS?
>> I WANT TO BE CLEAR.
I NEVER RAPED ANYONE.
THERE'S A DIFFERENCE.
I SHOULD KNOW.
>> HOW WOULD YOU KNOW?
>> I WAS RAPED.
>> ALICIA VIKANDER, "THE DANISH
GIRL."
>> EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED BETWEEN
YOU LAST NIGHT?
>> NOTHING.
IT WAS NOTHING.
>> DID HE KNOW IT WAS YOU?
>> IT WASN'T AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
>> I WATCHED HIM KISS YOU.
CAN YOU PLEASE MAKE AN EFFORT?
>> KATE WINSLET, "STEVE JOBS."
>> YOU HAVE TO THINK YOU'RE
HAVING A BIZARRE OVERREACTION TO
A 19-YEAR-OLD GIRL ALLOWING HER
MOTHER TO LIST HER OWN HOUSE?
>> SHE COULD HAVE TRIED.
>> SHE'S SUPPOSED TO STOP HER
MOTHER?
THAT PARTICULAR MOTHER --
>> SHE DID IT TO SPITE ME.
>> I DON'T CARE IF SHE PUT A
PIPE BOMB IN THE WATER HEATER.
YOU'RE GOING TO FIX IT NOW.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO -- A
ALICIA VIKANDER, "THE DANISH
GIRL."
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR ALICIA VIKANDER.
>> THIS IS INSANE.
WOW.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, THE ACADEMY
FOR THIS INCREDIBLE RECOGNITION.
I SHARE THIS WITH OUR FABULOUS
CREW AND CAST AND I WANT TO
THANK -- I WANT TO THANK GALE
AND ANN AND NINA AND WORKING
TITLE AND FOCUS AND TOM, WHERE
ARE YOU?
MY DIRECTOR -- THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR YOUR SUPPORT AND BELIEF IN
ME AND -- EDDIE, THERE YOU ARE.
THANK YOU FOR BEING THE BEST
ACTING PARTNER.
I COULD HAVE NEVER DONE IT
WITHOUT YOU.
YOU RAISED MY GAME.
I WOULDN'T BE HERE IF IT WASN'T
FOR MY DREAM TEAM, WHICH IS
TERESA, CHARLES, LAURA, I WANT
TO THANK MY FRIENDS AND MY MOM
AND DAD -- THANK YOU FOR GIVING
ME THE BELIEF THAT ANYTHING CAN
HAPPEN EVEN THOUGH I WOULD HAVE
NEVER BELIEVED THIS.
THANK YOU.
>> Announcer: COMING UP, STEVE
CARELL AND TINA FEY.
MUSIC FROM THE WEEKND.
PLUS, MORE FROM CHRIS ROCK.
¶
>>> WE'RE BLACK.
UM -- OF ALL THE GIRL ON GIRL
MOVIES I WATCHED THIS YEAR, I
GOT TO SAY, "CAROL" WAS ABOUT
THE THIRD-BEST.
HERE TO PRESENT THE AWARD FOR
BEST COSTUME DESIGN,
ACADEMY AWARD WINNER AND A
NOMINEE TONIGHT, LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, MISS CATE BLANCHETT.
>> COSTUMES ARE MUCH MORE THAN
JUST THE CLOTHES ACTORS WEAR ON
SCREEN.
THEY'VE BEEN CALLED THE SKIN OF
THE CHARACTER, AN INTEGRAL PART
OF DEFINING THE CHARACTERS WE
PLAY.
THIS AWARD RECOGNIZES THE
STYLE-MAKERS, COLORISTS AND
FABRICATORS OF THAT WONDERFUL
SKIN.
FROM THEIR ABUNDANT IMAGINATIONS
CAME FAIRYTALE FASHIONS,
POST-APOCALYPTIC CREATIONS AND
PRECISE HISTORICAL
RECONSTRUCTIONS -- ALL OF THEM
MASTERPIECES.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
ACHIEVEMENT IN COSTUME DESIGN.
"CINDERELLA," COSTUME DESIGN BY
SANDY POWELL.
"THE DANISH GIRL," COSTUME
DESIGN BY PACO DELGADO.
"CAROL," COSTUME DESIGN BY SANDY
POWELL.
"THE REVENANT," COSTUME DESIGN
BY JACQUELINE WEST.
"MAD MAX: FURY ROAD," COSTUME
DESIGN BY JENNY BEAVAN.
AND THE OSCAR GOES TO -- JENNY
BEAVAN, "MAD MAX: FURY ROAD."
>> THIS IS THE SECOND OSCAR AND
TENTH NOMINATION FOR JENNY
BEAVAN, WHO TOOK HOME HER FIRST
OSCAR IN THIS CATEGORY FOR "A
ROOM WITH A VIEW."
>> WHAT ANOTHER LOVELY DAY.
VERY QUICKLY, IF IAN SMITH, OUR
AMAZING EXECUTIVE PRODUCER FROM
SCOTLAND HADN'T SENT ME A TEXT,
SAYING, WHAT ARE YOU DOING AT
THE MOMENT, AND THEN GOT ME ON A
PLANE OUT TO MEET GEORGE MILLER
AND DOUG MITCHELL, I WOULDN'T,
OBVIOUSLY, BE STANDING HERE.
IT WAS A YEAR OF OUR LIVES IN
THE NAMIBIAN DESERT.
WE HAD THE MOST AMAZING CREW.
I HOPE THAT -- I HEARD THEY WANT
TICKER TAPE, THE NAMES WERE
GOING ON THE SCREEN, BUT
HONESTLY, IF ANYBODY WANTS TO
KNOW MORE ABOUT ANY OF THEM,
JUST GET IN TOUCH WITH ME,
THROUGH MY WONDERFUL AGENTS.
BUT IT WAS AN INCREDIBLE
EXPERIENCE, SO, I JUST WANT TO
SAY ONE QUITE SERIOUS THING AND
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT THIS A
LOT, BUT ACTUALLY, IT COULD BE
HORRIBLY PROPHETIC, MAD FAX, IF
WERE DON'T STOP POLLUTING OUR
ATMOSPHERE, SO, YOU KNOW, IT
COULD HAPPEN.
>> Announcer: PLEASE WELCOME
TINA FEY AND OSCAR NOMINEE,
STEVE CARELL.
>> PRODUCTION DESIGNERS TAKE US
TO BEAUTIFUL NEW WORLDS.
THE INTERIOR OF A SPACESHIP.
>> THE THING WHERE A BEAR LIVES.
>> AN ART STUDIO IN 1920s
COPENHAGEN.
>> TOM HANKS'S HOUSE?
>> A TYRANT'S MOUNTAIN LAIR IN
THE DYSTOPIAN STEAMPUNK FUTURE.
>> WHAT?
>> TINA HAS BEEN DRINKING.
BUT THAT SHOULD NOT TAKE AWAY
FROM THE BEAUTIFUL WORK OF THIS
YEAR'S NOMINEES FOR BEST
PRODUCTION DESIGN.
>> THE NONIMEES ARE --
"BRIDGE OF SPIES," PRODUCTION
DESIGN BY ADAM STOCKHAUSEN AND
SET DECORATION BY RENA DEANGELO
AND BERNHARD HENRICH.
"THE DANISH GIRL," PRODUCTION
DESIGN BY EVE STEWART AND SET
DECORATION BY MICHAEL STANDISH.
"THE MARTIAN," PRODUCTION DESIGN
BY ARTHUR MAX AND SET DECORATION
BY CELIA BOBAK.
"THE REVENANT," PRODUCTION
DESIGN BY JACK FISK AND SET
DECORATION BY HAMISH PURDY.
"MAD MAX: FURY ROAD," PRODUCTION
DESIGN BY COLIN GIBSON AND SET
DECORATION BY LISA THOMPSON.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO -- "MAD
MAX: FURY ROAD."
COLIN GIBSON AND LISA THOMPSON.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR COLIN GIBSON AND
LISA THOMPSON.
>> IT NEVER CEASES TO ANNOY ME
HOW MANY PEOPLE IT TAKES TO MAKE
ME LOOK COMPETENT, SO YOU GET
ONE OF THESE, YOU GET AN IDEA OF
THE MULTITUDES OF AUSTRALIANS,
NEW ZEALANDERS, BRITS,
AMERICANS, SOUTH AFRICANS,
NAMIBIANS, WHO ALL CAME TOGETHER
UNDER GEORGE'S VISION TO BRING
YOU A TALE ABOUT A MAN WITH
MENTAL HEALTH ISSUES, AN AMPUTEE
AMAZON AND FIVE RUNAWAY SEX
SLAVES, SO, I'D LIKE TO CHALK
THIS ONE UP AS THE FIRST OSCAR
FOR DIVERSITY.
>> THANK YOU, ACADEMY, AND THANK
YOU TO THE MOST AMAZING CREW.
THANK YOU.
>> Announcer: LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, MARGOT ROBBIE AND
OSCAR WINNER, JARED LETO.
>> EVERY ACTOR KNOWS THAT A
MEMORABLE CHARACTER IS A
COLLABORATION WITH A LOT OF
DIFFERENT PEOPLE, ESPECIALLY
WITH THIS NEXT GROUP OF
NOMINEES.
>> WITHOUT THE GENIUS
CONTRIBUTIONS OF MAKEUP ARTISTS
AND HAIR STYLISTS, WE WOULDN'T
LOSE OURSELVES IN CLASSIC FILMS
LIKE "THE GODFATHER," "ELEPHANT
MAN," "RAGING BULL," "MAGIC MIKE
2."
THINK ABOUT IT.
LET'S BE HONEST.
THEY DESERVE AN AWARD JUST FOR
PUTTING UP WITH THESE ACTORS,
NOT TO MENTION THE PROSTHETICS,
THE WIGS.
THE OCCASIONAL MERKIN.
IF YOU HAPPEN TO BE LAUGHING,
PLEASE EXPLAIN IT TO THE PERSON
NEXT TO YOU.
AND IF YOU AREN'T, GOOGLE IT.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
ACHIEVEMENT IN MAKEUP AND
HAIRSTYLING.
"MAD MAX: FURY ROAD," LESLEY
VANDERWALT, ELKA WARDEGA AND
DAMIAN MARTIN.
"THE 100-YEAR-OLD MAN WHO
CLIMBED OUT THE WINDOW AND
DISAPPEARED," LOVE LARSON AND
EVA VON BAHR.
"THE REVENANT," SIAN GRIGG,
DUNCAN JARMAN AND ROBERT
PANDINI.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO -- "MAD
MAX: FURY ROAD."
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR LESLEY
VANDERWALT, ELKA WARDEGA AND
DAMIAN MARTIN.
>> WOW.
AMAZING.
YOU CAN POP THE CORKS AT HOME,
WE'RE BRINGING HOME GOLD.
FANTASTIC.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH TO THE
ACADEMY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH TO WARNER
BROTHERS.
THANK YOU TO ALL OF FANTASTIC
CREW ACROSS THE GLOBE.
THERE WERE MANY OF THEM, AS
COLIN SAID.
A LOT OF IT HAS ALREADY BEEN
SAID BY JENNY AND COLIN, BUT
ONCE AGAIN, WE WANT TO THANK
GEORGE, WHO IS, YOU KNOW, IT WAS
HIS VISION, HIS VISION, AND
THANK YOU FOR TAKING US ALL
ALONG.
YOU'RE AMAZING, GEORGE, WE LOVE
YOU.
>> AND JUST LIKE TO THANK MY
PARENTS AND MY BEAUTIFUL
ONE-WEEK-OLD TODAY DAUGHTER AND
HER BEAUTIFUL MOTHER.
>> AND ALL OUR SUPPORTERS BACK
HOME.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU TO THE ACADEMY.
>> Announcer: LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, PLEASE WELCOME OSCAR
WINNER BENICIO DEL TORO AND
JENNIFER GARNER.
>> A "REVENANT" -- A DEAD SPIRIT
THAT COMES BACK TO LIFE TO
TERRORIZE THE LIVING.
REGARDING OUR NEXT BEST PICTURE
NOMINEE, IT REPRESENTS THE
EXTRAORDINARY POWER OF HUMAN
ENDURANCE.
INSPIRED BY TRUE EVENTS, IT'S
THE EPIC TALE OF A LEGENDARY
EXPLORER'S QUEST TO SURVIVE A
VICIOUS WINTER AND FIND
REDEMPTION AFTER HE'S BRUTALLY
MAULED AND LEFT FOR DEAD.
HERE IS "THE REVENANT."
>> YOU KNOW HOW FAR I CAME FOR
HIM.
HE'S AFRAID.
>> RIGHT HERE ON THE SMART END
OF THIS RIFLE.
BE HERE FOR AS LONG AS
NECESSARY.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
>> I DO THAT FOR YOU.
>> I AUNT AFRAID TO DIE.
I'VE DONE IT ALREADY.
>> IN OUR NEXT BEST PICTURE
NOMINEE, CIVILIZATION HAS
COLLAPSED AND THE WORLD IS A
TOXIC WASTELAND.
TWO REBELS ARE PURSUED BY A
RUTHLESS TYRANT AND HIS GANGS IN
A HIGH-OCTANE ROAD WAR.
HERE IS "MAD MAX: FURY ROAD."
>> AS THE WORLD FELL, EACH OF
US, IN OUR OWN WAY, WAS BROKEN.
IT WAS HARD TO KNOW WHO WAS MORE
CRAZY.
ME OR EVERYONE ELSE.
I AM THE ONE REDUCED TO A SINGLE
ENTITY.
SURVIVE.
MY NAME IS MAX.
>> Announcer: COMING UP, MORE
FROM CHRIS ROCK, LIVE.
¶
>>> OKAY, IT'S ALWAYS
FASCINATING TO MEET THE REAL
PEOPLE THAT THE MOVIES ARE BASED
ON.
AND SOME OF THEM ARE HERE
TONIGHT.
FROM "JOY," THE REAL JOY MANGANO
IS HERE.
GIVE IT UP FOR JOY.
FROM "SPOTLIGHT," THE BOSTON
GLOBE REPORTER, THE REAL MIKE
REZENDES IS HERE.
GIVE IT UP FOR MIKE.
AND FROM "STRAIGHT OUTTA
COMPTON," THE REAL SUGE KNIGHT
IS HERE.
GIVE IT UP FOR SUGE.
GLD TO SEE YOU COULD MAKE IT,
SUGE.
PLEASE WELCOME ONE OF TONIGHT'S
NOMINEES, RACHEL McADAMS, AND A
SHOULDA BEEN NOMINEE, MICHAEL B.
JORDAN.
>> THE UNIQUE VISUAL STYLES
COMPOSED BY OUR NEXT NOMINEES
WERE ACHIEVED BY CREATIVE USE OF
FORMATS AS VARIED AS THE STORIES
THEY CAPTURED.
>> FROM A SOFT AND SUBTLE LOVE
STORY SHOT ON SUPER
16-MILLIMETER FILM, TO A
LARGER-THAN-LIFE ACTION THRILLER
SHOT IN THE WIDESK PWIDESCREEN
70-MILLIMETER FORMAT, NOT USED
SINCE THE 1960s, HERE ARE THE
NOMINEES FOR ACHIEVEMENT IN
CINEMATOGRAPHY.
"THE HATEFUL EIGHT," ROBERT
RICHARDSON.
"CAROL," ED LACHMAN.
"SICARIO," ROGER DEAKINS.
"MAD MAX: FURY ROAD," JOHN
SEALE.
"THE REVENANT," EMMANUEL
LUBEZKI.
AND THE OSCAR GOES TO -- E MANUL
LIUBEZKI
LUBEZKI, "THE REVENANT."
>> THIS IS THE SECOND WIN FOR
EMANUEL LLUBEZKI.
HE HAS A TOTAL OF EIGHT CAREER
NOMINATIONS.
>> ACADEMY, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THIS IS INCREDIBLE.
I WANT TO SHARE IT WITH THE CAST
AND CREW, ESPECIALLY WITH MY
COME PCOMPADRE,INNARITU.
LEO AND TOM.
ALL THE PRODUCERS, REGENCY AND
FOX, ALL THE FREEDOM AND
SUPPORT.
MY WIFE, LAUREN, I LOVE YOU SO
MUCH.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
TO MY PARENTS, MY FRIENDS AND TO
ALL THE CINEMATOGRAPHERS THAT
WERE NOMINATED WITH ME, I ADMIRE
YOU SO MUCH, I LOVE YOUR WORK.
ALEJANDRO, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> Announcer: AND NOW, PLEASE
WELCOME PRIYANKA CHOPRA AND LIEV
SCHREIBER.
>> ALL NIGHT TONIGHT, WE'VE BEEN
TAKING YOU THROUGH THE
FILMMAKING PROCESS AS WE PRESENT
THIS YEAR'S OSCARS.
>> WE STARTED WITH THE SCRIPT,
ADDED IN OUR ESSENTIAL
PRODUCTION ELEMENTS -- DESIGN,
COSTUMES, HAIR AND MAKE-UP AND
CINEMATOGRAPHY.
>> ONCE SHOOTING BEGINS, THE
FOOTAGE EVENTUALLY ENDS UP IN
THE SKILLFUL HANDS OF AN EDITOR.
THE SUBTLE BRILLIANCE OF THIS
NEXT GROUP OF ARTISTS COMES
THROUGH IN THE ALMOST INVISIBLE
RHYTHMS OF GREAT FILMMAKING.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
ACHIEVEMENT IN FILM EDITING.
"THE BIG SHORT," HANK CORWIN.
>> FROM THE BOSTON GLOBE.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> "SPOTLIGHT," TOM McARDLE.
>> I WOULD JUST LIKE TO ASK A
FEW --
>> "THE REVENANT," STEPHEN
MIRRIONE.
>> "STAR WARS: THE FORCE
AWAKENS," MARYANN BRANDON AND
MARY JO MARKEY.
"MAD MAX: FURY ROAD," MARGARET
SIXEL.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
MARGARET SIXEL, "MAD MAX: FURY
ROAD."
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR MARGARET SIXEL.
>> WOW.
MAD MAX IS DOING OKAY TONIGHT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH TO THE
ACADEMY.
MAD MAX WAS THE BEST REVIEWED
FILM OF 2015.
AUDIENCES LOVED IT, AND TO BE
HONORED TONIGHT IS JUST MORE
THAN WE COULD HAVE EVER HOPED
FOR.
BUT IT TOOK ENORMOUS CREATIVE
COURAGE AND GUTS TO MAKE THIS
FILM.
SO, I WANT TO SAY THANKS TO
GEORGE MILLER, DOUG MITCHELL,
THE WHOLE CREW THAT ENDURED SIX
MONTHS IN THE DESERT TO BRING
BACK THE MOST AMAZING FOOTAGE.
IT'S IN THE EDIT ROOM THAT THE
FILM IS FINALLY FORGED.
IT'S THE FINAL REWRITE.
SO, I WANT TO THANK ALL THE
WORKING POSTS WHO WORK WITH
THEIR HANDS, HEADS AND MOST
IMPORTANTLY, THEIR HEARTS.
THANK YOU.
>> IN HONOR OF BLACK HISTORY
MONTH, THE ACADEMY OF MOTION
PICTURES AND ARTS AND SCIENCE
HAS PREPARED THIS SPECIAL
PRESENTATION.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
>> HELLO.
I'M ANGELA BASSETT.
THE ACADEMY OF MOTION PICTURE
ARTS AND SCIENCES HAS LONG
ACKNOWLEDGED PEOPLE OF COLOR.
AND TONIGHT, WE HONOR SOMEONE
WHO HAS SHATTERED BARRIERS WITH
HIS GROUNDBREAKING PERFORMANCES.
WHETHER IN SERIOUS DRAMAS LIKE
"ENEMY OF THE STATE" OR IN
WHIMSICAL PRODUCTIONS LIKE
"SHARK TALE" OR WHEN HE WAS A
FRESHER TALENT, THIS MAN HAS
LONG BEEN AN INSPIRATION TO HIS
PEOPLE.
YOU CAN CALL IT ACTOR, PRODUCER,
COMEDIAN, MUSICIAN.
BUT WE JUST LIKE TO CALL HIM
JACK BLACK.
FOR BLACK HISTORY MONTH MINUTE,
I'M ANGELA BASSETT.
>> Announcer: THE MINIONS ARE ON
THEIR WAY.
AND COMING UP, MUSIC FROM THE
WEEKND, AND LA
¶
>> Announcer: PLEASE WELCOME
CHADWICK BOSEMAN AND CHRIS
EVANS.
>> CHRIS AND I HAVE BEEN ASKED
TO PRESENT TWO AWARDS TO THE
INCREDIBLY TALENTED PEOPLE
RESPONSIBLE FOR STIRRING OUR
IMAGINATION THROUGH THE USE OF
SOUND.
>> SOUND ADDS DIMENSION TO FILM,
WHETHER IT BE SIMPLE AND
NATURALISTIC OR TERRIFYING AND
OUT OF THIS WORLD.
FIRST UP, HERE ARE THE NOMINEES
FOR ACHIEVEMENT IN SOUND
EDITING.
¶
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
"MAD MAX: FURY ROAD," MARK
MANGINI AND DAVID WHITE.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR DAVID WHITE.
THE FIRST WIN AND FOURTH
NOMINATION FOR MARK MANGINI, WHO
WAS PREVIOUSLY TOM NATE DNOMINA
"A
"ALADDIN" AND "THE FIFTH
ELEMENT."
>> YES!
>> FOR THOUSANDS OF YEARS, WE'VE
BEEN TELLING STORIES IN THE DARK
AROUND A FLICKERING LIGHT.
WHETHER A CAMPFIRE OR A
PROJECTOR, DAVID AND I DO IT
WITH SOUND.
GEORGE MILLER WOULD TELL US, MAD
MAX IS A FILM WE SEE WITH OUR
EARS.
I KNEW SOUND COULD TELL MY
STORY, BUT NOTHING QUITE LIKE
THIS.
SOUND ARTISTS ARE STORY TELLERS.
THANK YOU, GEORGE.
I HOPE TO SEE YOU AROUND THE
NEXT CAMPFIRE.
>> YEAH, I'M SO PROUD, SO PROUD
TO WORK ON THIS LOUD, LOUD, LOUD
FILM THAT ACTUALLY HAD SILENCE
IN IT.
SO GOOD TO WORK WITH THIS GUY
AND I'M PROUD TO REPRESENT ALL
MY AUSTRALIAN COLLEAGUES.
YEAH!
>> YEAH!
GO GEORGE!
>> ALL RIGHT.
WHY NOT?
>> THE NEXT OSCAR IS FOR SOUND
MIXING.
>> IT RECOGNIZES THE COMPLEX ART
OF PRECISELY MANIPULATING EVERY
SINGLE EFFECT, FROM THE FAINTEST
BREATH TO THE LOUDEST EXPLOSION.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES.
[ SCREAMING ]
>> USE THE CABLES FROM THE
GUIDELINE.
ANCHOR IT WITH THE ROVER!
>> WATCH OUT!
>> AHH!
>> CAN I TRY THAT?
I LIKE THIS THING!
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
"MAD MAX: FURY ROAD," CHRIS
JENKINS, GREGG RUDLOFF AND BEN
OSMO.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR BEN OSMO.
THE THIRD WIN AND FIFTH
NOMINATION FOR CHRIS JENKINS.
AND THE THIRD WIN AND SEVENTH
NOMINATION FOR GREGG RUDLOFF.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
FIRST OF ALL, BIG SHOUTOUT TO
THE ACADEMY.
THANK YOU FOR ALL YOUR SUPPORT
OF OUR CREATIVE CRAFT.
TO OUR FELLOW NOMINEES, WE CAN'T
SAY ENOUGH.
WE ARE SO PROUD TO BE IN YOUR
COMPANY AND WE'RE SO PROUD TO
REPRESENT TONIGHT.
TO GEORGE MILLER, YOU ARE THE
HEART AND SOUL OF ALL OF THIS.
CAN'T SAY ENOUGH ABOUT YOU.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU
FOR GIVING US THE OPPORTUNITY.
TO WARNER BROTHERS, TO ALL OF
OUR FRIENDS THERE, THE PEOPLE
THAT SUPPORT US, AND MOST OF
ALL, TO OUR FAMILIES, TO JEAN
AND TO SUE, TO JAMES UP IN THE
CHEAP SEATS, THANK YOU ALL VERY,
VERY MUCH.
>> THANKS, EVERYBODY.
THANKS TO ALL THE AUSTRALIANS,
NAMI
NAMIBIANS.
>> YOU SEE?
>> GO!
¶
>> Announcer: AND NOW, HERE IS
ACTOR AND PERFORMANCE CAPTURE
ARTIST, ANDY SERKIS.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING TO KNOW
ABOUT VISUAL EFFECTS IS THAT NO
MATTER HOW REVOLUTIONARY OR
SOPHISTICATED THE TECHNOLOGY WE
USE IS, IT STILL TAKES BEATING
HEARTS AND MINDS OF HUMAN
BECOMES TO MAKE MOVIE MAGIC.
AS FILM MAKERS AND AS ACTORS IN
THE 21st CENTURY, WE CAN CREATE
ANY WORLD WE WANT.
WE CAN PLAY ANYTHING WE WANT.
CHRIS, IF YOU WERE TO PUT ON A
MOTION CAPTURE SUIT RIGHT NOW,
YOU COULD PLAY A PLANET
THREATENING MONSTER TO DONALD
TRUMP AND -- ACTUALLY, THAT'S
NOT VERY DIVERSE, BUT ANYWAY.
HAVING HAD THE HONOR OF WORKING
WITH MANY OF THE GREATEST, I
HAVE A REAL SPECIAL APPRECIATION
FOR THE MEN AND WOMEN THAT
DEDICATE THEMSELVES AND FIND THE
DELICATE BALANCE BETWEEN
ILLUSION AND FLESH AND BLOOD.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR THIS
YEAR'S ACHIEVEMENTS IN VISUAL
EFFECTS.
"STAR WARS: THE FORCE AWAKENS,"
ROGER GUYETT, PATRICK TUBACH,
NEAL SCANLAN AND CHRIS CORBOULD.
"EX MACHINA," ANDREW WHITEHURST,
PAUL NORRIS, MARK ARDINGTON AND
SARA BENNETT.
"THE REVENANT," RICH MCBRIDE,
MATTHEW SHUMWAY, JASON SMITH AND
CAMERON WALDBAUER.
"THE MARTIAN," RICHARD STAMMERS,
ANDERS LANGLANDS, CHRIS LAWRENCE
AND STEVEN WARNER.
"MAD MAX: FURY ROAD," ANDREW
JACKSON, TOM WOOD, DAN OLIVER
AND ANDY WILLIAMS.
AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
"EXMACHINA."
ANDREW WHITEHURST, PAUL NORRIS,
MARK ARDINGTON AND SARA BENNETT.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR ANDREW
WHITEHURST, PAUL NORRIS, MARK
ARDINGTON AND SARA BENNETT.
>> I'M REALLY BAD AT PREDICTING
THIS, APPARENTLY.
THIS IS SO UTTERLY UNEXPECTED.
VISUAL EFFECTS IS MASSIVELY A
TEAM GAME.
MORE SO MAYBE THAN ANY OTHER
DEPARTMENT.
WE HAVE TO THANK PEOPLE IN TWO
DIRECTIONS.
WE'VE GOT TO THANK THE STUDIO,
WE'VE GOT TO THANK THE
PROD
PRODUCTION, ALEX FOR BEING AN
AMAZING DIRECTOR.
AND WE HAVE TO THANK THE TEAMS
OF ARTISTS, PRODUCTION AND
TECHNICAL PERSONNEL AND DOUBLE
NEGATIVE AND UTOPIA WHO ARE
AMAZING.
WITHOUT THEM, WE ARE NOTHING.
THANK YOU SO, SO MUCH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Announcer: LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, PLEASE WELCOME OLIVIA
MUNN AND JASON SEGEL.
>> PEOPLE OFTEN COMPLAIN --
JASON, THE OSCARS ARE TOO SHORT.
YOU SIMPLY DON'T GIVE OUT ENOUGH
AWARDS.
>> WHICH IS WHY WE HELD A WHOLE
OTHER OSCARS TWO WEEKS BEFORE
TONIGHT THAT'S SO EXCLUSIVE,
NONE OF YOU COULD COME.
THE ANNUAL SCI-TECH AWARDS.
YOU KNOW IT.
>> THE ACADEMY'S SCI-TECH AWARDS
HONOR THE WIZARDS WHO NOT ONLY
SEE THE FUTURE OF MOVIES, BUT
INVENT NEW WAYS TO BRING THAT
VISION TO LIFE.
>> JASON AND I WERE HONORED TO
HOST THIS YEAR'S CEREMONY AND
BASK IN THE ACHIEVEMENTS OF
HOLLYWOOD'S TOP ENGINEERS,
PROGRAMMERS AND SCIENTISTS TO
FIND OUT THE EXACT DAY ROBOTS
TAKE OVER.
AUGUST 27.
>> HERE ARE SOME HIGHLIGHTS.
>> THIS YEAR'S 11 SICIENTIFIC
AND TECHNICAL AWARDS WENT TO --
A GIGANTIC INFLATABLE GREEN
SCREEN.
>> FOUR DIFFERENT MEDIA REVIEW
STATIONS EACH ALLOWING
SIMULTANEOUS COLLABORATION BY
ARTISTS AROUND THE WORLD.
>> AN AMAZING COLOR MONITOR.
>> AND A REVOLUTIONARY ANIMATION
SYSTEM THAT USES 3-D PRINTERS.
>> AND THEN THERE WAS THE --
IMAGE SHAKER!
A DEVICE THAT ALLOWS CAMERAMEN
TO CREATE EARTHQUAKES ON DEMAND.
>> LET'S NOT LEAVE OUT THE
SOFTWARE.
THERE WAS A 3-D TEXTURING TOOL.
>> AND A TRACKING SYSTEM THAT
CREATES FANTASTICALLY REAL
IMAGES.
>> LASTLY, THE ACADEMY SALUTED
SMPTE, FOR 100 YEARS OF SETTING
THE TECHNICAL STANDARDS FOR OUR
INDUSTRY.
>> ON BEHALF OF THE SOCIETY OF
MOTION PICTURE AND TELEVISION
ENGINEERS, I THANK THE ACADEMY
FOR THIS PRESTIGIOUS
RECOGNITION.
>> THIS IS NOT THE WAY TO OUR
SEATS!
[ R2-D2 BEEPING ]
>> I FORGOT THE TICKETS?
HOW DARE YOU!
THE TICKETS WERE YOUR JOB,
NITWIT.
DON'T ENCOURAGE HIM, BB-8.
[ R2-D2 BEEPING ]
>> ACTUALLY, I DO NOT LOOK LIKE
HIM.
HE HAPPENS TO LOOK RATHER LIKE
ME.
HOW DO YOU THINK WE MADE IT THIS
FAR?
[ BB-8 BEEPING ]
>> OH, MY!
IT IS JOHN WILLIAMS!
I ALWAYS ENJOY HEARING HIS
MUSIC.
HE'S SO VERY TALENTED FOR A
HUMAN.
HIS 50th OSCAR NOMINATION
TONIGHT?
MY GOODNESS!
AND HE HAS ALREADY WON FIVE FOR
COMPOSING.
NO WONDER HE HAS A GOOD SEAT.
[ BB-8 BEEPING ]
>> YES, WE MUST FIND OURS AT
ONCE.
COME ALONG, YOU TWO.
HMM.
HE IS QUITE HANDSOME, I SUPPOSE.
WAIT!
WAIT FOR ME!
R-2!
BB-8!
DON'T LEAVE ME!
L RIGHT.
I'VE BEEN OUT HERE WORKING FOR A
COUPLE OF WEEKS, FOR A LITTLE
WHILE, RIGHT?
AND I'VE BEEN AWAY FROM MY TWO
DAUGHTERS AT A VERY IMPORTANT
TIME IN THEIR LIFE.
I HAVE MISSED MOST OF GIRL SCOUT
COOKIE SEASON.
I HAVEN'T BEEN THERE TO HELP
THEM SELL COOKIES, AND LAST
NIGHT, ZORA, MY YOUNGEST CALLED
ME UP, SAID, DADDY, HOW COME WE
NEVER SELL THE MOST COOKIES.
HOW COME MRS. DUNN WINS EVERY
YEAR?
IT WOULD BEEN SO MUCH TO MY TWO
LITTLE GIRLS IF WE COULD BEAT
LINDA DUNN.
SO, I WANT YOU TO REACH INTO
YOUR MILLIONAIRE POCKETS AND I
WANT YOU TO BUY SOME OF MY
DAUGHTER'S GIRL SCOUT COOKIES.
LOOK AT MY BABIES UP THERE.
ARE YOU GOING TO DENY MY
PRINCESSES SOME COOKIES?
ALL RIGHT, TINA FEY!
GET THAT MONEY, GIRL.
MAKE THAT MONEY.
YEAH, TINA FEY.
CHARLIZE THERON.
YES.
OKAY.
YOU GET THEM.
LEO!
YOU MADE $30 MILLION.
COME ON.
COME ON!
MICHAEL B. JORDAN'S HERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
NO, NO, YOU GOT ENOUGH GIRLS.
COME ON.
LET'S GET THIS MONEY.
LET'S GET THIS MONEY!
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
GIVE IT TO THE GIRLS.
OH, LOU GOSSETT.
WATCH OUT NOW.
YOUDIABETES.
YOU CAN'T HAVE THESE.
WHILE THIS IS GOING ON, LET'S
GET BACK TO THE AWARDS.
HERE TO PRESENT THE OSCAR FOR
BEST ANIMATED SHORT FILM, PLEASE
WELCOME THE MINIONS!
>> THANK YOU!
AH --
[ LAUGHTER ]
"BEAR STORY," GABRIEL OSORIO AND
PATO ESCALA.
"PROLOGUE," RICHARD WILLIAMS AND
IMOGEN SUTTON.
"SANJAY'S SUPER TEAM," SANJAY
PATEL AND NICOLE GRINDLE.
"WE CAN'T LIVE WITHOUT COSMOS,"
KONSTANTIN BRONZIT.
"WORLD OF TOMORROW," DON
HERTZFELDT.
>> "BEAR STORY."
THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND NAME
NATION FOR GABRIEL OSORIO AND
PATO ESCALA.
>> WOW.
>> WE ARE REALLY HAPPY RIGHT
NOW.
WE WANT TO THANK THE ACADEMY,
OUR FAMILIES, AND EVERYONE IN
CHILE WHO HAVE SUPPORTED US AND
TRUSTS IN OUR WORK.
PERSONALLY, I WANT TO DEDICATE
THIS ACHIEVEMENT TO MY
GRANDFATHER, WHO IS THE ONE WHO
INSPIRED THIS STORY, AND TO ALL
THE PEOPLE, LIKE HIM, WHO HAVE
SUFFERED IN EXILE.
WE REALLY HOPE THAT THIS MUST
NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
THANKS.
>> THANK YOU, ALL.
WE ARE FROM A SMALL COUNTRY
CALLED CHILE.
THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR FOR OUR
COUNTRY.
SO, IT'S VERY IMPORTANT FOR
US -- THANK YOU ALL.
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
>> Announcer: TO PRESENT THE
AWARD FOR BEST ANIMATED FEATURE
AS THEY CELEBRATE THE 20th
ANNIVERSARY OF "TOY STORY," HERE
ARE BUZZ LIGHTYEAR AND WOODY.
>> WOW, BUZZ, CAN YOU BELIEVE,
IT'S BEEN 20 YEARS SINCE YOU AND
I MET IN ANDY'S ROOM?
>> YOU MEAN 20 YEARS SINCE YOU
TRIED TO TERMINATE ME BY PUSHING
ME OUT THE WINDOW IN ANDY'S
ROOM.
>> COME ON, BUZZ.
I TOLD YOU, THAT WAS AN
ACCIDENT.
BESIDES, IF IT WASN'T FOR ME,
YOU'D STILL BE WALKING AROUND
LIKE A CLUELESS SPACE RANGER.
HI, I'M BUZZ LIGHTYEAR.
I COME IN PEACE.
TO INFINITY AND BEYOND.
>> REALLY?
YOU'RE GOING TO MOCK ME IN FRONT
OF 900 MILLION PEOPLE AT THE
ACADEMY AWARDS.
>> LOOK, BUZZ, AN ALIEN.
>> WHERE?
>> IF IT WASN'T FOR ME, YOU'D BE
WALKING AROUND LIKE AN OLD
COWBOY TV STAR.
HEY!
HOWDY HEY, YOU'RE MY FAVORITE
DEPUTY.
YEE-HAW!
RIDE LIKE THE WIND.
>> ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH ALREADY.
THE NOMINEES FOR ANIMATED --
REACH FOR THE SKY!
COME ON, BUZZ.
>> THE NOMINEES FOR ANIMATED
FEATURE FILM ARE --
"SHAUN THE SHEEP MOVIE," MARK
BURTON AND RICHARD STARZAK.
"ANOMALISA," CHARLIE KAUFMAN,
DUKE JOHNSON AND ROSA TRAN.
"BOY AND THE WORLD," ALÊ ABREU.
"WHEN MARNIE WAS THERE,"
HIROMASA YONEBAYASHI AND
YOSHIAKI NISHIMURA.
"INSIDE OUT," PETE DOCTER AND
JONAS RIVERA.
AND THE ENVELOPE PLEASE.
>> THANKS, GUYS.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
>> "INSIDE OUT", PETE DOCTER AND
JONAS RIVERA.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
SECOND NOMINATION FOR JONAS
RIVERA.
THE SECOND NOMINATION FOR PETE
DOCTER, WHO IS ALSO NOMINATED
FOR BEST SCREENPLAY THIS YEAR
FOR "INSIDE OUT."
HE TOOK HOME HIS FIRST OSCAR FOR
"UP."
>> WE ARE SO LUCKY, BECAUSE,
REGARDLESS OF A GOLD MAN OR NOT,
WE GET TO MAKE STUFF.
>> RIGHT, WE DO, AND ON THIS
FILM, EVERY SINGLE STORY BOARD,
EVERY SINGLE FRAME, CUT, LINE OF
DIALOGUE, EVERY SINGLE PIXEL WAS
DONE BY THE AMAZING ARTISTS WE
WORK WITH AT PIXAR.
THEY SHOULD BE UP THERE WITH US
TONIGHT.
WE LOVE THEM.
ALONG WITH THE AMAZING CAST.
BEST CAST EVER, WE LOVE YOU.
>> WE WANT TO THANK OUR WIVES,
AMANDA --
>> MICHELLE.
>> OUR KIDS.
THIS WAS BORN FROM WATCHING OUR
KIDS GROW UP, WHICH IS NOT EASY.
IF YOU ARE IN JUNIOR HIGH, HIGH
SCHOOL, WORKING IT OUT,
SUFFERING, THERE ARE DAYS YOU
ARE GOING TO FEEL SAD, ANGRY,
GOING TO BE SCARED.
THAT'S NOTHING YOU CAN CHOOSE,
BUT YOU CAN MAKE STUFF.
MAKE FILMS, DRAW, WRITE, IT WILL
MAKE A WORLD OF DIFFERENCE.
THANK YOU.
>> PLEASE WELCOME NEXT YEAR'S
HOST, KEVIN HART.
>> HELLO.
HEY, MAN, MAKE SOME NOISE FOR
CHRIS ROCK, DOING AN AMAZING JOB
UP HERE.
MY GUY.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, BEFORE I DO
THIS, I WANT TO TAKE A SECOND TO
GET SOMETHING OFF MY CHEST.
FIRST AND FOREMOST, I'M A
POSITIVE GUY.
I FEED OFF POSITIVE ENERGY AND I
FEEL LIKE POSITIVE OVERALL BEATS
NEGATIVE.
WITH THAT BEING SAID, I WANT TO
TAKE A MOMENT TO APPLAUD ALL OF
MY ACTORS AND ACTRESSES OF COLOR
THAT DIDN'T GET NOMINATED
TONIGHT.
THE REASON WHY I SAY THAT IS
BECAUSE I WANT THEM TO
UNDERSTAND THAT TONIGHT SHOULD
NOT DETERMINE THE HARD WORK AND
EFFORT THAT YOU PUT INTO YOUR
CRAFT.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, WE LOVE
WHAT WE DO AND WE ARE BREAKING
MAJOR GROUND DOING IT.
THESE PROBLEMS OF TODAY WILL
BECOME PROBLEMS OF THE OLD.
LET'S NOT LET THIS NEGATIVE
ISSUE OF DIVERSITY BEAT US.
LET'S CONTINUE TO DO WHAT WE DO
BEST AND WORK HARD.
WITH THAT BEING SAID --
CONGRATULATIONS ON AN AMAZING
YEAR, OKAY?
THAT'S FROM ME TO THEM.
CONGRATULATIONS.
I ALSO WANT TO SAY THAT I ONLY
CAME TONIGHT BECAUSE I THOUGHT
FOR SURE THAT I WOULD GET A SEAT
IN THE FRONT ROW AND IT STILL
DIDN'T HAPPEN.
I DON'T KNOW WHY, BUT I THOUGHT
THIS WAS THE YEAR TO KIND OF
SHOW MY FACE MORE IN THE FRONT
ROW BECAUSE OF ALL OF THE BLACK
STUFF THAT WAS GOING ON.
I WAS LIKE, THEY'LL GO TO ME.
AND YOU DIDN'T.
BUT WHATEVER.
IT'S OKAY.
I HAVE A SUIT WITH SHINY STUFF
ON IT, SO, I STILL MADE A
STATEMENT.
OKAY, GUYS, RIGHT NOW, LET'S
MOVE ON WITH THE SHOW.
LISTEN.
OUR SECOND NOMINATED SONG
TONIGHT WAS A BIG HIT FOR THIS
NEXT PERFORMER, WHO ACTUALLY
DOMINATED THE R & B CHARTS IN
2016.
PERFORMING "EARNED IT" FROM
"FIFTY SHADES OF GREY," LADIES
AND GENTLEMEN, PLEASE MAKE SOME
NOISE FOR MY GUY, THE WEEKND.
¶
¶ YOU MAKE IT LOOK LIKE IT'S
MAGIC
'CAUSE I SEE NOBODY
NOBODY BUT YOU, YOU, YOU ¶
¶ I'M NEVER CONFUSED
HEY, HEY I'M SO USED TO BEING
USED ¶
¶ SO I LOVE WHEN YOU CALL
UNEXPECTED
'CAUSE I HATE WHEN THE MOMENT'S
EXPECTED ¶
¶ SO I'MA CARE FOR
YOU, YOU, YOU ¶
¶ I'MA CARE FOR
YOU, YOU, YOU, YOU YEAH ¶
¶ 'CAUSE, GIRL, YOU'RE PERFECT
YOU'RE ALWAYS WORTH IT ¶
¶ AND YOU DESERVE IT
THE WAY YOU WORK IT ¶
¶ 'CAUSE, GIRL, YOU
EARN EARNED IT ¶
¶ GIRL YOU EARN EARNED IT ¶
¶ ON THAT LONELY NIGHT
WE SAID IT WOULDN'T BE LOVE ¶
¶ BUT WE FELT THE RUSH
IT MADE US BELIEVE IT WAS ONLY
US ¶
¶ CONVINCED WE WERE BROKEN
INSIDE
YEAH INSIDE YEAH ¶
¶ 'CAUSE, GIRL, YOU'RE PERFECT
YOU'RE ALWAYS WORTH IT ¶
¶ AND YOU DESERVE IT
THE WAY YOU WORK IT ¶
¶ 'CAUSE, GIRL, YOU
EARN EARNED IT ¶
¶ GIRL YOU EARN EARNED IT ¶
>> Announcer: 40 YEARS AFTER HIS
BIG SCREEN DEBUT, WILL ROCKY
BALBOA KNOCK OUT HIS OPPONENTS?
WE'LL FIND OUT, WHEN THE OSCARS
RETURN, LIVE FROM THE DOLBY
THEATRE, ON ABC.
>> Announcer: PLEASE WELCOME
ACADEMY AWARD WINNERS KATE
WINSLET AND REESE WITHERSPOON.
>> A GAME OF CAT AND MOUSE
DURING THE MOST FRIGID MOMENTS
OF THE COLD WAR SHAPES THE STORY
OF OUR NEXT BEST PICTURE
NOMINEE.
WHEN A SOVIET SPY IS CAPTURED
AND PUT ON TRIAL, ONE AMERICAN
MUST DEFEND HIS COUNTRY'S
FUNDAMENTAL PRINCIPLES OF
JUSTICE AND DECENCY AGAINST
ENEMIES BOTH FOREIGN AND
DOMESTIC.
HERE IS "BRIDGE OF SPIES."
>> I PLEDGE ALLEEN LEE JANS TO
THE FLAG.
>> WE HAVE ENGAGED IN A WAR WITH
THE SOVIET UNION.
>> SOVIETS GOT THEIR GUY.
WE WANT YOU TO NEGOTIATE THE
SWAP.
>> I'M AN INSURANCE AGENT.
>> YOU WORK FOR THE CIA NOW.
>> THE FAMILY OF A MAN TRYING TO
FREE A TRAITOR.
>> YOU SHOULD BE CAREFUL.
>> YOU DO NOT KNOW WHO YOU ARE
DEALING WITH.
WHAT'S THE NEXT MOVE WHEN YOU
DON'T KNOW WHAT THE GAME IS.
>> AND JUSTICE FOR ALL.
>> OUR NEXT BEST PICTURE NOMINEE
RECOUNTS A TRUE STORY OF
FEARLESS LOCAL JOURNALISM.
DESPITE OBSTACLES AT EVERY TURN,
A TEAM OF UNDAUNTED JOURNALISTS
INVESTIGATES ALLEGATIONS OF
SEXUAL ABUSE IN ONE OF THE
WORLD'S MOST POWERFUL
INSTITUTIONS.
HERE IS "SPOTLIGHT."
>> THE BOSTON PRIEST ABUSED 80
KIDS.
THE CHURCH DID NOTHING.
THIS STRIKES ME AS AN ESSENTIAL
STORY TO A LOCAL PAPER.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOUR TEAM WOULD
DO?
>> WE'RE GOING AFTER THE SYSTEM.
>> WE'RE GOING TO TELL THIS
STORY.
WE'RE GOING TO TELL IT RIGHT.
>> THIS IS NOT JUST BOSTON.
AND IT GOES RIGHT TO THE
VATICAN.
>> WE GOT TO GO WITH THIS NOW.
>> NO, I'M NOT GOING TO RUSH THE
STORY.
IF IT TAKES A VILLAGE TO RAISE A
CHIDE, IT TAKES A VILLAGE TO
ABUSE ONE.
>> HOW DO YOU SAY NO TO GOD,
RIGHT?
>> POWERFUL.
THANK YOU.
WELL, TONIGHT, I'VE BEEN CALLING
OUT HOLLYWOOD FOR ITS LACK OF
DIVERSITY AND I DON'T WANT TO
JUST COMPLAIN.
I WANT TO HELP SOLVE THE PROBLEM
AND THAT'S GOING TO TAKE A FRESH
PERSPECTIVE.
SO, I WENT FAR AWAY FROM
HOLLYWOOD, I WENT AS FAR AWAY AS
I COULD.
I WENT TO MY FAVORITE MOVIE
THEATER IN COMPTON.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
¶
>> IN YOUR OWN WORDS, WHAT IS
THE OSCAR CONTROVERSY ABOUT?
>> WELL, I GUESS IT'S ABOUT
GIVING BLACKS A CHANCE TO WIN.
>> WERE YOU UPSET WHEN YOU HEARD
THERE WERE NO BLACK NOMINEES
THIS YEAR?
>> ACTUALLY -- I MEAN, I WASN'T
SURPRISED, BUT I MEAN, KIND OF
BOTHERED ME A LITTLE BIT.
>> IT WAS TERRIBLE.
>> I MEAN, LIKE, SMACK A WHITE
MAN BAD?
>> ALMOST.
YOU STILL GO TO JAIL IN L.A. FOR
SMACKING A WHITE MAN.
>> YOU GET THREE YEARS FOR A
HARD LOOK.
>> RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
>> DID YOU THINK ABOUT RIOTING
AND LOOTING?
>> NO, WE DID THAT ALREADY AND I
DIDN'T GET NOTHING THE FIRST
TIME.
I WAS TOO LITTLE.
>> THIS WAS YOUR TIME TO GET
THAT TV.
>> I KNOW, RIGHT?
>> SO, DID YOU SEE ANY OF THE
OSCAR-NOMINATED MOVIES.
YOU SEE "SPOTLIGHT?"
>> NO, WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
>> NO.
>> DO YOU FEEL THAT "TRUMBO"
SHOULD HAVE BEEN A BIGGER HIT?
>> DID YOU SEE "THE BIG SHORT?"
>> I DID NOT.
>> "BRIDGE OF SPIES?"
>> WHERE ARE YOU GETTING THESE
MOVIES FROM?
>> THEY'RE REAL MOVIES.
>> I COME TO THE MOVIES ALL THE
TIME.
>> THESE ARE REAL MOVIES.
>> LIKE, IN LONDON AND STUFF?
>> DID YOU SEE "BRIDGE OF
SPIES?"
>> NO.
NO, I DID NOT.
I HAVE NEVER HEARD OF THAT
MOVIE.
>> TOM HANKS.
>> I'VE HEARD OF HIM.
>> AND STEVEN SPIELBERG.
>> DID YOU SEE "STRAIGHT OUTTA
COMPTON."
>> I DID SEE THAT.
>> I LOVED IT.
>> OF COURSE.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> YES, I DID.
>> OH, HELL YES.
>> WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE MOVIE OF
ALL TIME?
>> "SUPER FLY."
NOW, WHAT WAS YOUR FAVORITE
WHITE MOVIE OF THE YEAR?
>> OH, MAN.
>> "BY THE SEA."
WITH -- BRAD PITT AND ANGELINA
JOLIE.
>> WOW.
NOT EVEN THEY WOULD SAY THAT.
HERE'S A REAL OSCAR.
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU THIS AND I
WANT YOU TO LOOK INTO THAT
CAMERA AND GIVE YOUR SPEECH.
I WANT YOU TO TELL HOLLYWOOD HOW
YOU FEEL RIGHT NOW.
>> UM -- FIRST AND FORE MOST,
I'D LIKE TO THANK GOD.
>> THIS SHOULD BE NOT JUST
WHITE, IT SHOULD BE ASIAN,
HISPANIC, THERE'S SO MUCH TALENT
OUT THERE OF ALL RACES.
>> I FEEL LIKE MOST OF Y'ALL
KIND OF OWE US, SO, YOU'RE NOT
REALLY HIP TO, WHAT, THE YOUNGER
PEOPLE LIKE.
>> I LIKE TO THANK THE ACADEMY
FOR NOMINATING YET ANOTHER WHITE
PERSON THIS YEAR.
UM -- I WOULD COMPLAIN, BUT IT
WAS ME, SO, MAYBE I'LL COMPLAIN
NEXT YEAR.
>> YOU GIVE BLACK ACTORS MORE
AWARDS, BECAUSE THEY DESERVE IT
AND THEY WORK HARD FOR IT JUST
LIKE ANYBODY ELSE.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
AMERICA.
YEAH.
>> I TAKE THIS HOME.
>> NO, NO.
>> WHAT?
>> Announcer: PLEASE WELCOME
LAST YEAR'S OSCAR-WINNING
SUPPORTING ACTRESS, PATRICIA
ARQUETTE.
>> CONSIDER FIVE POWERFUL
PERFORMANCES, EACH ONE
COMPELLING, ORIGINAL, UNIQUE.
AN EX-NEUROLOGIST TURNED
FINANCIAL GENIUS.
A DISLOYAL AND SADISTIC FUR
TRAPPER.
A PERSUASIVE INVESTIGATIVE
JOURNALIST.
A SOVIET SPY, PIVOTAL TO A
PRISONER EXCHANGE.
AND AN AGING FIGHTER NAMED
ROCKY BALBOA.
THESE ARE THE CHARACTERS GIVEN
THOUGHTFUL PORTRAYALS BY THE MEN
NOMINATED FOR PERFORMANCE BY AN
ACTOR IN A SUPPORTING ROLE.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES.
CHRISTIAN BALE, "THE BIG SHORT."
>> THE HOUSING MARKET IS PROPPED
UP ON THESE BAD LOANS.
IT'S A TIME BOMB.
I WANT TO SHORT IT.
>> THROUGH WHAT INSTRUMENT,
MICHAEL?
THERE ARE NO INSURANCE CONTRACTS
OR OPTIONS FOR MORTGAGE BONDS.
THE BONDS ARE TOO STABLE.
>> LAWRENCE -- JUST -- THIS IS
WHAT I'M GOING TO DO.
I AM GOING TO GET A BANK TO MAKE
ME ONE.
>> TOM HARDY, "THE REVENANT."
>> YOU LIED TO ME.
I HAVE THE SKILLS AND THE SENSE
OF YOU, BOY.
THERE'S NO POINT, YOU
UNDERSTAND?
GOD GIVETH, GOD TAKETH AWAY.
>> MARK RUFFALO, "SPOTLIGHT."
>> THEY KNEW AND THEY LET IT
HAPPEN TO KIDS.
OKAY?
IT COULD HAVE BEEN YOU.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN ME.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN ANY OF US.
WE GOT TO NAIL THESE SCUM BAGS.
WE HAVE TO SHOW PEOPLE THAT
NOBODY CAN GET AWAY WITH THIS.
NOT A PRIEST OR A CARDINAL OR A
FREAKING POPE.
>> MARK RYLANCE, "BRIDGE OF
SPIES."
>> WAITING FOR ANOTHER MAN?
>> YEP.
>> YOU WANT HIM, TOO?
>> I WANT HIM.
>> DOESN'T MATTER WHAT HE WANTS.
I'M IN CHARGE AND YOU ARE FREE
TO GO.
PLEASE GO.
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
>> I CAN WAIT.
>> SYLVESTER STALLONE, "CREED."
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT I'M
DOING HERE.
I GOT OTHER PLANS IN MY LIFE AND
THIS WASN'T PART OF IT.
YOUR FATHER WAS SPECIAL.
TELL YOU THE TRUTH, I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'RE SPECIAL.
ONLY YOU WILL KNOW THAT.
I AIN'T GOING TO COME OVERNIGHT.
YOU ARE GOING TO TAKE A BEATING.
YOU ARE GOING TO GET KNOCKED
OUT, YOU'RE GOING TO GET UP AND
WE'RE GOING TO SEE IF YOU GOT
THE RIGHT THING.
BUT YOU GOT TO WORK HARD.
I SWEAR TO GOD, IF YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO DO IT -- I'M OUT.
>> OH, SORRY.
AND THE OSCAR GOES TO -- MARK
RYLANCE, "BRIDGE OF SPIES."
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR MARK RYLANCE.
>> I'VE ALWAYS -- I'VE ALWAYS
JUST ADORED STORIES, HEARING
THEM, SEEING THEM, BEING IN
THEM, SO, FOR ME TO HAVE THE
CHANCE TO WORK WITH, I THINK,
ONE OF THE GREATEST STORYTELLERS
OF OUR TIME, STEVEN SPIELBERG,
HAS JUST BEEN SUCH AN HONOR.
AND UNLIKE SOME OF THE LEADERS
WE'RE BEING PRESENTED WITH THESE
DAYS, HE LEADS WITH SUCH LOVE,
HE IS SURROUNDED BY MASTERS IN
EVERY CRAFT, AND NOT THE LEAST,
MR. TOM HANKS.
I'M SO PLEASED THAT OUR FILM HAS
BEEN NOMINATED SO MANY TIMES,
AND AS A FACE OF THE FILM, I
MEET MANY PEOPLE IN THE STREETS
AND IT'S LOVELY TO HAVE THEM,
THEY ARE ALWAYS SAYING, WOULD IT
HELP, AND ALL THAT STUFF.
AND IF YOU EVER WONDER ABOUT
ACTING WITH TOM HANKS, WOULD IT
HELP, THE ANSWER IS CLEARLY YES.
I WANT TO JUST SAY THANK YOU TO
MY FELLOW NOMINEES, I DON'T KNOW
HOW THEY SEPARATE MY ACTING FROM
YOUR GLORIOUS ACTING IN THESE
WONDERFUL FILMS THAT YOU ARE IN.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THEY SEPARATED
THE FIVE OF US FROM ALL THE
OTHER SUPPORTING ACTORS WHO ARE
MAKING FILMS AT THE MOMENT.
IT'S A WONDERFUL TIME TO BE AN
ACTOR AND I'M PROUD TO BE PART
OF IT.
THANK YOU.
>> Announcer: COMING UP, LOUIS
C.K., MORE FROM CHRIS ROCK, LADY
GAGA PERFORMS AND A SPECIAL
TRIBUTE FROM DAVE GROHL.
¶
>> I KNOW YOU'RE HUNGRY.
YOU WISH YOU GOT A COOKIE RIGHT
NOW, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW OUR NEXT PRESENTER FROM
HIS SHOW "HORACE AND PETE" AND
HIS WORK ON THE EMMY-WINNING
"CHRIS ROCK SHOW."
PLEASE WELCOME LOUIS C.K.
>> THAT'S GOOD, MAN, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
I'M HERE TO PRESENT THE AWARD
FOR BEST DOCUMENTARY SHORT FILM.
WHICH IS MY FAVORITE AWARD.
THIS IS EASILY MY FAVORITE
SUBJECT.
IT REALLY IS.
THIS IS THE ONE AWARD THAT HAS
THE OPPORTUNITY TO CHANGE A
LIFE.
BECAUSE, I MEAN, I'M HAPPY FOR
ALL OF YOU, BUT YOU CAME HERE
WINNERS AND YOU ARE LEAVING
MILLIONAIRES.
NOT GOING TO MAKE THAT BIG A
DIFFERENCE.
THE REST OF THE OSCARS ARE GOING
TO MANSIONS AND THE HOME OF
PEOPLE WITH GOOD UNIONS.
THIS IS DOCUMENTARY SHORT FILM.
YOU CANNOT -- IT'S NOT EVEN
DOCUMENTARY FEATURE, YOU KNOW?
AL GORE GOT ONE OF THOSE AND
MICHAEL MOORE.
THIS IS -- NO, YOU CANNOT MAKE A
DIME ON THIS.
THESE PEOPLE WILL NEVER BE RICH
AS LONG AS THEY LIVE.
SO, THIS OSCAR MEANS SOMETHING,
BECAUSE ALL THEY DO IS TELL
STORIES THAT ARE IMPORTANT.
NOW, YOU ALL DO, BUT YOU ALSO
GET RICH.
BUT THESE PEOPLE -- ALL THEY GOT
IS THIS OSCAR IS GOING HOME IN A
HONDA CIVIC.
THE PERSON WHO OWNS THIS -- THIS
OSCAR IS GOING TO BE THE NICEST
THING THEY EVER OWN IN THEIR
LIFE.
IT'S GOING TO GIVE THEM ANXIETY
TO KEEP IT IN THEIR CRAPPY
APARTMENT.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR BEST
DOCUMENTARY SHORT SUBJECT.
"BODY TEAM 12," DAVID DARG AND
BRYN MOOSER.
"CHAU, BEYOND THE LINES,"
COURTNEY MARSH AND JERRY FRANCK.
"CLAUDE LANZMANN: SPECTRES OF
THE SHOAH," ADAM BENZINE.
"A GIRL IN THE RIVER: THE PRICE
OF FORGIVENESS," SHARMEEN
OBAID-CHINOY.
"LAST DAY OF FREEDOM," DEE
HIBBERT-JONES AND NOMI TALISMAN.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO -- MAD
MAX -- NO.
"A GIRL IN THE RIVER: THE PRICE
OF FORGIVENESS," SHARMEEN
OBAID-CHINOY.
>> THIS IS THE SECOND OSCAR AND
SECOND NOMINATION FOR SHARMEEN
OBAID-CHINOY.
>> THANK GOD I HAVE TWO OF THEM
NOW.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
DETERMINED WOMEN GET TOGETHER.
FROM THE WOMAN IN MY FILM WHO
REMARKABLY SURVIVED AND HONOR
KILLING AND SHARED HER STORY, TO
SHEILA AND LISA FROM HBO, TO
TINA BROWN, WHO SUPPORTED ME
FROM DAY ONE.
TO THE MEN WHO CHAMPION WOMEN
LIKE JEFF BARTS IN MY FILM, WHO
EDITED THE FILM, TO MY FRIEND
WHO BROUGHT THIS FILM TO THE
GOVERNMENT, TO ALL THE BRAVE MEN
OUT THERE, LIKE MY FATHER AND MY
HUSBAND, WHO PUSH WOMEN TO GO TO
SCHOOL AND WORK AND WHO WANT A
MORE JUST SOCIETY FOR WOMEN.
LAST WEEK -- THIS WEEK, THE
PAKISTANI PRIME MINISTER HAS
SAID THAT HE WILL CHANGE THE LAW
ON HONOR KILLING AFTER WATCHING
THIS FILM.
THAT IS THE POWER OF FILM.
>> Announcer: AND NOW, PLEASE
WELCOME DAISY RIDLEY AND DEV
PATEL.
>> STORIES OF REAL LIFE AND REAL
LIVES ARE WHERE ALL
DOCUMENTARIES START.
WHEN THESE TRUE STORIES ARE
TURNED INTO GREAT FILMS, THEY
CAN ENGAGE AUDIENCES WITH A
SPECIAL INTENSITY.
>> THIS YEAR'S DOCUMENTARY
MASTERPIECES INCLUDE TWO
BIOGRAPHIES OF BRILLIANT BUT
TROUBLED ARTISTS, AND THREE
FILMS ABOUT PEOPLE FIGHTING BACK
AGAINST OPPRESSION AND INJUSTICE
WHEN POLITICS BECOME DEEPLY
PERSONAL.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
BEST DOCUMENTARY FEATURE.
"AMY," ASIF KAPADIA AND JAMES
GAY-REES.
>> I DON'T THINK I'M GOING TO
BE -- I DON'T THINK I COULD
HANDLE IT.
>> "CARTEL LAND," MATTHEW
HEINEMAN AND TOM YELLIN.
>> YOU CAN'T STOP THE CARTEL.
NO MATTER WHAT YOU DO.
>> "THE LOOK OF SILENCE," JOSHUA
OPPENHEIMER AND SIGNE BYRGE
SORENSEN.
"WHAT HAPPENED, MISS SIMONE?"
LIZ GARBUS, AMY HOBBY AND JUSTIN
WILKES.
>> NINA SIMONE WAS A FREE
SPIRIT, IN AN ERA THAT DIDN'T
REALLY APPRECIATE A WOMAN'S
GENIUS.
>> "WINTER ON FIRE: UKRAINE'S
FIGHT FOR FREEDOM," EVGENY
AFINEEVSKY AND DEN TOLMOR.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
"AMY," ASIF KAPADIA AND JAMES
GAY-REES.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR ASIF KAPADIA AND
JAMES GAY-REES.
>> OH, WOW.
THANK YOU.
THIS IS AMAZING.
THANK YOU TO EVERYONE IN THE
ACADEMY, EVERYONE THAT VOTED FOR
US.
ALL THE LOVE YOU HAVE SHOWN TO
THE FILM.
TO THE CONTRIBUTORS, EVERYONE
THAT TRUSTED US TO ACTUALLY MAKE
THIS FILM.
THIS FILM IS ALL ABOUT AMY,
SHOWING THE WORLD WHO SHE REALLY
WAS.
THE BEAUTIFUL GIRL, THE AMAZING
SOUL.
FUNNY, INTELLIGENT, WITTY.
SOMEONE SPECIAL.
SOMEONE WHO NEEDED LOOKING
AFTER.
WE JUST WANTED TO SHOW THE WORLD
WHO SHE REALLY WAS.
>> THANK YOU TO A-24, THE GANG
ON THE CORNER, EVERYBODY AT
UNIVERSAL.
CHRIS KING, OUR EDITOR, THIS IS
FOR YOU, MY FRIEND.
AND LASTLY, THIS IS FOR THE
FANS.
AMY'S FANS WHO LOVED HER THROUGH
THICK AND THIN.
THAT'S ALL SHE EVER REALLY
NEEDED.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> AND OUR FAMILIES AND OUR
WIVES AND OUR CHILDREN.
THANK YOU.
>> YOU KNOW, THE PEOPLE THAT
MADE UKRAINE ON FIRE ARE GOING
TO HATE AMY WINEHOUSE'S MUSIC
FOR THE REST OF THEIR LIVES.
CUT THAT OFF.
AS ALWAYS, THE RESULT OF
TONIGHT'S ACADEMY AWARDS HAVE
BEEN TAB EWE LATE EWE LATED
PRICEWATERHOUSECOOPERS.
I WANT YOU TO WELCOME MING ZU,
BAI LING AND DAVID MOSCOWI TZ.
IT'S OKAY.
IF ANYBODY IS UPSET ABOUT THAT
JOKE, JUST TWEET ABOUT IT ON
YOUR PHONE THAT WAS ALSO MADE BY
THESE KIDS.
OKAY?
>> Announcer: COMING UP,
PERFORMANCES FROM DAVE GROHL AND
LADY GAGA AND MORE FROM CHRIS
ROCK.
¶
>>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
THE BIG MOMENT OF THE NIGHT.
AND I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT BEST
PICTURE.
NO.
WE'RE ABOUT TO SEE HOW MUCH
MONEY WE RAISED SELLING GIRL
SCOUT COOKIES, ALL RIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
I WANT TO THANK ALL OF YOU,
BECAUSE A LOT OF YOU KICKED IN.
A LOT OF YOU KICKED IN.
HARVEY WEINSTEIN, KISS MY ASS.
BUT EVERYBODY ELSE, I LOVE YOU,
OKAY?
MY DAUGHTERS CANNOT WAIT TO SEE
HOW MUCH MONEY WE HAVE RAISED.
SO, HERE WE GO WITH THIS TOTE
BOARD.
NOW, LAST YEAR -- LAST YEAR, WE
MADE, YOU KNOW, $600 AND
FINISHED NUMBER TWO.
SO, LET'S SEE IF WE DID IT.
OKAY, LINDA DUNN.
HERE WE COME.
LET'S -- OH, YES!
$65,243.
THANK YOU.
AND I WANT TO SEND A SPECIAL
THANKS TO SUGE KNIGHT FOR BUYING
THE MOST COOKIES.
THANK YOU, SUGE.
THANKS A LOT, SUGE, ALL RIGHT.
OH, MAN, THIS IS GREAT.
LOLA, ZORA, LOVE YOU.
SEE YOU TUESDAY.
PLEASE WELCOME ACADEMY
AWARD-WINNER WHOOPI GOLDBERG.
>> IN ADDITION TO THE GOLDEN
STATUES WE'RE PRESENTING
TONIGHT, THE ACADEMY'S BOARD OF
GOVERNORS HONORS INDIVIDUALS FOR
EXCEPTIONAL CONTRIBUTIONS TO THE
MOTION PICTURE ARTS AND
SCIENCES, AND FOR HUMANITARIAN
EFFORTS THAT HAVE BROUGHT CREDIT
TO OUR INDUSTRY.
LAST NOVEMBER, THREE OUTSTANDING
ACADEMY AWARD NOMINATED ARTISTS
WERE RECOGNIZED WITH HONORARY
OSCARS -- ACTRESS GENA ROWLANDS,
FILMMAKER SPIKE LEE AND WITH THE
JEAN HERSHOLT HUMANITARIAN
AWARD, ACTRESS DEBBIE REYNOLDS.
HERE ARE A FEW MOMENTS FROM THE
CELEBRATION.
¶
>> GENA ROWLANDS SMASHED THE
FEMALE STEREOTYPE OF HER TIME.
>> SHE HAS HAD THE MOST PROFOUND
INFLUENCE ON MY WORK.
>> I THINK I'LL TAKE HIM HOME
WITH ME TONIGHT.
>> I AM TRULY PROUD AND DEEPLY
HONORED TO PRESENT THE
REMARKABLE DEBBIE REYNOLDS WITH
THE JEAN HERSHOLT HUMANITARIAN
AWARD.
>> DEBDEBBIE, FOR EVERYTHING TH
YOU ARE AND EVERYTHING YOU'VE
DONE, THANK YOU.
>> IT'S BEEN A WONDERFUL JOURNEY
WITH A WONDERFUL FRIEND, WHO
INSPIRES ME A LOT.
OUR PARTNER, PIONEER,
PHENOMENON.
>> IT IS EASIER TO BE THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES
AS A BLACK PERSON THAN THE HEAD
OF A STUDIO.
I DIDN'T FIND FILM.
FILM FOUND ME.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Announcer: LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, THE PRESIDENT OF THE
ACADEMY OF MOTION PICTURE ARTS
AND SCIENCES, CHERYL BOONE
ISAACS.
>> ON BEHALF OF THE ACADEMY,
CONGRATULATIONS TO ALL THE
NOMINEES AND OSCAR WINNERS.
YOUR WORK IS THE REASON THIS WAS
AN AMAZING YEAR FOR OUR
INDUSTRY.
YOUR ARTISTRY AND SKILLS ARE
TRULY WORTHY OF THE ACADEMY'S
HIGHEST HONOR.
AND AS WE REFLECT UPON YOUR WORK
OF THE PAST YEAR, TONIGHT IS
ALSO A TIME TO TALK ABOUT THE
FUTURE.
THE OSCARS CELEBRATE THE
STORYTELLERS WHO HAVE THE
OPPORTUNITY TO WORK IN THE
POWERFUL MEDIUM OF FILM.
AND WITH THAT OPPORTUNITY COMES
RESPONSIBILITY.
OUR AUDIENCES ARE GLOBAL AND
RICH IN DIVERSITY, AND EVERY
FACET OF OUR INDUSTRY SHOULD BE
AS WELL.
EVERYONE IN THE HOLLYWOOD
COMMUNITY HAS A ROLE TO PLAY IN
BRINGING ABOUT THE VITAL CHANGES
THE INDUSTRY NEEDS SO THAT WE
CAN ACCURATELY REFLECT THE WORLD
TODAY.
THE ACADEMY BOARD OF GOVERNORS
RECENTLY TOOK CONCRETE ACTION
AND SENT A MESSAGE THAT
INCLUSION ONLY SERVES TO MAKE US
ALL STRONGER.
AND IT'S IMPORTANT THAT ALL THE
MEMBERS OF THE ACADEMY, AND
EVERYONE IN THIS ROOM, HELP
DELIVER THAT MESSAGE.
EACH OF YOU IS AN AMBASSADOR WHO
CAN INFLUENCE OTHERS IN THE
INDUSTRY.
IT'S NOT ENOUGH TO JUST LISTEN
AND AGREE.
WE MUST TAKE ACTION.
WHILE CHANGE IS OFTEN DIFFICULT,
IT IS NECESSARY.
DR. MARTIN LUTHER KING ONCE
SAID, "THE ULTIMATE MEASURE OF A
MAN IS NOT WHERE HE STANDS IN
MOMENTS OF COMFORT AND
CONVENIENCE, BUT WHERE HE STANDS
AT TIMES OF CHALLENGE AND
CONTROVERSY."
I AM CONFIDENT THAT TOGETHER WE
CAN SHAPE A FUTURE OF WHICH ALL
OF US CAN BE PROUD.
THANK YOU.
>> Announcer: AND NOW, PLEASE
WELCOME ACADEMY AWARD WINNER,
LOUIS GOSSETT JR.
>> THANK YOU.
EVERY TIME WE REMINISCE ABOUT
A MOVING SCENE, LAUGH AT A
PRICELESS BIT OF COMEDY OR
RECALL A STORY THAT GAVE US A
NEW OUTLOOK ON LIFE, WE HONOR
THE ARTISTS BEHIND THOSE
MOMENTS.
NOW, TONIGHT, WE CELEBRATE THE
FINE WORK IN THE MOVIES, WE ALSO
REFLECT ON SOME OF THE
UNFORGETTABLE MEMBERS OF OUR
COMMUNITY WE HAVE LOST DURING
THE LAST YEAR.
SO NOW, WITH THIS SPECIAL
PERFORMANCE BY DAVE GROHL, LET'S
REMEMBER SOME CHERISHED FRIENDS
WHOSE LASTING WORK CONTINUES TO
INSPIRE AND ENTERTAIN THE WORLD.
¶
¶ BLACKBIRD SINGING IN THE DEAD
OF NIGHT
TAKE THESE BROKEN WINGS AND
LEARN TO FLY ¶
¶ ALL YOUR LIFE
YOU WERE ONLY WAITING
FOR THIS MOMENT TO ARISE ¶
¶ BLACKBIRD SINGING IN THE DEAD
OF NIGHT
TAKE THESE SUNKEN EYES AND LEARN
TO SEE ¶
>> TO US, MR. BOND.
WE ARE THE BEST.
¶ YOU WERE ONLY WAITING
FOR THIS MOMENT TO BE FREE ¶
¶ BLACKBIRD FLY
BLACKBIRD FLY ¶
¶
>> I WISH YOU THE BEST OF
EVERYTHING.
>> TRULY FOR SOME MEN, NOTHING
IS WRITTEN UNLESS THEY WRITE IT.
>> NOW YOU'RE TALKING.
WE GOT OLD HERBIE BACK!
>> I CAN TEACH YOU HOW TO
BEWITCH THE MIND AND ENSNARE THE
SENSES.
¶ BLACKBIRD FLY
BLACKBIRD FLY
INTO THE LIGHT OF THE DARK BLACK
NIGHT ¶
>> NO, I BUY YOU UP.
YOU DON'T BUY ME UP.
¶ BLACKBIRD SINGING IN THE DEAD
OF NIGHT
TAKE THESE BROKEN WINGS AND
LEARN TO FLY ¶
¶ ALL YOUR LIFE
YOU WERE ONLY WAITING
FOR THIS MOMENT TO ARISE ¶
¶ BLACKBIRD SINGING IN THE DEAD
OF NIGHT
TAKE THESE BROKEN WINGS AND
LEARN TO FLY ¶
¶ ALL YOUR LIFE
YOU WERE ONLY WAITING
FOR THIS MOMENT TO ARISE ¶
>> I BELIEVE I MIGHT BE OF
SERVICE.
¶ YOU WERE ONLY WAITING
FOR THIS MOMENT TO ARISE ¶
>> I HAVE ALWAYS BEEN AND ALWAYS
SHALL BE YOUR FRIEND.
¶
>>> ALL RIGHT, BEFORE WE MOVE
ON, I WANT TO GIVE A THANKS TO
THE GIRL SCOUTS OF LOS ANGELES
FOR THEIR HELP.
THANK YOU.
WOO, THIS IS CLOSE TO ME.
ALL RIGHT, FROM "ROOM," PLEASE
WELCOME JACOB TREMBLAY, AND MY
MAN -- WAIT, OH, ABRAHAM ATTAH.
COME ON.
>> WE'RE HERE TO PRESENT THE
AWARD FOR --
>> THANKS, CHRIS.
I LOVED YOU IN "MADAGASCAR."
HE'S A ZEBRA.
HE'S HILARIOUS.
FOR OBVIOUS REASONS, ABRAHAM AND
I ARE HERE TONIGHT TO PRESENT
THE OSCAR FOR BEST LIVE ACTION
SHORT.
>> THE NOMINEES THIS YEAR SHOW
THAT WHEN IT COMES TO MAKING AN
IMPACT ON THE BIG SCREEN, SIZE
REALLY DOESN'T MATTER.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
BEST LIVE ACTION SHORT FILM.
"AVE MARIA," BASIL KHALIL AND
ERIC DUPONT.
"DAY ONE," HENRY HUGHES.
"EVERYTHING WILL BE OKAY (ALLES
WIRD GUT)," PATRICK VOLLRATH.
"SHOK," JAMIE DONOUGHUE.
"STUTTERER," BENJAMIN CLEARY AND
SERENA ARMITAGE.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR BENJAMIN CLEARLY
AND SERENA ARMITAGE.
>> Announcer: PLEASE WELCOME
>> THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU MAKE YOUR
FIRST EVER FILM, YOU GOT TO
CONVINCE A LOT OF PEOPLE TO JUMP
ON BOARD AND TAKE A RISK FOR THE
FIRST TIME DIRECTOR, AND, YOU
KNOW, TO EVERY SINGLE MEMBER OF
THE CAST AND CREW, TO JUMP ON
BOARD, I'M FOREVER GRATEFUL.
TO THE ACADEMY, FOR THIS AWARD,
IT'S SUCH A HUGE HONOR.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
TO MY AMAZING PARENTS, FOR UP
THE SUPPORT, THANK YOU.
AND MATTHEW, YOU ARE THIS FILM,
BROTHER.
EVERY DAY IS A PROUD DAY TO BE
IRISH, BUT TODAY MORE THAN
USUAL.
FOR EVERYONE BACK HOME FOR ALL
THE SUPPORT, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
SHAWN, WE JUST WANT TO THANK BEN
FOR BRINGING US ON THE JOURNEY
AND FOR THE ACADEMY FOR HONORING
SHORT FILMS.
THANK YOU.
>> Announcer: PLEASE WELCOME
INTERNATIONAL STARS SOFIA
VERGARA AND BYUNG-HUN LEE.
>> THIS YEAR'S NOMINEES FOR
FOREIGN LANGUAGE FILM ALL
SHOWCASE THE SPECIAL ABILITY OF
MOVIES TO TRANSPORT US IN SPACE
AND TIME.
>> AN OUTPOST IN AFGHANISTAN, A
NAZI CONCENTRATION CAMP, A
CONSERVATIVE TURKISH VILLAGE,
THE AMAZON RAIN FOREST, AND THE
MIDDLE EAST DURING WORLD WAR I.
ALL OF THIS YEAR'S FILMS TAKE
PLACE ON BATTLEFIELDS OF ONE
SORT OR ANOTHER.
>> THE FILMMAKERS EXPLORE THE
FUNDAMENTAL ASPECTS OF HUMANITY
THAT BOTH DIVIDE US AND,
SOMETIMES, BIND US TOGETHER.
>> HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
BEST FOREIGN LANGUAGE FILM.
FROM COLOMBIA, "EMBRACE OF THE
SERPENT," DIRECTED BY CIRO
GUERRA.
FROM FRANCE, "MUSTANG," DIRECTED
BY DENIZ GAMZE ERGUVEN.
FROM HUNGARY, "SON OF SAUL,"
DIRECTED BY LASZLO NEMES.
FROM JORDAN, "THEEB," DIRECTED
BY NAJI ABU NOWAR.
FROM DENMARK, "A WAR," DIRECTED
BY TOBIAS LINDHOLM.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO -- "SON
OF SAUL," HUNGARY.
>> THIS IS THE SECOND OSCAR AND
NINTH NOMINATION FOR HUNGARY.
>> WOW.
THANKS TO THE ACADEMY FOR THIS
INCREDIBLE HONOR.
THANK YOU FOR TOM BERNARD,
MICHAEL BARKER, FOR SUPPORTING
US.
THANKS TO HUNGARY FOR FUNDING
THIS FILM.
I WANT TO SHARE THIS WITH MY
MAIN ACTOR, AND THE INCREDIBLE
CAST AND CREW THAT BELIEVE IN
THIS PROJECT WHEN NO ONE ELSE
DID.
YOU KNOW, EVEN IN THE DARKEST
HOURS OF MANKIND, WHEN -- IN THE
DARKEST HOURS OF MANKIND, THERE
MIGHT BE A VOICE WITHIN US THAT
ALLOWS US TO REMAIN HUMAN.
THAT'S THE HOPE OF THIS FILM.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
>> Announcer: LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, THE VICE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES, JOE BIDEN.
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
HEY, HOW ARE YOU?
NO, NO, NO.
THANK YOU.
I'M THE LEAST QUALIFIED MAN HERE
TONIGHT.
THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING.
AND THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
DESPITE SIGNIFICANT PROGRESS
OVER THE LAST FEW YEARS, TOO
MANY WOMEN AND MEN ON AND OFF
CLUJ
COLLEGE CAMPUSES ARE STILL
VICTIMS OF SEXUAL ABUSE.
AND TONIGHT, I'M ASKING YOU TO
JOIN MILLIONS OF AMERICANS,
INCLUDING ME, PRESIDENT OBAMA,
THE THOUSANDS OF STUDENTS I'VE
MET ON COLLEGE CAMPUSES, AND THE
ARTISTS HERE TONIGHT, TO TAKE
THE PLEDGE.
A PLEDGE THAT SAYS, I WILL
INTERVENE IN SITUATIONS WHEN
CONSENT HAS NOT OR CANNOT BE
GIVEN.
LET'S CHANGE THE CULTURE.
WE MUST AND WE CAN CHANGE THE
CULTURE, SO THAT NO ABUSED WOMAN
OR MAN LIKE THE SURVIVORS YOU
WILL SEE TONIGHT, EVER FEEL THEY
HAVE TO ASK THEMSELVES, WHAT DID
I DO?
THEY DID NOTHING WRONG.
SO, FOLKS, I REALLY MEAN THIS,
I'M SINCERE.
TAKE THE PLEDGE.
GO LOOK AT, VISIT ITSONUS.ORG.
PERFORMING HER OSCAR-NOMINATED
SONG "TIL IT HAPPENS TO YOU,"
WRITTEN WITH DIANE WARREN, FOR
THE FILM "THE HUNTING GROUND,"
WELCOME MY FRIEND AND A
COURAGEOUS LADY HERSELF, LADY
GAGA.
¶
¶ YOU TELL ME IT GETS BETTER
IT GETS BETTER IN TIME ¶
¶ YOU SAY I'LL PULL MYSELF
TOGETHER
PULL IT TOGETHER
YOU'LL BE FINE ¶
¶ TELL ME, WHAT THE HELL DO YOU
KNOW
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ¶
¶ TELL ME HOW THE HELL COULD YOU
KNOW
HOW COULD YOU KNOW ¶
¶ TILL IT HAPPENS TO YOU
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW IT FEELS ¶
¶ HOW IT FEELS
TILL IT HAPPENS TO YOU ¶
¶ YOU WON'T KNOW
IT WON'T BE REAL
NO, IT WON'T BE REAL ¶
¶ WON'T KNOW HOW IT FEELS
TILL YOUR WORLD BURNS AND
CRASHES ¶
¶ TILL YOU'RE AT THE END
THE END OF YOUR ROPE ¶
¶ TILL YOU'RE STANDING IN MY
SHOES
I DON'T WANNA HEAR A THING FROM
YOU
FROM YOU, FROM YOU ¶
¶ 'CAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW
TILL IT HAPPENS TO YOU ¶
¶ YOU DON'T KNOW HOW I FEEL
HOW I FEEL
HOW I FEEL ¶
¶ TILL IT HAPPENS TO YOU
YOU WON'T KNOW
IT WON'T BE REAL ¶
¶ HOW COULD YOU KNOW?
NO, IT WON'T BE REAL ¶
WON'T KNOW HOW I FEEL ¶
¶ TILL IT HAPPENS TO YOU
HAPPENS TO YOU
HAPPENS TO YOU ¶
¶ HAPPENS TO YOU
HAPPENS TO YOU
HAPPENS TO YOU ¶
¶ HOW COULD YOU KNOW?
TILL IT HAPPENS YOU
YOU WON'T KNOW
HOW I FEEL ¶
>> Announcer: COMING UP, THE
AWARDS FOR SONG AND SCORE.
PLUS, MORE FROM CHRIS ROCK, LIVE
FROM THE DOLBY THEATRE.
¶
>> Announcer: AND NOW, OSCAR
NOMINATED COMPOSER PHARRELL
WILLIAMS AND WINNER OF THE JEAN
HERSHOLT HUMANITARIAN AWARD,
QUINCY JONES.
>> JUST A HANDFUL OF NOTES WITH
JUST THE RIGHT COMBINATION CAN
UNITE A GROUP OF TOTAL STRANGERS
IN A DARKENED MOVIE THEATER.
I WAS BLESSED TO HAVE GONE TO
THE U.S.S., THE UNIVERSITY OF
STEVEN SPIELBERG, WHEN WE
COPRODUCED "THE COLOR PURPLE"
AND WE USED TO REFER TO THE
MUSIC AS EMOTION LOTION.
>> THIS YEAR'S EXCEPTIONAL
COMPOSITIONS ARE SURE TO BRING
THAT SPECIAL SENSE OF SHARED
EXPERIENCE TO AUDIENCES FOR
YEARS TO COME.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR BEST
ORIGINAL SCORE.
"BRIDGE OF SPIES," BY THOMAS
NEWMAN.
¶
"CAROL," BY CARTER BURWELL.
"SICARIO," BY JOHANN JOHANNSSON.
¶
"THE HATEFUL EIGHT," BY ENNIO
MORRICONE.
¶
"STAR WARS: THE FORCE AWAKENS,"
BY JOHN WILLIAMS.
¶
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
"THE HATEFUL EIGHT," BY ENNIO
MORRICONE.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
SIXTH NOMINATION FOR ENNIO
MORRICONE.
HE RECEIVED AN HONORARY AWARD IN
2006 IN RECOGNITION OF HIS MAG
KN
MAGN
MAGNIFICENT CONTRIBUTIONS TO THE
ART OF FILM MUSIC.
>> Translator: THANK YOU TO THE
ACADEMY FOR THIS PRESTIGIOUS
ACKNOWLEDGEMENT.
MY TRIBUTE GOES TO THE OTHER
NOMINEES, AND IN PARTICULAR TO
THE ESTEEMED JOHN WILLIAMS.
THERE ISN'T A GREAT SOUNDTRACK
WITHOUT A GREAT MOVIE THAT
INSPIRES IT.
I WANT TO THANK QUENTIN
TARANTINO FOR HAVING CHOSEN ME
TO MAKE THIS EXTRAORDINARY FILM.
I DEDICATE THIS AWARD TO MY
WIFE, MARIA, WHO IS THERE
WATCHING ME.
THANK YOU.
>> Announcer: LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, LAST YEAR'S OSCAR
WINNERS FOR ORIGINAL SONG,
COMMON AND JOHN LEGEND.
>> EVERY MUSICIAN DREAMS OF
WRITING AND PERFORMING A SONG
THAT RESONATES WITH THE PEOPLE
WHO HEAR IT.
WHEN THAT SONG BECOMES A PART OF
A MOVIE, IT'S FOREVER BONDED
WITH THE SPIRIT AND THE MESSAGE
OF THE FILM.
>> THE SONGS NOMINATED THIS YEAR
ARE AS POWERFUL AS THE FILMS IN
WHICH THEY APPEARED.
THREE OF THEM HAVE BEEN
PERFORMED FOR US TONIGHT.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR BEST
ORIGINAL SONG.
"MANTA RAY," FROM "RACING
EXTINCTION," MUSIC BY J. RALPH
LYRIC BY ANOHNI.
¶
"SIMPLE SONG #3," FROM "YOUTH"
MUSIC AND LYRIC BY DAVID LANG.
¶
"EARNED IT," FROM "FIFTY SHADES
OF GREY," MUSIC AND LYRIC BY THE
WEEKND, AHMAD BALSHE, JASON
QUENNEVILLE AND STEPHAN MOCCIO.
"TIL IT HAPPENS TO YOU," FROM
"THE HUNTING GROUND" MUSIC AND
LYRIC BY DIANE WARREN AND LADY
GAGA.
"WRITING'S ON THE WALL," FROM
"SPECTRE," MUSIC AND LYRIC BY
JIMMY NAPES AND SAM SMITH.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
JIMMY NAPES AND SAM SMITH FOR
"WRITING'S ON THE WALL."
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR JIMMY NAPES AND
SAM SMITH.
>> I ACTUALLY CAN'T BREATHE
RIGHT NOW.
OH, MY GOD.
THANK YOU TO THIS MAN RIGHT
HERE, JIMMY NAPES.
TO ALL THE NOMINEES, YOU'RE
INCREDIBLE.
GAGA, YOU'RE INCREDIBLE.
I READ AN ARTICLE A FEW MONTHS
AGO AND HE SAID THAT NO OPENLY
GAY MAN HAD EVER WON AN OSCAR,
IF THIS IS THE CASE, EVEN IF IT
ISN'T THE CASE, I WANT TO
DEDICATE THIS TO THE LGBT
COMMUNITY, ALL AROUND THE WORLD.
I STAND HERE -- I STAND HERE
TONIGHT AS A PROUD GAY MAN AND I
HOPE WE CAN ALL STAND TOGETHER
AS EQUALS ONE DAY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
CONGRATULATIONS, NO JOKES THERE.
NOT GOING TO GET ME IN TROUBLE.
PLEASE WELCOME OLIVIA WILDE AND
OSCAR NOMINEE SACHA BARON COHEN.
>> I KNOW WHAT YOU WERE THINKING
WHEN I WALKED ON.
HERE COMES YET ANOTHER TOKEN
BLACK PRESENTER.
BUT IT AIN'T JUST.
IT'S ALL PEOPLE OF ALL COLORS.
HOW COME THERE'S NO OSCAR FOR
THEM.
AND OF COURSE, THE AMAZING BLACK
LORD FROM "STAR WARS," DARTH
VADER.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
NOW, CHECK OUT A MOVIE ABOUT A
ROOM FULL OF WHITE PEOPLE.
¶ WHEN EVENING WHEN THE SUN WENT
DOWN ¶
¶ AND THE JUNGLE FIRE WAS
BURNING ¶
>> YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND, WE
CAN'T KEEP LIVING LIKE THIS.
>> YOU'RE JUST TRICKING ME.
>> JACK.
THE WORLD IS SO BIG.
WHEN JACK CAME, I JUST KNEW THAT
I HAD TO KEEP HIM SAFE.
>> GOING TO COME TO THE DOOR.
SO, YOU'RE GOING TO HELP ME.
>> I'M SCARED.
>> I KNOW.
YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE IT.
>> WHAT?
>> THE WORLD.
>> THE ENIGMA OF ARRIVAL CREATES
THE DRAMA IN OUR FINAL BEST
PICTURE NOMINEE.
A YOUNG WOMAN SEARCHING FOR A
BETTER LIFE MUST DECIDE WHETHER
TO RESIST THE PULL OF HER NATIVE
COUNTRY AND MAKE A NEW HOME IN
THE PLACE THAT HAS WELCOMED
GENERATIONS OF ASPIRATIONAL
NEWCOMERS.
HERE IS "BROOKLYN."
¶
>> WELCOME TO THE UNITED STATES,
MA'AM.
>> DEAR ROSE.
I STILL MISS YOU AND MOTHER AND
THINK ABOUT YOU EVERY DAY.
>> I'M NOT IRISH.
>> YOU DON'T SOUND IRISH.
>> FOR THE FIRST TIME I'VE BEEN
IN AMERICA, I'M REALLY HAPPY.
I GOT MARRIED IN BROOKLYN BEFORE
I CAME HOME.
I'M GOING TO LIVE IN BROOKLYN,
NEW YORK.
I KNOW IT.
>> YES.
>> Announcer: THE BIG ACTING
AWARDS ARE STILL TO COME.
PLUS, FIND OUT WHICH ONE OF
THESE DIRECTORS WILL TAKE HOME
THE OSCAR.
¶
>> Announcer: PLEASE WELCOME
WRITER, PRODUCER AND DIRECTOR,
J.J. ABRAMS.
>> TO THE FIVE DIRECTORS
NOMINATED TONIGHT, YOU HAVE BEEN
SINGLED OUT FOR YOUR COURAGE.
THE COURAGE TO STAY TRUE TO YOUR
VISIONS, TO INSPIRE PASSION IN
YOUR CASTS AND CREWS, AND TO
DREAM, EVEN THOUGH DREAMS CAN
EASILY AND UNEXPECTEDLY TURN
INTO NIGHTMARES.
BUT DESPITE THE INHERENT RISKS,
THE ASTOUNDING FILMS YOU'VE MADE
HAVE RESULTED IN A COMBINED 37
NOMINATIONS, INCLUDING THIS
AWARD.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
ACHIEVEMENT IN DIRECTING.
>> I'M JUST A BIG BELIEVER IN,
YOU DO WHAT YOU NEED TO DO TO
TELL THE STORY.
>> ADAM McKAY, "THE BIG SHORT."
>> IT'S A STORY ABOUT WHAT'S
HAPPENING RIGHT THIS SECOND.
IT'S GOT THE IMPORTANCE AND FUN
TO IT, AS WELL.
>> LIKE TO WORK AS MUCH AS I
POSSIBLY CAN FOR AS LONG AS I
POSSIBLY CAN WITH THE ACTORS.
>> LENNY ABRAHAMSON, "ROOM."
TOM McCARTHY, "SPOTLIGHT."
INVOLVED IN THE PRESENCE OF
THINKING THE THING INTO
EXISTENCE.
>> AT THE END OF THE DAY, OUR
JOB IS TO TELL STORIES, BUT IT
IS NICE TO FEEL LIKE THE MOVIE
HAS SOMETHING TO SAY.
>> TOM McCARTHY, "SPOTLIGHT."
>> IT'S RARE YOU GET TO WORK ON
MATERIAL THAT YOU GENUINELY
BELIEVE HAS SOCIAL RELEVANCE,
AND SO, I FEEL LIKE WE WERE
REALLY MOTIVATED BY THAT.
>> THE WAY I APPROACH THIS WAS
LONG TAKES, NOT MANY CUTS.
>> ALEJANDRO G. INARRITU, "THE
REVENANT."
>> VERY PRECISE CHOREOGRAPHY.
REHEARSE.
BEAUTIFUL WAY TO USE WHAT CINEMA
IS FOR.
>> SHOOTING MOSTLY IN CONTINUITY
REPLICATED WHAT THE CHASE IS.
>> GEORGE MILLER, "MAD MAX: FURY
ROAD."
>> IT WAS AN OPPORTUNITY TO DO
WHAT I ATTEMPTED TO DO BACK
THEN, BUT TO USE THE NEW
TECHNOLOGY.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
ALEJANDRO G. INARRITU, "THE
REVENANT."
>> THIS IS THE FOURTH OSCAR AND
SEVENTH NOMINATION FOR ALEJANDRO
G. INARRITU.
HE TOOK HOME THREE OSCARS LAST
YEAR FOR "BIRDMAN."
>> THANK YOU TO THE ACADEMY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS IS
HAPPENING, I -- IT IS AMAZING TO
RECEIVE THIS AWARD TONIGHT.
BUT -- IT'S MUCH MORE BEAUTIFUL
FOR ME TO SHARE IT WITH ALL THE
TALENT AND CRAZY CAST AND
COLLEAGUES AND CREW MEMBERS
ALONG THE CONTINENT THAT MADE
THIS FILM POSSIBLE, TO ALL AND
EACH OF YOU.
I THANK YOU FROM MY HEART.
LEO -- YOU ARE "THE REVENANT."
THANK YOU FOR GIVING EVERY SOUL,
YOUR SOUL, YOUR HEART.
YOUR LIFE.
TOM HARDY, ALL THE NATIVE
AMERICAN CAST, ALL THE ENGLISH
AMERICAN CAST, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH FOR YOUR TRUST, FOR YOUR
TALENT.
I WANT TO THANK CHIVO, THANK YOU
FOR BRINGING THE LIGHT TO THIS
JOURNEY AND I WANT TO THANK,
TOO, TO ARNOLD MILTON, THANK YOU
FOR YOUR UNCONDITIONAL SUPPORT.
MY PRODUCERS, ALL THE PEOPLE --
I -- I AM VERY LUCKY TO BE HERE
TONIGHT, OKAY?
BUT UNFORTUNATELY, MANY OTHERS
HAVEN'T HAD THE SAME LUCK.
THERE IS A LINE IN THE FILM THAT
SAYS, THEY DON'T LISTEN TO YOU,
WHEN THEY SEE THE COLOR OF YOUR
SKIN.
SO, WHAT A GREAT OPPORTUNITY TO
OUR GENERATION TO REALLY
LIBERATE OURSELVES FROM ALL
PREJUDICE AND, YOU KNOW, THIS
WAY OF THINKING AND MAKE SURE
FOR ONCE AND FOREVER THAT THE
COLOR OF SKIN BECOME AS
IRRELEVANT AND THE LENGTH OF OUR
HAIR.
THIS IS FOR MY FATHER.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Announcer: STILL TO COME, THE
MOST ANTICIPATED AWARDS OF THE
NIGHT -- ACTRESS, ACTOR AND BEST
PICTURE.
FIND OUT WHO WINS, RIGHT HERE.
¶
>>> YEAH!
IT IS LATE.
IT IS INFOMERCIAL LATE.
OKAY.
NOW, I WANT TO SAY HELLO TO
TONIGHT'S MUSICAL DIRECTOR,
HAROLD WHEELER.
SAY HELLO.
YEAH.
THERE HE IS.
ALL RIGHT.
WE DO THAT JUST SO HAROLD CAN GO
TO THE GOVERNOR'S BALL.
PLEASE WELCOME LAST YEAR'S
WINNER FOR BEST ACTOR AND A
NOMINEE TONIGHT, MR. EDDIE
REDMAYNE.
>> GOOD EVENING.
THE FIVE EXTRAORDINARY ARTISTS
NOMINATED FOR BEST ACTRESS
DELIVERED PERFORMANCES WITH
COMPLEXITY AND DEPTH.
THEY BROUGHT TO LIFE A
DIVORCE-BOUND WOMAN WHO FINDS
UNEXPECTED PASSION WITH A SHOP
GIRL.
A YOUNG MOTHER WHO, WITH HER
SON, ESCAPES CAPTIVITY AND
ADJUSTS TO THE WORLD OUTSIDE.
A STRUGGLING SINGLE MOTHER AND
INVENTOR WHO BUILDS A BUSINESS
EMPIRE.
A WOMAN WHOSE MARRIAGE IS TESTED
BY THE REVELATION OF A
DECADES-OLD SECRET.
AND A YOUNG IRISH IMMIGRANT TORN
BETWEEN TWO COUNTRIES AND TWO
SEPARATE LIVES.
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
PERFORMANCE BY AN ACTRESS IN A
LEADING ROLE.
CATE BLANCHETT, "CAROL."
>> HOW MUCH ARE YOU PAYING FOR
THIS?
>> I WISH I COULD OBLIGE YOU,
MA'AM, BUT THE TAPES HAVE BEEN
SENT TO YOUR HUSBAND.
>> THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT.
>> MY REPUTATION RESTS ON MY
EFFICIENCY.
>> HOW DO I KNOW YOU'RE NOT
LYING?
>> BRIE LARSON, "ROOM."
>> WE CALL HIM OLD NICK.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HIS REAL NAME
IS.
BUT HE PRETENDED HIS DOG WAS
SICK --
>> WHAT IS THE DOG'S NAME?
>> THERE WASN'T A DOG!
HE WAS TRYING TO TRICK ME.
OKAY?
THERE WASN'T A DOG.
OLD NICK STOLE ME.
>> I WANT A DIFFERENT STORY.
>> NO, THIS IS THE STORY THAT
YOU GET.
>> JENNIFER LAWRENCE, "JOY."
>> PLEASE.
TOMMY NEEDS TO BE CHANGED!
OH, CHRIS SEE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I JUST --
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> YOU'RE GOING TO LOSE ANOTHER
JOB.
>> YOU'RE SICK -- I'M A SINGER,
THAT'S WHAT I DO.
>> YOU'RE NOT MAKING ANY MONEY
SINGING.
GET IN YOUR CAR AND GO TO YOUR
JOB.
I CAN'T DO THIS.
I AM LOSING MY MIND!
>> CHARLOTTE RAMPLING,
"45 YEARS."
>> I REALLY NEED YOU TO WANT TO
BE THERE.
>> I DO WANT TO BE THERE.
>> THERE'S ONE THING, HAVEN'T
BEEN ENOUGH FOR YOU.
IT'S SOMETHING ALTOGETHER
DIFFERENT THAT EVERYONE ELSE
FEELS IT, TOO.
>> YOU REALLY BELIEVE YOU
HAVEN'T BEEN ENOUGH FOR ME?
>> NO, I THINK I WAS ENOUGH FOR
YOU.
I'M JUST NOT SURE YOU DO.
>> SAOIRSE RONAN, "BROOKLYN."
>> WE HAVE TALKED ABOUT YOU.
AND I LIKE YOU.
AND I LIKE BEING WITH YOU.
AND -- MAYBE I FEEL THE SAME
WAY.
SO, THE NEXT TIME YOU TELL ME
YOU LOVE ME, IF THERE IS A NEXT
TIME, I'LL SAY I LOVE YOU, TOO.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO -- BRIE
LARSON, "ROOM."
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
NOMINATION FOR BRIE LARSON.
>> OH, WOW!
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, FIRST, TO THE
ACADEMY.
I WANT TO START BIG, BECAUSE THE
THING THAT I LOVE ABOUT MOVIE
MAKING IS HOW MANY PEOPLE IT
TAKES TO MAKE IT, SO, I WANT TO
START FIRST WITH THE TORONTO
FILM FESTIVAL, WHO GAVE US A
CHANCE, WHO GAVE US A PLATFORM
FIRST.
A-24, FOR TAKING THIS MOVIE INTO
THEIR HANDS AND SHARING IT WITH
THE WORLD.
THANKS TO OUR DIRECTOR, WHO IS
ABSOLUTELY INCREDIBLE.
EMMA, WHO CREATED THIS WORLD.
JACOB TREMBLAY, MY PARTNER
THROUGH THIS.
IN EVERY WAY POSSIBLE.
MY REAL PARTNER, ALEX GREENWALD,
I LOVE YOU.
TO MY PARENTS, MY AGENT, MY
MANAGER, THE REST OF MY TEAM, MY
FRIENDS, MY FAMILY, THANK YOU SO
EVERYONE WHO PARATILTICIPATED I
"ROOM."
THANK YOU TO THE FANS.
THANK YOU TO THE MOVIE-GOERS.
THANK YOU FOR GOING TO THE
THEATER AND SEEING OUR FILM.
I APPRECIATE IT.
THANK YOU.
>> Announcer: NEXT, THE MOST
TALKED-ABOUT AWARDS OF THE YEAR.
WHICH ACTOR WILL WIN?
AND WILL YOUR FAVORITE FILM TAKE
HOME THE OSCAR?
>> Announcer: AND NOW, PLEASE
WELCOME LAST YEAR'S WINNER FOR
LEADING ACTRESS, JULIANNE MOORE.
>> THESE FIVE ACTORS HAVE
REWARDED MOVIE-GOERS WITH FULLY
DIMENSIONAL CHARACTERS, SOME
DRAWN FROM REAL-LIFE, ALL OF
THEM LARGER THAN LIFE.
THE BLACKLISTED SCREENWRITER
DALTON TRUMBO.
THE RESOURCEFUL ASTRONAUT
ABANDONED ON MARS.
THE VENGEFUL FRONTIERSMAN,
BETRAYED BY HIS COMPANIONS.
THE BRILLIANT AND COMPLICATED
CO-FOUNDER OF APPLE.
AND ONE OF THE FIRST PEOPLE TO
UNDERGO GENDER CONFIRMATION
SURGERY.
HERE ARE THE OUTSTANDING
NOMINEES FOR PERFORMANCE BY AN
ACTOR IN A LEADING ROLE.
BRYAN CRANSTON, "TRUMBO."
>> WHEN YOU HEAR ME WORKING, YOU
DON'T KNOCK.
>> BUT IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
>> YOU DON'T KNOCK.
EVER.
>> SO, THE HOUSE IS ON FIRE, YOU
DON'T WANT TO KNOW?
>> I WORK IN THE BATHTUB.
SURROUNDED BY WATER.
SO, I'M FAIRLY CERTAIN THAT EVEN
IF THE WHOLE COUNTRY WAS ON
FIRE, THAT I COULD STILL
FUNCTION AS THIS FAMILY'S
PERSONAL SLAVE AND ALL I ASK IS
NOT TO BE INTERRUPTED FOR EVERY
LITTLE SLICE OF BIRTHDAY CAKE.
>> MATT DAMON, "THE MARTIAN."
>> I'M ABOUT TO LEAVE WHERE I'M
GOING TO COMMANDEER THE AREA.
NOBODY GAVE ME PERMISSION TO DO
THIS AND THEY CAN'T UNTIL I'M ON
BOARD THE ARIES 4.
SO, THAT MEANS I'M GOING TO BE
TAKING A CRAFT OVER IN
INTERNATIONAL WATERS WITHOUT
PERMISSION, WHICH, BY
DEFINITION, MAKES ME A PIRATE.
SPACE PIRATE.
>> LEONARDO DiCAPRIO, "THE
REVENANT."
>> MICHAEL FASSBENDER, "STEVE
JOBS."
>> DON'T SEND HIM AROUND TO SLAP
ME AROUND THE PRESS.
ANYBODY ELSE, ANYONE BUT
RAINMAN.
DON'T MANIPULATE HIM LIKE THAT.
WHATEVER YOU MAY THINK, I'M
ALWAYS GOING TO PROTECT HIM.
>> COME ON, STEVE.
>> THAT'S WHAT MEN DO.
>> EDDIE REDMAYNE, "THE DANISH
GIRL."
>> I PROMISED --
>> EINAR IS DEAD.
WE BOTH HAVE TO ACCEPT THAT.
YOU TOOK CARE OF ME, BUT NOW, I
HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF MYSELF, I
HAVE TO HAVE A LIFE OF MY OWN.
AND YOU NEED TO DO THE SAME.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
LEONARDO DiCAPRIO.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OSCAR AND
SIXTH NOMINATION FOR LEONARDO
DiCAPRIO.
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU ALL SO VERY
MUCH.
THANK YOU TO THE ACADEMY, THANK
YOU TO ALL OF YOU IN THIS ROOM.
I HAVE TO CONGRATULATE THE OTHER
INCREDIBLE NOMINEES THIS YEAR
FOR THEIR UNBELIEVABLE
PERFORMANCES.
"THE REVENANT" WAS A PRODUCT OF
THE TIRELESS EFFORTS OF AN
UNBELIEVABLE CAST AND CREW.
I GOT TO WORK ALONGSIDE FIRST
OFF, TO MY BROTHER IN THIS
EN
END
ENDEAVOR, MR. TOM HARDY.
TOM -- YOUR FIERCE TALENT ON
SCREEN CAN ONLY BE SURPASSED BY
YOUR FRIENDSHIP OFFSCREEN.
TO ALEJANDRO.
AS THE HISTORY OF CINEMA
UNFOLDS, YOU HAVE FORGED YOUR
WAY INTO HISTORY.
WHAT AN UNBELIEVABLE TALENT YOU
ARE.
THANK YOU TO YOU AND CHIVO FOR
CREATING A TRANSCENDENT
CINEMATIC EXPERIENCE FOR ALL OF
US.
EVERYBODY AT FOX AND NEW
REGENCY.
YOU ARE THE CHAMPION OF THIS
EN
END
ENDEAVOR.
MY TEAM.
I HAVE TO THANK EVERYONE FROM
THE VERY ONSET OF MY CAREER, MR.
JONES FOR CASTING ME IN MY FIRST
FILM, MR. SCORSESE FOR TEACHING
ME SO MUCH.
TO MR. RICK YORN, THANK YOU FOR
HELPING ME NAVIGATE MY WAY
THROUGH THIS INDUSTRY.
TO MY PARENTS, NONE OF THIS
WOULD BE POSSIBLE WITHOUT YOU.
MY FRIENDS, I LOVE YOU.
AND I WANT TO SAY THIS.
MAKING "THE REVENANT" WAS ABOUT
MAN'S RELATIONSHIP TO THE
NATURAL WORLD.
A WORLD THAT WE FELT IN 2015 WAS
THE HOTTEST YEAR IN RECORDED
HISTORY.
OUR PRODUCTION NEEDED TO MOVE TO
THE SOUTHERN TIP OF THIS PLANET
JUST TO BE ABLE TO FIND SNOW.
CLIMATE CHANGE IS REAL.
IT IS HAPPENING RIGHT NOW.
IT IS THE MOST URGENT THREAT
FACING OUR ENTIRE SPECIES AND WE
NEED TO WORK TOGETHER AND STOP
PROCRASTINATING.
WE NEED TO SUPPORT LEADERS
AROUND THE WORLD WHO DO NOT
SPEAK FOR THE BIG POLLUTERS, THE
BIG CORPORATIONS, BUT WHO SPEAK
FOR ALL OF HUMANITY, FOR THE
INDIGENOUS PEOPLE OF THE WORLD.
FOR THE BILLIONS AND BILLIONS OF
UNDERPRIVILEGED PEOPLE WHO WILL
BE MOST AFFECTED BY THIS.
FOR OUR CHILDREN'S CHILDREN AND
FOR THOSE PEOPLE OUT THERE WHOSE
VOICES HAVE BEEN DROWNED OUT BY
THE POLITICS OF GREED.
I THANK YOU ALL FOR THIS AMAZING
AWARD TONIGHT.
LET US NOT TAKE THIS PLANET FOR
GRANTED.
I DO NOT TAKE TONIGHT FOR
THANK YOU SO VERY MUCH.
>> Announcer: LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN PLEASE WELCOME, OSCAR
WINNER MORGAN FREEMAN.
>> THE MOVIEMAKING PROCESS IS
COMPLETE.
THE PICTURE THAT HITS THE BIG
SCREEN IS THE RESULT OF
COLLABORATION BY DEDICATED
PRACTITIONERS OF THE ART, MANY
OF WHOM WE RECOGNIZED TONIGHT.
WRITERS, DIRECTORS, DESIGNERS,
CINEMATOGRAPHERS, EFFECTS
ARTISTS, EDITORS, COMPOSERS,
ACTORS AND NOW, OF COURSE, THE
PRODUCERS WHO GUIDE THE PROCESS
FROM THE FIRST GLIMMER OF AN
IDEA TO THE FINAL FADEOUT.
OUR LAST AWARD HONORS THAT
MAGICAL REALIZATION.
ONCE AGAIN, HERE ARE THE
NOMINEES FOR BEST PICTURE.
"BROOKLYN."
"ROOM."
"SPOTLIGHT."
"BRIDGE OF SPIES."
"THE BIG SHORT."
"THE REVENANT."
"THE MARTIAN."
"MAD MAX: FURY ROAD."
AND THE OSCAR GOES TO --
"SPOTLIGHT."
>> "SPOTLIGHT" HAS SIX OSCAR
NOMINATIONS THIS YEAR, WINK FOR
BEST ORIGINAL SCREENPLAY AND
BEST PICTURE.
>> THANK YOU, HELLO, EVERYBODY.
I LOVE YOU, LAUREN.
WOW.
THIS FILM GAVE A VOICE TO
SURVIVORS.
AND THIS OSCAR AMPLIFIES THAT
VOICE, WHICH WE HOPE WILL BECOME
A CHOIR THAT WILL RESONATE ALL
THE WAY TO THE VATICAN.
HOPE
POPE FRANCIS, IT'S TIME TO
PROTECT THE CHILDREN AND RESTORE
THE FAITH.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> WE WOULD NOT BE HERE TODAY
WITHOUT THE HEROIC EFFORTS OF
OUR REPORTERS.
NOT ONLY DID THEY AFFECT GLOBAL
CHANGE, BUT THEY ABSOLUTELY SHOW
US THE NECESSITY FOR
INVESTIGATIVE JOURNALISM.
>> WE'D LIKE TO THANK OUR
PARTNERS, EVERYONE AT OPEN ROAD.
JEFF AND JONATHAN AND EVERYONE
AT PARTICIPANT.
E-1 ANONYMOUS CONTENT.
JOSH STINGER AND TOM McCARTHY,
YOUR VISION IS UNPARALLELED.
TO OUR CAST, IF THERE EVER WAS A
PERFECTLY CALIBRATED ENSEMBLE,
YOU ARE IT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> ALL RIGHT!
THANK YOU.
I WANT TO UNVIT EVERYBODY HERE
TO THE B.E.T. AWARDS THIS
SUMMER.
AND I JUST WANT TO SAY GOOD
NIGHT.
THIS HAS BEEN AN AMAZING
EXPERIENCE.
CONGRATULATE ALL THE OSCAR
WINNERS.
BUY SOME GIRL SCOUT COOKIES.
BLACK LIVES MATTER.
THANK YOU!
BROOK LUNN!
OUR EXCLUSIVE BACKSTAGE
EXPERIENCE, EXTENDED THANK YOUS
AND MORE HIGHLIGHTS.
PLUS, LATER TONIGHT IT'S "JIMMY
KIMMEL LIVE" AFTER THE OSCARS
WITH CHRIS ROCK, BEN AFFLECK,
TRACY MORGAN AND MORE POST-OSCAR
FUN.
AND TOMORROW, "GMA'S" LIVE FROM
HOLLYWOOD WITH ALL ACCESS INSIDE
TONIGHT'S MOST GLAMOROUS PARTIES
AND EPIC SURPRISES YOU'LL NEVER
SEE COMING.
IT'S "GMA'S" OSCAR AFTER PARTY
TOMORROW MORNING!
THE RECIPIENTS OF THE OSCARS.
AND FINALLY, THE RESULTS OF ALL
THE SECRET VOTING ARE KNOWN ONLY
TO THE INDEPENDENT ACCOUNTING
FIRM OF PRICEWATERHOUSECOOPERS
UNTIL THE SEALED ENVELOPES ARE
OPENED ON THE AIR.