323 to 584.
You watch "Castle"
last night?
No. Melissa had the flu.
Ooh. Can I tell you one thing?
Uhuh, no spoilers, man.
- Excuse me.
- What the--
Excuse me. How much for sex
with both of you, hmm?
Also, I'd like
to report a stolen pony.
[spits]
Come on, Ice Cream, let's go!
Andale!
♪ We're too gangsta for TV
♪ That's why
you don't see us ♪
♪ But they still
wanna be us ♪
Ha ha!
Yes, I'm on my way
to the interview, Mom.
Yeah, of course
I brushed the back of my hair.
Oh, shoot. Hey, Mom,
can you Google whether someone
can repossess your car
while you're still driving it?
Yeah, but he's
still behind me.
I'm on the phone, sir!
Just remember,
this is temporary.
This is temporary.
Hi, um, I'm Billie Brown.
I'm here for
the babysitter position.
Oh, um, uh...
Yo soy--
You're the babysitter?
I'm here
for the interview,sí.
Yes,sí. Yes.
I'll follow you.
- Yikes.
- And is this where you put her?
Yes, in the sitting room.
Hello, hello!
- Welcome!
- Hi!
This is our home.
Can you believe it?
No, that's great. Hi.
- Please, sit.
- Oh, that sounds like fun.
It's Wilhelmina, right?
Oh, or Billie.
Most people call me Billie.
- Or Bobbie?
- Well, no.
This is my lovely wife,
Tanzy, and I'm Kent.
Russell, yes.
I just read an article about
your new hybrid sports car line.
It's so interesting
to read about--
It makes me uncomfortable
when people tell me things
I already know about myself.
So we looked over
your résumé.
Very impressive.
Harvard.
Both: - Wow. - Mm-hmm.
Oh, thank you,
but it makes me uncomfortable
when people tell me things
I already know about myself.
[chuckles]
I don't understand.
[giggles]
Tanzy, do you understand?
No, I was just thinking
about Danny DeVito.
"Twins." [both laugh]
It's funny.
Um, as you probably
also noticed,
I don't have a ton
of nannying experience,
but I love kids.
I'm sure I'd get along great
with your daughter.
Oh, she's not mine.
I've never been pregnant.
I wouldn't be able to drive.
Mmhmm.
Oh, that-- Is that her?
- Wesley Snipes.
- Yeah, it is.
Can I be honest
with you, Bill?
You know, my--my--
my daughter's a great gal,
but she had some trouble
with school.
Uh, that's great.
I taught in grad school,
so I could tutor her.
- Oh, that's perfect.
- Yeah.
I mean, she has to pass
her GED.
I'm sorry?
It was part of the deal
I worked out with the judge.
Judge--What judge--
Now, my daughter has--
How do I put this?
A criminal past...
present.
You know, I probably should
just let you two meet.
Oh, hey. There she is.
[rap music]
♪
♪ All this money,
all this money ♪
♪ What am I gonna do
with all this money? ♪
♪ All this money,
all this money ♪
♪ What am I gonna do
with all this money? ♪
Oh, [bleep] shoot!
- Am I late?
- No, no.
I wanted to make
a good first impression.
Is this her?
She's gorgeous.
Is this your natural skin?
Can I touch it?
Yeah, no, no.
It's okay. I like guys.
Oh, who are you?
This is my daughter,
Genevieve.
This is Bobbie.
Oh, you can call me Gene.
Like Eugene Levy,
but just the Gene part.
I thought you said
your daughter was seven?
Oh, she caught us.
Oh, she caught us,
didn't she, Tanzy?
This is a joke.
I don't know.
Yeah, we may have fudged
the age a little bit in the ad.
When we said "babysitter,"
we meant more of
a "court-appointed guardian."
Is that an ankle monitor?
- What?
- Is that...
both: An ankle monitor?
Is that an ankle monitor?
Oh, my gosh. I can do
a spot-on impression of her.
Yep. Yep.
Okay, I don't have
the background with criminal--
Come on, Bill. You never
had any trouble with the law?
No, no, no.
I-I-I jaywalked once
to save a hurt bird.
- Bird.
- What are you doing?
See?
You're practically twins.
Yeah.
It'll be, like,
constantly having
a gal-pal
to hang around with,
like "Sex and the City."
Ooh, I'll be Phoebe.
I look the most like her.
You have to give it to me.
- That's "Friends."
- Hire her.
Oh, I should check
this out first.
What are you doing?
No, no, no!
I'm just making sure
we don't have
a Mrs. Doubtfire situation
on our hands.
Ah.
Bobbie, I'm sorry.
She just saw
"Mrs. Doubtfire."
That's okay. I got to go
wash my neighbor's house.
Honey.
Robert, I've written a number
on this piece of paper.
I think the number
might change your mind.
Okay, thank you,
Mr. Russell.
The number's
what I'd pay you.
Yes, I got that.
Thank you very much.
Good.
[sighs] Aah!
Hi.
Oh, my God.
How much money it is?
I'm an academic.
Yeah, I mean,
I would technically
be teaching her, but, no.
No, you know what?
I'll sell my hair.
That's something people do.
Yeah, I'll cut off my hair,
and I'll sell it.
I will persevere.
I don't need money.
I mean, how much
could it possibly be?
Holy [bleep]! [crash]
[air hissing]
Hey, Billie!
I thought about it.
You can be Phoebe.
[classical music playing]
♪
[humming]
- What are you doing?
- Oh, my God.
Sorry, I was just unpacking,
listening to Beethoven.
The dog?
Uh, no. The composer.
Deaf. Never mind.
Oh, my gosh, you look
so good with short hair.
Oh, that's--
You should totally
rock this again.
That's not me.
That's my--my boy--
my ex-boyfriend, actually.
We're on hiatus.
I shouldn't--
Gosh, me too.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I mean, we were, and then he
got together with Mariah Carey.
But I think that's off.
Are you talking
about Nick Cannon?
I don't want to talk
about it.
Point is, it's tough
to find someone
who measures up
to your dad, right?
What is this?
It's from Mexico.
It's an antique.
Can I put it on
for a second?
- Is this cool?
- It's not clothes.
Oh, my God. It fits.
I should totally have this.
Yeah, I'll hang on to it
for you.
Oh, yeah.
You can borrow it, sure.
Thank you.
You really love
your dad, huh?
Yeah,
he's the frickin' best.
Are you kidding me?
He, like, bails me out
when I'm in trouble,
and he gets me cool stuff,
and he totally did
a commercial with a monkey.
My grandfather
died in those.
Can I?
[cell phone ringing]
Oh, sh-
The acting monkey was like,
"Places and set."
- Uh, Moishe's Gold Emporium.
- Back to one.
Moishe's Gold Emporium.
Uh, wrong number.
I know this before we even talk.
Shalom.
Oh, my gosh.
Was that a prank in reverse?
I'm in. I'm totally in.
What do I do?
No, I'm--
You're not in.
I'm evading
my student loan payments.
What?
I mean, if you owe 'em money,
you just pay it.
Yeah, but I don't have it.
[laughs]
Very funny.
- Can I have--
- This scarf doesn't work.
It's not a scarf.
It's dashiki pants.
What?
It's traditional
African garb.
Can I please--
Is there something
in your mouth?
My tongue and my teeth.
It's like you're allergic
to saying 'em.
"Daishiki."
How do you say it?
- "Da-shiki."
- Can I please--
- Oh, can I have this?
- Oh, yeah.
These actually I do want you
to pick up.
These are these really fun
aptitude tests I found
that I think we're
gonna start out with.
Wait, start me off with what?
What are you talking about?
For prepping
for the GED.
[laughs]
You got me again.
You're good.
Burn, sister.
Zzz-zzz.
You're on fire.
'Cause you're here
to be my friend.
That's why you were hired.
No, I'm being paid
to be your teacher.
What?
That's not funny
to joke about.
Are your parents
going somewhere?
I don't--
I just got here.
They can't--
Mr. Russell.
Oh, hey, Bill.
How's the guesthouse?
Oh, it's great.
Are you leaving?
Where are you going?
I don't know--
You [bleep] my dragons?
Aww. She took
her Ambien too early.
No, we are going to Japan
for three days
for a breathing workshop.
Yeah, I'm confident
you can handle everything.
Just make Gene
stays out of trouble.
You're leaving?
Oh, forgot to tell you.
Quick, come give me a hug.
[ankle monitor beeping]
Oh, kiddo.
I'll get you next time.
Air hug.
Yeah, let's go, Blaine.
No, but wait.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Busy guy, huh?
Yeah, he's the best.
You know, school doesn't
technically start till Monday.
- It is Saturday.
- So?
Maybe you could have
a couple friends over,
pop in a movie--
real chill, low-key style.
Yeah. I mean,
I could be down with that.
- Yeah.
- Hey!
Call me Beethoven,
'cause I can't hear you!
[all cheering] Gene!
You said this was just
gonna be a couple of fr--
♪
♪ Let 'em know we're here
♪ We going all out
Oh, my God. Okay.
Guys, take
whatever you want.
Whatever you can carry,
you can take.
Okay. Hey, Gene.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
Huh? No.
Ow! That's my bicep!
My bicep hurts.
Hey, I just wanted to say
this is a really cool party.
Someone puked in my hair.
I'm having a really fresh time.
Oh, cool. Nice. Really?
No, not really.
Someone puked in my hair.
I'm not having a fresh time.
That's a wonderful thing
to happen.
It's like a bird [bleep] on you.
It's good luck.
If you don't get rid
of these people,
I'm gonna call the police.
Eh!
Okay, well,
calling the police
would be the least
fresh thing you could do.
Do you hear me?
Top of the list.
Ow, ow, ow, ow,
ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Um, are you okay?
Yes, I will sleep with you.
What? No, no.
Why does everyone
want to touch my face?
Hey, bud.
How's it going?
I didn't know
you were here.
Billie, this is Chet.
He's my best non-sexual friend.
He lives next door.
He's got a big fanny.
I don't.
I have a normal-sized fanny.
Oh, okay.
Will you excuse me?
The puke that's in my hair
is running down my body
and filling my shoes.
What is happening
to me right now?
What?
I think I have
a girlfriend.
Well, news report--your
girlfriend is totally not cool.
She was cool for, like,
a hot second, and then--
You know what?
I think we just need
to give her a little push.
- I'll give her a push.
- Yeah.
- In the bush.
- No.
With my penis.
No, I think
I have a better idea.
Okay. But the penis plan
is still on the table, right?
- The penis plan?
- Yeah.
It's solid.
I mean, I feel like
it's foolproof.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Sizzurp!
Oh, nice.
Do you want some salad?
- Yeah, I would love some.
- Yeah.
Please leave.
People live here, and I need
to clean the kitchen.
We live here.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God!
Don't be racist.
I wasn't--I didn't--
I'm not being racist--
Billie.
I see you met Ting Poo.
Oh, my God.
Why is there a ponytail
in the sink?
Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow your brain wheels.
You're freaking out.
Hey, I've got an idea.
Let me French-kiss you.
- No!
- What?
Gene, you said
this was just gonna be
a couple of girlfriends.
Yeah. Relax.
I've got it under control, okay?
If anyone gets out of line,
Ting Poo has a gun.
You have a gun?
Don't worry.
It always jams.
The whole reason
we did this
was 'cause you wanted me
to have a fresh time,
but I'm not having
a fresh time
unless you're having
a fresh time, okay?
So let's raise
our glasses, yes...
I don't want
to have a fresh--
For a toast.
To my new babysitter...
[voice breaking]
And my new friend.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little choked up.
My new friend.
To Billie.
That's so sweet.
That's very sweet.
I don't really
want a drink, so...
- Do it.
- Okay.
She has a neat butt.
- Keep going.
- Oh.
Hey!
Call my Beethoven 'cause...
I love classical music.
Don't you?
- Yeah!
[all cheering]
[hip-hop music]
♪
Ting Poo's Dry Cleaners.
No Billie here.
[both laughing]
♪
Drink or die, babes!
[all cheering]
Oh, I do the best Austin Powers.
You ready for this?
Yeah.
[badly imitating Austin Powers]
Oh, baby!
Oh, that's so good.
How's mine?
[British accent]
Cheers, baby, all right!
It's good. You could work
on it a little bit.
♪
Black Eyed Peas!
All: Black Eyed Peas!
We're gonna live forever!
♪
- Joy!
We're out of rum, baby.
Hey, baby!
Both:
We're out of rum, baby!
♪
She is breathtaking.
Get it, girl!
Get it just like
Meg Ryan would.
Yeah, peyote's
not for lightweights.
I was halfway
through a hot dog
before I realized
it was a Coca-Cola bottle.
Don't feel bad about that.
That's totally a thing.
Switch?
Yeah.
I really don't think this is
how you play Apples to Apples.
No, it is.
Right, Ting Poo?
Can I be honest
with you guys?
I write "Ladyhawke"
fanfiction.
Oh.
As well, I'm having
a great time at the party.
Thank you, Gene,
for the wine glass.
I needed it.
"And thank you, Chet,
for putting a roofie in it."
- You're welcome.
- Chet.
What?
You aren't supposed
to tell her.
Tell me what?
Where's the bathroom?
It's cool.
She doesn't know.
She can hear you.
Hear what?
That we roofied you.
Oh.
Where's the bathroom?
Off limits,
and you know why.
[birds chirping]
Billie.
- Billie.
- Hey.
Hey. How you doing?
I'm good.
Wow. That was a crazy party
last night.
- Yeah.
- What is that?
- Okay.
Okay, okay.
Don't freak out,
but remember when Chet
and I roofied your drink?
We actually "hoofied"
your drink,
which is half roofie,
half horse tranquilizer.
Anyhoo, you've been
in and out of consciousness
the past couple days.
Also...
Angelina Jolie
killed Brad Pitt.
What?
Psych.
He's still alive.
My dad always said
to say something crazy
at the end of bad news
to soften the blow.
Okay, excuse me, ma'am.
Hi. Can you help me
with this?
All right,
I don't mind.
Do you want me to do it?
Do you want me
to pull it for you?
No.
Oh, I'm gonna be sick.
That was so gross.
Wait. Where are you--
What are you doing?
- Where are you going?
- I'm quitting.
What? Why?
Because you gave me
a date-rape drug
and put me in a coma!
And?
- And?
Both: And?
What else did you do?
Oh, I thought
we were playing a game.
- Ugh.
- Billie, look, look,
I'm really, really sorry.
This is totally my bad.
I wanted you to have
a good time,
and I just took it too far.
I totally get that now, okay?
Let's move on.
Maybe we can pick on Joy.
Joy! Joy, get in here!
There's something wrong
with you, you know that?
There is something
mentally amiss.
Okay, you know
what we're doing?
We're all focusing
on the bad stuff.
Maybe let's focus on the good
stuff I've done for you.
Like what?
Like while you were out
and your student loan people
kept calling,
and I paid it off.
You answered my phone
and paid my loans?
Yeah. That's why they call
me The Generous General.
That is my loan,
and I will work to pay it off.
You know what? I feel--
I feel bad for you. I do.
No one ever gets mad
at you, do they?
No, 'cause no one ever expects
anything from you, yeah.
Well, that is not me,
Gene, okay?
I am not just a problem
that you can throw money at.
Who put this money
in my wallet?
Nurse!
Take this one, take this one,
take this one for me.
Take this one.
It's clearly the nurse's money.
So, just tell your dad
I'm sorry.
He'll be back tomorrow,
but I quit.
Oh, no, they're--they're
coming back in a couple weeks.
My dad Tweeted.
They're going to, like,
Cannies Film Festival.
You mean Cannes?
Oh, right. Stupid.
Goodbye, Gene.
Uh, I was gonna go
to the mall later
if she doesn't-- Jesus.
Here.
- Is that enough?
- Yep.
- Billie!
- What? Go back!
- Go back!
- Your brakes!
- What?
I cut your brakes!
[tires screech]
No, you didn't.
I'm coming with you.
Gene, you can't.
Your ankle monitor.
I don't care!
No one has ever talked to me
the way you just did...
like you want me to be
a better person or something.
I'm scared of everything.
I'm scared of what I saw,
of what I did, of who I am.
And mostly I'm scared
of walking out of this room
and never feeling
my whole life
the way
I feel when I'm with you.
That is verbatim Baby's speech
to Patrick Swayze
from "Dirty Dancing."
Yes, it is, and then they
have amazing dance sex.
Oh, my God, remember
when she goes behind him
and grabs his butt?
It was, like, role reversal.
Totally. Whoo.
- Say you'll stay.
- No!
No, look, I am not
Patrick Swayze, Gene.
I am the older,
disapproving sister
who never did another movie.
Yes, she did.
She played Kevin's mom
in "Dishdogz."
- Sounds made up.
- Google it.
"Dishdogz" with a Z.
[siren wailing]
You hear that, Gene?
That's for you.
Maybe it's not, Billie.
Maybe it's
for Angelina Jolie.
Maybe she did murder
Brad Pitt.
- God damn it!
- What are you doing?
- Move.
- Oh.
Move again.
Get off your bike.
We're going to get you home.
Help me!
Oh, okay.
What is in here, rocks?
Drop it, drop it, drop it.
[police radio chatter]
Oh, [bleep]!
Okay, follow my lead.
Be invisible.
Go, go, go.
Oh, farts, Billie.
- I'll handle this.
- What? What are you doing?
I'm just gonna
go talk to them
and explain what happened--
it's no big deal.
The only excuse for breaking
probation is an emergency.
- Wait a minute.
- What?
Gene...
what are you doing?
Oh, good idea.
We'll brain the cops.
We'll stone 'em to death.
We'll both go to prison!
Oh, Billie, no.
Better idea--
break my hand.
What?
That's so much crazier.
I'm not gonna break
your hand.
Billie! Break my
[bleep] hand, Billie.
- No!
- If you love me,
if you're my best friend,
you will break my hand.
I just met you.
If it doesn't look
like an emergency,
we both go to jail.
I don't think that's true.
It is.
I need you, Billie.
Do it, Billie. Do it.
Oh, God.
This is temporary.
Tell me when it's over.
Let me know once
you've broken my hand.
Oh, God! [both screaming]
♪ Call me Polo, shorty
[rap music]
Make sure-- Excuse me.
What are you--
What's happening?
Just trying
to check to make sure
we don't have
a Mrs. Doubtfire situation.
Ah, I see.
- That's fair, right?
- Yeah, that's fair.
You just saw that movie.
That's great.
- I loved it!
- Yeah.
- Have you seen it?
- Uh-huh.