Provided by: FCB
>
Paolo
Paolo, are you there?
Oh Paolo, of course I love you.
'Confess Marriage Life'
Dear Marikla,
I'm writing to you
because I need your advise.
I am 24 years old and I am married
for 5 years.
Pretty, I've been told
and nice to be around.
I have a good job
and a wonderful husband.
I know I married a bit young
but everything is going very well.
A passionate relationship in the beginning,
and then much later
complicity.
But for some time,
I feel something strange.
It's hard to explain.
I want to have fun,
to live more intensely.
I feel that nothing interesting
happens.
I say it's the season
which brings out in me
these strange desires.
They become stronger,
more urgent every day.
Especially since that night
my sister Nadia took us to a party.
in honora Venetian poetess.
I'd penetrate you
without touching you.
And my tongue wanders
wanders casually
in the fleece of your ass.
I would like to offer your mouth
my honey flavor.
I would lock you
between my breasts generous
and down between your balls
and suck your cock whole.
And that fits your body
the accents of my body.
And back to your belly
to your heart.
And to find the rest
I would like
not knowing enjoying.
Bravo!
Wonderful!
Eccentric!
- Modern!
- Bravo!
As the best of Veronica Franco
and Patricia Valduga,
An exploration
of female sensuality.
It was sublime,
your book will be a smash!
I am Nadia Valentini,
I run a body-fitness gym.
Come check it out.
Nadia Valentini...
- I'd love to be able to write like you.
- Ah.
Your heart line is perfect,
it's rare.
Shall we dance?
Well, certainly!
I am an intruder,
I have no invitation.
I'm not invited
Neither do I.
I accompany the poetess.
In Venice, we are neighbors.
Venice is unique.
A French poet said:
Venise, sexe femelle d'Europe.
You are a sailor,
to have these tattoos?
I travel a lot.
I get the old stuff.
You could get the two old
sitting there!
This type interests you?
This is my husband!
A husband does not count!
For me, it is important.
I would like to enter,
without touching you.
My tongue wanders
wanders casually
on the fleece of your ass.
I'm sure you're wet.
Excuse me.
My head is spinning.
No need to go
in museums, idiots!
The art now is everywhere.
We are art!
Two examples of Baroque art.
With beautiful curves
generous!
It brings back to life.
Aside, here are two beautiful brows,
in pure rococo style.
But ...
Shhh. Do not be afraid of me.
I am afraid of nothing,
I do not know your name.
Ah, très juste.
Alphonse Donatien.
Pirate d'amour
I guess you are wet?
What are you doing?
I'm doing everything I promised to do.
Diana, are you there?
Yes, Paolo. Just a minute!
I hadn't seen you for a while.
Anything wrong?
Of course not, I just had to pee.
Do you want to leave, darling?
Yeah, I'm bored silly.
This party's shit.
As you like. Let's go.
You're soaked!
And it's not pee!.
What makes you
such an effect?
Well, if you touch me there,
of course I get wet.
You know how sensitive I am.
Do it some more..
Was it that guy or me
who brought it out in you?
- What guy?
- Your partner, you were dancing with!
Oh. He's French.
He has a home in Venice, he said.
It made me salacious proposals.
Oh, Paolo you're driving me crazy.
It was a little old, right?
No, not at all!
You should have called me.
It would have been an admission
of adultery.
I was in the toilet with him.
- The bastard!
- You did not realized.
He was behind the door.
Ah, you're kidding! It's just
another one of your silly stories!
- He had me naked in no time.
- Enough!
He wanted to take me by the ass
and if you had not happened ...
You're inventing everything.
I know it! I'm no idiot!
He thought my ass was beautiful.
How was? How was his thing?
You touched?
It was as hard as that?
You like my ass, Paolo, don't you?
How many times do I have to tell
you? It's the most gorgeous.
You can't give an opinion unless you..
unless you look at it first!
Tell me I have a beautiful ass!
It is beautiful, gorgeous...
Oh, God!
- We get home, quick!
- No, Let's do that here!
Hurry up!
Tell me, tell me you made it all up!
Oh, tell me!
Shut up!
And they call us whores, huh!
You're right!
Bonjour!
Okay now, lazy-bone, rise and shine!
I'll teach you some good manners!
You're hurting me, stop!
What are you doing?
I rape you!
It's 8 o'clock!
You rape me later.
Let me go!
If mother could see the chaos
you make me live in!
Which witch?
Sorry!
You're not to speak
about my mother like that!
All right, Mr.
the grumbling, I am silent!
It's the little musical
Aquatic Mozart.
That's complete amorality!
And you. Pig!
That son of a bitch
dribbled right up the middle!
You kidding?
That shit head's nowhere!
He couldn't find the hole in that hoop
if they stuffed his face inside it!
The boy's got great hands!
You know what Hal Taylor would do?
That turkey?
That so-called turkey
is a great clutch player!
Is that what you call a center?
He's the greatest center playing
in the league right now.
I'm out of patience with assholes
like you. Don't give me that shit.
who wouldn't know a point guard from pivot!
Your guys need a crooked umpire to win!
You ever seen a basketball game?
You let go of me, goddam it?
Let go of what? Jesus Christ, a fag!
I've been standing here
talking to a fag all this time!
You're the one who grabbed my cock! Now I
know why you like that Taylor kid so much.
You're just lucky,
this is my stop coming up!
Or what, you would've kissed me?
Miss, take my seat.
Thanks, no, my stop is coming up.
I'm sorry.
Hey, listen! You gotta get
a couple of things clear.
Get the mud out of your upstairs!
I can see it's hard on you.
That little thing
might just ruin your vocation!
Miss ...
Take my advice, kid.
Go confess all!
How about a phone call?
Do you know my number?
- No
- You're outta luck, boy!
Bye!
Hi Lello!
You're crying, what's the matter?
He left me!
He's gone back to his wife!
She said she was sick
and that it was his fault.
- And it's true?
- I do not know,
but maybe it does.
There are millions of men,
Why do this to me?
Going out tonight
and you will find full
that are better.
- You really think so?
- Guarantee!
Hey, your diet! Antonietta?
Like the lady said, everything I like is
either illegal, immoral, or fattening!
- Really
- Look! I've got a terrific surprise for you!
It reminded me
memorable nights with Peter.
Is there a new way in it, huh?
The 'Atom Bomb', just try it!
You're just dying
to take it home with you, Lello!
I bought six like it yesterday,
only a much better quality!
The least you could do,
is to make them.
Hello, kids, hard at work? That's fine!
Hi, Mr. Silvio.
Antonietta, I just got
new models.
Would you mind very much
modeling a few in the South Wing?
It's very nice of you!
Come along, my dear.
Some girls have all the luck, huh!
The rest of you can take a break!
let me see your breasts!
Now bend this leg a little.
And turn around now.
Pull your panties up
tight between the cheeks.
Oh, just my size!
This morning I woke up
with a third leg like a telephone pole,
and I thought of you right away!
I'm flattered,
Mr. Silvio.
Hello!
- Hello, Diana.
- Hello, Mrs. Tommasini
You seem to be dressed
in mourning, though.
Yes, I just lost
my little Danny.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
Somebody very close?
Yes, we were together for
years.
He was a wonderful Labrador.
Oh, I imagine.
And how's your husband the Senator?
In France, eating foie gras
and fighting hunger in the world.
Have you prepared
the items I ordered?
Of course.
I can't wait to fill up my drawers.
I'll try those.
These are the same as last Thursday.
I always put these,
They fit me well.
You should have seen the former,
they were in pieces!
That engineer has tastes of his own.
An engineer?
Your newest conquest, huh?
No, but one of the most generous.
Cartier!
Congratulations!
At least
I never get bored in the afternoon.
I've found a little group of friends.
I was introduced by Alicia.
She's a client of yours?
Mrs. Farconi?
Alicia, yes, I see,
Mrs. Dow.
She is attending
that people in high places.
It brings in a lot,
I could tell him about you.
It's kind of you,
thank you.
I'm still undecided ...
To make a whore?
I'm not really a pro. Fills in spare time!
And plenty of ladies do it.
Anyway, real whores never come.
I do, like an avalanche!
Oh, men have great imaginations!
I learn something
at each meeting.
And it does not interest you?
My husband has enough imagination.
Oh, mine doesn't!
How inventive can
an envoy to the European Parliament be?
Oh, but it's so romantic
to meet someone unknown,
in a hotel room, or apartment.
Your heart beats like crazy.
It's adventure,
How wonderful!
And this feeling
being for sale,
with all the shame and sin.
I'd give it a whirl, if I were you!
I must say I really think
I'll pass on your..
I know a Chilean archbishop
you would love.
Priests does not really excite me.
These are the best customers,
believe me.
I take those.
All right.
Ms. Tomasini is really nice.
She's a big success in what she does,
which is actually something like what I do,
if you want to know the truth.
In there getting poked, yes.
My precious favors
in return for a raise in pay.
My husband isn't sorry,
and neither am I!
How? He knows?
No guilt about it, for Pierre?
This is not a marriage
love, and he knows it.
You still betrayed
your husband, right?
I do not see at all
things like you.
Come on, do not tell me
stories!
It is difficult to define.
With Pierre, I have
tenderness and little else.
With others,
only for the trifle.
See you soon, Diana.
If you change your mind,
give me a call.
Okay, I'll keep it in mind, thanks.
I do not know how you can
sleep with the boss.
It's really big.
It does not bother me,
I do not care completely.
And then the ugly
are more generous
the handsome guys.
And ugly guys have more time
to dedicate ourselves.
- Maybe ...
- Some call it the defect.
It's just fun.
When I fuck the boss
I'm just a good time.
That's it!
A little sex is good!
- What if you fell pregnant?
- No danger of that happening to me!
I use the only real
natural method.
Just take it here!
Diana! My God.
Are you all right?
Huh? I'm alright. I'm okay.
Diana? Would you mind
coming to the workroom?
There's someone here to see you.
Yes ... yes, thank you.
I'm coming.
Nadia? What are you doing here?
A little tact, Nadia!
Aunt Emma just kicked the bucket.
My God, she did not do that?
Fortunately I had
asked to be tactful.
I can not leave the club,
it is you who will go to the funeral.
You were his favorite,
we all know!
But I do not know ...
I'm afraid of ...
I have work!
Do not worry about it.
Go to Venice.
Do not worry about Paolo.
I'll take care of him,
I promise.
Sorry, dear,
I wish I accompany you,
Do not worry, I'm great,
I know on my own.
I am concerned about your faithfulness.
You know that the funeral is sexy.
Paolo, stop! You're crazy!
It is an established historical fact:
creates a funeral
a funereal atmosphere that makes
a sense favorable
to love.
I read in an article
on adultery.
Statistics show that more
60% of Italian women cheat their husbands.
- What is that?
- Antonietta gave it to me!
But it is that these people
with whom you work?
People who are not ashamed
what they do,
bourgeois and not stuck like you.
And if you looked?
If you insist ...
Come in, please.
This gentleman is with you?
This is my husband.
Wait for me, honey.
Ah yes, it's nice.
Yes, like that.
Below ...
To the right.
Take off your clothes.
You're almost there!
Sit down there.
Spread well.
What do you think?
When you go to the ...
the gynecologist, is it ...
Him?
He has at least 70 years!
Guess he is young.
Well, it depends ...
You'd be upset
if I did?
I would be very angry!
And that's all
it would cause such reaction?
I would be very angry!
These things happen
all the time at the store.
This is our boss, a real sick!
He puts his hands almost everywhere.
Where does he touch you?
Everywhere!
On my breasts, my ass.
He stroked my ass
presenting his condolences.
How old bastard!
But you, what do you say?
Nothing! I bet you did not say anything.
Go! Tell me!
I wanted to digress.
But I was stuck in the back room.
Yeah?
What did he do to you?
He opened my legs.
- He touched me right on the button.
- Like that?
Yes, like that!
- What's Next?
- Then he turned me around
and made me bend forward.
Oh, dear, a little higher!
Higher up, darling, higher up! Please!
I can't take it!
It's your fault, you little sow!
That imagination of yours
excites me too much!
Gentlemen, can you do me a favor?
- Certainly!
- What do we have to do?
I want to be paid
1 million lire.
Why?
Give my virginity ...
that of my ass.
Giving money to a woman? Never.
I may be romantic,
but ass fucking a woman, no.
How dare you!
I am mourning.
Subject to clause
that binding
it will not be added
to those existing parts.
I bequeath to Marco Valentini,
son of my brother Luigi Valentini
and therefore my legitimate nephew,
the property of Villa di Mira
It was a plague, I'm sorry
for giving her the red dress!
She jokes?
It'll cost us more
to restore!
And similarly,
I leave also to Diana Bruni
daughter of the deceased
Giovanna Valentini,
the property that is
in the upper floor of a building
located at 1725 Via Tideca.
I bequeath also objects
and furniture that are therein
at the time of my death.
You're really lucky!
That's exactly what I wanted!
I needed
a pied-à-terre in Venice!
I give in this
my other properties
with what they contain,
and my bank account,
cash and securities,
to the convent of the Carmelites
Via Veneto
I helped convent
throughout my life.
Your signatures.
What a piece of ass!
You look great!
The air in Rome! Thanks.
I'm going to take a look at the penthouse.
Do you want to see it?
Impossible, Marco.
We have company for dinner tonight.
Don't worry about a thing, Nora.
Go on back to Padova.
I'll go along with Diana
and I'll be home in time for dinner.
Once again, please.
Father, you must sign.
The last shall be first!
I'm glad you came along with me.
Strange lady, aunt Emma.
She liked us a lot, you and me.
Actually, of all the relatives,
I'm the one
that spent the least time with her
But you knew about her?
Well sure. At least
the things the family said.
Discreet, organized, intelligent-
above all, skillful!
Skillful? In what sense?
In love! Two or three lovers
same time, and even four!
Rich people,
with good social position.
They helped her make a fortune.
Thanks to them
she has learned to manage property.
For his interest
and ours today.
How about uncle Harry?
A mystery, did he know
about her infidelities or didn't?
IDid he like it or was it killing him?
Well, I still think he was
really never interested in women.
But one thing's for sure,
Emma was always loyal over him.
And if he were alive today,
we would not have inherited.
Do not be afraid.
No one will take your apartment.
It is yours, you can do
what you want.
Perhaps will you come to Venice
a little more often?
No doubt.
- And how's it going with Nora?
- How about with you and Paolo?
- Marvellous!
- Does he know about us?
Know what, Marco?
That I had you before him,
And you and I in bed,
did everything you can do.
Everything? My dear.
I have some bad news for you!
Come on, hurry up.
I feel like going up to the tip
of the Dogana. Do you remember?
How could I forget?
You make me crazy!
I want more!
- I used to call you the erector set
- You used to say my erector set.
There's still the same stink
of pee here as always.
I bet with all the tourists,
even the ladies take a leak.
Open your legs. Not like that.
You were more enterprising.
You just forgot how
was standing.
- For heaven's sake.
- Yes ... I know.
What are you doing?
You will not leave me like that?
Let's go to my house. We can do it
in style and comfort there.
- Ah, you mean aunt Emma's penthouse!
- This house is mine.
I decided not to return to Rome
and stay until tomorrow.
I want to spend my first night
in my house.
Yeah, but I've got to get back home,
we have these guests coming for dinner.
Ah, as far as that goes,
I told Paolo that I'd return tonight.
No, Diana.
I simply can't do it. I can't.
No sweat, we'll make it
for some other time.
I'm going to make good use
of my house in Venice, yeah!
Marco, that's the ferry-boat
for the station.
If you run, you can catch it!
I want you to make me
visit this home.
I promise!
But must you hurry!
Faster!
Bye!
My God!
Who would have expected this?
You should not get bored ...
Well, it's sure to have cost you
a lot of blow-jobs this penthouse!
My dear aunt,
you are amazing!
I love you more with every snapshot!
I did promise Paolo I'd call.
Wonder if the phone works?
Donatien ...'' Alphonse.''
Allo!
Morning, could I please speak
with uh! Alphonse Donatien?
C'est moi.
Ah, you might not recall.
Diana Bruni, you and I met..
at someone's house in Rome
at the party to meet the poetess?
Ah, oui, the lovely lady
I struck up a conversation with.
Where are you calling from?
Oh, Venice, I was left a small apartment
that I like to redecorate it.
- And that is why you thought of me?
- Partly, after all, you said..
I'm delighted you did!
Let's talk about it, come on over!
Come on over? Where?
To my place, right now!
Palazzo Lorenzoni. It's easy to find.
I know Venice
I know where it is.
- Then hurry up, please!
- I'll be seeing you!
It's cold!
Voila!
Good evening.
Hello, uh, haven't we
already met some where?
Fresh, light, without a guide.
The mouth has its own sex.
Swellings which meet
in the same party.
This is more than strange. It's...
Go on in.
Alphonse is waiting for you.
Bonsoir!
You found the place
with very little effort, huh?
Sure!
You were with that poetess?
Oh, oui. Just work!
At this hour of the night?
Et toi, didn't you come here for that?
Ever since that night
it's been like this.
- This is the house of wonders?
- The best is yet to come
- Let's go upstairs ...
- In heaven?
The inferno, mon inferno.
- It's when you want.
- Go ahead, I am.
No, you go first.
I want to admire your ass, ton cul.
Is this all right?
Or do you want to see more?
- Hurry!
- Come and catch me!
Incredible!
It must have taken you quite
some time to collect all of these.
Oh, I started early, with that one!
It's my ex-wife.
She has a very expressive face.
Ah, oui.
From her I learned that the physiognomy
of a person is all in the nates!
Ici
This is a portrait gallery.
You can distinguish the timid ass,
the brave one,
the stupid one, the intelligent,
the happy, sad ...
Everyone is the ass that he has.
So what am I?
Voyons.
A headstrong, willful, disobedient
and a little ... tense.
Introvert.
Am I hopeless, Doctor?
Not if you can play by the rules.
Let's hear the rules.
You must follow orders and do for me
everything I want.
But if you cry out once, I stop.
Everything, at your command?
- Yes.
- Down on all fours, over there.
Why?
Oh, it's because the game
has already started, and you know it!
Feel the ..
Force ... the pride ...
- It's gonna hurt me, isn't it?
- You scream and I Quit!
It's up to you.
- I'm so scared!
- Do what I say.
And everything will be fine.
Breathe deep!
As if you were in child birth, in labor.
Breathe with me!
Good, come on!!
Come on!
Was that a scream, Diana?
No I broke through the canvas, though.
Oh, don't worry, c'est pas grave,
I'll have it restored.
L'enculeur sauvage!
... The ass is something
divine and precious ...
That's incredible.
That fur piece was still
hanging up in the closet.
I found some snapshots, too.
- The Old Aunt Emma!
- Who would have guessed?
The apartment is the same.
Nothing has changed.
- It looks nice.
- We see all of Venice!
For a couple of lovers,
this place is paradise.
Perfect for a young couple
love.
- Yeah, well we can rent it.
- But I wanted to keep us both!
We are a loving couple!
Is not it, darling?
It's new, you shave?
Just a little on the sides.
I must be a virtuous woman wise.
I am an heir after all.
- You're a slut!
- And you're a pig!
Aunt Emma got you excited, huh?
I guess I should be jealous!
I'm the one who ought to be jealous!
Tell me the truth, your cousin came over
to see the apartment, didn't he?
Of course he came over!
Marco wouldn't let a chance
like that go by.
Did he make a pass at you?
Well, he began to talk about when
the two of us used to go out together
Tell me.
We'd go up to the tip of the Dogana,
and he'd touch my little flower
under my skirt and I put my hand on him.
- I told him touched the hand.
- Show me how you did it.
Warning! This is tricky!
He'd grab my head and get it right down.
because he wanted me to take
it in the mouth.
- What did you do?
- I fought
but not too long.
And did you do it again yesterday,
in your apartment on the Giudecca?
Great, fantasies you got?
- Oh yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
I know you and Marco
didn't do a thing, right?
I decided to have fun
with Alphonse.
Who is he?
That French guy at the party
who I danced with.
That's how you
christen the apartment.
No, we were at his home ..
Nice decor.
Give me the details!
He was crazy about my ass.
He insisted I take it.
I couldn't have avoided it
even if I'd wanted to!
He spread my ass and started
licking my crack, down and up.
But it isn't so painful.
I could be persuaded.
- And did you..?
- Did I? Like an express train!
What's the matter?
You want me to stop?
- Who gave that hickey to you?
- What.
- That hickey on your neck!
- I don't know what you mean!
I thought it was a story
but you did!
No, please, let me explain!
No, it isn't a fantasy this time.
He fucked you!
- That bastard prick fucked you!
- No, Paolo, I swear it!
He didn't fuck me at all!
I took it up the ass!
Please, darling, don't pout.
- Better to talk it over, huh?
- Get away from me!
We've always had a laugh
over my little affairs.
You told me they made you horny!
You liked that just swell!
Because it was
just stories!
There's no difference, it doesn't matter
in the least. I'm really only yours.
Is it so naughty if I make it
with someone else?
I mean it's all,
happy banging, right?
Do not count on me
to participate in that!
I guess it seems like the end of the world
to you right now, but you'll see, tomorrow
Don't get near me.
We're history, the past!
There never will be a tomorrow for us!
I'm not going to share my marriage bed
with someone like you!
You slut!
I shouldn't be surprised after all.
Blood will tell,
but yours should be spilled!
Hey, you look all queer!
Thanks to Paolo. Big fight.
- Irreparable?
- He wants a separation.
No kidding! Another woman?
- No, something other than that.
- A man...
- Paolo?
- No, me.
- It was a guy in Venice.
- Oh, really! You had me scared!
It's over?
Turn's up!
Let me get the broads outta here!
Head for the showers!
I want to hear all the details!
Why did you tell him?
He would for sure take it badly!
I was tell him stories for fun.
Whether your are a whore,
or your are crazy!
All men are stupid pigs.!
You have to always deny,
even the obvious.
They always speak about liberty
for women, but not for theirs!
They're all the same!
I don't want that ended like that!
Yesterday I was alone in my bed.
I could not sleep.
Find yourself a guy.
You will not be alone!
A woman cannot be satisfied by
only one man.
And every man tastes differently.
A woman must try a lot of them!
Your problem, it's you husband
who left you.
You're the one having done
a mistake!
No, no, no with Paolo
it's really different!
I love him,
I do not want to lose it.
- Are you gonna help me?
- How?
Talk to him, persuade him,
tell him he is wrong.
Brilliant!
He has to realize the others
do not matter.
- And if he refuses to listen?
- No, he trusts in you,
He appreciates you very much.
Please, Nadia.
I have "Carte blanche"?
What do you mean?
A white hair!
My pussy is whitening!
Anyway you get "Carte blanche".
Okay then I think
I'll just pop on over at lunch break.
Thank you, Nadia. I knew that
I would be able to count on you!
Do you mind if I have
a shower along as I'm here?
I was in such a big rush getting out
this morning. I didn't even take a bidet.
That should never happen. If you must...
put off washing your face, chum
But before leaving, always take a bidet.
Hey, you never know
what might be coming up!
Yes?
Yeah? Ah, it's you.
Yeah, yeah, sure, of course.
Hi! I'm glad you came.
I could really use your advice.
That's true.
- Poor idiot!
- Why?
There's a terrific girl
you're treating like scum.
You don't know what she did to me!
I certainly do. I just don't see
where it's such a tragedy.
Well, how should I've handled it?
Give her a medal?
There was no need to do anything! You've
got the most wonderful girl in the world!
She's classy! She's great! Worships you!
So why do you put out her joy of living?
Because wives are supposed to make love
with their husbands, nobody else?
You dumb-ass moron!
We're talking
about a little affair of no importance!
You can't say that
marriage encompassed the universe
or that you represent men of all types!
We're not back in the time of your mother
and your father any more, take a look!
Would you like Diana to be like her?
No, of course not.
I'm the big loser in this case.
- What can I do? I'm jealous!
- Here we go!
But your jealousy is absurd
and no use!
It's absurd and useless,
there's no kind of sense to it!
Paolo, I could understand your misery,
if she were tired of you.
But no sorry! She just wants
minimal liberty, sex-wise!
Just the thing
you've always had, you bum!
That's what's so horrible! The thought
that she laughs with someone else.
That she uses the same little love words
as she does with me!
Who's to know?
She might even come!
I'm beginning to feel
there's a time-bomb inside me!
A few minutes ago I was asleep and dreaming
that I was with Diana. It was a nightmare.
I'm telling you.
I'm going, I'm going nuts.
I'm with you, Paolo,
and I can prove it to you.
I'm all wet.
You feel?
If you knew how I wanted
to feel your hands on me.
Lie down.
Oh, my God ...
I'm glad to see I don't turn you off.
Diana will not make a scene.
Nobody's going to see
any jealous scenes.
Diana does not care.
- She gave me permission.
- Diana?!
No, no, stop!
I don't want you. I want Diana!
Bullshit!
Your cock said otherwise!
Poor Diana,
she thought you were different.
You are all the same.
Full of old-fashioned principles.
Honor, virtuousness, betrayal!
And a girl who's liberated
is just a slut, right?
Try to understand Nadia.
I can't, I won't!
And if I did, it would be like
admitting Diana was right!
She's right, you're a fool.
She is absolutely right.
Fighting it's no use.
You silly bastard!
Your problem is that
you're a fag repressed.
- Your underwear!
I've met assholes before,
but men take the cake!
Here's hell to husbands in general
and ours in particular!
Hey, chin up, little sister!
We're out to enjoy life tonight.
Shorten up that long face!
Look at that!
Sexy, no?
Not bad! Let's take pot luck!
- Hey, handsome! Approach a little!
- Who, me?
I need information.
How are your hunk?
What the fuck!
Come back here, you cunt!
Just don't let me catch you!
Hi, girls!
Holy mother of God
What a beautiful ass!
It's a drag queen!
Hey, sweetheart!
You carrying a dong or not?
Watch!
What are you doing with that?
It is small.
- I can stick it in your ass.
- Or I might stick this thing in yours!
Fuck you!
Go assholes, so fuck you!
I said it first, you ugly,
pimping, bull-dyke bitch!
You fucking bitches, I'll catch you!
When we feel like living it up,
where do we go?
I know a disco, yay!
We can do better than that,
Mother Superior.
- A place where anything can happen to you.
- Even the worst?
If you get lucky!
Hey, wait.
Girls!
I want something strong.
What do you have?
Try a 'Delirium'. It'll make a
corpse dance.
That's exactly what I need.
- What's in it?
- Ecstasy.
Excuse me, could you
give me some information?
What size are you carrying?
You shouldn't have to ask.
We have already met each other!
The seminarian!
With a white collar,
the other day on the bus!
- What are you doing here?
- I'm doing my research!
How can I do a thesis about sin,
and not know what it is?
Viens avec moi!
Oh god, I'm gonna scream!
Shriek, bellow!
Ah, I never met a tongue
with a hard-on, you're great!
Are you sick?
No, not at all.
I am OK.
How's it going?
I'm minus underpants!
Give me one of those drinks!
Hello? Yeah, what's up?
What's the news?
No, shit no, back off!
I don't give a fuck
about any guarantee.
Just get me the fucking money quick,
or it's your ass!
Paolo!
It's Diana!
You got a party?
Oh, yeah. It's great fun, fantastic!
Diana, it's 4 A.M. You're drunk
Come back home.
- Who is with you?
- Men! A lot of men!
A group of fabulous men!
It's Paolo! Guys, say hi!
Hi, Paolo!
How's it sound, dear!
Stop it! I forbid you!
I'm your husband!
Nah, you know who you are?
You're a dumb stupid asshole!
I am free! I can sleep
with the whole planet!
And not only that,
I might not ever come home!
Come back or not, who gives a shit,
you won't find me anyway!
I'm getting my ass outta here.
I've had it.
I go to my parents!
Go, Go, Go!
I can't believe I ever sucked
your cock, shitface!
So, hurry to little mama
and, and screw her!
Cuckold!
Where are you going?
- Have you had it with the party?
- Yeah, he's gonna give me a lift.
I am exhausted.
and besides, I'm worried.
Paolo's threatening to move out.
Ah, come on, never!
He's too in love, that boy!
- I'm leaving.
- Fine, great. I'll stay a little more.
I found a hero of the resistance.
Think about what you do, Diana.
Think of us.
I love you. Paolo. "
do you still love me?
Dear Marikla,
not only do I still love him
But in my own way
I feel that I'm a faithful wife.
Going with other men doesn't mean
I'm betraying him.
Those are just casual flings
of no importance at all.
Oh, they're great for a quick thrill.
But they have nothing at all to do
with that mixture of body and soul,
that makes my relationship
with Paolo beautiful and unique.
That's why I have no guilty feelings,
no contrition,
I have no remorse.
That's why I don't want
the love we share to finish like this.
But how do I go about
making him understand that?
Diana.
Journal "Feelings", Milan.
Hey Sara! Come here!
Want some? I just caught.
- No! I hate them!
- Feel bad, uh?
Just think, you could be
between Diana's legs right now,
instead of sitting here
eating your heart out.
What are you getting out of it?
- Nothing!
- That's bullshit!
- You got a hard-on!
- He's a goddam traitor!
- Anything! You want me to say?
- No, no way! I'll tell you.
Your cock is more
intelligent than you.
He's got his priorities straight, he knows
she gives you everything with love.
He feels that you're acting like
a bit of an ass-hole.
Yes, because actually,
you should approve of her.
Yeah, you know what that means?
That he's a prick!
Yes, God, thank you!
Anyway what good is it
to destroy yourself with jealousy?
Develop a sense of irony and
have a laugh about it! With Diana!
Hey there!
Dig up any clams yet?
Hey, you know
I think we should be going!
- Okay!
- Must be looking for us!
Hello!
Yes? Who's there? Hello!
- Please fuck yourself in the ear.
- Who was that?
Probably an anonymous admirer.
This is the second time today.
But he will return, do not worry!
Husbands always do that.
Hello? Hello?
Who is this?
Paolo? Is that you?
Can't you say some little thing?
You're still hoping! What does he have,
this guy, that's so special?
I love him.
He has something special,
but he does not understand.
It's all his fault!
Fidelity is not natural!
Yeah, yeah. But anyhow he's gone.
Oh, oh my God, there he is now!
- Who? Paolo!
- No, not Paolo!
The Commodore Scarfatti,
with his latest piece, uh, niece!
That man is so butch
I just can't bear him!
- It's yours!
- Fine, I'll take the commission!
Hello, Commodore.
What a pleasure to see you again!
My dear Antonietta.
This is my long-lost niece, Maria.
A new?
Well, your family's remarkable!
All the nieces are so pretty!
Well ...
I've told Maria all about your things.
She wants some styles...
that are truly intimate.
- You understand me?
- I certainly do, Commodore.
Let's see what we can find.
What color?
White, red, black?
- Miss, what do you prefer?
- What do you think, uncle?
I must ask Antonietta just how
she feels about it.
Well, I always say
there's nothing like black, myself.
When a person has a light complexion
like your niece,
the effect is sensational!
Unless Maria
just stuck in there!
From there? Oh no!
My uncle, Come.
Give me your opinion.
I'm coming honey, I am coming.
It sounds a little too big.
Want to show us?
Of course, Commodore,
whatever you like!
Now do you see what I mean?
It's disgraceful to take advantage
of a young lady like that!
Sorry it saddens you.
Next the panties!
This girl is older than it seems.
She knows exactly what she wants.
Perfect!
And now the denouement, a fast fuck!
If he can manage to do it!
He'll manage, he'll manage!
And not just one!
It's just evil! Certain perversions
are simply intolerable!
It's all in how you look at it!
Do the same and it would bring
lots of customers like him,
and I could take
my retirement!
This is outrageous
he does so with his niece.
I know, and I've seen a lot!
Maybe for the commander,
that's right, love.
Love? He does not know
what it means!
No more than you
who only know the sex!
Diana, my dear,
is something wrong?
It's a bad period
I just have to get through.
- I had an argument with Paolo.
- Poor little innocent thing!
You mustn't have the clients
see you like that.
Come into my office.
So what's going on?
Tell me everything!
There's not much to tell,
Mister Silvio.
Paolo left me!
Oh my poor dear, cry your heart out.
You'll feel better.
It's awful. All because I went to bed
with a couple of other guys.
I'm sorry,
I did not want to hurt him.
Of course, I understand.
You did nothing wrong.
Oh, Mister Silvio.
What are you doing?
Nothing, nothing.
It's going to get better.
Hey! Wowee!
It's him!
I know the sound of that horn!
Diana, where are you going?
I told you:
A husband is just like a bad penny!
Mr. Silvio is a pig.
How is your family?
I did not go see them.
Really? That surprises me.
- I have something to say.
- To me? I'm listening.
I'll begin by saying
I'll never get over what went on.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm serious, Diana.
- I'm not joking around, you know!
- I know. Neither do I.
I can not leave you.
It's stronger than me.
Oh, Paolo!
I love you, Paolo!
So I made a decision:
live with your rules.
Do what you like
from now on.
I love when my man
talk like that!
- Who the hell gave you that?
- No, Paolo.
- Paolo, you go again already!
- I just want to know.
Before, I would have said
it was my lover,
This time around I'll just say
that I bumped into a tree.
Tell me the truth, Diana.
I need to know.
All right Paolo, the French antiquarian,
he's completely mad about little me.
You can do better than that.
Cousin Marco, he's arranging
an elopement with me.
Go ahead, torture me.
Get your jollies?
I have always done everything
to please you.
And I did it, right?
Yes, it's true.
I like the way you are.
I will not ask more questions.
And from now on,
the only truth is that!
What a beautiful ass,
I find
that embellishes this piece.
I bet you have not noticed
it was remakes.
It does not show.
There was a long tear
right in the middle.
Did you like
Your first night in Venice?
It was great.
That's it
what you have to say?
After all I've done
you dare say that?
It was fantastic
and I've never much enjoyed!
No, not now.
You'll ruin my eye-liner!
I have to go. Late already.
Where are you going dressed like that?
- Date with cousin Marco?
- I have no idea where I'll go.
The weather is beautiful.
Venice is a city that excites me.
And I'm happy!
Goodbye, my love.
I'm so in love with, with my husband.
My own way I feel I'm a faithful wife.
The other men are just casual flings.
That's why I feel no guilt.
Believe me, I did nothing wrong.
But how can I get him to see it? Diana.
Dear Diana. Hundreds of girls write me that
they betray their husbands, but love them.
What you call a whopping
is no longer the prerogative of
only the males in our society.
It belongs to the women too.
And men should not be jealous.
I tell my readers
to live marriage as a film,
not like a sporting event.
Instead of torture,
play an imaginary role.
Many women
have understood all that.
Just read their letters. "
Dear Marikla, I work as a cleaner
with a widower.
He likes to look at me and I can not
wear underwear.
I let him touch me
and sometimes more.
Am I abnormal?
Venice is an alcove,
more than just a city.
A French poet named it
sexe, femelle, d'Europe.
Alphonse, isn't it?
Mm-hmm.
I love you.
And me?
You love me?
I'll settle for loving this.
What about you? Do you love me?
Can't you tell that I love you?
Hey, that area's delicate too,
take it easy!
I know, but for the camera!
The problem is, I don't know how much
film is left in aunt Emma's camera!
Forget about the camera!
Concentrate on me!
Darling, it's true, we should live
our marriage as though it was a film.
A precious heirloom
for our grand children!
END
Synchro and Corrections: FCB