- Hey, Bobby.
- Hey, Nikki. The usual.
- Alrighty.
- Hey, Bob.
You guys wanna play pool?
- What a waste of space.
- What do you mean?
He hit a bad patch.
We all hit bad patches, don't we?
- You never hit a bad patch?
- No, this is my dream job.
- I'm gonna talk to him.
- Please, man.
These guys come to relax. You bug
them, they're gonna stop coming here.
I know him. I've talked to him
on the phone.
Hey, Bob.
Can I talk to you for a second?
- Sure. You wanna talk to me?
- Maybe we can go someplace.
- Let me finish the game.
- Okay.
Primo, it's late, man. All right?
- Tell me what it is you want.
- I want nothing.
You don't understand
how things work here.
Because it's different
from where you come from.
What's different?
Look, when a player like me
comes into a team like this...
...hey, man, shit gets worked out.
Right? You don't...
What is the problem with that?
What kind of uniforms
do you have down there?
- Just uniforms.
- Like these pussy pants you're wearing?
- What...? What colour?
- Blue.
- What number is on the backof yours?
- Eleven.
Primo, what is your price?
No price. You already
had a chance, baby. Okay?
- What's your fucking price?
- Go fuck yourself.
- Hey, don't walk away from me, man.
- Fuck you.
Motherfucker. What?
- Break it up!
- Get off of him.
- I want my fucking number, man.
- Chill out.
What are we talking about
Juan Primo for...
...when we've got Bobby Rayburn where
we want him, up close and exclusive.
Are you ready for your next caller?
- Let's get another caller.
- Bobby.
- You guys are getting a kickout of this.
- What are you talking about?
I'm talking about my season is like
a bad freeway accident.
And you guys, you're just
slowing down to watch.
I thought I'd enjoy this,
but the fact is, I feel for you.
I didn't know it'd be so rough.
Who we talking to? On the car phone,
we are talking to Gil.
Hey, is that our old buddy Gil?
Mr. Magical-Conjunction himself.
- Is this Jewel?
- You're on the air. Go ahead.
You're getting break-up
on the line here.
- I heard what you said about Primo.
- What's your question for Bobby?
Is Bobby listening? Bobby?
Hey, Bob?
Yeah, Gil, I'm here, man.
How you doing?
I wanna tell you that I know exactly
what you're going through...
...more than you'll ever understand.
This number 11 thing is a fucking joke.
You're the greatest player
this city's ever had...
...and you got some hot-dogger
like Primo...
...giving you a hard time
about your number.
There's a reason
you're paid 40 million.
The owners aren't doing
what they should be.
They should be protecting
their investment.
Pay him. Give him what he wants.
If he wants a million, give it to him.
If he doesn't want it and doesn't want
to give up his number, fuck him.
Get him out. What's the difference?
Just get you hitting again.
- Lf that's what it's gonna take.
- They say fans don't know...
...what they're talking about. The public
and the owners should listen to you.
Bobby, why isn't this guy
on your payroll?
Thanks, Gil. Maybe I should have you
try and talk some sense into Primo.
God knows I need
all the help I can get.
They say fans don't know
what they're talking about.
The public and the owners
should listen to you.
Bobby, why isn't this guy
on your payroll?
Maybe I should have you try
and talk some sense into Primo.
The owners should listen to you. Bobby,
why isn't this guy on your payroll?
Maybe I should have you try
and talk some sense into Primo.
God knows I need all the help
I can get.
Primo. Primo, lots of luck.
Primo.
Mr. Primo?
- Yeah?
- Can I just say...?
Did you ever think how one man
who's doing well...
...might throw off
the rest of the team?
I'm saying, you have to thinkof
what's best for the team, right?
You might have to
lay down a sacrifice.
I'm talking about
Bobby Rayburn's number.
I don't know if you understand
how much he needs that number.
- Number 11.
- I am number 11.
I know, but he needs it
more than you.
Are you with the press?
You with the hotel?
Then get out of here.
Go.
Get the fuckout of here.
It's a sad night here at the Stick
as the Giants tak e the field...
... for the first time since the murder
of hitting sensation Juan Primo.
Rayburn will take his place
in the lineup batting cleanup.
There's bound to be questions
about that, Jewel.
Now we all get to wear
the number, man.
Come on, let's play ball!
Now batting fourth, number 33,
Bobby Rayburn.
Bobby! Come on, Bobby!
Fuck you.
Come on, Bob!
That's it.
Attaway. You're back to your old self.
Fuck you.
This is the last place I'll look.
Then I'll quit.
Yeah, no, I've had it. I'm tired.
I mean, he's not here.
There he is. I found my man.
I'll talk to you later.
Is this how you celebrate
going four for four, huh?
What happened to pouring
champagne over your head...
...and banging some groupies, huh?
Bobby. Bobby, talk to me.
If the cops worry you,
they're not interested in you.
It's just an ongoing investigation.
Let it go.
I didn't ask for this, man.
You talking about Primo?
Come on, I know that's shit.
I thought about it a lot,
but I didn't ask for this.
You know, Bobsy...
...I wish five people dead
on my drive to work.
Five people. But wishing it
doesn't make it so.
You're not God,
lifetime average withstanding.
Yeah? Well...
...why do I feel so bad then, huh?
I don't know.
I don't...
This is gonna blow the hell
out of my shithead theory...
...but I think you feel guilty.
Jesus-hairy-Christ.
I've been wrong about you.
You're not a shithead at all.
I'm flabbergasted.
Come on, let's go, man.
I got a game tomorrow.
Number 33, Bobby Rayburn.
Go, Bobby! Bobby!
Safe.
Bobby Rayburn.
You're coming off
the worst slump in your career.
All of a sudden, you're hitting well over
.400, 11 home runs, 30 RBIs last month.
How do you explain this?
I wish I knew.
That's it? You wish you knew?
A "thank you" would've been nice.
Sean!
Be careful!
Don't go too far!
Sean, don't go too far, darling.
Bradley!
Bradley, come here!
Bradley, come back.
Go back, Bradley. Go back.
Sean!
Mr. Rayburn!
Shit.
Sean!
- Thank God for Mark Spitz over here.
- Jeez.
Okay. Just relax. Go on.
That's right, blow it out.
It's gonna be all right.
Are you all right, man?
- Just relax.
- He swallowed some water.
Jesus. You scared me half to death.
Where did you come from?
I was just walking on the beach,
I saw him in the water, and I went in.
Thank God, man. You all right?
Sean, you gotta promise me,
no matter what...
...not a word to your mother,
understand?
Next time you're looking
for attention, be more dramatic.
- Let's get some dry clothes.
- Play in traffic like the other kids.
- That little bonehead.
- Oh, shit.
- What did you say your name was?
- My friends call me Curly.
Curly. Well, come on, Curly,
let's go inside.
Elvira will get you some
dry clothes, all right?
Thank you.
- What do I say?
- Well, you know, I was just there.
You would've done the same thing.
If I lose this guy, man,
I don't know what I would do.
Looks good on you.
I don't know
about them pants, though.
They're yours.
- Can I get you anything?
- A beer.
Yeah, all right. I could swear...
Have I seen you before?
I get that all the time.
I got one of those faces, I guess.
You like baseball?
I'm not obsessed with it or anything.
Are you a player?
Yeah.
- You are?
- Yeah.
Barry Bonds?
No. No. I'm Bobby Rayburn.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- I was just kidding you.
- It's okay.
At least you're not one of them
die- hard baseball fans who...
Why is that?
Because those guys are losers.
Aren't the fans what it's all about?
Shit. Tell you something, man.
The fans are like women.
When you're hitting, they love you.
And when you're not, they'd as soon
spit on you as look at you.
Why is that?
Because they don't understand that
you're the same person hitting or not.
You know?
Only person you should play for
is yourself.
Hey, you wanna shoot some pool?
Yeah, sure.
- All right. Bring the beer.
- Sure.
Curly, Curly"..."
Curly Otis?
- Yeah, that's my old man.
- No shit.
I was in bigs for a cup of coffee myself
until my arm went south.
Man, tough break.
It's like my old catcher Coop
used to say:
"Enjoy it while you got it,
then move on."
Yeah.
That's a good philosophy, brother.
Good philosophy.
- Are all those hats yours?
- Yep, my pride and joy.
- Could I try one on?
- Yeah, sure. Sure.
Fits.
Looks good on you.
Hey, Bobby...
...did you mean it?
You'd do something for me?
Yeah, sure. I mean, within reason,
you know.
Don't be getting no ideas.
- Let me pitch to you.
- What?
Let me show you what I got.
I got a couple innings left in me.
Come on, Bobby,
let me show you what I got.
Bradley's gonna catch for us.
Must feel good
to be hitting again, huh?
Brother, you have no idea.
- How did you get out of that slump?
- Say what?
Got any idea what got you
out of that slump?
You know, Curly...
...I just stopped caring, man.
- What?
- I just stopped caring.
You stopped caring?
What do you mean?
All my life I've been working
to be the best.
You know?
Trying to be a perfectionist.
And I thought about it. That's probably
where I made my mistake.
And when Juan Primo died, man, that
completely changed the perspective.
I mean"..."
I mean, come on, let's be real here.
What are we doing? We're not
curing cancer, you know?
We're playing a game.
That's all it is. It's just a game.
So I stopped caring and relaxed...
...and I started hitting.
Stopped caring.
So that's your fucking insight
into life?
Just stop caring.
- You're pretty loose now, aren't you?
- Yeah.
All I'm saying is that there's
more to life than just baseball.
Like what? Like your house?
Like your bigass car?
Like your 40-fucking-million?
I mean, what the fuck
do you care about?
I care about my son.
That's what I care about.
I'm sorry. I just hate that attitude,
you stopped caring. I'm sorry.
What, do you have a better theory?
Yeah.
You got your number back.
Curly, my number didn't have
anything to do with it.
It looks good on you.
Thanks.
- That's great.
- I still haven't given you my best pitch.
- Sure you have.
- No.
Okay.
Look, Curly, I really want to thank you
for what you did for my son.
You know, what do you say?
Let's call it a night?
All right.
Come on, admit it. We're alone.
Admit what?
Admit you're hitting
because Primo's not around.
That's a bunch of bullshit.
Come on.
It doesn't hurt he's not around.
Come on, level with me.
Level with me.
Come on, I saved your kid.
You wanna pay me back?
Be honest with me and tell me
you're a little happy that he's dead.
- Hey.
- No, no. I'm not happy that he's dead.
Come on.
Curly. Curly, I already told you no.
No, I am not happy
that he's dead. Okay?
Okay? Can I have my hand back now?
Thanks.
I'm really tired. Really.
I'm going to sleep. Take care.
Simple "thank you"
would have been nic"e..."
...for a teammate
who lays down a sacrifice.
Hey, look,
you need a ride or anything?
I got my own wheels. Thanks, Bob.
Good. Bradley, let's go.
If you need anything,
just call me, all right?
And I'll get back to you.
Okay, bye.
Take care. Come on, Bradley.
Hey, Bob?
Bobby. What about the glove, Bob?
Keep it!
I remember when Mick recorded this.
December '77.
We drove home at dawn.
Who's Mick?
A great friend of mine.
- Where we going?
- We're going fishing.
- Why can't my dad come?
- Your dad could come.
But he has a big game tomorrow,
and we gotta pick up Coop.
Why are we fishing at night?
Night fishing is best. No boats
to scare the fish away.
We'll sucker them in with a flashlight,
cut them up with this.
Go ahead, take it. It's yours.
- You sure?
- Yeah, it's yours. Take it.
- Well, thanks.
- Just don't cut yourself.
- Hello.
- Hey, Curly.
Hey, Bobby. Hey.
Say hello to your father.
He's on the phone.
Hi, Dad. We're going fishing.
That's great. That's great, Sean.
Listen, Curly, could you
pick up the handset so we could talk?
Sure thing, slugger.
- Yeah.
- Curly, is it raining where you are?
- No, I'm far from the beach.
- Didn't know you'd take the car.
- I thought the kid, he'd like to get away.
- Listen, Curly...
...before you do anything stupid,
I don't think this is a good idea.
You don't think. You're a lucky idiot.
I'm not fucking with you.
- All right.
- Don't get angry at me, Bob.
- Curly?
- Bob?
I just want my son back.
- What?
- Bobby.
- What?!
Listen to you. You're hanging on every
word I say. This is really something.
Curly, what do you want?
What do you want from me?
Don't talk back.
You show me some respect.
Without people like me,
you're nothing.
We're the ones that get you
your 40 million.
- Look, what do you want?
- What do I want?
I want when they thinkof you,
they thinkof me.
Curly, I don't know what the fuck
I did to you to piss you off...
...but my son has nothing
to do with this.
Oh, Bobby, it's not what you did to me,
it's what I did for you, number 11.
- You owe me.
- I owe you what?
Check your freezer.
I'll hang on.
- There's a surprise.
- What the f...? Curly.
- Go ahead, check your freezer.
- All right, I'll check the freezer.
Curly, don't hang up this phone.
You hear me?
Oh, my God!
He finally figures it out,
ladies and gentlemen.
It's really true what they say
about sluggers.
They are really, really stupid.
Well, I'm a pitcher, Bobby.
Pitchers use their brains.
Come on, Bradley.
We'll play a joke on him,
so you just play along.
- All right.
- Okay?
Hey, Coop.
Gil.
- Gil Renard.
- Yeah.
Gil Renard.
Yeah, long time no see, Gil.
- This is my son.
- Hi.
Come on in, fellas.
Go ahead.
Man, that is a kick-ass car.
You done good for yourself.
You never see nothing like that
in the Bronx.
I always thought
you'd be managing by now.
- Managing?
- Yeah, in the majors.
Nobody calls me Coop anymore,
you sick son of a bitch.
How'd you find me anyway?
I looked you up.
Whose kid is that, really?
- You really want to know?
- Yeah.
- Bobby Rayburn's.
- Jesus fuck.
Same old fucking Gil. Come on.
Really?
He'll be on in a minute.
You'll recognize his voice.
All right, incoming call. Notify
incoming call. Turn off all radios.
Okay, this is it.
Bob.
- Yeah.
- Hey, Bobby, you still up?
- Bad time to be calling, huh?
- I'm up.
Hey, I hope I'm not calling at a bad time.
Probably got some people over, huh?
I can't hear you. You'll have to
turn the music down.
Oh, I'm sorry, slugger.
Curly, I want to talk to Sean.
Sean, he's asleep now, but he's doing
fine. Don't worry about him. He's fine.
- Curly, what do you want?
- "I've been thinking it over."
You know, in life, life just...
...comes down to one single action.
What do you want?
I want you to hit a home run
for me, Bob.
Are you serious?
Remember that kid in chemo...
...whose life was unfair to him?
That's how I'm feeling.
My life has been unfair to me.
The only difference is, I'll be able to see
you hit that home run tomorrow.
And I got a photo here.
I'm gonna get it to you. And I want you
to put it on the Jumbotron, okay?
- Yeah.
- Then I want you to stand up and tell...
...the 50 million viewers...
...that this home run
is dedicated to Gil, a true fan.
- What do you think?
- I can't believe you're serious.
I'm serious as a heart attack, Bobby.
That's pretty serious, isn't it?
There comes a time in everybody's life
when you have to stand for something.
Otherwise, you're just
passing on through.
So, Bobby, I'm watching you.
If that pitcher goes easy on you,
I'll kill your fucking kid.
Surprise, surprise.
Hey, Bobby.
I'm still here.
Now do you care?
You get in some serious shit for that.
Cops are gonna be all over us.
Boy, all of a sudden,
you lost your sense of humour.
- Did you get it?
- Couldn't get him.
He's calling from Rayburn's car. We
should be able to nail him to the district.
You're not gonna believe this kid.
Just like old times, huh, Coop?
- You know, that's not my real dad.
- It's okay, kid.
Come on, I'm waiting.
I'm waiting. The signals.
What happened? Did you forget
everything? Come on, Coop.
Hang in there, kid.
Bring the bat up, slugger.
Come on, look like a hitter.
Bring it up.
Bring it up. Come on.
Come on! Come on, slugger,
bring the fucking bat up.
Come on.
That's my boy.
It's all right, kid, hang in there, now.
Hang in there.
Coop, you dickhead!
Come on, kid. Come on.
Go. Go. Up the fence. Come on.
Come on, push. Push. Go.
Go. Go on. Go, kid, go.
Coop, what are you doing?
Why did you do that?
We could've been teammates.
We were teammates.
We could've made it to the bigs.
It was Little League.
We were 12 years old.
Come on.
That's my boy.
Ladies and gentlemen,
leading off the second inning...
... Giants centre fielder, number 33,
Bobby Rayburn.
Well, the forecast is for rain tonight.
There's a mist falling as Rayburn steps
towards the box.
He's been more aggressive
the last month of the season.
Who do we have on line two?
- Just a fan.
- Hey, Mr. Fan, how you doing?
Wanna say you're lucky to be
in the stadium tonight.
Really? Why's that?
- Is that a Giants watch I hear playing?
- Yes, it is.
- Is that my buddy Gil?
- Maybe.
This'll be one of the most amazing
nights in the game's history.
- "It'll be incredible."
- Really? Why's that, Gil?
I'm telling you,
the Kirk Gibson homer...
...Ripken breaking Gehrig's record,
peanuts compared to tonight.
You're talking about classic moments
in baseball history.
What's happening tonight
that could top those?
Let's just say Bobby Rayburn's...
- "... in for the night of his life."
- Why, Gil?
Well, some people are ungrateful.
They should be taught a lesson.
Strike!
Are you calling from
inside the stadium?
- Wouldn't you like to know?
- "Well..."
You got good seats? Are you behind
first base? Can you see me?
Can I see you?
Yeah, you're waving right at me.
Have a nice night.
Gil, wait. Before you hang up,
I wanted to ask you a question.
- Trying to trace the call, Jewel?
- What? What was that, Gil?
You'll never find me.
- Strike!
- Have a nice night.
Gil. Fuck!
Come on, man, go get him!
Play!
Yes!
Shit.
Now batting, number 10, Brad Tjader.
- Did you feel that raindrop?
- What?
I felt rain.
- The guy's not gonna be crazy enough...
- He's here! The guy's here.
- He could've been near a radio.
- He's in the stadium.
Look at that. That is one fine piece
of craftsmanship.
- What?
- The knife.
It's a first edition. See how it
says "prototype?
That means it's a collector's piece.
"Renard & Garrity." It's a local firm,
isn't it? Gilbert Renard?
What are you waiting for,
a clue, an invite?
This guy is gonna kill Bobby's kid
if you don't find him in nine innings.
Ladies and gentlemen, leading off
the bottom of the eighth...
... number 33, Bobby Rayburn.
Bobby's as safe as Kennedy was
in Dallas. What are you looking for?
Play!
Ball one.
- What, are you walking me?
- Consider it a compliment, dickhead.
Fuck! Do you know what you're
doing to me?!
- They're giving him first base.
- Throw the pitch!
Fuck!
Fuck.
Oh, man, the ump's gonna
call the game. Oh, my... Fuck.
Oh, God, please don't do this.
I'm begging you.
Don't... Throw the pitch.
For God's sake, listen to me!
Throw the pitch!
Throw the fucking pitch!
- Do you know what you're doing to me?
- "The umpire has decided..."
... to send both teams
into the dugouts.
It looks like we've got a rain delay.
Ladies and gentlemen, the umpire
has called for a rain delay...
... with the Padres
leading the Giants 2 to 1.
Do you and your dad have a special
place he and you like to go?
Stadium in the Sky's
our Little League park.
My dad used to play there
when he was a kid.
Is my daddy in trouble?
Ladies and gentlemen...
... we resume play with the Giants
batting in the bottom of the eighth.
Proceed to Little League park
Stadium in the Sky, 24th and Sanchez.
We pick it up in the eighth inning...
...on what might be Rayburn's
last at-bat.
They'll play on this wet field.
The cold night air is getting
to everybody. Look at Rayburn.
He's going to the mound to have
a chat with Martinez.
- Oh, shit.
- I don't give a fuck what he tells you.
Throw the ball over the plate,
or I'll break your head in.
- Fuck you.
- You hear me?
This may go back to when Martinez
pitched for Pittsburgh.
He drilled Rayburn in his back
with a fastball.
We are seeing it all tonight, Rick.
- Let's go, gentlemen.
- First pitch is at your head, buddy.
Come on, man, do this! Do this!
A critical at-bat for Rayburn,
the $40 million San Francisco Giant.
Probably his last chance
to get the Giants even.
Here in the bottom of the eighth,
the Giants trail 2 to 1.
- "Swung on. Strik e one."
- Strike!
All right, come on! Come on, Bobby!
Swung on and missed. Strik e two.
Rayburn in the hole.
One strik e left
for Bobby Rayburn tonight.
Jesus Christ, man.
Air Seven copy. Proceeding
to Stadium in the Sky. Over.
- Man.
- They're gonna call the game.
They're gonna call this fucking game.
Two and two. Two balls, two strik es.
And Rayburn down to his last strik e.
Bobby knows he's had
two pitches to drive there.
Now at 2-2, you're not gonna
get another good pitch to hit.
Maybe, since it's damp, he's having
trouble holding the ball.
This game could be called
at any second.
Play ball!
San Diego protecting
its one-run lead.
Martinez readies, steadies
and delivers to...
Rayburn drives it deep
to right centre field!
- Yes!
- Yes! Go!
- Run!
- Home run!
It's off the wall. Rayburn could get
three if he hustles.
Robinson having trouble
just getting to the ball.
Rayburn, rounding second,
headed for third.
He ran through the stop sign. It could
be an inside-the-park home run!
The relay from Park er!
Rayburn slides, headfirst!
And he is...
... in there!
Yes!
You're out!
What is that?
Bad fucking call, man!
- You're out! Sit down!
- No, no, no.
I beat it by a fucking mile!
You're out. You're questioning my call?
Sit down! You're out! Sit down!
You're the fucking guy!
He's the fucking guy!
It's the umpire!
What the fuck is that?
This way! Break it open!
- Shit.
- What the hell's going on?
Okay, okay. I just want my kid back.
Batter up, Bobby.
I waited a long time for this.
No, no, no, wait. No. Okay, look.
- Where's Sean?
- Where do you think he is?
Come on, where is my son?
Where's...? Bobby,
where's my home run?
What?! Curly. Curly.
Where's my son?!
Where is he? I don't know.
I guess he's in that big stadium
in the sky.
I'm telling you, Curly,
if you hurt my fucking kid...
...I swear to God I'll kill you!
- Bobby. Bobby. Be nice, Bob.
What do you want from me?
I don't want anything.
I just want you to...
- I never showed you my best pitch.
- Curly!
Curly!
Freeze!
No, no, don't shoot! He's got my son.
Now do you care?
Bobby, now do you care?
Just a little bit?
Curly, don't!
Curly, where's my son?
Where's Sean, Curly?
Where's my son?
A simple "thank you"
would have been nice.
Where's my son?
Curly, where's my son?!
There she is,
site of the old stadium.
Sean!
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- I love you, Sean.
- I love you, Dad.
I got him!
What you are seeing here
is a sad turn of events indeed.
Gil Renard, an unemployed
knife salesman...
... was shot to death by the police
during tonight's game.
Here's how it happened.
Bobby Rayburn...