From Adam to Seth, from Seth
to Enosh...
Enosh to Kenan, Kenan to
Mahalalel...
to my father, Methuselah, then
to me.
Today, that birthright passes
to you...
Noah.
My son.
The Creator made Adam in
His image...
and then placed the world
in his care.
This is your work now.
Your responsibility.
May you walk alongside The
Creator in righteousness.
So I say to you...
The Shrine of Seth!
Men.
Hide.
We mine here.
The ground is rich with tzohar.
This is The Creator's land.
What are you doing?
The Creator?
My mines run dry.
My city withers and must be fed.
And what has He done?
He cursed us to struggle by the
sweat of our brow to survive!
Damned if I don't do everything
it takes to do just that.
Damned if I don't take
what I want.
This relic belongs to the
descendants of Cain now.
The line of Seth ends here.
It is ours.
Now, dig!
Ham.
What are you doing?
It's pretty.
You see those other flowers?
How they're attached to
the ground?
That's where they should be.
They have a purpose.
They sprout.
And they bloom.
The wind takes their seeds,
and more flowers grow.
We only collect what we can use,
and what we need.
Do you understand?
Shem.
Ham.
Let's go.
Men.
Hide, hide.
Go.
You found our kill.
How fortunate.
But for you maybe not.
You know how long it is since
we ate meat?
Since we even saw an animal?
Easy.
Please.
What do you want?
Justice.
Why did they kill it?
They eat them.
Why?
They think it makes them stronger.
Is it true?
They forget strength comes
from The Creator.
Mama!
Mommy!
See your brothers?
Ham saw men hunting today.
They are getting closer.
How was he?
A little too interested.
He had to see it sometime.
I saw something else.
A flower...
bloom from nothing.
Rest.
Perhaps He will finally make
things right.
Methuselah.
Did He speak to you?
I think so.
Will He help us?
He's going to destroy the world.
It's a long and dangerous journey
for the boys.
How do you know your grandfather's
still alive?
I don't.
I saw his mountain.
We need to go and find out if
he knows what we're to do.
Shem.
Can you help me with this?
We could take the boys and
find a place to hide.
There'll be no hiding.
We should have left already.
Ham, let me show you how to
do that.
Push it in here.
Next time we come through...
we'll know we've got certain
things we might need.
There are cities ahead.
We will not get too close.
Is that a Tzohar mine?
It was once.
Before they dug it all up.
Should we go around?
No.
Do you think they're all dead?
It looks that way.
They must have been scavenging
here.
And someone scavenged from them.
Dada!
Stay close.
Father!
Here!
May I see?
Let me see.
Tell me your name.
You have a name?
Ila.
My name is Ila.
You're going to be all right,
Ila.
This is Shem.
He's going to hold your hand
tight, and he won't let go.
Up the hill!
Hurry! Hurry!
We have to go.
Now.
Up the hill.
Run.
We can't go there.
We have no choice.
Hurry!
Hold, men!
Hold!
The giants!
They'll kill you!
Shem!
Protect your mother, first
and last.
I love you.
Run!
Noah!
Noah. Noah.
Are you all right?
We are to see Methuselah.
My grandfather.
A child of the old one?
You should have killed them.
But, Samyaza...
This is a man, Og.
Do you forget how they betrayed
The Creator?
It is He who sends us!
It lies!
Leave them here to rot.
What are they?
The Watchers.
Dada?
Sleep now.
Sing to me.
I want my daddy to sing to me.
You know, I, too, lost my father
when I was very young.
There's a song he used to
sing me sometimes...
when I couldn't sleep.
Would you like to hear it?
The moon is high.
The trees entwine.
Your Father waits for thee...
to wrap you in His sheltering
wings...
and whisper you to sleep.
Your Father is...
the healing wind...
that whispers you to sleep.
That whispers as you sleep.
It's an ugly wound.
She'll never have children.
If the fever doesn't take her,
I think she'll live.
Follow me.
I'm sorry I frightened you.
Watchers have learned to
fear men.
Then why are you helping us?
The Creator formed us on the
second day.
The day He made the heavens.
We watched over Adam and Eve.
Saw their frailty and their
love.
And then we saw their fall.
And we pitied them.
We were not stone then, but
light.
It was not our place to interfere.
Yet we chose to try and help
mankind.
And when we disobeyed The
Creator...
He punished us.
We were encrusted by your world.
Rock and mud shackled our fiery
glow.
Still, we taught mankind all
we knew of Creation.
With our help...
they rose from the dust, became
great and mighty.
But then they turned our gifts
to violence.
Only one man protected us.
Your grandfather Methuselah.
We were hunted.
Most of us killed.
Those who lived...
were left prisoners in these
stony shells...
marooned upon this barren land.
We begged The Creator to take
us home.
But He was always silent.
And now you claim that you have
heard His call.
Samyaza cannot accept this.
A man? When it is men who
broke the world.
But I look at you...
and I see a glimmer of Adam,
again.
The man I knew.
The man I came to help.
Why can't I come?
Because I need you to look
after Mother.
Do you understand?
And you look after your father.
Watch over them.
They are in good hands.
Grandfather?
Noah.
This is your great-grandfather.
Show him respect.
Tell him your name.
I am Shem.
My eldest.
Come closer.
Let me see you.
You're a lucky boy.
I think you must have your
mother's looks...
not your father's.
Come tell me about yourself.
So, what do you like most, in
the world?
Berries.
What?
Berries, yes.
What can compete with fresh,
ripe berries? Nothing.
Yes, it's been so long...
I can barely remember the taste
of them.
Tell me, did you bring me any?
No?
I'm craving them now.
Well, perhaps one day.
You must be tired.
It's a long way, up here.
Yeah.
Why not rest?
How perfect.
What we need to discuss is not
for boys.
You know why I've come?
Yes.
Before he walked on, my father
Enoch told me that one day...
if man continued in his ways...
The Creator would annihilate
this world.
So what I saw is true?
All life blotted out because
of what man has done?
Can it not be averted?
Noah, you must trust that He
speaks in a way...
that you can understand.
So, you tell me.
Can this destruction be averted?
No.
He sent me here.
Why send me if there's nothing
I can do to stop it?
Well, perhaps He simply sends
you here...
to share a cup of tea with
an old man.
So, is that all you saw?
The fires of destruction on
this place?
No, not fire.
Water.
Water?
My father said it would be fire.
I saw water.
Death by water.
I saw death.
And I saw new life.
There's something more,
Grandfather.
Something I'm to do.
I know it.
I just didn't see what it was.
New life.
Well, perhaps there is more
for you to see.
Did He not send you here to drink
a cup of tea with an old man?
The medicine always tastes bad.
She was the only one moving.
Was she hurt badly?
She had a big cut on her belly.
Mother helped and I held her
hand.
That must have made her feel
safe.
Well?
Fire consumes all.
Water cleanses.
It separates the foul from the
pure.
The wicked from the innocent.
And that which sinks from that
which rises.
He destroys all...
but only to start again.
You sure?
Yes.
The storm cannot be stopped.
But it can be survived.
Yeah.
You may need this.
It's a seed.
From the first Garden.
From Eden.
Remember, Noah...
He chose you for a reason.
You can't get me!
Dada!
My grandfather lives.
He's helped me see what we're
here to do.
Men are going to be punished for
what they've done to this world.
There will be destruction.
There will be tragedy.
And our family has been chosen
for a great task.
We've been chosen to save
the innocent.
The innocent?
The animals.
Why are they innocent?
Because they still live as
they did in the Garden.
Yes.
And we need to save enough of
them to start again.
But what of us?
I guess we get to start
again, too.
We get to start again in a new
and better world.
But first...
we have to build.
Build what?
A great flood is coming.
The waters of the heavens will
meet the waters of the earth.
We build a vessel to survive
the storm.
We build an ark.
Take the traitor back.
He is a child of the old one!
Stop!
There is work to do.
Help us.
Help you?
We tried to help your kind once.
And we lost everything because
of you!
Not everything.
We can save what is left.
We can serve Him again.
You treacherous snake!
The Creator.
Children!
What is this?
This...
This is our ark.
We will help this man.
No!
Shem.
Wait.
Please.
It still hurts?
Ham!
Shem!
He doesn't have anyone.
Come.
Father, did you see them?
Father?
Yes, Japheth.
It begins.
Ready?
It sleeps.
Gently.
See, that's a boy one, and
that's a girl one.
After the storm, they'll become
a mother and a father.
And the hatchlings will spread
right across the world.
We have to be gentle with
them...
and we have to be protective.
If something were to happen...
that would be a small piece
of Creation lost forever.
All of these innocent creatures
are now in our care.
It's our job to look after them.
Father?
All the birds are two.
You have Mother, Shem has Ila.
But what of me?
What of Japheth?
Who is there for us?
Did you see how He made the
forest...
to give us wood for the ark?
How He sent the birds?
So...
hasn't He sent everything
we need?
Mother!
What is it?
What?
Snakes!
Snakes are coming, too?
Yeah.
All that creeps, all that crawls,
all that slithers.
It's all right.
Father!
Don't be afraid.
No one will hurt this boy.
What's your name?
Ham.
Ham?
I am Tubal-Cain.
Do you know me?
You don't know your king?
My father says there can be no
king in The Creator's garden.
Ham, come here.
Do not take my best soldier.
He's nothing of yours.
Look at his hand on that weapon.
I believe he is something of
mine.
Ham?
Leave it.
No, he gave it to me.
Do what I tell you.
When I heard talk of miracles,
I dismissed them.
But then I saw the birds with
my own eyes, flying here...
and I had to come.
There isn't anything for you,
here.
No?
This all belongs to me.
This land.
This forest.
That stronghold of yours.
Did you really think you could
protect yourself from me, in that?
It's not protection from you.
Then, what is it?
An ark...
to hold the innocent...
when The Creator sends his
deluge...
to wipe out the wicked from
this world.
The Creator does not care what
happens in this world.
Nobody has heard from Him since
He marked Cain.
We are alone.
Orphaned children...
cursed to struggle by the sweat
of our brow to survive.
Damned if I don't do everything
it takes to do just that.
Damned if I don't take what
I want.
We have met?
I am the son of Lamech!
Eight generations descended
from Seth!
Return to your cities of Cain!
Know we have all been judged!
I have men at my back, and you
stand alone and defy me?
I'm not alone.
Take the children!
Do not fear, my people!
Don't be afraid!
Stand!
Hold your line, men.
His minions, they're with you?
Miracles?
A deluge, you claim?
Well, perhaps you're right.
Perhaps casting us out of
Paradise was not enough.
Perhaps, He returns to finish
us off.
Well, if He does...
I will ride the storm in that
ship of yours.
There is no escape for you
and your kind.
Your time is done.
The land is dying.
Ham.
The cities are dead.
Don't listen to him.
My people follow me!
And more will follow them!
I'm not afraid of miracles,
son of Lamech!
If you refuse my dozens now...
I shall return with legions!
Move.
Father?
Will so many really come?
We need to finish as fast
as we can.
The sooner He sends the rain,
the better.
Until then, we're safer inside.
We build.
First weapons, then men.
Feed only those that will fight.
Arm them, train them...
and there is nothing they
can't do.
With an army, we can crush
those giants.
Please, we're hungry!
Give us meat.
Our children are starving.
Please help us!
Let us go!
We're starving!
Should I come back?
No.
Do you think those men are
going to attack us?
When the rain comes.
What do you think it'll be like?
I've imagined it.
Seeing that much death...
I'm not sure there are words.
The end of everything.
The beginning.
The beginning of everything.
So what is it?
Whatever he's done or said,
Shem is very fond of you.
Shem needs a woman.
A real woman.
He should have a family.
I can't give any of that to him.
And I'm not going to deny him
those things...
even if he wants me to.
I won't do it.
Besides...
why would The Creator want
a barren girl on His ark?
Ila... Ila.
When we first took you in...
I thought you were going to
be a burden.
And I didn't want to see anybody
else ruined by this world.
But I was wrong.
You're a gift.
A precious, precious gift.
Just don't forget how precious
a gift you are.
I know you'll be going to find
wives for Ham and Japheth.
You should find one for Shem, too.
Ila.
Where do you think you're going?
Please, please don't take my
baby!
Let them go!
Please!
Sorry, we have to eat!
Don't take my baby!
No!
Don't take my baby! No, no,
please, will you stop him?
Let them go!
No!
Quit struggling!
It'll be easier.
Come with me!
Stop struggling!
You! You!
I have two girls!
I have two girls to trade!
Take the girls!
Give me the meat!
Give it to me!
What happened?
All of this should be inside
by now.
The storm is coming.
What about our wives?
Where are they?
Did you not hear what I just
said?
But when are they coming?
There will be no wives.
What? What?
No!
You said that The Creator would
give us what we'll need.
Help your brother.
No.
Listen.
Listen, you can't do this!
You can't.
How am I supposed to be a man?
I said, help your brother.
You want me to stay a child!
No!
I'm asking you to be a man
and do what needs to be done.
Ham!
What are you doing, Noah?
The wickedness is not just
in them.
It's in all of us.
I saw it.
No.
Noah.
There's goodness in us.
Look at our boys.
Shem's loyalty.
Japheth's kindness.
Ham's integrity.
Good men.
They'd be good fathers.
Shem is blinded by desire.
Ham is covetous.
And Japheth lives only to
please.
I am no better.
And you?
Is there anything you would
not do, good or bad...
for those three boys?
We would both choose to kill,
in order to protect our children.
Yes.
We're no different.
We were weak, and we were
selfish...
to think we could set ourselves
apart.
We will work, complete the
task...
and then we'll die.
The same as everyone else.
They are children!
They are our children, Noah!
Have you no mercy?
The time for mercy has passed.
Now our punishment begins.
Ham!
Grandfather?
Did you bring me something?
Did Noah plant the seed I gave
him?
Yes.
And in all that forest there
were no berries?
Shem promised me berries.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
It's a pity.
Then why did you come here?
It's Noah.
He leaves our boys with no one.
Shem has Ila, but she's barren.
There'll be no other wives,
so no children.
Jusfice.
The Creator destroys this world
because we corrupted it.
So, we ourselves must be
destroyed.
No.
I can't believe that's true.
Not when I look at my sons.
All they desire is love.
Isn't that all their hearts
need to be good?
Who is good?
Who is wicked?
How am I supposed to know what
is right?
That choice is Noah's.
Nof mine. Not yours.
It sounds like he has made it.
So then you will not help me?
I don't know if I even could.
But if I tried, it could cause
pain and possibly tragedy.
And in the end, it would just
come back to Noah again.
Is that what you wish?
I want my sons to have children.
I want them to be happy.
I can't bear to think of them
dying alone.
Out of the way!
Coming through!
Please!
Get away!
No.
No, no...
It's all right... it's all right.
I'm not...
I'm not going to hurt you.
I have food.
Here.
What do you want?
Nothing.
Are you alone?
Yes.
And you?
I can help you get away.
No.
Well, then, I'll stay a little
while.
If that is all right?
My name is Na'el.
Shem!
Go and find them and bring
them back.
Be careful.
Ham?
Don't be afraid, granddaughter.
Don't be afraid.
Grandfather?
Yes.
What are you doing down here?
I'm looking for berries.
I have a craving.
Come and help me look for them.
My eyes aren't as good as they
used to be.
I have to find Ham.
There's time enough for that.
Come here.
Come.
Come here and help me.
They're here somewhere.
They're here somewhere, berries.
I know there are berries.
There's nothing here, Grandfather.
Let me take you to Noah.
No.
No need for that.
You go now.
You go.
Wait.
Ten years you've been with my
own. With my own family.
Ten years.
Do you love them?
Shem?
And Noah?
He saved my life.
Raised me.
Yes, he did.
Yes.
And you are now as his own
daughter.
My own great-granddaughter.
Ten years in the shadow of
my home...
and yet I have never given you
my blessing.
May I?
Ham!
Ila!
You can go now.
Go to him.
You go.
Go now.
Ila!
We have to get back...
We have to go.
Come on. Now!
I am a man.
Made in Your image.
Why will You not converse
with me?
I give life.
I take life away.
As You do!
And I am like You, am I not?
Speak to me.
Speak to me!
It has begun!
Death comes from the heavens!
This rain...
is meant to wash us off the
face of this world.
But we are men.
We decide if we live, or die.
We are men!
And men united are invincible!
Do you want to live?
Yeah!
We kill the giants!
We kill Noah!
We take the ark!
Yeah!
Noah!
Where's Ham?
Get it off me, no!
No, no, no!
We have to get away!
I won't leave you.
I won't!
Ham!
Father, help!
Help!
Help her!
Help me, please!
Please, help me, please!
Please... someone please
help me!
Help me!
No!
Ham!
Samyaza!
Noah!
Where is Ham?
Ham is through!
Quickly!
Run!
Ham.
Ham!
Faster!
Forward!
Protect your mother.
Protect them all.
Part!
My Creator...
forgive me.
The Creator brings him home.
Ham?
Shem.
Shem, go inside.
Go inside.
They are upon us.
Go inside!
Good-bye, son of Adam.
Son, where are you?
Ham!
Ham?
It's all right.
Shem!
Father!
Japheth, where are you?
Ila, I'm here!
Father!
Mother, where's Father?
Please, Noah...
there must be something we
can do.
We can drag ropes.
They cannot all be soldiers,
Father.
They are just people.
And there's room.
There is no room for them.
Soon everything we knew will
be gone.
All that is left of Creation
will lie within these walls.
Outside...
just the waters of chaos again.
You are angry.
You judge me.
Let me tell you a story.
The first story my father
told me...
and the first story that I told
each of you.
In the beginning...
there was nothing.
Nothing but the silence of an
infinite darkness.
But the breath of The Creator
fluttered against...
the face of the void, whispering,
"Let there be light."
And light was.
And it was good.
The first day.
And then the formless light...
began to take on substance and
shape.
A second day.
And our world was born.
Our beautiful, fragile home.
And a great, warming light
nurtured its days.
And a lesser light ruled
the nights.
And there was evening.
And morning.
Another day.
And the waters of the world
gathered together...
and in their midst emerged
dry land.
Another day passed.
And the ground put forth the
growing things.
A thick blanket of green stretching
across all Creation.
And the waters, too, teemed
with life.
Great creatures of the deep
that are no more.
Vast multitudes of fish...
some of which may still swim
beneath these seas.
And soon the sky was streaming
with birds.
And there was evening.
And there was morning.
A fifth day.
Now the whole world was full
of living beings.
Everything that creeps, everything
that crawls...
and every beast that walks upon
the ground.
And it was good.
It was all good.
There was light and air and
water and soil...
all clean and unspoiled.
There were plants and fish and
fowl and beast...
each after their own kind.
All part of the greater whole.
All in their place.
And all was in balance.
It was paradise.
A jewel in The Creator's palm.
Then The Creator made Man.
And by his side, Woman.
Father and mother of us all.
He gave them a choice.
Follow the temptation of
darkness...
or hold on to the blessing
of light.
But they ate from the forbidden
fruit.
Their innocence was extinguished.
And so, for the ten generations
since Adam...
sin... has walked within us.
Brother against brother.
Nation against nation.
Man against Creation.
We murdered each other.
We broke the world.
We did this.
Man did this.
Everything that was beautiful...
everything that was good...
we shattered.
Now, it begins again.
Air, water, earth, plant, fish,
bird and beast.
Paradise returns.
But this time...
this time there will be no men.
If we were to enter the Garden
again...
it would only be to destroy it
once more.
No.
The Creator has judged us.
Mankind must end.
Shem and Ila...
you will bury your mother and I.
Ham, you will bury them.
Japheth will lay you to rest.
You, Japheth...
you will be the last man.
And in time you, too, will
return to the dust.
Creation will be left alone,
safe and beautiful.
I'm very sorry about that girl.
And I'm sorry for you.
But we have been entrusted with
a task...
much greater than our own desires.
Ham.
Noah...
Does he know I'm here?
No, no, no. No.
Why are you helping me?
There was a girl.
I tried to bring her.
But he just let her die.
And now you want revenge.
No.
Yes, you do.
There's no more land.
Everything out there must be
dead.
It had to be what He wanted.
A world without man.
You see that, don't you?
What I see...
is how hard this was for you
to do...
as a man who respects life...
a man who loves his children.
You've been strong.
But it's done.
It's done now.
And you can put that burden
down.
Noah.
It's all right.
If your father found me, he
would kill me.
We must be ready, but I am
too weak.
What are you doing?
I must get my strength back.
The beasts are precious.
There are only two of each.
And there is only one of me.
But the rain, all these miracles,
are for them.
Them?
Your father fills a ship with
beasts while children drown.
He belittles you by telling
you you must serve them.
No.
They serve us.
That is the greatness of men.
When The Creator finished
making the sky...
the ground, the sea, and this
beast...
He wasn't satisfied.
He needed something greater.
Something to take dominion over
it and subdue it.
So He made us in His image.
Us.
This is your world, Ham.
Seize it.
Ila.
Grandfather.
What is it?
You're not sick.
But that's impossible.
What?
What is it?
Noah.
It is his grandchild.
What's wrong?
Father.
Noah.
We've come to ask for your
blessing.
I don't understand.
I am with Child.
It's not possible.
You're barren.
You can't conceive.
How...
How is that possible?
Grandfather.
I asked Grandfather...
To what?
Undermine The Creator?
To give our children a future.
To give humanity a future.
Have you any idea what you've
done?
All those lives!
All those people!
For nothing!
Do you know what this forces
me to do?
No!
Please!
I cannot do this! Tell me I
don't need to do this!
Please.
Have I not done everything that
You asked of me?
Is that not enough?
Why do You not answer me?
Why?
I will not fail You.
It shall be done.
Father?
The rains have stopped.
The Creator smiles on our child.
The rains have stopped because
of your child, yes...
but He does not smile.
If your child is a boy...
he will replace Japheth,
last man.
If it is a girl...
who could mature into a mother...
she must die.
Are you mad?
That is my Child!
If you should bear a girl...
in the moment of her birth,
I will cut her down.
Mother!
Mother, my bird!
Nothing.
No mud.
We still have to go.
Ila...
there's nothing.
There's nothing out there.
You have food and water for
how long? Weeks?
A month?
A month.
Please wait.
Wait until the bird finds land.
Please.
Japheth, send him again.
He's too tired.
Then wake another.
Here.
Please.
One that can find us a home.
No.
We leave today.
They will die out there.
Not if they stay.
And let you kill their Child?
Noah.
Noah!
I did this.
I did this, Noah!
Please!
Punish me!
Punish me, Noah!
Not them.
Not the child.
Please.
The child is not being punished.
We are all being punished.
All of us.
It's not something I want
to do.
It's something I have to do.
It is painful...
but it is just.
Just?
How?
How is this just?
It's a baby, Noah.
If you hold to this...
you will lose your sons, you
will lose Ila...
you will lose me.
I love you, Noah.
And I have followed you
everywhere.
Through everything.
I forgave you.
When everyone was dead,
I was ready to die with you.
But this...
I will never forgive.
Boy or girl, I will never
forgive!
And you will die alone!
Not just alone, but hated!
Hated by everyone you love!
That is just!
That is just.
It's time.
Bring him through there.
One blow will finish it.
Just in case, huh?
I don't know if I can.
He killed your woman.
And now he plots to kill your
brother's first-born.
Is that what you want?
You want your sister to die
on the seas?
A man isn't ruled by the heavens.
A man is ruled by his will.
So I ask you...
are you a man?
Good.
Because if you're a man...
you can kill.
But he won't follow me.
Thank you, Japheth.
You take care of that baby.
Don't be afraid, Mother.
We'll see each other in the
new world.
Father.
No!
How could you?
I thought you were good!
I thought that's why He
chose you.
He chose me because He knew
I would complete the task...
nothing more, son.
Mother.
It's your time.
Come.
Come with me.
You're all right.
Japheth, stand back.
Come now.
Come inside.
That's right.
You're all right, Ila.
You're safe here.
Please keep it inside.
Your baby's coming.
Your baby's coming, Ila.
Don't think about anything
else.
Father!
Father, they're awake!
They're awake!
They're eating each other!
The beasts.
What?
Come.
Come!
It's not possible for them to
have woken up without our help.
Which way, son?
That's right.
The line of Cain.
I told you...
I'm not afraid of miracles.
That's right.
A bit more.
Boy or girl?
What's happening?
There's another.
Two?
Twins.
Mother, so?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Sisters.
No.
No!
He will not touch our daughters.
Shem!
I should have killed you when
I killed your father.
Well, now we finish it.
Now!
The evils of mankind will not
live in this new Eden.
Leave us!
Leave us alone!
He's mine!
The ark, the beasts, and all
of your women are now mine.
I will build a new world in
my image!
Now you are a man.
The Creator has not forgotten us.
Her name was Na'el.
She was innocent.
She was good.
It's a boy.
Move away.
Where is she?
No... no... no.
You can't.
They're beautiful.
They?
You can't kill two.
He sent us what we need.
No... no.
No!
You can't!
Noah!
Ila!
Noah.
Please.
These are my children!
Your grandchildren!
I will not be stopped.
I know I cannot stop you, but
they're crying!
Please don't let them die
crying.
Let me calm them.
Please, just let them be at
peace.
The moon is high.
The leaves entwine.
Your Father waits for thee...
to wrap you in His sheltering
wings...
to whisper you to sleep.
To wrap you in...
His welcoming arms...
till the night sky breaks.
Your Father is the healing
wind...
that whispers you to sleep.
That whispers as...
you sleep.
You do not need to see this.
I will hold them.
Do it quickly.
Do it quickly!
I cannot do this.
It's all right.
Hide your eyes, Japheth.
Ham?
He's here.
You don't have to go.
I don't belong here.
For what it's worth...
I'm glad that it begins again
with you.
Maybe we'll learn to be kind.
Will he come back?
Some things cannot be unbroken.
I have to know...
Why did you spare them?
I looked down at those two
little girls...
and all I had in my heart
was love.
Then why are you alone, Noah?
Why are you separated from
your family?
Because I failed Him.
And I failed all of you.
Did you?
He chose you for a reason, Noah.
He showed you the wickedness
of man...
and knew you would not look
away.
But then you saw goodness, too.
The choice was put in your hands
because He put it there.
He asked you to decide if we
were worth saving.
And you chose mercy.
You chose love.
He has given us a second chance.
Be a father.
Be a grandfather.
Help us to do better this time.
Help us start again.
The Creator made Adam in His
image...
and placed the world in his
care.
That birthright...
was passed down to us.
To my father, then to me, and
to my sons...
Shem...
Japheth...
and Ham.
That birthright is now passed
to you...
our grandchildren.
This will be your work...
and your responsibility.
So I say to you...
be fruitful and multiply...
and replenish the earth.