Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Julian.
You came all the way out here?
I had to leave somebody at the beach.
- It's been weeks.
- Hi.
Hello, girls.
You didn't fly to Rio
for the weekend?
Don't mind them.
They're just jealous.
I've been trying
to reach you all day.
Yeah, I got the message. Number?
Tonight. It's a woman
from Charlottesville.
She's flying in for negotiation
on her husband's estate.
- First time?
- Yeah.
She's meeting lawyers in the morning.
They want a chauffeur.
- Is she into drugs?
- No, no drugs.
1,000, right?
600 for me.
- Don't start this again.
- You want 50/50, get Mike,
or one of those drop-outs
you like so much.
There's no percentage in it
if I don't get 50/50.
You already cut me out of repeaters.
It's only fair. Only fair.
It ain't fair, Julie,
but I don't have any choice.
You got a lot of choice. You can
keep dealing retarded faggots...
Look who's talking!
All right... 50/50.
Who ' d you drop off up the beach?
- Wouldn't you like to know.
- Why do you do this to me?
You know anybody else
who gets in the LA Country Club?
And that's not the Hillcrest
or the Riverside or the Riviera.
I gotta run.
Leave the info on the service.
You don't want to take some sun?
I'm sure the girls
would like some company.
No, thanks. No way. See you later.
How's the Swedish coming?
OK.
Do you want me to help you?
Listen to the recording
and repeat what you hear.
Listen and then repeat.
I am not interested in that.
How much farther have we to go?
Is this your first visit?
Yeah?
OK, let him through.
Hey, Leon, what's up?
Julie, I hate to bug you,
but you gotta help me.
I had this Palm Springs gig
set up for Joey
and he ain't nowhere around.
I can't do it. I'm getting a haircut
I got something on this afternoon.
Baby, this is a two-hour gig.
Plus the drive.
5C, straight in-and-out job.
Nothing fancy. Do me a favour.
I don't know. Maybe.
If I get some time.
I'll give you 50 bucks.
Go fuck yourself.
You think I'm a charity?
Wait a minute.
Who's doing who a favour?
Who called who up, begging for a sub?
OK. I'm sorry. I appreciate it.
Anything for a friend.
Ex cuse me.
Mind if I take my cap off, ma'am?
No, of course not.
Thank you.
I think I know this hotel
better than my own apartment.
All the important people
come and stay here.
You know,
I used to be a pool boy here.
Anything I can do to help you?
I'll open the champagne for you.
- Open up the...?
- Julian. My name is Julian.
You don't have to open the champagne.
I will give you a tip, don't worry.
Jesus.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Tolbin.
That's not what I meant. I was...
I'm sorry.
Is this your first time in LA?
- Maybe you can be a help to me.
- Yeah?
Well, I haven't been here for years,
and I was wondering if there are
any new good restaurants.
You know, where the famous people go?
Yeah, well...
it's probably safer to recommend
the more established restaurants.
There's... Ma Maison and La Scala...
Scandia.
And of the newer ones,
I hear that Le Dome is quite nice.
Very popular.
My, you are making me
thirsty just standing there.
Now you can open the champagne.
Pour me a drink...
and set the bottle down.
Yeah, she liked the pool boy bit.
I'm going to see her
again tomorrow afternoon.
Yeah.
OK, Anne. Love you, too.
Paging Mrs. Anderson.
Hey, pretty lady.
- Hi.
- Got my other jacket?
- Sure. Here you go, Julian.
- Thanks.
- Good evening, Mr. Kay.
- How you doing?
Fine.
Then he has the nerve
to hit on my sister.
No, he's not.
I told you. He's looking right at us.
What'll it be?
No, that's OK, Jimmy.
Mr. Kay would like another drink.
- Dry Manhattan on the rocks.
- Yes, sir.
- You speak English.
- You fooled me.
- And you me.
How long have you
been in Los Angeles?
I live here.
You live here? I don't understand.
You wouldn't. I'm just trying
to refresh my college French.
I usually practise with a friend,
but she's not here yet.
Where are you from?
I was born in Torino,
but I studied at Nantes.
You hardly have any accent at all.
Yeah, I've been travelling too much.
I envy you. I love to travel.
I used to travel a lot, but my
husband's involved in local politics.
So now I just practise French.
He thinks it's chic
to have a bilingual wife.
I think he's right.
Where are you going?
I made a mistake.
My husband's in New York.
What about your friend?
I'm not waiting for anyone.
- You still don't understand.
- Understand what?
Who I am.
Who are you?
You don't even understand
who you are, why you're sitting here.
Why are you here?
- I've got to go.
- All right. Just one thing.
Why did you come on to me?
Like I said, I made a mistake.
I heard you speaking French.
Often in these big hotels, you run
into women from foreign countries
who may need
a translator... or a guide.
And they hire you?
Yes.
How many languages do you speak?
Five or six.
Plus the... international language.
That's right.
Well, now,
you're something really
special, aren't you?
You're one to talk.
I saw you sitting here. You wanted me
to come over. I came over.
I know what I see.
How much would you have charged me?
As what? Translator or guide?
No. Just one fuck.
Now you've made a mistake.
I don't do that.
You don't, huh?
I know what I see, too, Monsieur Kay.
It's been a pleasure talking to you,
Madame Joste.
Look, someone's made a mistake here.
I don't do fags.
- I didn't mean that.
- Or couples.
No, no, no. You don't understand.
It's just my wife Judy. Not me.
Just her.
- But I can watch.
- Of course.
Would you like a drink?
Not yet.
- I think I'd like my money now.
- Sure. Sure.
- I like to talk after.
- Sure.
Hello, Judy.
You're a very sexy lady,
a very good-looking woman.
A very pretty woman. You'll like me.
I can tell...
because I like you. I like you.
So just relax and close your eyes.
Just relax
and let your mind run free.
Don't worry about anything.
I can take care of you.
I know what you want.
That's right. Close your eyes.
Forget about him.
This is just you and me.
No, no, no, from behind.
It has to be from behind.
Ok, baby, just flip over
on your stomach.
Just relax. Don't worry.
Leave everything to me,
'cause I'm going to take care of you.
I'm going to get you wet, very wet.
I know how to do this.
Now slap her.
Slap that cunt.
- Hey, Leon.
- How you doing, Jule?
I want to thank you
for helping me out, Julie.
Finally found Joey holed up
with one of his... boyfriends,
just banging away,
you know how it is. Dumb bastard.
- Hello, Julian.
- Hi. I'll just have a Perrier.
You made quite a hit in Palm Springs.
They want you back.
I'm serious.
They want you back this week.
I wouldn't take much,
you know. It's...
They're regulars for me.
You lied, Leon.
It was a rough trick.
I forgot. You got scruples now, huh?
I don't like playing
the same numbers too often.
They get possessive.
- I can't be possessed.
- Does that include Miss Anne?
Anne who?
I don't know why you fool around
with that dumb bitch.
I'll tell you why, Leon. She's got
a job coming up for me in a week.
Eight grand.
Can you get me that?
All right. All right.
Thanks, hon.
Just trying to warn you, that's all.
That bitch will sell you out.
But you really care about me,
don't you? Don't you, Leon?
You care.
You know, you walk
an awful thin line, Julian.
I wouldn't want to be in your shoes.
You're getting cocky.
The other boys are happy,
with a car, a house, but not you.
You got all your rich pussy lined up,
once-a-month tricks,
a dip in the pool,
a little tennis, and orgasm.
I'm just to warning you as a friend.
If those bitches ever turn on you,
you're through.
You're sure about that?
They'll cut you out.
Yeah?
Says she's a friend?
Where does she know me from?
Yeah, send her up.
I'm Michelle.
- How did you find me?
- It wasn't hard.
Are you surprised?
What do you want?
I would have thought that you'd live
in a place with thick red carpet,
- big bed, mirrors on the ceiling...
- Bordello.
This is my apartment.
Women don't come here.
- You're going out?
- Yeah.
Business?
- Maybe.
- Isn't it a little late?
- Isn't it late for you?
- My husband's still in New York.
I'm alone.
I thought it would be easier.
What did you say?
I said I thought it would be easier.
What?
To be with you, to procure you.
I told you, you're mistaken.
Why are you doing this to me?
- What am I doing?
- Embarrassing me.
I'm not embarrassing you.
I can't keep up...
this front much longer.
I came here.
I found out who you were,
where you lived.
I came here
in the middle of the night.
I wanted to know what...
it would be like... to fuck you.
I brought money.
What more can I do? I...
I...
I like...
I don't want to know.
Don't say that.
You got me aroused
just thinking about it.
I'm lying here with a hard-on,
it's not even 10:00 yet.
Don't tease me.
Come on, baby, you're teasing me.
I'm gonna have to hang up
and jerk off right now. I am.
Yeah, I'm touching myself.
You like that, don't you?
Oh, come on, baby. Don't say that.
We're talking about having more
pleasure than you've had in years,
you got to bring up
some stupid little $1,200 stereo?
How much does your husband make?
What's he worth?
A couple of million?
Of course I could do without it.
I can listen to the radio.
The speaker's cracked.
Lisa. Lisa, listen to yourself.
You know what you're saying?
Can you hold on a second?
Somebody's at the door.
Good morning.
What do you want for breakfast?
Coffee, juice, croissant, eggs?
Julian Kay.
I want two coffee,
orange juice, croissant...
No eggs.
..one scrambled egg
and a side of cottage cheese.
Lisa, I'm here with a hard-on,
people all over, I can't talk.
I'll see you about 5:00. Bye-bye.
So, what do you think?
About what?
Did you make the right decision
to come here last night?
Was it what you expected?
No. It was like really making love.
I'm not used...
It's not what I expected.
Do you remember
what you said last night?
Yes.
Now, if I bid, I have to buy it.
Right.
The one I want is over here.
There it is.
What does it say?
"Jacobean, late 17th century".
Estimated at 4,800 to 5,200.
This has been worked on.
There's glue in it.
Yeah.
I don't know. My guess is this
is gonna go for 5,000. 55 maybe.
It's a great piece,
but it's not a great bargain.
At 48, that's a bargain.
What do you think?
It's perfect for the guest room,
but I... don't know.
I saw a George III chest around here
somewhere, going for, like, 22, 23.
It's a lot, but a good investment.
Beautiful lines on it.
Probably the best bargain is that
tacky garnisher set over there...
- What is it?
- Do you see who I see?
- Who is it?
- It's Randolph Sloan's widow.
- A stockholder in Jim's company.
- She's still alive?
She's gonna make a beeline for us.
There goes the garnisher set.
- What am I gonna do?
- I don't know.
Come, Lisa, we must face the enemy
before they face us.
Lucille!
How lovely to see you.
Are you buying or selling?
- Just looking.
- Oh, how nice!
There is an ex quisite
garnisher set over there!
Lucille,
this is Wilhelm Schoenfeld.
He's helping me redecorate
the guest house.
Great hospitality, madame.
Oh, the dress! Look, the dress.
Beautiful dress. It goes
with her face. They're both beige.
Wilhelm.
Madame!
- What is going on here?
- I don't know. So sorry.
Lisa, we must go.
Did you see her face?
Come on.
I wish your husband would come back.
- He has.
- Good.
I can't stop thinking about you.
Do you mind?
What have you been doing?
- When?
- This morning.
Driving around.
I drove to Anaheim,
then I drove to Long Beach.
I pumped my own gas in Long Beach.
Then I drove here.
You know, Michelle,
I'm really not part of your problems.
I'm certainly not the solution
to your problems.
I brought money.
Don't...
I don't want your money.
I'll buy you something, then.
- I'll buy you that stereo.
- I got a stereo.
What, then?
Come on.
- What?
- We're going to my room.
- You want it?
- No.
Good, ' cause you're
not gonna get it.
Tell me everything about you.
Right now.
God. Why?
I don't know. It seems important.
We just made love, didn't we?
Yes.
Then you know everything
there is to know.
That's silly. Where are you from?
I don't know. I'm not from anywhere.
I'm from this bed.
Anything worth knowing, you can learn
by letting me make love to you.
That's not true.
Why do you sleep with older women?
I prefer older women.
Why?
What's the use of bringing
some high-schooler to climax?
Some silly teenager gets wet in the
movies and goes home to masturbate.
No challenge.
It has no meaning.
The other night...
That night I met you
at the hotel...
I was with a woman...
Somebody's mother.
Her husband didn't care
about her any more.
She hadn't had an orgasm in 10 years.
Took me 3 hours to get her off.
For a while,
I didn't think I could do it.
When it was over, I felt
like I'd done something worthwhile.
Who else would've taken the time
or cared enough to do it right?
My God.
These are not the handcuffs your wife
was wearing when she was killed.
Those we found in the study.
They were in a filing cabinet...
along with some dildos, paddles...
You know what I'm talking about.
Your private sex life is
of no concern to me or to the LAPD.
However, the manner
in which your wife was assaulted
suggests the killer may have
been a guest in your home once.
I'll try to keep what you tell me
in the strictest confidence.
However, I'll have to have
detailed information
about you and your
wife's sex practices...
and the names of any parties
that were involved. All right?
Sorry. Here you go. This, too.
I get the Salvation Army.
Mrs. Stewart.
Hi. Ex cuse me.
Does Mr. Julian Kay live here?
I'm Detective Sunday.
I'm with the homicide bureau.
I'd like to ask him a few questions.
What do you want?
You're Mr. Kay?
Hello, I'm Detective Sunday.
How are you?
Come on.
I'm walking into Westwood.
You want to talk there?
- Sure.
- I'll pick that stuff up later.
I'm investigating the Rheiman murder
from the Los Angeles area.
You heard about the case?
- Yeah. It was in the paper, right?
- Yeah.
- Palm Springs.
- Right again.
- Yeah, I read about that.
- I bet.
- Cup of coffee?
- Sure!
We'll sit in the back.
Now, what were you doing
Tuesday night?
Tuesday.
Tuesday night, I was...
I was with a friend
at a pre-auction viewing.
She'll verify that?
We're talking about a woman
of substance here.
I think she enjoys her privacy.
..if that's what this is
to you. OK? I don't want it!
Come over here.
You can't mix May and December.
It just never...
Maybe she likes the guy, huh?
- I'm sorry.
- Am I a suspect?
No, but we'll have to check
your alibi for your sake.
Now, this work that you were
doing for the Rheimans,
was this as a translator
or a chauffeur?
Neither. This was...
This was more of a personal matter.
- You're friends?
- Not exactly.
Not exactly. All right, then.
What exactly is it
that you were doing for the Rheimans?
Nothing special.
Chit-chat. I don't know.
I have a hard time remembering
these things. I meet a lot of people.
Yes, yes.
No, I understand your problem.
You got there, you had a few drinks.
Next thing, you're back in LA?
More or less.
You want another cup of coffee?
That's bullshit. I'm taking you in.
It'll be good for your memory.
You seem like a young man
who needs a little self-improvement.
Look, Mr. Sunday...
Detective Sunday.
Look, Detective...
I want to cooperate with the police
in any way I can, but these...
these are very delicate matters...
things that may not fall
under the exact letter of the law.
Publicity's the last thing I want.
I'm not gonna book you or
take away your chauffeur's license.
I'm not gonna bring you up on drug
charges. I could do all of that.
Just tell me about the Rheimans.
Please welcome Charles Stratton.
Mack, thank you.
I hope you're having
as good a time as us...
trying to figure out
what the stuff is on our plates.
But most of all,
I'm happy to have the opportunity
to speak to you in an informal way
about the problems
facing southern California.
More than any other
community in the country...
Do you follow
California politics, Julian?
Not very much.
You're smart. They're all whores.
..but we also have the technological
means and know-how
to help free America
from the grip of fossil fuels.
In times of austerity like these,
it is the privileged
who should lead the way,
who should set an example
for the rest of the country.
This guy is a real comer.
She's pretty, isn't she?
Yes, very.
Jim, Thank you for coming.
You know Michelle.
Mrs. Laudner, how nice of you to come.
It's a pleasure to see you.
Bullshit. Can we talk later?
Certainly. Mrs. Laudner,
my wife Michelle.
How do you do?
- And this is Julian Kay.
- It's an honour. Enjoyed the speech.
Mrs. Stratton.
You're a fortunate man, Senator.
- You know what he is.
- That boy will go far.
Got a nice wife, too.
- Tell me about them.
- I told you he's a comer.
No. I want to hear
about them as a couple.
- How is their marriage?
- Julian, you are incorrigible!
No, I want to hear about it.
I hear she's very unhappy.
- Julian!
- Well, hello.
What a surprise.
- You do a lot of shopping here?
- No. Just browsing.
Just browsing.
Well, I gotta go.
Lot of appointments.
Been very nice talking to you...
Mrs. Stratton.
Wait.
I have to talk to you.
Yeah. Me, too.
Want to have a drink?
It's kind of early for a drink.
Maybe we do that in about an hour.
What do you think?
I think you're awful.
I think you're right.
Come on.
I've seen your husband
on television.
He's very impressive.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing. I'm sorry.
I would never do anything
to hurt him politically.
I could never leave him.
Don't let him blackmail you.
He has this big
political thing about...
having... a family.
He keeps wanting me to be pregnant.
What are we talking about here?
What he wants or what you want?
I can't tell any more.
What can I do?
I don't know.
Be yourself.
Leave him?
His career will survive.
People forget.
These things have to
be done quietly.
Don't let him fool you with his talk
about duty and self-sacrifice.
He's getting exactly what he wants.
You've got to do the same.
Take your pleasure when you can.
How about you? Where do you come in?
How do you get pleasure?
What a surprise. Mr. Kay.
Detective Sunday.
You are full of surprises.
Come on in. Sit down.
- Take a shine. You need it.
- Thank you. You're dressed up today.
I'm going to the country club.
To the country club.
We checked on your alibi.
Mrs. Williams said you had
been with her Tuesday night.
But...
you dropped her off at 7:00.
The Rheiman murder was at 10:00.
Shit.
I described the house, the bedroom.
She said
you were helping her redecorate
and you'd been picking
out a bureau...
I understand why.
She has a reputation to protect.
How do you do it, Julian?
This afternoon with Mrs. Jarvey
and tonight at the country club.
How do you seduce
all these women, huh?
I don't like you poking around
in my private life, Sunday...
bugging my friends.
I'll tell you what.
You lay off my clients,
I'll give you a few pointers
picking up women.
How's that?
First, obviously, you dress for shit.
Anybody can fix that, no problem.
It's your face. Bad face.
And that body? You have back
problems? You look like a monkey.
Hey, back. Shoulders back.
And your jaw, work the jaw.
Ex ercise. You don't want it slack.
Up tight, tight. Tight, yes.
Would you be willing
to come in for a line-up?
- Sure. Why not?
- Doesn't it ever bother you, Julian?
- What?
- What you do.
Giving pleasure to women?
I'm supposed to feel guilty?
- But it's not legal.
- Legal is not always right.
Men make laws.
Sometimes they're wrong.
They're stupid... or jealous.
And you know better?
Some people are above the law.
How do these people
know who they are?
They know.
They ask themselves.
Eugene, thanks.
I'll take care of you in a minute.
Yes, sir.
- May I?
- Please.
Yeah, the other one
could use some work.
Why didn't you tell me
you handcuffed Mrs. Rheiman?
- I didn't.
- Yeah, you said that.
That's why I checked twice
with the coroner.
Apparently, she must have
put up quite a struggle.
There were cuts on her wrists
from being handcuffed.
Underneath the cuts were bruises from
where she was handcuffed earlier.
The coroner estimates
about 48 hours earlier,
which would be the night
you were there.
Jesus Christ.
She was beaten with
a heavy metal object,
raped and violated... with an object,
presumably the murder weapon.
Yeah.
Yeah, I handcuffed her.
But you gotta understand about
these people... like the Rheimans.
It's like a game to them.
I'll explain.
Julian.
Yeah? What is it?
They were here two hours...
the police.
They were here two hours.
They had a search warrant.
It's all right. It's OK.
What's going on?
Jill, it's Julian.
No, it's OK, it's OK.
Send the maid up now.
Hi. How you doing, Timmy?
Julian! You're becoming
a regular visitor. What's happening?
There's something
I want to talk about.
I don't like anybody
here when Tim visits.
Courts might not
let me see him at all.
Let's go down to the beach, then.
Watch out.
Thank you.
I think I'm in a frame.
- Who's putting you in?
- I don't know.
All I see is a frame.
It's that Rheiman murder
out in Palm Springs.
You tricked with them?
Once. Just once. Favour to Leon.
- Two-timing bastard.
- I'm nice. I can't help it.
You check around for me?
Why don't you ask
your new friend Leon?
I may just do that.
You trick for other people,
cheat me out of money,
and then when you need a favour,
you come back to me.
If I help you...
you'll have to help me.
How?
You'll have to come back to me,
work strictly for me.
Wait a minute.
It's got nothing to do with that.
Like shit it doesn't.
I made you, Julie.
I taught you everything you know,
how to dress, how to behave,
how to treat women, how to make love.
Then you say, "I'm too good for you,"
and cut me out.
It ain't right, Julie.
Things are different.
I'm more than I used to be.
I'm getting older, Anne.
I got to keep moving forward.
Please, Julie, save me the speeches.
- How's your Swedish coming?
- I'll be ready.
She's flying in
from Stockholm on Thursday.
She apparently has certain
sexual idiosyncrasies.
Are you going to come back with me?
- You did it, didn't you?
- What?
The Rheiman killing.
Don't worry, Julie.
It doesn't matter.
Thank you.
It's been a wonderful evening.
- Can I see you again tomorrow?
- How about this one?
There was a sexy
girl from Borgan Place...
Do you live alone?
It's such a sweet face.
- No, not yet.
- Why not?
- Let's just kiss some more, OK?
- What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong. I just don't...
want to make love.
I love to be with you.
I love it when you kiss me
and when you touch me,
but when you make love,
you go to work.
If it's your period, I don't mind.
Don't give me that.
You know what I'm talking about.
I can't give you any pleasure,
and you can't fool me any more.
You don't know what you're saying.
Yes, I do... and so do you.
Yeah, I know.
You're talking about me giving up
what I am, what I do.
Is that so shocking?
I care about you. I really do.
That's still not enough.
It's all I'm good at.
That's not true.
It doesn't matter.
I can't quit anyway.
If I quit, I'm out on a limb.
Well, then we'd be even.
I'm already out on one.
People I know
take care of each other.
I need their protection.
I'm being framed by somebody.
I don't know who.
There was a murder, Palm Springs,
a couple weeks ago.
Police think I did it.
It was a woman. A woman I met once.
I wasn't there,
but my alibi completely denies it.
- Why would anyone do that to you?
- I can't figure that out.
- It doesn't make any sense.
- When was the murder?
A week ago Tuesday.
- Weren't we together that night?
- Baby, I wish we were.
All right,
boys, stand full-face, please.
This is bullshit. These cops...
Number three, take off your glasses.
Number two, straighten up.
Turn to your right.
No, Number three, to your right.
Jerk.
How much you getting paid?
What are you talking about?
I'm just a con.
So am I. I'm getting 15.
- You are?
- Yeah. 15 bucks.
Now left, please.
Left.
Thank you.
- The wino's getting 20.
- You're kidding.
You ain't getting paid,
you're getting screwed.
Shit! What the fuck's going on?
I want to speak to my lawyer!
You'll see your lawyer.
Get in line.
Make sure I speak to him.
Number one, turn to your right.
I know my rights. This isn't Russia.
We have a constitution here.
- I know my rights.
- Thank you. You can leave now.
How about this fuckin' jerk
here, three.
You getting paid, too?
What the fuck is going on?
Well, what do you think?
- Not bad.
- I'm gonna steal your thunder.
He's teaching me how to dress.
This is Lieutenant Curtis
from Palm Springs.
He's...
- He's in charge of this case.
- Wait a minute. I thought you were?
No, I'm in charge
of pimps, prostitutes and hustlers.
Pretty low on the pole.
Good joke, huh?
You've been identified, Julian.
- Julian.
- By whom?
Who could possibly identify me?
You parked 50 feet
from the Rheiman house
around 10:00 on the 22nd,
proceeded up the street
and entered the house.
- Someone saw you.
- I request formal charges...
I don't understand.
Who would say this? I was not there.
Then she identified
subject number one.
Then she wasn't sure
which one of you it was.
- You got the license number?
- She didn't see it.
- Shit!
- Right.
Here.
We looked around your house.
We had a warrant.
- We know.
- You recognise these?
- They were under your mattress.
- So what?
They had Mrs. Rheiman's fingerprints
all over them. That's so what.
- Did you find the jewels?
- What jewels?
I read the paper, too.
Jewels stolen from Rheiman's house.
Whoever planted that money
probably planted the jewels.
There were no jewels.
Didn't you ever wonder
this may be a frame?
- It occurred to us.
- It occurred to you.
- Did you check Rheiman?
- He has an alibi.
- Big deal.
- You're grasping at straws.
What about Leon James, the black guy?
- He said you were high-class.
- What do you think?
I think you're guilty as sin.
I think you went to the Rheimans',
did a trick,
played some rough games.
You got drugged or stupid or both.
You beat her, killed her,
stole the money and the jewels.
Then there's no use talking further
until you press charges.
Whether we think Julian's guilty...
we're not going to arrest him.
If you're being framed,
you're gonna be more use to us
floating around.
Can we go now?
Just one more thing, Julian...
don't tell cons
they get paid for line-ups.
Some cops don't have
a sense of humour.
Hi. I'm here
to see Mrs. Williams.
- I'm Julian Kay.
- I'll take care of this, Wilma.
- Julian, why are you here?
- Can I talk to you?
What about?
Were the police here?
There was a detective here.
I was very surprised
you used my name.
I'm very, very sorry
about that, Lisa,
but this is very important to me.
I told him the truth.
Lisa, you didn't,
I was with you until after midnight.
That's not the truth.
Julian, I can't...
you weren't here.
What is it, dear?
This is Julian Kay,
the one who is helping
with the decorating.
The boy who said he was with me
the night of that murder.
Mr. Kay, it's bad enough
you made a fool of my wife
But then spreading lies...
- Leave us alone.
- I wasn't lying.
Whatever you did, you won't
to get out of it by dragging...
I just came here for the truth.
- I know you're lying.
- How do you know I'm lying?
Because I was here with my wife
the entire evening.
Thank you, Mr. Kay.
You're not very good at this.
- What?
- Following people. You're lousy.
- What are you talking about?
- Who's paying you?
- You're not a cop.
- I'm calling the police.
You want to call? Go ahead, call.
What have we got here?
Floyd... Floyd Wicker. Nice name.
Born 7-23-52.
Hawthorne Avenue, LA.
Driver's license, American Express,
Mastercharge,
picture of girlfriend...
So-so,
eyes too close together, Floyd.
What else have we got?
California State
Congressional Library pass,
California State identification,
California...
State Senate pass...
Senator Charles Stratton.
- Who the fuck are you?
- You can read.
Here.
You work for Senator Stratton?
Yes.
- Why are you following me?
- I was told to.
- By the senator?
- Who else?
Why didn't he ask me
about my private life himself?
Huh? You don't know. You don't know.
Well, Floyd, I'm gonna
make this easy for you
so you don't forget.
This is my telephone number.
Now, you tell... the senator
if he wants to talk to me...
he can just give me a call,
all right?
Now, you fuck off
and leave me alone!
I received your message, Mr. Kay.
- Thought I'd see you.
- Good evening, Senator.
- A vodka tonic.
- Yes, sir.
This is heartwarming.
Nice to see you haven't lost touch
with your constituency.
I'm not talking as a senator,
but as a husband.
That's too bad. I'm not a wife.
Very funny.
What do you want?
- Want?
- I know who you are.
I can't stop my wife being a fool,
but I can stop her
from being blackmailed.
- I don't know what you mean.
- You don't?
The police think you're involved
in a murder in Palm Springs.
Three days later,
you seduced my wife at a fund-raiser
to blackmail me into helping you.
- You're crazy, mister.
- Am I?
Last night, my wife asked me
about the Rheiman murder.
Didn't make any sense
till I heard about you.
You talked to Michelle about this?
You're not gonna blackmail me.
You don't know anything about this.
But I do know a whore when I see one.
How much?
Not to see your wife again?
5,000.
You'll have the cash in the morning.
I'm seeing Michelle
because I want to see her...
and because she wants to see me.
I don't want a dime from you.
That may be even simpler.
You live off the good graces
of a few people,
like Mrs. Andros,
who was at the door a minute ago...
and of places such as this.
You're just a hanger-on.
Unless you want to find
a new crowd to hang onto,
don't see my wife again.
- How you doing?
- Not bad. How about you?
I'm looking for Leon James.
Seen him around?
Yeah. He's probably at Probe.
OK. Thanks. Take care.
Hey, Julie.
Hey, Jason.
I haven't seen you lately.
What brings you here?
Have you seen Leon around?
Oh, yeah.
He was showing off his new boy.
I think he's over there someplace.
OK, thanks.
Hey, Julie!
I thought that was you.
I've been looking for you.
I want to talk.
- Let's go out back.
- OK.
What you doing here?
You... coming from a funeral?
I hear you're
showing off a new boy.
I'm gonna make sure none
of these fruits snatch him from me.
You heard anything
about the Rheiman killing?
That's all I've heard about.
Cops on my ass like white on rice.
- They're giving me the third degree.
- Everybody else, too.
I may need your help.
I don't have an alibi.
You're the one that sent me.
You need one?
Yeah.
I'll see what I can do.
Who do you think killed her?
If I was the police,
I'd be more interested in Rheiman.
He's a freak, you know.
He's a freak...
but he's got an alibi.
An alibi?
Julie, I got something working
tonight, a little thing.
I'll cut you in on it
if you're interested.
Straight?
This time of night? Are you serious?
Leon, I'm sick of doing your shit.
No more fag stuff.
No more kink. Nothing.
- Finito! Got it?
- I heard about your problems.
What problems?
Your clientele, Julie,
your rich pussy.
They won't touch you.
They say it's too hot.
- They're looking for new boys.
- Fuck ' em. Fuck ' em!
Hey, Julie, listen...
you ask me to help you
out of a tight spot,
I'm glad to do it.
But I ask you to do my trick,
you say no.
Now, how you expect me
to help you, huh?
You give me the alibi,
then we'll talk about tricks.
- I have to talk to you.
- Hey, baby.
God, I'm glad to see you.
Are you OK? You look so worn out.
I didn't sleep much.
- Want to go for a walk?
- Yeah.
I'll get my shoes.
What's wrong?
Are you gonna tell me about it?
Hey.
Hey... you.
Come on, tell me.
When I said I didn't want
to make love to you,
I didn't mean it. I want to fuck you.
I always want to fuck you.
- Is that what you came to tell me?
- No.
Charles asked me to leave
for two months,
till the primaries are over.
I'm going to Rome.
Two months...
I'll be back. Wait for me.
I don't know if I can.
The police searched my apartment.
- Maybe Charles...
- That's not what I'm saying.
I don't know what I'm saying.
All my life... I've been
looking for something.
I don't even know what it is.
- Let me...
- Maybe you're what I'm looking for.
I gave Charles my word.
I've got to go.
It'll be all right.
Yeah.
I have to leave.
Shit!
I don't know.
I haven't seen him since yesterday.
- Tell me.
- I don't know. Honest.
The police have been
here all morning.
- Another cop's in his room.
- Does he call in?
I'm not supposed to tell.
OK. Next time he calls in
I've gotta talk to him.
Ask if I can meet him.
Do you know a blonde kid
that hangs around with Leon James?
Nah. Couldn't tell you.
Anne, I'm sorry.
I've got to talk to you.
I can't now.
I'm looking for somebody.
Perino's? Look, I don't have time.
Yeah, all right, Perino's. Yes, 8:30.
Jill, this is Julian.
Yeah, I know.
You got some messages for me?
Michelle?
Tell her to meet me at Perino's.
Son of a bitch, it's Rheiman.
Mr. Julian.
You can't come in like this.
I was working. I forgot.
- I'll get you a jacket.
- No, it's OK.
Julie, you look like shit.
What's wrong?
- Everything. Straight bourbon.
- What are you doing?
The way you look
you couldn't get a maid to fuck you.
Anne, the cops are after me. They're
framing me for the Rheiman murder.
- Where have you been?
- Looking for somebody.
Last night?
Mrs. Farfter came in last night
on a flight from Stockholm.
There was no one there to meet her.
She was furious.
I've got hell to pay. What happened?
Did you hear me?
I said the cops are after me...
for murder.
So you stand me up.
Jesus Christ!
What do you want?
Are you gonna help me?
I've checked around, Julie.
You are in trouble.
That's why I need your help.
You never did anything for me.
Never did anything for...
- I'm your number-one boy.
- And you fight me every turn.
You ask favours, then blow a gig
I worked six months to arrange.
- I explained that already.
- I'm through, Julie.
You'll have to fend for yourself.
I don't care
what happens to you any more.
Ex cuse me. I'll be back.
Julian, thank God you got my message.
I've been looking for you.
It's all right, baby. It's OK.
No, it's not all right.
Charles talked to the DA.
They found the weapon.
They're going to arrest you.
That can't be. It can't be.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
What can I do to help?
- Nothing.
- There's gotta be something.
Don't you understand?
I'm in big trouble.
- Just stay away.
- No.
There's gonna be a scandal.
You know what a scandal is?
You know what that's like?
Stay away from me.
I'll ruin your life, your husband's.
It's all over.
Not if you're innocent.
How do you know I'm innocent?
Look at me, right in the face
Can you tell me without hesitation
you know I'm innocent?
Yes.
Listen, forget me.
Is someone in there?
I never loved you.
- Julie?
- Let me in. It's important.
You look terrible.
You want to clean up, shave?
I'm sorry to bug you this late.
I've been looking for you.
I'm listening.
You got my alibi ready?
I'm gonna need it today.
It's not ready yet, Julie. Tomorrow.
I'm still piecing it together.
It's not easy.
I'm trying to get it right.
- Why are you framing me?
- What?
Judy Rheiman's murder...
you were behind it. You, Rheiman,
your cute little blonde
boyfriend in the bedroom there,
who planted the jewels in my car.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
What the fuck is that, then?
He's the one that
actually killed her, isn't he?
Leon, what happened?
You sent him out there
with Rheiman and his wife,
he got rough and he killed her.
Shut your fucking face!
I never saw that shit
before in my life.
I want to know one thing.
What will it cost
to get you off my back?
You ain't talking money,
you're talking murder.
- How much?
- I feel sorry for you.
How much?
It don't make no difference
how much, Julie.
The other side will always pay more.
Got it on real tight, huh?
You're real proud
of yourself, aren't you?
The police found the murder weapon
a block from your apartment.
That bitch in Palm Springs
is gonna change her mind
any time now and identify you.
Police want you real bad, Julie.
Now they got you.
Look, I'm worth maybe...
20, 30 grand. It's yours.
I'll break your new boys for you.
I'll work just for you.
Just for you, Leon,
40/60 split.
It's fair, 40/60.
40...
30/70. I'll...
I'll do fag tricks. I'll do kink.
I'll do anything you want me to!
Leave me alone and get out, Julie.
Why me?
Why did you pick me?
Because you were framable, Julie.
You stepped on too many toes.
Nobody cared about you.
I never liked you much myself.
Now get out.
Who's down there?
Your new boyfriend? You motherfucker!
Oh, my God!
Don't let me fall!
Please, Julie, help me!
Don't fall. I need you.
Give me your hand.
- Reach up.
- I'm trying.
Help me. Help me, please!
God! Don't fall!
Julian!
Would you answer a few questions?
- Who was involved?
- How old are you?
How long had you
been seeing Mrs. Rheiman?
- Any Hollywood notables?
- How much money have you made?
Julian, give me an ex clusive.
How much do you get for a trick?
Give me a break, Julian.
Do you feel
you're being framed, Julian?
Were you ever afraid of the husbands?
I wish I had arrested you earlier.
It would've been easier
for everybody.
You'd better end
this pretrial publicity.
We're moving him
to Palm Springs soon.
You have anything to say, Julian?
Julian?
No.
Hello, Julian.
Going away on your trip?
No. I decided not to.
- Does your husband know you're here?
- No.
Why did you come?
I didn't think
I'd ever see you again.
Don't come back, Michelle.
Are you satisfied with your lawyer?
It doesn't matter.
Don't go.
Michelle Stratton is paying
for my services, Julian.
I think you know this is
a matter of some secrecy.
Tell her not to bother.
Julian, you'll have to help us more.
You tell Michelle to forget me.
I'm more worried
about your defence, Julian,
than about her private life.
We'll must go into the details
the night of the murder.
The maid saw you trying to save Leon,
so the police are only pressing
the Rheiman case.
The papers and TV
are trying you already.
The police aren't
investigating any more.
We need some help, some facts,
to get the investigation going again.
Then we can find out
about Leon, Rheiman...
maybe the blonde boy.
How about it, Julian?
Lieutenant Curtis?
Yes, Mrs. Stratton. This is an honour.
May I sit?
I was told you wanted to see me.
I want to talk to you about
the Julian Kay/Rheiman murder case.
Yes.
I'm paying
for Mr. Kay's defence.
I know.
I'm paying for Mr. Kay's defence
because I know he's not guilty.
I don't want
an obstruction of justice.
How do you know he's not guilty?
Because he wasn't
in Palm Springs that night.
- No?
- No. He was with me.
I told them, Julian.
I heard.
You didn't have to do that, Michelle.
You could have forgotten me.
I'd rather die.
What will you do now?
I don't know. I can't go home.
The newsmen
are waiting outside for me.
There's dozens of them.
Why did you do it?
I had no choice.
I love you.
My God, Michelle...
it's taken me so long
to come to you.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player