1
00:00:29,532 --> 00:00:31,212
Clara was my babysitter.

2
00:00:31,332 --> 00:00:35,652
I was only 12 years old, naive and somewhat trusting.

3
00:00:35,731 --> 00:00:37,812
But all that was about to change.

4
00:00:37,812 --> 00:00:40,133
Some babysitters take you to the movies,

5
00:00:40,133 --> 00:00:42,732
or roller-blading in the park.

6
00:00:42,812 --> 00:00:45,332
Mine brought me on a date with a serial killer.

7
00:00:45,332 --> 00:00:46,812
Patrick Bateman.

8
00:00:46,932 --> 00:00:49,531
Not my idea of a romantic evening.

9
00:00:50,531 --> 00:00:52,131
God, look at her.

10
00:00:52,211 --> 00:00:55,210
All drugged up and tied to a chair.

11
00:00:55,330 --> 00:00:58,530
I knew we should have gone to the movies.

12
00:01:01,211 --> 00:01:03,331
At first, I was scared.

13
00:01:03,331 --> 00:01:06,730
I wanted to get out of there as fast as I could.

14
00:01:06,811 --> 00:01:09,531
But then...

15
00:01:09,531 --> 00:01:11,530
something came over me.

16
00:01:14,130 --> 00:01:17,329
As soon as I was free, I got really pissed.

17
00:01:18,129 --> 00:01:22,409
He was about to make a real mess of my babysitter.

18
00:01:22,530 --> 00:01:25,650
So, I did what many of you would have done,

19
00:01:25,730 --> 00:01:28,530
I took matters into my own hands.

20
00:01:28,530 --> 00:01:31,129
And it changed my life forever.

21
00:01:33,130 --> 00:01:35,049
Is everything all right in there?

22
00:01:35,128 --> 00:01:39,929
-I thought I heard a crash.
-Yes, everything's fine. Thanks.

23
00:01:39,929 --> 00:01:43,128
They found Bateman and his final victim a few days later.

24
00:01:43,128 --> 00:01:45,728
The FBI quickly uncovered a psychopath,

25
00:01:45,808 --> 00:01:47,729
and a few extra unsolved murders,

26
00:01:47,809 --> 00:01:51,329
and he became an instant celebrity, an overnight sensation.

27
00:01:51,329 --> 00:01:53,128
They even wrote a book about him.

28
00:01:53,208 --> 00:01:56,328
Only in America. As for me?

29
00:01:56,408 --> 00:01:58,648
I was never tied to the scene.

30
00:01:58,727 --> 00:02:00,207
And rather than self-destruct,

31
00:02:00,327 --> 00:02:02,927
or spend the rest of my life on some shrink's couch,

32
00:02:03,047 --> 00:02:05,127
I told no one of what had happened.

33
00:02:05,207 --> 00:02:07,047
I silently vowed to devote my life

34
00:02:07,127 --> 00:02:08,927
to stopping other psycho killers.

35
00:02:09,047 --> 00:02:10,927
I couldn't wait to grow up.

36
00:02:32,326 --> 00:02:35,127
The next six years of my life were a blur.

37
00:02:35,206 --> 00:02:37,207
My parents wrote me off emotionally.

38
00:02:37,325 --> 00:02:39,127
My mom became a raging alcoholic,

39
00:02:39,206 --> 00:02:41,646
and my dad was busy fucking the secretary.

40
00:02:41,726 --> 00:02:44,126
Pretty cliché, huh?

41
00:02:54,924 --> 00:02:56,724
So, here I am today,

42
00:02:56,805 --> 00:03:00,725
attending the most renowned behavioral studies program in the nation.

43
00:03:00,806 --> 00:03:03,124
Here they focus on profiling,

44
00:03:03,124 --> 00:03:06,524
the art, craft and science of tracking serial killers.

45
00:03:06,645 --> 00:03:09,724
The subject matter itself attracts some weirdos.

46
00:03:09,804 --> 00:03:11,524
Hey, Rachael.

47
00:03:11,524 --> 00:03:13,923
But then again, maybe it's just me...

48
00:03:14,044 --> 00:03:16,404
The problem is, I don't have time for games.

49
00:03:16,522 --> 00:03:18,723
I've got to focus on my work.

50
00:03:18,804 --> 00:03:22,523
-You can do better than that.
-That's what your mama said.

51
00:03:23,723 --> 00:03:25,324
And what can I say?

52
00:03:25,324 --> 00:03:28,323
Studying murder often brings out the best in people.

53
00:03:28,323 --> 00:03:29,523
Thought you quit!

54
00:03:32,323 --> 00:03:35,042
Getting into West Washington wasn't easy.

55
00:03:35,123 --> 00:03:36,723
I busted my ass in high school

56
00:03:36,723 --> 00:03:39,801
and maintained a perfect 4.0 grade point average.

57
00:03:39,922 --> 00:03:43,801
All this, so I could study with the best mind in the field,

58
00:03:43,922 --> 00:03:46,722
Professor Robert Starkman.

59
00:03:46,802 --> 00:03:49,803
Possibly the most revered hunter of serial killers

60
00:03:49,921 --> 00:03:51,722
the FBI ever produced.

61
00:03:51,722 --> 00:03:54,921
After solving every high profile crime ever thrown at him,

62
00:03:55,042 --> 00:03:58,641
he suddenly made a startling life change and became a teacher.

63
00:03:58,721 --> 00:04:00,642
Some say it was his last case,

64
00:04:00,720 --> 00:04:04,121
the mysterious death of serial killer Patrick Bateman.

65
00:04:04,121 --> 00:04:05,401
Good morning.

66
00:04:05,521 --> 00:04:07,400
Funny how life works, isn't it?

67
00:04:07,521 --> 00:04:08,400
Good morning.

68
00:04:08,521 --> 00:04:10,401
Starkman never discusses the Bateman case...

69
00:04:10,520 --> 00:04:11,921
Never.

70
00:04:11,921 --> 00:04:15,521
Congratulations on getting through the first half of the semester...

71
00:04:15,521 --> 00:04:18,120
alive.

72
00:04:18,200 --> 00:04:20,040
I have here...

73
00:04:20,120 --> 00:04:21,920
the official application form

74
00:04:21,920 --> 00:04:24,720
for the teacher's assistant position for next year.

75
00:04:24,720 --> 00:04:26,719
This is my golden ticket to Quantico,

76
00:04:26,800 --> 00:04:29,639
the FBI's elite training program.

77
00:04:29,720 --> 00:04:32,039
Unfortunately, everyone else is here for the same reason.

78
00:04:32,119 --> 00:04:35,719
They know that nine out of Starkman's last 10 assistants,

79
00:04:35,800 --> 00:04:39,319
-were accepted into the FBI.
-...Announcing my new assistant

80
00:04:39,399 --> 00:04:42,119
by the end of the week, just before we head off for Spring Break.

81
00:04:42,200 --> 00:04:44,399
And, talking about Spring Break,

82
00:04:44,518 --> 00:04:46,800
don't forget the party at the Dean's mansion.

83
00:04:46,918 --> 00:04:50,518
We'll have the opportunity to say goodbye to Miss McGuire

84
00:04:50,518 --> 00:04:53,118
who's leaving us for bigger and better things.

85
00:04:59,519 --> 00:05:03,119
Well, after weeks of grueling, if not gruesome work,

86
00:05:03,119 --> 00:05:04,318
let's have some fun, shall we?

87
00:05:04,398 --> 00:05:07,118
Today we'll be looking at the unique aliases

88
00:05:07,198 --> 00:05:09,917
the FBI, the press and the general public

89
00:05:09,917 --> 00:05:13,316
have nicknamed serial killers, and why.

90
00:05:13,316 --> 00:05:16,517
His present TA is Elizabeth McGuire.

91
00:05:16,517 --> 00:05:18,317
She's already been accepted to Quantico...

92
00:05:18,396 --> 00:05:20,316
Early admissions.

93
00:05:20,316 --> 00:05:22,038
I'm the front runner to replace her.

94
00:05:22,118 --> 00:05:24,717
Nobody comes close to my rock solid GPA.

95
00:05:24,717 --> 00:05:28,716
Dr. H.H. Holmes was once vilified, in a biography,

96
00:05:29,717 --> 00:05:31,316
as the "Arch Fiend."

97
00:05:31,396 --> 00:05:33,636
I'd like to say none of them have a chance,

98
00:05:33,716 --> 00:05:35,315
but grades aren't everything.

99
00:05:35,396 --> 00:05:37,716
And I do have some competition.

100
00:05:37,796 --> 00:05:41,316
Contender number one: Brian Leads.

101
00:05:41,395 --> 00:05:45,036
A GPA as low as his wouldn't normally pose a threat.

102
00:05:45,114 --> 00:05:46,715
But his family's fortune,

103
00:05:46,796 --> 00:05:51,035
easily numbering in hundreds of millions, can open a lot of doors.

104
00:05:51,116 --> 00:05:53,715
How do you think he got into the school?

105
00:05:53,796 --> 00:05:55,715
Can you spell "donation"?

106
00:05:55,795 --> 00:05:56,795
He can't.

107
00:05:57,795 --> 00:06:00,315
Albert Fish, AKA "The Moon Maniac"...

108
00:06:00,395 --> 00:06:02,914
AKA "The Werewolf of Wisteria."

109
00:06:02,914 --> 00:06:06,313
Contender two: Cassandra Blaire.

110
00:06:06,394 --> 00:06:08,393
They say she and Starkman have been going at it

111
00:06:08,514 --> 00:06:10,314
since the beginning of the semester.

112
00:06:10,314 --> 00:06:12,914
But my guess: No way.

113
00:06:13,035 --> 00:06:16,035
He's old enough to be her grandfather.

114
00:06:16,114 --> 00:06:18,114
Nannie Doss...

115
00:06:18,194 --> 00:06:21,033
"The Black Widow" who murdered four of her husbands.

116
00:06:21,113 --> 00:06:24,313
Contender three: Keith Lawson.

117
00:06:24,313 --> 00:06:26,394
He poses the biggest threat of the three.

118
00:06:26,513 --> 00:06:29,313
He and I have been sparring all year in this class.

119
00:06:29,393 --> 00:06:31,913
But, I've yet to lose a single round.

120
00:06:32,033 --> 00:06:35,914
The fact is, none of them have a chance.

121
00:06:52,712 --> 00:06:54,312
Oh, Bobby.

122
00:06:57,112 --> 00:07:01,192
Red lips, red leaves fall on my knees like autumn

123
00:07:01,312 --> 00:07:05,711
I miss cigarettes every single day of my life

124
00:07:05,711 --> 00:07:07,791
When you make love to me

125
00:07:07,911 --> 00:07:10,311
I close my eyes and pray you say goodbye

126
00:07:11,631 --> 00:07:13,191
Damn

127
00:07:13,311 --> 00:07:17,630
She's dawning on me

128
00:07:19,510 --> 00:07:23,510
She's beautiful

129
00:07:23,630 --> 00:07:26,910
She's beautiful

130
00:07:27,031 --> 00:07:30,910
And I bet you don't know what love means

131
00:07:31,030 --> 00:07:36,510
It's just that you do not love me.

132
00:07:40,909 --> 00:07:44,109
The application is a mere formality.

133
00:07:44,189 --> 00:07:49,029
Come Friday, I will be Starkman's new teaching assistant.

134
00:07:49,109 --> 00:07:51,109
The position is mine.

135
00:07:51,189 --> 00:07:53,709
I deserve it and I'm going to get it.

136
00:07:53,709 --> 00:07:57,509
Yes, there may be a few more hoops I have to jump through,

137
00:07:57,509 --> 00:07:59,508
but I can handle them.

138
00:07:59,629 --> 00:08:04,308
Besides, failure is not an option.

139
00:08:05,708 --> 00:08:08,027
Why don't we just start over here,

140
00:08:08,108 --> 00:08:10,508
because I suggest you reconsider your position on this.

141
00:08:10,628 --> 00:08:13,788
I'm sorry, Mr. Leads. I can't make any exceptions.

142
00:08:13,908 --> 00:08:16,108
Your GPA is simply not high enough.

143
00:08:16,187 --> 00:08:18,788
Are you saying no to me? Do you know who my father is?

144
00:08:18,908 --> 00:08:20,787
Mr. Leads...

145
00:08:20,907 --> 00:08:23,507
I am well aware of your family's legacy.

146
00:08:23,627 --> 00:08:28,507
Heed my advice. A bird in the hand is worth two in the bush.

147
00:08:28,507 --> 00:08:30,507
That's your fucking advice?

148
00:08:30,507 --> 00:08:33,508
I have some advice for you. Get ready to take a long vacation.

149
00:08:33,627 --> 00:08:36,707
Go with God, dear heart. Next!

150
00:08:36,707 --> 00:08:38,387
Can you believe this shit?

151
00:08:38,387 --> 00:08:42,306
Wait till she sees my GPA after my cousin hacks into their mainframe.

152
00:08:42,306 --> 00:08:43,307
Oh!

153
00:08:43,385 --> 00:08:45,386
Do they give these things up for bitch of the month?

154
00:08:45,506 --> 00:08:47,786
That hag could be the reigning champion.

155
00:08:47,906 --> 00:08:49,905
She's lucky I don't bash her brains in.

156
00:08:51,786 --> 00:08:53,305
Next!

157
00:08:56,305 --> 00:08:57,306
Hi.

158
00:08:57,387 --> 00:09:00,705
I was told to drop off my application here.

159
00:09:03,625 --> 00:09:06,106
Looks like everything's in order here.

160
00:09:06,106 --> 00:09:07,505
Thank you.

161
00:09:07,505 --> 00:09:08,705
Wait a second.

162
00:09:08,785 --> 00:09:10,384
-What's this?
-What?

163
00:09:10,504 --> 00:09:12,784
It says here that you're a freshman.

164
00:09:12,904 --> 00:09:15,104
Yeah, so what?

165
00:09:15,104 --> 00:09:18,103
We don't usually allow freshmen or sophomores to become TAs.

166
00:09:18,184 --> 00:09:20,784
You have to be a junior or above.

167
00:09:20,905 --> 00:09:23,384
This isn't your usual situation.

168
00:09:23,505 --> 00:09:26,104
Professor Starkman told me I could apply.

169
00:09:26,184 --> 00:09:29,304
Shouldn't this decision be left up to the professor?

170
00:09:29,384 --> 00:09:30,624
'Fraid not.

171
00:09:30,704 --> 00:09:33,624
I'll run this up the flagpole and see who salutes.

172
00:09:35,383 --> 00:09:37,904
I'll have to speak with your teacher.

173
00:09:38,023 --> 00:09:41,902
I have a schedule to keep. It's all worked out.

174
00:09:42,022 --> 00:09:43,502
We do this for your own good.

175
00:09:43,502 --> 00:09:47,704
Freshmen can be extremely overwhelmed, being at college,

176
00:09:47,704 --> 00:09:50,703
and away from home for the first time in their lives.

177
00:09:50,782 --> 00:09:51,903
Here, take this.

178
00:09:52,023 --> 00:09:55,382
"Beat common freshmen fears in 10 easy steps."

179
00:09:55,502 --> 00:09:58,382
So many new experiences.

180
00:09:59,622 --> 00:10:01,622
It's so exciting.

181
00:10:01,622 --> 00:10:04,902
Look, the only experience I want

182
00:10:04,902 --> 00:10:07,501
is to be Professor Starkman's TA next semester.

183
00:10:07,621 --> 00:10:10,622
'Fraid not! It just wouldn't be right.

184
00:10:10,702 --> 00:10:13,902
I'm sure he will put in a good word for you,

185
00:10:13,902 --> 00:10:17,501
but I don't see how I can make any exceptions at this point

186
00:10:17,501 --> 00:10:20,900
without setting a dangerous precedent in school policy.

187
00:10:21,021 --> 00:10:23,780
I'll be informing the Dean of the situation.

188
00:10:23,901 --> 00:10:28,300
I'm sorry, Miss Newman. You'll just have to wait.

189
00:10:30,180 --> 00:10:31,699
Have a nice day.

190
00:10:31,781 --> 00:10:34,380
Hmm.

191
00:11:07,498 --> 00:11:09,019
Ricky Martin?

192
00:11:10,298 --> 00:11:11,498
Ricky?

193
00:11:13,698 --> 00:11:16,698
Ricky? Come to mama.

194
00:11:17,617 --> 00:11:19,298
Ricky?

195
00:11:19,376 --> 00:11:23,097
Ricky Martin? Ricky?

196
00:11:24,498 --> 00:11:25,898
Ricky?

197
00:11:26,017 --> 00:11:27,018
Oh!

198
00:11:27,097 --> 00:11:30,377
Ricky, you got some explaining to do.

199
00:11:30,497 --> 00:11:32,177
Ricky?

200
00:11:38,177 --> 00:11:39,897
Oh, thank God.

201
00:11:52,016 --> 00:11:54,616
What happened to you?

202
00:12:29,613 --> 00:12:33,094
Bad things

203
00:12:33,174 --> 00:12:36,094
Dead things

204
00:12:36,175 --> 00:12:41,293
Sad things have to happen

205
00:12:43,693 --> 00:12:47,014
Bad things

206
00:12:47,092 --> 00:12:50,372
Dead things

207
00:12:50,493 --> 00:12:54,612
Sad things have to happen.

208
00:13:02,893 --> 00:13:04,292
Hey, Miss Newman.

209
00:13:04,373 --> 00:13:06,691
Wow, Brian. Are you stalking me now?

210
00:13:06,772 --> 00:13:10,092
No, Rachael. If I was stalking you, you'd know it.

211
00:13:10,092 --> 00:13:12,891
I mean--you wouldn't know it. You know?

212
00:13:12,891 --> 00:13:14,691
I thought we should get together and...

213
00:13:14,691 --> 00:13:18,491
discuss the state of the union and life in general.

214
00:13:18,612 --> 00:13:20,292
Get to the point, Brian.

215
00:13:20,372 --> 00:13:24,012
My inside source says he has narrowed it down.

216
00:13:24,091 --> 00:13:26,010
Guess who's still in the running?

217
00:13:27,011 --> 00:13:28,892
Keith, Cassandra and me.

218
00:13:29,011 --> 00:13:31,691
Unless you can raise your GPA.

219
00:13:33,011 --> 00:13:35,290
That problem's already solved.

220
00:13:35,370 --> 00:13:38,010
Do you want to catch a bite to eat tomorrow night,

221
00:13:38,090 --> 00:13:40,291
maybe some dinner and discuss it?

222
00:13:40,369 --> 00:13:43,490
What's to discuss? It's no big news.

223
00:13:43,490 --> 00:13:45,290
We were always the front runners.

224
00:13:45,370 --> 00:13:50,091
We could get together and form an alliance,

225
00:13:50,170 --> 00:13:52,289
eliminate our competition.

226
00:13:53,490 --> 00:13:56,289
That sounds intriguing but...

227
00:13:56,370 --> 00:13:59,089
-I have a paper to write.
-A paper?

228
00:13:59,089 --> 00:14:01,089
We should get to know each other better.

229
00:14:01,089 --> 00:14:05,369
Is it just me or is there unspoken sexual tension between us?

230
00:14:05,488 --> 00:14:09,889
We should bring it to the surface and stop lying to each other.

231
00:14:10,009 --> 00:14:12,089
Are you on crack?

232
00:14:12,089 --> 00:14:15,689
I don't know. It was white, it was in a pipe--

233
00:14:15,689 --> 00:14:19,368
-So, what do you say?
-I have a paper to write.

234
00:14:19,368 --> 00:14:20,488
No, no, no...

235
00:14:20,608 --> 00:14:23,007
I won't take no for an answer twice in one day.

236
00:14:23,088 --> 00:14:25,887
You have to eat, right? I have to eat. We both have to eat.

237
00:14:25,887 --> 00:14:27,688
Let's just eat together. It's no big deal.

238
00:14:27,767 --> 00:14:30,368
I was just fucking around with this sexual tension stuff.

239
00:14:30,488 --> 00:14:32,008
I just throw stuff out there.

240
00:14:32,088 --> 00:14:35,288
I'm crazy, I'm like a volcano, just waiting to erupt--

241
00:14:35,368 --> 00:14:36,367
Okay!

242
00:14:36,487 --> 00:14:39,167
Okay, fine. Pick me up at 8:00.

243
00:14:39,287 --> 00:14:42,087
-Eight? Like 8:00 pm?
-Yeah.

244
00:14:42,167 --> 00:14:45,087
-Between 7:00 and 9:00?
-Yeah!

245
00:14:45,087 --> 00:14:46,367
Okay.

246
00:14:46,487 --> 00:14:47,766
‘Cause it's great for me--

247
00:14:47,886 --> 00:14:50,086
-I'll see you at 8:00.
-Whatever.

248
00:14:50,166 --> 00:14:53,005
Maybe I'll be there five minutes later.

249
00:14:54,887 --> 00:14:57,686
So...what are you doing for Spring Break?

250
00:14:57,767 --> 00:15:00,287
I'm just gonna hang around and get some work done.

251
00:15:00,287 --> 00:15:04,086
What, "hang around"? You mean stay on campus?

252
00:15:04,166 --> 00:15:05,486
Yeah.

253
00:15:05,605 --> 00:15:07,606
You're not going home?

254
00:15:07,686 --> 00:15:09,286
Why?

255
00:15:09,286 --> 00:15:11,165
Because I have work to do.

256
00:15:11,286 --> 00:15:13,485
My family's coming for my mom's birthday

257
00:15:13,604 --> 00:15:15,605
to see how the other half lives.

258
00:15:15,684 --> 00:15:17,765
-Okay, that sounds terrible.
-I know.

259
00:15:17,885 --> 00:15:19,365
What are you doing?

260
00:15:19,486 --> 00:15:22,605
Bobby's taking me up to his cabin in the Northern Cascade--

261
00:15:22,685 --> 00:15:25,005
Cassandra, don't call him Bobby in front of me.

262
00:15:25,005 --> 00:15:25,885
I'm sorry.

263
00:15:26,005 --> 00:15:28,684
Professor Starkman is taking me up to his cabin.

264
00:15:28,764 --> 00:15:30,485
When do you guys leave?

265
00:15:30,605 --> 00:15:33,764
He's got to go upstate first, to meet Diane and Louisa.

266
00:15:33,764 --> 00:15:35,684
You mean, his wife and his daughter?

267
00:15:35,765 --> 00:15:38,284
Whatever! Yes, them.

268
00:15:38,364 --> 00:15:40,763
He's meeting them at his in-laws'.

269
00:15:40,883 --> 00:15:44,084
I can't stand how much of his time they take up.

270
00:15:44,084 --> 00:15:46,284
Cass, they're his family!

271
00:15:46,364 --> 00:15:47,604
Whatever.

272
00:15:47,684 --> 00:15:50,363
I'm late for a study session. I should just go.

273
00:15:52,003 --> 00:15:55,283
I can't believe you're actually going out with Brian.

274
00:15:55,364 --> 00:15:57,003
How did that happen?

275
00:15:59,883 --> 00:16:01,603
Okay...

276
00:16:01,683 --> 00:16:05,483
the other day, our eyes met across a crowded room,

277
00:16:05,483 --> 00:16:08,603
and there was this--this spark,

278
00:16:08,682 --> 00:16:11,082
the sign I've been waiting for my whole life.

279
00:16:11,082 --> 00:16:16,283
It was then that I knew that Brian was my soul mate.

280
00:16:18,082 --> 00:16:20,602
-Oh my God.
-I know.

281
00:16:20,681 --> 00:16:24,001
-Really?
-No, not really.

282
00:16:32,082 --> 00:16:35,081
It's great to be with you tonight.

283
00:16:35,161 --> 00:16:37,881
-Mmm-hmm.
-Hi.

284
00:16:37,881 --> 00:16:41,360
Hi. Can I get you something to drink?

285
00:16:41,480 --> 00:16:44,280
Yes. I'll have a Kettle One martini, straight up,

286
00:16:44,361 --> 00:16:47,161
very dry. Very, very dry.

287
00:16:47,280 --> 00:16:49,600
And the lady will have...

288
00:16:49,600 --> 00:16:53,480
-I'll have a glass of house red.
-House red.

289
00:16:53,480 --> 00:16:57,080
Good. I'll be right back.

290
00:16:59,080 --> 00:17:01,999
-So, you look great.
-Thanks.

291
00:17:02,080 --> 00:17:05,079
our hair is different. It looks good.

292
00:17:06,159 --> 00:17:09,280
-Thanks.
-No problem.

293
00:17:12,279 --> 00:17:15,879
It's great that we finally have some "us" time.

294
00:17:15,879 --> 00:17:18,879
-You and I hanging out.
-I agree.

295
00:17:22,878 --> 00:17:25,278
Yeah. Listen, Rach,

296
00:17:25,359 --> 00:17:28,478
before we embark on our evening,

297
00:17:28,478 --> 00:17:30,478
I have a confession to make.

298
00:17:30,598 --> 00:17:33,078
Can you wait until we get our drinks

299
00:17:33,078 --> 00:17:35,277
before you start making your confessions?

300
00:17:35,357 --> 00:17:38,477
-Oh yeah, sure.
-Thanks.

301
00:17:43,758 --> 00:17:45,477
Look. Our drinks.

302
00:17:46,677 --> 00:17:47,878
Thank you.

303
00:17:49,677 --> 00:17:51,477
-There you go.
-Thank you.

304
00:17:52,677 --> 00:17:54,877
It's my first day.

305
00:17:56,996 --> 00:17:58,277
So, ready to order?

306
00:17:58,277 --> 00:18:01,876
Can you just give us a minute here?

307
00:18:01,876 --> 00:18:03,276
Sure.

308
00:18:03,356 --> 00:18:06,157
Take your time.

309
00:18:07,277 --> 00:18:09,277
Thank you.

310
00:18:11,076 --> 00:18:13,756
Okay. What would you like to confess?

311
00:18:16,076 --> 00:18:17,876
This is difficult for me,

312
00:18:17,995 --> 00:18:20,595
because I really want us to remain friends after--

313
00:18:20,676 --> 00:18:24,475
regardless of who Starkman picks for the TA position.

314
00:18:24,595 --> 00:18:27,675
Wow, I'm touched. Brian, I really am.

315
00:18:28,876 --> 00:18:31,675
You should know I'm determined to get the position.

316
00:18:31,675 --> 00:18:33,075
Over the last few months,

317
00:18:33,156 --> 00:18:36,675
I've been doing a little research on Cassandra Blair.

318
00:18:36,755 --> 00:18:38,874
What kind of research?

319
00:18:38,995 --> 00:18:42,354
Let's just say that if she gets the position,

320
00:18:42,354 --> 00:18:44,754
the Dean's office is going to receive an anonymous letter

321
00:18:44,875 --> 00:18:48,074
regarding her and Starkman's relationship,

322
00:18:48,154 --> 00:18:51,153
accompanied by some very revealing photographs.

323
00:18:51,273 --> 00:18:53,874
-How Christian of you.
-Thanks.

324
00:18:53,874 --> 00:18:56,154
I guess that narrows it down to three.

325
00:18:57,874 --> 00:18:58,874
Yeah.

326
00:19:00,474 --> 00:19:02,274
You know who my father is, right?

327
00:19:02,274 --> 00:19:05,473
Yes, we're all in awe of your family's money.

328
00:19:05,473 --> 00:19:08,872
You know, you and Keith are very smart.

329
00:19:08,993 --> 00:19:11,272
So I've had to go to great lengths

330
00:19:11,353 --> 00:19:16,072
to ensure that my bright future in the FBI goes without a hitch.

331
00:19:17,072 --> 00:19:18,352
What are you smiling at?

332
00:19:23,072 --> 00:19:24,152
This.

333
00:19:26,072 --> 00:19:27,471
That is the press release

334
00:19:27,471 --> 00:19:30,592
for the new Carson-Leads Behavioral Sciences Building.

335
00:19:30,592 --> 00:19:33,071
It's just one of my dad's new pet projects.

336
00:19:37,151 --> 00:19:38,351
So...

337
00:19:38,351 --> 00:19:40,671
I have an offer you can't refuse.

338
00:19:41,752 --> 00:19:43,672
Drop out of the race for the TA position,

339
00:19:43,751 --> 00:19:48,871
and I'll ensure you have seven digits of my family's gratitude.

340
00:19:53,471 --> 00:19:54,670
Brian?

341
00:19:55,750 --> 00:19:57,471
Are you bribing me now?

342
00:19:58,589 --> 00:20:00,150
Bribe? Did I say bribe?

343
00:20:00,269 --> 00:20:02,869
Just think of it as a business opportunity.

344
00:20:02,990 --> 00:20:04,071
Trust me,

345
00:20:04,150 --> 00:20:07,670
the alternative wouldn't be too pleasant.

346
00:20:09,870 --> 00:20:12,989
"I'll let you be in my dreams if I can be in yours."

347
00:20:14,349 --> 00:20:16,868
-What?
-It's a quote.

348
00:20:16,989 --> 00:20:18,989
Bob Dylan, maybe you've heard of him?

349
00:20:20,148 --> 00:20:22,069
-Oh, yeah.
-You know, Brian,

350
00:20:22,148 --> 00:20:23,868
you should get out more.

351
00:20:24,868 --> 00:20:27,068
Maybe I will.

352
00:20:28,989 --> 00:20:30,469
The night's young.

353
00:20:30,590 --> 00:20:32,869
That it is.

354
00:20:32,989 --> 00:20:34,348
Cheers.

355
00:20:44,347 --> 00:20:45,347
Don't!

356
00:20:47,147 --> 00:20:49,347
Shh!

357
00:20:55,867 --> 00:20:58,867
We're home, we're home.

358
00:21:03,867 --> 00:21:04,747
Wow!

359
00:21:05,866 --> 00:21:08,066
This is like...a room.

360
00:21:13,066 --> 00:21:18,746
Do you want to be my girl?

361
00:21:18,866 --> 00:21:24,265
Do you want to be my friend?

362
00:21:24,346 --> 00:21:29,745
Do you want to start it all?

363
00:21:31,345 --> 00:21:33,066
We can stop if you want.

364
00:21:34,265 --> 00:21:38,983
-No, no...I just don't-
-What, you don't have any?

365
00:21:39,064 --> 00:21:42,745
Don't worry, I'll take care of everything when the time comes.

366
00:21:42,866 --> 00:21:45,745
Oh, the old "pull out and pray" trick.

367
00:21:45,864 --> 00:21:48,144
Great, a Renaissance man.

368
00:21:48,144 --> 00:21:49,464
Wait a second!

369
00:21:49,464 --> 00:21:51,584
The convenience store, down the street--

370
00:21:51,664 --> 00:21:54,063
I'll just go down there, it's right around the corner.

371
00:21:54,063 --> 00:21:56,664
It's really convenient and I'll get some, I'll get tons.

372
00:21:56,743 --> 00:21:57,584
Wait a minute, what am I saying?

373
00:21:57,663 --> 00:22:01,864
My roommate's got tons of them, drawers full of them.

374
00:22:01,864 --> 00:22:03,344
A real prophylactic factory.

375
00:22:06,464 --> 00:22:08,463
Are we done here?

376
00:22:10,143 --> 00:22:11,463
No, we're not done.

377
00:22:11,463 --> 00:22:14,063
I'll walk down the hall, and get some from a friend.

378
00:22:15,743 --> 00:22:18,742
-Oh, great.
-Make yourself comfortable.

379
00:22:18,863 --> 00:22:21,262
Sure, great.

380
00:22:23,142 --> 00:22:24,261
I'll be here.

381
00:22:44,581 --> 00:22:47,741
Jeez. A piss-sheet.

382
00:22:59,580 --> 00:23:01,460
Jesus.

383
00:23:03,260 --> 00:23:04,740
What the fuck.

384
00:23:35,858 --> 00:23:38,058
Ribbed, for her pleasure.

385
00:23:39,859 --> 00:23:42,259
Yep, I just killed Brian.

386
00:23:42,259 --> 00:23:45,058
But you've got to look at the positive side...

387
00:23:45,058 --> 00:23:47,458
I'm killing for a better tomorrow.

388
00:23:47,458 --> 00:23:49,458
Once I get into the FBI,

389
00:23:49,458 --> 00:23:51,458
I'll be able to stop dozens,

390
00:23:51,458 --> 00:23:54,657
maybe even hundreds of serial killers every year.

391
00:23:54,738 --> 00:23:56,457
Okay, think about it...

392
00:23:56,457 --> 00:23:58,577
I'm killing the few to save the many.

393
00:23:58,657 --> 00:24:01,257
Sort of like Robin Hood, you know?

394
00:24:01,336 --> 00:24:05,058
God, I think I need some professional help.

395
00:24:06,138 --> 00:24:09,257
Rachael, have you ever been to a psychiatrist before?

396
00:24:09,257 --> 00:24:10,577
No.

397
00:24:10,577 --> 00:24:13,057
-No, how does it work?
-It works like this.

398
00:24:13,057 --> 00:24:16,856
You want answers, so we get together weekly,

399
00:24:16,977 --> 00:24:20,056
and we ask the questions that will lead you to your answers.

400
00:24:20,136 --> 00:24:21,576
All right?

401
00:24:22,856 --> 00:24:26,737
I could tell you anything, and you'd still never know me.

402
00:24:26,856 --> 00:24:29,257
You could, and that's your choice.

403
00:24:29,336 --> 00:24:30,856
But why would you lie to me?

404
00:24:30,856 --> 00:24:33,656
Because I don't expose my Achilles' heel to anyone.

405
00:24:35,256 --> 00:24:39,255
-Why do you say that?
-I just need to be on watch.

406
00:24:39,335 --> 00:24:41,854
If I'm not looking out for number one, then who is?

407
00:24:41,854 --> 00:24:44,974
It's a dog-eat-dog-world out there,

408
00:24:45,055 --> 00:24:48,654
and my future depends on not getting eaten by the other dogs.

409
00:24:48,734 --> 00:24:51,334
I have schedules, appointments and dreams

410
00:24:51,334 --> 00:24:53,055
that only I can fulfill.

411
00:24:53,134 --> 00:24:55,575
No one is going to do that for me.

412
00:24:55,654 --> 00:24:58,574
Who do you think is keeping you from achieving these goals?

413
00:24:58,655 --> 00:25:02,133
-Other people.
-What people?

414
00:25:02,254 --> 00:25:04,853
Anyone who gets in my way.

415
00:25:04,974 --> 00:25:09,573
If you could be anyone in the world, except yourself,

416
00:25:09,653 --> 00:25:11,453
who would that be?

417
00:25:11,574 --> 00:25:14,653
Elizabeth McGuire.

418
00:25:14,734 --> 00:25:17,253
Elizabeth McGuire? Who's she?

419
00:25:17,333 --> 00:25:20,054
She's Professor Starkman's present TA.

420
00:25:20,054 --> 00:25:22,333
And the next in line to go to Quantico.

421
00:25:22,453 --> 00:25:25,732
-And Quantico is?
-My goal.

422
00:25:25,853 --> 00:25:30,052
-My destiny.
-I see.

423
00:25:30,133 --> 00:25:32,652
Have you ever wanted something so bad

424
00:25:32,732 --> 00:25:34,851
that you'd do anything to get it?

425
00:25:35,851 --> 00:25:37,252
Sure.

426
00:25:37,332 --> 00:25:39,973
Go on.

427
00:25:41,573 --> 00:25:44,852
And that's why I went to West Washington.

428
00:25:44,973 --> 00:25:47,971
I've always known that, really,

429
00:25:47,971 --> 00:25:49,732
there were only three other people

430
00:25:49,732 --> 00:25:52,132
who could steal the TA position away from me.

431
00:25:52,251 --> 00:25:54,971
What happens if you don't get the position?

432
00:25:55,052 --> 00:25:57,250
I can't even consider that.

433
00:25:57,331 --> 00:26:00,251
Failure is not an option. I'll get the position.

434
00:26:00,331 --> 00:26:04,451
-How can you be so sure?
-Because I am.

435
00:26:09,451 --> 00:26:12,650
-Why don't we stop there?
-Okay.

436
00:26:13,850 --> 00:26:16,250
My secretary will get your billing info.

437
00:26:16,330 --> 00:26:17,570
Okay.

438
00:26:17,650 --> 00:26:20,969
So, same time next week?

439
00:26:20,969 --> 00:26:23,570
-You bet.
-Okay.

440
00:26:29,250 --> 00:26:31,129
Starkman.

441
00:26:34,129 --> 00:26:35,649
Hey, Bobby. It's Eric.

442
00:26:35,729 --> 00:26:37,729
Hey, Eric. What's up?

443
00:26:37,849 --> 00:26:40,968
I just had a first time session with one of your students.

444
00:26:41,048 --> 00:26:42,968
Wow, wow, wow...

445
00:26:43,048 --> 00:26:45,648
Aren't we violating some sort of privacy code here?

446
00:26:45,648 --> 00:26:48,049
Yes and no. I'll tell you what...

447
00:26:48,049 --> 00:26:49,968
I won't tell you the name,

448
00:26:50,049 --> 00:26:52,649
if you promise not to say it once you've figured it out.

449
00:26:52,728 --> 00:26:57,128
-Is that a deal?
-Okay. Fire away.

450
00:26:57,249 --> 00:26:59,048
All right.

451
00:26:59,128 --> 00:27:03,048
I think I've identified this person as a textbook sociopath.

452
00:27:03,048 --> 00:27:05,846
It's a prerequisite for getting into college in the first place.

453
00:27:05,846 --> 00:27:10,567
Tell me about it. Still, this girl has no concept of reality

454
00:27:10,647 --> 00:27:12,046
or the difference between right or wrong.

455
00:27:12,127 --> 00:27:13,728
A girl.

456
00:27:13,847 --> 00:27:16,248
Mmm, the plot thickens.

457
00:27:16,248 --> 00:27:19,646
She's obsessed with becoming your assistant next semester.

458
00:27:19,727 --> 00:27:22,447
If that's her obsession, it's no big deal.

459
00:27:22,566 --> 00:27:25,566
These kids think I'm their ticket to the FBI.

460
00:27:25,647 --> 00:27:27,247
Just keep your eyes open.

461
00:27:27,247 --> 00:27:29,445
This girl--

462
00:27:29,445 --> 00:27:30,967
she scared me.

463
00:27:31,045 --> 00:27:35,325
Jesus, if she's that dangerous, tell me her name

464
00:27:35,446 --> 00:27:37,847
before she turns up in class with an AK-47.

465
00:27:37,847 --> 00:27:41,846
I can't do that. I've already broken the law by placing this call.

466
00:27:41,846 --> 00:27:45,045
Just be aware this student's in your class.

467
00:27:45,045 --> 00:27:48,445
What exactly do you mean, "be aware"?

468
00:27:48,565 --> 00:27:52,125
25 years in the FBI...turn your radar on.

469
00:27:52,244 --> 00:27:54,964
Just make sure she doesn't get out of hand.

470
00:27:55,045 --> 00:27:57,965
-She's identified three of her peers--
-Dr. Daniels?

471
00:28:06,044 --> 00:28:09,845
-Okay, okay, Mother.
-Mom?

472
00:28:09,963 --> 00:28:11,844
I've got to go, I've got an appointment.

473
00:28:12,844 --> 00:28:14,644
I love you. I do.

474
00:28:14,644 --> 00:28:17,443
Okay, I'll see you this weekend. Bye.

475
00:28:17,443 --> 00:28:18,644
Rachael?

476
00:28:18,644 --> 00:28:21,043
I am so sorry to disturb you.

477
00:28:21,043 --> 00:28:23,043
I didn't realize you were on the phone

478
00:28:23,043 --> 00:28:25,444
-and your secretary wasn't there.
-It's okay.

479
00:28:25,563 --> 00:28:27,844
I just left my keys here.

480
00:28:27,963 --> 00:28:30,443
I am such a textbook nut case sometimes.

481
00:28:30,563 --> 00:28:33,643
I'd probably lose my head if it wasn't screwed on.

482
00:28:33,643 --> 00:28:36,242
Oh, there they are.

483
00:28:39,122 --> 00:28:42,842
It's so nice that you stay in touch with your mom.

484
00:28:42,842 --> 00:28:46,122
-How old is she?
-72.

485
00:28:47,242 --> 00:28:48,241
Wow.

486
00:28:48,322 --> 00:28:50,443
72, that's a great age.

487
00:28:50,562 --> 00:28:53,322
So many new and exciting things, the golden years.

488
00:28:53,441 --> 00:28:55,442
Grandchildren?

489
00:28:55,562 --> 00:28:57,842
No. I'm--

490
00:28:57,962 --> 00:29:00,121
My wife and I never had children.

491
00:29:00,242 --> 00:29:02,321
Was she not able to?

492
00:29:02,441 --> 00:29:04,641
Actually, we're divorced.

493
00:29:05,640 --> 00:29:07,641
I have another patient coming in soon.

494
00:29:07,641 --> 00:29:09,241
I have to prepare for him.

495
00:29:09,320 --> 00:29:11,119
So I'll have to ask you to leave.

496
00:29:12,841 --> 00:29:14,840
Which is it, Eric?

497
00:29:14,840 --> 00:29:18,721
An appointment downtown or a patient in your office?

498
00:29:23,040 --> 00:29:25,840
It's not nice to lie to your dear old mom.

499
00:29:29,040 --> 00:29:30,839
See you next week.

500
00:29:49,838 --> 00:29:53,438
After my session with Eric, I really needed some therapy.

501
00:29:53,558 --> 00:29:55,839
That guy just about drove me nuts.

502
00:29:55,957 --> 00:29:58,557
So, I went back to something my dad always said,

503
00:29:58,557 --> 00:30:01,319
"nothing like a change of scenery to clear your head,

504
00:30:01,439 --> 00:30:03,719
to ease the burden of a busy schedule."

505
00:30:03,838 --> 00:30:04,838
Besides,

506
00:30:04,958 --> 00:30:07,958
tonight's the Behavioral Sciences party at the Dean's.

507
00:30:08,038 --> 00:30:12,317
I have to look good. I wanna be dressed to kill.

508
00:30:12,437 --> 00:30:16,957
Sometimes she feels so sad

509
00:30:19,438 --> 00:30:24,717
And other times feels twice as bad

510
00:30:26,837 --> 00:30:32,037
When the tears are in her eyes

511
00:30:33,636 --> 00:30:36,636
She never cries

512
00:30:39,836 --> 00:30:44,435
Ordinary girl

513
00:30:44,435 --> 00:30:48,237
I know

514
00:30:48,237 --> 00:30:51,636
We're different

515
00:30:51,716 --> 00:30:55,035
But I'm stranger in the world

516
00:30:55,035 --> 00:30:56,835
Ordinary girl

517
00:30:58,835 --> 00:31:02,635
Ordinary.

518
00:31:07,034 --> 00:31:09,434
-Excuse me?
-Bite me, Barbie.

519
00:31:09,553 --> 00:31:13,434
The Anthony Perkins character in Psycho was modeled on Ed Gein.

520
00:31:13,554 --> 00:31:16,234
My heart rate nearly triples when I get there

521
00:31:16,315 --> 00:31:19,555
and see the vultures have descended upon Starkman.

522
00:31:19,634 --> 00:31:23,633
He broke the mold because he only killed two people in his entire career.

523
00:31:23,714 --> 00:31:25,834
I must have lost track of time running on.

524
00:31:25,953 --> 00:31:27,832
I had planned to get here early to get

525
00:31:27,953 --> 00:31:29,953
as much time with Starkman as possible.

526
00:31:30,033 --> 00:31:32,313
And now I'm late. This is a disaster.

527
00:31:32,432 --> 00:31:34,233
Bitch!

528
00:31:34,233 --> 00:31:37,633
...for Leatherface in The Texas Chainsaw Massacre--

529
00:31:37,713 --> 00:31:40,953
-Hello, Miss Brown.
-I'll be right back.

530
00:31:40,953 --> 00:31:42,833
It's good to see you.

531
00:31:42,833 --> 00:31:45,832
-Hey, how is it going?
-Hey!

532
00:31:45,952 --> 00:31:48,433
How was your date with Brian?

533
00:31:49,713 --> 00:31:51,711
Fine. Short. I don't know.

534
00:31:51,832 --> 00:31:54,632
Short? How short was he?

535
00:31:54,711 --> 00:31:56,431
I mean, "it."

536
00:31:56,552 --> 00:31:58,831
We didn't get that far. He went home after dinner.

537
00:31:58,951 --> 00:32:02,032
What do you mean? Why did you come to borrow a rubber,

538
00:32:02,112 --> 00:32:05,312
-if he went home after dinner?
-What's up with the third degree?

539
00:32:05,432 --> 00:32:08,312
I'm just confused. Did you guys get it on or not?

540
00:32:08,431 --> 00:32:10,431
It's none of your business.

541
00:32:10,431 --> 00:32:13,431
-Can we drop this, please?
-Whatever.

542
00:32:14,831 --> 00:32:17,230
Sometimes I don't understand you.

543
00:32:17,311 --> 00:32:19,310
It's like you're not even here.

544
00:32:20,310 --> 00:32:22,230
What did you do last night?

545
00:32:22,230 --> 00:32:24,550
-Bobby came over for--
-Cassandra!

546
00:32:24,631 --> 00:32:27,631
I'm sorry. Professor Starkman came over for a study session.

547
00:32:27,631 --> 00:32:31,551
And let me assure you, it was definitely not short.

548
00:32:31,630 --> 00:32:34,430
I'm gonna vomit.

549
00:32:37,630 --> 00:32:40,429
What are you smiling at, freak?

550
00:32:40,549 --> 00:32:42,429
Come here.

551
00:32:44,708 --> 00:32:46,549
Bob--I mean the professor,

552
00:32:46,629 --> 00:32:48,550
said I'm a shoo-in for the TA position.

553
00:32:49,629 --> 00:32:51,829
I wasn't supposed to tell anyone,

554
00:32:51,949 --> 00:32:53,949
but since we are so close...

555
00:32:54,029 --> 00:32:55,629
I was gonna burst.

556
00:32:55,709 --> 00:32:58,828
Now I get to spend all this time with my sweetie.

557
00:32:58,948 --> 00:33:01,628
And his wife'll think we're working.

558
00:33:02,628 --> 00:33:05,229
Wait, maybe I'll go to Quantico.

559
00:33:05,229 --> 00:33:08,027
How great would that be?

560
00:33:08,108 --> 00:33:09,947
Just don't tell anyone, okay?

561
00:33:10,028 --> 00:33:12,109
-Not even Brian.
-Don't worry.

562
00:33:12,228 --> 00:33:14,028
our secret's safe with me.

563
00:33:14,108 --> 00:33:16,028
This party's such a dud.

564
00:33:16,109 --> 00:33:18,628
Let's blow it off and you give me the details.

565
00:33:18,628 --> 00:33:21,428
Perfect. Let me talk to Starkman,

566
00:33:21,547 --> 00:33:23,107
and we'll go to Jittery Joe's for coffee.

567
00:33:23,228 --> 00:33:25,427
No! It's way too crowded.

568
00:33:25,547 --> 00:33:28,226
You don't want anyone to know about you and Bobby.

569
00:33:28,307 --> 00:33:31,306
Let's grab some wine and go to your room.

570
00:33:31,427 --> 00:33:33,027
That sounds great!

571
00:33:33,106 --> 00:33:35,547
Just make sure you don't tell anyone, okay?

572
00:33:35,627 --> 00:33:38,027
-Don't let me down.
-Don't worry,

573
00:33:38,027 --> 00:33:40,546
I would never let you down.

574
00:33:41,827 --> 00:33:43,626
Like I said, Cassie,

575
00:33:43,706 --> 00:33:48,026
student-teacher relationships just never work out.

576
00:33:56,225 --> 00:33:58,306
It's Cassandra, I can't get to the phone,

577
00:33:58,306 --> 00:34:01,106
so leave a quickie and I'll get back to you.

578
00:34:01,226 --> 00:34:04,625
Hello Cassandra. Professor Starkman here.

579
00:34:04,705 --> 00:34:08,825
Listen, it's 11:25 and you missed your study session.

580
00:34:08,825 --> 00:34:11,625
Call me back to reschedule.

581
00:34:22,104 --> 00:34:24,024
Doctor Daniels?

582
00:34:25,024 --> 00:34:28,024
I'm sorry to drop in without an appointment,

583
00:34:28,104 --> 00:34:29,624
but there is something on my mind.

584
00:34:29,624 --> 00:34:31,944
Sure.

585
00:34:32,023 --> 00:34:33,944
Sure, Rachael.

586
00:34:34,023 --> 00:34:37,223
-How are things with you?
-They couldn't be better.

587
00:34:37,223 --> 00:34:38,223
Really?

588
00:34:38,303 --> 00:34:41,222
Any word on that TA job yet?

589
00:34:41,222 --> 00:34:43,423
He won't announce it until before Spring Break.

590
00:34:43,423 --> 00:34:45,542
When does that start for you guys?

591
00:34:45,623 --> 00:34:48,223
-End of the week.
-Really?

592
00:34:48,304 --> 00:34:49,702
-Two days?
-Yeah.

593
00:34:49,702 --> 00:34:52,703
-And how do you feel about that?
-Pretty confident.

594
00:34:52,822 --> 00:34:56,702
-You think you'll get the job?
-I don't think. I know.

595
00:34:57,702 --> 00:34:59,022
Okay, Rachael.

596
00:34:59,022 --> 00:35:01,942
Worst case scenario:

597
00:35:02,022 --> 00:35:03,542
you don't get the job. What then?

598
00:35:03,622 --> 00:35:06,022
What are you talking about, Dr. Daniels?

599
00:35:06,101 --> 00:35:07,821
It's mine.

600
00:35:07,821 --> 00:35:11,022
You want me to come up with some idea of what's wrong with me,

601
00:35:11,101 --> 00:35:13,222
but I'll be honest. I came here

602
00:35:13,301 --> 00:35:15,221
to tell you I'm not coming back next week.

603
00:35:15,221 --> 00:35:18,102
Don't worry, I have every intention to pay for your time.

604
00:35:18,221 --> 00:35:22,820
However, I feel the problem we have connecting lies mostly with you.

605
00:35:22,820 --> 00:35:26,020
Look, this is a small town.

606
00:35:26,020 --> 00:35:29,300
My guess is you know almost everyone here.

607
00:35:30,421 --> 00:35:33,420
You were born here, right?

608
00:35:33,540 --> 00:35:36,020
It must be so disappointing to see all these college kids

609
00:35:36,020 --> 00:35:38,820
come in and out of your town every year,

610
00:35:38,820 --> 00:35:41,620
moving on to bigger and better opportunities,

611
00:35:41,700 --> 00:35:45,420
while you stay here, year after year, getting older and older.

612
00:35:45,539 --> 00:35:48,619
And all while taking care of your dear old mom.

613
00:35:48,700 --> 00:35:51,099
And on top of this, you're divorced?

614
00:35:51,099 --> 00:35:54,099
God! The female population in this town,

615
00:35:54,219 --> 00:35:56,938
aside from the sexy little college girls running around,

616
00:35:57,019 --> 00:35:59,220
must be pretty weak.

617
00:35:59,300 --> 00:36:01,539
This alone would cripple any man.

618
00:36:01,620 --> 00:36:04,938
our level of frustration must be through the roof.

619
00:36:05,019 --> 00:36:07,938
A dead-end job with no love life,

620
00:36:08,019 --> 00:36:11,699
all while taking care of your sick mom.

621
00:36:11,818 --> 00:36:13,818
Just the other day,

622
00:36:13,818 --> 00:36:16,097
I noticed you were judging me.

623
00:36:16,097 --> 00:36:19,817
Is that fair? I mean really, is that?

624
00:36:19,817 --> 00:36:22,018
I don't think so.

625
00:36:23,218 --> 00:36:26,018
our life is very similar to Ed Gein's.

626
00:36:27,018 --> 00:36:28,298
Ed Gein?

627
00:36:28,418 --> 00:36:32,938
Yes, Ed Gein. Very famous serial killer.

628
00:36:33,017 --> 00:36:36,297
A bachelor, raised by his domineering mother,

629
00:36:36,416 --> 00:36:38,816
until she died when he was roughly your age.

630
00:36:38,936 --> 00:36:42,616
God, he went nuts! He couldn't handle the loss.

631
00:36:42,697 --> 00:36:44,936
What would you do without your mother?

632
00:36:44,936 --> 00:36:46,697
Okay Rachael, that's enough.

633
00:36:46,816 --> 00:36:48,537
You don't know me, and I don't know you.

634
00:36:48,616 --> 00:36:51,096
We were getting to know each other.

635
00:36:51,217 --> 00:36:53,616
These sessions are a process.

636
00:36:53,696 --> 00:36:56,015
So don't go jumping to conclusions.

637
00:36:56,096 --> 00:36:58,616
No. I'm not jumping to any conclusions here.

638
00:36:58,695 --> 00:37:02,816
If you just open up your eyes, you'd see I'm already there.

639
00:37:05,416 --> 00:37:08,095
Have a good day, Doctor.

640
00:37:11,536 --> 00:37:16,215
Let's talk about Ted Bundy for a minute, shall we?

641
00:37:16,215 --> 00:37:19,015
What kind of a killer was he?

642
00:37:19,015 --> 00:37:20,934
How was he perceived?

643
00:37:22,614 --> 00:37:26,935
Mr. Lawson wishes to participate. Please, let's hear it.

644
00:37:27,014 --> 00:37:29,294
He was perceived as a very organized killer.

645
00:37:29,413 --> 00:37:31,933
-Very calculated.
-Hmphf!

646
00:37:32,014 --> 00:37:34,215
You don't agree, Miss Newman?

647
00:37:34,215 --> 00:37:36,614
Yes and no.

648
00:37:36,614 --> 00:37:40,934
Come on, this guy planned each and every detail in advance.

649
00:37:41,014 --> 00:37:44,533
He chose his victims with extreme accuracy, stalked them meticulously,

650
00:37:44,614 --> 00:37:46,534
and waited for the precise moment to attack.

651
00:37:46,613 --> 00:37:48,614
All while maintaining an air of patience

652
00:37:48,614 --> 00:37:50,813
not even the FBI's greatest could penetrate.

653
00:37:50,813 --> 00:37:54,532
-No offense, sir.
-None taken.

654
00:37:54,532 --> 00:37:58,812
-But I still don't agree.
-And he picked all his dumping sites

655
00:37:58,812 --> 00:38:00,293
with the outmost caution.

656
00:38:00,412 --> 00:38:02,613
He was unquestionably an organized killer.

657
00:38:02,613 --> 00:38:06,933
-Premeditated, with a capital "P."
-Capital "P"?

658
00:38:07,012 --> 00:38:10,292
It's a letter in the alphabet.

659
00:38:10,412 --> 00:38:11,612
Between "O" and "Q."

660
00:38:15,011 --> 00:38:17,211
You have something to say, Miss Newman?

661
00:38:20,091 --> 00:38:22,012
He started out organized,

662
00:38:22,012 --> 00:38:24,931
but spiraled down late in his so-called career.

663
00:38:24,931 --> 00:38:28,210
He began to keep bodies for days, washing their hair

664
00:38:28,291 --> 00:38:30,812
and even applying makeup before disposing of them.

665
00:38:30,931 --> 00:38:34,290
And he littered the dumping sites with evidence, using the outmost caution.

666
00:38:34,411 --> 00:38:38,690
However, his last victim, and his youngest girl ever,

667
00:38:38,810 --> 00:38:40,410
fell out of his typical victim selection.

668
00:38:40,530 --> 00:38:43,929
She was chosen out of sheer availability.

669
00:38:44,010 --> 00:38:46,210
The sheer need to kill.

670
00:38:46,210 --> 00:38:48,011
He was both,

671
00:38:48,090 --> 00:38:50,610
an organized killer and off-the-charts lunatic.

672
00:38:50,610 --> 00:38:53,409
With a capital "L."

673
00:38:53,530 --> 00:38:56,089
You're right. He was both.

674
00:38:56,210 --> 00:38:59,009
Very impressive, Miss Newman.

675
00:38:59,009 --> 00:39:02,809
Now, Pr. Starkman, how would you classify a killer

676
00:39:02,809 --> 00:39:07,009
whose downward spiral was actually calculated into their grand scheme?

677
00:39:07,009 --> 00:39:10,010
That's a very interesting hypothesis, Miss Newman.

678
00:39:10,010 --> 00:39:13,609
Unfortunately, in this class, we stick to the facts.

679
00:39:13,689 --> 00:39:16,529
And there's no known case-study of that nature.

680
00:39:59,606 --> 00:40:01,806
Keith's little display of brainpower

681
00:40:01,927 --> 00:40:03,526
was totally unacceptable.

682
00:40:03,606 --> 00:40:06,926
It's a day before Starkman announces his new TA.

683
00:40:07,005 --> 00:40:08,606
This could be catastrophic.

684
00:40:08,685 --> 00:40:11,685
I wasn't about to watch years of hard work go down the drain.

685
00:40:11,805 --> 00:40:14,525
It was time to pick Keith's brain.

686
00:40:17,405 --> 00:40:19,285
You know that feeling you get

687
00:40:19,405 --> 00:40:22,525
when you realize that there are people out there just like you?

688
00:40:22,525 --> 00:40:24,605
It almost makes you feel normal.

689
00:40:24,685 --> 00:40:27,525
All this time, I thought he was taking notes.

690
00:40:27,606 --> 00:40:32,004
But no. Look at his work, his sketches.

691
00:40:32,004 --> 00:40:34,803
They're absolutely brilliant.

692
00:40:34,803 --> 00:40:37,085
This may be a waste of a rare mind.

693
00:40:37,203 --> 00:40:39,924
But, a girl's gotta do what a girl's gotta do.

694
00:41:20,002 --> 00:41:22,001
Hi, Professor Starkman.

695
00:41:22,001 --> 00:41:24,002
-Hey!
-Miss Brown.

696
00:41:24,081 --> 00:41:26,001
-How are you?
-Good.

697
00:41:26,082 --> 00:41:29,001
So, the big day's tomorrow, right?

698
00:41:30,001 --> 00:41:32,682
-What do you mean?
-For the TA position.

699
00:41:32,802 --> 00:41:35,521
-You're announcing it tomorrow?
-Yes, of course.

700
00:41:35,602 --> 00:41:40,000
-At noon, in my classroom.
-I can't wait.

701
00:41:40,081 --> 00:41:42,920
My chances are much better this year than they were last.

702
00:41:43,001 --> 00:41:46,281
I would think so. It's a very tight race this year.

703
00:41:46,401 --> 00:41:47,920
Mmm-hmm.

704
00:41:48,000 --> 00:41:52,280
Were you looking for Cassandra? She wasn't in class.

705
00:41:52,400 --> 00:41:53,999
She probably left for Spring Break.

706
00:41:53,999 --> 00:41:59,920
-Well, actually, the--
-It's Cassandra, isn't it?

707
00:42:00,000 --> 00:42:02,000
She got the position.

708
00:42:02,080 --> 00:42:04,680
Good for her, but--

709
00:42:04,799 --> 00:42:07,680
I can't say I'm not disappointed,

710
00:42:07,799 --> 00:42:11,079
but "what doesn't kill you makes you stronger."

711
00:42:13,199 --> 00:42:15,199
I'll see you.

712
00:43:32,396 --> 00:43:34,595
It's Cassandra. I can't get to the phone,

713
00:43:34,675 --> 00:43:36,915
so leave a quickie and I'll get back to you.

714
00:43:51,513 --> 00:43:54,793
-Hello?
-Eric, for God's sakes!

715
00:43:54,793 --> 00:43:55,995
She's dead!

716
00:43:57,394 --> 00:43:59,994
-Who is?
-She is!

717
00:44:00,074 --> 00:44:03,673
The "she" whose name we agreed not to say aloud.

718
00:44:03,793 --> 00:44:06,273
My patient? Dead? How?

719
00:44:06,394 --> 00:44:08,793
She hung herself.

720
00:44:09,793 --> 00:44:11,593
You didn't say she was suicidal.

721
00:44:11,593 --> 00:44:15,072
She had suicidal tendencies,

722
00:44:15,192 --> 00:44:17,072
but I was more concerned for the sociopathic

723
00:44:17,192 --> 00:44:19,073
and homicidal patterns that were emerging.

724
00:44:19,073 --> 00:44:21,512
Spare me your psychobabble bullshit.

725
00:44:21,512 --> 00:44:23,192
This girl...

726
00:44:24,192 --> 00:44:27,792
she may have been a little forward, but she wasn't crazy!

727
00:44:27,912 --> 00:44:30,792
I'm sorry, but you didn't see what I saw.

728
00:44:30,912 --> 00:44:33,791
-She was not a pretty picture.
-Listen, Eric,

729
00:44:33,912 --> 00:44:35,590
I spent a lot of time with her,

730
00:44:35,671 --> 00:44:38,671
and I have to say I don't agree on this one.

731
00:44:38,791 --> 00:44:40,510
There are tons of kids in your classes.

732
00:44:40,591 --> 00:44:43,911
How could you know her as well as you think you did?

733
00:44:43,911 --> 00:44:47,672
We're bound by the guidelines

734
00:44:47,791 --> 00:44:49,670
of doctor-patient privilege, right?

735
00:44:53,990 --> 00:44:57,670
You didn't, Bob? You weren't sleeping with her?

736
00:44:58,791 --> 00:45:01,510
No wonder she was obsessing over you.

737
00:45:01,589 --> 00:45:04,910
-How could you do this to Diane?
-None of your business.

738
00:45:04,989 --> 00:45:08,390
Fine. Why did you call me, then?

739
00:45:08,390 --> 00:45:10,990
‘Cause you're my fucking shrink!

740
00:45:11,070 --> 00:45:14,789
I'm sorry. I just needed someone to talk to.

741
00:45:16,590 --> 00:45:18,189
I loved her.

742
00:45:22,909 --> 00:45:25,269
Can you get me some Valium?

743
00:45:25,388 --> 00:45:29,388
Yeah. I'll call it in to the pharmacy.

744
00:45:29,388 --> 00:45:32,669
Can I give you some advice?

745
00:45:38,269 --> 00:45:39,909
Hello?

746
00:45:49,907 --> 00:45:52,786
So, here we are. The big day.

747
00:45:52,907 --> 00:45:55,788
In moments, I'll be crowned Starkman's new TA,

748
00:45:55,788 --> 00:45:58,988
and be one step closer to the FBI.

749
00:45:59,067 --> 00:46:02,787
Too bad Brian, Cassie and Keith couldn't be here to watch me.

750
00:46:02,787 --> 00:46:04,387
But wherever they are,

751
00:46:04,387 --> 00:46:08,186
I'm sure they'll realize they didn't give up their lives in vain.

752
00:46:08,267 --> 00:46:10,387
I will make them proud.

753
00:46:13,666 --> 00:46:16,505
Guys, can I have your attention, please?

754
00:46:16,586 --> 00:46:19,587
Professor Starkman told me to tell you

755
00:46:19,587 --> 00:46:22,586
that unfortunately he's decided that his sabbatical,

756
00:46:22,666 --> 00:46:24,586
which was scheduled for next year,

757
00:46:24,666 --> 00:46:26,986
is now effective immediately.

758
00:46:27,066 --> 00:46:31,785
In other words, there'll be no TA position for next semester.

759
00:46:31,785 --> 00:46:33,505
Sorry.

760
00:46:33,585 --> 00:46:36,185
Have a great Spring Break.

761
00:46:51,264 --> 00:46:54,504
This is an obsession

762
00:46:54,585 --> 00:46:57,264
A kind of aggression with himself

763
00:46:57,384 --> 00:47:01,183
It's the way he'll always be

764
00:47:01,264 --> 00:47:03,983
He loves to rebel

765
00:47:04,064 --> 00:47:06,584
To go against his Ten Commandments

766
00:47:06,584 --> 00:47:09,184
For him

767
00:47:09,184 --> 00:47:11,584
That's just being free

768
00:47:11,584 --> 00:47:13,982
And over there

769
00:47:14,063 --> 00:47:16,183
Stands my angry angel

770
00:47:16,183 --> 00:47:19,063
And he's shaking his head

771
00:47:19,182 --> 00:47:21,583
In disgrace with me

772
00:47:21,662 --> 00:47:24,061
Over there

773
00:47:24,182 --> 00:47:26,502
Stands my angry angel

774
00:47:26,502 --> 00:47:29,063
And he's frowning like hell

775
00:47:29,183 --> 00:47:31,983
But I'm not feeling guilty.

776
00:47:42,982 --> 00:47:44,902
Professor Starkman?

777
00:47:47,181 --> 00:47:49,061
Professor Starkman?

778
00:47:51,380 --> 00:47:52,981
Rachael.

779
00:47:56,981 --> 00:47:58,381
Why--

780
00:48:00,261 --> 00:48:02,581
why haven't you gone home?

781
00:48:03,780 --> 00:48:06,979
I'll just hang around here during the break.

782
00:48:07,060 --> 00:48:08,060
Why?

783
00:48:09,060 --> 00:48:13,059
Don't you have family waiting at home for you?

784
00:48:13,179 --> 00:48:14,379
No.

785
00:48:14,499 --> 00:48:17,059
Actually, they'll come visit me here.

786
00:48:19,060 --> 00:48:21,580
Are you okay, Professor?

787
00:48:21,659 --> 00:48:24,499
I heard about the change in plans.

788
00:48:28,979 --> 00:48:31,579
Is that why you're here?

789
00:48:31,579 --> 00:48:34,979
Is that all you people ever think about?

790
00:48:35,058 --> 00:48:37,978
The Goddamn teaching assistant job?

791
00:48:39,378 --> 00:48:40,580
Quantico?

792
00:48:40,658 --> 00:48:43,499
Don't you kids get it? It's not that important.

793
00:48:44,658 --> 00:48:46,659
It's important to me.

794
00:48:46,779 --> 00:48:50,177
I have a schedule, a plan, a dream. I need it!

795
00:48:50,258 --> 00:48:52,178
What makes you think you'll get it?

796
00:48:53,978 --> 00:48:56,377
Other students have applied too.

797
00:48:56,497 --> 00:49:00,178
-Some more qualified than you.
-I beg your pardon?

798
00:49:00,256 --> 00:49:03,656
I believe I am the most qualified for this position.

799
00:49:03,777 --> 00:49:06,057
Name someone who's more dedicated or intelligent,

800
00:49:06,177 --> 00:49:07,897
that's had more experience than me.

801
00:49:07,977 --> 00:49:11,177
You don't know what you're talking about.

802
00:49:11,257 --> 00:49:13,496
Go home.

803
00:49:24,976 --> 00:49:28,056
-What are you doing?
-Shh.

804
00:49:28,176 --> 00:49:30,176
Just relax, Bobby.

805
00:49:41,375 --> 00:49:43,255
Where did you get that?

806
00:49:45,655 --> 00:49:47,255
And the dress?

807
00:49:51,494 --> 00:49:54,574
-What's going on here?
-Bobby, what's wrong?

808
00:49:54,574 --> 00:49:56,775
Don't fuck with me.

809
00:49:57,775 --> 00:49:59,574
That necklace...

810
00:49:59,654 --> 00:50:01,574
and Cassandra's dress.

811
00:50:01,654 --> 00:50:03,773
It was a present.

812
00:50:03,894 --> 00:50:06,173
Bobby, don't you remember?

813
00:50:06,254 --> 00:50:08,373
You gave it to me.

814
00:50:09,774 --> 00:50:11,573
Stop it...

815
00:50:11,653 --> 00:50:13,973
this instant!

816
00:50:14,973 --> 00:50:17,374
I said, go home.

817
00:50:18,374 --> 00:50:19,894
I mean it.

818
00:50:22,173 --> 00:50:24,173
I have a confession to make.

819
00:50:24,173 --> 00:50:27,053
I've had feelings for you for a long time,

820
00:50:27,173 --> 00:50:29,772
longer than you can imagine.

821
00:50:30,773 --> 00:50:33,572
I've always wanted something to happen between us.

822
00:50:33,652 --> 00:50:35,772
Something beautiful.

823
00:50:36,891 --> 00:50:38,972
I love you, Bobby.

824
00:50:38,972 --> 00:50:41,973
-What?!
-Please, don't be upset, Bobby.

825
00:50:42,052 --> 00:50:43,892
Stop calling me Bobby!

826
00:50:43,972 --> 00:50:46,971
Okay. I'm a little confused.

827
00:50:47,052 --> 00:50:49,572
You are? How do you think I feel?

828
00:50:50,571 --> 00:50:53,252
Rachael--Ms. Newman...

829
00:50:54,251 --> 00:50:58,171
-this is unacceptable.
-It is?

830
00:50:58,251 --> 00:51:00,171
But it was okay for you and Cassandra?

831
00:51:00,251 --> 00:51:01,771
How did--

832
00:51:01,891 --> 00:51:04,171
I don't know what you're talking about. Leave.

833
00:51:04,251 --> 00:51:06,251
I've always loved you.

834
00:51:06,371 --> 00:51:08,970
Ever since I first saw you.

835
00:51:09,051 --> 00:51:12,170
Before Diane ever loved you. Before Cassandra.

836
00:51:12,170 --> 00:51:15,370
Before Clara even ever loved you. It was always me.

837
00:51:15,490 --> 00:51:17,170
Don't you get it?

838
00:51:17,250 --> 00:51:19,251
How did you know about Clara?

839
00:51:19,369 --> 00:51:21,569
That was six years ago.

840
00:51:21,569 --> 00:51:23,049
I was there, Bobby.

841
00:51:23,170 --> 00:51:26,168
-Clara was babysitting me that night. -Clara.

842
00:51:26,168 --> 00:51:29,169
He's here! Do something.

843
00:51:29,169 --> 00:51:31,769
I was in Bateman's apartment.

844
00:51:31,769 --> 00:51:34,369
Clara used to babysit me all the time.

845
00:51:34,489 --> 00:51:36,649
She'd tell me about your relationship with her.

846
00:51:36,769 --> 00:51:38,570
She'd show me pictures of you.

847
00:51:38,648 --> 00:51:41,568
You were my first crush.

848
00:51:41,649 --> 00:51:44,649
You were in Patrick Bateman's apartment

849
00:51:44,769 --> 00:51:46,968
the night he killed Clara?

850
00:51:49,368 --> 00:51:50,568
Yeah.

851
00:51:53,169 --> 00:51:56,248
I know you quit the FBI because of what happened.

852
00:51:56,368 --> 00:51:59,169
I think you blame yourself for her death.

853
00:51:59,248 --> 00:52:02,247
Bobby, all work, no play.

854
00:52:02,368 --> 00:52:04,567
-You want to play?
-Uh-huh.

855
00:52:04,567 --> 00:52:05,647
Okay.

856
00:52:05,767 --> 00:52:09,167
She was the one who looked through your stuff and found Bateman's file.

857
00:52:09,167 --> 00:52:10,888
She's tracked him down.

858
00:52:10,966 --> 00:52:13,767
And she went to his apartment that night and dragged me along.

859
00:52:13,887 --> 00:52:17,247
Rich and good-looking. Why are we together again?

860
00:52:17,367 --> 00:52:19,048
You shouldn't blame yourself.

861
00:52:19,048 --> 00:52:21,566
She went over there to cheat on you.

862
00:52:21,647 --> 00:52:23,887
-She was a slut.
-Shut up!

863
00:52:23,967 --> 00:52:26,967
It's the truth. She got what she deserved.

864
00:52:27,046 --> 00:52:32,486
And so did Cassandra. She thought you didn't love her enough.

865
00:52:32,566 --> 00:52:35,045
It's my turn now. I've waited six years.

866
00:52:35,045 --> 00:52:38,765
I won't let anyone stop me, not even Diane and your baby.

867
00:52:38,886 --> 00:52:41,166
Don't you threaten my family.

868
00:52:41,166 --> 00:52:43,886
So now you care about your family?

869
00:52:46,765 --> 00:52:49,365
You just can't hold a relationship together.

870
00:52:49,365 --> 00:52:51,885
-Please.
-You think you're a catch.

871
00:52:51,885 --> 00:52:54,885
But you're just the opportunity of a lifetime.

872
00:52:54,964 --> 00:52:57,484
-Stop.
-After you can't break any more hearts,

873
00:52:57,564 --> 00:53:01,564
you'll still break one more...your baby daughter's.

874
00:53:01,644 --> 00:53:04,565
Please, no more.

875
00:53:14,164 --> 00:53:15,964
Goodbye, Bobby.

876
00:53:16,044 --> 00:53:20,363
The sun is shining

877
00:53:20,363 --> 00:53:24,883
We should be making haste

878
00:53:24,963 --> 00:53:27,484
I hope you had a safe trip.

879
00:53:35,243 --> 00:53:38,243
Hey, nice mop!

880
00:53:44,961 --> 00:53:46,962
Sweet dreams.

881
00:53:50,963 --> 00:53:55,762
We are sleeping on our feet

882
00:53:55,762 --> 00:53:59,162
We stole the songs from birds in trees

883
00:53:59,162 --> 00:54:01,561
But it's time on easy street

884
00:54:01,642 --> 00:54:06,041
Now it's past, and it's not me.

885
00:54:08,041 --> 00:54:09,760
Hey!

886
00:54:10,760 --> 00:54:12,560
Hey, stop!

887
00:54:15,361 --> 00:54:18,561
Yeah, that's it. Bring it back.

888
00:54:18,640 --> 00:54:21,241
Yeah, bring it--yeah.

889
00:54:21,360 --> 00:54:24,159
Back it up. That's it. You got it.

890
00:54:24,159 --> 00:54:27,041
Bring it in here. Thank you very much.

891
00:54:27,160 --> 00:54:30,160
Driving around like goddamn maniacs.

892
00:54:30,240 --> 00:54:33,560
That's good. Perfect. Thank you very much.

893
00:54:33,639 --> 00:54:35,879
I sure do hope you've got--

894
00:54:37,639 --> 00:54:39,879
Holy shit.

895
00:54:39,879 --> 00:54:41,880
(car door closes)

896
00:54:42,879 --> 00:54:45,879
-What the hell's going on?
-Oh, that?

897
00:54:45,959 --> 00:54:48,759
That's Professor Starkman. He's out of it tonight.

898
00:55:01,638 --> 00:55:05,558
You've reached Professor Starkman, in the Behavioral Sciences Department.

899
00:55:05,639 --> 00:55:07,239
Please, leave a message.

900
00:55:07,357 --> 00:55:08,957
Hey, Bobby, it's Eric.

901
00:55:09,038 --> 00:55:11,957
I felt bad about the other day. I wanted to say I'm sorry.

902
00:55:12,038 --> 00:55:14,958
I hope you got that prescription filled okay.

903
00:55:15,037 --> 00:55:18,237
Call me if you need anything. Bye.

904
00:55:23,757 --> 00:55:27,357
-Dr. Daniels' office.
-Mary, if that's Bobby Starkman,

905
00:55:27,477 --> 00:55:30,757
-I'll take it.
-He'll take you at 3:00. All right.

906
00:55:33,876 --> 00:55:36,476
It was for an appointment, not the professor.

907
00:55:36,556 --> 00:55:38,156
Okay.

908
00:55:38,236 --> 00:55:40,637
I put her in at 3:00, Rachael Newman.

909
00:55:40,755 --> 00:55:42,556
She wanted to come in today.

910
00:55:44,755 --> 00:55:46,355
What?

911
00:55:48,155 --> 00:55:49,756
Rachael Newman? Are you sure?

912
00:55:49,876 --> 00:55:52,635
Yeah. Are you okay?

913
00:55:56,635 --> 00:55:58,755
I can reschedule if you want.

914
00:55:58,875 --> 00:56:00,354
I'm--

915
00:56:01,635 --> 00:56:04,475
no, I'm--I'm fine.

916
00:56:04,554 --> 00:56:07,554
It's just--it's been a long day.

917
00:56:07,554 --> 00:56:10,355
-Let me know if you need anything.
-Sure.

918
00:56:12,233 --> 00:56:13,755
Bye.

919
00:56:13,874 --> 00:56:15,875
Bye, Mary.

920
00:56:28,553 --> 00:56:31,033
Come on.

921
00:56:31,153 --> 00:56:35,032
You've reached Professor Starkman in the Behavioral Sciences Department.

922
00:56:35,153 --> 00:56:36,872
Please, leave a message.

923
00:56:36,952 --> 00:56:40,154
It's Eric again. Call me when you get this.

924
00:56:40,233 --> 00:56:42,033
I'm really confused about something.

925
00:56:42,154 --> 00:56:44,152
If you don't reach me by 3:00,

926
00:56:44,233 --> 00:56:47,033
I'll drop by your office between 4:00 and 4:30.

927
00:56:47,153 --> 00:56:48,752
Bye.

928
00:57:07,351 --> 00:57:10,551
-Hi, honey!
-Mom!

929
00:57:10,631 --> 00:57:12,751
-Dad?
-We made it!

930
00:57:12,872 --> 00:57:15,231
Hello, princess.

931
00:57:15,231 --> 00:57:17,550
Won't you invite us in?

932
00:57:18,751 --> 00:57:21,031
Jeez, I'm sorry. Please, come in.

933
00:57:21,150 --> 00:57:23,230
Wow! Hi, happy birthday!

934
00:57:23,351 --> 00:57:25,551
Thank you, sweetie.

935
00:57:25,631 --> 00:57:28,151
We've been planning this for months.

936
00:57:29,151 --> 00:57:32,549
Sweet Jesus! It smells like somebody died in here.

937
00:57:32,549 --> 00:57:36,150
The toilet's clogged up and maintenance isn't up and running,

938
00:57:36,150 --> 00:57:39,350
-so there's nothing I can do.
-That's wretched.

939
00:57:39,350 --> 00:57:43,229
Sweetheart, you are such a clothes-horse.

940
00:57:43,349 --> 00:57:46,749
-What will I do with you?
-Don't open the closet.

941
00:57:46,869 --> 00:57:51,030
-our present's in there.
-Oh, I'm sorry, sweetie.

942
00:57:51,150 --> 00:57:54,629
Look at me, always spoiling the surprise.

943
00:57:54,749 --> 00:57:56,629
What will we eat? I'm hungry.

944
00:57:56,629 --> 00:57:59,869
Good. I made reservations for 5:30.

945
00:57:59,869 --> 00:58:02,149
I'm going out of town later tonight.

946
00:58:02,149 --> 00:58:04,748
Is this restaurant reasonably priced?

947
00:58:04,868 --> 00:58:05,947
Yes.

948
00:58:05,947 --> 00:58:08,148
Is there an early bird special?

949
00:58:09,148 --> 00:58:11,867
-I don't think so.
-That's too bad.

950
00:58:11,948 --> 00:58:14,228
-What's it called?
-Chez Gerard's.

951
00:58:14,348 --> 00:58:18,468
Is that Italian? our father cannot digest Italian food.

952
00:58:18,548 --> 00:58:21,347
-It's too spicy.
-Mother, it's French.

953
00:58:21,468 --> 00:58:23,348
French!

954
00:58:24,946 --> 00:58:27,347
-How sophisticated!
-Yeah, okay.

955
00:58:27,347 --> 00:58:30,227
I've got to finish packing and finish writing some papers.

956
00:58:30,227 --> 00:58:32,027
So why don't you go back to the motel

957
00:58:32,146 --> 00:58:34,467
and we'll meet at the restaurant at 5:30?

958
00:58:34,467 --> 00:58:37,347
Sounds good to me. I've got to use the head.

959
00:58:37,467 --> 00:58:39,228
Get maintenance up here.

960
00:58:39,228 --> 00:58:41,147
Daddy, I called.

961
00:58:41,147 --> 00:58:43,747
How will we ever find this place?

962
00:58:43,866 --> 00:58:46,746
We'll be back at 5:15 to pick you up.

963
00:58:46,746 --> 00:58:48,946
-Okay.
-Bye, princess.

964
00:58:48,946 --> 00:58:51,346
I love you, guys.

965
00:59:23,024 --> 00:59:25,344
-You've reached Professor Starkman

966
00:59:25,344 --> 00:59:27,544
in the Behavioral Sciences Department.

967
00:59:27,625 --> 00:59:29,545
Please, leave a message.

968
00:59:29,624 --> 00:59:33,545
Bobby, it's Eric. I know you're going through tough times,

969
00:59:33,623 --> 00:59:36,943
but she--the she who hung herself--

970
00:59:36,943 --> 00:59:40,143
she made an appointment to see me. I don't know if it's a joke,

971
00:59:40,143 --> 00:59:42,943
but something's off. Call me, all right?

972
00:59:46,022 --> 00:59:48,544
Roses are red, violets are blue,

973
00:59:48,544 --> 00:59:52,143
the Daniels will soon be calling back you.

974
00:59:52,223 --> 00:59:54,343
Mom, you've got to change that message.

975
00:59:54,464 --> 00:59:57,743
I'll come by around 5:30 to pick you up for our big date.

976
00:59:57,743 --> 01:00:01,142
And I'll get you back in time for Murder She Wrote. Bye.

977
01:00:12,143 --> 01:00:15,221
-Bon appetit.
-Happy birthday, Mom.

978
01:00:15,342 --> 01:00:19,941
Oh, it's gorgeous.

979
01:00:20,942 --> 01:00:23,541
This is the most beautiful thing

980
01:00:23,621 --> 01:00:27,141
I have ever received in my life. How did you afford it?

981
01:00:27,221 --> 01:00:32,860
-Stainless steel.
-It's silver, you old lump.

982
01:00:32,940 --> 01:00:35,340
Stainless steel. Silver has...

983
01:00:35,340 --> 01:00:38,220
that distinguished look about it.

984
01:00:38,220 --> 01:00:42,020
Anyway, as I was saying before,

985
01:00:42,141 --> 01:00:45,939
I said to Leora she ought to have it looked at immediately.

986
01:00:45,939 --> 01:00:50,139
So what does she do? She waits an entire month.

987
01:00:50,139 --> 01:00:52,019
And when she sees the doctor,

988
01:00:52,139 --> 01:00:55,620
he orders a biopsy and it comes back positive.

989
01:00:55,738 --> 01:00:58,219
Well, could you just die?

990
01:00:58,338 --> 01:01:00,619
If she had taken my advice,

991
01:01:00,739 --> 01:01:02,619
she could have avoided this mess!

992
01:01:02,739 --> 01:01:05,739
I know we'll eat dinner at some point.

993
01:01:05,858 --> 01:01:09,939
-The question is, when?
-I'll go use the restroom.

994
01:01:10,019 --> 01:01:11,858
Don't forget to wash your hands.

995
01:01:14,017 --> 01:01:16,337
Now, where is my steak knife?

996
01:01:16,458 --> 01:01:18,218
My mother drives me crazy.

997
01:01:18,338 --> 01:01:21,858
That sounds cliché, but how many people envision

998
01:01:21,937 --> 01:01:24,938
carving into their mother's neck and yanking out her vocal cords?

999
01:01:24,938 --> 01:01:28,938
Or ripping her tongue out and serving it to her as an early-bird special?

1000
01:01:28,938 --> 01:01:32,138
-Bonsoir.
-Bonsoir. Daniels. Table for two.

1001
01:01:32,138 --> 01:01:34,337
I've got a table right here for you.

1002
01:01:34,457 --> 01:01:35,737
After you.

1003
01:01:38,857 --> 01:01:40,856
Why don't you sit on the other side?

1004
01:01:40,937 --> 01:01:42,737
Get a view of the whole thing.

1005
01:01:43,856 --> 01:01:46,336
Excusez-moi, garcon.

1006
01:01:46,456 --> 01:01:48,537
Could I have un autre, uh...

1007
01:01:48,618 --> 01:01:50,617
steak knife, s'il-vous-plait?

1008
01:01:50,737 --> 01:01:52,136
Oh.

1009
01:01:52,217 --> 01:01:54,936
-Of course. Voila, madame.
-Merci.

1010
01:01:54,936 --> 01:01:56,856
How about a table closer to the window?

1011
01:01:56,936 --> 01:01:59,936
-That would be very nice.
-Okay, I'll ask.

1012
01:02:01,016 --> 01:02:02,535
-Good evening.
-Good evening.

1013
01:02:02,535 --> 01:02:06,455
I was wondering if we could get a table closer to the window.

1014
01:02:06,535 --> 01:02:08,855
That section is closed for Spring Break.

1015
01:02:08,935 --> 01:02:10,535
Sorry.

1016
01:02:12,536 --> 01:02:15,535
No problem. I understand. This table is fine.

1017
01:02:15,615 --> 01:02:18,735
Good. Can I get you something to drink?

1018
01:02:18,735 --> 01:02:20,855
I'll have a whiskey sour. Mom?

1019
01:02:20,935 --> 01:02:24,335
I'll need some water to take my pills.

1020
01:02:26,935 --> 01:02:28,614
As I stare at myself in the mirror,

1021
01:02:28,734 --> 01:02:31,854
I realize I can't let my mother get the best of me.

1022
01:02:31,854 --> 01:02:33,853
I'm Robert Starkman's next TA.

1023
01:02:33,934 --> 01:02:35,934
And that's where I'll focus my energies.

1024
01:02:35,934 --> 01:02:38,734
I should set up a meeting with Bobby when I get back.

1025
01:02:38,734 --> 01:02:41,335
Maybe we can brainstorm at his cabin tonight.

1026
01:02:41,453 --> 01:02:44,013
I'll make him my special eggs.

1027
01:02:49,612 --> 01:02:50,932
Sorry.

1028
01:02:50,932 --> 01:02:52,933
Ready to order?

1029
01:02:54,132 --> 01:02:56,933
Maybe you'd give us some more time?

1030
01:02:57,012 --> 01:02:59,213
Sure. Of course.

1031
01:02:59,334 --> 01:03:01,133
I'll be just over there.

1032
01:03:01,133 --> 01:03:03,333
-Take your time.
-Thank you.

1033
01:03:05,012 --> 01:03:07,932
-Cheers.
-Cheers, my dear.

1034
01:03:11,212 --> 01:03:12,451
Oh my God.

1035
01:03:17,332 --> 01:03:21,011
Hello, Dr. Daniels. It's great to see you.

1036
01:03:23,852 --> 01:03:26,131
And this must be your mother.

1037
01:03:26,211 --> 01:03:28,732
Hello, Mrs. Daniels. How are you doing?

1038
01:03:28,851 --> 01:03:30,612
I'm fine, dear.

1039
01:03:30,731 --> 01:03:32,931
Oh my God.

1040
01:03:33,011 --> 01:03:35,531
I just love that hat.

1041
01:03:35,531 --> 01:03:37,611
I'd kill for a hat like that.

1042
01:03:37,731 --> 01:03:40,010
It is just so cute!

1043
01:03:41,330 --> 01:03:44,131
I have to be getting back to my table.

1044
01:03:44,209 --> 01:03:47,731
-It was great meeting you.
-It was nice meeting you too.

1045
01:03:50,530 --> 01:03:52,530
See you later, Eric.

1046
01:03:58,130 --> 01:04:01,330
Who is that pretty girl? A new girlfriend, I hope.

1047
01:04:01,330 --> 01:04:03,528
No.

1048
01:04:03,609 --> 01:04:05,729
She's a patient.

1049
01:04:05,849 --> 01:04:08,449
A very sick patient.

1050
01:04:09,448 --> 01:04:11,209
-Excuse me for a second.
-Of course.

1051
01:04:11,329 --> 01:04:13,129
-I'll be right back.
-Yes.

1052
01:04:18,928 --> 01:04:21,129
Excuse me. Sorry to interrupt your dinner.

1053
01:04:21,209 --> 01:04:24,329
I'm a friend of your daughter's. Ms. Newman,

1054
01:04:24,447 --> 01:04:26,728
could I have a word with you for a moment?

1055
01:04:26,728 --> 01:04:28,928
Sure.

1056
01:04:28,928 --> 01:04:31,928
Mom, Dad, I'll be just a minute.

1057
01:04:33,128 --> 01:04:35,128
Excuse me.

1058
01:04:36,128 --> 01:04:37,527
That's it. I'm eating.

1059
01:04:38,608 --> 01:04:40,447
Didn't he call her a different name?

1060
01:04:43,328 --> 01:04:45,727
You have some explaining to do.

1061
01:04:45,727 --> 01:04:47,928
First of all, you insult me.

1062
01:04:47,928 --> 01:04:50,726
Then you threaten my mother. You're seeing a married man.

1063
01:04:50,847 --> 01:04:54,926
Then I hear you've hung yourself. And you act like nothing happened.

1064
01:04:55,006 --> 01:04:57,525
-What's going on?
-You heard I hung myself?

1065
01:04:57,606 --> 01:04:58,527
Yes.

1066
01:04:58,606 --> 01:05:01,007
Eric, why would you say that?

1067
01:05:01,126 --> 01:05:04,006
Let's say a mutual friend told me he found you.

1068
01:05:04,127 --> 01:05:06,605
Dead.

1069
01:05:06,726 --> 01:05:11,845
-Is this some sort of sick joke?
-He never found me. He found her.

1070
01:05:13,525 --> 01:05:15,325
Her who?

1071
01:05:16,605 --> 01:05:20,124
It doesn't even matter anymore. It's not important.

1072
01:05:20,205 --> 01:05:23,325
What's important is my mom's birthday, and she's here.

1073
01:05:23,446 --> 01:05:26,445
I'll catch up with you later. Goodbye.

1074
01:05:32,325 --> 01:05:34,845
Honey, why did he call you Ms. Newman?

1075
01:05:34,924 --> 01:05:36,723
I don't know. Could we just eat?

1076
01:05:36,844 --> 01:05:39,844
-I have to go home and pack.
-Can't you cancel?

1077
01:05:39,924 --> 01:05:42,204
We never get a chance to see you.

1078
01:05:42,323 --> 01:05:44,323
I wish I could, but I can't.

1079
01:05:44,323 --> 01:05:47,724
-They're very special plans.
-A boy?

1080
01:05:49,324 --> 01:05:52,923
-Yes, it's a boy.
-What's his name?

1081
01:05:52,923 --> 01:05:54,924
Bobby Starkman.

1082
01:06:10,523 --> 01:06:12,323
Bobby?

1083
01:07:05,920 --> 01:07:08,919
-Hey, Jim.
-Dr. Daniels.

1084
01:07:08,999 --> 01:07:11,520
A cup of apricot-peppermint blend?

1085
01:07:11,520 --> 01:07:13,999
Thank. We might have a bit of trouble.

1086
01:07:14,119 --> 01:07:17,198
-Is Harv in?
-He's in the back.

1087
01:07:17,319 --> 01:07:19,838
If it's not Sigmund Freud himself!

1088
01:07:19,838 --> 01:07:21,600
-What's the good word?
-Not much.

1089
01:07:21,719 --> 01:07:24,319
I want to file a missing person's report on Robert Starkman.

1090
01:07:24,319 --> 01:07:26,519
-You're kidding?
-I wish I were.

1091
01:07:26,599 --> 01:07:30,118
His wife called 20 minutes ago to do the same thing.

1092
01:07:30,118 --> 01:07:33,518
He didn't show up at his in-laws' upstate like he was supposed to.

1093
01:07:33,598 --> 01:07:35,917
-You're kidding?
-I wish I were.

1094
01:07:35,998 --> 01:07:38,518
-It's been a crazy year.
-What do you mean?

1095
01:07:38,518 --> 01:07:41,918
It's the third MPR we've filed this year. Right, Jimmy?

1096
01:07:41,918 --> 01:07:44,517
-That's a record around here.
-Who else was there?

1097
01:07:44,599 --> 01:07:46,317
Let's have a look.

1098
01:07:49,717 --> 01:07:52,598
I've got a brand new one here. A woman, Gerty Fleck,

1099
01:07:52,717 --> 01:07:55,917
from Student Services. Just up and disappeared.

1100
01:07:55,917 --> 01:07:58,516
And of course, that Newman girl.

1101
01:08:01,116 --> 01:08:03,596
A student, Rachael Newman, disappeared.

1102
01:08:03,717 --> 01:08:05,517
The first day of the semester.

1103
01:08:05,517 --> 01:08:08,196
Jimmy and I toddled up on campus to check it out.

1104
01:08:08,315 --> 01:08:10,117
And guess what?

1105
01:08:10,117 --> 01:08:13,916
I'm Sheriff Winslow, and this is Deputy Duncan.

1106
01:08:13,997 --> 01:08:16,196
Just looking for a--

1107
01:08:16,316 --> 01:08:20,196
-Are you Rachael Newman?
-Yeah. What's wrong?

1108
01:08:20,315 --> 01:08:24,116
We're checking on a MPR on yourself.

1109
01:08:24,116 --> 01:08:26,436
You're not missing, are you?

1110
01:08:26,514 --> 01:08:28,914
No, I'm okay.

1111
01:08:28,914 --> 01:08:30,834
She was there, unharmed.

1112
01:08:32,435 --> 01:08:34,715
Are you sure I can't offer you some tea?

1113
01:08:34,835 --> 01:08:36,515
No, thanks, Jim.

1114
01:08:36,515 --> 01:08:38,594
I actually know this Rachael Newman girl.

1115
01:08:38,714 --> 01:08:40,594
To be honest, I don't trust her.

1116
01:08:41,835 --> 01:08:44,995
Are you telling me the parents just dropped the report?

1117
01:08:45,114 --> 01:08:47,114
I never said nothing about parents.

1118
01:08:47,193 --> 01:08:49,514
The Newman girl, she was an orphan.

1119
01:08:49,594 --> 01:08:51,914
The report was filed by some student friends of hers.

1120
01:08:51,994 --> 01:08:54,593
-But it was a false alarm.
-How do you know it was her?

1121
01:08:54,713 --> 01:08:58,913
There's only one Rachael Newman registered at school.

1122
01:09:01,434 --> 01:09:04,314
Can I convince you guys to come to the campus with me

1123
01:09:04,434 --> 01:09:06,913
to make sure everything's okay?

1124
01:09:06,913 --> 01:09:09,513
Yeah, no problem, Doc.

1125
01:09:13,113 --> 01:09:15,713
-Should I get in here?
-That's fine.

1126
01:09:23,192 --> 01:09:26,912
You're reached Professor Starkman in the Behavioral Sciences Department.

1127
01:09:26,993 --> 01:09:29,112
Please, leave a message.

1128
01:09:29,112 --> 01:09:31,431
Hey, it's me. I'm almost done packing.

1129
01:09:31,512 --> 01:09:34,911
I'll be there soon. I hope you're as excited as I am.

1130
01:09:34,991 --> 01:09:36,831
If you need me to go to the store,

1131
01:09:36,911 --> 01:09:40,190
I'll be here another five minutes. Otherwise, see you soon.

1132
01:09:40,311 --> 01:09:42,911
I love you. Bye.

1133
01:09:51,512 --> 01:09:53,510
God, you stink.

1134
01:09:56,310 --> 01:09:58,510
Now, how did you get open?

1135
01:09:58,510 --> 01:10:00,710
Trying to sneak out on me?

1136
01:10:00,710 --> 01:10:03,989
I just brought you up and you're already causing problems.

1137
01:10:07,509 --> 01:10:10,430
Don't fall apart on me now, Rach.

1138
01:10:13,190 --> 01:10:15,990
Wow! I like your room.

1139
01:10:16,109 --> 01:10:17,710
Actually,

1140
01:10:17,710 --> 01:10:19,709
I like your name too.

1141
01:10:19,709 --> 01:10:21,709
Rachael.

1142
01:10:21,709 --> 01:10:23,988
You don't mind if I borrow it?

1143
01:10:24,109 --> 01:10:27,588
Well, this is a wild-goose chase, I guess.

1144
01:10:27,709 --> 01:10:31,308
-Have a good day.
-You too. Thank you, Officers.

1145
01:10:34,829 --> 01:10:37,708
Hey, Mom, I know I've been out of touch,

1146
01:10:37,829 --> 01:10:39,589
but I got accepted to West Washington.

1147
01:10:39,708 --> 01:10:42,188
I know. Can you believe it?

1148
01:10:42,308 --> 01:10:44,428
It's so sad about your parents.

1149
01:10:44,509 --> 01:10:47,707
That car accident thing and all. So tragic.

1150
01:10:47,827 --> 01:10:50,308
Must have been hard growing up an orphan.

1151
01:10:50,428 --> 01:10:53,907
But, I'm glad you shared it with me.

1152
01:11:10,106 --> 01:11:12,106
Oh, Bobby.

1153
01:11:12,106 --> 01:11:14,907
I told you to get your beauty sleep.

1154
01:11:14,907 --> 01:11:17,186
We have a long night ahead of us.

1155
01:11:21,106 --> 01:11:23,586
You're disgusting.

1156
01:11:29,425 --> 01:11:33,425
So, I'm two cans of gas and a brick away from Quantico.

1157
01:11:33,425 --> 01:11:37,425
I just have to dot the Is and cross the Ts, and I'm home free.

1158
01:11:39,184 --> 01:11:40,905
Look out!

1159
01:11:40,905 --> 01:11:44,424
-Jesus!
-That was the Newman girl!

1160
01:11:44,505 --> 01:11:46,504
We're on the move! Hang on!

1161
01:11:54,504 --> 01:11:56,505
Not now, Bobby.

1162
01:11:56,583 --> 01:11:58,584
Wait till we get to the cabin.

1163
01:11:58,704 --> 01:12:01,704
I'll make you a fire. I'll heat you up real good.

1164
01:12:08,824 --> 01:12:11,184
This qualifies as breaking the speed limit.

1165
01:12:11,184 --> 01:12:12,903
-Don't you think?
-Doing?

1166
01:12:12,984 --> 01:12:14,583
60...

1167
01:12:14,703 --> 01:12:16,703
-in a 35.
-Yeah.

1168
01:12:33,702 --> 01:12:36,703
She's coming up on Old Mill Bend. She'll slow down for the curve.

1169
01:12:36,822 --> 01:12:38,702
-We'll take her there.
-Take it easy.

1170
01:12:38,702 --> 01:12:41,582
-We don't want anyone getting hurt.
-It's all under control.

1171
01:12:41,701 --> 01:12:43,902
That's 275 bucks.

1172
01:12:43,981 --> 01:12:46,822
-Can you pull up next to her?
-Yeah, for a bit.

1173
01:13:02,181 --> 01:13:03,301
Jesus!

1174
01:13:07,700 --> 01:13:10,900
-Can you do something?
-Yeah. Take the wheel.

1175
01:13:22,420 --> 01:13:25,300
She's slowing down. That did the trick.

1176
01:13:34,098 --> 01:13:35,579
Doc, you stay here.

1177
01:13:35,698 --> 01:13:38,098
Just be careful. She's a loose cannon.

1178
01:13:38,179 --> 01:13:40,178
It's all part of the job, right?

1179
01:13:57,498 --> 01:13:59,178
Ma'am.

1180
01:14:01,097 --> 01:14:02,977
Ma'am, open the door.

1181
01:14:04,177 --> 01:14:05,177
Come on!

1182
01:14:06,897 --> 01:14:10,298
Come on, guys. Don't let her get away!

1183
01:14:27,176 --> 01:14:29,695
This don't look good.

1184
01:14:38,495 --> 01:14:40,095
Jesus.

1185
01:14:41,815 --> 01:14:44,895
-What the hell?
-Don't let it be Bobby.

1186
01:14:44,895 --> 01:14:46,575
Christ!

1187
01:14:47,974 --> 01:14:50,094
Bobby.

1188
01:14:50,094 --> 01:14:51,495
How the hell...

1189
01:14:52,894 --> 01:14:54,815
Starkman.

1190
01:14:54,895 --> 01:14:57,895
Where the heck is our lady friend?

1191
01:15:05,574 --> 01:15:06,974
Come on.

1192
01:15:07,094 --> 01:15:08,893
Bobby.

1193
01:15:19,294 --> 01:15:20,573
Jesus!

1194
01:15:20,693 --> 01:15:22,173
Bobby.

1195
01:15:29,973 --> 01:15:33,292
A bizarre killing spree came to an end last night

1196
01:15:33,292 --> 01:15:36,972
when 18-year-old West Washington student Rachael Newman, now identified...

1197
01:15:37,092 --> 01:15:39,691
Rachael Newman's killing spree is believed to have begun

1198
01:15:39,812 --> 01:15:41,893
Wednesday evening with the murder of Gertrude Fleck...

1199
01:15:41,893 --> 01:15:43,813
The body of Cassandra Blair was found

1200
01:15:43,892 --> 01:15:46,292
-hanging in her...
-Brian Leeds' body,

1201
01:15:46,292 --> 01:15:50,292
-from the Leeds family...
-Keith Lawson was...

1202
01:15:50,292 --> 01:15:52,692
The bodies of a West Washington security guards

1203
01:15:52,812 --> 01:15:56,291
-were found within hours...
-Once a typical girl,

1204
01:15:56,291 --> 01:15:59,290
Rachael Newman's death leaves many questions unanswered.

1205
01:15:59,411 --> 01:16:02,410
The most burning question of all: Why?

1206
01:16:10,491 --> 01:16:12,411
As a case-study,

1207
01:16:12,490 --> 01:16:15,170
Rachael Newman was as rare as they come.

1208
01:16:15,290 --> 01:16:17,690
She was more obsessed than Dahmer,

1209
01:16:17,810 --> 01:16:19,690
she was more calculating than Bundy,

1210
01:16:19,690 --> 01:16:21,890
and certainly more faceless than Bateman.

1211
01:16:23,290 --> 01:16:26,690
In a perfect world, she'd still be alive.

1212
01:16:27,808 --> 01:16:30,170
But for her, it all ended...

1213
01:16:30,290 --> 01:16:32,170
in a blaze of fire

1214
01:16:32,291 --> 01:16:34,810
in which she and her final victim,

1215
01:16:34,890 --> 01:16:37,969
a friend of mine, Robert Starkman--

1216
01:16:38,969 --> 01:16:40,568
they burned to death.

1217
01:16:41,888 --> 01:16:45,289
I wish I had a chance to study her mind more,

1218
01:16:45,289 --> 01:16:48,888
but all we ended up with were dental records.

1219
01:16:48,969 --> 01:16:51,889
All in all, she killed eight people.

1220
01:16:51,967 --> 01:16:54,409
Eight people which we know of.

1221
01:16:55,408 --> 01:16:58,688
Rachael Newman is one in a billion.

1222
01:16:58,688 --> 01:17:01,088
One in a billion.

1223
01:17:02,168 --> 01:17:04,407
She's in a league of her own.

1224
01:17:05,408 --> 01:17:08,568
But she will remain a constant and strong reminder

1225
01:17:08,568 --> 01:17:11,168
that people aren't always what they seem to be.

1226
01:17:14,287 --> 01:17:16,688
Thanks for taking the time to come out.

1227
01:17:28,886 --> 01:17:31,286
-Thank you for coming, Doctor.
-It's a pleasure.

1228
01:17:31,406 --> 01:17:34,286
-Who should I make it out to?
-Louis Okon.

1229
01:17:35,566 --> 01:17:37,405
-Here you go.
-Thank you.

1230
01:17:38,486 --> 01:17:41,086
-Can I have a different pen?
-Here you go.

1231
01:17:42,086 --> 01:17:45,486
-Who should I make it out to?
-Elizabeth...

1232
01:17:47,166 --> 01:17:50,686
-Elizabeth McGuire.
-McGuire.

1233
01:17:56,284 --> 01:17:58,484
our work is so inspiring.

1234
01:17:58,565 --> 01:18:00,964
It's a huge honor to meet you.

1235
01:18:01,084 --> 01:18:04,084
If you could be anyone in the world,

1236
01:18:04,165 --> 01:18:06,485
-who would that be?
-Elizabeth McGuire,

1237
01:18:06,565 --> 01:18:09,884
Professor Starkman's present TA, and the next in line for Quantico.

1238
01:18:11,484 --> 01:18:15,484
-You can't be?
-What, Eric?

1239
01:18:15,484 --> 01:18:17,164
One in a billion?

1240
01:18:23,164 --> 01:18:25,283
Hello, Dr. Daniels--

1241
01:18:25,283 --> 01:18:28,483
-Do you know that girl?
-Who?

1242
01:18:28,483 --> 01:18:32,284
-Elizabeth McGuire.
-You mean, Agent McGuire.

1243
01:18:32,284 --> 01:18:34,683
She's the first Quantico student in history

1244
01:18:34,803 --> 01:18:37,564
to be drafted into the Bureau in her sophomore year.

1245
01:18:45,682 --> 01:18:48,081
Are you all right, Doctor?

1246
01:18:55,962 --> 01:18:57,561
It's like they say...

1247
01:18:57,682 --> 01:19:01,082
"The brightest futures are based on forgotten pasts."

1248
01:19:01,082 --> 01:19:04,282
In the end, I did put Dr. Daniels in a bit of a pickle.

1249
01:19:04,282 --> 01:19:06,480
But you've got to give to take.

1250
01:19:06,480 --> 01:19:11,481
He gets his national best-seller, which is ever so flawed...

1251
01:19:11,481 --> 01:19:15,680
I wonder how he sleeps at night, knowing I still walk the streets.

1252
01:19:15,680 --> 01:19:16,880
Me?

1253
01:19:16,961 --> 01:19:18,960
I need for him to know.

1254
01:19:19,081 --> 01:19:22,401
What's the point of pulling off the perfect set of murders,

1255
01:19:22,480 --> 01:19:26,281
to realize my dream, if there isn't someone alive who knows?

1256
01:19:27,800 --> 01:19:31,399
It would be as if I'd done nothing at all.

