Make it rain
I'm gonna make you rain, rain
MR. 305, second remix
Hold up, these platinum chains, diamonds and rings, I want some more of
Got me some froze up
If you are my love
You'd better do me like you'd never did before
Make it rain down till the
If you want me, gimme more
Then you stop teasing
No kisses, please in
Swear me if I could drown
Cause baby I'm hot
Everyone can make this rain drop
Don't stop
Girl be my water
Ain't nobody hotter
Go make it rain
I, I, I, I'm gonna make you rain, rain
You do it better
I'm gonna make you wetter
I'm gonna make you great
I, I, I, I'm gonna make you rain, rain
I'm gonna make you rain
And you never change
Cause forever sweating for you
I'm gonna make you rain
And you never change
Cause forever sweating for you
You can ask mommy
I'm gonna make you rain down
Move, move
Get out the way
Here's comes the hurricane
I don't throw my money in the air
But I'm gonna make that momma rain
Mommy it not taste so bad, It look like in a rain I think
I just want to play your feelings
Get it quit, stay a minute
Hold on! Wait a minute
We're both adults and no time for brain-breasts
So baby it's time for that dirty talk
Wake up and you hardly walk
Do me, you text me baby, see dick
I've been like hold down
You see it like sure bite, they comes up here
Cause make that butty
Papa! Feel it wormer
Cause it is nothing it you waited
Just give me a minute
I bet that she'll be call me back
Girl be my water
Ain't nobody hotter
Go make it rain
I, I, I, I'm gonna make you rain, rain
You do it better
I'm gonna make you wetter
I'm gonna make you great
I, I, I, I'm gonna make you rain, rain
MR. 305, second remix
I'm gonna make you rain, rain
I'm gonna make you rain
Can you feel the change?
Cause forever sweating for you
I'm gonna make you rain
And you never change
Cause forever sweating for you
Subtitled By : Zachariah