Here in the upstate,
things don't change much.
Fall means football season.
Being married to a coach
Means measuring things
mainly by wins and losses...
Except for that one year.
Jimmy Carter
declared that if elected
He would do everything possible
To clean up
the federal government.
In South Carolina weather,
Late night
and early morning low clouds...
Come on,
let's go.
No, mom!
What's wrong with you, boy?
Get out of my way!
Damn!
Laird, son,
How many years
you been playing for me?
Two years, coach.
You want to make that three? Yes, sir.
I suggest you start
paying attention here.
Yes, sir.
We do things as a team,
gentlemen.
One player doesn't execute,
It's the difference
between six yards or six points.
Honeycutt,
What say
we do some up-downs,
As a team,
So we can further appreciate
that concept.
You heard the man!
Get them feet
chopping, now!
Get it up nice!
Get those knees up!
Get them legs going!
Get it up!
Get it up,
right now!
Come on!
Hit it.
Get them up!
Come on! Get them up!
Let's go. Come on, man.
Come on, now!
Hey, you.
Now, might any
of those xs and os
Be for me tonight?
How's it coming?
Almost done.
Mary Helen home yet?
Mary Helen's been in bed
for an hour, Harold.
You know,
Y'all do have a week
Before you actually
have to play this game, right?
Right.
I'll be right up.
Ah, the first "I'll be right up"
of the season.
Ready! Set!
Hut!
Let's go, now.
Team!
Full speed!
Live to the ball!
¶ goodbye, hard life ¶
Ready!
Blue, 24!
Set!
¶ goodbye, hard life ¶
¶ don't cry ¶
¶ would you let it ride? ¶
Hey, einstein.
Why don't you try
picking the ball up?
Yeah, you, dummy.
What, you deaf?
Yeah, pick it up.
There you go.
Throw it over here.
Come on, throw it.
¶ ride, ride, ride
let it ride ¶
¶ ride, ride, ride ¶
Hey, man, what are you doing?
Hey, coach.
He took our ball.
¶ let it ride ¶
Run it again!
¶ ride, ride, ride
let it ride ¶
See you tomorrow.
Okay, see you later,
Mary Helen.
Bye.
You're getting
home late.
Oh, hey, daddy.
I tried calling a couple times,
but the line was busy.
Your mama's asleep.
Oh, I'll talk to her
in the morning, okay?
All right.
Night.
Goodnight.
Heard Mary Helen
made varsity cheerleader.
She's really excited.
I'll bet.
I'll bet Linda
is too.
Yeah, I guess so.
Do it again!
One more time!
You got them
running something?
Hit it!
Come on, dope!
Hey, boy!
Watch this. Watch this.
Bring them in.
Gather up!
On the double!
Well, is someone
going to tell me
What's going on here?
How about it, Johnny?
Nobody move.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I just want
to help you.
It's okay.
I'm just going
to cut the tape off you.
You've got
to hold still.
Just try to hold still, now.
You got to hold still for me.
Look at me.
Hold still.
I'm not going
to hurt you.
Just hold still.
I don't want
to cut you.
My god.
It's all right.
Calm down
a little bit.
It's okay.
I got it.
Going to get you
out of this mess.
Okay, you're free.
Anybody got
anything to say?
Tell your folks
Practice is going to run late
tomorrow.
Mary Helen tells me
The cheerleading squad's
got itself, what,
Half-a-dozen new faces
this semester,
Isn't that right?
I also hear
the athletic director
Now has to take
The top spot
on the pyramid
At the pep rallies,
Isn't that right?
Harold,
What do you say
you stop by
And see what kind
of no-good
Your daughter's
up to?
Yeah, sure.
You got a couple of phone calls,
daddy.
From who?
Bobby taggert's folks.
Frank Clay.
I wrote them down for you.
What'd you tell them?
That you'd call back.
Harold,
have you decided
What you're going to do
about these boys?
Not yet.
Well, I'm sure most of them
Have never done
anything like this before.
You didn't see the look
on this young man's face, Linda.
He was terrified.
Coach Jones?
Go on. Good idea.
Might I have
A minute
of your time,
Please, sir?
Y'all, excuse me.
Anybody ever
said no to you on that,
Principal daniels?
Nobody still working here.
He scores.
What can I
do for you?
I hear we had
an incident
Yesterday.
Yes, ma'am, we did.
You taking
care of it?
Well, let's just say
Today's practice
won't be
The shortest one
we've ever had.
Good. Good.
You know, Harold,
That boy has been
rolling by here
For a long time now,
Minding his
own business.
Never caused any
problem for anybody.
I need you all to
keep it that way.
I appreciate it.
No, I don't want
the football.
I just want
to tell you
I'm sorry about what happened.
I thought
you needed
To hear that
from someone.
No, I don't want
the football.
You keep it.
Why don't you bring it
by practice later?
I'll find you
something to do.
Maybe you can
help us out.
Nothing more
is going to happen, son.
I promise you.
See you later.
All right?
All right,
the nine of you.
You know
who you are.
Get on down there.
Take your
shoulder pads off.
Line up
on the chalk.
Let's go.
Hustle up!
Well, what do you
want to do?
Run them.
How long?
Till I say stop.
On the line, now!
Where you're
going to be.
Ready!
All the way to the line, coach.
Don't quit on me now!
Don't you quit on me!
All the way through that line!
All the way through!
Hi.
Hey.
Long day?
Yeah.
How was yours?
Long.
So the report is
that Mary Helen
Got off to
a great start
In lit class,
But she's
struggling a bit
With the math.
Well, the lit part sounds good.
Come on, Harold.
It's bad enough when
a parent misses
A parent-teacher conference,
But it's worse still
when the parent's a teacher.
If the parent's a teacher,
he knows how his kid's doing.
He doesn't need a conference
to tell him that.
What?
Please just tell me
that you forgot to go.
Come on, now.
You know I had to deal
with those boys.
Oh, those boys.
Can't you just make room
For your daughter
and those boys?
Don't lecture me,
All right?
I'll go see ms. Marks tomorrow,
if it'll make you feel better.
Make me feel better?
This is not about me.
She's a junior,
Harold.
I mean,
she's got this year and next,
And then she's gone.
Go!
Y'all ready?
Yes, sir!
Yes, sir! Yes, sir! Yes, sir!
I want you
to close your eyes for a minute.
to listen.
You hear that?
I want you
to imagine
What that's going to sound like
After we've all
done our job tonight...
And then...
I want you to imagine
what that's going to feel like.
I want you
To picture your man
Right across from you.
You see him?
You make the effort
on every play,
You're going to beat them.
You play smart,
you're going to outthink them.
You play with heart
and character
And give your teammates
everything you've got
On every single
play out there,
You can walk off
the field tonight
Calling yourselves
a football team.
Okay.
Let's play
with Hanna pride
And never stop
believing in each other.
You win your battles,
We'll win our war.
What say let's
have some fun
And get it done.
Your Hanna yellow jackets!
Let's go, jackets!
The kickoff is high and deep
And sends
the jackets' Johnny Clay
Back near the goal line.
Johnny Clay,
Behind a convoy
of Hanna blockers,
Heads up the right sideline.
Go! Go!
Get up there!
Finally knocked out of bounds
at the 42-yard line.
Throw right, 63 flag.
Come on. Go.
Come on!
First and 10 for the jackets.
Marcum back to pass.
Finds hawkins in the right flat
for another jacket first down.
Come on. Get over here.
Come on. Come on.
36 crossbuck.
Look, once you
get that ball, son,
I don't want
to see nothing
But the back
of your jersey.
All right.
Get out there.
The handoff is to Clay.
Finds a big hole.
Now cuts outside.
Beats one tackler...
And another.
Get upfield, son.
Turn it on!
He may go all the way.
Touchdown, Hanna!
Yeah! All right.
Johnny Clay with a 30-yard run
gives the jackets the lead
With less than two minutes
to play.
Yeah!
That's a 30-yard
run, son!
That's our
ball game!
Evening, fellas.
Hey.
Hey, coach.
Harold.
Honeycutt.
Del. Don.
Kurt. Dennis.
Just brewed that pot
10 minutes ago, coach.
Got yourself
the first cup,
Right there.
All right.
Well...
Didn't exactly thump them,
But it wasn't too bad
As far as
season openers go.
Frank,
your boy, Johnny,
Had himself
a heck of a run there.
Just give him the ball.
He'll make
a smart man out of you.
Did notice
a few things
We need to work on.
Well, coach,
You reckon these are the boys
going to take us back to state?
Come on, clive.
Little early
for that kind of talk, isn't it?
I hear easley
Has a pretty decent
crop of speed this year.
Well, I guess we'll
see about that next week,
Won't we?
Do you think
you might want
To throw the ball
a little more?
I think
about a lot of things, Irv.
Now, listen, boys,
The last thing
coach here needs
Is us asking him
a slew of questions,
Especially after the way
he got those young men to play
In the fourth quarter.
We got them revved up
a little bit, didn't we?
So how do you plan
On beating
those easley boys
Come Friday night?
Well, Frank,
If I was to
tell you that,
Y'all wouldn't have
a thing to talk about
All week, would you?
Boy, that's a good cup tonight,
Del.
Thank you.
Come on,
turn it up!
Turn it up!
Good job!
Hey, honeycutt.
Yeah?
See that young man over there?
Yeah.
What do you
figure he wants?
I don't know.
Come on, spaulding!
Bring it
around there!
I think maybe he's thirsty.
Go on.
All right. Five minutes.
Get yourselves a drink.
Get on special teams.
How you doing?
Yeah, you.
No, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
It's all right.
Settle down, now.
I ain't going to give you a hug
or nothing.
Just got a little water here.
See?
I'm dropping
something off here.
Little something
from coach Jones.
Got a name, son?
You ain't going to talk to me,
are you?
All right.
Go ahead.
Go on, give it a squeeze.
Set! Hut!
Good job. Good job, justin.
All right, bring it in!
Hi.
Glad you came by.
Thank you.
What's your name?
Why don't you come on in?
I got some, uh...
Got some hamburgers
coming.
Get your buggy.
Come on in.
Really good burgers.
Oh, you found
some music you like.
Good.
¶ sha la la la la la la ¶
Hey, look who's here.
No ketchup, no onion.
Thank you.
He tell you
his name yet?
He doesn't
talk too much,
But he's sure
taken a liking
To that radio
of yours.
Radio.
Radio?
You know,
it's just sitting there.
You can have it,
As far as
I'm concerned.
Hey, you hear that?
Radio?
Coach honeycutt says
You can take that
home with you,
If you like.
Hey, are you hungry?
Would you like
a hambu...
You going to
want something
To wash it
down with too?
Root beer? Coke?
Coke.
Man knows
what he wants.
Coke, it is.
¶ yeah, baby ¶
¶ oh, make me happy, baby ¶
Well...
Which way's home, radio?
¶ who's that lady? ¶
¶ beautiful lady ¶
You know, there's
nothing wrong
With a good
country station...
¶ real fine lady ¶
But I can get used
to this too I guess.
¶ hear me calling out ¶
¶ 'cause that's all
that I can do ¶
¶ your eyes tell me to pursue ¶
¶ but you say, look, yeah
but don't touch ¶
You know,
the boys call me coach Jones.
Coach Jones.
You can call me
what you like
When you get
around to it.
All right?
¶ sexy lady ¶
¶ who's that lady? ¶
¶ beautiful lady ¶
¶ real fine lady ¶
¶ who's that lady? ¶
¶ I would dance upon a string ¶
¶ any gift she'd want
I'd bring ¶
¶ I would give her anything ¶
Now, I hope you can
Come by practice tomorrow.
All right?
The same time.
See you then, okay?
Afternoon, ma'am.
I'm Harold Jones.
I coach the football team
over at Hanna high.
I was just...
Giving your boy a ride home.
Come on in now, baby.
Hey.
Hello.
Yeah.
Look.
I see
You got yourself
another one.
Oh, look at that.
You get that
from him?
Yeah.
Coach Jones.
Look at that one.
He a nice man?
Yeah.
Good.
I think it's time
You got yourself
washed up for dinner.
You hungry?
Yeah.
I made you
some fried bread.
All right.
Get yourself
Washed up
for dinner.
Set! Hut!
Get in there!
Bring it in!
Come on, hustle up.
Let's go.
Come on, hustle up!
Bring it in.
Good job. Good job.
Good practice, men.
We've got a lot
to think about
This week.
Easley's got a ton of speed.
Defense, containment.
We've got to keep them
from getting outside.
Offense, ball control.
We're going to
grind it out.
We've got to
keep their offense
Off the field.
Now, there's one other thing.
See the young man over there?
Believe some of you
already know him.
He goes by radio,
And he's going to
be helping us out
For a while,
And are not going
to have a problem with that.
No, sir.
Call it up, danny.
One, two, three!
Beat easley!
What's he doing?
That's it.
That's it,
get your knees up.
Look at him
out there.
That one! That one!
Whoops.
Careful.
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Johnny.
I'm sorry.
You okay?
Fine.
What the hell
is going on out there?
The yellow jackets
still looking to get on track.
Marcum back to pass.
Intercepted!
¶ hand me down my walkin' cane ¶
¶ hand me down my hat ¶
¶ hurry now and don't be late ¶
¶ 'cause we ain't
got time to chat ¶
¶ you and me, we're goin' out ¶
¶ to catch the latest sound ¶
¶ guaranteed to blow your mind ¶
¶ so high you won't come down ¶
¶ hey, y'all, prepare yourself ¶
Whoa!
¶ you've never heard a sound ¶
¶ like the rubberband man ¶
¶ you're bound to lose control ¶
¶ when the rubberband
starts to jam ¶
Come on! Come on!
Good job.
Don't quit! Don't quit!
¶ I was so surprised
I was hypnotized ¶
¶ by the sound
this cat's puttin' down ¶
¶ when I saw
this short, fat guy ¶
¶ stretch a band
between his toes ¶
¶ hey, I laughed so hard
'cause the man got down ¶
¶ when he finally
reached his goal ¶
¶ hey, y'all, prepare yourself ¶
¶ for the rubberband man ¶
¶ you never heard a sound ¶
¶ like the rubberband man ¶
¶ you're bound to lose control ¶
¶ when the rubberband
starts to jam ¶
That was a good one.
I liked that one.
Radio!
Hi, everybody.
Quite a show you put on
out there tonight, coach.
Just wondering if you were
running a football program
Or a social club.
Radio, I need to talk
to your mama.
That okay?
She right there.
Hi, mama.
Hey, baby.
There's a sandwich in there
for you.
Oh. Okay.
I'll be in there directly.
Okay, mama.
Ma'am.
Hey.
I was wondering
If we might carry your son
on up to wade hampton tomorrow
On the team bus.
Got us a football game.
Well, what your boys
done to my son
Was wrong, coach,
But I'm not looking for you
to make up for it.
The boys are taking to him
real good.
They're still boys,
now, ain't they?
I'll keep a good eye on him.
I guess it's all right with me.
I don't mean
to pry, ma'am,
But, ...
I was hoping, ...
I might be able
to ask you
What exactly
is wrong with him.
Well, the doctors never could
give me a name for it.
Say he the same
as everybody else,
Just a little slower than most.
I got an older boy, walter.
He's fine and all.
And their daddy?
He died a while back.
I'm sorry.
You got your hands full.
Well, they got me
working 10 hours a day
At the hospital,
Some days more,
So I'm wondering where he's at
half the time
And worrying all the time,
Because I figure
They're only going to need
one excuse to put him away.
James is a good boy, coach.
He got himself a good heart.
Most folks just don't
take the time to see it,
Is all.
James.
James Robert Kennedy.
Thank you, ma'am.
No, he is not
getting on that bus.
Harold, he is not a student.
You don't even know
how old he is.
Look, he has a handicap
we know nothing about,
And what if he has
Some kind
of a seizure
Or something?
He's not the one
who's going to have the seizure.
This has got nothing to do
with any of that.
If you are suggesting
that I am overly concerned
About my students
being in the company
Of a severely handicapped
black man,
I assure you that I am,
But my concern
Is not necessarily
for my students.
I'm not so sure we're trying
to help somebody here,
Or whether he's being used
As nothing more
than a glorified mascot.
You know me a hell of a lot
better than that.
Put your
game face on.
Wipe your smile
off your faces.
Start thinking
about football.
Coach Jones!
Hey, radio.
It raining hard.
Radio...
Going to be
wet out there.
Yeah, it sure is.
Listen,
We're not going
to be able
To take you
on the bus today.
Some folks,
They don't think
it's a good idea.
They just don't understand yet,
but they're going to catch on.
Believe me.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
And in local sports,
Hanna's yellow jackets
travel to wade hampton tonight.
With a 4-4 record,
They'll need to win
both their remaining games
To keep their playoff hopes
alive.
Clock winding down
now in the fourth quarter.
The yellow jackets have trailed
all night long
But are now
within striking distance,
Trailing 14-13.
Danny marcum
Barks out
the signals.
He's back to pass.
Incomplete.
Second down, now.
Still time to mount
one last drive,
And there's the draw play.
Playing
up the middle,
To five, 10,
first down, jackets.
Jackets will go
for a field goal
To win it.
Less than
a minute to play.
Here's the snap.
The kick.
No good!
The jackets'
last-ditch efforts
Fall short.
Final score...
Wade hampton, 14,
Hanna, 13.
Here, here.
Use a spoon.
There you go.
Let me get some
of these things
Out of your way.
All right.
Thank you, grace.
Which one
of those cobblers
You got today?
I got-
I'm not done.
Don't talk with your
mouth full, now.
Um, peach and blackberry.
Peach and blackberry.
What's it going to be, radio?
Both.
Give the man both.
I'd like some more coffee too,
Please.
Yeah, I take both.
Radio, look at me
for a minute.
I want my pie.
You got some mustard
on your cheek.
I'll get it for you.
There you go.
Football season's
just about over.
You know that,
don't you?
One more game.
Yep. One more game.
You going to be
okay with that?
Where's my pie?
Don't worry,
they're coming.
She'll bring you your pie.
Don't worry about it.
I like both.
She's got your order.
Football.
I like football.
You know,
some of us felt pretty bad
About leaving you
off that bus last night.
I'm going to find a way
to make it up to you.
How you going to do that, coach?
Your Hanna yellow jackets!
Jackets!
Hey. We're having fun.
This is a good one.
Nothing like archrival westside
to get jackets fans stirred up.
Winning this one
Would even Hanna's record
at 5-5,
And though a far cry
from early season hopes,
Salvage a measure of pride
for the home squad.
Here we go.
All right, four right,
24 flank and reverse.
Third and six on the 40.
That was
a good one, coach.
a good one.
Yeah. We'll see.
Ready!
That was a reverse!
Reverse!
Radio,
come back here.
Come back here.
What... He's telling the play!
Westside defense
calling an audible,
Bringing in
both outside linebackers.
Danny, check it off!
Reverse!
Jones signaling for time,
but marcum doesn't hear him.
Marcum rolls right
and pitches it to hill
On a flank and reverse.
He is crushed in the backfield
and fumbles the ball,
And it's recovered by westside.
Dadgum it!
Come on.
No wonder!
They knew the play.
They knew the play!
Defense,
get out there.
Radio, radio, radio.
Listen to me.
You can't let the other team
know what we're going to do.
How they know that, coach?
Tommy,
get out there!
Good god.
Set!
Hike!
Snead back to pass
for westside.
It's broken up by bradley,
But a flag is thrown
on the jackets' cornerback.
No!
Got him in the back, coach.
Are you kidding?
In the back.
You blew that call
And you know it.
I need you to move back.
Don't do it.
That was a chickenshit call.
15 more!
Oh, come on!
Another penalty on Jones.
Chickenshit! Chickenshit!
Radio!
Get him out of there,
honeycutt!
Get him back.
Unsportsmanlike conduct!
Just called a third penalty
on the jackets' bench.
It looks like a damn
train wreck down there.
Honeycutt, get him
off the field.
How many flags you got here?
You got any more flags?
Get him back!
A total of 45 yards
now on the play.
There goes
my evening.
Let's go, buddy.
Here we go.
Any chance
I can get the ball tonight?
Nobody speaks
in this room
Unless coach Jones
says he does.
Sit down, Clay.
There your ball.
Now that we got that
taken care of...
Jackets trying to hold westside
here in the fourth quarter.
They've stiffened
here in the second half
And still trail by only four.
Here comes the jackets' blitz.
He got him!
Go!!
The ball
will go back to the jackets
With time for one last drive.
¶ when the sun comes up
on a sleepy little town ¶
¶ down around san antone... ¶
Hut!
Marcum keeps it.
Pitches to smalls.
Bounces off one tackler
and breaks free!
First down, jackets!
Ford, come here.
Flanker right,
split left.
24 z post.
Get on your horse.
Hey, honeycutt,
I got a good feeling
about this one.
Good feeling. Good feeling.
Set!
Hut!
Marcum fakes the handoff
and drops back to pass.
Looking long.
Mitchell's open!
Touchdown, yellow jackets!
That was a good one!
What'd I tell you?
With less
than a minute to play,
Hanna has overtaken
rival westside
With a stunning
37-yard touchdown.
Yeah!
That's the way
the game's
Supposed
to be played.
Good job.
All right.
I got it!
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey.
Settle down, now.
Listen up.
That was a great team effort
out there tonight.
Great comeback.
Y'all played your hearts out.
I'm proud of you. Good job.
Honeycutt.
For standing behind us
all season long,
Especially tonight,
The game ball...
Goes to radio.
Can you sign this?
Yeah, sure.
There you go.
Thanks.
Hi.
Hey.
How are you?
Much better now.
Yeah?
You want me to bring
this home tonight?
You only got
one of them?
I had a lot
to choose from,
Didn't I?
No kidding?
You going over
to the shop?
I suspect so.
Shouldn't be
too painful.
Well, don't forget to
bring some of that
Unsportsmanlike
conduct home.
All right.
Evening, fellas.
Harold.
Irv. Clive.
Nice win tonight,
coach.
I'll make us
a fresh batch.
Well, this will be fine, Del.
Well, I know a 500 season
isn't what we all had in mind,
But I did
see some things tonight
I think we can build on.
The boys made some
good adjustments at halftime
And ol' danny marcum finally got
the offense moving a little bit.
He sure did.
He sure did,
coach.
I'm real proud of all the boys.
Always good to beat westside,
And it's nice
to win the last one.
Wasn't long ago
We were winning
most every one.
There something you need to say,
Frank?
Well, I think we got...
Too good a team
To be losing half our games.
Anybody else?
No.
It's all right,
you can speak up.
Well, if nobody else
is going to say anything,
I sure as hell will.
You got yourself a distraction
needs dealing with.
A distraction?
Is that what you think radio is?
Well, you're damn right I do.
Come on, now, Frank.
You know, I think I'm going
to do us all a big favor
And let you all finish this one
on your own.
Coffee's been better, Del.
Sorry, coach.
Well, now you show up.
You chickenshit.
I figured I'd
just be in the way.
How'd it go?
That good, huh?
I'm afraid we've got
A disgruntled booster
on our hands.
Hmm.
Banker Frank?
Yeah, he says we got a problem
With radio
being on the sidelines.
What do you think?
I think that one's up to you.
How's the
basketball team
Looking?
Just fine,
long as Johnny stays healthy.
Why?
Oh, I just thought radio
might need something to do.
You know,
I reckon we could use some help.
Good.
I'll see you Monday.
Hey, what you
got now, boy?
Football.
A football?
Coach Jones
gave you that?
Yeah.
Wait a minute, now.
What's the matter?
We all done.
Oh, now...
We all knew
The season was going
to end sometime.
Yeah?
Yeah.
But look
what you got.
A football and
a sweatshirt
And lookee here.
Look at all of this.
Look at that.
That radio.
Yeah.
See?
Now, next fall's
going to be here
Before you know it.
Promise.
Now, give mama a hug.
Boy, what's that?
I want me a hug.
I'm always here for you, baby.
President-elect Jimmy Carter
Met president ford
today
At the white house,
Also meeting
With cia boss
george bush.
Meanwhile,
the new york post
Has been sold
To australian
publisher
Rupert murdoch...
Morning, girls.
And in sports,
morning.
Free agent
reggie jackson
Signed
a five-year deal
To play with
the new york yankees.
Hi, nicole.
Hi.
Coach Jones.
Well, good morning,
lou.
Good morning.
What brings you
To this neck
of the woods?
Seeing as you never
drop by my office,
I thought I'd
pop up for a visit.
And how is
everything?
Everything's fine.
Why?
A little bird told me
Mr. Kennedy's
been spending
Quite a bit of
time with you
Inside the building.
Yeah,
that's correct.
Do you see that as a problem?
Disrupting a football game
is one thing.
Disrupting
a classroom
Is a different
matter.
Hmm?
I want him with you
all the time.
Okay?
Yes, ma'am.
...I-o.
"radio,"
And that's how
you spell it.
Here, you want
to try it?
You want to do it?
Look. It's easy.
You know, you just
take the chalk
And it writes
right on there.
Well, we don't have
to do it right now.
Radio.
Blueberry and pumpkin today.
Pie, not cobbler.
Both.
Coach Jones, you're needed in the office.
All right, everybody,
just keep working.
Radio, I want you
To keep everybody
under control
While I'm gone, now.
Keep an eye
on everything.
No talking.
No....
Well, now,
How long would you say
mr. Kennedy has been
In an actual
classroom setting?
Well, let's see, about a month.
And the thinking behind that?
Well, he was doing
fine with the team.
I didn't see any harm in it.
Look, mr. Tucker,
I know you've got a job to do
But is...
Me having radio in the classroom
really worth all this trouble?
Well, that's
what the school board
Would like to find out.
This is a young man
Who's been spending
his entire lifetime
Wandering around all by himself
out on the streets.
Which is quite different
Than being
inside a public school.
Wouldn't you agree?
Yeah, well, that's the point,
isn't it?
Mr. Tucker,
I am well aware
Of the liability risk
we are running here.
Harold here will be
first to tell you,
That my list of reservations
is longer than most.
I'm sure
that's the case,
But the fact of the matter is,
None of us has any experience
With having
a severely retarded man
Wandering
the same halls
As our students.
The risk is enormous.
Please keep that
in mind.
I will.
Ms. Daniels.
Mr. Jones.
Thank you,
mr. Tucker.
Well,
This is a hell of a position
you've put me in.
Yeah, I suppose it is, lou,
But radio's
not going to do anything.
Harold...
Why on earth are
you doing this?
Same reason you are.
Defense!
Defense! Come on, let's go!
How you doing?
I'm good, I'm good.
That's in.
That's all right.
Looks like radio's
doing okay.
Long as there's
a ball.
How you doing?
Oh, hell, honeycutt,
you know me.
Get near Christmas,
And I start
counting down the days
Till next season.
Look at him,
honeycutt.
Wasn't long ago
You couldn't get
a word out of him.
Yeah,
I miss those days sometimes.
Yeah, I got that one.
I like that one.
Okay, here we go.
All right,
bring it in.
¶ have a holly
jolly Christmas ¶
I'll get it.
¶ it's the best time
of the year ¶
Hello?
Hey, mrs. Jones.
It's radio.
Hi, radio.
Is coach Jones there?
Just a minute, radio.
I'll get him.
Harold!
Mom?
Have you seen
my red clip?
Uh...
My red hair clip.
Yes, yes,
on the washer.
Harold!
Radio,
Can I help you
with something?
What pants I put on?
Well, didn't your mama
lay out any clothes for you?
No, she not here.
She working tonight.
Oh.
Well, just pick something out
and put it on.
I'm sure
it'll look fine.
It's a big night.
We're going to do
the Christmas tree up.
That right?
That's right,
So just grab something
and put it on.
Okay.
Harold?
Is that radio?
How about this one?
What?
Tell him
those look fine.
Those look
fine, radio.
Okay.
Radio going to put them on.
¶ joy to the world ¶
¶ the savior reigns ¶
¶ let men their songs employ ¶
¶ while fields and floods ¶
Put it right there.
There.
¶ repeat the sounding joy ¶
Big radio in there, mrs. Jones.
Big radio.
I'm going to
get a cookie.
All right, don't eat
too many, now.
All right.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
Little something from us
for radio.
Great, thanks a lot.
Have a great one.
Merry Christmas.
I'm going to take
these presents
Over to radio's house.
Of course you are.
I'll go with carolyn.
All right.
Thanks.
He sure cleaned up
this Christmas.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
Merry Christmas
to you.
Merry Christmas, coach.
Del, have
a good one.
Merry Christmas.
Thank you, guys.
Hey, daddy.
Hi, honey.
These are
from mr. Wagner's store.
Thought radio
might be needing a few shirts.
Great, thanks.
This is nice,
You getting folks
to help radio out.
No shortage of people
feeling sorry for him.
We're not asking people
to feel sorry for him.
That's the last thing he needs.
Okay.
Look, Mary Helen...
I know we haven't had
much chance to talk lately.
There's been plenty of chances,
daddy.
You just don't take any of them.
It's all right.
Radio needs
what you're doing
More than I do.
Look, we'll-
Time to go,
coach Jones.
Time to go.
Merry Christmas,
Mary Helen.
Merry Christmas, radio.
Ooh, presents.
A bunch of them.
Yeah. So beautiful.
Christmas!
Goodnight, daddy.
I'll see you at home.
You all set to go?
Merry Christmas,
coach.
radio.
I can't wait till mama
see all these presents.
Yeah, she's going
to be surprised, isn't she?
I can't wait
to get home.
This is so beautiful.
I'll tell mama
about the tree.
Think we'll be able to fit them
all in the house?
No.
Ooh. That's a big one.
I can't wait to open these.
These are all beautiful.
Think it'd be all right
to open one tonight?
Sure. Yeah.
Which one I open?
Here.
I got one right here for you.
Open this one.
Who that from, coach?
Mrs. Jones,
Mary Helen, and me.
It is?
Okay.
I hope you like it.
It's a radio.
Yeah.
Turn it on, see if it works.
¶ whenever you call me ¶
It's working, coach.
It's a good one.
It's working on there.
Whoo!
Mama, it's working.
Come on, mama. Come on, mama.
Dance.
Come on,
dance with me.
All right,
all right.
Whoo!
This is a good one.
Come on, coach.
Come on, it's Christmas.
All right, all right.
¶ now, I found out today ¶
Go, radio, go!
¶ that all the words
had slipped away ¶
¶ but I know ¶
Whoo!
Go, radio, go!
Dance. Whoo! Whoo!
Whoo! Whoo!
I like that one.
Thank you, coach.
You're welcome.
Merry Christmas.
Thank you, coach.
That's a good one.
Oh, hush now.
Lord, we ain't never seen
no Christmas like this.
You cut a pretty
mean rug, there, coach.
Oh, come on.
That's where
he gets it.
Well, he may not get
everything I try to teach him,
But he did get that.
The hospital's
got me working 16 straight,
Right through Christmas day.
At least tonight
I get a little bit of holiday
with my boy.
Good.
You know, coach,
It wasn't
that long ago
I see you drive up
in that truck of yours
And be wondering
why you doing what you doing.
So why are you doing
what you're doing?
I figure
it's the right thing to do.
There's a whole lot out there
that's right.
Don't mean we always do it.
No, ma'am, it doesn't.
James has been telling me
Next year's team's
shaping up as a good one.
Well, we're hoping.
If all works out.
You'd let me know
if he was a problem?
He's no problem at all,
believe me.
How does it feel to be out
from behind bars, angels?
Good night, darling.
From all of us
to all of you,
A very merry Christmas.
Cloudy and cold today,
so stay by that fire
And keep it right here
on waim.
We'll keep you warm
with your favorite hits,
Commercial-free
all morning long.
Merry Christmas.
Quite a load you got there.
Yeah.
Right there.
Put that right there.
Mind telling me
where it came from?
Presents for me.
Put that right there.
Hold up.
That's a pretty
decent Christmas-
No, no, no.
That's for me. That's for me.
What's your name, son?
Radio.
Radio?
Yeah.
Hey. Hey.
Keep it here.
Hey. No.
I said
keep it here.
No.
I said keep-
Hey. No.
Keep it still.
Come on.
Let's go.
Radio.
Yeah, yeah,
you got your radio.
Come on.
That you, newdall?
Yeah!
We got a sandwich
in here
In case you're hungry.
Oh, man, you see how much
they're paying dr. J.?
How much?
You're making this harder
than it has to be, son.
Can't be for
one season.
Ain't nobody makes
a half a million dollars
For playing
basketball one year.
Who you got
back there, kojak?
I'm not sure yet.
He won't tell me his name.
He ain't been here
a week,
Got hisself
a john doe.
Let's go see
who it is.
When was the last time
We had anybody here
on Christmas anyway?
Hell, I don't know.
Oh, shit.
Hey, radio.
I want to go home.
We going to get you
out of there.
The 76ers in red...
That's dr. J.,
radio.
That's dr. J.?
Ooh, that's a good one.
Did you like that?
Like that right there.
He put the basket.
Well, it's the doctor's
team this year,
No question
about it.
Why don't you wear
your hair like that.
My hair
like that?
Morning, Irv.
Hey, radio.
Oh, hey, coach Jones.
We're watching dr. J. There.
Dr. J.
Harold, did you meet
officer newdall yet?
No, I don't believe
I have.
I need more presents.
I need more.
That's a good one.
Okay, I'm going to put
this one up here.
Put that right there.
Okay.
Come on. Come on.
What else down there?
Give me another one.
Oh, that a good one.
Morning, there.
Merry Christmas.
There you go.
Here you go.
That's a good one.
Give another one.
Hey, coach Jones.
Presents all gone.
Yeah, I see that.
Yeah.
I brought your buggy
home for you
And got you
something to eat.
Thought you might
be hungry.
Oh. Okay.
Ooh...
So how you doing?
All right?
Okay.
Your brother
walter's inside.
He's going to stay here
till your mama gets home.
Okay.
I like
the french fries.
When do I start
school again?
Real soon.
Miss winniver gonna
let me in 11th grade,
Ain't that right,
coach?
That's right.
You remember
what we talked about, now,
About you staying close
to the teachers?
Don't want you to go
wandering off on your own.
That was a good thing
you did today, radio.
Huh?
That was a good
thing you did today
With the presents.
You didn't do
anything wrong.
You understand that?
I'm real
proud of you.
Proud.
Proud of radio.
Good morning.
Hey, radio.
Come on in.
Come on, radio.
We gotta go, man.
Okay, let's go.
I'm ready.
We ready to go.
Good morning.
Morning, radio.
Morning.
You have
a good Christmas?
Yeah, coach Jones
bailed me out of jail.
Ah! No running.
Stop!
No running.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm the hall monitor.
But that's okay.
Oh, thanks, radio.
Morning.
How you doing?
Get your man!
Jump, jackets, jump!
Jump way up!
Outside pass to Clay.
Clay pulls up for a 17-footer.
Good!
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Cover the screen!
The screen!
You've got to keep radio
on the bench, coach.
Hey, radio, stay
on the bench.
Stay on the bench, now.
Who?
You.
Oh, okay.
¶ come on and take a free ride ¶
Bring it up!
Take a pick!
Clay working off the pick.
Drives right side.
No basket!
Offensive foul, Johnny Clay.
1-5 out of control!
You're killing me.
Time-out! Time-out!
Ref, did you think
about that?
Morning, everybody!
Morning, radio.
Morning, ms. Winniver.
Morning.
Uh, radio,
where's my hug?
There it is.
Who'd you catch running
in the hall this morning?
Billy samson.
I swear, you have
turned out
To be quite
the hall monitor.
Morning, Hanna!
You know who this is?
This is radio.
Today our menu is...
Salisbury steak.
French fries.
French fri-
Oh, I like them
french fries.
Black-eyed peas.
Black-eye-
we got black-eyed peas?
We sure do.
We got black-eyed peas!
Brownies.
We got some brownies.
And hot rolls.
With the hot rolls.
And pear halves.
And what?
Pear halves.
We got pear halves.
You ever seen
anything like that?
Yeah.
Hey, yo.
Radio!
Hey, how you doing, man?
What's going on, bud?
How you doing?
Hey, where's honeycutt at,
man?
Coach honeycutt,
he around?
No, he gone.
He's gone.
All right.
Well, hey, check it out,
Coach dalrymple's got
a couple things next door
She wants you
to come get.
Huh?
Mrs. Dalrymple.
Don't worry, man, don't worry.
It's just her. She's alone.
Girls are gone.
I- I can't do that.
All right, man.
All right,
But she's gonna be
real disappointed.
You don't want
to let her down,
Now, do you?
Okay, radio.
See you.
Okay.
Okay...
Mrs. Dalrymple?
Radio!
You can't be in here.
Bad radio. Bad radio.
Coach Jones. Coach Jones.
Coach Jones.
No, radio. No, radio. No.
You know, it'd be one thing
If you'd gone and done
something like this before
On your own.
Radio, listen to me.
It's important
that you tell me
Why you went in
the girls' locker room.
Mrs. Dalrymple
needed me.
What for?
She wanted me
to pick up stuff.
Did she ask you?
No.
Who did?
Radio, who asked you to go
in the girls' locker room?
Who asked you?
No.
Well, I don't know
what I'm supposed to do here.
Be mad at radio.
You're willing
to do that?
Take the blame
for someone else?
You're a better
man than me.
I'll say that
for you.
Hey, Johnny,
what's up?
I got a letter last
week from clemson.
See, they know
I'm a junior,
And they're looking at me
for a full ride after next year.
That's great.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Excuse me.
I need to speak with mr. Clay
For a minute.
What's up,
coach Jones?
It's one of those days
I wish I wasn't a teacher,
So I could just
lay into you right now.
What you talking about?
What's gotten into you, huh?
I thought you'd learned
something the past few months.
I guess I was wrong.
What are you
talking about?
Don't saw a word
unless I tell you to,
You understand me?
Now, you might think
you're clear on this,
Because honeycutt wasn't around,
but let me tell you something,
This is my call.
There's no way you're suiting up
tomorrow night.
Right.
What did you say?
Coach Jones?
Mr. Clay?
What seems to be
the problem here?
You hear the problem, ma'am.
Young man,
students do not tell me
What I do and do not hear.
He said I can't play tomorrow.
Is that what you're thinking,
coach Jones?
That's what I'm saying.
Well, then,
Seeing that coach Jones
is the athletic director,
I say you are not playing.
Ma'am, this is westside.
If we win, we're in first place.
Well, that's all the more reason
For you to cheer on
your teammates, isn't it?
Anything else?
Yeah, why don't you
tell your boy
That I said thanks.
Radio didn't sell you out, son.
There are plenty of other people
willing to do that.
Yes, sir.
Well, I appreciate
your understanding.
We'll talk soon.
Thank you.
That's the last of them.
Did you talk to Mary Helen yet?
She's fine.
She knows
it wasn't radio's idea.
Oh, Harold.
Harold, you are
too close to this.
It's not that
Johnny talked radio
Into doing something,
it's that he did it.
I mean, what if
it's something worse
Next time?
He'll know.
Are you sure?
Hell, I'm already under
a microscope anyway.
I got a school to run,
I have a thousand children
that I'm responsible for.
I just-I need to know
where all this is going.
I don't know, lou.
Harold, that may not
be good enough anymore.
No, I'm sorry.
I've been trying to call,
And I haven't gotten a hold
of either of them.
I tried several
different places.
I'm not sure-
Oh, here he comes right now.
I'll tell him.
What's the matter?
It's radio's mama, daddy.
What happened?
She had a heart attack.
Oh, no.
Is she all right?
No, she's gone.
I was trying
to call you or mom,
But I couldn't
reach anybody,
And they're telling me
That he won't come
out of his room.
I don't know
what to do, daddy.
All right.
Put your coat on.
He's just sitting
there in his room.
You got it?
Irv.
Coach, thanks for coming.
Walter's going to be here
in a few minutes.
How's radio?
He's pretty upset.
Tore the place up
pretty good too.
Radio?
Radio...
It's just me.
It's coach Jones.
It's just coach.
Coach.
Coach...
That's radio.
Yeah.
That's you.
Radio
right there.
There's mama-
there's mama there.
Mama said we got-
we got good football this year.
Yeah.
That's what mama said.
We got good-
Radio, ain't nothing I can say
Is gonna make you feel
any better.
Mama.
Your mama was a fine,
beautiful woman.
She loved you
with all her heart,
Didn't she?
Oh, boy,
did she love you.
She still does.
She love
the radio.
She said she's always gonna
be there for radio.
James...
Look at me.
She will always be there
for you.
All right? She will.
You understand that?
Always be with you,
inside,
Right in your heart.
All right?
We're gonna be
all right.
Come here.
Where's my mama?
Hold on just a second.
I want to tell you
something.
Something I never told anybody.
When I was about 12,
I had a paper route.
Crack of dawn every day.
Wasn't many houses
around here then,
So I had to cover
quite a lot of territory,
And I used to
cut through the woods
On this little dirt road,
And one morning,
I was riding through there,
And I heard this noise.
Sounded like a rabbit
or something, you know,
Caught in a trap,
And then I realized
it was coming
From one of these houses
set back up in there.
I started-
kind of walked over there,
And didn't seem like
anybody was home,
So I walked on up.
It had, you know, chicken wire
and barbed wire
Around the bottom of it.
I figure to keep
the critters out, you know?
And then all of the sudden,
I saw these fingers
coming through the wire,
And I put my bike down
And got down
on my hands and knees,
And I...
And I looked under there,
And there was this boy
about my age.
I don't know
what was wrong with him.
Something was.
They used to keep him
under there,
And I...
I looked right at him.
You know, he looked back at me.
We just sat there
Staring at each other
for a while.
I ran that route
for two years, Mary Helen...
And I never did a thing.
I just wanted you
to know that.
Thanks, daddy.
How long
before he comes back?
I'm hoping tomorrow.
His brother walter's
moved in with him.
Honeycutt says
He let loose
on that house
Pretty good.
Yeah.
Says he's not
the only one
That knows about it
either.
The man had just
lost his mother, lou.
I didn't ask why
He took a swing
at his wall.
I just asked you
who knew about it.
Well, why are you
asking me that?
Our friend from the board
is back.
He wants to see you.
With his mama gone,
it's all different.
Every bit of it.
Good luck.
Mr. Jones,
in the last month or so,
How much time would you say
mr. Kennedy has spent alone?
Uh, during the day, at least.
Mr. Jones?
Past few weeks?
Everybody's been keeping
a pretty steady eye on him.
So we talking an hour a day?
Or two?
An hour, maybe.
Well, it could be a half-hour.
Well...
As you may
have guessed,
The board
has received reports
Of mr. Kennedy's rather
inconsistent behavior.
What kind
of reports?
From who?
Reports
of resisting arrest,
Uh, tearing up
the inside of his home,
And barging into
the girls' locker room.
Oh, barging?
Who's been feeding you
this crap?
Mr. Jones,
I'm not here
To argue with you.
I'm not arguing
with you.
I asked you
a simple question.
Who's been feeding you
this crap?
The reason I ask is because, um,
Those were
all instances
In which he wasn't
being supervised.
Says who?
Bottom line,
with ms. Kennedy gone,
James faces
some rough times ahead now.
To keep him
in a school setting-
Let me tell you something, son.
This school is the reason
He's doing as well
as he's doing.
But to keep him
in a school setting-
You take him out of this school,
You might as well
just take his life from him.
I have compiled a list
Of outside
care agencies.
Oh, I'll bet
you have.
Yes, ma'am, I will take care
of it personally.
Yes, I will.
Yes, ma'am.
Is that a fact?
That's
some serious money.
Well, all right.
Yes, I will.
All right, now.
You too.
Harold.
Hello, Frank.
It's been
a long time
Since you came
through my door.
Yeah, it sure has been.
So...
What can I do
for you?
What are you trying
to do here, Frank?
I'm afraid I don't understand.
Yeah, you do.
Calling the school board,
making complaints about radio.
This is about you
Getting back at me
for cracking down on your boy,
And nothing more
than that.
Let's not go off
making this all personal.
It is personal.
It is not personal...
Besides which, if it was,
I wouldn't have
most of the guys
Over at Del and don's
feeling the same way I do.
Yeah, what way is that?
Harold,
you're one of the finest coaches
In the upstate,
And with Johnny and the boys
we got coming back next year...
It's just better
If we do things
the way we used to.
You just want to be the one
runs radio out of Hanna.
At least I know where you stand.
Radio.
That's the o,
big, round circle.
Yeah, you try it now.
Come on,
it's all right.
It's okay.
There you go,
take the pencil.
You can do it.
I know you can.
That's it.
Look at that.
You did it.
Congratulations.
Good job.
Radio right there.
Yeah.
Hey,
look who's back.
What's up, Jimmy?
Johnny,
welcome back, man.
What's this?
He brought that in
a little while ago.
Hi.
Sorry coach Jones
got mad at you.
He got real mad.
Yeah.
Yeah, he did.
Real mad.
Jackets playing tough d.
And there's a steal by walker!
Honeycutt calling the play now
As the jackets
walk it up the floor.
Two! Two!
Jackson has it in the corner.
Finds Clay,
Who drives foul line.
Great pass to cunningham.
Underneath for an easy two.
All right!
Johnny Clay,
doing it all tonight.
Down the floor,
up the score!
We want two!
Now Clay from deep.
Good!
Johnny Clay has 17 points.
And that's the end
of the first half
With the score
Hanna, 39, easley, 34.
That's a good
first half, boys.
That's a good first half.
You gonna stick around?
Yeah.
Save my seat for me.
All right,
bring me a drink, will you?
Yep.
Well, I talked to mr. Tucker
and his colleagues,
And we all agreed
That the best thing
for everybody
Is to get together
and have a meeting.
Well, I don't want
to talk about him.
Harold.
Wait, I know
what you were thinking.
I thought you and I
were together on this.
I'm trying to find
The best possible
solution for everybody.
It's not about who-
What is it about?
You remember asking me
where all this was going?
Do you?
You know, I still don't know,
but I do know one thing.
I am not going to sit back
And let Frank Clay
make the rules on this.
Clay saves it off the tip.
Underneath to henry.
Great teamwork!
And the jackets go up by seven.
Clay off the screen.
Jumper!
Good!
Johnny Clay in the zone now.
Easley working the ball
Upcourt...
And Clay with the steal.
Great pass by Clay to greer
for the easy two.
And the jackets
are running away
With this one!
Feels good, don't it?
Feels real good.
Settle down,
settle down, settle down.
Now, I've coached a lot
of basketball over the years,
But I've never, ever had a team
play better
Than you all did tonight.
Johnny Clay,
it's nice having you back.
Yeah, it is.
It's good to be back,
coach.
Good.
We're still
in this race.
I want you all
to rest up tomorrow,
We're gonna
hit it hard Monday.
All right? Get some sleep.
Play it.
You got a shot.
You better
believe it.
Hey, there's my boy.
Always a pleasure
to see you.
Good game, son.
32.
Yeah, but what's with
all that passing?
With the defense
they were playing,
You could have gone
for 50.
Bye-bye, see you later.
You gotta take advantage
of these chances, son.
See you later.
Bye-bye.
See you later, radio.
Bye, Johnny. Bye, now.
See you later.
What's that?
Okay. Okay.
It's nothing.
Look, son, we got a whole lot
to look forward to next year,
And I don't want anything
or anyone getting in the way.
You understand?
Radio's not the one
getting in the way, dad.
And that Frank,
He's just scared you got it in
for his son, is all.
When gloria was a baby,
I never left her alone.
Wherever I went,
I made sure
edith stayed with her.
I forgot to tell you
honeycutt called.
Yeah, some of the parents
asked for a meeting with lou
On Sunday night.
With just lou?
Yeah, I don't think
they're particularly interested
In your side of things. Do you?
No, I guess not.
What the hell
kind of a father-
What the hell kind of a father
are you?
Aw, hell.
Maybe the whole thing's
just a big mistake.
Radio probably
would've been better off
If we'd just gotten him
some help.
Help?
And what you've been giving him
has been...
Couldn't have been easy
on you and Mary Helen,
Me spending all this time
with radio
Past few months.
Harold, wait.
You can't believe
that's been a mistake,
You being with radio.
You've been so great
for each other.
Yeah, well,
look where it's got us.
Where it got you
Is a school full of kids
that love him,
And Mary Helen
feels the same way,
And anything
that Frank can do or say,
That's not going to change
anything.
It's never a mistake
To care for someone.
That's always a good thing.
Right?
Thank you, reverend.
God bless you,
sister.
And god bless you.
That was quite a sermon.
Indeed.
Praise the lord.
God bless you, radio.
Coach.
Praise the lord.
I love that sermon.
I like that.
All hands are jesus' hands,
I like that,
The way
everybody singing.
Yeah, that was
a nice service.
A nice service.
I need to talk to you
About a little something
here.
Hey, hey.
You remember telling me
about being in 11th grade?
Oh, you talking
about ms. Winniver.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah,
I like ms. Winniver.
Well, there's been
some talk
About maybe you going on
to 12th grade.
That'd be something,
wouldn't it?
You know,
have you graduate.
Radio, listen to me.
Put your-
take your radio d-
Radio, listen,
put your radio down.
Look at me.
There ain't nothing wrong
with moving on, son.
Everybody gets around to it
sooner or later.
No.
No, I like the 11th grade.
I like the 11th grade.
No. No.
I do the-
I do the menu in the morning.
I do the menu.
I say,
"we're all gonna have hamburgers
And we're gonna have
mashed potatoes,"
And then I see people
in the hallway,
I say,
"hey. No running.
No running.
Everybody, no running. "
And everybody know that's radio.
I'm there.
Everybody like that.
Ms. Winniver like that.
They say, "hi, radio!"
All right, listen.
No. No.
I like-
We'll talk about it
closer to the fall, all right?
Let's not worry about it
right now.
All right?
Radio like the fall.
That's when
the football come.
Yeah, that's right.
It's football,
we go exercise,
And everybody have
no shirt and t-shirts on,
And coach honeycutt,
He be, "let's see
some Hanna spirit!"
Yeah, and hey,
coach, you say,
"let's get the quarterback,"
And radio, he defense coach.
I'll be defense coach.
That's right,
because we gonna go all the way.
That's right, radio.
We gonna go
all the way.
We gonna go all the way.
Because we got
the spirit.
We going
all the way.
We going all the way.
My point is
that this man
Is a disruptive force
in our community
And represents a threat
to our students.
Thank you, mr. Clay.
Okay, okay.
I understand how some of you
might be feeling.
All I am asking
is that if we decide
That there's no other way
around this
That we dole out
as little hurt as possible.
Fine.
Honeycutt, is there anything
you'd like to add?
Evening, Del. Don.
Harold.
Evening, everyone.
Evening.
Hi, lou.
How you doing?
I'm good.
How are you?
Good.
I was gonna
call you.
Well, you got yourself
a crowded shop tonight, Del.
Yeah, coach.
I think y'all know my wife,
Linda,
And my daughter,
Mary Helen.
Evening.
Evening, ma'am.
Well, I had a talk with radio
this morning,
And I told him,
In not so many words,
That we might be looking
at some changes.
It didn't take long to see
the more I talked,
The more he didn't
understand me.
We got a lot of that
going on around.
When I was playing,
I had a coach,
He used to tell me
to keep my priorities straight.
He'd say, "son, you figure out
what's important.
You push everything else aside. "
I love football.
I love everything about it.
I love Friday nights
When you're looking for a win,
And Saturday morning
when you found one.
But that's not what's important
right now.
We got ourselves a young man
we're not thinking about...
The same young man
Who could hardly talk
when we first met him,
And now he's making
announcements in the morning
Over the loudspeaker.
The same young man
Who got himself
a football letter last fall,
But he never wears it,
Because he can't afford
a jacket.
Now we're asking him to leave.
Harold, we are not asking-
The man's not done,
Frank.
I know some of you don't know
or don't care
About all that radio's learned
over these past few months.
Well, the truth is
We're not the ones
been teaching radio.
Radio's the one
been teaching us.
Because the way he treats us
all the time
Is the way we wish
we treated each other
Even part of the time.
Look, I know
something's gotta happen here.
I know-I know some changes
gotta be made...
And I know
I can't let what happened
last season
Happen again.
So I've decided to step down
as head football coach.
See what you've done, Frank?
You know,
I'd like to keep teaching,
If that's all right.
Keep an eye
on radio,
Make sure he stays
out of trouble,
And I'd like to spend
a little more time
With a few other folks
I've neglected over the years,
While I still
have a chance to.
Much as I love
this game, you know,
It's not
half as important
As setting that right.
That was a pretty good cup
tonight, Del.
Thank y'all.
Good night.
This what
you wanted?
Is this worth it?
That was a crazy idea.
Weren't expecting
that one, now, were you?
I can't believe
You're gonna stop
coaching football.
Found it.
Oh, there.
Under the mattress
with everything else.
All right.
Oh, you look great,
radio.
Thanks, Mary Helen.
I'll see you
out there, daddy.
All right, honey.
There she go.
Get your collar down.
You look good, now.
You look really good.
You know where
we're gonna be, right?
Yeah.
All right.
Do a good job.
I'm awful proud of you.
Okay, coach. There I go.
Hey, radio.
Oh, hey, Johnny,
how you doing there?
How you doing?
I heard you got yourself
a letter.
Yeah, they gave me a letter.
Me and the boys thought
you might need something
To put it on.
That for radio?
Yeah.
How you like that one?
Looks good on you, man.
Thanks, Johnny.
Hey, congratulations, man,
and, uh...
Thanks a lot.
Yeah.
Patricia ann yearwood.
Thanks, radio.
You're the best.
Thank you.
I would also like
to extend a special thank-you
To our honorary graduate,
Mr. James Robert
Kennedy...
Yeah, radio!
All right!
Who has decided
to return
This coming fall
As an 11th-grade student
At Hanna,
Where he will be welcome
For as many such years
as he so chooses.
Looks like you got
your assistant coach back.
Yes, we did.
Yeah!
In that moment,
my husband was prouder
Than if his team had won
a state title.
Radio was now officially
a part of Hanna
And a part of our lives
forever.
So if you happen to be
in anderson
On a Friday night in the fall,
Get there early.
You'll see the man
they call radio
Leading the yellow jackets
onto the field.
Radio's in his 50s now,
And he's the most beloved coach
Hanna's ever had.
Coach Harold Jones.
Harold Jones?
Well, he was recently inducted
Into the South Carolina
coaches hall of fame.
He's retired from teaching now,
But still maintains
his special friendship
With Hanna's favorite
11th-grader.
¶ close your eyes ¶
¶ the light of love
will lead the way ¶
Ready?
Are you ready?
Down!
¶ in the eyes of a child
we're all the same ¶
¶ if we are all god's children
the logic is so simple ¶
¶ the one you call a stranger
is really your brother ¶
¶ love don't start
with the eye ¶
¶ it starts with the heart
yeah ¶
¶ look deep down inside ¶
¶ you know that you have
the chance ¶
¶ to make the choice
to make a change ¶
¶ so make the choice ¶
¶ to look
with the eyes of your heart ¶
¶ no, I don't mean to preach ¶
¶ some may say
that it's unrealistic ¶
¶ 'cause none of us
is perfect ¶
¶ but the way that I see it
why don't you just try ¶
¶ to see the world
through different eyes ¶
¶ 'cause you see ¶
¶ that what is done to you
it's done to me ¶
¶ we are one humanity
yeah ¶
¶ oh, love don't start
with the eye ¶
¶ it starts
with the heart ¶
¶ love digs inside ¶
¶ you know that
you had the chance ¶
¶ to make the choice
to make a change ¶
¶ so make the choice
to look with the eyes of ¶
¶ love ¶
¶ don't be afraid to love ¶
¶ you have the chance ¶
¶ to make the choice
to make a change ¶
¶ so take the chance ¶
¶ and make the choice
to make the change ¶
¶ so make the choice ¶
¶ to look
with the eyes of your heart ¶
¶ Anderson, South Carolina ¶
¶ till Hanna High ¶
¶ the people there
will tell you ¶
¶ just ask any passerby ¶
¶ about the kid who speaks
in gibberish ¶
¶ folks'll tell you ¶
¶ shoot, wasn't nothing ¶
¶ but a little love
and attention ¶
¶ gave voice to a mute ¶
¶ come football fridays ¶
¶ they let radio be the star ¶
¶ he falls in
with the marching band ¶
¶ then with the color guard ¶
¶ he jumps
when the cheerleaders jump ¶
¶ with pom-poms on his hands ¶
¶ he cusses
like the coaches do ¶
¶ and high-fives
with the fans ¶