=It's another happy morning.
How are you? I'm Gim Jang Wan.=
=The drizzle outside the window
seems beautiful too...=
=This is Pak So Hyeon's 'Love Game'.
Pak So Hyeon joins you in today's program.=
=Let us enjoy a wonderful time together...=
=I'm the host of Wonderful Radio, Sin Jin A.=
=My dear listeners, thank you
for accompanying me all this while...=
-=Wonderful Radio=-
Here you go.
Thank you.
Aigoo...  our hope, you are tired too, right?
(Aigoo - oh dear, oh my god)
I'm all right.
Don't drink too much coffee.
You're going to be 30 years old soon.
All of your hair is going to be white before you know it.
Wait until I release my new album.
I'll visit the hair salon everyday.
Your album? What a joke.
The script for the third
and fourth segments.
Who are they?
Colpi Girls.
Didn't they say they invited Dal Shabet?
Our program should also invite those
currently popular kids. Please.
We're already lucky to get Colpi Girls
to appear in our program.
Get in quickly.
Next week, please do me a favor
and invite a male idol group.
Looks really alike. Looks really alike.
Hello! We are the Colpi Girls.
You all are really pretty.
I hope we have an enjoyable time today.
Yes, we will.
Giving a good greeting is the most crucial.
When I was still a member of Purple, I felt that
meeting sunbaes was harder than going on stage.
(sunbae - senior, mentor)
- Eonni, you were a singer?
- Purple?
(Eonni - older sister)
No way.
Don't you know Purple?
- Eonni. We're going on air soon, get ready.
- Okay.
=Power FM.=
The third and fourth segments of
Wonderful Radio will be done together
with the new female group, Colpi Girls.
Hello everybody! We are the Colpi Girls.
They're a really cheerful and energetic group.
Their high vitality is like carps in
a whirl that are rushing to breed.
They are extremely impetuous,
but are also an extremely
ignorant yet innocent group.
Thank you!
So, for the first song of today,
we'll start off with a song from Colpi Girls.
"Get Out Boy".
It seems that you don't know Purple.
What year were you girls born in?
- 1991.
- I was born in 1994.
Year 2004, Republic of South Korea...
Oh, damn!
I knew it would be like this.
What should I do? What should I do?
Be quiet!
Really, shut up will you?
Hyeong!
(Hyeong - older brother)
This song is sure to be a hit.
Sin Jin A is here! Sin Jin A!
- Sin Jin A?
- Sin Jin A.
Omo!
(Omo - oh my)
Please, just wait a second.
Let's talk! Didn't you say you were
going to give that song to me?
Quick, go in!
- Hey!
- Wait a minute!
Wait, don't be impulsive!
Oppa!
(Oppa - older brother)
Come out.
Oppa, come out now!
Oppa!
Jin A.
I understand that you're very angry.
I completely understand.
However...
It was my only choice.
The more it is like this,
the more we have to be reasonable.
Didn't you say that song was
specifically written for me?
Yes, but...
After the lyrics were written,
I realized that the song is
perfect for idols. Idols!
Oppa!
Jin A.
At the beginning of next month,
my fourth child will be born.
Furthermore, they're twins. I have to earn
money for their powdered milk and diapers!
So what if it is just one song?
I want to earn it even if it is just 100 dollars. This is reality...
More importantly,
idols are the current trend.
You really disappoint me.
From now on, I won't accept the songs you
compose even if you give them to me for free.
Goodbye.
Jin A.
Hey!
What is my schedule for tomorrow?
Nuna, I'll send you a text message
about it when I get home.
(Nuna - older sister)
Why do you want to send a text?
Just tell me now.
Nuna, we're very lucky and have
a solo concert tomorrow.
At the Sangmun Elementary School's
24th class graduates reunion.
We're planned to perform there.
Hey! Who do you think I am?
What? I'm going to sing at
Sangmun Elementary School's
24th class graduates reunion?
Cancel it!
My credit card's debt
deadline is approaching,
and in fact these 3 days I have
been using soap to wash my hair.
You... didn't I tell you that I will
be releasing a music album soon?
Oh, you're back?
Hello auntie.
Dae Geun, you're here?
You've worked hard.
Have a meal before you leave.
Okay!
Hey...
Oh yes, auntie. I have to go back
to adjust tomorrow's schedule.
I'll come by and have a meal next time.
Bye.
Dae Geun, have a meal then go...
You... wretch.
Why are you so fierce to Dae Geun?
Where is there still such a good kid like him?
You must treat him better, wretch.
You can't even give him his wages on
time & you still treat him like that?
Just rest a while, why do you work till so late?
After resting enough, it's a must to
continue working hard to earn money.
I really don't know what to do about you.
There isn't even a single customer!
Isn't it good to close the shop and rest?
Rest, what rest?
Why is it so hard to tie...
Welcome! Please come inside.
abeoji, come and have a sit here.
(abeoji - father)
You see, here comes 6 more people!
Daughter-in-law, come quickly.
Aigoo...really pretty.
This is the vicinity's most famous shop.
What should we eat?
I'll get another menu for you,
please wait for awhile.
You must eat more later...
Aish, you wretch.
Done.
=To me, there are two Christmas in one year.=
=Once in December,=
=and once in June.=
=This week,=
=is my self-appointed midsummer Christmas.=
=During Christmas this June,=
=I haven't confirmed=
=what wish I want to make=
=to Santa Claus.=
What about you?
Do you want to find
a wishing box together with me
and place June's wishes in one at a time?
Right now,
=let us make our wishes towards
the seemingly bored Santa.=
Today's Christmas,
please don't let me be alone again.
The second segment of Wonderful Radio will now
use the writing method to interact with the listeners.
Humans themselves are what causes desperation,
and they are also what changes desperation into hope.
Listener 2065, thank you for sending in an
exciting quotation with beautiful fresh flowers.
Next, lets listen to a requested song.
After School's...
-=Requested song: After School's "Love Love Love"=-
PD, can I also request one song today?
(PD - Program Director)
Purple's "You're My Angel".
PD Yun Ji Seon who has been
working together with us for 4 years,
has to temporary say goodbye to us
because she is going into labor.
This is to show my gratitude to PD Yun.
I wish that everything proceeds smoothly for you.
Aigoo...she actually dare to use her past song
for broadcast.
You were looking for me?
Sit.
It's been a while.
Let's be straightforward,
you need to take over the program, Wonderful Radio.
Are you talking about Yun sunbae's program?
(sunbae - senior/mentor)
Frankly speaking,
the listenership of this program is a complete mess!
I estimate that there will be a meeting
very soon to discuss the issue of DJ replacement.
But no matter how you say it, that program
was created with Yun sunbae's painstaking effort...
That's true,
but the listening rate is only 2%.
I will speak with PD Yun,
so you take over and turn the situation around.
Lock the door before leaving.
Yes.
Remember to cultivate a good habit and go home early,
=Okay?=
Have a safe trip.
Hyeong, you're leaving already?
Didn't you say you were going to bring me the album?
I'm sorry, I'll bring it for you next time.
You cannot keep forgetting...
I know, I know already. Sorry, and have a safe trip.
Hyeong, why did you come here?
Aren't you supposed to come by next week to be our PD?
Wonderful?
Baekhwaju?
(Baekhwaju - wine made of 100 varieties of flowers)
Just give anything.
But how come it's you who's coming?
Our program doesn't allow you
to broadcast songs as you like.
How's the DJ?
You mean Jin A?
She's treated as a princess.
I seriously hate that style of people.
I presume Jin A also hates people like you.
Maybe.
Do you really need to make the schedules so rushing?
Nuna, do you remember that
whenever I step on the brake,
our car makes a very weird sound?
I went and repaired it at the
repair shop today, now listen to it...
Hey! Cha Dae Geun!
Should I give her a call?
Oh, eonni.
(eonni - older sister)
eonni...
- Quickly, quickly. Why are you only here now?
- Do you have makeup remover?
My makeup is totally ruined.
I heard that the new PD has a
character that is as bad as a dog.
I also heard that, like a dog.
He came so early?
He was here since just now...
Hello, I am Sin Jin A's manager, Cha Dae Geun.
- Rumors always...
- What time is it already?
Why are you so late? How do you feel about
making us wait here for Miss Sin Jin A for half an hour?
That is because there was traffic congestion and also...
Before your DJ highness arrived, we roughly
got familiarized with one another.
A large portion of the program's
topics can be reluctantly accepted,
but there is a problem.
'My love equation'.
It is so mushy that it causes goosebumps.
But PD, I like this topic...
The response from audiences is very good and it
is necessary to have a suitable extent of mushiness
to gain popularity. Right, right?
Who told you the audience's reactions were good?
Submit to me a new proposal of the
program's activities before 11 tomorrow.
Tomorrow...
11 O'clock...
PD,
do you think this is the internet where you can
just press the computer keyboard and get what you want?
Think about how hard it is to plan a new proposal...
That is why there is a writer here isn't it?
But may I ask, why do you keep interrupting my lines?
For first meetings, you should at least
be polite and do a self-introduction
to be roughly familiar with one another.
Not create an atmosphere that
seems to be filled with adjustments.
Only then can you work together
properly isn't it? Right, right?
Your eyes are really beautiful.
People often say that.
So, we'll end here.
I felt that you should like this kind of beverage...
Men with exquisite beauty should like expresso...
Oh, right...
When lying down,
first start from your head.
Then slowly place your spine down one segment at a time.
Straighten your waist,
and assume a bent posture.
Try pressing down,
and maintain.
How's PD Yun doing?
She is on a maternity leave.
Then who replaced the PD?
There is a new one.
Is it a man?
Yes it is. But he has completely
no proper upbringing! Annoying guy.
Stern city man?
Nope. City man who is always finding fault with others.
Talking about finding fault, that group Colpi Girls
or something...
is really asking for it.
Think about our past.
In the past we were idolized and powerful!
Exactly. Every weekend we will be able to hear...
Topping the chart this week is Purple!
Thank you!
Thanks to all the fans and friends of our fan club. I love you!
So, up next,
Purple's encore of "You're My Angel"...
~ You are my angel, angel, angel to me. ~
~ Just like this, forever treasure and keep our love. ~
~ You are my angel. ~
Thank you everyone, see you at the next performance!
I love you, I love you everyone.
Really miss those times...
Camera!
Scene 423.
Action!
Cut! Cut! Good! Enough! Don't film already!
Film the next title.
Director, is it okay?
- Okay!
- Hey, didn't I say okay already?
Miss Mi Ra, you've grasped the feeling well.
Cut! Cut! Okay! It's good! The feeling is good, you've grasped it well.
Film one more time.
Enough, enough, enough... There's not
enough time. Do you think you're filming a movie?
Okay!
You're really great, Representative Lee.
Director Jin, you must also know
that advertisements need to be smooth.
Do you remember Ajinomoto? Seasoning.
How long do you think they took to shoot URUSA?
(URUSA - A type of liver medicine made from bear bile)
They took a half-moon bear from Jirisan
(Jirisan - A mountain in the southern part of South Korea)
and drained it for so many years.
The century hearing aid's advertisement
that was filmed over 10 years using one left ear,
has a huge advertisement in the Korean daily newspaper!
'Carrying a guitar' was also filmed for so many years!
Mi Ra is the same kind of long term worker.
Get ready.
Thanks to your company artist's good fortune,
life has been comfortable recently.
It is thanks to hyeongnim's good fortune instead.
Only if you're doing well then we'll have a good life.
Especially that 10 O'clock slot 'Idol'.
- Who was it that the program brought over? Pink Dolls?
- You're talking about Pink Dols?
- Yes, yes, yes...
The amount of listeners tuning in is really significant!
It's all because you chose well, hyeongnim.
The majority of listeners of the 10 O'clock
segment is still secondary school students,
so it is more suitable to rely mainly on idols.
6 O'clock is the time to get off work, hence arrangements
has to be made to consider the working population and taxi drivers.
That's why it is more suitable to
rely on those with higher reputation,
such as Yeun Mi Ra. What do you think?
Mi Ra?
Of course it's not a bad idea.
Not bad, right?
Not bad.
This proposal was painstakingly prepared by the writer and I...
So?
What I'm trying to say is that using this kind of manner
to treat the author who has put in so much effort isn't too good...
For me, doing well is more important than working hard.
I believe that a good DJ should have three requirements.
Popularity, ability,
as well as personality.
Or at least possess two out of three.
No. Must at least have one, don't you think so?
What's the purpose of you telling me this now?
Don't always mix in too much personal
emotions when we are having a meeting,
you'll let people see through your character.
What is your target when it comes to the listener rating?
4%.
Just merely 4%?
The listenership hasn't exceeded 2% within the past half a year,
and you dare to say just merely 4%?
Is the past that important?
Dreams must be ambitious!
In that case, the proposal of the program's new topics...
should be done by Miss Sin Jin A.
Me?
I...what? I can do well...
I do...what? I'll do, I'll do it, I'll do it.
I, I can do well...
I will look forward to it.
Where did such a fellow come from?
What should I do about this?
Should we wait for the next lift?
Nevermind, just take this.
Hello.
It's been a while, Miss Jin A.
I've recently been watching your drama.
Is it?
I'm really thankful for you saying such a thing.
But, sorry,
I haven't been able to listen to your radio broadcast.
Looks like you only have that little bit of ability.
Do well, Sin Jin A.
If you can only fare so badly after
abandoning Purple for your solo pursuits,
I will feel really bored.
I'll see you again.
Goodbye.
Encore! Encore!
I don't suppose you intend to say that matter here, right?
Jin A,
don't.
Let's think about it again.
It isn't a must for that matter to be said today, isn't it?
I'd like to express my heartfelt thanks to
everyone who came to our concert today.
Today,
there is something I need to announce...
Today's performance will be our last.
From today onwards, our group Purple will be disbanded.
All these while...
thank you for loving us all this while.
Stretch out your other arm
parallel to your eye level.
Now, focus your vision to the direction
where your hand is pointing.
For those who can accomplish that,
please bend your arm backwards
and grab hold of your other hand.
Breathe in,
breathe out.
Inhale and feel the expansion of
your abdominal region and thoracic cavity.
Breath and relax your body muscles.
When doing yoga exercises, remember to
concentrate only on one's feelings.
How did both of you get acquainted?
He's the PD I told you about.
Radio?
Oh, so it's that annoying guy?
Hey!
What about both of you?
Don't you know Purple's Ji In Yeong?
You don't recognize me?
Oh, the the flat-chested Ji In Yeong?
You've worked hard.
What did he say about me?
Why is he like that?
That's why I asked you to put some sponge pads...
Hey! How do you expect me to put
padding when I'm practising Yoga?
I'm very glad to see all of you.
Then, lets do well.
Bring them for a meal.
Yes, I understand.
See you next time.
Do they think that we are UNICEF?
(UNICEF - The United Nations Children's Fund)
Why do they bring this kind of people here?
So, what do you intend to do about it?
Wait a little longer, there will be a revision soon...
Are you sure?
Now all the popular DJ are our people, why do you still worry?
That's why what I meant was,
this time we have to do it for real.
I do not want to wait too long.
Hey! What I like most is to do it for real!
Hey, shall we go and eat?
Oh...isn't this the newcomer PD Lee?
- Hello everyone.
- It is said that you're now very popular.
What?
Are you talking about me going to the 9 O'clock program?
Not that. Aren't you now working with Jin A?
- Are you very familiar with Sin Jin A?
- Of course.
Before Purple was disbanded, they were
regular guests on our show for 2 months.
They were really awesome and their
songs were especially nice to listen to.
~ You are my angel, angel... ~
I bumped into her not long ago and she started
asking about you and what kind of person you were.
Then what did you say?
I said that you're as stingy as a beggar.
You really are like a beggar,
the DJs all hide and run when
they see you, only you do not know.
You have to treat her better,
there aren't many like her at this age.
She has loyalty and is sexy, pure and courteous.
You on the other hand really resembles a beggar.
How is your yoga practice coming along?
I'm going crazy soon, my body is all stiff.
You will really learn how to be gentle,
you must learn more from me.
He is a faithful yoga fan.
Okay, I understand.
Namaste something...
(Namaste - A traditional Indian salutation)
Hyeongnim,
please don't drink alcohol and do the program anymore.
Hey!
What drink alcohol and do the program?
At most is do the program after drinking.
Exactly.
You can't say it like that,
it can be very fatal.
- At that time you really caused others to receive the blame.
- You have worked hard.
You make me really upset.
Do you want to go for a drink?
I'll call you tonight.
Okay. You've worked hard.
As the saying goes, a brief encounter is also fate.
Life is boundless,
please look around your surroundings.
For all of you to accompany me at this point of time,
means having such a large amount of fate with me.
Therefore, being able to hear my voice in the next 2 hours,
doesn't it mean that you and I have a very different kind of fate?
Wonderful Radio, this is Sin Jin A.
Today, our program's new PD Lee Jae Hyeok is right here.
He is one who only drinks ice americano and is a very cool guy.
PD Lee Jae Hyeok, fighting!
-=New program's proposal??=-
-=How dare you!!=-
-=Broadcast this song as the first=-
So, let's listen to the first song of today.
Are you ready?
Sistar's...
"How Dare You".
-='Seldom is it not the skill of love, but the technique.'
Alphonse Daude -2065=-
I always feel lethargic at this time.
I on the contrary, like this time the most,
as I can eat some light snacks.
-=Change the music.=-
-="Like rain and like music."=-
=Our Wonderful Radio...=
The song for our 3rd segment of Wonderful Radio,
is a song that is very suitable for a rainy day like this.
- Gim Gwang Su's song "Like rain and like music".
- What? Gim Gwang Su?
Whose song did you say this was?
Oh, is it Kim Hyeon Shik's?
I'll correct it when the broadcast is over.
You think that a simple correction is enough?
No, that wasn't what I meant...but this kind of mistake
is hard to avoid, and I originally have problems
differentiating between Gim Gwang Su and Gim Hyeon Shik --
How can you possibly not be able to differentiate
between Gim Gwang Su and Gim Hyeon Shik?
Hey, hey! What are you doing
when broadcast is still ongoing?
Let me go!
Hey! How can you be regarded as a singer?
Let's talk outside.
Did you guys see that?
He even slammed the table. Looks like the rumor
about you having a dog attitude is true. Dog, dog!
Nuna, I will...
Outside shouldn't be able to hear right?
You are a dog! Dog! Dog!
I'm feeling really giddy.
You better be careful in the future!
Quickly, drink some water.
So, the rumors are true...
Miss! Do you have time?
I have time, but not energy.
Are you still angry?
What's wrong with that guy? He's like a crazy viper,
he must really have something wrong with his brain...
But, do you know?
If you were to say and scold bad things about
the music I liked when I was 20 years old...
I will feel as if I have been stripped of my youth.
I also didn't scold, just merely said
the wrong name accidentally...
For example, if someone were
to miscall Purple as Fin.K.L,
I will definitely go crazy, really!
Oh, right,
this is Lee Jae Hyeok's youth.
Listen to it on your way back.
~ Further and further away... ~
~ I once thought that youth will remain stagnant, ~
~ and that my heart will
become more and more open. ~
~ But I can now no longer find anything... ~
~ The period of death will repeat itself... ~
~ Our love, ~
~ has became insecure because of tears... ~
~ How much longer... ~
-=Annoying guy=-
-=Today is the last day.=-
-=To submit the proposal!=-
-=Annoying Guy
Today is the last day. The new corner!=-
Did you catch a cold?
Mom, should I resign from
my job at the radio station?
Suit yourself.
You either sing at a nightclub,
or follow him your entire life.
Mom, how can you say such
things to your own daughter?
I am Purple's Sin Jin A! I am
also still alive and can still sing!
Did you swallow a train engine?
Ever since the day you became a DJ,
you haven't stopped complaining...
~ How long more... ~
~ before I can see you again... ~
~ Across the years of river flow, ~
~ our love... ~
Oh yes, that's it.
~ has became insecure because of tears... ~
eomma, I found it, I found it.
Oh yeah!
Crazy girl.
Look for people with stories to tell,
prepare for that to go on air next week.
See! I told you that you wrote it well.
Back in secondary school, I was
a writing champion, champion.
Fighting!
=Our Wonderful Radio...=
Wonderful Radio has a new segment to offer you,
'Songs that are sung for you'.
The first protagonist of today's new
segment is a 22 years old military man,
who used his precious
vacation to attend our program.
So, shall we listen to his story together?
I am Chong Kwang Tae, the Chief
of the military service in Pyeongchang.
It's not because of anything else but I...
have someone I really like.
However, she doesn't want to
accept me. I'm going crazy soon.
Last year I even ran away
from the army because of her,
and was arrested by the police and nearly hanged...
That shouldn't be so serious...
so, let us listen to his song together?
With my sincerity, I present to you a
song by Brown Eyed Soul's Jong Yeop called
- Nothing B!
- Er...
then shall we listen to "Nothing Better" together?
Hey!
Im Sul Ki from the department of English,
don't belittle me, I will surely be
as good or be better than you.
You just need to wait there honestly--
Please calm down, let us listen to "Nothing Better".
Angel Sul Ki, Im Sul Ki! Im Sul Ki!
~ Just like breathing, you
always remain by my side... ~
Soo Ki, are you okay?
Hey! If it's you, will you be okay?
From tomorrow onwards, you
must start growing angel wings.
~ Remain here just like this without leaving... ~
~ Nothing better, nothing better, than you... ~
This is really! I can't take it!
Chong Kwang Tae, you're dead!
Ajussi! Can you please turn the radio off?
(Ajussi - Uncle)
We received a call saying that they want
to sue us for fabricating a broadcasted story,
and also accused us for being able to
do anything to raise the listenership.
Bujangnim, this program's item is much better than
expected, if only you can give us a bit more time...
(Bujangnim - General Manager)
Of course it's good to raise the
listenership, so maybe we'll maintain the
current situation until the time for revision.
Or we might as well change the DJ and program
segment all at once. What do you think?
What?
Have a good thought about it.
Why are you here?
Did you get reprimanded by the higher ups?
Then did you think I'll get praised?
I'm sorry.
Why? Why are you sorry?
No, it's because of me that's why...
I was the one who chose the proposal for the new item.
It's a PD's job to choose and be responsible
for the program's segment. This time is no difference.
You don't need to worry. I'll be
responsible for our team till the end.
Try and see.
Hey, Cha Dae Geun! Can't you see
the car is going to explode soon?
Can't you, can't you just inspect it beforehand?
Can you be responsible for our late arrival?
Heavens, what time is it already?
I'm sorry.
Quickly get a taxi.
Really too much!
Really too much! How can you get a taxi here?
Ah!
Help! Help!
I listen to your broadcast often.
Ah, thank you.
Wow, your child is so cute and
your wife is also very beautiful.
That photo was taken really well.
May I ask, can I participate on one of your broadcast?
PD, this is the original manuscript.
She actually anyhow changed
the program. Where's Jin A?
She's here.
=Our Wonderful Radio...=
Wonderful Radio, 'Songs that are sung for you'.
Today's hero is a 42 years old
taxi driver, Mr. Kim Ji Hyeong.
So, would you please tell us your story personally?
Hello.
I wonder what story will there be today?
- Keep quiet.
- My name is Kim Ji Young.
There is a letter that I was
unable to send to my wife in time.
That is why I am here today.
Yun Yeong, this is Ji Hyeong.
It's been three years since you left us.
I would first like to say that I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for letting you experience so much hardships.
When you were alive, I didn't even write you one
letter. I'm sorry that I wasn't a considerate husband.
Oh right, I've prepared the song that you really liked.
You used to laugh at me for not being able to sing well.
Then listen, I'll start singing.
Yun Yeong,
Yun Yeong, our Min So...
The doctor said she has cancer like you.
I know you really miss Min So right?
I know, I know but I cannot give Min So to you.
I must let Min So recover,
to grow up and get married, and to give
birth to a grandchild who will look like you.
So, no matter how much you miss her,
you must leave her by my side till that happens.
I'm sorry, I'll be counting on you.
I'm sorry.
~ My hot lips, ~
~ wants to come near to your gentle lips. ~
~ Let my love ~
~ get conveyed into your heart. ~
~ If you still ~
~ do not know the love I have for you, ~
~ I love you more than anyone else in the world. ~
~ No matter when, I will still love you. ~
~ I will love you just like this very moment. ~
~ Compared to everyone else in the world, ~
~ I love you more. ~
~ No matter when, I will still love you. ~
~ I will love you just like this very moment. ~
~ Compared to everyone else in the world, ~
~ I love you more. ~
-= Mr. Kim Ji Hyeong touched audiences by
dedicating a song to his late wife. Popular DJ Miss
Sin Jin A's interview received much attention. =-
- Hello.
- Yes.
Hey, hey, hey. Tae Young, why did you greet him?
He is your father...
Ah, really...
Let's go together!
It's so frustrating, forget it.
Let go of me!
Da Hui, have you eaten?
Your father is talking to you.
Forget it.
Ajussi. Please don't greet
my friend next time.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Da Hui...
Just let her be, aren't children all like this?
~ I felt very tired walking and walking, ~
~ so I stopped my footsteps. ~
~ The thing that passed by... ~
Da Hui, I didn't see you so I just placed it here.
Da Hui, if you love singing then continue doing so.
I like it the most when I see my daughter sing.
In my heart, you are always the best.
Happy Birthday to you...
~ That's when I feel love, love, love... ~
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Yes...it's thanks to you. Congratulations to PD as well.
It's only a trifle matter, there
shouldn't be a need to congratulate...
You know how to compose too?
Of course. I am a woman with copyrights.
That is really unexpected.
What is?
Aren't you of idol origins?
What is it with being an idol? Can't idols compose?
Nuna, why are you still here?
That guy, PD Lee is currently...
Hello, PD.
I'll go back to the car first.
Have a nice day.
He really didn't even miss a week.
What do you think this person does?
A florist?
Who cares what he does? As long as its
for certain that he will be someone very fragrant.
Look at how contented you are...
Hello. PD, this is the information
and story for today's lead person.
Must let Sin Jin A read this before the program begins.
That was chosen by eonni.
- Hello everybody.
- Hello.
Eonni, this is for you.
What is there for us to listen to?
Why? What is it?
Da Hui sent a text message to
ask us to listen to the radio.
Radio?
='Songs that are sung for you'=
Today, we welcome a very cute
secondary student to our studio.
Hello.
Hello. I am Yun Da Hui,
a 10th grade student.
Then, can you introduce to us your story and song?
Dad, can you hear me?
I'm on the radio station
that you used to love.
Dad, you know right?
Mom got remarried.
=That ajussi is uglier than you.=
But, he treats Mom very well.
After you passed away,
it was such a difficult time for Mom and me.
That ugly ajussi, that annoying ajussi...
He said that he is very happy to have a daughter like me.
As long as you allow it,
I'd like to accept that ajussi now.
I'm really sorry for this period of time.
Thank you for the gift.
Dad.
~ I hope you can understand that
I can't be close to your heart. ~
~ Tears tell me my earnest hope. ~
~ I once loved, and once complained, ~
~ missing that someone ~
~ who used to love me more than anyone else. ~
~ Always by my side but have
never been able to get near. ~
~ Yes, I will complain... ~
~ Please listen to what I have to say, ~
~ I only require some time. ~
~ I once loved, and once complained, ~
~ missing that someone ~
~ who used to love me more than anyone else. ~
~ Hidden deep in my heart, ~
~ yes, I once loved... ~
The stories you chose were not bad.
That was nothing hard.
I thought of a question during recording.
What is Wonderful Radio to you?
A time when I can talk about my stories. I mean in the past,
but not anymore.
Listen to other people's stories,
to feel touched and to comfort them.
And I myself can find comfort through that.
I have learnt a lot.
I really feel like singing.
Only now then I really understand what I
should say through the help of music.
Nuna! Nuna! What should I do?
It's hot!
Nuna and PD, it's really not a joke.
It's totally hot and all over youtube and reports!
Yes, reporter, interview is it? Sure, no problem.
Leave it to me.
Since when did you start seeing it?
Three days ago.
Three days?
Wow, that is quite long...
This time it's really long enough.
Not bad.
~ You are my angel, angel, angel to me.  ~
~ Just like this, forever treasure and keep our love. ~
~ Today, you are as wonderful as yesterday, ~
~ not leaving behind even the smallest regret... ~
Today's Wonderful Radio will
soon say goodbye to everyone.
The cool and refreshing wind
makes such a fine night.
Doesn't pork bone soup with soju
sound perfect for this kind of night?
(Soju - Native Korean distilled alcohol)
Wow. That's simply great.
There is one song that I'll like
to recommend, "Night's Starlight",
a song by Lee Seung Hwan.
-=It's Kim Hyun Shik's song.=-
Lee Seung Hwan's peculiar timbre gives us
a different feeling from the original song.
Do we have Lee Sung Hwan's version?
Would you please enjoy this song while
I bid my goodbye to everyone here.
I wish everyone will have a fine night.
~ The night is just like your breathing, ~
~ that quietly wipes away my tears. ~
~ Starlight... ~
I heard that Wonderful Radio
is very popular, hyeongnim.
PD Lee has gotten himself into something big.
Congratulations hyeongnim. This is really...
If it's like this, what about me?
Why are you like an amateur? You can't
always pull down people who are doing well.
But hyeongnim, listen to me,
I will be so regretful.
But, this kind of regret can be changed anytime.
Representative Lee, are you
still not familiar with this line?
If you pull Sin Jin A down now,
you'll only create nonsensical rumors.
~ It obviously wasn't me who sent you away, ~
~ and it obviously wasn't me who left. ~
PD, who do you like more?
Gim Yeon Shik or Gim Gwang Su?
Gim Gwang Su.
Then you must list Gim Gwang Su's
song names while I do the same for
Gim Yeon Shik. How about that?
You still want to say when you can't even
differentiate who sang "Like rain and like music".
Loser must grant a wish.
Good, good.
Right, "Like rain and like music"!
No, I'm not playing, I'm not playing...
10...9...8...
"Although I loved you", "Although I loved you"...
"The four seasons".
"When I was 30 years old".
"Watercolor painting of a rainy day".
Eh...that is not.
It was sung with Kang In Ran and Kong In Ha.
Really good.
Okay, okay. "The story of an old couple".
Wrong! The correct name should be
"The story of a 60 years old couple".
That's right, that's right.
Grant a wish! Grant a wish! Grant a wish!
Wait! Wait...
I'll change it, I'll change it.
Kim Yeon Shik's "The terminal of goodbye".
Bleh...you have obviously lost.
Is this a shop you come to often?
Considered so. I come here everyday.
This wine is very beneficial towards the body.
Today's pork bone soup is amazing.
Are you implying that yesterday's
pork bone soup wasn't any good?
But, PD, you're really handsome.
Do you know me?
Of course, the annoying guy.
Don't be like this, Madam Lee...
Wasn't it what you said?
The annoying city man.
Shall I introduce the both of you?
This is PD Lee,
and this is my mother.
I have always loved listening
to your radio broadcasts.
Although Jin A may be a little ignorant and loves
to throw tantrums, but she is actually a good kid.
If she doesn't listen, I'll
count on you to discipline her.
Since when did i throw tantrums? When did I?
You keep quiet.
And also, Mr. PD,
It's only out of concern that's why I'm saying more.
- I hope you do not misunderstand.
- Yes.
In principle, I am more against office romance.
I'm a bit sorry and afraid that you may
laugh at me for flaunting my daughter.
- But there is nothing I can do
because being pretty is also a kind of sin.
- Mom!
What are you shouting for? You frightened
me that I would have nearly dropped a child.
Oh my, what did I just say?
Be careful, be careful.
You must send her home safely!
Aigoo, aigoo. It must be really exhausting.
That looks really heavy.
My head!
It's a bit unexpected.
What's unexpected?
Nothing, its just...
I didn't expect you to know how
to take of others. Isn't it unexpected?
Of course I can take care of people!
I want to go home! Go Home!
I've to faster get home!
Be careful!
Just find a place to sit.
Right, just now I won the game but I haven't told you my wish.
Tell me your wish then.
Give me a pleasant surprise on my birthday?
When is your birthday?
It will tell you.
That program of yours is really good.
Honestly speaking,
it was my mom who gave me the idea.
When I was younger, the boat my dad was on
went missing at the ocean near Russia.
But, my mom said she likes that word a lot,
missing.
He's not dead, but missing.
Which is why my mom adorns herself everyday,
and not move house.
My dad also loves the way my mom sings,
so she would always be humming a song.
That was where I got my idea from.
This is the first and last gift my dad gave me.
Can you guess what I wrote with it?
What?
"You're My Angel".
My first song.
That song is really nice to listen to.
This is surprising, you actually praised me.
Jin A, your song
has a story behind it.
Of course!
I'm a woman with a story to tell.
You haven't been composing recently?
Not much inspiration.
It's like I lost something from here.
Here, one shot.
Why did you give me so much?
One shot!
Oh my, it's really spicy.
Do you want another cup?
Lee Jae Hyeok, where are you going?
Walk properly, did you hear me?
I'm not going anywhere.
1, 2, 4. 4th one.
2, 4, 3, 4.
That's too funny.
Hey, I drank with a celebrity.
Wait, how did we get here?
Which way?
Please give me a bottle of soju!
I found it, go in that direction.
Over there. Hey, celebrity, let's go.
Let's go together...
Get up!
Where are we?
Mo...motel.
You jerk!
No wonder I felt it was strange,
last night you kept making me drink!
- Calm down a bit.
- What, what, what are you doing?
- Where are you trying to climb? You really...
Wait, wait.
You drank so much yesterday
until you weren't acting like a person.
What? What did you say?
If I'm not a person then what am I?
Don't tell me Dae Geun and I...
- did some inhuman things here?
- No, no, no!
Things weren't like that.
You probably don't remember,
but when I was driving, you asked me to
spit and stuff like that.
You even scolded me a bastard and
said that you didn't want to go home.
Then you suddenly said you wanted to undress...
Bastard, there's no way
I could have acted like that!
Why must you lie?
It's the truth!
Omo, omo!
You see, see, see...
Panty, panty...
Where's your pants?
I asked you where did your pants go?
Annoying.
Yesterday you vomited 4 times
in the middle of the night!
That is why I turned from side to side
without being able to sleep.
It's so early in the morning,
where did I get this bad luck from...
and you even hit me...
Sometimes, whatever expressions are
also unable to make you pleased.
When you feel you're unable to
withstand the pressures of life,
Wonderful Radio hopes to be able to
become your family, friend or lover.
~ eomma, don't give up! I will
accompany you by your side... ~
~ Honey, I love you. ~
Congratulations Miss Sin Jin A!
You are extremely popular!
When are you going to release a new album?
Actually, there are a few songs that aren't too bad...
So, we'll be able to hear your songs once again?
I would also really like to meet my fans again...
-='Only when you're in love then
can you understand true love.' -2065=-
Please don't tell anyone else.
Mr. Dae Geun!
Looks like we are really a match made in heaven.
'Songs that are sung for you'.
Today, we have invited our 13th guest,
29 years old Miss Ru Mi.
She labels herself as a white swan
who becomes a musician for her dream.
So, shall we listen to her story?
Today I would like to dedicate a song to someone
who is none other than DJ Miss Sin Jin A.
Me?
It's really an honor,
thank you.
For more words that I want to say,
I'll like to use my singing to replace it.
Then, let's listen to it together?
~ Why is it that time passes
more slowly when I'm sad? ~
~ Why is it that time takes so long to pass by? ~
~ Am I overcoming it or slowly getting used to it? ~
~ All the pacing back and forth with indecisiveness, ~
~ where exactly is the endpoint? ~
PD,
there is someone who keeps
uploading the same video online.
~ Please let me gradually ~
~ become stronger. ~
No, no...it's not like that.
~ Everything will change. ~
Miss Sin Jin A,
isn't this melody very familiar?
It was my first publication at
a club in Hongdae in 2002.
It is called "Island".
In 2004, I received an invitation
to release an album, but it failed.
The then ultimate female group, Purple,
actually plagiarized my melody.
Miss Ru Mi,
that melody was composed by me.
That's right, it was composed by me...
Seems like you made a mistake.
-=Don't act impulsively,
quickly end the conversation.=-
Don't you know you're wrong?
-= Don't act impulsively,
quickly end the conversation. =-
Don't you know you're wrong?
I just...
-= Hurry! =-
My reason for coming here
is to find my stolen melody.
My reason for coming here is to find my stolen melody.
The melody you stole!
My first song...
Are you able to take responsibility
for what you said just now?
How are you going to prove
you composed that melody?
I have the performance video of last time,
and the song which I just performed myself.
Do you need anymore?
"You're My Angel"?
Purple?
What a joke...
- Hey! You liar!
- Quickly turn off the microphone.
What are you talking about now?
This is a live broadcast, what
do you think you're doing?
Nuna, calm down!
Miss Jin A,
what exactly happened?
You actually shouted and
scolded during a live broadcast,
at least give me an explanation.
So you expected me to
remain calm and composed?
She said I plagiarized her work!
The internet and mail inbox
has the video of her past
performance circulating around.
What exactly is the truth?
You too...
PD, you also...
do not believe me.
I'm leaving.
Miss Jin A!
Don't you even know that under that
kind of circumstances, you should have
turned off the microphone and play music?
Do you know the extent of the damage done?
What will happen to Sin Jin A?
Do you really not know?
From tomorrow onwards, ban her
from the program! Do you understand?
Shouldn't you at least
give her a chance to explain?
Explain what?
Plagiarism?
Whether or not she plagiarized,
since she caused this kind of trouble,
she should have some conscience!
That's why I said that it is a
must to switch Jin A off the program.
I've mentioned before,
if it is Mi Ra,
where would there be such a scenario?
I understand.
That is why,
is it possible to let Mi Ra join that program?
Hyeongnim, how is that feasible?
Like this she will become Jin A's live scapegoat...
That is simply unreasonable.
That's why I'm begging you.
I understand. Since it's hyeongnim's
request, I will consider it carefully.
- Thank you!
- I don't even know when I'll be
able to enjoy your good fortune.
How should I hit this ball?
Oh, In Yeong...
=Hey! Are you okay?=
=At home?=
=Want me to go over and find you?=
=You're alone at home, right?=
=I better come over.=
I'm fine.
Hey! Why are you worried?
=Hey! You're afraid I'll be worried that's why
you are holding it back and not saying, right?=
=I'm really fine with that.=
=No matter what the world says about my past,=
=I am already fine with that.=
=So, don't hold it in like this,=
=voice out what you feel like saying.
Think more about yourself.=
=Okay?=
Okay, enough. Hang up.
=Jin A...=
=Sin Jin A!=
Time really flies.
I've known everyone for already a month.
For me, the audiences are
already like close relatives.
What about everyone?
I'll dedicate my favorite song,
a song by Lee Sin Cheol.
"Super Hero".
How was it?
Just now that was Lee Seung Hwan's song.
You can correct it when the song is over.
Was that how I said it?
I'm really sorry, I will correct it.
PD, when the program ends,
do you want to go and eat sashimi?
I'll treat.
Maybe next time.
Next time is a must!
Are there any recent news about Sin Jin A?
Seems like there is no news regarding her.
Don't know whether she can make a
comeback, I think it is hopeless for her.
Your Wonderful Radio...
did you not know that it nearly died prematurely?
It was proceeding fine,
but the General Manager said that all
the program's personnel, including the PD,
Script Writer and DJ will be changed.
Do you know how Miss Jin A
reacted after finding out?
She actually rushed into the
General Manager's office immediately!
She asked whether did he actually
consider about the hardworking personnel
working behind the scenes?
The General Manager must
have been furious at that time.
What's the use?
She can't even take care of herself...
Excuse me,
is the Director still in a meeting?
I've made an appointment to see him at 2 pm.
Please wait for a moment.
Director, Miss Sin Jin A is still...
Yes, I understand...
~ I did not know that the past memories ~
- ~ would be like this... ~
- Stop, stop.
Sounds like it's lacking feeling.
I assure you, I'll be like a
singer who has just debuted,
one who seriously composes and sings.
- Director, please give me an opportunity, I will...
- Jin A!
The present Sin Jin A
is not comparable with the idol star of before.
The feeling is completely different.
I do not wish to say any further.
Ah, yes, that song just now...
was composed by you, right?
Now Infinite is the most popular.
No they are not, Beast is the most popular!
- Isn't that Sin Jin A?
- Sin Jin A...
That's the person who
plagiarized other people's work.
Hey! It's not the first time
you've came across such people.
She used to think so highly of herself,
look at what she has become now.
That's why I say those who are artists
are different compared to
the person they were before.
Hey, have you heard her attitude
and manner in the past broadcasts?
It is completely disgusting, disgusting.
Hey, let's go, let's go.
She's still holding a guitar, does
she really think she is a singer?
- Stop saying, what if she scolds us?
- Hey, hurry up!
Looks like there is no performance today.
Yes, there isn't.
Recently business also hasn't been too good,
I can't pay them to perform.
Which is why I play music to pass time.
- Are you by any chance a musician?
- Nope.
I suddenly recalled a friend who
performed here 10 years ago.
That's impossible! We've only been open
for 4 years now. It used to be a PC Bang.
(PC Bang - PC Room)
What did you say?
See for yourself if you don't believe.
I want to switch the beauty salon, I don't like this one.
You didn't even patronize that place for long.
They always make me wait very long.
Just tell them about it yourself, silly...
Oh oppa, it's making me anxious.
- People always ask me when my new album is coming out.
- Oh, new album?
I have already spoken with the fatty, Shin Sa Dong,
to let him create a song based on your style and name.
- Really?
- Of course.
Move aside!
- There's still a meeting going on.
- You're playing really happily...
You startled me.
- PD Lee, what is this about?
- Miss Ru Mi,
- ten years ago is it?
- Yes?
You said you performed "Island" in 2002 is that so?
Yes! But why do you suddenly ask this?
A club that opened only in 2007,
yet you could perform there in 2002?
PD Lee, what exactly are you trying to do?
You suddenly rushed into other people's office.
Do you have any manners?
Representative Lee,
how could you do something like that?
Just because of a scumbag like you,
an innocent person who wanted to use
sincerity to host the radio program was wasted!
Scumbag?
- Who do you think you're talking to?
- Call Sin Jin A back.
Hey, PD Lee! PD Lee!
- Faster sleep.
- Hyeong, you really don't understand my heart.
- Why is it whatever I say you still...
- Sleep!
I'm sorry for frightening you, Mr. driver.
It's all right, it's all right. I can
see that he isn't in a very good mood.
- I'll play a cheerful and lighthearted
song for you guys to hear.
- Sure, that's fine.
Oh, this song used to be famous, who sang it?
- Should I give you a hint?
- Okay.
A very famous group.
The predecessor of idol groups as well as
the beginning of idols and then the end.
- Purple...
- Purple!
- Purple, Purple...correct, Purple! I know them.
- So you still remember...
I still remember their dance.
This, this and this, right?
- I also know.
- Sleep!
This is how you dance it, isn't it?
Taking advantage of the good atmosphere,
let me bring you to a fun place.
- You can look forward to it.
- Just drive.
- Mom.
- Why did you come in?
I came by to see whether there
is anything I can help you with.
This is so unlikely, I'm so touched.
If there's nothing, fine.
How is the matter about plagiarism coming along?
Not very good. Mom, how about we...
drink some alcohol?
Are you crazy? But how come
it's so much to my intention?
Cheers!
Eat some side dishes, or else
you will harm your stomach.
- No...
- You learnt your dad's bad habits.
I've got a question for you.
Why is there no news about PD Lee?
How did you know? We even quarreled...
It doesn't seem that way...
It's not what you think, we are
completely unsuitable for each other.
Your character is exactly like your dad.
Do you still think a lot about dad?
Yes, occasionally.
Are you still waiting for him?
Yes...
If your father comes back,
I really want to boast to him
how well I raised you by myself.
- Mom.
- You do not need to worry about me.
Believe me, keep your hopes up!
Okay, I believe.
You should have told me earlier,
I thought you already promised
a date with the children.
But you know...you've
encountered some problems recently.
The parents have quite a few opinions about it.
You experienced a problem on the program and plus
the plagiarism incident, I'm in a really tough spot.
Your mom said you didn't allow
her to tell me where you were,
I had to beg for a long time
before she finally told me.
Thinking about it, I realized I have never
placed myself in your shoes to face the problem.
I should have believed in you.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry,
I have already gotten over it.
Not being able to host the radio
program, and not being able to sing,
were the result of me messing up.
Don't give up on singing.
Remember you once said...
That you already understood what you should sing.
Continue singing.
sunbaenim, so you're actually the producer?
(sunbaenim - respected senior/mentor)
Nothing is certain yet, I haven't
even prepared myself and,
it is a bit abrupt... Wow, hyeong!
Hey, work that doesn't receive
remuneration always feels extremely practical.
Sin Jin A, welcome to my world. It's Dream Factory!
Then, let's begin.
1, 2, 3, 4.
~ I did not know that the past memories ~
~ would be like this, ~
~ gradually... ~
This is the feeling.
~ What has obviously already been discarded, ~
~ is now slowly being recalled. ~
~ I have obviously already forgotten... ~
~ I put my dedication and heart
and soul into loving you, ~
~ I put my dedication, without
retaining any effort to hurt you, ~
~ I put my dedication, and I want to
fall into the river of love once again. ~
~ Not once forgetting the bitterness of love, ~
~ not forgiving myself for
once treating you indifferently, ~
~ I want you to know how much I miss you... ~
~ I put my dedication and heart
and soul into loving you, ~
~ I put my dedication, without
retaining any effort to hurt you, ~
~ I put my dedication, and I want to
fall into the river of love once again. ~
~ Not once forgetting the bitterness of love, ~
~ not forgiving myself for
once treating you indifferently, ~
~ I want you to know how much I miss you... ~
=I sincerely apologize.=
Has Ru Mi's problem been settled?
Yes. I've already told her to
remain abroad for 2 to 3 months.
=I didn't expect it to cause
such a serious consequence.=
It really leaves me speechless.
You also better not make any mistakes, understand?
- Sorry.
- Go out.
=This matter arose all because of me,=
=it is unrelated to anyone else.=
=That is what I'll like to announce.=
There are so much silly incidents in the office...
Not bad...the atmosphere is
harsh and awkward enough.
Just get to the main topic.
Why must you have such a grim attitude?
Since your sudden visit last time,
I learnt and understood a lot.
That's why this time, aren't
I trying to help you guys?
Is this regarding the public broadcast
event of the 1000th episode?
Television and radio will have live broadcasts.
Let's use Representative Lee's manpower to arrange.
That's a good idea,
but I will decide the list of appearances,
and of course you do not need to
worry about Representative Lee's people.
That is of course, you're the PD.
But I'm very curious what
hidden card you have in your hands...
It's Miss Sin Jin A.
No...no, but even if the matter has been settled,
isn't it a bit too early?
I will submit my proposal plan.
- Then, I'll take my leave.
- Hey, PD Lee.
Hey, PD Lee!
Hey, you...
PD Lee...
Do you think the blow is greater if the
radio station has one less capable PD?
Or if the people controlling the program
such as the DJ and others leave
would deal a greater blow?
Representative Lee,
are you trying to threaten me?
It seems that way.
Go ahead and use Sin Jin A,
but wager this.
Give me my handphone.
Here it is.
Where did Yong Shik oppa go?
Representative Lee was looking
for him so he left hastily.
He didn't even tell me my schedule for today.
He asked you to wait for a while.
Mi Ra,
Have you been getting on well?
You actually came to find me. Is there anything?
I...have rumors about being
from a girl's home right?
I don't really want to listen.
That is not a rumor.
During my Secondary 2 school days,
I was on the way home after being dismissed
when I saw my stepfather abusing my mother.
I had to stop him no matter what...
But when I withdrew my actions, I discovered...
that I had already killed him.
It was the day before our last concert,
when a reporter called and said that
he wanted to expose that incident.
Jin A said that,
as long as Purple disbands,
only then can we stop that report.
She said to let her see me being
branded as a murderer my whole life,
is something she couldn't do.
What's the point of you
coming to tell me this now?
I do not care.
I have to go now.
Mi Ra,
don't hate Jin A so much.
I said I do not care.
Please sign your autograph.
You must treasure Sin Jin A's historic
comeback album like it's a family heirloom.
Oh right, about the matter I mentioned
regarding the radio station's reinstatement...
I already said I don't want to work there...
Very soon it will be Wonderful Radio's
1000 episode special broadcast,
I hope that will be Miss Jin A's comeback stage.
I don't have the confidence.
Why? The accomplishments of
Wonderful Radio are all because of you.
So, I hope you will definitely stand on that stage.
I am now formally inviting
you using my status as PD.
I'll count on you.
Oh, and this is my present for you.
Take a look at it when you're home.
Hey, singer Sin Jin A!
Here, I also have a gift for you.
Hey, this...
Are you trying to demonstrate the
strength of your wrist infront of me?
Gift, my gift.
It's okay, it's okay...
=Hyeong, must we really do it like this?=
=What's wrong? Didn't you make a promise?=
=- But hyeong...
- Enough nonsense, quick catch up.=
= - Let's start.
- It's not like this...=
=Hyeong, wait! One more time, wait...=
=Hyeong! I really can't do it!=
=Will she like it even if I do this?=
=Just believe me. A split second of embarrassment
can guarantee you a lifetime of love.=
=Come, it's the 4th take.=
=Does it really have to be like this?=
=Of course, didn't you promise me?=
=Hyeong, just wait and see.
I must take revenge on you.=
=Hyeong, you know that I really can't sing...=
=You're a grown man, why are
you going back on your word?=
Hey! Don't you know
how to bid farewell?
Ajussi! Can you stop playing
songs that are so old?
You, this...this...don't you
know whose song this is?
Whose song?
This...how should I phrase it?
The predecessor of predecessors,
The start of idols...and then the end.
An eternal evil spirit,
and she also doesn't age. Do you know Purple...
This is Purple's "You're My Angel".
Ajussi, let's just go quickly.
Hello?
Hello!
What?
I love you, Sin Jin A!
Sin Jin A!
I have already confirmed the
program's performance sequence.
Do you really have to do this?
Don't you what kind of person
Representative Lee is?
You'll only hurt yourself if
you continue on like this!
General Manager,
I want to do the program
according to my wishes.
I'm sorry.
eonni!
eonni...
How have you been?
You've become more beautiful.
It was tough, wasn't it?
It was tough, because you weren't around.
Eonni, hurry up. Yong Shik oppa
wants you to get out quickly.
Where did you get this from?
Oh, at the terminal...
But, so what if she releases a new album?
It can't change anything as it is over for her.
But...will Sin Jin A really
perform at this public broadcast?
If she really comes, Representative Lee
will surely not give up so easily.
Oppa, its me.
I'll be there soon.
=Okay, come quickly.=
That...oppa.
=Why? Tell me, what is it? Why, why, why...=
It's regarding Jin A going on stage today.
=No need to worry, I'll see what
to do about it, believe me.=
No, it's not like that...
- =What's wrong?=
- I no longer bother whether
or not Jin A goes onto the stage.
=What are you talking about?=
=Don't talk nonsense.=
=And Mi Ra, this isn't just about you.
It also concerns my self-esteem.=
=Furthermore, even if Sin Jin A comes, there
is no way she'll be able to stand on the stage.=
=Do you understand? I'm hanging up!=
Oppa. Oppa!
Eonni, we have to faster go.
Come out quickly!
- Have the guests being checked?
- Yes.
Hey, did you know that Miss Jin A is here?
If you're glad then at least smile a bit...
Okay, it's the last commercial.
Okay.
1...2...cue!
Hello everybody, today we finally usher in
Wonderful Radio's 1000 episode.
Thank you everyone for being able to
attend this rather significant activity today.
Today's spectators also consists of a lot of
lead characters who had shared
their life experiences with us before.
Im Sul Ki! Im Sul Ki!
Wonderful Radio, wonderful life,
will now officially begin.
I heard that you released a new album.
I should have at least congratulated you
through Kakao Talk, but I was so busy
that I forgot about it.
(Kakao Talk - messaging app for phones)
I have to prepare for the performance,
can you just come to the main point?
What's so urgent?
When Purple disbanded, I should
have insisted keeping you.
Mi Ra is good at everything,
except that she doesn't have the tenacity.
But you do.
Your tenacity of being able to bet
on the PD's life and go on stage,
is something Mi Ra is unable
to do. It's a little regretful.
What did you just say?
PD's life?
PD Lee's life.
Nuna!
Your dongsaeng is really tall.
(dongsaeng - younger brother)
I will appreciate it well.
PD, something big went wrong.
Jin A nuna is now...
Hurry, hurry...
Why? What's wrong with Jin A nuna?
What's wrong? Faster tell me what's wrong!
Why didn't you tell me what
you wagered on this stage?
Do you think my heart will feel
comfortable by you doing this?
I cannot step on this stage.
Are you running away?
Have you not thought about the
spectators who are waiting to hear you sing?
More importantly, those who
support you are waiting for you.
Purple disbanded and the
accusation of plagiarism was fake...
Do you think by sacrificing yourself,
you'll be able to help others?
Just sing, do it for yourself,
and...do it for me.
Oh, mom.
=My princess, did you remember to eat?=
No...
=Hey! You have to eat in order to sing well...=
=Jin A, mom and dad will be here to hear you sing,=
=so don't be nervous and do well.
Do you understand?=
=Wretch, why are you not saying anything?=
=Our Jin A, faster get over it and come home
soon. Tonight, let's drink till our fill, okay?=
- I understand.
- =What?=
- I said I understand. Let's hang up.
- =Fighting!=
Prepare the lines.
Next, we will like to invite the
last guest of our second segment.
Speaking about Wonderful Radio,
we certainly cannot forget to mention her, right?
Since the beginning of Wonderful Radio till
now, she has always been a guardian by our sides.
Only until not long ago, she has
always been the center of Wonderful Radio.
She was also once the leader
of Purple, Miss Sin Jin A.
Please welcome her with a
warm round of applause.
Hello. To be able to once again
greet everyone in Wonderful Radio,
makes me really happy. I am singer Sin Jin A.
During the time when Purple was active
and when I was hosting Wonderful Radio,
I used to often say 'thank you'
and 'I love you' to everyone.
Actually, those were only what
were written in the script,
and not because of my sincerity.
The reason for me returning here is because...
I feel that I can now really
sincerely say to everyone
thank you, and I love you.
To me, Wonderful Radio is a kind of love.
After leaving here in that way, I have
really missed this stage and everyone as well.
Everyone...thank you.
I love you.
Next, I'll like to perform for everyone
my song called "Again". Thank you.
Where are you going?
Come back quickly, this is a live broadcast.
Turn off the lights!
Wait. What do you think you're doing?
Hyeongnim, hyeongnim...do you
think I'm doing a non-profitable sale?
From today onwards, our DJ and
everyone else will withdraw from SBS!
(SBS - South Korean television and radio network)
- Withdraw then.
- All to be withdrawn!
- What did you say?
- I asked you to withdraw everyone.
Even without you, there is a whole row of people
who wants to collaborate with us. Do you know?
You just try and see. I will ban everyone from
your company from entering the television station.
Hyeongnim, that wasn't what I meant...
- Wait...
- Please go out, please go out.
- Hyeongnim, please don't misunderstand my intention.
- Please go out.
I will wait for you at the cafe near the entrance.
Aigoo, not like he's a hooligan.
I've searched for you for a long time.
But then, what kind of relationship do we have?
We are not meeting with the
identities of PD and DJ, right?
Yes.
What kind of PD would even bet this on a ex-DJ?
This...is what the General Manager gave you.
I also have something to give you.
Here, house beat...
and to cultivate the mood, there
will be some rock and then shouting...
How was that?
Yes, yes...I also don't feel this is very good.
Then let's take a look at this. Here, there's
another one. Here...a sorrowful lyrical song.
The prelude will be 'I love you, I love you'.
Baek Ji Young originally wanted
this song but I refused and hid it,
to keep it for you.
Just 3 minutes. Just 3 minutes.
Remake of senior Lee Mi Ja's
best-selling song, "Miss Dong Baek".
This is the hip-hop version. This part...
~ Dong Baek ~...I used the staggered beat here.
~ With 200 people standing in a row,
let them all wear shorts. ~
~ Miss...Dong...Baek... ~
This song really causes people
to have goose-bumps, right?
- You've worked hard.
- No, no, no! Wait...it's not like that.
Jin A!
=This is a beautiful early morning,
I am Gim Jang Wan.=
=Hello everybody, this is
Love Game's Pak So Hyeon.=
=The next song I'm going to broadcast
is an  extremely special song.=
=She got rid of the social stigma of
plagiarism and has finally started over.=
=- She was once Purple's leader...
- Once Purple's leader.=
=and was also once the DJ of
Wonderful Radio, Miss Sin Jin A.=
=Yes, she overcame a period of difficulty,
and has since released a new album.=
=We all also understand that kind of feeling right?=
=What? It is said that all the songs were
personally composed and written by her.=
=It is really inspiring and also very amazing.=
=May everyone also please cheer her on,=
=to let her feel the strength her
audiences and friends are giving her.=