We'll have very special guests
in the studio.
I'm Shin Jina and you're listening
to Wonderful Radio.
LOVE ON-AIR
Here's your script.
Thank you.
Aren't you tired, Baby Bun?
I am very much.
You should cut back on coffee.
You're not getting any younger.
I'II get the most expensive facial treatment
when my album comes out.
Ha ha, very funny.
Your script for part 3 and 4.
Who are they?
Coby Girls.
It's not Dalshabet?
Can we please get someone
that people actually know?
I'm more than grateful that
they agreed to come on the show.
Go into the studio.
PIease book a boy band next week.
Can we get Beast?
Two, three...
Hi! We're Coby Girls!
How pretty you all are!
Let's have a good show.
We'II do our best!
My word of advice would be
'always be polite.'
I didn't think much of it back in the day
when I was in Purple.
You were a singer?
You haven't heard of Purple?
You mean Iike
Tinky Winky?
10 seconds to go, Jina.
Sure.
In part 3 and 4,
we'II be with the new girl group,
Coby Girls.
Hi, everyone!
We're Coby Girls!
They are sensational,
energetic,
audacious and clueless
Iike the fish in the pond.
Wow!
Thank you so much!
We'II start part 3 with
Coby Girls' hit single,
Get out boy!
So you don't know
who Purple is?
How old are you?
- I'm twenty-one.
- Eighteen!
Back in 2004,
when Korea was...
Get out, boy
Out of my Iife
Great song!
How do I know this tune?
Hang on a second.
Recording was so hard...
Shut up for a minute!
Bro!
You gotta check this out.
It's genius.
Shin Jina is here.
- What?
- It's Jina.
- Oh shit!
- You!
Listen to me, honey.
Calm down, Jina.
We need to talk.
That song was meant for me!
Let's take a seat first.
- Open this door!
- PIease?
- Don't touch me!
- Let him explain.
Let go of me!
PIease.
Get over here.
Get your ass over here, now!
Honey, I know you're really pissed.
I understand.
I totally sympathize with you.
But!
You gotta gather your senses
especially...
You wrote this song for me.
But once I got the Iyrics...
It was suitable for a girl group.
Hey!
My wife is due next month.
We're having twins.
It means double the cost
of everything.
I'm in a tight spot.
And more importantly,
girl groups are the trend.
I'm very disappointed in you.
I'm not taking songs from you
ever again!
- See you Iater, sir.
- Jina, wait!
Ouch!
What's on schedule tomorrow?
I'II text it to you
when I get home.
Tell me now.
You're booked
for a special private concert
for Sangmun elementary reunion,
class of 89.
What?!
I, Shin Jina, is to sing
at an elementary class reunion?
Cancel it.
Our overdraft account is
almost maxed out
and I have no money
to buy shampoo.
I told you my album is
coming out soon.
Hi!
Hello, Mrs. Shin.
How are you?
Grab some supper.
Hey!
Well, actually... I have to Iook over
tomorrow's schedule.
So, maybe next time.
- Bye.
- Stay! Wait!
Why are you being such a bitch to him?
There is no-one Iike him.
Be nice.
You're not even
paying him properly.
Why didn't you
take the day off?
I'm refreshed
and ready to work.
You never Iisten to me.
It not Iike you have any customer.
Don't be silly.
Hello!
PIease, come in.
You see?
Six people! Yay!
What a pretty girl!
This is the best spot
in the neighborhood.
What should we get?
I'II bring you the menu.
Won't be a moment.
Jina...
I celebrate two Christmases
every year.
One in December
and one in June.
This is the week I decided
to call summer Christmas week.
I haven't decided what
I'm going to ask Santa
for this Christmas in June.
Why don't you
put your June wishes
in the wish box
for Santa Clause
who must be bored to death
at this time of the year.
PIease don't Iet me
be Ionely this Christmas.
In part 2, we'II have
text messages from Iisteners.
It's people
that frustrate you
but also people that
turn dispair into hope.
Thank you, for the nice quote
and flowers.
Here is your requested song
from After School...
Actually, can I play
my request today?
It's Purple's
"You're my Angel"
- What's she doing?
- Hmm.
The producer of this show
who's been with us for 4 years
is taking a temporary Ieave
to have her baby.
This is from my heart.
Best of Iuck and see you again soon.
She's filling up the time
with her old songs?
You asked for me?
Take a seat.
Let me cut to the chase. I want you
to take charge of Wonderful Radio.
You mean Yun's show?
The ratings are atrocious.
They'II talk about dropping Jina
in the fall program reshuffle.
But the show is Iike
Yun's baby.
And the ratings reflect her Iove,
at only 2 percent.
I'II take care of Yun.
I need you to bring in
a fresh touch to the show.
- Lock up when you Ieave.
- Sure.
You should go home time to time.
See you Iater.
- See ya.
- Bye.
- Where are you going, man?
- Did you bring my spec 55 back?
I forgot.
I'II bring it next time.
- Can't use that because of you.
- AIright. I'm sorry.
What bring you here?
Heard you're joining us
as new producer.
Wonderful Radio.
- Beer?
- Give me one.
How come
they're sending you?
You can't play the songs
you Iike on our show.
- What is she Iike?
- Jina?
She's a princess.
The type I detest.
You're not exactly
her type either.
I guess.
Can you drive properly
for once?
You know this van used to make
squealy noise when I brake?
I had it Iooked at
at the service station.
See if you can still hear it.
Cha Dae-geun!
Shall I give her a call?
Hurry!
What took you so Iong?
Do you have make-up remover?
- What do you need it for?
- I got smudges.
I heard the new producer
is a bit of an ass.
- I heard that, too. A total asshole.
- Shutsh.
He's here?
For a while already.
How are you, sir?
I'm Shin Jina's trusted manager.
- You know, rumors are just...
- What's the time now?
We had to wait for the Ms Shin
for half an hour. What do you think?
Well, the traffic was terrible
for one...
We made introductions
before you arrive.
My thought is that we keep
most of the structure as it is.
There is one thing though.
Love Equation of My Life
It's just too corny.
I Iike that segment.
And the Iisteners Iove it too.
Besides, a bit of corniness
does good for the ratings.
- Aren't I right? Right?
- Who said that Iisteners Iove it?
I want ideas for a new segment
by 1 1 :00 tomorrow morning.
- That's a Iittle...
- too short-noticed.
Hey, you can't google new ideas
from off their heads.
Don't you know how hard it is
to come up with a new segment...
Isn't that what
writers are for?
Why do you keep
interrupting me?
Since this is our first meeting,
we should make introductions
and have a group dinner
or drinks to break the ice.
Aren't I right? Right?
You have beautiful eyes.
I get that a Iot.
I gotta go.
Esprresso with extra shot
for a chic city man...
Damn!
Lower down slowly
one vertebra at a time.
- Move to Jungle postion.
- Hi, sweetie.
Hey you!
How is Producer Yun?
Is she doing okay?
She went to have her baby.
Who's taking her place?
We got a new producer.
- A male?
- Yes.
but he is a total BCM.
A BIase City Man?
No, a Big-headed City Moron.
Well, the real morons were...
Coby Girls?
I could have given them a good smack.
If only I met them
back in the day.
We were the business
Remember the sound we used to
hear every weekend?
Ans this weeks No. 1 goes to...
Puuuurple!
I would Iike to thank
all our fans and
our supporters from "Purple Scent".
I Iove every one of you!
PIease give it up for Purple
performing "You're my Angel"!
? You are my angel, angel,
angel to me
? I'll cherish your love
forever and ever
? You're my angel...
See you all again.
We Iove you!
I miss the days.
Camera,
- Roll!
- 3 of 23,
Action!
Cut! That Iooks good.
Stop. That's enough.
Hey, camera!
Get a close-up.
Was that an okay, director?
Okay.
I said okay already.
You did great, Mira.
Cut! Cut! That's good.
Fanstastic.
- One more take!
- We got no time.
- Are we making a movie here?
- Fine. That was great, Mr. Lee.
You should think about
making commercials in series.
They used good old Mama Kim
for the seasoning commercial
for decades
and the same grizzly bear
for Iiver supplelment ads.
Segi Hearing Aid campaign went on
for a decade with just the Ieft ear.
The fat-and-tall duo practically
grew old with the pump company.
- Think along the same Iine with Mira.
- Yes, sir.
I'm having great days
because of your boys and girls.
I owe it all to you.
Especially the 1 0 o'clock girl group,
what are they called again?
- Pink Dolls?
- That's right!
The rating is fantastic.
You did good
picking the right host.
1 0 O'clock Iisteners are
mostly students
so girl or boy band is right.
6 o'clock is all about people
getting off work and taxi drivers.
so, you want a popular face,
Someone Iike Yun Mira, for example.
What do you think?
- Mira?
- Yeah.
- Sounds good.
- Right?
That's right.
Nan-sol put a Iot of thought
into that.
And?
How can you dismiss her Iike that
when she tried so hard?
I don't care about working hard.
I care about doing well.
There are three virtues
that make a good radio host.
Popularity, talent and personality.
Shouldn't you have
at Ieast one of them?
Why are you telling me this?
I want you to refrain from displaying
your emotion during a meeting.
What's it gonna take?
4 percent.
Only 4?
You never surpassed 2 percent
in the Iast 6 months.
You shouldn't be hung up on the past.
You should dream big.
Why don't you come up with
an idea for a new segment, then?
Me? Ha ha ha...
Why not?
I can totally do it.
I'II do it.
No problem.
I can do it.
I'II Iook forward to it, then.
Where did he come from?
What am I supposed to do?
Shall we get the next one?
Never mind.
Oh, hi!
Long time.
I Iike your TV series.
I'm glad you Iike it.
But I'm sorry.
I never get the chance to
Iisten to your radio
when that's the only thing
you do.
You gotta do better
than that, Jina.
After walking out
on Purple Iike that!
Bye.
You're my angel, angel,
angel to me
I'II cherish your Iove
forever and ever.
Jina!
You're perfect today
Iike you were yesterday.
There is nothing
I want to ask of you.
The way you Iook at me
makes me feel great.
I can understand
your every gaze.
You read my mind.
I give all my heart to you.
I only want to give you joy
You're my angel, angel,
angel to me.
I'II cherish your Iove
forever and ever.
I got mid-terms tomorrow!
But you're way more important
than exams to me!
I'm nobody without you.
You're my angel.
One more time! One more time!
You're not gonna make
the announcement now, are you?
Don't, Jina.
Give it another thought, please.
It doesn't have to be today.
Thank you all for coming
to our show tonight.
Tonight,
I would Iike to make
an important announcement.
As of this moment,
Purple is splitting up.
No! Is she serious?
Thank you guys...
for all your Iove and support.
Extend the other arm
to the side.
Look at the tip of the hand.
Those who can, fold your arm
and Iock your hands together.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Breathing in slowly,
expanding your Iungs
and chest.
Breathe out and relax
your strained muscles.
Focus only on yourself
during the practice.
How do you know each other?
He's the new producer
I told you about.
From the radio?
The BCM?
Hey!
How do you know each other?
Don't you know
Ji In-yeong from Purple?
You don't know me?
The curvaceous In-yeong?
Right...
- Namaste.
What!
- What's wrong with him?
- You forgot your push-ups.
Can't wear them
during yoga!
Good to meet you.
Let's work hard.
Why don't you
take them out for dinner?
Yes, sir.
See you around.
Are we goddamn Unicef?
They Iook Iike orphans
from third world.
What are you going to do
about me?
Give me some time.
It's sweeps week soon.
Are you sure about this?
We have the hottest
hosts and DJs.
What have you got
to worry about?
So, take care of this
once and for all.
Taking care of things is
what I do.
Let's get something to eat.
- Hey, man.
- What's up?
I heard about it. Is it true?
...that I moved to 6 o'clock?
I mean working with Shin Jina.
- Do you know her?
- Of course.
She was a regular on our show
in the Purple days.
They were great.
I Ioved their song.
You're my angel...
I ran into her the other day.
She asked me about you.
- What did you tell her?
- That you're an asshole.
Well, you are.
AII the hosts despise you.
Anyway, be good to her.
She's not what she seems.
She's Ioyal, sexy and
has a pure soul.
Unlike you, asshole.
How's yoga working out?
It's driving me up the wall.
I'm so stiff.
You need to have flexible mind
as well as your body.
It's all about the Yoga Fire.
- You know what I'm saying?
- Sure, bro.
- The whole namaste deal.
- That's right.
- Hey,
- Hmm?
Don't drink-and-broadcast again.
Technically,
it was 'after'-drinks broadcasting.
- That's right.
- Don't mention that again.
- AImost destroyed us.
- That was a sweaty moment.
- See you around.
- A nightmare.
You want a drink Iater?
- I'II call you.
- Sure. See ya.
They say even a person who brushes
your sleeve is predestined by your karma.
Look around you.
At this very moment in time,
those around me are
my predestined fates.
So are all of you out there who'II be
Iistening to me for the next 2 hours.
You're Iistening to Wonderful Radio,
and I'm your host, Shin Jina.
I have in front of me, the new producer
for our show, Mr. Lee Jin-hyeok.
He's a cool guy
who only drinks iced coffee.
Let's do a good job together.
Ideas for new segment?
How dare you!
Next song, Nan-sol.
- Here is the first song.
- Rady?
Sistar sings "How dare you".
y shoulders feel stiff
around this time.
We'll change song to
"Like Rain, Like Music"
The opening song
for part 3 is
also a perfect song
for a rainy day Iike today.
It's "Like Rain Like Music"
by Kim Gwang-seok.
Who's song is this?
Oh, is it by Kim Hyeon-sik?
I'II make correction
after the song.
And you're off the hook?
Hey, it was a mistake.
I get the two mixed up
all the time.
How can you get them
mixed up?
Hey, we're in the middle
of a Iive show.
- Let go of me.
- Get out of there.
And, you call yourself a singer?
Get out!
Did you see that?
Did you see me slam the table?
What they say about you was true.
- They can't hear me outside, right?
- No.
You're a dog!
You're goddamn dog.
- He must have gotten my message.
- I feel dizzy.
Walk on your paws, bastard!
So, the rumor was true.
Pretty-face,
you got some time?
I got time
but no energy.
Are you still mad?
What's wrong with him?
He's a damn psycho!
You know...
If someone bad-mouthes the music
I Ioved in my 20s,
you can feel offended as if
they're insulting my memories.
I wasn't insulting.
I just got the names wrong.
If anyone referred to
Purple as Pink,
I know I'd flip out
there and then.
This is his heydays.
Listen to it on your way home.
It gets further
?and further away.
?what I thought was
?a lingering youth
?Within my emptying heart,
?l can't find anything anymore.
?Even though the seasons returns,
BCM - Today is deadline
for new segment ideas
You got cold?
Mom, shall I quit radio?
Do as you please.
I don't care
if you sing in a cabaret.
How can you talk that way
to your daughter?
I'm Shin Jina from Purple!
I'm not done.
I'II sing again.
Quiet down, will you?
This all started from the day
you started that radio show.
? How long should I live
? before I see you again
? Over the river of time,
our love sways
That's it.
Mom, that's it! I got it.
Yes!
What's gotten into her?
Start gathering stories
so we can start next week.
I told you
he would Iike it.
I used to win essay comepetition
back in elementary school.
Let's go!
- One, two, three,
- Go!
This is a new segment from the show,
The Song I Sing to You
The first guest we have on the show
is a 22-year-old soldier
who took time off
his precious Ieave.
Shall we hear it from him?
My name is Jeong Gwang-tae.
I'm serving in Cheolwon.
I came in to talk about this girl
that I have a crush on
who won't return my feelings.
I went AWOL Iast year
because of her
and got in some serious trouble
for that.
You should never go that far.
Shall we hear your song then?
With all my heart,
I would Iike to sing.
Jeong Yeob's 'Nothing Very.'
Let's hear it from him.
'Nothing Better'
Lim Seul-gi, English Major
at Hanyang University!
I'II be your boyfriend
after I get out of the army.
- Wait for me!
- Calm down
and Iet's hear you sing,
'Nothing Better'
Suyuri angel, Lim Seul-gi!
Lim Seul-gi!
? Rest in me like in the dreams
and stay with me forever
Are you okay, Seul-gi?
Would you be okay,
if you were her?
? I would always stay
by your side
? Nothing better,
nothing better than you
For crying out Ioud!
I'II kill him!
? Nothing better...
Nothing better than you
Driver,
please turn off the radio!
We had tons of complaints and
criticisms abour your Iittle stunt.
This is actually a good segment.
If you give it some time...
Raising the ratings is good but
why don't we just drop the program
in the next reshuffle?
Excuse me?
Think about it, okay?
What are you doing here?
Did you get told off?
Did you think
I got praises for that?
I'm sorry.
About what?
- Well, it was my idea...
- I made the decision.
I take responsibility for my decisions.
That's part of my job.
Don't worry.
I'II take care of my team.
Are you trying
to blow up the car?
Why didn't you
get it checked?
What are you gonna do
if I'm Iate?
I am so sorry.
Grab a taxi. Now!
How are you supposed to get
taxi in the middle of the bridge?
Save us! PIease!
Help!
I Iove your show.
Thank you.
You have a beautiful child
and a gorgeous wife.
What a nice picture!
Would you Iike to hear a story?
Here's the script.
Where is she?
She changed the guest Iast minute?
She's here.
The Song I Sing to You
We have in the studio
a 42-year-old cab driver.
Would you Iike
to tell us your story?
Hi!
What's today's story about?
Shutsh!
I have a Ietter for my wife
which I never got to send her.
That why I came
on the show today.
Hi, honey!
It's me, Ji-hyeong.
It's been almost 3 years
since you went to heaven.
I want to say sorry first
for putting you
through a hard Iife.
I'm sorry
I never wrote you a Ietter
when you were still
with me.
I practiced the Dongmulwon song
that you Iiked.
You used to tease
for being a terrible singer.
So, hear me out.
Honey,
our Iittle girl is diagnosed with...
... with cancer.
Like you.
You must miss her terribly.
I know, honey. But I can't
Iet her go to you just yet.
PIease make her
healthy again.
So, she'II grow and get married
and have babies that Iook Iike you.
PIease don't take her away.
Let her stay with me.
I beg you.
I'm so sorry.
Excuse me.
? I want my hot lips to touch
your soft lips
? So that you can feel
my love in your heart
? Ifyou still don't know how I feel
? I will love you
? more than anyone
in the world
? I will love you always
? I will always love you
Iike Ilove you this moment
? I will love you
? more than anyone
in the world
?l will love you always
?I'll always love you
?like I love you this moment
?l will love you
?more than anyone
?in the world
- Hello, Mr. Lee!
- Hi.
Why did you say hi?
He is your dad.
- Urgh!
- Hey, wait.
Forget it.
- Wait!
- No!
Did you have dinner,
sweetheart?
Answer your dad.
Forget it.
- Mister?
- Yes, honey.
Don't you say hi
to my friends.
Oh... Sorry about that.
- Da-heui!
- Leave her alone.
She's at the age.
I don't get to see you much
these days,
so I'll leave this here.
I want you to do
what you love doing best.
I love it when your sing.
You're daddy's number one girl.
To me, you're the best
in the world.
Happy birthday, sweetheart!
Thank you.
Congrats!
I owe it all to you.
Congratulations.
Is something
I can take credit for?
You write, too?
I've written tons of songs.
I didn't expect that.
What do you mean?
You're an ex-girl group member.
What about that?
Girl groups aren't supposed
to write music?
What are you doing here still?
That bastard producer is
keeping you...
Oh, good afternoon.
I'II be at the car.
Hope you have a good afternoon.
Every single week,
he never skips once.
A florist?
Whoever he is,
he must be a scentful man.
You'd think, eh?
- Hi.
- Hey.
This is today's
guest info and story.
Make sure Jina reads it
before we start.
She picked this story herself.
Hi, everyone!
- Hey!
- How are you?
Hello...
- Here you are.
- Thanks.
Listen to what?
Honey?
Da-heui just texted me
and told me to turn on the radio.
The radio?
"The Song I Sing to You"
We have a sweet highschool girl
in the studio today.
- Hi, there?
- Hi.
My name is Yun Da-heui.
I'm a junior at high school.
Would you Iike to tell us
your story and your song?
Dad, can you hear me?
I'm on the radio
that you used to adore.
You know
mom got remarried.
To this ugly-Iooking man.
But,
he is real good to mom.
Mom and I had it real hard
since you died.
But that ugly man
who I really really hate
he says he is so happy
to have a daughter Iike me.
If it's okay with you, dad,
I want to accept him as family.
I'm so sorry I've been a brat.
And thank you for the present...
Dad.
? I wish you knew
how I felt
? even though
I couldn't come closer
? How much I wanted to
? my tears say it all
? We loved each other
and loathed each other
? You cared for me more than anything
and I miss you so much
I never got close even
when you were with me
? Oh did I hate you!
? Please hear me out
Hear my story
? I need more time
? We loved each other
and loathed each other
? You treasured me more than anything
and I miss you so much
? I never got it out of my chest
? but, I really really loved you
You have a good eye
for picking stories.
I do what I can.
I have a question for you.
What does this show
mean to you?
It's a space
where I tell my stories
Before, at Ieast.
Now it's different.
I Iisten to others' stories,
share the stories and console them.
and I end up getting consoled.
I Iearn a Iot.
I want to do music.
I feel as if I finally know
what I want to talk about.
Jina!
- Oh, Jina! You won't believe this.
- Ouch! Hot!
You won't believe this.
It's all over Youtube and
is taking over the internet.
Hello?
How have you been, Mr. Bae?
You'd Iike an interview?
How Iong you been with her?
- 3 days.
- 3 days?
- Sounds Iike a serious stuff.
- Yeah, only 3 more days...
That's commitment.
I'm thrilled for you, man.
?You're my angel, angel,
?angel to me.
?I'll cherish your love
?forever and ever.
?You're perfect today
?like you were yesterday.
?There is nothing
?l want to ask of you.
This is all we got time
for this evening.
It's a Iovely evening
with cool breeze.
How about some soju
and pork bone soup?
There is a song that comes
to my mind on a day Iike this.
Lee Seung-hwan sings
'Darkness and Star Lights'
It's a Kim Hyeon-sik Song
Lee Seung-hwan's warm voice
tugging at your heart string...
Is there is a remake version
by Lee Seung-hwan?
We'II Iisten to this Iast song
and sign off for the night.
Hope you have a wonderful evening.
I hear Wonderful Radio
really hit it off.
As you heard,
Jae-hyeok did a great job.
Congratulations, bro.
What's going to happen
to our arrangement?
Come on,
you know how it works.
I can't pull down someone
who's doing well.
Listen, man.
I'm in the position
of asking you favors.
But position can always change,
you know?
You know how things work
in this business.
If I drop Shin Jina now,
it'II only stir up gossips.
?It's not like I let her go.
Jae-hyeok,
who do you Iike best?
Kim Hyeon-sik or Kim Gwang-seok?
Kim Gwang-seok.
Then, Iet's play a game.
You name all the Kim Gwang-seok songs,
and, I'II name Kim Hyeon-sik songs.
How about it?
Forget it. You can't even get
'Like Rain Like Music' right.
Loser must do a favor
for the winner.
Sounds fun!
'Like Rain Like Music'
I'm not playing.
Ten, nine,
- Eight,
- Eight...
'I Loved You but'
'Spring Summer Fall Winter'
'Around Thirty'
'Watercolor on a Rainy Day'
But, that's not his song.
He sang it with
Gang In-won and Gwon In-ha.
She's right.
AIright. Fine.
'Story of an OId Couple'
Wrong answer!
Learn your songs.
The correct title is
'Story of an OId Couple in 60s'
- Hurrah.
- Yay, I won!
- Wish! Wish!
Wish! Wish!
Wait a minute.
Swap over.
I'II do Kim Hyeon-sik.
- Boo!
- Boo you. You Iost.
Is this your favorite restaurant?
I guess.
I come here everyday.
This Iiquor does wonders
for your health.
Thank you.
Ma'am, the soup is amazing today!
When wasn't it ever?
You're a real handsome man.
Uh... do you know me?
Of course! Mr. BCM.
What are you doing, Mrs. Lee?
But you call him BCM.
Big-headed City Man, right?
I forgot to make
the introduction.
This is Mrs. Lee,
the owner of this restaurant
and my mother.
I Iisten to your show religiously.
My Jina has a bit of a temper
but in the core,
she is really an angel.
PIease guide her and treat her well.
I don't have a temper.
Shut up.
And I may be worrying for nothing,
- but I Iet me just say this.
- Yes, ma'am.
I'm against office relationship.
It might sound Iike
an oblivious bragging but
she is so pretty and as her mother
it's only natural to worry...
Mom!
What! I almost shit my pants,
damn it!
Oops... I'd better go.
Careful.
- Make sure she gets homes.
- Sure.
She Iooks heavy.
He's a good man.
Oh, my head.
This is a surprise.
What is?
I mean
your Iooking after everyone.
I always do.
I'm getting another drink!
- Hey!
- Calm down, darling.
Take a seat
wherever you want.
I didn't say my wish
from the game.
Go on, then.
A surprise present
for my birthday.
When is your birthday?
This will tell you.
I really Iike
your new segment.
I got the idea from mom.
When I younger, my dad's fishing boat
went missing in Russian Sea.
Mom said
she Iike the word.
'Missing'
Not deceased by missing.
So she always wears make-up
and we never moved house.
My dad Ioved mom's singing.
So, she always hums it.
That's where I got the idea.
This is the first and Iast gift
that my dad ever got me.
You know
what I wrote with it?
What was it?
My first song, 'You're My Angel.'
It's a good song.
You're actually paying complement?
Your song has a story.
Oh, I'm a gal with stories.
You don't write any more?
I can't.
Something's missing here.
Bottoms up!
You poured a Iot more for me.
Bottoms up.
Man, it's strong.
One more?
Hey you!
Where are you going?
- You talking to me?
- Walk straight.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm way past my Iimit.
Two, three, four.
I'm feeling great.
I had drinks with a celebrity.
Where are we going now?
I want more soju.
Let's go that way.
Come on, celebrity.
Come on!
Go away.
Where are we?
We're at a motel.
You, fucking pervert!
Is that why you tried so hard
to get me drunk?
Calm down, Nan-sol.
Don't come up here,
you monster!
Hey, wait! Wait!
You weren't...
really human Iast night.
What?
Are you saying that we were
Iike animals here together, you and I?
No no no no no.
That's not what I'm saying.
So, you don't remember.
I was driving
and you were Iike...
you were spitting at me.
Remember?
You were calling me names.
Said you weren't going home.
Then, you said you were transforming
and started taking off your clothes.
Liar!
I would never do that!
But I'm telling the truth.
What have you got there?
Look at you!
In your boxers.
Where are your pants? Huh?
What did you do to me?
You threw up on my pants!
It was gross.
I couldn't sleep because of that.
Grossed me out.
I threw up washing my pants.
There are times
when nothing consols you.
When the burden is too heavy.
Wonderful Radio would Iike to be
your family, your friend and Iover.
Cheer up, Mommy
We're always here for you
I Iove you darling dearly
Wait outside.
Contratulations! Your show is
the talk of the town.
Will we be hearing
your new album soon?
I've been actually getting
some offers.
Then it won't be very far off.
Hopefull not.
What are you doing here?
We can only Iearn about Iove...
PIease keep this
a secret from Jina.
Dae-geun,
we were meant for each other.
The Song I Sing to You
we have 1 3th guest on the show.
She is 29 years old
and describes herself
as umemployed wannabe musician.
Shall we hear her story?
This song I'm singing today
is dedicated to you, Miss Shin.
To me? What a great honor.
Thank you!
I'II tell my story
through this song.
A round of applause for her?
?Why do moments of crisis
?pass so slowly?
?Why is time of endurance
?always so long?
?Am I getting over it
?or just getting used to it?
?What's at the end
?of all this wandering?
Someone is posting
a Youtube Iink on our website.
?Make you stronger
If this was written in 2002,
?Make yourself stronger
No... It can't be.
?Never change
You recognize this melody,
don't you?
This is the song called "Island"
which I wrote and released back in 2002.
I was approached about an album deal
but it fell through.
Because the hottest girl band
at the time, Purple
released a song
with the same melody.
But, I wrote this song.
You must be mistaken.
Don't get heated up
I'm mistaken?
I came here to get my song back.
Just close up the song
The song that you stole from me.
Can you vouch
for your accusation?
How can you prove
that this song is yours?
The footage of me performing it.
And the song I just sang.
What more do you need?
You're My Angel?
Purple?
My ass...
You fucking psycho!
Turn off the mic! Now!
What are you saying?
- Jina, calm down.
- Jina.
- You want me to say it?
- Jina, please.
You're telling a Iie on-air.
- Calm down, Jina.
- Jina.
PIease calm down.
Jina, what happened in there?
You cursed and blurted out
on a Iive show.
Am I supposed to say nothing?
She accused me of plagiarism.
Footages with dates are
being posted on our website.
How do you explain that?
You're Iike the rest of them.
You don't believe me, do you?
I gotta go.
Jina!
You should have shut down
the mic and played music.
What's going to happen to Jina?
You're asking me?
She's axed forever!
She must be given a chance
to explain herself.
Explain what?
PIagiarism is a secondary issue.
She acted irresponsibly on the Iive show.
What did I tell you?
We should've changed her.
Mira would have never
made a mistake Iike that.
Since you mention it,
will it be possible for Mira to fill in?
Come on, bro.
That makes Mira a stand-in.
You're not making sense.
That's why I came to you.
I'm asking you a favor.
Only because you're asking.
Thanks, man.
When will I ever benefit from you?
It's tricky.
Plagiarism, cursing on-air
Shin is falling from grace once again
Hi, In-yeong.
Are you alright, sweetie?
Are you home alone?
I'll come over.
I'm okay.
What are you worrying about?
You are not keeping quiet
because of me. Are you?
I'm really okay.
I don't care
what people think about my past.
So, just think only about yourself.
Okay?
I know. I gotta go.
Jina!
What flows faster than time?
It's been almost 1 month
since I joined.
You feel Iike family to me now.
How do you feel?
Let me play
one of favorite songs.
Lee Seung-cheol sings
'Super Hero'
How did I do?
It's a Lee Seung-hwan song.
Make a correction after the song.
Did I? I'm sorry.
I'II make a correction.
Shall we get some sushi
after the show? I'II buy.
- Maybe some other time.
- Promise?
Heard any news about Jina?
Nothing at all.
I doubt she'II ever
be able to come back.
Did you know that this team
faced a crisis once?
We were doing really well
and the director was going to get
bigger producers and writers for the show.
And you know what Jina did?
She confronted him
saying if he was ignoning the hardwork
of everyone who made this show happen.
It must have been shocking.
What good is all that
when she can't Iook after herself?
?What's at the end?
Excuse me.
Is Mr. Cho still in a meeting?
I have an appointment at two.
One moment, please.
Mr. Cho,
Ms Shin Jina is still waiting...
Yes, sir.
Lingering memory slowly...
That's enough. Thanks.
It doesn't move me.
At all.
I'II give my everything
Iike this is the first time.
If you only believe in me...
You don't have that feeling
from the days as Purple.
Let's not have this conversation.
Anyway...
Are you sure you wrote this song?
Infinity is the Iaw.
Forget Infinity.
Beast is the best.
- Infinity rules.
- No, Beast.
Isn't that Shin Jina over there?
The plagiarist?
- Did you watch Entertainment Now?
- No.
She was acting as if she was all that.
Look at her now.
You can't guess
what they are capable.
Oh my gosh, did you hear her
go berserk on radio?
No.
It was a total disaster.
Look at her holding her guitar.
So she is still a musician, huh?
Come on, she might hear us.
Let's get out of here.
Let's go.
There is no gig today?
No.
Business is slow.
I can't afford Iive bands.
Are you a musician?
No, I was just thinking about someone
who played here 1 0 years ago.
That can't be.
We've been only open for 4 years.
- There was an internet shop before.
- What?
Look.
I want to move my beauty shop.
But you only just changed.
They keep making me wait.
Then you should cut in.
I'm in a tight spot.
People keep asking me
when my next song is coming out.
Your song?
I got that arranged
with a composer.
He will write something that
you can publish under your name.
- Really?
- Of course.
He is in a meeting now.
Look what we have here.
You can't barge in here Iike this.
What brought you here?
So...
- 1 0 years ago, was it?
- Pardon me?
You said you performed "Island"
back in 2002.
That's right. Why?
You played a gig in 2002
in a bar that opened in 2007.
Hey, what do you think
you're doing?
Barging in on me Iike this?
How can you have staged this?
Because of a scumbag Iike you,
there is no room for people
who Iove radio!
Scumbag? Since when
were we on such informal terms?
Put Shin Jina back
in her place.
Hey, you!
- Come on. Let's get you home.
- Bro, you just don't understand me.
Go to sleep!
Sorry about
my buddy and the fuss.
He seems upset about something.
Shall I play something cheerful?
Be my guest.
What is this song?
Wasn't it a massive hit?
- Do you want some clues?
- Sure.
The first of the firsts.
Fairies forever.
The beginning of the girl group
and the end.
- It's Purple!
- Purple!
Purple! Purple!
I remember.
You remember
because you're an artist.
I remember the dance.
I used to know
the entire routine.
- I know that dance, too.
- Go back to sleep!
It's good, huh?
This is a great evening.
Shall I take you
for a drive around the town?
Just go home.
Yes, sir.
- Mom.
- What do you want?
You need help with anything?
Well, that's a first?
I was being nice, okay?
How's work going?
Not well.
- Mom.
- Huh?
Shall we have a drink?
What's gotten into you?
Coming up with
such a brilliant idea?
- Cheers!
You should always eat something
with your drinks.
You get that from your dad.
How is that producer of yours doing?
You didn't hear from him?
It's good that he never calls.
We only used to fight all the time.
Oh come on.
We never got along.
You are a spitting image of your dad.
You still think about him?
Sometimes.
Still wait for him?
When he comes back,
I wanted to show him
what a great job I did raising you.
Mom...
Don't worry about me.
I'm okay.
Believe me, darling.
I believe you.
Feel like crying tonight
Our love sways
over the river of time
with my tears
How long should I go on for...
Wonderful Radio DJ
Jina's Birthday!
You could have called me
to Iet me know.
With the recent scandals,
patients' guardians complainted
that it's bad for the children
The incident on Iive show
and plagiarism scandal, you know.
I asked your mother.
She wouldn't tell
but I insisted.
I guss I only Iooked at it
from my perspective.
I should have stood by you.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I'm okay, now.
Not being able to do the show
and not being to able to sing.
I don't blame it on anyone.
You should sing.
I came to tell you that.
You said you finally know
what you want to sing about.
Let's sing.
You were the producer?
Well, it's not confirmed yet.
It doesn't feel right
in my heart.
I haven't had the chance
to prepare myself.
You got it for me!
Free stuff always
brings me peace.
Shin Jina, welcome to my world.
This is Dream Factory.
Let's start.
One two three four.
?Lingering memories
?come back to me
?You come back to me
?although I left you,
?forgot about you
?l poured out my heart
?to love you, to hurt you
?and to love you again
?It's so bitter the memory
?So bitter because I remember
?because I miss it
?l poured out my heart
?to love you, to hurt you
?to love you again
?It's so bitter the memory
?So bitter because I remember
?because I miss it
I apologize sincerely.
Rumy is all taken care of?
I arranged for her to Ieave
the country for a few months.
I thought I could kickstart
my debut ifl raise issues.
Do your job right.
- I'm sorry, sir.
- I did...
- Get outta here.
- everything single-handedly
and my label had nothing
to do with it.
You got tons of trashy music
in your office.
Nice and stuffy in here.
Juts cut to the chase.
What's wrong with you?
I Iearned a Iot
from your Iast visit.
I'm only trying to help you.
He's talking about the special show
commemorating 1 000th show.
TV, It'II be aired Iive
on radio and TV.
We'II fill up the Iineup
with Lee's boys and girls.
That's a great idea.
but I'II come up
with the final Iineup.
Of course, you won't need to worry
about your boys and girls.
Well, you're the producer in charge.
It Iooks Iike you have
something up your sleeve.
It's Shin Jina.
Her name is cleared but...
isn't it too early
to make a come back?
I'II present you
with a preliminary Iineup.
Jae-hyeok! Jae-hyeok!
Wait.
You think it would hurt the station
more to Iose one good producer
or an entire army of their
most popular hosts and DJs?
Are you threatening me?
I think so.
Put Shin Jina on the Iineup.
And hang this on the Iine, too.
- Give me my cellphone?
- Here.
Where is Yong-sik?
He had a call from Mr. Lee.
He didn't update me
on the afternoon schedule.
He'II be right back.
How have you been, Mira?
What are you doing here?
You know the rumor
about my time in juvie.
I don't want to hear about it.
Well, it's not a rumor.
When I was in 1 3
I came back from school
and my step father was beating
the hell out of mom again.
I had to stop him somehow.
And I realized
I had killed a man.
On the night before our Iast concert,
a reporter told me he'd run the story.
Jina said...
That we can stop it
if we break up the group.
Jina said she couldn't watch me
branded a murderer
for the rest of my Iife.
Why are you telling me this now?
I don't care. I gotta go.
PIease don't hate her
so much.
I said I wasn't interested.
Your autographs, please?
This is Shin Jina's
historical comeback album.
Cherish it as a treasure.
About the comeback broadcast
that I mentioned earlier.
I'm not performing
on TV or radio.
Wonderful Radio's 1 000th
special broadcast is coming up.
I want that to be
your comeback stage.
I don't think I can do it.
Why?
You brought the show this far.
I would really Iike you
to be part of the show.
I'm making an official request
as the producer of the show.
PIease.
And, this is my present.
Open it when you get home.
Shin Jina, the recording artist!
I have a Iittle something
for you, too.
Hey, that's uh...
Don't flex your muscles on me.
- Come on, man.
- There you go.
That's okay.
Come on.
But I can't do it.
What's the matter?
You promised me.
- But, bro...
- Stop being a sissy.
This doesn't feel right.
Wait. Wait!
?Love comes to you quietly
?and makes your heart pound
?The voice that I could no longer hear
?l miss your voice so much
I really can't do it.
- Will she Iike it?
- Believe me.
Moment's embarrassment
guarantees Iifetime of Iove.
Let's go.
Man, do I really need to do this?
You promised.
- Come on, man.
- What's wrong with you, man?
I'II revenge you.
You know I can't sing.
Will you stop crying
Iike a Iittle girl?
How about 'Thank you'?
Where is your manner?
- Little brats...
- Hey!
Stop playing that crappy song.
Don't you know
whose song this is?
Whose is it?
How do I explain this?
First of the firsts.
The beginning
of the girl band syndrome.
And the end.
Eternal fairies.
They don't even age that much.
This the masterpiece of Purple,
'You are My Angel'
Let's get going, man.
Hello? Hi!
Pardon?
We Iove you, Jina.
Shin Jina!
You're the truth, Jina
I saw the cue sheet.
You really have to push forward?
Don't you know what Lee is Iike?
You'II end up hurt.
I'm going to make the show
that I want.
I'm sorry.
- Jina!
- Oh, Jina!
- I missed you so much.
- How are you?
You Iook good.
Good job with the preparation.
It's been so hard
since you Ieft.
Come on, Mira.
They want you inside.
Where did you get this?
In the waiting room.
What difference is it going to make?
She's finished.
Is really performing
on the show tonight?
Mr. Lee will flip out.
- It's me.
- Hey, darling.
- I'm going in now.
- You arrived early.
- Listen.
- What is it, honey?
About Jina performing tonight.
Don't worry about it.
It's all taken care of.
No, actually...
Then what?
I don't care
whether she performs on stage.
What are you talking about?
Don't be silly.
And this doesn't just concern you.
This is about my pride.
Even if Jina comes to the show,
she'll not singing on that stage. Okay?
In-seok! Wait.
Come on, we gotta go.
- Did you check the artists?
- Yes.
Do you know
that Jina is here?
If you're happy and
you know it, smile, man.
- Last commercial.
- Okay.
One, two, go.
Hi everyone,
Wonderful Radio is celebrating
its 1 000th show tonight.
Thank you all for coming here to celebrate
with us this special moment.
Here with us tonight,
we have guests
from "The Song I Sing to You"
Lim Seul-gi! Lim Seul-gi!
Wonderful Radio and wonderful Iife
starts now.
I heard you released
a new album.
I should have sent you a congratulatory
tweet or something
but I've been too busy.
Can you make it quick?
I need to prepare
for my performance.
What's the hurry?
When Purple split up,
I should have kept to you
no matter what.
Mira is perfect
except for the guts
which you have.
In this business, you need the guts to go
on stage even at the cost of your producer.
Mira Iacks that quality.
What did you say?
Whose neck is on the Iine?
Your producer, Lee Jae-hyeok.
Jina!
You have a very tall friend.
I'II Iook forward to your show.
? I rememberyour face
from when you first came to me
? You touched my heart
and it stood broken since
Jae-hyeok, it's Jina!
Hurry!
Come on, now.
What about her?
Tell me what happened?
Why didn't you tell me
what was at stake on this show?
Did you think about
how I would feel?
I can't play this gig.
Are you running away?
Don't you think about everyone
in the audience who is waiting for you?
There are people supporting you
waiting for your song.
Breaking up of the band,
PIagiarism scandal...
You think you can only help others
by sacrificing yourself?
Sing.
For yourself.
And for me.
? I'll love you always
? I'll love you like this moment
? More than anyone in the world
Hi, mom.
Did you eat?
Not yet.
You gotta eat
ifyou're gonna sing.
I'll be listening to you
from here with daddy.
So, don't be too nervous.
Just do your thing, okay?
Answer me, silly girl!
Come home and have beer
with me later, okay?
Sure.
- What?
- I said 'Okay'!
- Go, my girl!
?l only kept in my heart
Mira, you ready?
?Yes, I loved you
We'II have the Iast guest of part.
We can't talk about Wonderful Radio
without mentioning this person.
She was with you from the very
first show till not Iong ago.
Jina!
At the heart of Wonderful Radio
and the former Ieader of Purple,
Give it up for Shin Jina!
Hi everyone! It's so great to see you
again on Wonderful Radio.
I'm Shin Jina.
While I was in Purple and
presenting Wonderful Radio
I said "I Iove you" and "Thank you" a Iot.
But, that was all in the script.
My heart wasn't really in it.
The reason I'm here again is
because now I feel
that I can really say
I Iove you and "Thank you"
with my heart.
To me, Wonderful Radio was Iove.
After I Ieft the show Iike that,
I missed it so much.
I missed you so much.
Everyone,
Thank you.
I Iove you.
I'II sing my new song, "Again".
Thank you.
Where are you going?
It's a Iive show.
? When darkness drapes over,
the stories offorgotten dreams
? songs I put aside come to me
? like tiny lights,
pieces of thoughts
? hang over the cloud
? and shine down on me
? Tears and lies
? and feelings I couldn 't get go
? all the times I tried
and all the people
? I'm letting them go
here and now
I poured out my heart
but that wasn't sincere
- So here I go again
- Turn off the Iights!
What are you doing?
Director!
How can you do this to me?
From today on,
I'II walking out with
all my hosts from your station.
- Pull them out.
- Pull them out!
Excuse me?
I said pull them out.
There are tons of people
who are dying to working with us.
Go on. I'm boycotting
all your artists from this station.
Well, that's not what I meant...
PIease Ieave this room.
- Director! Bro!
- PIease step outside.
You seem to have misunderstood me.
I'II wait for you at the coffee shop.
What an idiot!
? I'm going to sing my song
? I'm letting it all go
here and now
I poured out my heart
but I wasn't sincere
So here I go again
I'm starting over again
? For me who will shine
like the stars
? I'm letting it all go
here and now
I've been Iooking all over for you.
What's our relationship?
Aren't we producer and host?
Yes.
What kind of a producer sticks
his neck out for his host?
This is from the director.
And I got something for you too.
On the house beat,
we'II add an elemnet of rock.
And shouting!
What do you think?
Not very hot, huh?
I thought so too.
I have a heart-ringing ballad for you.
Listen to the intro.
Ji-yeong begged me for it
but I kept it aside for you.
3 minutes!
Just give me 3 minutes.
This is a hiphop remake of
Lee Mija's mega hit, "Camellia Girl."
This bit here...
Feel the beat?
200 backup singers with short pants
going "Camellia girl"~~
It gave me goose bumps.
- Good job.
- Don't go.
Jina. PIease!
Hi, this is Kim Chang-wan
from Beautiful Morning.
- I have a real special song for you.
- Hi, I'm Park So-hyeon.
The next song is
rather a special song.
Bouncing back
from the plagiarism accusation,
the former leader of Purple and
beloved host
of Wonderful Radio
She overcame hardships
and released a new album.
I know what that's like.
I'm sure you do.
She wrote all songs by herself.
That's incredible.
Send her your support and love.
and show her the power of listeners
and lover of radio.