And is one happy early morning. Hello everybody I am Jinchang prefecture level city in Gansu alkane.
Shutter other drizzle also to seem so beautiful.
Plain and simple worthy or virtuous person love game
plain and simple worthy or virtuous person with you along to enter today's program.
Let we together to pass this paragraph beautiful that time light.
I am perfect broadcast to extend precious thing son.
My dear audience friend. Thank you long term to accompany sb.
-= perfect broadcast =-
Give you.
Thank you.
Small hope. You also tired.
Is it better?
Don't drink so more coffee.
Soon will thirty be careful in a short while done full head white or gray hair.
Wait for me send new album my every day all go hairdressing shop.
And to carry what album?
Third. Fourth department Taiwan copy.
They who is it?
Colpi. Girls.
Isn't it said please Dal. *. Shabet.
We program also please please those currently popular  children okay or not.
Can please to colpi. Girls already not bad.
Quickly go inside.
Next week remembered please a man idol to assemble. Rely on you.
Too like. Too like.
Hello. We are colpi. Girls.
You all really adorable. Hope we work happily together.
Is. Know already.
To call out to sb hit okay or not is most crucial point.
At I still Purple one person that time
also feel that to meet sunbae compared to at the stage play and tired people.
- Sister you before is singer
-Purple.
Won't be right.
You all don't know Purple.
Enter Taiwan to declare. Please prepare.
Power. FM.
Wonderfule. Radio third. Four part
will soon with new age person woman to assemble colpi. Girls together to complete.
Hello everybody. We are colpi. Girls.
Really one spacious and well-lit and rich energetic to assemble.
Vigorous like is eddy to flow and to catch up go to breed silver carp the same.
Extremely rude and impetuous.
Also extremely confused fresh and pure to assemble.
Thank you.
So today's first head song
we just from colpi. Girls song started.
Get. Out. Boy.
You all unexpectedly don't know Purple.
You all is year to be born.
-1991 year. - I am 1994 year.
2004 year Republic of South Korea.
Dregs.
My that's why know will be like this? What to do what to do?
Quiet a bit.
Whether or not keep quiet.
Elder brother.
This head song will surely bonus.
To extend precious thing son came. To extend precious thing son.
To extend precious thing son.
Heavens.
And so on. Wait a moment.
Talk to me. Then head song didn't you say want to give me?
Quickly go inside.
Wait a moment.
And so on. Don't to have an urge.
Elder brother.
You come out.
I want to you quickly come out.
Elder brother.
Precious thing son.
I know you very angry. My understand.
My extremely understand.
But.
I also can only like this.
More is like this. We more want to reason.
Didn't you say this head song specialist give me write?
Correct. But.
To wait until to fill or stuff good enough song lyric.
Then discovered this head song must want to to give idol send sing.
Brother.
Precious thing son.
Next month at first.
My the fourth child will to go out gave birth to.
Futhermore, is twin. Want to to earn their powdered milk money to urinate disc money.
Then afraid is one head song
more to earn 100 dollar money I also have to to earn. This is it reality?
More importantly is.
Go idol itinerary is presently general trend.
Really let me disappointed.
From today in future. You write poem for singing that is white give i also don't want to.
See you again.
Precious thing son.
Hey.
MD.
Tomorrow schedule to arrange have what?
Wait a moment perfect later my to reissue newsletter give you.
And send what newsletter? Just now say.
Very to have good luck. Tomorrow we have a alone concert.
Sanmen county in Taizhou [Tai2 zhou1], Zhejiang middle school first 24 to arrive at school mate will.
We want to go to add to the fun perform.
What? You thought my to extend precious thing son who is it?
Based on what at Sanmen county in Taizhou [Tai2 zhou1], Zhejiang middle school 24 to arrive at school mate will to add to the fun perform?
Give me to cancel.
Credit card to be in debt time limit soon will arrived.
Furthermore, in fact this three days. I already is use soap to wash head.
I am not say what to you i will immediately, will to go out album?
Just returned.
Auntie. Hello.
To substitute root you came.
Have worked hard. Eaten food then go.
Good.
I said.
Right auntie. I have to go back to adjust tomorrow schedule to arrange.
Food my next time again come eat.
See you again.
Eaten food then go. To substitute root.
You this bad head.
Why you to to substitute root so terrible?
There and also like to substitute root so good child.
Want to to he good bit. Stench head.
You also cannot on time give he send wages and to have the nerve like this is that correct he?
You just rest a bit. How still want busy to so late?
Rest good enough then want to get up continue to put in effort to earn.
Really get you there is nothing to be done.
The shop one person also do not have. To close shop in the evening rest will be good.
To rest what to rest?
How come so difficult system?
Welcome. Inside please.
Father. Come here side sit.
You see. Here we go again six individual.
Daughter-in-law you also quickly come sit.
Aigoo. Have grown really good see.
This is this nearby most famous shop.
To eat what good?
I'm going give you all more get one copy menu.
Kindly wait a moment. Immediately come.
Wait a moment want to eat some more.
Rotten girl.
Good enough.
To me. One year in have twice Christmas time.
12 month once.
6 month once.
This one week.
That is my give oneself to set midsummer Christmas to make a circuit.
Here 6 month Christmas time in.
I have not definite.
Want to towards Father Christmas.
To make a promise like what desire?
So what about you?
You want or do not want also with my together.
Find one to make a wish box.
Will soon 6 month desire a item adornment go inside.
Just at now.
Let we together
towards to seem extremely bored Father Christmas to make a promise our desire.
Today year Christmas time.
Please do not let me again lone.
Perfect broadcast second department
According to character method with audience friend proceed with interactive.
Let people to feel desperation is human beings oneself.
And will soon desperation change become hope similar also human beings oneself.
2065 audience
thank you today also send came brilliant quotation with beautiful fresh flowers.
Next. Please listen one head requested song.
Afterschool.
-= requested repertoire :after. School "lovelovelove"=-
afterschool.
Don't know today can cannot let I also bit one head song. Director.
Purple you is my angel.
With we together shared delights and common hardships ; to share life's joys and sorrows four years Yin Ji Seon director.
Because about to labor.
Want to temporarily with we say see you again.
To send Yin director my one portion intention.
To wish you everything smoothly.
Is really. Now and actually dare get oneself old-fashioned song.
Get transmitter-receiver in to sow.
You find I am.
Sit.
Long time have not seen.
Straight talk straight say.
You want to go to take over perfect broadcast this official records program.
You are saying Yin sunbae program.
Say is really.
This official records program to listen rate simply until very blur.
Estimate very quickly just to hold a meeting to discuss to replace DJ issue.
Is no matter how say that also Yin director painstaking effort to create program?
Painstaking effort to create correct.
To listen rate then 2%.
Yin director there I will with she said.
You over to take over. Go change a bit of aspect.
To lock up good gate then go.
Good.
Want to remembered come back early. To cultivate a good one habit.
Know.
Walk slowly.
Elder brother. You want left already.
Didn't you say give me bring album come?
Sorry. Next time give you bring over.
Cannot be every time don't remember.
Know already know already. Sorry. Walk slowly.
Elder brother. How come you came here?
Isn't it said next week you want come over do our director.
Perfect.
Come bit beer.
Anyhow give something?
But how can is you come?
We this program is cannot be according to you to sow oneself like song.
DJ people how is it?
You are saying precious thing son.
We there is is princess.
My hate most this type of.
Estimate precious thing son also hate most you this type of.
My see also.
Really have to get time do like this nervous.
Older sister. Able to remember our car one to step on the brake just backbite backbite backbite ring.
To issue this type of strange voice.
I today go repair shop to decorate a moment. Now you listen listen.
Hey. Car to substitute root.
Give her hit a phone.
Older sister.
Precious thing son older sister.
- Quickly quickly. How come your then come
- you have to remove makeup oil?
My to adorn oneself all give to destroy.
I heard say newcomer director nature like dog the same to exceed difference.
I also heard. Say like dog.
He come so early.
Just now and will arrived.
Hello. I am to extend precious thing son agent car to substitute root.
Rumors always.  Now What's the time?
We just for to extend precious thing son Miss wait here half hours
you all to do what impressions?
Then is because of on the road have a bit of traffic jam furthermore,.
DJ sir come ago we are already more or less know a moment.
In large part program unit but also to do with difficulty maintain.
But have a problem.
My life love equation.
Sickening let people to rise whole body goose pimples.
Director sir. I like this unit.
Audience to react also very well. And also to need suitable sickening.
Like this then can gather popularity. Right right.
Who tell you audience to react good.
Tomorrow 11 bit ago submit new program unit to plot case.
Tomorrow.
11 bit.
Director.
You thought this is Internet to search to hit a moment keyboard just can come out.
To plot one new proposal to have a think about it have more difficult.
That's why have author here isn't it?
But Excuse me, may I ask.  Why you nevertheless to interrupt my words?
First time meeting must come a self-introduction to need at least must polite.
Have a roughly know.
To do a will food to adjust a moment atmosphere and so on.
Like this then can well develop work isn't it. Right right.
Eyes really beautiful.
Day to day someone like this say.
Then just first to here.
I feel that you should be like this type of drinks.
Exquisite man should be like.
To.
Lie come down that time.
Start from head started.
Spinal column one festival one festival to go to delegate.
Straight to rise waist body.
To assume before bent posture.
To try to to press come down.
To keep.
Yin director sister living well.
Go give birth to child.
Then who do director.
Came one new.
Male.
Is a male. But completely never to train. Annoying male.
Grave and stern city man.
Mistake. Everywhere find flat city man.
Talking about find flat. Call colpi. Girls or something coming here.
Really very annoying.
To have a think about it we previously.
At before we then is high and powerful.
In other words. Every to weekend we just able to hear that voice.
Copy to make a circuit first 1 position. Purple.
Thank you.
Thanks we fan of a singer club  purple to bewilder friends. I love you.
So next.
Request the pleasure of Purple the classics song ( you is my angel )
You. Are. My. Angel. Angel. Angel. To. Me.
Want forever to have you full love.
You. Are. My. Angel.
Thank you everybody. Next one the stage see you again.
I love you. I love you.
Really to cherish the memory of.
Camera.
First 423 a scene.
To begin shooting.
Cut. Good enough enough. Don't shoot.
Shoot next one.
Director. OK.
OK. Didn't I say already OK?
The Americas gauze Miss. Feelings catch very well.
OK. Able to. Feels like not bad catch very well.
Again shoot once.
Able to able to
don't have much time you thought are you, at filming a movie.
OK.
Lee Representative you really difficult to deal with.
Gold director you also want to know.
To advertise this kind of thing need flowing.
Taste 's raw silk remembered. Seasoning.
You say just it shoot how long? URUSA to inject one kind of liver medicine.
Just to pull one head wisdom different mountain half-moon bear.
And salted vegetable doing so more year.
Century hearing aid. Use one only left ear shoot ten year to advertise.
Korea and Japan to drop hit to stick.
Carry one guitar similar also shoot so more year.
The Americas gauze is the same long term work.
Prepare.
Thanks to you small subsidiary company in artists  good fortune.
Recently life How are you getting by and very satisfied?
Is prop your good fortune then correct. Hello we also then have good life past.
Special is that? 10 a bit of time official records idol singer.
- Call what coming here
- you is said Pink? Dols.
Pink. Dols. Correct correct.
To listen rate really considerable.
Is you to choose good. Big brother.
10 bit that period of time audience or as secondary school students to be in the majority.
So as idol send singer to rely mainly on Lai'an county in Chuzhou [Chu2 zhou1], Anhui parallelism comparatively suitable.
6 bit is get off work time
main as office workers as well as taxi chauffeur to rely mainly on.
So want to to arrange those reputation to compare high.
For example say like Yin the Americas gauze and so on. You feel that.
The Americas dream is that so?
Of course not bad.
Not bad.
This to plot case but rate author with my to rack one's brains ; to take great pains to think sth through prepared.
So.
I am say. You use this type of manner treat
with utmost care do proposal author have a bit of not so good.
To me with regard to. Did well compared to to put in effort do become important?
My to believe a good one DJ must have three condition.
Popularity. Ability.
As well as nature.
Or at least have among 's two.
Not. At least one have.
Now you tell me this what it all means?
Don't want to always at to hold a meeting that time to mix together too many individual feelings.
Be people see wear your character.
To listen rate you want how much?
4%.
Then merely 4%.
Recently half a year also do not have to surpass 2%.
And to dare say merely 4%.
Over very important.
To dream of must want to far-reaching.
Then. New program unit to plot proposal.
Just from to extend precious thing son you come and do.
My.
I'll do just I'll do. I can do good.
I'll do just I'll do. Good. I will do.
I can do good.
Lit. To wipe one's eyes and wait ; to wait and see.
There come such a fellow.
What should we do then good?
Sit down one trip.
Do sit this.
How do you do?
Precious thing son Miss long time have not seen.
Recently always at see your television drama.
Is that so?
Can you like this say too thanks.
But. Really sorry.
My at a loss listen your transmitter-receiver.
I think you also if just that little bit ability.
Well do. To extend precious thing son.
You throw next Purple bill to fly. If can only confused like this poverty-stricken.
I will feel that very to have no strength.
See you again.
Encore. Encore.
You should don't tell me is plan to here say that matter.
Precious thing son.
Don't want to.
We think again want.
That matter also not today not say not is not just.
Heartfelt thanks today to come we concert eveyone.
Today.
Have a news want to declare.
Today's perform will soon is our last one scene.
Today in future we Purple to assemble will to dissolve.
Thank you you all this is for a long time since.
This long since always to show concern and care for we?
Will soon another only arm.
And line of sight flat to stretch forward place.
Now. To take note of will soon line of sight will naturally invest towards your hand point.
Able to accomplish it people please to bend your hand arm.
Grab hold of another only hand.
To inhale.
To breathe out.
To inhale. To sense lung department with thoracic cavity expansion.
To breathe out. To loosen you whole body muscles and bones.
At do excellence gamma movement that time. Remembered only concentrated his own to sense.
Both position is how do you know?
That is ago with you to carry past director.
Transmitter-receiver.
Originally that is that annoying male?
Hey.
Both position and is how do you know?
Purple to assemble pond humane. You do not know.
You do not know my.
Right. Peace princess pond humane.
Have worked hard.
He said my what?
He this person how come like this?
So it is said ask you pad bit sponge.
Hey. Practice excellence gamma you still want to my pad then things.
Very happy to see you all.
Then, we and will do good do.
You bring they go eat food.
Is. I understand.
Next time see.
As for me this is at do benevolent.
This type of quality people also to go here bring.
So it is said. You plan to how to do it?
Wait a while longer. Immediately, must to revise the current edition.
You sure.
To appear amongst all most popular DJ all is our people
you and worry what?
So what I meant was say?
This time, we must want to come really.
I am not want wait too for a long time.
My most like that is come really.
We go eat food.
Oh. Isn't this newcomer Lee director.
- Hello everyone
- it is said that now you very bonus.
What is it?
You are saying I'm going 9 bit official records program.
It's not. You now, is not with to extend precious thing son together to cooperate.
You with to extend precious thing son very familiar.
Before Purple and never leisurely that time
in our program done it two month fixed esteemed guest.
Really very great. Song especially good listen.
You. Are. My. Angel. Angel.
My not long ago to come across her her and asked you say how are you?
Then how come your say?
I said you sour like beggar.
Really very beggar.
DJ seen you all to hide go. Is you do not know only.
You want to her good bit.
At her such a large people in very rare like her this kind of.
To talk about loyalty. And sex appeal. And pure. And courteous.
You to fall really like a beggar.
Yoga practice how is it?
My all going crazy. Body very stiff.
You and really to learn gentle and soft. Everywhere is. Want to more towards my learning.
He but a faithful excellence gamma to bewilder.
I understand.
Excellence powder similar.
Big brother.
Don't again drink alcohol do program.
Shut up.
What drink alcohol do program at most is after drinking do program only?
That is.
Is cannot be that way say.
Then but very fatal.
Then to return really let other people to receive many guilt. You have worked hard.
Say people upsetting.
Want or not to go drink one cup.
Late give you phone.
Have worked hard.
As the proverb says brief encounter also is cause.
Life free free.
Please to look around a moment your all around.
Can hereto quarter to accompany sb my around you you all.
With my between is to have such a large fate or chance that brings people together.
So. Can at future both hour in to listen my voice you.
With my between is or is not also to have one portion very not the same fate or chance that brings people together.
Perfect broadcast. I am to extend precious thing son.
Today. Our program
newcomer Lee at awe-inspiring director this moment just at side.
Drinks only drink United States ice coffee. Is one ruthless ruthless boyfriend.
Lee at awe-inspiring director. We want to Fighting.
-= new program to plot case =-
-= just based on you =-
-= rate. First head song to sow this head song =-
Good. We come listen today's first head song.
To be ready.
To come from sister.
Just based on you.
-= difficult is not love technology but love skill
"Alphonse. Daude"-2065=-
My every to this time I already feel that special to trap.
My contrary to what one might expect most like this time?
Able to eat a bit light refreshments and so on.
-= to change music =-
-=" like rain the same like music the same "=-
Our perfect broadcast.
Perfect broadcast. Third department to begin song.
Is one head very suitable today this kind of rainy days song.
- To come from gold light stone stone song. " like rain the same like music the same "
- what? Gold light stone.
You say this is who song.
Is gold worthy or virtuous person to plant right.
To sow finish later my again correct a moment.
You thought simple correct a moment will be enough is that so?
This bit lapse is hard to avoid stone
gold light stone gold worthy or virtuous person to plant my originally have a bit of min unclear.
Gold light stone with gold worthy or virtuous person to plant how is it possible will min unclear?
Hey hey. Is still broadcast you this is do what?
You let go my.
Hey. You to regard as a what singer?
We go out say.
You all seeing don't have.
Even tried to shoot table
legend you just one dog character looks like is really strip dog. Evil dog.
Older sister. My come.
Outside should be never listen right.
You are strip dog. Evil dog.
My head good confused.
In future you is be careful bit.
Quickly. Drink cup water.
Originally rumors in have said all really.
Miss. To have time.
Time is have. That is don't have energy.
Is still angry.
That guy how can that way? Like a crazy  viper
really brains have problem.
But. Do you know.
I at my twenty season liked music
if you say it to scold it bad.
I will feel my whole youth all be deprive to fall the same.
My and never to scold. Only not careful call mistake name only.
Hold a case. If someone get purple call done pinkle.
Then I will surely crazy to fall. Really.
Right.
Is me Lee at awe-inspiring youth.
On the road listen listen see.
More and more distant.
Once thought will stuck and not moving forward ; stagnant youth.
More and more spacious and empty central point.
Any more cannot find it any things.
Time to elapse will to double come.
Our love.
Because tears became not firm.
Still want how long?
-= annoying male =-
-= today is new regular column or segment to plot case =-
-= deadline =-
still want how long?
-= annoying male =-
-= today is new regular column or segment to plot case =-
-= deadline =-
Caught the flu.
Mom. Transmitter-receiver work my might as well to resign a post forget it.
Up to you.
Either run go night party to sing a song. Either just lifetime run scene child.
Mom. How can you like this with oneself daughter talk?
I am purple to extend precious thing son. I'm not die but also to sing a song.
You this girl. To swallow train engine is or is not.
From do DJ that day to rise you just like this noisy a never finish.
Still want how long?
I then can see you again to you.
To cross over years river.
Our love.
Correct. That is it?
Because tears and became not firm.
Mom. My found it. My found it.
Really great.
Crazy brat.
Get have old practice people find it out.
Prepare next week immediately program.
You see. I just say you write very well.
My comma middle school that time but writing champion. Champion.
Fighting.
Our perfect broadcast.
Perfect broadcast. For you to offer  one new regular column or segment.
For you and sing song.
Today we new fence objective first place lead actor
is one 22 years old serviceman.
Make use of he valuable on leave time come arrived our program.
So. We just all together listen listen he old practice.
I am at iron root clothes military service soldiers grow Zheng light safe.
Is not because of other. My have a extremely like people.
But her not answer to receive my. I am really quickly crazy to fall.
Last year my even and because of her and done it army deserter.
Be police to arrest nearly to hang or suspend to fall.
That also cannot should be so too much.
So. Just let we together come listen listen he song.
Bring my heart intention. To offer to God Zheng blaze of fire Mister one head song.
-Nothing. Better
-
Then just let we together come listen listen Nothing. Better.
Hey.
Next emperor's carriage Dae Yeong language system to assign a type of standing harp, smaller than konghou, with 5-25 strings fine jade.
You don't see now with this kind. Will surely with how do you do
you just honest over there and wait?
Ask you clam down. We together come listen song.
A type of standing harp, smaller than konghou, with 5-25 strings fine jade angel to assign a type of standing harp, smaller than konghou, with 5-25 strings fine jade. To assign a type of standing harp, smaller than konghou, with 5-25 strings fine jade.
Like breathe the same. You from beginning to end to stay somewhere temporarily at my at one's side.
A type of standing harp, smaller than konghou, with 5-25 strings fine jade. You is it better?
Hey. Is you you will okay.
Tomorrow started want to to sprout angel wing.
Just like this Remaining here don't want to leave.
Nothing. Better. Nothing. Better. Than. You.
Is really. Unable to take it.
Zheng light safe. You're dead.
Ajussi. Whether or not get broadcast turn off.
Have call on the phone said to to sue our
say we to compile broadcast accident.
And say we just to to raise to listen rate anything able to do come out
anyway say whatever all have?
Bureau chief. This time, regular column or segment contrary to what one might expect compared to to imagine in is much better
only want you can again for we one a bit of time?
To raise to listen rate is of course good
or just first maintain current situation. To wait until to adapt that time.
Might as well get DJ with regular column or segment whole to change to fall what do you think?
What?
You first well to have a think about it.
What is the matter?
Be on top of to be criticized is that so?
Don't tell me you thought will be to patronize.
Really sorry.
Why? Why say sorry?
All because of me that's why?
New fence objective proposal is me to choose.
Director work that is choose with to be in charge of regular column or segment
this time, also no not the same.
No need to worry. We group I will to be in charge of exactly.
Try and see.
Hey. Car to substitute root. You see car all must to explode or burst.
You just cannot. Cannot be in advance inspection a moment.
Arrived late can you to be in charge of. Heavens. Now already late.
Sorry.
Quickly call taxi.
Is really.
Is really. Here how is it possible call to taxi?
Help. Help.
My day to day listen all of you broadcast.
Extremely grateful you.
Wow. Small child is so cute. You married woman also very pretty.
Photo seeing that really good.
Excuse me, may I ask.  My can to announce you all one program.
Director. This is manuscript.
Unexpectedly anyhow to change program? Precious thing son where is it?
Her. Here.
Our perfect broadcast.
Perfect broadcast. For you and sing song.
Today's hero is 42 years old taxi chauffeur gold aspiration model Mister.
Ask you personally with we to say sth your old practice.
Hello everybody.
Don't know today and have what old practice listen?
- Keep quiet
- i am called gold aspiration model.
I have one to confer haven't come yet and send give my wife the letter.
So today come arrived here.
Yes Ying. Is me aspiration model.
You leave we are already have three year.
I think first say what to you sound sorry?
Let you to receive so more hard.
At you alive that time. Even to confer letter also do not have write past give you
I am not one considerate  good husband.
Right. I've prepared one head you like very much zoo 's song.
Before you always laugh my to sing a song bad listen.
Than, I will just started sing. You listen.
Yes Ying.
Yes Ying. Quick lucky her.
Doctor say she is cancer. With you the same.
I know you to miss sb to read quick lucky.
I know. I know but I cannot get quick lucky let give you.
I must certainly let quick lucky well to recuperate.
Let her grown up getting married. To be born one with you is similiar daughter's son.
So no matter whether you how you think her
also must certainly remain her by my side to at that time?
Sorry. Rely on you.
Sorry.
My to broil hot lip.
Want near you gentle and soft lip.
Let me love.
To pass on to in your heart.
If you still.
Don't know i regarding your love.
My compared to in the world anyone all must love you.
Whenever. I already will love you.
I will love you. Just like now the same.
My compared to in the world anyone.
All must love you.
Whenever. I already will love you.
I will love you. Just like now the same.
My compared to in the world anyone.
All must love you.
-= gold aspiration model Mister for to die wife to offer song to move everyone
popularity DJ to extend precious thing son Miss interview to fully experience to pay attention to =-
- Hello
- how do you do?
Hey. Very large at Ying. You with he doing what to call out to sb?
Is not your father.
You really are.
Wait for me a moment.
- Is really
- real frustrating.
Let's go together.
Let go my.
More prosperous. Eaten food.
Father at say what to you?
No need to you bother.
Ajussi. Generic name for hemp, flax etc bother you in future do not again with my friend say hello.
Good. Sorry.
More prosperous.
Let her. A little child not all like this.
Go go. Feels like too tired.
To stop footstep.
To wipe body and past.
See not until more prosperous you. I just get it put it here.
More prosperous. You like to sing a song then just continue sing.
My most like see my daughter to sing a song time the appearance.
At father central point. We more prosperous forever all is the best.
Happy birthday.
That's. When. I. Feel. Love. Love.
That's. When. I. Feel
love. Love. Love. Love.
That's. When. I. Feel. Love. Love. Love.
Thank you.
Congratulations to you.
Thank you. Thanks to you. Also congratulations to you.
Trifle only. At least not to congratulate.
You and will to compose is that so?
Of course. I am have copyright woman.
Really unexpected.
What?
Didn't you idol send singer born with?
Idol send what's wrong? Idol send just cannot write song.
Older sister. How come your still here Lee director that fellow currently?
How do you do? Lee director.
I first enter in. To wish you cheerful.
Really one week have not dropped it. You say this person what exactly is do what?
To bloom shop.
Bother he is do what? In short will surely is a delicious people.
See get you give happy.
How do you do? Director
this is today lead actor information with old practice.
Must certainly let to extend precious thing son at program before comma a moment.
That is precious thing son older sister to choose.
- Hello everybody
- how do you do?
Older sister. This give you.
Let us listen what?
How is it?
More prosperous came text message. Say let us listen broadcast.
Broadcast is that so?
For you and sing song.
Today. We to welcome came one extremely adorable secondary school students.
How do you do?
How do you do? I am called Yin more prosperous. Is senior high school two grade student.
So. Can give we introduce a moment
your old practice and also you song.
Father. You able to hear.
My  father most like radio program.
Father know. Mother have gotten married.
That ajussi compared to father clown more.
But. He to mother very well.
Father passed away suddenly. Mother and me all very sad.
That clown father's younger brother  that horrid father's younger brother.
He said have my this kind of daughter. So very happy.
If father to permit.
I want to go to accept that father's younger brother.
This period of time. I really extremely sorry.
Thank you for your gift.
Father.
Hope you are able understand. I can't be close your heart.
Tears to complain say me fervent hope.
Once to love each other. Also once to complain.
To miss once compared to anyone.
All to love dearly my you.
Always at at one's side. But always unable to near.
Yes. My once to complain.
Please you listen listen my to tell sb.
I'm only need some time.
Once to love each other. Also once to complain.
To miss once compared to anyone.
All to love dearly my you.
At my heart abyss collection.
Yes. My once affectionate past.
To choose came out old practice all very not bad.
This also no.
Diary program that time i thought of a question.
Regarding you come say. Perfect broadcast is what?
To talk about my old practice space. I am say once.
But now, is not.
Listen listen other people old practice. On behalf they to move to comfort they.
And myself also can from to get to comfort.
Learn arrived a lot things.
Really want to sing a song.
My good like now then really to understand
should be by means of music say have something.
Older sister. What to do?
Good to scald.
Older sister. Director. Simply is not kidding
youtube and to report to one's superiors to transmit completely a popular craze.
Is. Hurried reporter. Interview is that so? Good.
To cover at my body.
At what time started see?
Three days.
Three days is that so?
Wow. Is long period of time.
This time, is really enough for a long time.
Great.
You. Are. My. Angel. Angel. Angel. To. Me.
Just like this forever collection our love.
Today's you also like yesterday the same perfect.
Not left behind a bit very small regret.
Today's perfect broadcast. Will with everybody say see you again.
Cool and refreshing wind. Usable night to become in this way beautiful.
Don't know this kind of night
is or is not sweet potato soup to join name of a famous Tang dynasty wine will to seem become beautiful.
Wow. Simply really great.
Have head song want to recommend give you listen night then rub starlight.
To come from Lee to bear brilliant song.
-= is gold worthy or virtuous person to plant song =-
Lee to bear brilliant specific  tone to carry to we and former bent different to move.
Have Lee to bear brilliant version.
Please everybody enjoy to one's content enjoy this head song
to extend precious thing son right here in with everybody say sound see you again.
To wish everybody have a the Americas good night.
Night. Just like your breathe.
Noiseless wipe my tears.
Starlight.
Heard perfect broadcast very fire. Big brother.
Lee director this time is to rush a disaster.
Congratulations you big brother. Is really.
If it's like this. I will how is it?
How come your like a spare time the same
always cannot be get do properly people stiff to pull come down?
But big brother. You listen I said.
Then I more regret.
But. This type of regret is able to at any time to change.
Lee Representative. This circle you still not familiar with.
Now get to extend precious thing son to pull come down
only know how to to bring about some nonsense to guess?
Obviously It wasn't me. Sent away.
Also obviously It wasn't me. Leave.
Director. Gold worthy or virtuous person to plant with gold light stone you become like who.
Gold light stone.
Then you say one gold light stone song people
I said one gold worthy or virtuous person to plant song people. How is it?
You even like rain the same music the same you all min unclear and say.
Lose people want to to achieve win people one desire.
Good. Good.
Right. Like rain normally like music normally.
Not. I do not play. I do not play.
10. 9. 8.
Even if love past.
The four seasons.
Thirty years old that time.
Rainy day watercolor.
That is not just.
With Gang humane beautiful authority humane river together sing.
Really difficult to deal with.
Good. Good. Old husband and wife old practice.
Who is wrong. Correct name should be sixty years old old husband and wife old practice.
Correct. Correct.
Desire. Desire. Desire.
Wait a moment. Wait a moment.
To change come over. To change come over
I said gold worthy or virtuous person to plant. Leave other terminus.
Expression of surprise. Obviously just already lose.
Is you often come shop.
To regard as right. Every day all come.
This wine drink to body very advantageous.
Auntie. Today's sweet potato soup really especially good drink.
Yesterday sweet potato soup just bad drink is that so?
But. Director you really handsome.
You know my.
Of course know. Annoying male.
Don't be like this. Lee lady.
Is not what you say?
Annoying city man.
Ask you ask sound good.
This is this house shop Lee president.
Also is my mother.
My have always very love listen all of you program.
Precious thing son she has bit do not understand matter. Love to play with small character
but in fact is a pretty good child.
If her not too to do what one is told? Please you more to discipline a moment.
When can I to play with small character. My where have.
Quiet a bit.
And also. Director Mister.
I'm only because care for then more say a few words.
- Hope you're not want to misunderstanding
- Of course.
In principle I am to compare oppose office romantic love.
Afraid you listen will laugh I am at to show off my daughter
have a bit of very sorry?
- But there is nothing to be done. Grown beautiful also one kind of guilt
- mother.
- Call what call? Scared me to death
- nearly child just to fall.
My days. I just then all say whatever?
Be careful. Be careful a bit.
Want to get her safe send back home.
Aigoo. Surely want to to become exhausted.
Seemingly very to double.
My head.
Have a bit of unexpected.
Unexpected what?
Nothing. Only.
Didn't expect you and will to take care of people? Don't tell me just unexpectedly other.
Must. I am very will to take care of people.
I want to return home. Return home.
Hurry return home.
Be careful.
Find a position anyhow sit?
Right. Just now game my win. And never say me desire.
Then just tell me.
At my birthday that time give me one to be pleasantly surprised.
Until when can you birthday.
It will tell you.
Your that program really very well.
To be honest.
Is my mother give me inspiration.
Young that time. Father sit a boat.
At Russia before ocean missing.
But. Mother say her like very much that sentence.
Missing.
Is not death. But missing.
So mother every day all to make into  to adorn oneself.
Will also not to move house.
Before father like very much mother to sing a song the appearance.
So mother also always to groan song.
I am, that seeing her that way suddenly to find inspiration.
Father send give me gift. The first also last one.
To guess to guess my use it write what?
What?
You is my angel.
My first publication.
Then head song really very well listen.
Sun from west side come out. Unexpectedly will to boast my.
Precious thing son your song.
Is have old practice.
Then of course.
I am a have old practice woman.
Recently never at to compose.
Nothing inspiration.
Seems like here lost already what thing?
Come. Cheers.
Why give me so many?
Readily doing.
Heavens. Really hot.
Otherwise again have a cup.
Lee at awe-inspiring. There run.
Walk carefully road. To hear.
My anywhere also not go.
One two four. Fourth.
Two four three four.
Too funny.
I with artists drink wine.
And so on. To go there go coming here.
To go  side.
Please give me one bottle name of a famous Tang dynasty wine.
Found it. To go that side go.
That side. Artists let's go.
Let's go together.
Get up.
This is where is it?
Visitor. Guesthouse.
You this bastard.
I just feel that strange.
Yesterday late previous one strength give me to irrigate wine.
- Calm down a bit
- doing what? You.
- To go there to crawl. You.
Wait a moment wait a moment.
Rate. You yesterday drink both are not people kind.
What? What?
I am not people what is that?
Don't tell me with to substitute root you here.
- Done it those worse than a beast matters is that so
- is not? Is not.
Matters it's not like that.
You possibly don't remember.
At my drive the car time is you first towards my.
To spit saliva and so on.
And to scold my bastard. Say do not want to return home.
After that suddenly and just say want to become body undress.
Muddy egg. My cannot be are like that.
Say whatever lie?
Absolutely really.
Heavens. Heavens.
You see you see you see.
Underpants underpants.
Trousers went where.
Ask you trousers went where.
Annoying you.
Yesterday rate you all to spit fourth.
So my be to toss from side to side  one lodge for the night never sleep.
So early in the morning. My this is to fall  all one's life bacteria.
You still so hit me.
Sometimes. Like what language all unable to let you to feel to be gratified?
When you think unable to to bear live pressure.
Perfect broadcast hope able to to become your family
friend or spouse.
Mother. Fighting. My partner you around you.
My dear. I love you.
Congratulations precious thing son Miss. Precious thing son Miss bonus to explode or burst.
Not sure you exactly at what time that's why to go out gramophone record?
In fact. Is have a few pretty good poem for singing.
Then, we able to one more time to hear your song is that so?
I also to miss sb see you again fan of a singer.
Only be in love. Then to understand true love.
Don't want to tell other people.
To substitute root.
Looks like our really is natural matching pair.
For you and sing song.
Today we to invite arrived our first 13 position esteemed guest.
29 years old willow the Americas Miss.
Her to fit oneself for to dream of become a music people daytime goose.
So. Let us listen a moment her old practice.
Today I want to offer song that person.
She is DJ to extend precious thing son Miss.
My.
Really very honor.
Thank you.
More want want to say.
I think use my singing voice come replace.
So just let we together come listen listen.
Sad that time why time How are you getting by will become slow?
Why my the time How are you getting by like this very long?
Is me at overcome or at slowly habit.
All to imitate irresolute.
End where is it exactly in?
Director.
Someone always get like one video to go to upload.
Please let me gradually.
Become even more staunch.
Is not. No, not like that.
Everything all will not to change.
To extend precious thing son.
This melody is or is not very familiar in all cases.
2002 year at great big bar to issue poem for singing. My first publication.
To be called island.
2004 year receive it send disc to invite but or to be defeated.
That time optimum woman to assemble Purple.
Unexpectedly to plagiarize my poem for singing.
Willow the Americas Miss.
That is my to do bent.
Is me to do bent. Correct.
Seems like you do who is wrong.
-= don't want to to have an urge at once to end dialog. To sow music =-
seems like you do who is wrong.
Do who is wrong
-= don't want to to have an urge at once to end dialog. To sow music =-
Do who is wrong.
I'm only.
-= quickly =-
just to look for return my to lose poem for singing then come here.
Just to look for return my to lose poem for singing then come here.
Just to look for return once be you grab go my poem for singing.
My first publication.
Can you to just now you so words to say to be in charge of.
How come your proof it is you to do bent?
I have my perform that time video.
As well as I am now one's own mouth sing my song.
Still need more.
You is my angel.
Purple.
Are you joking.
- Hey. You this swindler
- turn off microphone.
You what are you saying?
This is live broadcast what do you want to do?
Older sister. Calm down a bit.
Precious thing son.
Exactly is what happened?
You actually at on-the-spot live broadcast in and to quarrel and to scold.
At least you explanation a moment.
Don't tell me I want to remained slient.
She said my to plagiarize.
Internet with to leave a message board in.
To upload to print that time time video.
Exactly the truth about sth is what?
You also the same.
Director you also.
Not believe me.
I am going.
Precious thing son.
That kind of circumstances just should turn off Mike to broadcast music. This don't even know.
Know harm have how big?
To extend precious thing son her will how is it?
And use ask.
From tomorrow started to prohibit her program.
At least want to give her one explanation opportunities.
Explanation what?
To plagiarize.
Don't care her have anything to plagiarize.
Unknownly her to make done this type of trouble. Just have a bit of conscience.
So my say whatever? Must get precious thing son to change to fall.
I said already.
If is the Americas gauze.
Will have such a thing feeling happen.
My understand.
So it is said.
Can cannot let the Americas gauze enter that program.
Then how can?
Like this she become real  done precious thing son person blamed for sb else's faults.
Simply unreasonable.
So my then come beg you.
Know already. Unknownly is big brother your request
I will good consider consider.
- To thank
- don't even know at what time then can to enjoy to enjoy elder brother good fortune?
This ball how hit?
Humane. What's wrong?
Hey. You are you okay.
At house is that so?
Otherwise my over find you.
You yourself at house. Right.
I still over.
I'm all right.
You blind to grasp what heart?
Have you or not afraid that I worry then endure do not say.
I already really it's all right.
Don't care the outside world to me over say whatever?
I already not to care.
So you also don't be like this to choke.
Get want have said all say it. More for you yourself to have a think about it.
Know.
Good enough. Hang up.
Precious thing son.
To extend precious thing son.
Time How are you getting by really quickly?
With everybody already know one month.
Regarding my. Audience eveyone was already one's close relatives sort existence.
Not sure you is or is not also like this feel that.
Send one head my most like song.
To come from Lee Seung Cheol  one head.
Super. Hero.
How is it?
Just now then head is Lee victory brilliant song
song to sow finish later you again to correct a moment.
I am said that.
Really sorry. I will to correct.
Director. Program to end later.
Want or not to go eat sashimi.
My treat.
Or next time.
Next time must certainly go.
To extend precious thing son recently have what's the news?
Do not seem to regarding to her news.
Don't know and whether or not to come back out of retirement. My see is to be hopeless.
Your that perfect broadcast.
Not quite will to die young or prematurely you to know don't know.
Proceed with properly.
To assign bureau chief say director to write a play DJ all changed to new.
Do you know precious thing son to hear later is what to react?
Her unexpectedly direct to rush went into bureau chief room.
Her ask exactly have anything
get hard work work behind the scenes personnel put in eye in.
To assign bureau chief that time surely very angry.
Then and what is the use?
Even oneself all to take care of bad.
I think Excuse me, may I ask.  A moment.
Head Director he is still to hold a meeting is that so?
We made appointment both bit meet.
Please wait a moment.
Head Director. To extend precious thing son Miss her is still.
Is. Know already.
To stay somewhere temporarily at the mind in to remember.
Gradually.  Good enough.
Listen is really is nothing feels like.
My guarantee. I will like just to make one's first public performance  singer the same.
Seriously to create. Seriously to sing a song.
- Head Director. Beg beg you to give me a opportunities I will.  - Precious thing son.
Presently to extend precious thing son.
With before or idol send that time at a loss compared to.
Feels like completely will no the same.
I also do not want to be more say whatever?
Just now then head song.
Is you yourself to create correct.
Now Infinite most bonus.
Then is not. Beast most bonus okay or not.
- That is no to extend precious thing son
- to extend precious thing son.
That is that to plagiarize other people work people?
And not never seen this type of people.
Before so to believe oneself infallible.
See she is now that way child.
I just say do artists this type of career people.
People predecessor later both are not one appearance.
Last time live broadcast in her that manner.
Completely to spoil one's appetite.
Go go go. Quickly leave here.
And hold guitar. Really when oneself is singer.
- Don't say anymore. To scold we what to do
- go quickly?
Looks like today don't have perform.
Today is don't have.
Recently business also not very good.
Also no money give they to begin work resources.
Just to release bit music confused time.
- Are you, to do music
- is not.
Suddenly to recall ten years ago here perform past one friend.
Kidding
we then to open shop four years more. Before this is at internet cafe.
What are you saying?
Not letter you yourself see.
I want to to change a beauty salon. I don't like to appear here a.
You have not go how long a period of time?
They always let me have waited a long time.
You yourself with they say.
But elder brother. Urgent die my.
- People always ask me new work at what time come out
-? New work.
That I already with new cave big fat person already said.
Let him following your style with your name to do one poem for singing.
- Really
- then of course.
To get out of the way.
- Inside is still to hold a meeting
- play really happy.
Frighten me.
- Lee director. This is doing what
- willow the Americas Miss?
- Ten years ago is that so
- what?
You say you play island is at 2002 year is that so?
Correct. But you suddenly ask this do what?
2007 year then open a business bar.
You but can at 2002 year just there perform.
Lee director. You exactly thinking do what?
Suddenly to rush enter other people office. And have anything politeness.
Lee Representative.
How come your do to obtain such a thing feeling?
Just because you this type of people slag.
Want use sincerity go performing arts radio program people but be innocent to waste.
People slag.
- You thought you at with who talk
- call to extend precious thing son come back.
Lee director. Lee director.
- You quickly rest
- elder brother. Really do not understand my this heart.
- Why what I've said you all?  - Quickly sleep.
Chauffeur Mister. Very sorry to quarrel to you.
It's all right. My see him feeling not very big good.
- To release head cheerful and lighthearted song give you all listen
- Good.
This head song before to exceed bonus. Who sing coming here.
Want to my give a hint
good.
To explode or burst bonus to assemble.
Idol group primogenitor. Idol send started also to end.
Purple.
-Purple correct. I know they
- originally you still remember.
My and remembered they dance.
- I also know
- sleep your a nap.
Like this jump. Right or wrong.
Take advantage of atmosphere good. Bring me you all go fun  place.
- Able to expectation a moment
- open your car.
- Mom
- you come in doing what?
I came to have a look have what able to help your?
Sun from west side come out. To move die my.
If don't have, forget about it.
To create how did matter kind?
Not really good. Mother otherwise we.
Drink cup bomb bar.
Are you crazy. How can say like this joint my intention?
Cheers.
Eat a bit snacks. Otherwise, will hurt stomach.
- Not eat
- you this girl clean learn your father those bad fault.
Ask you thing.
How don't have Lee director news?
How can I know? We and to quarrel one to support.
My see not like.
Is not you think that way. He with me completely will no suitable.
Character with your father exactly the same.
You think father.
Occasionally.
Is still wait father.
Your father what if just returned?
To miss sb towards he is showing off a moment myself also can get you to raise  like this good?
- Mom
- mother no need to you worry.
Believe me girl. Fighting.
Good. My believe.
You should be tell me earlier my.
I thought all already with children made appointment.
You recently is not occured some matter.
Head of a household have many views.
Program to go wrong plus to plagiarize events. I also really very to feel embarrassed or awkward.
Auntie say you're not let her tell me you where is it?
My beg long time her then have said.
To have a think about it my never before seen stand from your position thought of problem.
I should want to each other believe you then correct.
Sorry.
Don't worry.
I already to get over.
Cannot be again program. Also cannot again to sing a song.
Matters is let myself give to do smash.
Don't want to give up to sing a song.
Remembered you once said.
Seems like already to understand should be want to sing have something.
Continue to sing a song.
Originally sunbae you that is to make people.
Now and uncertain. I'm not make preparations.
Have a bit of too to be rude.  Wow. Elder brother.
Not to receive reward work total energy let people feel that special practical.
To extend precious thing son. Welcome you to come our dream work scene.
Then just started.
One, Two, Three four
" I do not know ".
Once recollection memory.
Just like this.
Gradually.
That is this feeling.
Obviously is already discard.
Now but and gradually to recall.
Obviously already forget.
With heart and soul to throw into. Heart and soul go love you.
With heart and soul to throw into. Hair without reservation go to harm.
With heart and soul to throw into. I want to again to drop into the river of love.
Never forget romance bitter and astringent.
Cannot be forgive me once cold and detached.
Want let do you know is how to miss you?
With heart and soul to throw into. Heart and soul go love you.
With heart and soul to throw into. Hair without reservation go to harm.
With heart and soul to throw into. I want to again to drop into the river of love.
Never forget romance bitter and astringent.
Cannot be forgive me once cold and detached.
Want let do you know is how to miss you?
My heartfelt say sound sorry.
Willow the Americas matters to process good enough.
Is. Already call her go foreign country stay both three month.
Didn't expect will to bring about like this serious consequences?
Really call me to remain silent.
You also don't again to go out what mistake? Understand.
- Sorry
- go out.
This time, matters is because my and to rise.
With other people unrelated.
I at this statement.
Inside the office so many silly matters end.
Atmosphere enough stiff enough awkward. Not bad.
You and just say currently topic.
You this person manner like this stiff do what?
You last time suddenly to visit.
From you there learn to a lot. Neck will go to also a lot.
So my isn't this want help you all.
Is at say regarding this time, first thousand to gather special collection
openly announced live broadcast matters.
Television with broadcast have live broadcast.
Use Lee representative's manpower come to arrange.
Is a good plan.
But. To go out act person list I think I will decide.
Of course. Lee representative's people you then do not worry.
Then of course. Are you, to implement director.
But my contrary to what one might expect very curious
seemingly you my hands have what trump card?
Is to extend precious thing son.
But.  Even if, matters already to settle.
But unavoidable also too early bit.
I will get my to plot proposal submit to go up.
- Then I leave first
- hey. Lee director.
Hey. Lee director.
Hey. You this.
Lee director.
You say. Is transmitter-receiver in less one
able director blow big.
Or to steer  festival objective.
DJ whole and leave blow big.
Lee Representative.
You this is at to threaten me.
Seems like like this.
You just use to extend precious thing son.
Bet this.
Get cell phone give me.
Here.
Brave to plant elder brother went where.
Lee Representative find he to be occupied with sth hastily and left.
Will also not tell me a moment today's schedule to arrange.
He said let you wait a moment.
The Americas gauze.
Living well.
Something happened. You actually will come find me.
My. Is not have less teach so born with rumors.
I don't quite want listen.
That is no rumor.
Middle school two grade that time. At that time, I just to dismiss students at the end of the school day return home.
Seen stepfather and at sudden hit my mother.
Don't care how is it my must stop he?
Afterwards one time past God then discovered oneself.
Already kill people.
Just at open the last time concert the day before.
Have a reporter hit came phone. Said to to expose that matter.
Precious thing son say.
Only want Purple can to dissolve. And then will able to stop this to cover news.
Say let her look at me whole life hit murderer brand alive.
Her cannot do it.
Until now, you then come tell me these want how is it?
I'm not determined by.
I have to go back.
The Americas gauze.
Don't want to too to hate precious thing son.
I said my not to care.
Give me sign your name.
To extend precious thing son historic to come back out of retirement album. Want to to manage the household jewel come collection.
Right. Regarding last time said transmitter-receiver re-instatement matters.
Already said I do not do transmitter-receiver.
Again past not long that is perfect broadcast first thousand to gather special collection broadcast.
I hope that the stage is precious thing son your to come back out of retirement the stage.
I don't have confidence.
How can? Presently perfect broadcast
is because of have you that's why have today's accomplishment?
So. Hope you must can stand get on that a the stage.
I am now therefore director identity formal to invite you.
Rely on you.
And also this is mine gift. Return home open take a look.
Hey. Singer to extend precious thing son.
Here. I also have gift.
You this.
You this is want in front of my face to reveal you wrist strength.
My gift. My gift.
Nothing wrong. Nothing wrong.
Elder brother. Really have to to accomplish like this.
What's wrong? Is not tell me good enough.
- But. Elder brother.  - Less nonsense. Quickly to catch up with.
Started.
Elder brother. Wait a moment. And so on.
Elder brother. I really unable to do.
Even if I do this. Her will like.
You just listen my. Split second ashamed can to ensure forever love.
Come. Go fourth everywhere.
Really have to if do like this.
Of course must. Didn't agreed that?
Elder brother. Wait and see I must certainly to make reprisals you
you this kid.
Elder brother. You should also know I don't quite to sing a song.
You one big man. At to play with what to depend on?
Hey. Leave don't even know want to hit sound to call out to sb.
Father's younger brother. Very old song do not again to release.
You. You do not know this is who song.
Who is it song?
This.  I'm really don't know no matter how you say then good?
Primogenitor to hit the target primogenitor.
Idol send started.  With to end.
Forever evil spirit.
Her will also not old. Do you know Purple.
This is Purple famous song. You're. My. Angel.
Father's younger brother. We or quickly let's go.
Hey.
Hello.
What?
I love you. To extend precious thing son.
To extend precious thing son.
Program broadcast performance sequence exterior surface I already if confirmed already.
You have to like this do cannot.
You do not know Lee Representative is what people?
You continue like this and be hurt.
Bureau chief.
I want to do myself want to do program.
Sorry.
Precious thing son older sister.
How are you getting by are you okay?
And became beautiful.
Very hard work.
Is very hard work. Because sister not around.
The Americas gauze older sister. You quickly. Brave to plant elder brother let you quickly come out.
You this is from do come.
Is at airport departure terminal.
But even if, again to go out album but also change anything
anyway all already is finished.
But. To extend precious thing son her really will to go out act this time, performances.
If her really come. Lee Representative surely will not good good to give up.
Elder brother. Is me.
I am now go back.
Come is early.
That. Elder brother.
What's wrong? What is the matter you say?
Is regarding today precious thing son the stage matter.
No need to worry. I will do as I see fit you just believe, my.
Is not. It's not like that.
- What's wrong
- precious thing son not the stage? I will later not wishing to do anything again to take a lot of trouble.
You what are you saying?
Stop talking nonsense.
Furthermore, the Americas gauze. This not only is you issue
this also to relate to my self-respect issue.
Furthermore,. Even if, is to extend precious thing son her really came also absolutely cannot be the stage.
Understand. Hang up.
Elder brother. Elder brother.
The Americas gauze older sister. We have to quickly go then can. Quickly come out.
- Esteemed guest all if confirmed already
-
Precious thing son her came do you know.
Happy you just laugh one laugh.
Good. Is last one business to advertise.
OK.
One. Two. Started.
Hello everybody. Today we at last to welcome came.
Perfect broadcast first thousand to gather.
Thanks eveyone to be capable of attend today like this rather sense activity.
And at today's spectators banquet in also came a lot.
Once and we to share with others life experience those lead actor.
To assign astringent fine jade. To assign astringent fine jade.
Perfect broadcast. Perfect life.
Now formal started.
Heard you to go out album. Copy should give you send a KaKaO. Talk
( to inject : South Korea cell phone chatting software ) To congratulate a moment and so on.
Is really is busy have a bit of confused and disoriented.
I have to for perform do prepare. You able to say to recount.
What urgent?
Purple to dissolve that time. Copy should to brace oneself to do sth get you retain.
The Americas gauze anything good. That is don't have annealed strength.
To extend precious thing son you contrary to what one might expect have?
Able to bet to implement director life the stage that kind of annealed strength.
The Americas gauze but don't have these. Have a bit of regret.
You. Just now say whatever?
To implement director life.
Lee director life.
Precious thing son older sister.
Your younger brother have grown really enough grow.
I will well to appreciate.
To transmit to sow something big happened. Precious thing son older sister now.
Quickly. Quickly.
What? Precious thing son older sister what?
What has happened? You contrary to what one might expect quickly say?
Why you don't have tell me? This the stage you bet is what?
You think you like this become my chest will comfortable.
I cannot publish this the stage.
Are you, want to escape.
You just not for those sit at spectators banquet in
and wait listen you to sing a song the people to have a think about it.
For you Fighting. More precious those people they is waiting for you.
Purple to dissolve. To plagiarize right and wrong.
You thought only to sacrifice oneself oneself then can help to other people is that so?
Sing. Just to you yourself.
And also. Just for me.
Mom.
My house princess. Have anything taking eat food.
Don't have.
Eat good food then can well to sing a song.
Precious thing son. Mother will here with your father together listen you to sing a song.
Unimportant to open up well sing. Know already.
Rotten girl. Why not talk?
We precious thing son. Well doing light breakfast come back
tonight just together overjoyed drink one cup to burn beer how is it?
- Know already
- What?
- I said I understand. Hang up
- Fighting.
An actor's lines prepare.
Next we want to to invite second department last one esteemed guest.
Talking about perfect broadcast. Just certainly have to to carry her.
From perfect broadcast head to sow until now,
her always protect in our body beside.
Until not long ago her or always is perfect broadcast center.
She also once is Purple to lead a group. To extend precious thing son Miss.
Please use warm applause welcome.
Hello everybody. Can one more time at perfect broadcast in with everybody to say hello to.
Let i feel that very cheerful. I am singer to extend precious thing son.
Purple activity period. As well as at finish the Americas broadcast that time.
Once always to everybody say thanks everybody. I love you.
In fact. Then all only script for play, opera, movie etc  an actor's lines.
Don't have to pour into what I really want? My redo returning to this is at because.
Feel that now able to sincerity to eveyone say.
Thanks everybody. I love you.
Perfect broadcast to me that is one kind of love.
At that way leave here in future
this the stage and also eveyone all let me extremely to miss.
Eveyone. Thanks everybody.
I love you.
Next I want to for everybody act sing a song
to extend precious thing son song Again. Thanks everybody.
Where did you go?
Quickly come back. This is live broadcast.
Turn off illumination.
And so on. What is this you are doing?
Elder brother. You thought I am at do -less copy buying and selling.
From today in future our DJ whole all from SBS to retire.
All take away
all take away.
What are you saying
I said let you take away?
Even if, don't have you all
want with we to cooperate people all a row done line  know.
You just try and see
I will let you all company one's affiliation people whole to prohibit to go out and come in television station.
Big brother. My that's not what is meant?
And so on
ask you go out.
Big brother. Don't want to misunderstanding my meaning
please you go out.
I will at door before that coffee shop wait your.
And not rogue.
Find half of the day.
But. We considered to be have what relationship?
Not as director with DJ identity meet.
Yes.
What director will just to predecessor DJ even this all bet?
This. Is bureau chief give your.
I also have things want to give you.
Come. Grand Slovakia rhythm. (House. Beat)
To cultivate mood. Here come paragraph most perfect song (Shouting)
How is it?
Is is. This i also feel is nothing.
Then just come take a look this. Sorrowful to express emotion song.
Prelude. I love you I love you
this song originally white Ji Young want with I want to I already hide get up don't have give.
Give precious thing son you remain.
Come. One-third handleless cup. Just one-third handleless cup.
Cover song. Lee the Americas child teacher.
Immortal to sell well song. Winter cedar Miss.
Hip-hop version. This part.
Winter cedar. Here use to crisscross beat.
200 people stand as row let her all wear as shorts.
Winter. Cedar. Small. Older sister.
This song really is let people to rise goose pimples. Is that so?
Have worked hard
no, it's not. And so on. Don't be like this.
Precious thing son.
This is at beautiful early morning. I am Jinchang prefecture level city in Gansu alkane.
Hello everybody this is at romance game. I am plain and simple worthy or virtuous person.
Next one head song I want to for you to broadcast extremely special song.
Her to arrange remove to plagiarize dirty people at last and start all over.
- She also once is Purple to lead a group.  - Once is Purple to lead a group.
Also once to hold a governmental office or post past perfect broadcast DJ to extend precious thing son.
Yes. Overcome one paragraph difficult that time a period of time
after that and is making an announcement album.
We also very understand that kind of feeling right.
What? It is said that all song all from her personally to do word to compose.
Very inspiring. Really extremely great.
Please everybody also have to for her Fighting to cheer for.
Also have to let her to feel we audience friends to carry to her power.