I was in a forest.
I couldn't find my way.
I was hopelessly lost.
It kept getting darker.
I started to panic.
I thought,
I'll never find my way again.
UNDER THE RAINBOW
And then... I see a man,
stock still,
looking at me,
with so much kindness.
He reaches out,
and I go to him, without thinking.
And someone is behind him.
Like an angel.
He is an angel.
Pointing at him.
He carries me up and away.
Wait, the angel carries you?
No, the man.
Then he and I are flying.
On a horse, but a weird one,
with a bird's head.
A hippogriff.
A horse with a bird's head.
It's called a hippogriff.
So we're flying,
flying over the countryside.
And suddenly I felt great.
I was confident.
All my fear was gone.
And we fly over my home,
and I see my dad as tiny.
Really tiny!
Waving his arms, yelling to me.
Not that way!
"Not that way!"
Stop that, Lauranie!
Give me those...
...wands.
This is not a game.
Look! Now it's broken.
It won't work anymore!
And the flowers, the pumpkins!
I'm not picking them up!
Mathieu, Lulu! You hear me?
Nina is so absorbed.
Stock still,
totally into her book.
Yeah, it's the Bible.
- The Bible?
- Yes.
Every chance she gets,
she reads the Bible.
- Your dream?
- That's all I remember.
It's idiotic, but I was thinking...
there's a chance
it will never happen to me.
What?
I woke up and I thought,
I've never really felt that.
I've never been carried away
like that.
I've never really loved. I...
never really loved someone.
It got me so depressed.
Come on,
you're so young, you have time!
Nothing but bad luck lately.
Yeah, what can you do?
I had the 4 and the 11.
4th time in a row I had 2.
That's the trifecta.
You need 3, that's the whole point.
Anyway,
there are more dire things.
Right.
- My condolences, Pierre.
- Thank you.
You hadn't seen your dad
in how long?
I was just wondering that,
last night.
I don't know...
2 or 3 months, I guess.
I feel nothing.
I hadn't seen him in ages,
but it affects me.
Affects you.
Because you decided it would.
My father was nothing to you.
He was not nothing to me.
What does that mean?
Don't exaggerate.
He's your dad.
He was always there for Sandro.
And he was very shaken.
Where is Sandro?
Did you ask him about the deposit?
I didn't get a chance.
We buried someone. You notice?
What deposit?
Well...
I either live at Mum's till I'm 50,
or rent a place.
Pierre!
Oh, I loved your father so!
- Be strong, OK?
- Yeah.
You can still talk to him.
He hears you.
- You'll talk to him?
- Sure.
In any case, you'll see him soon.
- You must speak to him.
- Yes, I will.
That's good.
Madame Irma. She still exists?
Apparently.
And still sick.
You remember the date?
Date?
Of your death, remember?
Come on!
How should I remember that crap?
Date of your death?
No, it's horseshit.
A crazy lady
who used to do everyone's horoscope.
It's nonsense.
So... when is it?
I said I can't recall.
I can. It made an impression on me.
Not that I believe it.
Sure, it's horseshit but...
it makes an impression.
There they are, I'm off.
You're off?
Aren't you coming to Odette's?
Certainly not.
Come by the office,
talk about the deposit?
- Your girlfriend has kids?
- As you can see.
Can't be fun for you.
No, it isn't.
I'm parked at the corner.
Pull it up!
Pull the handle up,
the thingy will fall.
This is great.
Enough room for a vegetable garden.
You said a tiny garden.
It's not so tiny.
No, don't drink the water!
It's supposedly drinkable, but...
Which reminds me,
Eric said he might stop by.
Tell him the water's back,
but it's brown.
Nina, I'm leaving!
That's my mum, I'm not taking it.
Did her operation go well?
Hands aren't easy, I'm told.
That's her again.
If I answer,
we'll just argue as usual.
Nina!
She won't say goodbye.
The Red Sea must be parting.
You free Saturday?
Not Saturday.
That's the Princes' Ball.
- You never showed me your dress.
- Right!
Actually, there are two.
I loved them, so I got both.
I don't really want to go.
Why?
Your dream might be an omen.
You could meet someone.
That's exactly
what Mrs Bérard said.
Is she your fortune teller?
Well, she's a radiesthesist.
Hello, Ma'am.
A survey on the fears of the French.
No, thanks!
Hello. A survey...
The crisis.
This is a time of crisis.
Terrorism.
Unemployment.
Poverty, disease.
Like I said, the climate.
It's all mixed up.
Winter in summer,
summer in winter.
Summer in winter.
Well, thanks.
You're welcome.
I'm not working enough.
I have to work on the recital!
My goddamn father!
What's he got to do with it?
Here I am doing stupid surveys.
Will he lift a finger?
He runs a driving school.
Is he rich?
No, but...
My grandfather just died.
Left him money, he could help.
Every single time,
I have to beg him.
For the deposit,
I have to get on my knees.
The grandfather you liked?
Going to the party?
What party?
The princes' ball, on Saturday.
I have a quintet rehearsal.
Shit, you're rehearsing.
Why? You're going?
Well I don't know...
I won't know anyone.
Julien's brothers got comps.
Frankly,
I don't feel like going but...
Without you...
They might finish early.
I could meet you there.
I was sure you were going.
I'll try to skip a movement.
Could totally suck.
It could always totally suck.
Why do anything?
Just come and see.
- Got to go!
- Later!
You know them, it's your milieu.
I don't.
I'll feel like an idiot.
My milieu? Don't go overboard.
You're not from the jungle.
And you have to dress.
I don't own a suit.
You don't need one.
Got a black jacket?
Anyway, on Saturdays
I have to pick up my mum.
Pick up your mum?
She works Saturday nights.
I drive her home.
She's afraid she'll get mugged.
So at midnight, in any case,
I'll have to split.
Where's your dad?
He's in the cemetery.
When does he go to heaven?
Heaven? No.
No, he'll stay in the cemetery...
- Morgane, eat your carrots.
- I'm eating them!
Are you going to die?
Sure, one day. We all die.
So when do you die?
I have no idea.
Enough, Johanna.
Doesn't bother me.
Stop, you'll break your glass!
Eat your vegetables.
I'm eating them!
Will you go to heaven when you die?
You don't go to heaven when...
You stay in a sort of...
Like... Like in a box.
Can't hear myself talk!
- Got any olive oil?
- On the right.
It's not the body.
The spirit goes to heaven.
And there you meet
everyone you knew.
People think you go to heaven,
because they need
to believe in an afterlife.
But no.
You turn into a skeleton.
You've seen those before, right?
The skin goes and the bones remain.
Personally, I think we go to heaven.
The truth is, no one knows.
You do as you see fit.
Put that glass down!
No way I drink that water!
Or even wash with it.
Washing with brown water!
It's not dirty, it's rust.
I don't wash with rust.
It won't last.
There you go. It works.
For more heat, press here.
Minus, plus.
This button. Minus, plus.
Got it?
If it turns off... It won't.
But if it does,
press here, with the flame.
I'll never remember.
Fine.
Well, I'll say goodbye to Nina.
Yeah, I remember.
He's the first one who...
Isn't John the Baptist
from Jesus' family?
No! Jesus has no family.
Even his parents aren't his parents.
Oh I see.
- Know what "Jesus" means?
- Tell me Tuesday.
It means "saviour".
She keeps scratching. Notice?
She never stops.
Then sometimes not at all.
It's very psychosomatic.
Right. Everything is psychosomatic.
Well everything is!
I didn't say it,
the dermatologist did.
I don't get it. I clicked OK.
And it says to enter my code again.
Enter it.
All right.
I enter it...
And it says "incorrect code".
I don't know.
Maybe you spelled it wrong.
Wait, I know.
It might be another one.
What? You have several codes?
Sure! I have a code for...
Why? Use one code!
I only have one code.
Shit, that one didn't work either!
Take a look?
I know there's a way to...
Why don't you look?
For once, pick up a manual.
Say, "I can do this. I'm no dummy."
Objects don't hate me!
Like an old lady!
Want to end up like my mum,
who can only push on or off?
Is that your technological aim?
Seriously, Marianne!
Fine. I asked because you were here!
Finding your new man's email
is no fun.
He was never my man.
And I no longer see him!
But fine, no problem.
I'll figure it out.
It's no joke.
She really wants a first communion.
Nina!
She wants a first communion.
You quit med school.
What did Dad say?
Not a word...
What's your point?
He was disappointed but he let you.
This is the same.
It's fine for her to do this.
It will give her time to find
what she really wants to do.
Don't answer for her.
I'm talking to Laura.
That's right. A gap year.
And that was your own idea?
Sure.
Incredible. You don't like
what she does, you look at me.
Your daughter keeps scratching.
"The Casseul Empire Shaken."
Listen, no.
Don't bother. Thanks.
Talk to you later.
What was that?
Pain in my ass!
Thierry.
Any article that skewers me,
he just has to read it to me.
Enough!
It's been 2 weeks! I know about it.
They're sick. "An Empire Shaken"!
They have no right!
They can't just print that bull!
Don't worry, darling.
I am worried.
About time! I called twice!
Don't yell at me! I hurried.
My phone's off.
What good is a cell phone?
Get on. I have to get back.
I ask you to pick me up once,
it's like pulling teeth!
Where's your shoe?
Strap your helmet. I got a party!
Is it a shoeless party?
Why are you missing a shoe?
The Casseul Inc. empire is shaken.
The CEO, Vincent Casseul,
and 4 executives,
accused of massive toxic...
Pierre? What's the matter?
I just got in. Everything all right?
Go ahead.
Oh, that's why.
So you're actually interested.
You don't believe in that.
You're reason incarnate.
If you can't remember, I won't say.
March 14th.
This one. This year.
Oh I see.
No. Just asking.
I wanted to know.
Had a little trouble sleeping.
You don't have to tell me that.
Of course!
Of course it's horseshit.
I'm just curious.
You reminded me of it
at the cemetery and...
So I'm feeling a little guilty
about Sandro.
I'm thinking he must be waiting,
all alone.
Then, I see him dancing
with this incredible girl.
And from then on,
hypnotised, under her spell.
She approached me.
I didn't get it.
She liked you.
These things happen.
Can we start?
In any case,
I don't even have her number.
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
You're weird.
Can we start?
There, great.
No! Don't cover his butt,
cover his face!
Now...
Hang on. A little over...
There. Good.
My wand. Or this won't work.
No, not now.
Not too noisy?
I gave them 5 minutes.
No, it's fine.
Joanna wants you to say good night.
Really?
- Yeah.
- Oh my.
What?
No, I...
I don't know how.
To say good night?
It's uncomfortable. What do I say?
- Are you kidding?
- No.
You kiss her, say "Good night."
Well...
All right.
Maybe it was a bad idea
to come here with the kids.
Why?
We put you out.
Not at all.
It's not like that.
It's fine.
No, we're putting you out.
You were alone, 3 of us move in.
Eléonore, I said it's fine.
Come on. I can take it.
I can adjust
for 3 or 4 months, without...
Three months, barely.
I move in on March 14th.
March 14th?
That's right.
- How about that?
- What?
Well it's...
That's very precise.
That's the date on the lease.
Hopefully, it'll be ready on time.
I'm exhausted.
I wanted to kill Morgane tonight.
So annoying!
So is Joanna, in her own way.
They're kids. Kids are annoying.
They demand attention,
every second. It fries your brain.
You repeat yourself over and over.
It's animal training. Awful.
That's undeniable.
I mean, when you look at it head on.
Head on, that's how it is.
No, Laura. Don't confuse things.
I do argue with your dad,
we have differing views.
But I'm sure.
I know he's incapable
of doing such a thing.
Polluting,
knowingly and voluntarily.
No, it's nonsense.
The lady I see told me,
"Ordeals await you."
Your fortune teller?
Not a fortune teller,
a radiesthesist.
I swear,
everything she said is true.
Yeah? Like what?
That ordeals awaited me.
That I was too sensitive.
I had a burning need to be loved.
That I lacked confidence.
And that I'd meet
the man of my dreams.
Why don't you ask her
where your musician is?
She's not a dowser.
I know one who is.
You do?
Nina?
It's your father. Come down!
Now you tell me.
- Couldn't you warn me?
- They just called.
I can't turn work down.
What is it?
Voice work.
For a shampoo.
Eco-friendly.
So I'd keep her till Thursday night?
Fine, what else can I say?
The blue tube is... in any case.
The yellow one
is if it itches really, really bad.
Oh and...
I said no, but...
if she has a fit,
she sleeps with that.
This is getting hard to take.
OK, bye.
Bye, and thanks.
I have to concentrate
full time on my music,
if I want to make it.
You, instead of a bank,
you go see your dad.
Mum told me...
that Grandpa left you something.
Here, this is for the deposit.
About the rest, I'll think it over.
Got a minute for...?
Excuse me. Do you have a minute...?
Excuse me...
TWO MONTHS LATER...
"It's easier to split an atom
"than a prejudice."
According to Einstein.
I would also agree with him
that a rumour
is harder to combat
than an entire army.
Relax, he'll be here.
His rehearsal was over at 4:30.
He should be here.
He'll be here.
That's enough talk.
Now it's time to get down
to serious matters.
Bravo, daddykins.
Where the hell is Sandro?
He's working, constantly.
His audition is coming up.
Plus those surveys.
Why not give him money?
Out of principle?
Yes, principle.
Why are we here?
"So the parents can meet."
Isn't that 19th-century?
Not just the 19th century.
Nowadays, too.
They met a month ago.
The parents have to meet already?
It's been two months.
And this is the occasion.
Don't start, Pierre.
I'm begging you.
I think it's fun.
I never saw a Legion of Honour.
Didn't quote me once in your speech.
What should I have said?
Let me congratulate you.
I'm very happy for you.
You might have said...
"I congratulate my sister.
"An actress unjustly ignored,
"she brings my life
all the humanity it needs."
Oh, Mr Alexis!
Seen my bracelet?
Yes. Really pretty.
He can't afford better.
Which I like.
He's so real-life, it's refreshing.
He struggles all day,
thinks only about music.
He was cute...
Do you have any drinkable red wine?
Then go and see!
Wait.
Want to order?
Hello. I'm fine, thanks.
Sandro, my dad. Dad, Sandro.
Pleasure.
I thought he was a waiter.
Hello, sir.
How are you?
Did your parents come with you?
No, I'll go get them.
Does he stutter, or am I...
I knew you'd say that.
He does? I didn't notice.
Marianne!
What are you doing?
Getting bored silly. Why?
Mum, come on.
We're over here with Laura and...
You have a license.
I have the license, but...
I haven't driven in so long.
I need to regain confidence.
I've moved out of town.
You see?
Now I absolutely have to...
I have a car I don't use.
It's parked outside, I don't use it.
Seriously.
Rules of the road?
Basically, I know them.
No, not basically.
The rules are important.
Anyway, if you want
I could give you lessons.
Nice of you.
Rehearsal go OK?
Yeah, fine. Fine.
But I missed you.
So did I.
I didn't hear a word my dad said.
Your mother is so young.
Not that young.
I have to get back.
It's funny.
He wet the bed until the age of 15.
A lot of people told me that...
that and stuttering
often go together.
But why? I mean...
It happens
to converted left-handers.
But he's a righty! So...
No one knows.
Or some childhood trauma,
they say that often.
As far as I know, frankly,
he wasn't particularly traumatised.
However you bring them up is wrong.
Excuse me,
I must tell my husband something.
I turn around and I see Sandro,
staring back
with an angel pointing him out.
Because there was this statue
behind him, a finger
pointing at him.
The fortune teller said that?
No, it was my dream.
I see,
but the fortune teller said it.
She's not a fortune teller,
but yes she said it.
You remember
I didn't want to go to that party.
I remember. Do you?
Girl's totally nuts.
Come on...
But how old is her mother?
That's her mother?
You're the fairest of them all.
As usual.
Don't bother.
My father believes in nothing.
This is verified. They're facts.
Facts... They're coincidences.
Anyway, anyway...
what we wanted to say is...
we're getting engaged on...
March 14th.
We had said the 13th,
but it was a Friday.
I was wondering,
is there some medicine...?
No connection.
But since I have these thoughts
that keep coming back,
I thought maybe
there's some drug to...
get rid of them, stop them.
What kind of thoughts?
Not the thoughts themselves.
It's how they keep coming back,
all the time.
Listen,
I can't help, I'm a podiatrist.
But I know a good therapist.
Want his address?
No, I was just asking.
No, I'm fine.
It's just...
I'm a little tense right now.
That can't help.
I got people at the house.
Tiresome...
Yes. Getting back to your feet,
the soles.
Wear them every day,
or the pain returns.
Isn't love beautiful?
I'm not objective.
Meaning?
Really?
I get it.
I didn't know.
I meant it ironically.
I don't think love is so great.
Some detail you get attached to,
fabricating a myth.
- Don't you agree?
- Not at all.
Of course not.
I must not be very perceptive.
I didn't see a thing.
No one saw a thing.
Think you'll be destroyed for long?
Lots of charming guys around,
you know?
- Like you?
- Yes, good example.
- You don't believe in love.
- No.
But... I believe in friendship.
I hate seeing you like that.
Kiss her already!
What did we say?
I tap my wand and he turns into...?
- Prince Charming.
- Right, and kiss her!
Come on, not this again.
You wanted to be Prince Charming
and now...
you won't kiss her.
That's not charming, sorry!
You too! Everybody!
Get into character!
You have to believe a little!
Lulu, same thing!
Each time you offer the apple,
you look apologetic.
You're a witch.
So act like a witch a little!
I don't like being a witch.
Oh? What do you want to be?
A tree.
A tree?
Get to the right.
Right. Right!
Get to the right! The right!
Excuse me, I'm sorry. Sorry.
OK, we're all right, but...
when I grab the wheel,
you have to let me.
You fought me, you can't fight.
- I'm sorry.
- Sorry!
How long has it been
since you drove?
I don't know, 10 years.
Sure, but even then,
it was the same.
I was paralysed.
I thought I was more mature.
That I'd be more at ease.
But it's like before.
I'm paralysed... terrified.
No reason to be terrified.
There is!
I keep feeling I'm going to die.
Or else kill people.
It's a fantasy.
I understand.
A fantasy, but that's just it.
It is a fantasy.
You can't always just submit.
Take control, we're not children.
We must be capable
of taking control.
Right.
That's what I'm trying to do.
Maybe acupuncture,
at the same time, could help.
Maybe it will relax me.
Well, in any case, thanks.
For dropping me off.
No problem, it's on my way.
- See you Thursday?
- Right. Thursday.
- Sure you won't have coffee?
- No, I'm fine. Thanks.
See? That's my car.
See you Thursday.
Thursday.
Excuse me...
Excuse me, I'm lost.
I'm going to Rue des Acacias.
Lost my way.
Rue des Acacias?
I'm going there.
Can I drop you?
No. Thank you, but...
I wanted to walk. I've been there,
but I always drove.
Now I'm completely lost.
All right.
It depends
what you expect from life.
If you want to go fast,
no time to lose,
if you know exactly what you want,
it's straight ahead, then right.
But if you're more of a dreamer,
open to the unknown, a thinker,
that way.
It's longer, but much prettier.
It's called "Needle Way".
Well thanks.
Don't mention it.
I'm waiting to see which way you go.
I got totally lost.
I cut through the woods.
I got all turned around.
Fortunately,
this guy straightened me out.
He wanted to drive me.
He was strange. Know what he said?
This corkscrew is impossible.
Hello.
Was it pretty? Like the walk?
You know each other?
He's the one.
The man who gave me directions.
This is Maxime. My neighbour.
I mentioned him.
Laura, my darling niece.
Laura...
Want some wine?
Sure.
I'll go, Marianne.
You can stay.
I have to go anyway.
A pleasure, Laura.
Maybe see you soon?
Yes, maybe.
Tomorrow your life changes.
You'll have a 21st-century corkscrew.
One that unscrews corks.
Thanks for the extension cord!
He's great.
You know he's in music?
Really? What does he do?
I don't know,
I didn't really get it.
I know he writes articles.
Critiques... I don't know.
And he works for a festival.
Or an orchestra.
I can't recall, but he's in music.
Funny.
- Pretty, right?
- Yeah.
"Hi, Mum! Hi, Laura!"
How are you, Laura?
I have no idea what's wrong.
It's been 2 hours.
She won't talk, won't answer.
The Bible's not doing her any good.
I'll go say hello.
In any case,
I know when this shit got into her.
Well then, please Eric, let's do it.
Let's at least try.
- We'll go see Devaux, the 3 of us.
- No, please.
What's so terrible?
What are you afraid of?
I'm afraid of nothing.
I won't go see some guy
with his own ideas about parenting
so he can drum us full
of his personal morality! What a bore!
You don't know, you never tried.
And this is for Nina.
Not for you.
I'm not trying to convince you.
Try.
A shrink can tell me nothing new.
It's our separation
that Nina can't stand.
Are you doing so much better
since you started therapy?
Yes, I'm doing better.
Hundreds of dead fish.
Utter devastation.
Local people all point
to upriver Casseul Industries,
saying they fill these waters
with toxic waste.
CEO Guillaume Casseul
denies his company had a role
in this ecological disaster,
but the company stock price
took a plunge...
Mum?
Mum, could I take this
to Dad's tomorrow?
You're not going.
He called.
He can't. Something came up.
Come on.
I mentioned it, I didn't call him.
It just came up.
He'll feel obliged.
He'll think I put you up to it.
I don't care if he comes!
Hardly knows I make music!
And if it's so he can scowl
like at the Legion of Honour,
no thanks!
I said it just came up.
I said Sandro's concert is soon.
I didn't say to come.
"Sandro's concert."
What? It's not your concert?
It's a finals recital.
There are others. It's not just me.
I say "Sandro's concert," too.
We don't care about the others.
Did Laura hear it already?
Did she like it?
He won't let me. He wants me
to hear it fresh, in concert.
Directly at the concert?
Of course, Mum. No comparison!
I'll be finished in two minutes.
Where do we meet after?
My place?
Your place?
Your place is better.
My place?
My place.
She sees herself
in a pretty white dress, that's why.
Sure, but...
that's incidental.
Lots of girls
want a first communion.
It's not about that.
The move maybe.
Maybe.
As I see it,
I'm hearing about a girl
who's not with us.
Who isn't concentrating.
You know, when children...
when they feel things are
a little... unstable,
they need to find reassurance.
I was recently separated.
But it's fine. Everything's fine...
For the child,
I certainly hope so.
By the way,
I thought it over.
I'm OK with it.
You're OK with what?
What you wanted.
How you wanted us to be.
To be freer.
I'm OK with it.
You're right.
Want us to try?
To get back together?
You don't love me anymore.
Don't. I'll always love you.
That's not the point.
Sorry, I'm no good.
No big deal, we're alive.
No, I can't even drive.
I can't even...
I'll never drive again.
You can drive.
Just check the rear-view mirror.
I'll give you a manual, for review.
My husband did the driving.
He didn't want me to drive.
He was right. We nearly died!
It's your second lesson.
I wanted only to be alone,
to be independent.
It was my dream.
Now I realise...
I need help with everything.
I'm handicapped, it's horrible.
I have to re-learn everything.
It sucks to be alone.
No, don't say that.
It's wonderful.
The peace of mind.
No obligations, no negotiations.
No noise.
Well...
Should we go?
Ignition, signal, rear-view.
Are you sure?
We can't stay here.
You don't want to drive?
I already know how.
We almost died!
No. I'm not supposed to die today.
You're not?
When are you supposed to die?
March 14th.
- This year?
- This year, yes.
Really?
Just a note of levity.
This astrologer, a madwoman...
told me that 40 years ago.
They never say the date of death.
They see it, but they don't tell.
I'm surprised!
Well I don't care.
Fortune-teller ethics don't matter to me.
I really don't care.
Ready to go?
They have no right.
Yeah, I know. But I don't care.
Ignition.
Signal.
Rear-view.
No, the rear-view
is to see behind you.
- Bravo again!
- Thank you.
- Call me?
- Sure.
- I was so embarrassed.
- I didn't hear it.
Like it?
It was remarkable. Quality writing!
Look. Behind you.
The composer?
Maxime Wolff.
I know who you are.
Your work is great.
I'll leave you to your friends.
But here's my card.
This is my card.
Call me.
I'd like to discuss an idea.
All right.
Laura, why are you here?
Are you lost again?
No, not this time.
Too bad, I can't help you.
See you round?
- See you?
- Yes.
You know Wolff?
- Did you know he was coming?
- No, I didn't!
- Incredible. What luck.
- You knew?
No, I didn't know!
Is he famous?
What do we do first?
We put our stuff away!
That's right!
What is it? Why the long face?
Why are you frowning? Simon.
Want to be a squirrel,
if you won't kiss her?
She's the one who won't.
Really? Why?
She doesn't love me anymore.
We'll see, no big deal.
It is a big deal.
No, listen...
We'll think it over...
we'll work it out.
- I don't know...
- Can I be a dog?
Sure, yeah...
Well, is there a dog in the show?
There are lots of animals.
Sure, no problem.
Want to be a squirrel?
No, I don't play animals.
Well... Sure you don't mind,
half way through the term?
No! Just the opposite.
No, I need a flower.
I need a squirrel.
My mushroom shows up
only half the time.
See you Wednesday?
- Yes, thanks.
- My pleasure.
Well... goodbye.
Goodbye, girls!
Time to go!
The worst is when even close friends
start to have doubts.
Maybe they're not that close.
It's understandable.
So tempting to join the pack.
And he's not even polluting.
There you are!
One more reason not to worry.
Rumours pass.
People will tire of it.
That's what made you so sad?
Yes. Well...
Life in general.
These days, I don't know...
it's complicated.
True, it's complicated.
Oh, Maxime! You here?
- Hi.
- How are you?
Not cold?
SEPARATE AND GROW
GETTING FAMILIAR WITH DEATH
And with your father?
No, with my father it's fine.
He's dead anyway, so...
Want to talk about him?
How'd your father treat you?
No, listen. I said no.
My problem is...
I don't understand.
I don't recognise myself.
I don't buy that shit.
How can it get to me?
That's what I want to know.
Is this the first time
you can't control something?
Look,
I think coming here was a mistake.
I need an answer here and now.
I don't want to...
spend years just...
How much do I owe?
Nothing.
Thank you.
Very good solo, Julian.
From the same place again, please.
So I pushed it, I said,
"why not play it at the festival?"
He said yes, on the spot!
- Horwitz?
- Horwitz!
That's amazing!
Horwitz wants to play my piece?
Holy shit!
He liked it that much?
He might tell you himself.
I gave him your number,
he'll call you.
Holy shit, this is... amazing.
Amazing!
Wait a second.
I don't understand.
The orchestra is full. So he...
He would take the place
of the 1st violin. Got to.
Julien's place?
If his name is Julien, then yes.
- Really?
- Of course.
He's my friend.
Not about your friend.
You want your music to be known?
This is an uncanny break.
You don't get that?
Sure I do.
It was really special today.
Nice of you.
It's not nice, it's what I think.
Great, Sandro.
I'm very happy.
- Very happy.
- Right.
Sandro!
Starting to shape up!
Did Wolff like it?
- You think I'm awful.
- No way.
- I'm ashamed.
- Of what?
I'm in love with Sandro.
I think of someone else,
it's not normal.
Normal or not...
What is normal anyway?
Can't imagine how guilty I feel.
Yes, I imagine it very well.
I ruined my life with that guilt.
He invited me to a party.
Really?
But I'm not going to go.
Fuck...
I have to call Sandro.
I don't know how to tell him.
What do I do?
He left me so many messages,
it's terrible.
Maybe a text message?
Not as harsh.
Well, not as harsh for you.
Eat your apple!
In this light, I see them.
Mum!
My mother says I have wrinkles.
Not wrinkles, fine lines.
- Wrinkles!
- Fine lines.
Come on, she's fabulous.
She's perfect.
Marianne, I know about this.
You have to act early.
The sooner the better.
She can't get a facelift at 24,
that's ludicrous!
I use creams.
It's not a facelift. It's acid
produced by the body, re-injected.
She's 24. She's got time!
She doesn't have to act like you.
Like me? Meaning?
I don't know...
Like you.
You have stuff done.
Why? What stuff do I have done?
I don't know.
I have no idea what you got done.
You're 62, Fanfan.
I didn't mean to hurt her feelings.
- Then why say that?
- I said her age.
I can't pretend to...
You think old age is fun?
What do you mean?
As an actress, well...
You like your wrinkles, folds,
sagging flesh?
You think it's fun?
No, I don't.
Neither does she.
Nobody does.
It was about Laura.
We have to go now anyway.
Nina, stop.
You'll get all marked up.
Should I drop you?
No, thanks. We'll walk a little.
You still don't drive?
No, I still don't.
What are you doing?
The apartment is ready.
I'm starting to pack.
It's ready? Today is only the 8th.
Yes, but it's ready.
Morgane?
Go get me your sister's bag.
Why doesn't she go?
She never does a thing!
We're leaving tomorrow.
Tomorrow we'll be gone.
A relief for you,
and me too actually.
For everyone.
But...
All right.
That contrite pose is great.
It's not a pose.
I'm... surprised.
A pleasant surprise, isn't it?
We'll get past this rough period.
- Rough?
- Oh yes.
You went through hell and I...
Thank you. You did us a favour.
You took us in.
Three people, invading your space.
It was your idea.
You suggested it.
I never got why
you were so closed up, so icy.
I even thought you had
a serious problem, you couldn't share.
I had one.
What?
Nothing, it's silly.
Something... stuck inside my head.
What? You thought I'd force your hand,
form a new family? That it?
No. You never talk anyway.
You're shut tight like a vault.
No one can talk to you.
Anyway, we'll be gone tomorrow.
Who is he? Do I know him?
Oh, I know him!
I said no.
Well...
Rehearsals going well?
Yeah, fine.
I'll come get my things.
I brought them for you.
You're a funny one.
These things happen.
Four days out.
Go tell the caterer.
Cancel everything.
Call everyone back. Lovely.
I know, everything I do is bad.
You have time, darling.
To fall in love, to...
There's nothing in the paper.
Where do they say you did nothing?
Page 10. Now that he's innocent,
no one cares.
I don't get it.
You met the man of your dreams.
Two minutes later, it's over.
You don't realise.
I do realise!
I'm not a retard,
whatever you think.
I won't get married
because you ordered cheese puffs
and a new pair of breasts!
Stop being angry at your dad.
I'm not angry.
I don't care.
He always did his part.
I know, Mum. He's perfect.
- Always has been.
- Not perfect.
He's been up front.
He always said he didn't want kids.
Always been there in a pinch.
I know, you told me.
- That's right.
- Right, and all is well.
Are you getting on?
I'm not taking anything.
I'm trying to muddle through.
Is it working?
Well, no.
I'm stuck.
Have you tried sophrology?
Yoga. Yoga is very good.
Really?
You believe in all that?
I believe in what does you good.
Eléonore is very happy.
She says thanks... for the kids.
- No problem. Very cute girls.
- Yeah.
No?
Sure, they're cute.
Didn't I park a little crooked?
No, it's fine.
I can't Tuesday. An audition.
- Good!
- Well...
But Saturday is good.
In the morning.
I might be dead by afternoon.
Oh shit. The 14th?
If you'd rather stay home, I get it.
I'm kidding, no problem.
I'm obsessed but...
I haven't gone mad.
- Saturday?
- Yes.
Saturday.
Marianne guessed
we'd get together.
Really?
Right away!
You believe in destiny?
What?
No, nothing.
I didn't hear. What?
Do you believe in destiny?
I'm going now.
You staying, or should I drop you?
I looked at your message.
By accident.
My message?
A text message.
From Rose.
By accident.
You went into my phone by accident?
I read her message, it was...
"Your kisses all over me.
And now I have to wait!"
That's her message.
Laura...
it isn't nice to go through
other people's things.
Open the wrong door,
don't complain about what you find.
If anyone can complain, it's me.
In case you didn't know,
there is such a thing as privacy.
I'm going,
close the door behind you.
... temperatures
well above normal for the season...
...a crisis without precedent.
... this spring,
unemployment spiked,
especially among rural youth...
...attributable to human activities,
to deforestation, to greenhouse
gas emission increases.
Clearly, all this yields
an unrelenting warming of the planet,
at a rate never before
recorded in human history...
No desire to see it, or know it.
That's why you shouldn't
have looked, he's right.
But...
fidelity...
It's just an idea.
It doesn't hold up.
People sleep with each other.
That's how it is.
Then it's horrible!
When I'm in love,
I desire no one else.
Or it means I'm not in love.
You say that
because your lifestyle...
is a little unusual.
But...
Unusual?
Really?
Extremely free.
Extremely free?
That's him.
He wants to see me.
The way she looked at him...
Like she looked at me,
but it wasn't me.
Wolff is a frisky one.
He's very frisky.
He wanted to take me home
after rehearsal.
Really? No!
Yeah, he did.
He must hit on everybody.
By the way,
when do you tell Julien he's fired?
I don't feel right.
I'm going to... tell him.
I'll tell him.
That language you use!
"Anti-social"!
A 9-year-old,
"anti-social, chronic failure"!
All I said was...
You have little boxes,
to file people away!
You always imply
Marianne is a bad mother.
I think she's an excellent mother!
And I've seen her!
No reason to get upset.
There is reason!
I am getting upset.
I think it's incredible...
that you are so... uncharitable.
There. I'm going.
Anyway, that covers it.
Sorry. She got to me.
No, don't be sorry.
That was great.
I wish I could answer her like that.
Plus, Nina's doing better. Right?
Not scratching as much.
Yes. She hardly scratches anymore.
- She gave up on communion.
- Really?
She wants to ride a pony.
No shit?
She's searching.
You really think I'm a good mother?
Of course I do.
Bravo.
That's all for today, thank you.
I have one note.
The woodwinds, at bar 8...
a little more character
and it would be perfect.
I'll speak to them.
What's with Clémence? Is she mad?
I don't know.
Get a drink?
I can't, I have an appointment.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
Fine. I'm very glad.
Horwitz will be here at noon
tomorrow, for the second go-around.
We'll re-schedule rehearsals.
He can't do mornings.
- Fucking drag!
- Excuse me?
No, I mean...
The Julien thing bothers me.
Bothers you? How?
I don't want to replace him.
I don't want to.
You don't want to?
Little late for regrets.
I never liked it.
Julien's been there all along.
He's a friend. My friend.
Did you say no?
Did you tell me no?
No, if you don't mind,
I'd rather you don't drive today.
Oh yeah, right.
You very rarely signal.
Really?
I must have forgotten.
We could have had coffee
at my house.
Yeah, that's true.
How did your audition go?
I'm in the final three,
they'll call back.
But...
The kids' show is coming up.
It's almost ready.
Will you come see it?
- No?
- Well, no. Because...
You're not seriously
thinking about it?
About what?
The date of... Today.
That thing... Your date of death.
How many lessons do I need?
You know how to drive already.
It's all in your head.
When you're with me, I'm OK.
But alone...
Look out!
Sorry.
- It's OK.
- I never saw it.
Never saw it.
What a wonderful wine.
Won't you order something?
I'm not hungry.
You live on love and Saint-Emilion?
Go ahead,
you can answer if you want.
Yes, I know.
Did you see her?
See who?
Rose.
Answer me.
We covered this.
Must we speak of Rose each time?
- If you still love her, tell me.
- If I still love her?
You don't?
Stop, this is ridiculous.
Why? If we're together,
it's natural for...
If we're together?
Laura, we've been out 3 times.
More.
Five times, maybe six?
We're not together.
I don't want to be with anyone.
I thought that was clear.
I was an idiot. Believe me, I know.
I couldn't tell you.
I'm sorry. I feel terrible.
That's why I saw Horwitz.
I wondered why he was here.
Fuck...
It's great.
- Yeah, but...
- No, it's great!
Horwitz!
You can't say no.
You know that Wolff
is seeing Laura?
I heard, yeah.
Wolff's a charming guy, isn't he?
I'm cancelling.
You play or I cancel. He can't...
No! Don't cancel a thing!
Are you nuts?
It's great. Everyone will come.
Everyone will hear you.
It's really great.
We've got years to play together.
We're friends.
We won't be out of touch.
We're friends, right?
Why are you here, Mushroom?
My wand! It doesn't work!
Did you replace it?
You brought it for repair?
It broke right before
the concert. Fantastic!
What a situation. So...
Clémence?
Meet you later?
I left you a message.
It's done. I told Julien.
How did he take it?
He was great.
It was horrible.
I said I'd cancel
if he wasn't playing with us.
- He said no.
- Of course not.
- What do you mean?
- What could he say?
You knew he'd say that.
The time to act was before.
It's easy to play hero now.
Wow.
No clemency from Clémence.
What? You want sympathy, as usual?
Julien gets my sympathy.
It's always about you!
I'm sick of showing clemency!
I got to go.
Laura's waiting for you.
How are you?
Looking for Maxime?
I'm not looking for Maxime.
Are you well?
Yeah. Sure.
- And you?
- Great!
How are your parents?
Are you busy? This a bad time?
No, but...
You got something to do?
Got something to say?
Yeah, I can't remember.
I better go.
Sure you're OK?
Oh right!
I just wanted to mention this.
I can't remember which scientist.
My dad is clean as a whistle.
He did nothing, it's proven!
I just mentioned it.
Where the hell is my car?
Oh right, I didn't drive.
Yeah. Jacqueline, it's me.
It's Pierre.
You must be working.
Actually, I just called to...
No, it's stupid. Never mind.
Anyway, I hope you're doing well.
Love you.
Love you, Jacqueline.
Marianne!
Too bad you're not home.
Oh shit.
I wanted to tell you, you're right.
It's great to be free.
Marianne...
Want a beer?
Why are you here?
I wanted to see you.
So you know where I live?
Come on up.
Right.
I wanted to tell you,
I thought it over. You can have it.
The money you wanted.
I don't need it, I worked it out.
Really?
Oh shit.
I'll give it to you anyway.
I can't use it.
No, I'm telling you,
I worked it out.
I thought it over.
It should be yours.
He loved you.
If he had made a will...
If he had the time...
Come on, please.
Keep it.
Well, then thank you.
So Laura, in the end...
- Didn't work out?
- No, it didn't.
How's your music?
Yeah.
Last time, I was curt because...
every time you call
you ask for money.
What else can I ask of you?
I never saw that picture
of you and my father.
What's going on?
Nothing.
- I don't like outbursts.
- Yeah, I know that.
Want something to drink?
Something strong?
Yeah, I have vodka.
Vodka would be fine.
- Not too much.
- Say when.
Did you have plans?
No, it's fine.
It's nice.
Wait up.
That's Laura, Sandro's girl.
- You sure?
- Yeah, that's her!
Yes, all right.
Thank you, Clémence.
Laura is on the street in a stupor.
A friend said she's totally drunk.
Laura, your...
What can I do about it?
We can't leave her like that.
Where is she?
I didn't want to worry you, but...
We're here.
We're at the bus stop.
Be right there. She left me
this crazy message. I'm coming.
A little further up.
- Here.
- Yes.
Careful.
No-one saw her.
Maxime, finally.
Sorry about the messages...
Really?
Really? Is she...
How is she?
We'll be right there.
She's outside my house.
He found her on the sidewalk.
Unconscious.
She doesn't react.
Thirsty...
Sitting...
Zirsting, sting...
She wants to sit up.
She says she's thirsty.
Let her drink, but wake her up.
She took something.
- Took what?
- Not sure.
I think she said she took stuff.
I'm going.
I'll go with you.
Sorry, she won't wake up.
I'm calling an ambulance.
No, don't get all worried.
I know a way
to wake a sleeping princess.
See? It works.
I have to get up early.
Good night.
Good night, Marianne.
Everything worked out in the end.
Well...
I pushed Laura into his arms,
instead of...
Awful.
You say he's usually charming?
When he wants to be,
he is charming. He was...
super-charming.
By the way, bravo!
- Bravo?
- Yes!
You drove on your own, at night.
While making calls,
down all those streets!
Bravo.
I did?
I did.
Two-fifteen.
It's late.
So it's the 15th.
- And you're not dead.
- Hey, that's right.
Guess you're laughing now.
No, I'm not actually.
Nice of you.
You took care of me.
Clémence saw you
and she called me.
Clémence.
Are you with her now?
Not to Daddy.
The show's going to start.
You can wave from over there.
Go, Mushroom. Go.
OK, you stay here.
Go stand behind there.
What are you doing here?
I came to see the show.
The show?
Watch out, lots of kids in it.
I wanted to see you, too.
I want to talk.
You were right, I...
I was afraid of, I don't know.
But I realised...
It's starting.
Once upon a time,
a beautiful young princess,
like every princess,
believed with all her heart
a great love awaited her.
But... she was lost in a forest
and couldn't find her way.
Kiss her.
Kiss him!
Kiss him?
They're supposed to kiss,
but things go awry.
But the forest is still overjoyed!
THEY LIVED HAPPILY EVER AFTER
AND OFTEN STRAYED...
Bravo!
Anaïs,
the princess and the prince, come!
The princess! Anaïs!
The Prince, Simon.
Gabriel, the mushroom.
Mathieu, the rabbit.
And Selma, the pretty flower.
Lauranie, the squirrel.
The strawberry, Flore.
Laura, the wolf.
Lulu, the tree.
And another flower, Candy.
And I forgot... the dog, Joanna.
Bravo, thank you.
You can go
and say hello to your parents.