1
00:00:47,434 --> 00:00:50,853
After all... I'm stupid.

2
00:00:50,938 --> 00:00:55,108
After all, yes, I must. I must!

3
00:02:02,141 --> 00:02:05,852
- Michel! Take me with you!
- What time is it?

4
00:02:05,936 --> 00:02:08,398
- 10:50.
- No.

5
00:02:08,482 --> 00:02:11,233
I'm on my way, hey-hey!

6
00:02:30,798 --> 00:02:36,093
If he thinks he's gonna pass me
in that crappy thing!

7
00:02:45,022 --> 00:02:47,440
I pick up the cash,

8
00:02:47,524 --> 00:02:51,778
I ask Patricia, yes or no, and then...

9
00:03:04,125 --> 00:03:07,253
The countryside's nice.

10
00:03:15,638 --> 00:03:18,475
I really like France.

11
00:03:22,939 --> 00:03:26,484
If you don't like the sea,

12
00:03:26,568 --> 00:03:29,862
if you don't like the mountains,

13
00:03:29,988 --> 00:03:36,119
if you don't like the city,
then get stuffed!

14
00:03:42,251 --> 00:03:46,338
Little girls trying to hitch a ride!

15
00:03:46,422 --> 00:03:49,049
I'll charge a kiss per kilometer.

16
00:03:50,719 --> 00:03:54,472
The short one's not bad.
Nice thighs.

17
00:03:54,556 --> 00:03:57,517
But the other one...

18
00:03:57,601 --> 00:04:00,812
Shit, they're too ugly.

19
00:04:24,256 --> 00:04:26,966
The sun is beautiful.

20
00:04:32,432 --> 00:04:37,812
Women are such cowards
behind the wheel. Overtake him!

21
00:04:37,896 --> 00:04:40,273
Oh, there's roadworkâ€™s.

22
00:04:50,577 --> 00:04:52,787
Never use the brakes.

23
00:04:52,871 --> 00:04:57,334
As old Bugatti said:
"Cars are made to run, not to stop. "

24
00:04:59,044 --> 00:05:00,502
Shit! Cops!

25
00:05:15,187 --> 00:05:17,397
The wire's come off!

26
00:05:18,274 --> 00:05:21,819
This could get me nabbed!

27
00:05:36,753 --> 00:05:40,214
Don't move, or I'll waste you.

28
00:06:32,064 --> 00:06:37,193
- Miss Franchini's room?
- She isn't here. She's out.

29
00:06:45,912 --> 00:06:49,415
Girls never have any cash!

30
00:06:49,499 --> 00:06:51,292
Espresso.

31
00:06:53,671 --> 00:06:57,507
- How much is ham and eggs?
- 1.80.

32
00:06:59,719 --> 00:07:03,472
- Right. I'll have some.
- OK.

33
00:07:04,308 --> 00:07:07,142
Just going for a paper.

34
00:07:28,834 --> 00:07:32,087
- Oh, wow, Michel!
- Can I come in?

35
00:07:32,171 --> 00:07:35,591
- How are you, sweetheart?
- No jacket?

36
00:07:35,675 --> 00:07:38,386
I left it in my Alfa Romeo.

37
00:07:38,470 --> 00:07:45,309
- Want breakfast at the Royal?
- I must be at the TV station by 9:10.

38
00:07:49,482 --> 00:07:53,778
It's torn. Listen to this.

39
00:08:01,870 --> 00:08:06,918
- What have you been up to?
- Nothing, I've been travelling.

40
00:08:07,002 --> 00:08:09,753
What's new around here?

41
00:08:09,837 --> 00:08:14,926
- You don't go out?
- To the discotheque sometimes.

42
00:08:15,011 --> 00:08:19,222
- Still making films?
- No. You need to sleep around.

43
00:08:19,307 --> 00:08:21,099
Do you recollect Enrico?

44
00:08:21,184 --> 00:08:25,938
"Remember" or "recall",
not "recollect".

45
00:08:26,022 --> 00:08:30,109
I work with him at the station.
I'm a script-girl.

46
00:08:30,194 --> 00:08:35,574
When I was broke in December,
I was assistant on a film at CinecittÃ !

47
00:08:35,658 --> 00:08:37,326
You?

48
00:08:37,410 --> 00:08:42,289
Ever been a gigolo?
I was just asking.

49
00:08:43,334 --> 00:08:46,461
I wouldn't mind.

50
00:08:48,422 --> 00:08:51,800
Call me back in a few minutes.

51
00:08:53,386 --> 00:08:56,763
Is Gaby back from Spain?

52
00:08:56,848 --> 00:08:59,934
He's bought the Pergola.

53
00:09:00,018 --> 00:09:03,855
Great. It was stupid
to paint it all black.

54
00:09:04,857 --> 00:09:08,861
- What's it say there?
- "Why?"

55
00:09:09,028 --> 00:09:13,366
Never finished it.
I smoke Luckies now.

56
00:09:13,450 --> 00:09:18,662
- Can you lend me 5000 francs till noon?
- I might have known.

57
00:09:19,831 --> 00:09:23,793
- You're a creep, Michel.
- I'll pay you back.

58
00:09:23,878 --> 00:09:27,381
I don't have that much.

59
00:09:27,465 --> 00:09:31,635
- Here's 500 if you want.
- No, keep it.

60
00:09:55,663 --> 00:09:59,958
- So, no breakfast at the Royal?
- I'm really late.

61
00:10:00,043 --> 00:10:02,628
Okay, then.

62
00:10:07,176 --> 00:10:11,304
- Is Mr Tolmachov here?
- He's here, but he's not here.

63
00:10:11,847 --> 00:10:15,642
- Seen Patricia?
- Yes, over there.

64
00:10:23,485 --> 00:10:26,070
Come with me to Rome?

65
00:10:28,490 --> 00:10:33,411
It's crazy, I wanted to see
if I'd be glad to see you again.

66
00:10:33,496 --> 00:10:35,706
Have you been in Monte Carlo?

67
00:10:35,790 --> 00:10:40,211
No, Marseilles. I was in Monte Carlo
before that to see a guy.

68
00:10:40,295 --> 00:10:44,924
- I called on Monday, from Marseilles.
- I was out of town.

69
00:10:47,554 --> 00:10:51,307
- I'll take one.
- That's kind.

70
00:10:55,605 --> 00:11:01,943
- You said you hated Paris.
- No, I said I've got enemies here.

71
00:11:02,027 --> 00:11:06,240
- So you're in danger?
- Yes, I am. Will you come to Rome?

72
00:11:06,324 --> 00:11:09,368
To do what?

73
00:11:09,452 --> 00:11:14,749
- No, I've things to do here.
- You going up or down the Champs?

74
00:11:14,833 --> 00:11:19,004
- What's the "Champs"?
- The Champs ElysÃ©es.

75
00:11:19,881 --> 00:11:25,552
I'm going to Avenue George V.
Go on, walk with me.

76
00:11:25,637 --> 00:11:28,473
Just to the corner.

77
00:11:38,067 --> 00:11:43,822
Here, no horoscope! It's the future.
I want to know the future.

78
00:11:43,907 --> 00:11:47,826
- Don't you?
- Sure.

79
00:11:52,625 --> 00:11:56,796
- What's the matter?
- Nothing, just looking at you.

80
00:11:59,090 --> 00:12:05,096
- You angry I left without a goodbye?
- No, I was furious because I was sad.

81
00:12:06,515 --> 00:12:10,144
It's nice to wake up next to a girl.

82
00:12:10,228 --> 00:12:13,981
Are you staying in town?

83
00:12:14,066 --> 00:12:16,858
I have to see a man who owes me money.

84
00:12:16,943 --> 00:12:22,740
- Then I have to see you.
- You don't have to.

85
00:12:23,034 --> 00:12:26,745
- There are prettier girls than me.
- No.

86
00:12:26,830 --> 00:12:31,500
I slept with two girls since you.
It was a washout.

87
00:12:32,919 --> 00:12:39,301
- What's "washout"?
- They were pretty, but it was no fun.

88
00:12:39,385 --> 00:12:44,139
So will you come to Rome?
I'm fed up with France.

89
00:12:44,224 --> 00:12:49,478
I have to enroll at the Sorbonne
so my parents will send money.

90
00:12:49,562 --> 00:12:53,483
- We only had 3 nights together!
- No, 5.

91
00:12:53,567 --> 00:12:58,822
- Why don't you wear a bra?
- Don't be rude!

92
00:13:00,032 --> 00:13:04,954
- What time is it? See you later?
- Not later. Tonight. Okay?

93
00:13:05,038 --> 00:13:08,791
- Yes. Where?
- Round here.

94
00:13:27,146 --> 00:13:30,064
LIVE DANGEROUSLY UNTIL THE END!

95
00:13:37,073 --> 00:13:42,995
- Sir? You've nothing against youth?
- I have. I like old people.

96
00:14:03,727 --> 00:14:06,313
POLICEMAN'S KILLER IDENTIFIED

97
00:14:13,072 --> 00:14:17,576
- Is Mr Tolmachov here?
- At the airline desk.

98
00:14:34,971 --> 00:14:36,888
Hi, amigo.

99
00:14:36,973 --> 00:14:42,729
- You came by at ten?
- Yeah, for my money.

100
00:14:56,452 --> 00:15:00,206
I got bored down south.
I came up to see a girl.

101
00:15:00,290 --> 00:15:05,419
- I'm rusting away here.
- Better rusted than busted.

102
00:15:09,509 --> 00:15:11,593
Over here.

103
00:15:14,973 --> 00:15:18,601
Do you have the envelope I gave you?

104
00:15:25,401 --> 00:15:30,030
- Idiot! Why did he cross it?
- Just sign it over to someone else.

105
00:15:30,114 --> 00:15:33,826
Not to me.
I blew my last penny on the races.

106
00:15:33,911 --> 00:15:39,499
- And your pal, Bob MontagnÃ©?
- He's in prison.

107
00:15:39,583 --> 00:15:44,422
- There's Berruti, but I don't trust him.
- I thought he was your pal.

108
00:15:44,506 --> 00:15:49,177
- Is he back?
- Yes, I saw him last night.

109
00:15:55,810 --> 00:16:00,230
- What was his number again?
- ElysÃ©e 99-84.

110
00:16:00,315 --> 00:16:04,069
- Can I call from here?
- Go ahead.

111
00:16:07,030 --> 00:16:11,784
- Who's the girl you came for?
- A New Yorker.

112
00:16:11,868 --> 00:16:15,288
She's amusing. I like her.

113
00:16:15,414 --> 00:16:19,251
ElysÃ©e 99-84?

114
00:16:20,044 --> 00:16:22,922
I'd like to speak to Antonio.

115
00:16:23,006 --> 00:16:27,176
I see. No, I'll call back.

116
00:16:28,763 --> 00:16:31,681
He's out. I'll ask around.

117
00:16:31,765 --> 00:16:35,519
- Bye, sonny.
- Ciao, amigo.

118
00:16:41,902 --> 00:16:46,365
- Inter-Americana Agency?
- Yes, that's us.

119
00:16:46,449 --> 00:16:50,535
- Do customers have mail sent here?
- Yes.

120
00:16:50,621 --> 00:16:54,832
- Know a certain Michel Poiccard?
- No.

121
00:16:54,916 --> 00:16:57,961
Also goes by the name Laszlo Kovacs?

122
00:16:58,045 --> 00:17:02,215
Ask that gentleman.
He'll help you.

123
00:17:16,148 --> 00:17:18,609
If it isn't Tolmachov!

124
00:17:20,028 --> 00:17:21,819
Hello, Inspector.

125
00:17:21,904 --> 00:17:26,575
- In the travel business now?
- As you can see.

126
00:17:29,538 --> 00:17:33,958
Remember how you grassed
on your friend Bob?

127
00:17:34,043 --> 00:17:39,214
- What of it?
- Well, you're going to do it again.

128
00:17:39,299 --> 00:17:45,262
Michel Poiccard, 1 metre 79,
brown hair, former Air France steward.

129
00:17:45,347 --> 00:17:50,101
- He has his mail sent here.
- Yes, I know him.

130
00:17:50,186 --> 00:17:53,897
- He been around lately?
- No.

131
00:17:53,981 --> 00:17:56,150
Miss!

132
00:18:01,740 --> 00:18:05,618
Nobody been to see
Mr Tolmachov recently?

133
00:18:05,703 --> 00:18:11,041
- Just 5 minutes ago, quite a tall man.
- Bloody hell!

134
00:18:12,502 --> 00:18:15,462
Accessory to murder. Think about it!

135
00:18:46,789 --> 00:18:49,542
THE HARDER THEY FALL

136
00:18:49,627 --> 00:18:51,543
Bogey...

137
00:19:29,586 --> 00:19:34,341
I saw a man die.
An accident.

138
00:19:34,426 --> 00:19:39,055
- Take me out to dinner?
- Evidently.

139
00:19:39,973 --> 00:19:43,935
Let me make another call first.
Wait for me?

140
00:19:44,019 --> 00:19:50,526
- Call from the restaurant.
- No. I'll just be a second.

141
00:19:50,610 --> 00:19:55,406
The French always say one second
when they mean 5 minutes.

142
00:20:49,675 --> 00:20:53,470
- Where we going?
- Anywhere. To Saint Michel.

143
00:20:53,554 --> 00:20:56,599
Sleep with me tonight?

144
00:20:56,683 --> 00:21:00,102
- Don't you like it with me?
- Sure, I do.

145
00:21:00,186 --> 00:21:05,483
I just read something in the paper.
About a bus conductor.

146
00:21:05,568 --> 00:21:10,155
He stole 5 million to seduce a girl.
Impersonated a rich impresario.

147
00:21:10,240 --> 00:21:14,326
He took her down to the Riviera.
They blew the lot in 3 days.

148
00:21:14,411 --> 00:21:18,289
The guy didn't chicken out.
He told her:

149
00:21:18,374 --> 00:21:22,669
"It's stolen money, I'm a bad guy,
but I like you. "

150
00:21:23,921 --> 00:21:28,926
It's great she stuck by him.
She said: "I like you, too. "

151
00:21:29,010 --> 00:21:34,098
They came back to Paris,
and were caught burgling villas.

152
00:21:34,183 --> 00:21:37,769
She was the look-out.

153
00:21:39,730 --> 00:21:45,360
- Excuse me, got a light?
- Go buy yourself some matches!

154
00:21:45,445 --> 00:21:49,908
- I forgot! I have an appointment.
- Who with?

155
00:21:49,992 --> 00:21:54,580
A journalist on the Champs Elysees.
It's a press conference.

156
00:21:54,664 --> 00:22:01,587
- Where? Now?
- You can really get on my nerves.

157
00:22:01,671 --> 00:22:06,007
- So you're leaving me?
- But I'll see you tomorrow.

158
00:22:06,093 --> 00:22:08,470
Not tomorrow, tonight, Patricia.

159
00:22:08,554 --> 00:22:13,350
- I told you I can't.
- Why are you so cruel?

160
00:22:13,434 --> 00:22:20,649
- Any taxis around?
- My car's near the Opera. Want a lift?

161
00:22:20,734 --> 00:22:26,322
- What happened to the Ford?
- It's in the garage.

162
00:22:26,406 --> 00:22:31,078
- Let me stay with you.
- I've got a headache anyway.

163
00:22:31,162 --> 00:22:36,459
- We won't make love.
- That's not it, Michel!

164
00:22:42,424 --> 00:22:45,761
- Why are you so sad?
- Because I am.

165
00:22:45,845 --> 00:22:47,972
That's silly.

166
00:22:49,474 --> 00:22:52,184
Why are you sad?

167
00:22:52,269 --> 00:22:57,148
- Should I use "vous" or "tu"?
- Either. But I can't do without you.

168
00:22:57,232 --> 00:23:01,236
- Yes, you can.
- Maybe. But I don't want to.

169
00:23:04,783 --> 00:23:07,575
Look at that great Talbot. A 2.5 litre.

170
00:23:08,412 --> 00:23:12,666
- You're a kid...
- What?

171
00:23:12,750 --> 00:23:18,672
- Oh, I don't know.
- I forbid you to meet this guy.

172
00:23:23,803 --> 00:23:27,014
Alas, alas, alas!

173
00:23:27,140 --> 00:23:31,186
I love a girl who has a nice neck,
nice breasts,

174
00:23:31,312 --> 00:23:37,568
a nice voice, nice wrists,
a nice forehead, nice knees.

175
00:23:42,282 --> 00:23:45,410
But she's such a coward!

176
00:23:48,038 --> 00:23:52,709
- It's there. Stop.
- I'll park.

177
00:23:54,963 --> 00:23:57,841
Get lost then!

178
00:23:57,925 --> 00:24:02,095
I never want to see you again.
Get lost!

179
00:24:04,473 --> 00:24:07,267
Get lost, you creep!

180
00:24:54,153 --> 00:24:59,449
- I'd be sad if that happened to you.
- We'll see.

181
00:24:59,535 --> 00:25:02,702
What's wrong?

182
00:25:02,787 --> 00:25:06,749
If I could dig a hole
and hide in it, I would.

183
00:25:06,833 --> 00:25:13,214
You should be like an elephant.
When they're sad, they vanish.

184
00:25:24,395 --> 00:25:28,523
Let me tell you a story.
It'll take your mind off things.

185
00:25:28,608 --> 00:25:32,736
I've known a girl 2 years.
And now, I suddenly think:

186
00:25:32,821 --> 00:25:36,741
I'll ask her to sleep with me.
It had never occurred to me.

187
00:25:36,826 --> 00:25:42,789
We met for lunch. I wanted to say:
"We're friends, let's sleep together. "

188
00:25:42,873 --> 00:25:47,794
I don't know why,
but it completely slipped my mind!

189
00:25:49,339 --> 00:25:52,925
Later I sent her a telegram,

190
00:25:53,010 --> 00:25:56,637
saying I'd forgotten to say
we should sleep together.

191
00:25:56,722 --> 00:26:00,850
3 hours later I get
a message back, saying:

192
00:26:00,934 --> 00:26:03,604
"What an amazing coincidence!

193
00:26:03,688 --> 00:26:07,941
I was going to suggest the same thing!"

194
00:27:22,107 --> 00:27:25,944
- Is this the late edition?
- Yes, sir.

195
00:28:42,738 --> 00:28:47,534
- My key isn't here?
- You must've left it in the door.

196
00:28:52,582 --> 00:28:54,876
Oh, no!

197
00:28:57,296 --> 00:29:02,050
- What are you doing here?
- The Claridge was fully booked.

198
00:29:02,134 --> 00:29:06,179
So I came here.
I took the key downstairs.

199
00:29:06,264 --> 00:29:12,353
- There are other hotels.
- I always stay at the Claridge.

200
00:29:12,438 --> 00:29:15,190
You're crazy!

201
00:29:15,274 --> 00:29:18,526
- Don't sulk!
- I can never be alone...

202
00:29:18,610 --> 00:29:21,279
It doesn't suit you.

203
00:29:22,825 --> 00:29:26,077
- What's "sulk"?
- This.

204
00:29:32,960 --> 00:29:36,088
It suits me fine.

205
00:29:36,172 --> 00:29:38,423
You're even crazier than me.

206
00:29:38,507 --> 00:29:45,223
What a pain. I always fall for girls
who aren't for me.

207
00:29:45,307 --> 00:29:49,978
Did you notice
I followed you last night?

208
00:29:52,148 --> 00:29:57,528
- What's wrong?
- Leave me alone. I'm thinking.

209
00:29:57,613 --> 00:30:00,781
What about?

210
00:30:00,866 --> 00:30:04,620
The thing is, I don't even know.

211
00:30:04,704 --> 00:30:08,582
- Well, I do.
- No, nobody does.

212
00:30:08,666 --> 00:30:12,253
You're thinking about last night.

213
00:30:12,337 --> 00:30:17,509
Last night I was furious,
but now I couldn't care less.

214
00:30:17,593 --> 00:30:21,263
I'm not thinking about anything.

215
00:30:24,851 --> 00:30:29,230
I'd like to think about something,
but I can't seem to.

216
00:30:29,314 --> 00:30:33,442
Well, I'm tired, very tired,

217
00:30:33,528 --> 00:30:36,779
and I'm going back to sleep.

218
00:30:42,245 --> 00:30:46,707
- Why are you looking at me?
- Because I am.

219
00:30:46,792 --> 00:30:50,378
- You should've stayed last night.
- I couldn't.

220
00:30:50,462 --> 00:30:54,716
You should've told the chap
you couldn't see him.

221
00:30:54,801 --> 00:31:00,306
I had to. He's getting me articles
to write. It's really important for me.

222
00:31:00,390 --> 00:31:03,767
What's important
is going to Rome with me.

223
00:31:03,852 --> 00:31:07,188
Maybe, I don't know.

224
00:31:07,273 --> 00:31:10,901
- Did you sleep with him?
- No.

225
00:31:10,985 --> 00:31:15,531
- I bet you did.
- No. He's really sweet.

226
00:31:15,615 --> 00:31:19,785
He said one day we'd sleep together,
but not now.

227
00:31:19,869 --> 00:31:25,083
- But he doesn't even know me.
- Not you. Him and me.

228
00:31:25,167 --> 00:31:31,590
- We had a drink in Montparnasse.
- I was there, too. At what time?

229
00:31:31,674 --> 00:31:35,803
I don't know. We didn't stay long.

230
00:31:35,887 --> 00:31:39,724
Why did you come here, Michel?

231
00:31:39,808 --> 00:31:46,522
- I want to sleep with you again.
- That's hardly a reason.

232
00:31:46,648 --> 00:31:52,654
- Sure it is. It means I love you.
- But I don't know yet if I love you.

233
00:31:53,698 --> 00:31:57,869
- When will you know?
- Soon.

234
00:31:57,953 --> 00:32:04,668
- In a month, in a year?
- Soon means soon.

235
00:32:04,753 --> 00:32:07,588
A woman never wants to do
in eight seconds

236
00:32:07,672 --> 00:32:11,384
what she'll want to do
eight days later.

237
00:32:11,468 --> 00:32:15,221
Eight seconds or eight days,
it's all the same.

238
00:32:15,305 --> 00:32:20,770
- Why not eight centuries?
- No, eight days is good.

239
00:32:21,813 --> 00:32:24,982
A woman's all half-measures.

240
00:32:25,066 --> 00:32:27,818
It gets me down.

241
00:32:29,863 --> 00:32:32,324
Why won't you sleep with me again?

242
00:32:32,409 --> 00:32:38,789
Because I'm trying to find out
what it is that I like about you.

243
00:32:38,873 --> 00:32:44,796
- I want us to be like Romeo and Juliet.
- Just like a girl!

244
00:32:44,880 --> 00:32:50,593
You said last night you couldn't
live without me, but you can.

245
00:32:50,678 --> 00:32:55,683
Romeo couldn't live without Juliet,
but you can.

246
00:32:55,767 --> 00:32:59,520
No, I can't live without you.

247
00:32:59,604 --> 00:33:03,524
Just like a man!

248
00:33:03,608 --> 00:33:06,570
Give me a smile.

249
00:33:06,654 --> 00:33:10,240
Right. I'll count to 8.

250
00:33:10,325 --> 00:33:14,954
If by 8 you haven't smiled,
I'll strangle you.

251
00:33:16,331 --> 00:33:18,124
Two.

252
00:33:18,209 --> 00:33:19,875
Three.

253
00:33:19,961 --> 00:33:22,170
Four, five, six.

254
00:33:22,254 --> 00:33:24,047
Seven.

255
00:33:24,131 --> 00:33:26,342
Seven and a half.

256
00:33:26,426 --> 00:33:29,260
Seven and three quarters.

257
00:33:29,346 --> 00:33:34,016
You're such a coward
I bet you're gonna smile.

258
00:33:37,605 --> 00:33:41,024
Enough games for today.

259
00:33:43,820 --> 00:33:47,781
- Too bad you're a coward.
- Why do you say that?

260
00:33:47,866 --> 00:33:51,578
- You get on my nerves.
- And you get on mine.

261
00:33:51,662 --> 00:33:54,874
- I'm not a coward.
- How do you know I'm scared?

262
00:33:54,958 --> 00:33:59,253
If a girl says she's not scared,
then can't even light her cigarette,

263
00:33:59,337 --> 00:34:05,551
it means she's scared of something.
I don't know of what, but she's scared.

264
00:34:07,179 --> 00:34:10,973
- Have one.
- None of those Chesterfields.

265
00:34:11,057 --> 00:34:13,852
Hand me my jacket.

266
00:34:13,936 --> 00:34:17,689
- In this one?
- Give it here!

267
00:34:18,316 --> 00:34:22,862
- This is your passport?
- My brother's. Mine's in the car.

268
00:34:22,946 --> 00:34:28,744
- But it says Kovacs here.
- He's not my real brother.

269
00:34:28,828 --> 00:34:33,499
My mum was divorced
by the time he was born.

270
00:34:41,842 --> 00:34:44,428
See? I'm not scared.

271
00:34:44,512 --> 00:34:49,224
- I never said you were.
- You bet, pet.

272
00:34:50,268 --> 00:34:55,523
But you wish you had said it.
And now you're angry.

273
00:34:55,607 --> 00:34:59,235
I'm not talking to you anymore.

274
00:35:04,200 --> 00:35:09,997
Do you ever think about death?
I do, all the time.

275
00:35:12,292 --> 00:35:16,463
- What?
- Say something nice.

276
00:35:16,547 --> 00:35:19,883
- Like what?
- I don't know.

277
00:35:19,968 --> 00:35:23,095
Then neither do I.

278
00:35:24,639 --> 00:35:29,603
- I like your ashtray.
- It's Swiss.

279
00:35:29,687 --> 00:35:33,648
My granddad had a Rolls-Royce.
Great car!

280
00:35:33,733 --> 00:35:37,820
Never had to raise the bonnet
in 15 years!

281
00:35:39,280 --> 00:35:42,783
Seen my new poster?

282
00:35:42,868 --> 00:35:48,456
Come here!
Come here, for Christ's sake!

283
00:35:48,540 --> 00:35:52,628
It won't do here. Where can I put it?

284
00:35:54,798 --> 00:35:57,758
Why did you slap me
when I looked at your legs?

285
00:35:57,842 --> 00:36:00,386
It wasn't my legs.

286
00:36:02,515 --> 00:36:04,516
It's exactly the same thing.

287
00:36:04,600 --> 00:36:09,479
The French always say things
are the same when they're not at all.

288
00:36:11,191 --> 00:36:15,319
- I've thought of something nice.
- What?

289
00:36:15,404 --> 00:36:19,741
I want to sleep with you again
because you're beautiful.

290
00:36:19,867 --> 00:36:22,243
I'm not.

291
00:36:22,327 --> 00:36:27,124
- Then because you're ugly.
- Is it the same?

292
00:36:32,173 --> 00:36:34,549
Yeah, baby, it's the same.

293
00:36:34,633 --> 00:36:38,594
- You're a liar, Michel.
- No, lying's stupid.

294
00:36:38,679 --> 00:36:42,140
It's like at poker...
It's better to tell the truth.

295
00:36:42,224 --> 00:36:47,647
The others think you're bluffing,
and that's how you win.

296
00:36:47,731 --> 00:36:50,316
What is it?

297
00:36:53,112 --> 00:36:57,741
I'll stare at you
until you stop staring at me.

298
00:37:25,439 --> 00:37:29,735
I'm going to put my poster
in the bathroom.

299
00:37:29,819 --> 00:37:33,447
- Can I phone?
- Yes.

300
00:37:36,576 --> 00:37:40,329
- It's not bad here.
- Just fine.

301
00:37:45,795 --> 00:37:51,175
- Do you like this poster?
- It's not bad.

302
00:37:52,386 --> 00:37:57,724
- Renoir's a really great painter.
- I said, not bad!

303
00:37:59,310 --> 00:38:03,188
Think she's prettier than me?

304
00:38:04,899 --> 00:38:09,653
When you're scared or surprised,
or both at once...

305
00:38:09,737 --> 00:38:13,073
.. there's a funny glint in your eyes.

306
00:38:13,158 --> 00:38:17,828
I want to sleep with you again,
because of that glint.

307
00:38:21,876 --> 00:38:24,836
Mind if I piss in the sink?

308
00:38:25,672 --> 00:38:30,009
- Guess what I'm going to say.
- No idea.

309
00:38:30,093 --> 00:38:33,180
I'm pregnant, Michel.

310
00:38:36,726 --> 00:38:39,062
You heard me.

311
00:38:39,146 --> 00:38:43,232
- Whose is it? Mine?
- I think so.

312
00:38:43,317 --> 00:38:47,196
- Seen a doctor?
- Yesterday.

313
00:38:47,280 --> 00:38:51,241
I have to go back Thursday for tests.

314
00:38:51,326 --> 00:38:54,911
You should've been more careful!

315
00:39:08,386 --> 00:39:14,266
Get me ElysÃ©e 99-84.
99-84.

316
00:39:17,813 --> 00:39:21,858
Is Antonio there?

317
00:39:21,943 --> 00:39:28,073
You don't know if he's coming back?
I'll call back.

318
00:39:28,157 --> 00:39:30,784
Michel Poiccard.

319
00:39:38,168 --> 00:39:40,963
ElysÃ©e 25-32.

320
00:39:43,258 --> 00:39:47,427
I'm calling
the man who owes me money.

321
00:39:49,098 --> 00:39:51,891
Mr Tolmachov, please.

322
00:39:53,436 --> 00:39:56,021
Hey, sonny.

323
00:39:59,234 --> 00:40:03,404
I can't find Berruti.

324
00:40:03,488 --> 00:40:07,700
I wandered
around Montparnasse all night.

325
00:40:09,913 --> 00:40:11,997
The police?

326
00:40:14,501 --> 00:40:17,627
Thanks. Ciao, sonny.

327
00:40:19,256 --> 00:40:20,714
Shit!

328
00:40:20,799 --> 00:40:23,885
- What?
- I slipped.

329
00:40:23,969 --> 00:40:28,307
Heard the one
about the condemned man?

330
00:40:28,391 --> 00:40:33,520
As he's climbing the scaffold,
he slips and says, "that figures!"

331
00:40:39,403 --> 00:40:45,450
- You look like a Martian up close.
- Because my head's in the clouds.

332
00:40:45,534 --> 00:40:49,830
- Some idea, having a kid!
- But it's not sure.

333
00:40:49,914 --> 00:40:51,999
I wanted to see what you'd say.

334
00:40:52,084 --> 00:40:55,420
- Take your clothes off.
- What's the point?

335
00:40:55,504 --> 00:40:58,882
You Americans are so stupid.

336
00:40:58,967 --> 00:41:02,885
You adore La Fayette
and Maurice Chevalier.

337
00:41:02,970 --> 00:41:08,476
And they're the stupidest Frenchmen!
I'm making another call.

338
00:41:11,145 --> 00:41:13,231
Belle Epine 35-26.

339
00:41:13,315 --> 00:41:15,900
Patricia, come here!

340
00:41:18,278 --> 00:41:21,323
Hello, Mr Mansard?

341
00:41:21,407 --> 00:41:27,537
Will he be in this afternoon?
Tell him I'll come by.

342
00:41:27,622 --> 00:41:30,875
I'm a friend of Tony's. From Marseilles.

343
00:41:30,959 --> 00:41:34,462
Laszlo Kovacs. I've got an American.

344
00:41:36,841 --> 00:41:40,470
- An American?
- Laszlo Kovacs.

345
00:41:41,639 --> 00:41:46,851
Not you. An American car.

346
00:41:51,357 --> 00:41:56,278
I can't find the man
who owes me money. What a pain!

347
00:41:56,362 --> 00:42:01,493
- Do you prefer records or the radio?
- Quiet, I'm thinking!

348
00:42:18,930 --> 00:42:23,224
- I know them all so well.
- How old are you?

349
00:42:23,309 --> 00:42:29,482
- I'll put the radio on. I'm 20.
- You don't look it.

350
00:42:29,567 --> 00:42:34,112
- Why don't you like music?
- It depends. I do.

351
00:42:34,238 --> 00:42:37,364
Come on, Patricia, come to Italy.

352
00:42:41,162 --> 00:42:45,123
What's the point of studying
at the Sorbonne?

353
00:42:45,208 --> 00:42:48,377
You never took any exams.

354
00:42:48,462 --> 00:42:52,590
Sure, the baccalaureate.
But I packed it in.

355
00:42:52,675 --> 00:42:57,596
- What's "packed it in"?
- I did other things.

356
00:42:57,680 --> 00:43:00,766
- I sold cars.
- Here?

357
00:43:00,851 --> 00:43:03,686
No.

358
00:43:03,770 --> 00:43:09,692
In New York,
did you sleep with a lot of men?

359
00:43:09,776 --> 00:43:13,655
Not so many.

360
00:43:13,740 --> 00:43:16,367
How many?

361
00:43:17,494 --> 00:43:20,622
- How about you?
- Me?

362
00:43:22,665 --> 00:43:25,960
Not so many either.

363
00:43:26,044 --> 00:43:32,343
You know where I'd like to live?
Mexico. I hear it's really lovely.

364
00:43:32,427 --> 00:43:36,931
When I was a kid my dad would say:
We'll go next Saturday.

365
00:43:37,016 --> 00:43:39,726
But he'd always forget.

366
00:43:41,771 --> 00:43:46,650
No, Mexico doesn't grab me.
I bet it's not all that great.

367
00:43:46,734 --> 00:43:52,407
People are such liars.
It's like Stockholm. Everyone says...

368
00:43:52,491 --> 00:43:57,537
"Swedish girls are terrific.
I had 3 a day. Go there. "

369
00:43:57,621 --> 00:44:01,166
I went there. It's not true.

370
00:44:01,250 --> 00:44:04,545
Swedish girls don't act
the way they do here.

371
00:44:04,629 --> 00:44:07,881
Most of them are dogs
like Parisian girls.

372
00:44:07,965 --> 00:44:11,677
No, Swedish girls are very pretty.

373
00:44:11,761 --> 00:44:14,722
It's a myth.

374
00:44:14,807 --> 00:44:20,478
One or two maybe, like in Paris
or London, but not all of them.

375
00:44:20,604 --> 00:44:24,524
The cities where the girls are pretty,

376
00:44:24,609 --> 00:44:28,821
not gorgeous, but like you, charming,

377
00:44:28,948 --> 00:44:35,245
girls who rate 15 out of 20,
because they have something...

378
00:44:36,914 --> 00:44:43,087
Aren't Rome or Paris or Rio
but Lausanne and Geneva.

379
00:44:45,507 --> 00:44:51,347
- Now you tell me something nice.
- I don't know what, either.

380
00:44:55,102 --> 00:44:58,855
Would you let another man caress you?

381
00:45:01,985 --> 00:45:05,945
You know, you said I'm scared.

382
00:45:06,030 --> 00:45:11,410
It's true, I'm scared.
Because I want you to love me.

383
00:45:11,495 --> 00:45:16,958
But at the same time,
I want you to stop loving me.

384
00:45:17,042 --> 00:45:20,795
I'm very independent, you know.

385
00:45:22,757 --> 00:45:26,551
I love you.
But not the way you think.

386
00:45:26,637 --> 00:45:29,889
- How then?
- Not the way you think.

387
00:45:29,973 --> 00:45:34,143
But you don't know what I think.
You don't know.

388
00:45:34,227 --> 00:45:37,647
- Yes, I do.
- No, it's impossible.

389
00:45:37,731 --> 00:45:43,654
I want to know
what's behind your face.

390
00:45:43,739 --> 00:45:48,868
I've looked at it for 10 minutes,
and I still know nothing.

391
00:45:48,952 --> 00:45:52,997
I'm not sad. I'm scared.

392
00:45:53,082 --> 00:45:55,291
Sweet, gentle Patricia.

393
00:45:55,376 --> 00:46:00,298
OK, then, cruel, stupid,
heartless, pathetic...

394
00:46:00,382 --> 00:46:03,592
- .. cowardly, despicable.
- Yes.

395
00:46:03,678 --> 00:46:10,058
You don't even how to apply
your lipstick. Now you're hideous.

396
00:46:10,142 --> 00:46:15,189
Say what you like, I don't care.
I'll put all this in my book.

397
00:46:15,273 --> 00:46:18,317
- What book?
- I'm writing a novel.

398
00:46:18,443 --> 00:46:22,697
- You?
- Why not me? What are you doing?

399
00:46:22,781 --> 00:46:26,117
- Taking off your top.
- Not now.

400
00:46:26,202 --> 00:46:30,246
You're a bloody pain! What is all this?

401
00:46:30,332 --> 00:46:33,292
You know William Faulkner?

402
00:46:33,376 --> 00:46:38,965
- Who's he? Someone you slept with?
- No way, Jose!

403
00:46:39,049 --> 00:46:42,594
To hell with him, then!
Take off your top.

404
00:46:42,678 --> 00:46:46,389
He's one of my favourites.
Have you read Wild Palms?

405
00:46:46,474 --> 00:46:53,397
- Take off your top, I said.
- The last sentence is beautiful.

406
00:46:59,614 --> 00:47:03,783
"Between grief and nothing,
I will take grief. "

407
00:47:03,868 --> 00:47:08,372
- Which would you choose?
- Let me see your toes.

408
00:47:08,498 --> 00:47:12,293
Toes are important in a woman.
Don't laugh.

409
00:47:12,378 --> 00:47:16,923
- Which would you choose?
- Grief's stupid.

410
00:47:17,008 --> 00:47:18,800
I'd choose nothing.

411
00:47:18,926 --> 00:47:23,722
It's not better,
but grief's a compromise.

412
00:47:23,806 --> 00:47:28,520
I want all or nothing.
And now I know.

413
00:47:28,604 --> 00:47:32,357
Now I do.
Why are you shutting your eyes?

414
00:47:32,441 --> 00:47:36,444
I'm shutting my eyes tight
so everything goes black.

415
00:47:36,529 --> 00:47:40,366
But I can't do it.
It's never entirely black.

416
00:47:40,450 --> 00:47:46,873
Your smile, seen in profile,
it's the nicest thing about you.

417
00:47:46,957 --> 00:47:50,585
- That's you.
- That's me!

418
00:48:00,389 --> 00:48:05,060
We look each other in the eyes,
and it means nothing.

419
00:48:06,979 --> 00:48:09,565
Patricia Franchini.

420
00:48:09,649 --> 00:48:14,320
I hate that name.
I'd like to be called Ingrid.

421
00:48:15,823 --> 00:48:20,077
Kneel for me.

422
00:48:20,161 --> 00:48:24,122
What's wrong?

423
00:48:24,207 --> 00:48:29,545
- I'm looking at you.
- The French are stupid, too.

424
00:48:36,846 --> 00:48:41,058
- I want you to stay with me.
- OK.

425
00:48:41,142 --> 00:48:47,189
We interrupt our programming
in order to synchronize our networks.

426
00:48:53,615 --> 00:48:57,576
Funny, I can see
my reflection in your eyes.

427
00:48:57,660 --> 00:49:00,913
A real Franco-American reconciliation.

428
00:49:00,998 --> 00:49:03,624
We're hiding like happy elephants.

429
00:49:03,708 --> 00:49:08,379
- Women's hips move me somehow.
- It's hot under here.

430
00:49:20,894 --> 00:49:26,525
If it was another man caressing you,
would you mind?

431
00:49:26,609 --> 00:49:30,362
Our musical program is about to start.

432
00:49:51,637 --> 00:49:53,720
There!

433
00:50:04,358 --> 00:50:09,780
You know Dylan Thomas'
Portrait of the Artist as a Young Dog?

434
00:50:12,576 --> 00:50:16,455
Sunday morning is most satisfying

435
00:50:16,539 --> 00:50:20,625
to have a really long lie-in.

436
00:50:20,710 --> 00:50:23,629
I'm getting dressed.

437
00:50:23,714 --> 00:50:26,924
- What time is it?
- Noon.

438
00:50:27,008 --> 00:50:29,219
Was it good?

439
00:50:31,389 --> 00:50:35,767
- Let's stay in bed.
- Nope, I've got to buy a dress.

440
00:50:35,852 --> 00:50:39,897
- Have you got your car?
- Yeah.

441
00:50:41,649 --> 00:50:44,777
Good morning, Michel.

442
00:50:52,579 --> 00:50:55,706
ElysÃ©e 99-84.

443
00:51:00,713 --> 00:51:02,797
Hello.

444
00:51:04,049 --> 00:51:06,426
Good morning.

445
00:51:06,511 --> 00:51:09,972
Has Antonio been back?

446
00:51:10,056 --> 00:51:14,226
Oh, no. This is unbelievable!

447
00:51:16,021 --> 00:51:19,274
You don't know where he is?

448
00:51:19,358 --> 00:51:24,362
No, never mind.
Michel Poiccard again.

449
00:51:24,446 --> 00:51:27,073
Want me to wear a bra?

450
00:51:35,125 --> 00:51:40,880
Which do you like best:
my eyes, my mouth or my shoulders?

451
00:51:40,964 --> 00:51:44,092
If you had to choose.

452
00:51:48,640 --> 00:51:54,771
- There was no press conference.
- No, it's at Orly in a little while.

453
00:51:54,855 --> 00:51:59,651
I'm not much of a looker,
but I'm quite a boxer!

454
00:52:03,574 --> 00:52:06,492
Going to your press conference?

455
00:52:06,577 --> 00:52:10,664
- I have to drop by the office first.
- I'll come with you.

456
00:52:10,748 --> 00:52:13,124
Eisenhower, with General de Gaulle,

457
00:52:13,209 --> 00:52:17,546
will lay a wreath
on the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier.

458
00:52:17,630 --> 00:52:20,466
- Were you in the army?
- Yes.

459
00:52:20,550 --> 00:52:25,722
- What did you do?
- I did in the sentries.

460
00:52:25,806 --> 00:52:30,936
- "Did in"?
- I laid them out flat like this.

461
00:52:33,982 --> 00:52:39,863
- I'm exhausted. I'm gonna die.
- You're crazy.

462
00:52:39,947 --> 00:52:43,032
Yeah, totally barmy.

463
00:52:43,117 --> 00:52:47,705
- What's "barmy"?
- I am.

464
00:53:05,933 --> 00:53:09,979
- Your car's not here?
- Yes... No... Yes.

465
00:53:10,063 --> 00:53:13,066
It's at the garage.

466
00:53:36,551 --> 00:53:39,136
Great, a Ford!

467
00:53:48,605 --> 00:53:51,107
- What floor?
- Fifth.

468
00:54:11,465 --> 00:54:14,592
I got the wrong floor.

469
00:54:44,459 --> 00:54:48,630
- Scared of getting old? I am.
- You're stupid!

470
00:54:51,717 --> 00:54:55,888
I told you,
the worst flaw is cowardice.

471
00:54:58,307 --> 00:55:01,810
- Will you buy me a Dior dress?
- No way!

472
00:55:01,936 --> 00:55:04,730
There are nicer dresses
at the supermarket.

473
00:55:04,815 --> 00:55:07,651
You make calls at Dior.

474
00:55:07,735 --> 00:55:12,864
It's the only place
where you can phone for free.

475
00:55:12,949 --> 00:55:16,869
France Soir! France Soir!

476
00:55:24,211 --> 00:55:29,633
- Give me one!
- Here you go.

477
00:55:29,717 --> 00:55:31,467
Thank you.

478
00:55:31,553 --> 00:55:34,763
- I'll take one, please.
- Yes, sir.

479
00:55:41,980 --> 00:56:29,497
POLICE KILLER STILL AT LARGE

480
00:56:29,532 --> 00:56:33,203
- How long will it last?
- Half an hour or so.

481
00:56:33,287 --> 00:56:36,414
I'll go and see my guy, then.

482
00:56:55,604 --> 00:56:59,774
Why did you call your novel "Candida"?

483
00:57:01,235 --> 00:57:04,780
I'm sure that the French
will give my book

484
00:57:04,864 --> 00:57:08,575
a cool reception
because of their prudishness.

485
00:57:08,660 --> 00:57:11,245
Mr Parvulesco!

486
00:57:13,748 --> 00:57:18,711
Can one still believe
in love in our time?

487
00:57:18,796 --> 00:57:22,674
Of course, especially in our time.

488
00:57:24,469 --> 00:57:26,762
What about Rilke's saying:

489
00:57:26,888 --> 00:57:31,058
"Modern life increasingly separates
men and women?"

490
00:57:31,142 --> 00:57:36,398
Rilke was a great poet,
he was probably right.

491
00:57:36,482 --> 00:57:38,066
Move back a bit!

492
00:57:38,150 --> 00:57:42,029
Typical PathÃ©-Journal!

493
00:57:43,990 --> 00:57:50,538
Do French and American women
differ in their romantic attitudes?

494
00:57:50,622 --> 00:57:54,292
French women
are totally unlike Americans.

495
00:57:54,376 --> 00:57:59,255
American women dominate men.
French women don't yet.

496
00:58:02,845 --> 00:58:06,013
What's your greatest ambition?

497
00:58:06,098 --> 00:58:10,477
Who are more moral:
unfaithful women or deserting males?

498
00:58:10,561 --> 00:58:12,312
Unfaithful women.

499
00:58:12,396 --> 00:58:16,149
Are women more sentimental than men?

500
00:58:16,234 --> 00:58:20,989
Feelings are a luxury
few women can afford.

501
00:58:21,991 --> 00:58:27,871
Do you think there is a difference
between eroticism and love?

502
00:58:30,041 --> 00:58:32,709
No, not really.

503
00:58:32,793 --> 00:58:35,755
I don't think so, because...

504
00:58:35,839 --> 00:58:39,842
Eroticism is a form of love,
and vice versa.

505
00:58:39,926 --> 00:58:43,805
Does the soul exist in modern society?

506
00:58:47,394 --> 00:58:52,523
Do women have a role to play
in modern society?

507
00:58:53,691 --> 00:58:58,781
If she's charming and wears
a striped dress and dark glasses.

508
00:58:58,865 --> 00:59:03,952
Casanova said that there's no woman
who can't be seduced with gratitude.

509
00:59:04,037 --> 00:59:06,705
Cocteau will answer that.

510
00:59:06,790 --> 00:59:12,712
How many men can a woman love
in a lifetime? Physically, I mean.

511
00:59:17,843 --> 00:59:20,220
More than that!

512
00:59:20,305 --> 00:59:24,767
- Miss, you're in the shot.
- Two things matter in life.

513
00:59:24,851 --> 00:59:29,897
For men, it's women,
and for women, money.

514
00:59:29,981 --> 00:59:33,401
If you see a pretty girl
with a rich chap,

515
00:59:33,485 --> 00:59:37,072
you know she's nice
and he's a bastard.

516
00:59:40,911 --> 00:59:44,206
- Do you like Brahms?
- Like everyone, no.

517
00:59:44,290 --> 00:59:46,999
- And Chopin?
- A creep!

518
00:59:47,084 --> 00:59:49,920
What's your greatest ambition?

519
00:59:53,800 --> 00:59:58,137
To become immortal and then die.

520
01:00:40,518 --> 01:00:43,646
Are you Claudius Mansard?

521
01:00:43,730 --> 01:00:46,482
Yes, Mr Kovacs.

522
01:00:46,566 --> 01:00:51,320
I called this morning.
I was told you'd be here.

523
01:00:51,405 --> 01:00:55,242
- Tony sent me.
- Yes, Mr Kovacs.

524
01:00:55,326 --> 01:01:00,122
- Didn't we meet in Nice?
- No, Mr Kovacs.

525
01:01:00,206 --> 01:01:05,252
- Did they call?
- They said it'd be an Oldsmobile.

526
01:01:05,336 --> 01:01:07,923
It fell through at the last minute.

527
01:01:08,007 --> 01:01:11,927
- And so?
- So, it's this.

528
01:01:24,192 --> 01:01:27,319
- 800,000.
- OK.

529
01:01:28,571 --> 01:01:34,953
- I'll have the money next week.
- You bastard!

530
01:01:35,079 --> 01:01:39,248
And you, Mr Kovacs?
Who are you?

531
01:01:41,210 --> 01:01:46,005
- So what?
- You don't get the money now.

532
01:01:46,090 --> 01:01:49,551
Tough. Is it 3 o'clock yet?

533
01:01:49,635 --> 01:01:52,763
Can I use the phone?

534
01:02:08,491 --> 01:02:13,286
- Is Antonio there?
- He just left.

535
01:02:13,371 --> 01:02:17,833
He said to meet him at the Escale at 4.

536
01:02:17,917 --> 01:02:20,128
OK, thanks.

537
01:02:23,339 --> 01:02:26,425
Don't bother. I carry my cash on me.

538
01:02:26,510 --> 01:02:31,264
- Lend me 10,000.
- No.

539
01:02:31,348 --> 01:02:33,808
5000?

540
01:02:33,893 --> 01:02:36,479
2500?

541
01:02:41,485 --> 01:02:44,613
She's not running?

542
01:02:46,115 --> 01:02:49,243
Hey, you!

543
01:02:49,327 --> 01:02:53,915
You remove the distributor cap?

544
01:02:55,083 --> 01:02:59,170
- You owe me a phone call!
- For a taxi!

545
01:03:00,172 --> 01:03:05,594
Step on it! Never mind
the pedestrians! Just hurry!

546
01:03:05,679 --> 01:03:08,096
Step on it!

547
01:03:09,349 --> 01:03:15,896
The Thunderbird's left wing torn off!
Me, not a scratch!

548
01:03:15,981 --> 01:03:22,612
That's where I was born.
Look at the eyesore they built opposite!

549
01:03:22,697 --> 01:03:27,117
Houses like that get me down.
They ruin the whole block.

550
01:03:27,202 --> 01:03:31,414
I have a feeling for beauty, Beauty.

551
01:03:32,916 --> 01:03:37,795
Go through ChÃ¢telet!
If we're late it's your fault.

552
01:03:37,879 --> 01:03:41,424
Overtake that Peugeot!

553
01:03:41,508 --> 01:03:47,056
Don't brake for a 4CV!
You're being overtaken by a scooter!

554
01:03:47,140 --> 01:03:50,059
Take the next left!

555
01:03:50,143 --> 01:03:53,730
- Wait. I'll be back.
- Yes, sir.

556
01:04:21,595 --> 01:04:23,805
He left 5 minutes ago.

557
01:04:23,890 --> 01:04:26,599
The friend who owes you money?

558
01:04:26,683 --> 01:04:30,896
Antonio Berruti, yeah,
and it's your fault.

559
01:04:30,980 --> 01:04:35,359
Now it's double or quits.
I'll tell you later.

560
01:04:35,485 --> 01:04:37,529
Overtake that 2CV.

561
01:04:37,613 --> 01:04:42,200
- Where you going?
- To the New York Herald.

562
01:04:42,285 --> 01:04:47,164
- Why bother writing?
- To have money and not rely on men.

563
01:04:47,248 --> 01:04:51,126
Paris girls look like tarts
in those short dresses.

564
01:04:51,210 --> 01:04:57,759
Makes me want to run up behind them
and do like this.

565
01:05:07,103 --> 01:05:11,691
- We'll be right back.
- Not paying the fare?

566
01:05:18,115 --> 01:05:22,494
- Where are we going?
- To the Champs Elysees, on foot.

567
01:05:22,579 --> 01:05:26,749
I hate taxi-drivers who are afraid
their car will get scratched.

568
01:05:26,834 --> 01:05:31,588
The Gestapo put up a wall here
so nobody could escape them.

569
01:05:31,672 --> 01:05:35,342
I've been thinking about that girl.

570
01:05:35,426 --> 01:05:41,474
The one with that chap on the Riviera.
You said you admired her.

571
01:05:41,559 --> 01:05:45,561
Yeah, an ordinary girl. That's rare.

572
01:05:48,107 --> 01:05:52,111
- Come with me to the paper?
- No, I've a call to make.

573
01:05:52,195 --> 01:05:57,282
I'm going to see my tailor.
I'll pick you up later.

574
01:06:16,347 --> 01:06:19,975
You're late. They're waiting.

575
01:06:46,755 --> 01:06:50,925
- Miss Patricia Franchini?
- Over there.

576
01:07:09,405 --> 01:07:14,076
You speak French?
Do you know this man?

577
01:07:21,460 --> 01:07:23,544
No.

578
01:07:31,596 --> 01:07:35,975
Careful, little girl,
don't mess with the Paris police.

579
01:07:36,059 --> 01:07:39,104
- Yes, it's Michel.
- Poiccard?

580
01:07:39,188 --> 01:07:43,233
I didn't recognise him.
It's an old photo.

581
01:07:43,317 --> 01:07:48,822
You were seen with him this morning
just outside.

582
01:07:48,906 --> 01:07:55,413
He was driving
a Ford Thunderbird, 3382 GM 75.

583
01:07:55,498 --> 01:07:59,960
- Where is he?
- I don't know.

584
01:08:00,044 --> 01:08:03,922
Watch it,
watch what you say, little girl!

585
01:08:04,007 --> 01:08:06,884
I've seen him five or six times.

586
01:08:06,969 --> 01:08:12,098
I found him nice. I don't know
where he lives or what he does.

587
01:08:12,182 --> 01:08:15,477
Known him long?

588
01:08:15,561 --> 01:08:20,024
I met him 3 weeks ago in Nice.
I was on holiday.

589
01:08:20,108 --> 01:08:24,028
He came to Paris to see someone
who owes him money.

590
01:08:24,112 --> 01:08:28,158
- Who?
- I don't know. Some Italian.

591
01:08:30,412 --> 01:08:33,747
- Think you'll see him again?
- Maybe.

592
01:08:33,831 --> 01:08:38,795
Sometimes he calls me
and asks me out. Like this morning.

593
01:08:42,841 --> 01:08:45,718
- Got a work permit?
- Yes.

594
01:08:45,803 --> 01:08:49,514
You don't want any passport problems?

595
01:08:49,598 --> 01:08:53,769
So if you see him, here's my number.

596
01:08:55,772 --> 01:08:59,149
Danton 01-00.

597
01:11:45,877 --> 01:11:50,422
President Eisenhower
is waving his arms.

598
01:11:55,262 --> 01:12:00,224
Was that what you meant
by double or quits?

599
01:12:00,308 --> 01:12:04,061
- More or less.
- Let's go see a western.

600
01:12:04,146 --> 01:12:07,274
Yeah, better wait till dark.

601
01:12:19,497 --> 01:12:24,293
Beware, Jessica. On the kiss's
beveled edge time is a void

602
01:12:24,377 --> 01:12:28,588
Avoid, avoid memory's broken pledge.

603
01:12:31,009 --> 01:12:36,264
You're wrong. Your tale is noble
and tragic as the mask of a tyrant.

604
01:12:36,348 --> 01:12:41,102
No drama so perilous or magnetic.
No detail can make our love pathetic.

605
01:12:50,698 --> 01:12:52,157
Hi, cutie!

606
01:13:07,258 --> 01:13:10,134
- What's it say?
- I'm reading it.

607
01:13:10,219 --> 01:13:15,558
The cops are stupid to be after me.
I'm one of the few who like them.

608
01:13:15,642 --> 01:13:19,395
Patricia, let me caress you.

609
01:13:21,022 --> 01:13:24,609
- Say something!
- Well!

610
01:13:24,694 --> 01:13:28,447
- So you're married.
- Show me.

611
01:13:30,992 --> 01:13:35,455
That was ages ago.
She was crazy. She dumped me.

612
01:13:35,539 --> 01:13:40,668
- Or I dumped her. I can't remember.
- I really like you, Michel.

613
01:13:40,753 --> 01:13:43,797
What's it like, to ride in a stolen car?

614
01:13:43,882 --> 01:13:46,549
- And killing a policeman?
- I was scared!

615
01:13:46,634 --> 01:13:53,557
- How did they know I knew you?
- Someone must've seen us together.

616
01:13:53,642 --> 01:13:57,771
That's very bad.
Grassing people up.

617
01:13:57,855 --> 01:14:03,193
No, it's normal. Grasses grass,
burglars burgle,

618
01:14:03,278 --> 01:14:07,447
murderers murder, lovers love.

619
01:14:10,202 --> 01:14:13,204
Look, isn't the Concorde gorgeous!

620
01:14:14,874 --> 01:14:18,877
Yes, mysterious, with all the lights.

621
01:14:18,961 --> 01:14:22,924
I was a fool to keep this car.
Gotta switch.

622
01:14:23,008 --> 01:14:26,135
- What?
- Switch cars.

623
01:14:39,234 --> 01:14:43,654
- Let's steal the Cadillac.
- Sure.

624
01:14:43,738 --> 01:14:46,200
Cadillac Eldorado.

625
01:14:46,284 --> 01:14:50,955
You drive, I hide.
They leave the keys in the car here.

626
01:14:55,168 --> 01:14:59,089
- What do I tell the man?
- Say goodnight... in English.

627
01:14:59,173 --> 01:15:02,968
He won't say a thing.
The French are chickens.

628
01:15:03,052 --> 01:15:05,804
- "Chickens"?
- Scared stiff.

629
01:15:05,888 --> 01:15:10,059
- Are you scared?
- It's too late to be scared.

630
01:15:17,109 --> 01:15:18,693
Goodnight Madam.

631
01:15:18,778 --> 01:15:25,909
ARREST IMMINENT

632
01:15:35,921 --> 01:15:38,799
I really must find Antonio.

633
01:15:38,884 --> 01:15:43,638
Once you look for someone,
you never find him.

634
01:15:46,641 --> 01:15:49,185
Who was that?

635
01:15:49,270 --> 01:15:52,648
- Step on it, poppet.
- What's "poppet"?

636
01:16:12,337 --> 01:16:16,299
- Seen Antonio?
- I'll tell you if I can kiss her.

637
01:16:17,384 --> 01:16:20,219
It's not up to me,

638
01:16:20,304 --> 01:16:22,721
it's up to her.

639
01:16:25,810 --> 01:16:28,896
He's with Zumbart in Montparnasse.

640
01:16:31,066 --> 01:16:33,150
Carl!

641
01:16:36,572 --> 01:16:40,199
- How's things?
- Antonio's not with you?

642
01:16:40,284 --> 01:16:42,869
There he is.

643
01:16:44,957 --> 01:16:47,791
- Who's that?
- Antonio?

644
01:16:47,875 --> 01:16:52,421
Patricia Franchini, Carl Zumbart.

645
01:16:52,505 --> 01:16:57,219
Let's see those socks.
Silk socks with a tweed jacket!

646
01:16:57,303 --> 01:17:01,765
- I like silk.
- Not with tweed!

647
01:17:01,850 --> 01:17:06,187
- Hi, amigo.
- Hi, sonny.

648
01:17:06,313 --> 01:17:13,069
- You wanted to see me?
- I'm in shit, deep shit.

649
01:17:13,153 --> 01:17:16,823
Shit. Got a minute?
It's that man.

650
01:17:16,907 --> 01:17:21,912
- What do I say?
- Anything you want.

651
01:17:21,997 --> 01:17:26,835
- What will they do?
- Take photos of her kissing the man.

652
01:17:26,919 --> 01:17:30,046
Blackmail, probably.

653
01:17:48,359 --> 01:17:51,862
- Right.
- I'll be right back.

654
01:17:51,946 --> 01:17:57,285
- Who's the chick?
- I'm in love with her.

655
01:18:17,391 --> 01:18:20,226
1.3 million, is OK.

656
01:18:20,312 --> 01:18:24,398
- What's your bank?
- The B.N.C.I.

657
01:18:27,234 --> 01:18:30,279
- What shall we do?
- I don't know.

658
01:18:30,363 --> 01:18:36,453
- Where can I reach you tomorrow?
- The hotels are crawling with tourists.

659
01:18:36,537 --> 01:18:42,668
- My friend in Montmartre has a big flat.
- Not Montmartre.

660
01:18:42,752 --> 01:18:47,423
- Why not?
- Too many enemies in Montmartre.

661
01:18:47,507 --> 01:18:52,637
- Try Zumbart's Swedish girl.
- Rue Campagne PremiÃ¨re?

662
01:18:52,722 --> 01:18:56,892
- Call me there tomorrow.
- Bye, amigo.

663
01:19:12,243 --> 01:19:18,750
- Antonio said we could stay the night.
- Sit down. I'll be right with you.

664
01:19:23,672 --> 01:19:25,841
OK. Smile.

665
01:19:25,925 --> 01:19:28,676
Smile!

666
01:19:28,761 --> 01:19:34,183
- You could pose. It pays good.
- You have to sleep around.

667
01:19:34,268 --> 01:19:39,272
I was just thinking... I can't decide.

668
01:19:39,356 --> 01:19:41,232
Decide what?

669
01:19:41,316 --> 01:19:45,487
I don't know.
Otherwise I wouldn't hesitate.

670
01:19:51,412 --> 01:19:55,123
- You dumped your journalist?
- Yes.

671
01:19:55,249 --> 01:19:59,670
- Why did you say hello?
- To be sure I didn't love him anymore.

672
01:19:59,754 --> 01:20:02,589
You make life difficult.

673
01:20:02,674 --> 01:20:06,969
That's it.
Drop me on the Champs Elysees?

674
01:20:11,684 --> 01:20:13,768
Bye.

675
01:20:22,195 --> 01:20:27,116
- What record is it?
- Mozart's clarinet concerto.

676
01:20:27,202 --> 01:20:30,829
- Do you mind?
- No, I like that one.

677
01:20:30,913 --> 01:20:35,335
- I thought you didn't like music.
- This one's OK.

678
01:20:35,419 --> 01:20:42,132
My dad played clarinet.
He was brilliant on the clarinet.

679
01:20:42,217 --> 01:20:46,346
Want to turn in? Sleeping's so sad.

680
01:20:46,430 --> 01:20:52,061
- We're forced to apart.
- To be apart.

681
01:20:52,145 --> 01:20:56,316
They say "sleep together",
but it's not true.

682
01:21:08,121 --> 01:21:11,248
What is it?

683
01:21:14,044 --> 01:21:16,630
Nothing.

684
01:21:18,799 --> 01:21:21,676
Patricia, come here.

685
01:21:30,771 --> 01:21:34,941
Go buy the newspaper
and a bottle of milk.

686
01:21:41,449 --> 01:21:45,202
- What time is it?
- Five.

687
01:21:50,376 --> 01:21:52,544
Engaged all the time.

688
01:21:59,636 --> 01:22:04,265
- Michel... Nothing.
- The newspaper!

689
01:22:04,349 --> 01:22:07,143
I'm looking at you.

690
01:22:10,315 --> 01:22:14,193
It's your lucky day. Take a ticket.

691
01:22:14,278 --> 01:22:18,072
- A whisky.
- Don't have any.

692
01:22:22,160 --> 01:22:25,163
Danton 01-00?

693
01:22:26,624 --> 01:22:29,835
Inspector Vital, please.

694
01:22:35,218 --> 01:22:39,387
Hello? Patricia Franchini.

695
01:22:40,473 --> 01:22:45,227
I've just seen the man
you're looking for.

696
01:22:45,311 --> 01:22:50,232
He's at 11, rue PremiÃ¨re Campagne.

697
01:22:50,316 --> 01:22:55,697
Yes. 11, rue Campagne PremiÃ¨re.
Hello?

698
01:23:48,463 --> 01:23:51,216
- Thirsty?
- No.

699
01:23:51,301 --> 01:23:54,970
Antonio's on his way. He just called.

700
01:23:55,096 --> 01:23:58,724
We're on our way to Italy, baby!

701
01:24:00,101 --> 01:24:04,022
- I can't go.
- Sure you can, I'm taking you.

702
01:24:04,106 --> 01:24:09,654
Berruti's lending me his sports car.
An Amedeo Gordini model.

703
01:24:09,738 --> 01:24:13,074
Michel, I called the police.

704
01:24:13,158 --> 01:24:17,536
- I said you were here.
- Are you mad?

705
01:24:17,620 --> 01:24:20,748
No, I'm fine.

706
01:24:22,001 --> 01:24:27,215
No, I'm not.
I don't want to go with you.

707
01:24:27,299 --> 01:24:30,719
I knew it.

708
01:24:30,803 --> 01:24:35,974
I just talked about myself,
and you, yourself.

709
01:24:36,058 --> 01:24:39,979
You should've talked about me,
and me, about you.

710
01:24:40,063 --> 01:24:43,691
I don't want to be in love with you.

711
01:24:44,735 --> 01:24:48,613
That's why I called the police.

712
01:24:48,697 --> 01:24:54,160
I stayed with you
to see if I was in love with you.

713
01:24:54,245 --> 01:24:57,873
Or if I wasn't in love with you.

714
01:24:59,376 --> 01:25:05,632
And since I'm being cruel to you,
it proves I'm not in love with you.

715
01:25:05,716 --> 01:25:07,885
Say that again!

716
01:25:07,969 --> 01:25:14,975
And since I'm being cruel to you,
it proves I'm not in love with you.

717
01:25:16,603 --> 01:25:19,648
They say there's no happy love.

718
01:25:19,732 --> 01:25:24,736
If I loved you... It's too complicated!

719
01:25:24,820 --> 01:25:29,574
On the contrary,
there's no unhappy love.

720
01:25:29,659 --> 01:25:34,914
- I want people to leave me alone.
- I'm independent.

721
01:25:34,998 --> 01:25:39,252
- Maybe you love me.
- You think you are. You're not.

722
01:25:39,336 --> 01:25:44,633
- That's why I gave you away.
- I'm better than you are.

723
01:25:44,717 --> 01:25:49,346
Now you have no choice but to go.

724
01:25:49,431 --> 01:25:52,642
You're out of your mind!

725
01:25:52,726 --> 01:25:56,520
That's a pathetic way to reason!

726
01:26:02,612 --> 01:26:06,699
You're like those women
who sleep with everyone,

727
01:26:06,783 --> 01:26:11,495
except the one man who loves them,

728
01:26:11,580 --> 01:26:15,750
saying it's because they sleep
with everyone.

729
01:26:17,337 --> 01:26:20,464
Why don't you go?

730
01:26:22,634 --> 01:26:27,097
I've slept with lots of boys.
Don't count on me.

731
01:26:28,349 --> 01:26:31,935
- Just go. Why wait?
- I'm staying.

732
01:26:32,019 --> 01:26:36,064
I'm in bad shape.
Anyway I want to go to jail.

733
01:26:36,149 --> 01:26:40,319
- You're mad!
- Yes.

734
01:26:42,198 --> 01:26:48,203
Nobody will talk to me.
I can look at the walls.

735
01:26:48,287 --> 01:26:51,290
Oh, shit! Berruti!

736
01:26:51,375 --> 01:26:54,502
Hey, amigo! I'll just park.

737
01:26:57,339 --> 01:27:01,926
Cops are coming.
The American girl grassed on me.

738
01:27:02,011 --> 01:27:07,600
- Get in! You fool! Get in!
- No, I'm staying.

739
01:27:10,311 --> 01:27:15,942
I've had enough. I'm tired.
I want to sleep.

740
01:27:16,027 --> 01:27:21,281
- You're crazy! Get in!
- Stuff the police. I'll save my neck.

741
01:27:21,365 --> 01:27:26,328
I shouldn't be thinking of her
but I can't help it.

742
01:27:26,413 --> 01:27:31,167
- Want my automatic?
- No.

743
01:27:31,251 --> 01:27:35,004
- Don't be stupid!
- Get out of here!

744
01:29:36,765 --> 01:29:39,892
I am a real creep.

745
01:29:51,907 --> 01:29:57,119
- What did he say?
- He said: "You're a real creep. "

746
01:30:01,584 --> 01:30:04,545
What's a "creep"?

