SAMir Offers
The film-maker does not intend Gustave Minda’s
“ethics” to be a Morality
The characters and situations of this work, inspired by a novel…
…have no basis in reality
No conclusions should therefore be drawn…
…from the methods of investigation
employed in the story
At birth, man is granted only one
right: the choice of his own death
But if this choice is governed by disgust with life…
…then his existence will have been purely ridiculous
Second Breath
It’s set for December 28th
If it comes off, you get your cut
And if it doesn’t come off?
It’s set for December 28th.
Forget your trip
I’ll be right back, as agreed
You might find yourself detained in Paris,
and you’re indispensable here
It’s a risky job, and without you…
Without me?  I’ll be back this time tomorrow
Blame the bastard Jacques the Notary
We can deal with him later.
I need you here, Jeannot
No one’s indispensable
-Did you do anything this evening?
-I went to the movies
-Any good?
Not bad
It’s a good thing the cashier’s coming back next week
What’s up?
Gu has escaped
Let’s go home
Alban – two cognacs
It’s extraordinary
Ten years ago I tried to help him…
…and he told me just to heave him to die in peace
I was afraid he might kill himself
Now, at forty-six years of age…
Gu has escaped
We must help him lie low
What happened?
Did you see anything?  Then keep
your mouth shut like the rest of us
Look out below
See you tomorrow
-Is it Madame?
No, Jacques.  Send everyone home
Watch out, they’re here!
Everyone in the wagon.
Don’t touch that, for God’s sake!
Who did the shooting?  Her?
It wasn’t here.  She owns the place
We’ll get you later
I doubt if he’ll tell you much
Good evening, Manouche
Jacques Ribaldi, “Jacques the
Notary” because he once studied law
He never had a chance to use it
Were you in a better position?
You know I don’t use guns any more
And I know all your enemies are dead
That’s a bit much
Try not to faint.  Anyway, as long as
Manouche is O.K., that’s all you care
Gather around
I won’t enquire about customers:
I presume there weren’t any tonight
Gentlemen, the remnants of food on the tables…
…are not signs of a hurried departure
It happens all the time, leaving
courses of a meal unfinished
No doubt they heard that the
Queen of England was hitch-hiking outside
Furthermore, Alban here did not see a thing
He was crouched behind the bar, swatting flies
When he looked up, the bad guys –
and who knows what they wanted – had gone
He’s not an inkling whether it was one man
or a tribe of Tuaregs
Right, Alban?
That’s about it
Manouche, now.  Gossip says Jacques the
Notary had a soft spot for her
But what could that have to do with anything?
Manouche saw nothing:
she was concentrating on making up a bill
And here’s the second barman: Marcel
from St Etienne, if memory serves
A fierce man bursting in so distressed
Marcel, he can’t possibly describe him
He hid behind the bar, and only now he has ventured out
He didn’t see a thing.  Right, Marcel?
Take your time
It’s just as if you had been here
Note the honesty and the amenability
of the witness, gentlemen
Here we have the commissionaire,
an honorable man whose name escapes me
He saw customers come in, but
heard nothing because of the traffic
Trains and the trucks are so noisy
He saw customers come out, but of course,
saw nothing unusual in that
They told him a man had died and
he’s still suffering from shock
Are you able to speak yet?
A real shock it was
I have no wish to torture you further.
Do sit down, don’t be so agitated
A village idiot could see that these
people saw nothing, gentlemen
As for the disappearing diners,
they aren’t paid to reason why
We aren’t all gifted with imagination.  That’s it gentlemen
Don’t bother
Am I mistaken in thinking that
the kitchen staff have gone home, Alban?
There was nothing for them to do
It’s like a kindergarten
May I repeat the request of two years ago?
It’s up-to-date
The staff records;
they won’t provide very rich pickings
Have the corpse picked up
That’s strange; it looks as though they
fired towards the street as they left
Unless someone within was shooting at them
I hope you killed at least one of them, Alban.
We’ll know in a day or two
Only the corpse is to go; the
standard formula will cover the rest
You may be wanted for questioning:
don’t leave town without advising us
He had family in Paris?
No.  Not as far as I’m aware.
They’re in Corsica
His mother and two younger brothers
Alone again, Manouche?
It’s a pity the vacancy costs so dear
It’s over
One comes to a dead end, then someone
new turns up and everything changes
Good night, Alban.  You can read this to her tonight
Former Public Enemy No. 1,
Gu Minda, escapes from jail…
…after serving ten years of a fife sentence
for robbing “The Gold Train”
Jeannot’s still in a coma
-Haven’t you had a doctor?
Sure.  Jeannot’s calling for you
I’ll go to Paris with you
Jacques wanted me to go away with him for a while
Perhaps he did love me
Hold it!
Call Manouche
Don’t you find the artillery heavy?
What have you done to Alban?
Come to finish the job, have you?
That depends
After fifteen years, I know the score
Maybe you don’t
This business can stop…
…whenever you say
-How much?
We’re not greedy
50,000 francs each
Hands up!
Don’t say anything, Manouche.
You two, lie flat on the floor
Frisk them.  Who has the key to the handcuffs?
He’s out cold.  Tell him not to say my name
Playing games, were we?
So you’re letting punks take you these days, are you?
Get up
Put your hands down.  It’s
easy hitting from behind, isn’t it?
Now we have a little chat.  What’s your name?
Henri… Henri Tourneur
Who sent you?
You shouldn’t make me ask you twice
-Jo… Jo
who? Jo Ricci
He knew my buddy
He said to hang on, that he’d put us onto something big
So we went to Jo’s every night,
and tonight he told my buddy…
…well, “that chicken’s ripe for plucking”
is what he said
Why tonight?
They killed Jacques three days ago
Were you told about her?
Just that she couldn’t go to the cops
Alban, let’s go
Where are we going?
Step on it, we’re there
I told Manouche to pick us up outside Ville d’Avray
My place is no good, Gu
We’ve had Homicide on our tails
Their boss is weird
Yes, Inspector Blot.
We heard quite a bit about him inside
How about Montrouge?
-What’s there?
-Don’t worry, you’ll be fine there
Your kingdom for a bit
The keys
-Who sent for him?
-He’s my wife’s cousin
I have to get back, but we’d better bury him in the garden first
I’d have met you if I’d known.
How did you get here, by air or by train?
By car.  I’m flying back right away
Why the fast trip?
The cigarette deal with Jacques the Notary…
He and Jeannot are both dead.  End of problem
Jeannot’s dead?
You’ll miss your partner, you always need one
Not always
I went to see my brother Jo, but I realized he wouldn’t do
But I’ve had another idea.
Orloff’s back in France; he’s in Marseilles
Yes, I know.  He has the reputation of being a lone wolf
Big money could change that
I agree.  I’ve asked him to call me at home tonight
Or better – and safer – to come and see us there
A man like Orloff would prefer that.
I’ve sent my wife to see her people
We’ll be alone
-Thanks for coming
When Paul asks, I come
Two friends and I have a proposition.
I’d like you to meet them
Pascal Leonetti
Orloff
Antoine Ripa
Do you want to start the year with two million francs?
A year can begin in many ways;
maybe even not begin at all
Yes, but in this case I have first-hand information
It’s a month from now.
We’ll be given the time, everything
A shipment escorted by two motorcyclists:
500 kilos of platinum
Five shares of two million francs each.
My informant insists on a share
Four of us and him makes five
Is it getting so hard to find the right man?
As you see
Your confidence overwhelms me
I presume the details are worked out:
I have only to accept or refuse?
I shall therefore ask no questions before deciding
I neither refuse or accept
I need a week in which to make up my mind
We have to be ready in four weeks
If I refuse, you will have three weeks
to find a fourth, or settle on three
It’s impossible with three
Three is a good combination.  I’ve done jobs on my own, too
But all that platinum warrants handling with care
You’re quite entitled to look around
for someone else while I think it over
-Scotch?
A very small one
To our coming collaboration
Come in a moment, please
Check where these two hung out
Tourneur and Bartel were at Jo Ricci’s
bar in Rue Washington every day
Two punks, stylishly iced by an ace hit man
Madame Simone Peltier is here
I’m glad to find you here, Inspector
I came to ask your permission to leave Paris
My cashier is back and I want to get away.
This business is getting me down
It doesn’t show
We’ve know each other for a long time,
and you know what I think
For many women, men killing each other
over them would be the ultimate tribute
I settle for less
Look…
These represent the death of two men…
…left half hidden, as if it hardly mattered
whether they were found or not
The work of a master
Go where you like, Manouche.  Sell up if you want…
…and meet new people, find yourself a new life
It wouldn’t be a bad move, Simone
You know, it’s a bit late to change, Inspector
For a woman like you?  You must be joking
Well?
Permission granted
Thank you
Good luck
-What do you think?
Risky
More than you think
But people like that need a lot of rope
I’ll pay Jo Ricci a visit.  His brother Paul
got screwed in a cigarette deal
Cigarettes killed Jacques the Notary,
and Jo knows about it
The corpses in the car hung out at Jo’s bar
And Manouche is quite calm and easy,
as though she’d just found a champion
Look at him: he had a lot of money once
Now he’s broke, and won’t leave the
country that way of he can help it
He’s still dangerous
Gu, it’s me
She’s coming to dinner tonight.
I thought you’d like to dress up
She has news about your getaway
I’m off.  Someone has to see to the bar
You’re safe here, you know:
only the three of us know
Manouche said she’ll fix the dinner
It’s me
You shouldn’t have; I wanted to do it all myself
Why?  You’re the guest, aren’t you?
It’s not very nice here
Compared to where I’ve been and what’s ahead…
My picture must be in every cop’s pocket
So what?  A picture isn’t the same thing as the man
Cops aren’t all that bright
Which reminds me, I saw Blot this morning
He sort of flirted with me
Told me I could go wherever I liked, and so forth
Complete freedom, you know the sort of thing
Yes, I know the sort of thing
We have to play it Blot’s way
You and I, we grew up together on the wrong side of the law
It would be the end of the world
if we couldn’t get you clear away
Whatever happens, I’m not going back inside
And me?
What about you?
Where do I fit into all of this?
You haven’t understood at all,
have you, Manouche?
You know it happened: I gambled and I lost
It’s nobody’s fault.  Now they’re looking for me,
and they’ll never stop
Good evening, Jo.  Discerning as ever
-Will you join us?
-That might be very pleasant
Mesdemoiselles Colette and Marcelline.
What will you have, Inspector?  Cognac?
I never touch alcohol; but if I may
off these young ladies something?
I’ll have a tomato juice
Colette and I do everything together
The two of us are inseparable
I’m not a man I used to be, but I
cound try to get out of my appointment
May I make a call
Pity about the girls,
but I’m too busy
Don’t over do it, Inspector
Tell them my friend has left
I have two corpses on my hands,
so I thought of you
You’re too kind
-Heard from your brother Paul?
-He’s going straight now
He’ll be taking holy orders next
When Jacques the Notary bought it, Paul came to mind
Everyone knew Jacques… Manouche, too
And you know me.  Am I fool enough to
think Jacques died because of Manouche?
Opinions differ
I’m not here to play games or get at you
You’re right about opinions
differing, and here’s what I think
You had nothing to do with it
Your brother Paul is liquidating opposition
Jacques was the big fish in cigarettes.
Now Paul is taking things easy
More or less easy, I’d say,
because I know something you don’t know
Three days after Jacques…
…a couple of third-class punks,
hardly rating even that high…
…get taken for a ride at Ville
d’Avray – you’ve seen the papers?
I knew them… just as customers,
I mean
Still the same old Jo
-What will you have, Inspector?
-A cognac
So this Tourneur and this Bartel used to come here, did they?
Two cheap crooks, yet they get
themselves killed like big shots
You realize what a scene those
two upstarts wormed themselves into?
Unless someone fixed it
There’s a house close to the spot
where we found the car…
…yet no one heard a thing
They were shot in the car while it
was still on the road
I spent the night combing a pile of
records.  Guess what I found?
The death of Francis the Gimp, fifteen
years ago.  A straight road, three shots
But at the time everyone thought that
Gu did it.  I find that extraordinary
Don’t you?
It is funny
Gu has escaped.  Gu means
Manouche and Alban
You mean Paul… by extension Jacques.
And Jacqes means Manouche and Alban
Get it?  Our two punks were here,
Probably heard about Manouche
I hadn’t thought of that
Never mind.  I’m paid to think,
and sometimes do it without thinking
So our two punks learn that
Manouche’s boyfriend is dead…
…and decide a visit to the widow
might bring easy pickings
Off they go, and run straight into Gu
We can fill in the details later.
Maybe
If he goes on like that,
he won’t stay out long
So much better for you
For me?
That Wop’s got nothing to do with me
Maybe he thinks he has
Gu would have wanted to know
who sent them
And if you ask me, they’re the kind
who talk
So your name was mentioned.  Gu will
love someone making trouble for Manouche
I don’t give a damn what he thinks
I’m not responsible for my customers
Suppose he disagrees?  He knows where
you are, but you don’t know where he is
Do you know?
Not yet, but I will
This Gu is crazy
How’s your son doing at school?
I’m sending him to England, then
Germany, to help with his exams
I hope you live to see him receive his diploma
I’m not afraid
That won’t make the danger go away.
Think of your family
I must talk to you again.
I can’t think tonight
You know where to find me.
I’ll leave the back way
It’s me
I was fast asleep
I’ll take these, or she’ll
go crazy looking for them
She’s leaving
She says she can’t stand the rain in
this country and that you need sun
She’ll make sure she isn’t followed,
then find you a hideout in Marseilles
Her cousin Theo Cassini has a boat.
You know him?
Sort of
He’ll tell you about papers,
depending on where you’re going
I’m broke, Alban.  I can’t leave
the country empty handed
I know a place in Italy, but
I need at least a small stake
I have an account to settle, too
I’d hate to leave Jo Ricci
to grow old and fat
Some things you can’t swallow
I know you’d insist on helping,
so maybe I’ll let it go
I’ll just do the driving
Here is Jo Ricci’s bar in Rue Washington,
with a back entry through the yard
This is where he lives,
in the Place des Etats-Unis
Have both telephones monitored…
…his home and the bar
I’ve got Jo nervous enough to make
a move. He may be getting a call
-What sort of call?
An invitation to a funeral
You won’t get advance notice.  Don’t
act until afterwards, and make it good
You won’t have time before, anyway
So, if I get you right, Chapter One:
Jo breakfasts on hot lead
Chapter Two: if we can’t act, we wait.
Who appears in Chapter Three?
Gu and Alban
-Isn’t in the bag
-No, it isn’t
Alban can hit a crow’s foot
at I forget how many paces
He’s why Manouche stays healthy
I told you about Gu the other night
If they come, Jo won’t eat Christmas
Turkey.  Only those two can get to him
So this is an order: if you don’t
have a clear shot, do nothing
It’s now or never.  I doubt if
Jo’s going to hang around for long
Leterrier’s in position at the bar.
Alban’s strolling along the street
And Jo Ricci’s booked on the
two o’clock flight to Corsica
At Jo Ricci’s house I saw luggage
being loaded into his Ford
If we’re quick, we can catch him
at the bar
Drive past without stopping
It’s a one-way
Go round the Etoile and come back
We’re at each end of the street.
Get Leterrier out of there
Alban checked the back entry
With luck there won’t be crowds about
We’re almost there
I’m not going in
Did you spot something?
No, it didn’t feel right
I think I’d better leave you here
until Manouche sends word what to do
My dear Alban… at a loose end?
Out walking
So am I.  Shall we go this way?
-How’s your charming employer?
-She’s gone
She’d had enough
For how long a rest?
Oh, she just went…
you know how it is
Everyone seems to be leaving.  I know
someone who’s flown off to Corsica
Some have all the luck
But you’re staying?
I have to run the business
for Manouche
Not a word as the whereabouts
of Gustave Minda
He’s really covered his tracks
Old boars are always the hardest
to flush out
And when you do, they always manage
to kill two or three hounds
I don’t enjoy hunting a man like that
That’s understandable.
I cross over here
Watch how you go
Long live the underworld!
Tell the boys that’s it for today
You’ve got to help me, Theo
I need a furnished house locally.
Price doesn’t matter, but no names
An out-of-the-way place where
I can hide someone
Who’ll be needing the boat?
It’s Gustave Minda
I thought so
Can you fix it?
There’s my father’s old house.
No one goes there in winter
I’ll go and get it ready
You’ll be saving his life
What about the boat?
It isn’t small fry.  It won’t be easy,
getting him through
-I’ll try it.  Does he have papers?
-Not yet
We’ll see to it
What’s this she’s dreamed up?
A crate marked “This side up”
I might do the trip upside-down, like a fakir
Cops are everywhere
Naturally.  What do you suppose it
was like after I went over the wall?
I live my own plan
Try to work it out right
I’m carrying
This is different.  I’ve never
been parted from it
My dear Alban…
-Is your boat in good shape, Theo?
-Still afloat, as you see
It could be on its way to Sicily
before very long
I’m going to be on a big deal…
or at least, maybe I am
I’ve got an Italian trip on, the south,
I think.  Maybe we could combine them
I’m not too keen.  Which is the
riskiest bit, leaving or arriving?
Arriving, but mostly during
the trip itself
It’s something important?
You’ll be able to retire soon
-This one I’m only charging expenses
-You’ve changed
The thing is, he needs papers.
You can tell… it’s Gu
I’ll see to the papers.
When does he want to leave?
They’re waiting on me
His woman’s going, too
Tell him the papers will take a week,
and he should grow a moustache
Also I need to get two photographs,
or a film I’ll develop
Don’t mention my name
Money?
It’s strange, but I feel like
making a donation, too
One other thing: ask Gu if he wants
to pick up two million before leaving
Miami’s fine for millionaires
Two million francs?
It’s the job I mentioned.
But I’ve got time, Gu hasn’t
It comes off in three weeks from now.
Tell Gu I need a quick decision
Meanwhile, no matter what,
I’ll see about those papers
We have to wait, though
Theo will see about the papers
and tell us when he can take us
I’m in no hurry to get to Italy broke
We’re not broke
Not us.  Me
I thought I was going along
Exactly
It’s Theo
I’ve got news
We need two photographs for papers.
I have a camera.  Also…
What would you say to two million?
Some guy needs a hand.  Equal shares:
two million francs each
Two million and you’re not
interested yourself?
I’m too old to risk it
You have some nerve!  Don’t you think
it’s risky for Gu, too?
Ask him if that gold train job
he did was easy
It didn’t kill me
What about your friend Roger?
-No one made him take part
-No one’s making you act stupid
I have no choice
I won’t let him do it
-Can you name names?
Paul… Paul Ricci
Count me in, then
If I’d known, I’d never
have got in touch with you
Listen, Manouche…
I know you’re straight, and I like
your care in choosing your team
I didn’t refuse on the spot
because it’s too big a deal
But I’ve considered carefully
If the hold-up is on the highway,
I can only take a few seconds
How can you deal with the motorcycle
escort in so short a time?
Kill them
In that case, two million
doesn’t seem enough to me
Don’t worry, a hundred million
wouldn’t be.  I’m opting out
Now, if I may, I’ll tell you about
someone who wants to opt in
No one asked you to do that
It’s a risky job
-Some foreigner?
-No
It’s someone you know well.
His name is Gustave Minda
Gu?  The cops are after him; I thought
he was far away by now
Gu here?  In this hole?
A last fling before leaving France.
He doesn’t know who’s in on it, though
Tell him about me, that he’s in, and
if he wants anything, just to ask
He won’t
The years inside must have aged him
I’ve met some of his cell mates
He’s finished.  He might crack
at any time
Yet he escaped
They got him out.  That guy who
escaped with him, Bernard…
…he jumped off a cliff when caught
The moral is don’t get caught.
Three of them escaped
Gu’s fine, the other two are dead.
I’ll answer for him
You don’t have to work with him
Gu will be in the car with Pascal and
me.  He’ll do fine, better than Jeannot
I’m sure of that
What about afterwards?
During and after.  But so what?
I’ll do my job and take my cut
If things go wrong in the car,
you’ll have to do his job
Afterwards, you said?
Yes.  Gu hasn’t moved with the times
His ideas could lead to problems
I’ll answer for afterwards, too
In that case, I agree
-Can we talk details with Gu?
-If you meet me here two hours before hand
-How soon will we know when?
-We’ll know the time the day before
Let me know; Gu will be there
By the way, don’t mention my name.
Gu doesn’t know I’m involved
He’d want to see me, and I’d rather
not know where he’s hiding out
Some you trust, some you don’t
Gentlemen, you know you have
my good wishes
He’s beginning to get up my nose
I wouldn’t let it show
What could he do, for all his airs?
If you want to grow old to enjoy
your cut, forget Orloff
Tell Alban to stop worrying.
My luck’s come back
Suppose things go wrong,
what could I do?
When you get back, everything will be fine
Here’s Theo
The same night, 23.58
The van and two motorcycles escorts
leave Toulon tomorrow at two p.m.
They’ll head for Cap d’Agde
along secondary roads
There’ll be a man sitting beside
the driver…
…and another with the crates
in the back
I’m glad you’re here, Gu
Gypsy?
Come and sit down
Get him a drink, Antoine
-How do you feel?
Don’t worry, it’ll be fine
It’s a load off our minds
to have you with us
Tell me about it, Paul
It’s a big one, Gu, but it means
split-second timing
We’ve picked a pretty wild spot
Antoine will stash an estate car, and
hide on top of the hill with a rifle
There’s a hut right there to lock away
the three guys from the van
We’ve a hideout near at hand
The van will be escorted by
two motorcyclists
We drive up in the Mercedes
Not far from Antoine…
…an unmade road joins the main
road at the bend
We wait there till the convoy passes
If we followed it too long,
they’d get suspicious
We jump them as soon as Antoine kills
the first motorcyclist.  The second…
I kill from the car.  That terrifies
the men in the van
We lock them up and go home, right?
Aren’t you afraid they might reinforce
the escort at the last moment?
No.  No chance
My informant is the man who
gives the orders
He asked for two motor-cyclists,
not four
The platinum will be in twenty cases,
each twenty-five kilos
About this big, with hand grips,
easy to handle
I think that’s all
About the motorcyclists… if we
could have avoided killing them…
But if one of them gets away,
we blow it
Besides, the men inside will be armed,
if they’re scared, they’ll keep quiet
Groundsheets?
To cover the bodies with;
saves moving them elsewhere
Good idea
Right, you never know.  I’ve a
big one we can cut in two
What’s the time?
12:05
You can get started, I think,
but don’t drive too fast
Remember to change the plates
en route
Let me hear your gun drop
What happened?
I don’t know.  I thought I heard shots
Get in, or I’ll kill you
It’s me!
I found him looking at
one of the bodies
The place belongs to my in-laws
Forty-five minutes since it started
When the van doesn’t arrive, they’ll
phone Toulon to see what’s up
Well, I’m off.  Who’s coming with me?
Me
Do you want to come with Pascal
when he picks up the cases?
There’s no need, I trust you
Let me know when, and I’ll come for my cut
You should stay with us
Maybe you won’t be around when
I go to Paul’s place to collect
Maybe
I just wanted to say it was good
working with you
I was against you being in on it
But I don’t know…
those motorcyclists…
It was just you and me
Your informant… only he would have
known all the details
He’ll be questioned, and he’s
not like us
-But we can’t…
-We must
-Only Paul knows him
-Then let Paul do it
Drop me at the station
Good Luck!
Marseilles, please
That’s it for today.  Everyone
back to the station
-Give us a break, Inspector
Bet your life I wll!
You’ve made an arrest already,
haven’t you?
Playing coy won’t help your promotion
You here?  I’m too busy to bother
with you
Nice Christmas present you’ve got
Killing police escorts, hit and run
style.  Someone will pay for this!
If you can present the bill
Ten years I’ve been on the job
and I know them all
No one gets smart with me.  Wait till
I’ve worked some of them over
I’m sure you’ll be delighted
to co-operate
It’s an order to hand over the
bullets removed from the bodies
Because we’re no experts, unlike you,
I suppose?
Very well.  Make a necklace of them
if you like
I shall not let your attitude
go unremarked, Fardiano
See if these bullets are from the gun
used in the Ville d’Avray killings
Two marksmen, one with a Colt,
the other with a rifle
Witnesses in Marseilles
are of no help
They say the car was navy, pale green,
maroon, black
As to the make, it wasn’t French
This is the laboratory
It’s the same Colt
Gentlemen, our Marseilles killer
also did the Ville d’Avray job
Now listen carefully
Jo Ricci sent two hoods after Manouche,
probably to blackmail her
They were nabbed and killed in a car heading
for the Ville d’Avray.  By Whom?
I’d say by Gu, he used the same method
on Francis the Gimp fifteen years ago
Afterwards, he didn’t get rid of the
Colt he used
He’s no longer your average killer;
he knows he’s done for
On the Marseilles job…
…he killed the motorcycle escort
with the same gun…
…because he was used to it he wouldn’t
try a new one on an important job
Now let’s consider the others
Manouche returned to Paris before the
job.  Alban never left Paris
So Gu was in on it with
other associates.  Now he’s flush
It’ll be a month or two before
he can cash in and leave the country
That’s all we know
Manouche and Alban will try to see him
Yes, but they have no problem
shaking a tail
I’d rather give them a bit of rope
Fardiano?
He won’t come up with anything.  He’ll
pull in a few suspicious characters
The guys who did the job are something
else.  After all, they knew Gu
Policemen aren’t magicians, you know
If we don’t get a break, Gu will be off and that’ll be it
We can lay our hands on the others
But someone in hiding is easier
to find
He’s behaving abnormally
We could run pictures in the papers
No pictures.  Gu wouldn’t venture out,
and we want him to do that
So have to trust to luck.  Or fate
Call it what you will
We need something, then we can
go to work on it
Police four hours late at scene
of bloody hold-up
Luckily his name isn’t mentioned
anywhere
Just as well Blot isn’t in
on this
The Parisian police don’t stick their noses into regional affairs
No, of course
I’ve a crazy hankering to go
to Marseilles
But I’m scared I might start
something if I do
I’ll be right back
I’m off, then
I have two things to say, if I may
Pascal will tell you what I feel
about your informant
Your brother Jo…
Yes, I know, but he’s my brother
Tell him nothing
You’re pushing it
His dealings are sometimes a bit off
He never knew, but I nearly
knocked him off
He ran away, anyway,
guilty conscience
You want to know about it?
His brother is O.K.
As a favor for you, Paul, I’ll
let him live to a ripe old age
Even if I wasn’t on the run,
I think I wouldn’t stay here
-Now what?
I fade into the background
Take care
Keep your hands where they are
You can get out
This is where the guy who escaped
with you got surrounded
He jumped from up there
We thought you’d like to die here.
I know you’re the sentimental type
Not too chatty, are you?
We didn’t bring you here to talk about
your life or your platinum
We don’t give a damn about that
You’ve sunk low, Gu.  Very low
You don’t care who you work with
Sorry, but Angel won’t stand
for that
Angel?
Nevada?
That was our job, and Angel doesn’t
like being double crossed
You know that, Gu.  We’ve got you…
…and we’ll find the others
You’re all going to get it,
one after another
Angel knows me.  Ten years inside and
I didn’t say a word.  I haven’t changed
Yet you stabbed him in the back
for a few bars of platinum
Is Nevada crazy, or what?  He knows
I’ve been out of circulation
I was offered a job.  If there was any
funny business, I wasn’t in on it
Well, you see, Angel thinks different
Does the work of a man like me
mean nothing?
Look at you, with your hoods
and your guns…
…talking nothing but crap.
What do you know about me?
You know nothing!  Did Angel dream
I’d double cross him?
Is he crazy, or what?
Ricci, now, do you think he’s
on the level?
-Which one?
-Both
Yes, both of them, Jo and Paul
-Paul is my friend
-So what?
-Then you weren’t in on it?
-On my word.  Angel could be wrong
No, he couldn’t
He had five million coming, and
he hasn’t received a single franc
It’s impossible. Or else Paul’s
gone mad
Nevada turned the job over for a 50%
cut: day, time, everything
Instead, Paul kept the lot, and
you’re splitting it four ways
Four ways?  No, five
Our informant had to have his cut
That’s the best joke yet!
The informant was Nevada
So Paul grabbed himself a double share
Listen carefully, now.  I’ve changed
my mind a bit
Paul’s for it, no question about that
But we want to see the others.
Maybe they were taken, like you
Why don’t you take us to them?
You don’t want much
You won’t?
Sorry.  Blot of Homicide.
We’ve taped the conversation
Everything’s legal
I won’t sign a statement, you…
Tell that to Fardiano… and
Paul Ricci.  My job is done
Gu Minda did the job with Paul Ricci.
You may find this recording useful
It’s phony, I didn’t talk!
He will here, they all do
A silly thing: a warder from the jail
you were in was on leave
He was playing boule and he
recognized you in the crowd
Much it does me, knowing that
Handcuff him to the pipes
The worst thing about it is that
your reputation’s going to suffer
Paul isn’t going to like it.  You
used to keep your mouth shut
Time was when anyone hobnobbing with
regional police would be cut dead…
…and police didn’t fraternize with crooks
Now you’re all pals together
and pass each other tips
It makes the job easy, but
it makes me want to be sick
Try not to be sick here.
Fardiano’s no nurse
I’m going back to Paris.  Any messages
for Manouche and Alban?
Friends of yours?
No, yours.  Old friends
Inspector… you make me laugh
Go ahead, while you still have
a head on your shoulders
Well, big shot?  We’re picking up your
friend, then we can all work this out
You’ve already shopped him.
Why not tell us a bit more?
I don’t like being looked at like that
You won’t be so proud
when I’m done with you
I’ll have my lawyers on you for this!
One of your friends says he did that
platinum job we know so little about
He also says you were in on it,
so we picked you up
You’ll make us lose our tempers,
shouting like that
Keep it for the peasants
Listen to this
On my word.  Angel could be wrong
No, he couldn’t
He had five million coming, and
he hasn’t received a single franc
It’s impossible.  Or else Paul’s
gone mad
Nevada turned the job over for a 50%
cut: day, time, everything
Instead, Paul kept the lot, and
you’re splitting it four ways
Four ways?  No, five
Our informant had to be cut in
That’s the best joke yet!
Our informant was Nevada
So Paul grabbed himself
a double share…
Well, was I bluffing?
It’s not true!
Remorse is to be expected
Is this a madhouse?
That depends on who we get here
I’m innocent.  I know nothing,
met no one!
I want a lawyer!
Bring up a chair
You’ll find it easier to talk.  Where
were you on the afternoon of the 28th?
At home.  I went down with flu
on Christmas Eve
-We’ll check that.  Anyone see you?
-My wife
-Anyone else?
-Isn’t she enough?
Sure.  Naturally no one else saw you
because you were out killing policemen
If you have the flu, people don’t pay
social calls
You?  At home with your wife?
We love each other.  Is that against the law?
He must be thirsty.  Give him a drink
I don’t think it was you who shot
the two motorcyclists
You were driving, weren’t you?
You won’t be able to claim we
roughed you up: no bruises
Be reasonable.  You’ll make us
get cross
Wouldn’t it be more sensible to talk,
especially if you were driving?
I know nothing about a car,
and I haven’t done anything
I want to see my lawyer
Here we go again
Do you know him?
No, I’ve never seen him before
But there are limits!
He is a human being
Weren’t the two motorcyclists?
Didn’t they have families?
Did you give them a chance?  No,
you condemned them without a hearing
I’m sure you’ll adopt their kids
Confess, that’s all I ask
Out already!  “The bloody hold-up
affair”
“To save his life, Gu Minda talked”
“One of his associates, Paul Ricci,
is in custody.  Other arrests imminent”
Ambulance!
He hates being thought a squealer.
Make sure the word gets around
He didn’t talk, I know that
It’s a lie, to make people desert him
No one will believe that,
Gu was arrested first
Do you?
I don’t give a damn.
For me, Gu is Gu
Mine alone
He won’t want to live with people believing that
So we help?
We’ll wait a few days.  It’s no use
with the cops on the alert
I warned him, but your brother
swore by Gu
It’s no surprise.  Even in prison,
Gu didn’t toe the line
It’s a pity Paul didn’t check with me.
It’s obvious Gu squealed
Let’s wait till Paul’s hearing.
There’s only Gu’s word against him
Let’s hope that’s all Gu says
He and Orloff are two of a kind
Yes, Paul bawled me out because
I didn’t care for Orloff’s airs
Orloff was in on this?
We went to see him because
he put Gu in touch with Paul
He’s still in Marseilles
Let’s ask what he thinks about Gu
We should do just that
Tell him I’m waiting
He won’t be overjoyed
A friend… Gu’s woman
Orloff, a friend of Gu’s.
I’ve been in touch
-You’ve seen him?
-No, I haven’t seen him
Could you find a way for me to see him?
I’ll try.  I’ll come back tomorrow
around three, to let you know
How will this turn out for Gu?
With a woman like that on his side,
his troubles will fade away
Meanwhile, I have to see Jo Ricci
I’ve set up a meeting in a place I own
Watch yourself.  Jo Ricci has a lousy reputation
I’m more worried about that kid Antoine
This is serious about Paul
He’s always used good men
Them, too
Paul’s inside, not them
You wished that louse on Paul,
who was sorry for him
You’ve been fed lies
Let’s stick to you and Gu
Alright.  If Gu denounced Paul,
why not you two as well?
Seeing Paul, maybe
He’ll shop us if he gets scared again
I think a trap was laid for him.
Inspector Blot has been around
Traps don’t work if you keep your
mouth shut and mind your airs
You got Paul into this
I’m ready to help
Paul has a brother and friends
You take care of Gu
I see
Gu had help all around since his escape,
and it’ll probably continue
If he escapes again, kill him
and we’ll say no more
It’s only right
And we’ll all rest easy
You have it all worked out
I like to know where I stand
If it can be proved that Gu squealed,
he dies
Haven’t you read the papers?
They don’t mention Blot.  Only Gu,
Blot and Fardiano know the truth
My brother has talked to his lawyer.
Gu shopped him all right
Your brother trusted Gu completely.
He was all for it when I suggested him
That’s no reason.  I have all the
proof I need
Gu has got to die
Listen, Fardiano isn’t
particulary bright
I can make enquiries.  If they confirm
what you say, I’ll kill Gu
If not?
It’s not my concern
We needn’t follow suit
You can do as you like
And if we can’t get to Gu,
we can always settle with you
When?
Whenever you like
People get worked up in situations
like this.  You talk too much
You’re looking out for Paul, and that’s
fine.  But I’m not on your payroll
A brother is a brother;
I quite understand
But keep your friend under control.  I won’t say that again.
If Gu squealed, he dies.
That’s all I have to say
I know you’ve done nothing to
blame yourself for
I came out with his name.
Me, Gu Minda!  Do you realize…
I have to get him out
His lawyers will tell him
you didn’t sign a statement
A taped voice won’t be enough
to convict him
The bastard Fardiano’s getting
his own back, saying I talked
I can’t bear that.  It isn’t possible
No… you deserved better than this
I should have never come back
Yes, you should
Drive on till I tell you to stop.
We’re going to have a chat
Pull up on the left
Switch off
Take this
You’re going to write an open letter
to the press…
…saying you lied about me because
you couldn’t make me talk
How Blot tricked me, and there’s no
proof Paul and I admit nothing
Got the idea?  Go ahead, then,
and make it convincing
Right.  Now sign it
Since you’re the in the mood, write
another to the Minister of Justice
Tell him the same thing
Tell him how you get your confessions
Say you’re sorry and you’ll never
do it again
-Handcuffs in which pocket?
-The left
Lean forward against the wheel
Put your hands behind you…
both of them
Smile!
One wonders where the papers get their stories…
Not from you, of course
They misinterpreted me
You know, I wasn’t very proud of
killing that motorcyclist
-Why are you telling me this?
-Isn’t it your job to know?
There were four of us.  Antoine Ripa,
Pascal Leonetti, Paul and me
Stop it!
Antoine was waiting with a rifle
I’m not listening!
That’s a shame, I know lots of people
who’d like to
You’ve changed, but not all that much
Don’t play the lone wolf.
You’ll get nowhere
I was so worried
Some things have to be done
Hundreds of cops are looking for you;
you can’t go out
Jo Ricci, Pascal and Antoine
are after you, too
Let me finish.  I’m meeting them today
I’ll ask for a few hours to prove
you didn’t shop Paul
Meanwhile, you vanish with Manouche
What about Paul?
Forget Paul.  His wife and his lawyers
will take good care of him
But I’ll see Fardiano and try to…
Suppose Fardiano won’t play?
Then I’ll have it out with the others.
No problem
Meanwhile, I sit here while Manouche
makes me a cup of tea?
You won’t have time for that.  Blot
and his men arrived last night
Blot is here?
He’ll have his work cut out
He works fast.  You’d better leave
Not till I clear my name
That’s my job
No, it’s mine
This is Fardiano’s confession.
He wrote it before he died
Why have you…
Because I don’t need it anymore
This is for Alban
Fardiano’s confession.  Don’t leave it
with them; the newspapers will want it
I’ll be back
Tell me where you’re going, so I’ll know just in case
There’s no need, I’ll be fine
I trust you, but my whole life
is in this book
I put myself on the line to get it.
Anything could happen; I’d rather know
1, Rue Vinci.  Third floor
All clear outside?
Hold it, Antoine!
A bit of a shock, I expect?
Are you in the chair, Jo?
Nothing to say?
So you’re here to avenge Paul?
That’s nice
I’ve Fardiano’s confession in my
pocket.  Do you take my word?
I believe you, Gu
That’s nice.  What about you two?
Sitting like stuffed dummies…
did you hear?
He believes me.  So what was
all this fuss about?
Where’s Orloff?
Shut up!  I’m doing all the talking
And you, Pascal, have you nothing
to say?
I’m all for believing you
That’s nice.  So you just came along
to pass the time
So you two will leave here telling
everyone it was all a misunderstanding?
Anyone can make a mistake
I wasn’t talking to you, Jo
Put your hands up high
Back up
Turn around
You see before you
the world’s biggest rat
He lives as a scavenger
Right now he’s after his brother’s
loot, and probably his wife, too
If he could send his brother to the
guillotine, he wouldn’t hesitate
Third floor
Go to the second floor
Throw down your weapons, Gu
Manouche
A real massacre. Jo Ricci, Antoine
Rip and Pascal Leonetti
Please let me through
Let her through
It’s all over, Manouche
Did he say anything?
Not a thing
Go home, Manouche; go back to Paris
What happened?
Gu Minda killed three men
and died himself
You dropped something
I did?
I’m sure of it