Women on the Verge
of a Nervous Breakdown
Ivan and I moved here
a few months ago.
The world was falling apart...
...and I wanted to save it
and save myself.
I felt like Noah.
In the coop on my terrace...
...I wanted to save
a couple of each species.
Anyway...
...I couldn't save
the couple I cared about most:
Ivan and me.
Pepa, darling...
...I never want to hear you say,
"I'm unhappy."
Yours, Ivan.
Life means nothing without you.
Will you marry me?
A million nights
wouldn't be enough.
I can't live without you.
I love you,
desire you, need you.
That night in the jungle
was heaven.
Let's get married again.
You're the geisha of my life.
Sayonara.
With you by my side,
I don't need success.
I'm willing
to accept you as you are.
Baby, some things
are unmistakably American.
I'm all yours.
- I accept you as you are.
- Great.
How many men
have you had to forget?
Say something nice.
Lie.
Tell me you've been
waiting for me...
...and you'd die
if I didn't return.
Say you still love me
as I love you.
Thanks.
Thanks a lot.
Call these two numbers.
First, I'll call one...
...then the other.
Pepa.
Pepa, sweetheart,
did you oversleep?
We started without you.
Listen. Pack all my stuff
in a suitcase.
I'm going on a trip tomorrow.
I'll come and pick it up
and say goodbye...
...but I'll call you before.
If you don't want to see me,
just leave it downstairs.
Thanks for being so understanding.
I don't deserve it.
I'll call later, darling.
Ivan?
"EXA." Hello.
Is Ivan there?
He just called me.
Sorry. He just left.
But your director is here
having a fit because you're not here.
Yes. Here he is.
I'm sorry, German.
I couldn't sleep,
so I took a pill.
Don't worry. Just come now.
I'll be right there.
I have to stop by
for some test results on my way.
Okay, but make it quick.
Some people are lucky.
I'll call your cab now.
Who wanted a taxi?
Whoever asked for a taxi,
come to the front desk.
Don't smoke...
...eat properly,
and you'll be fine.
Mr. Salcedo,
please pick up the telephone.
It's about time. Studio seven.
Did Ivan call again?
No. Forget him, honey.
I'm working on it.
Just give me time.
And cut the microphone.
Give me that paper!
Give me that!
- I'm really sorry, guys.
- Okay, let's go.
Arturo, do you take...
...Eugenia as your wife...
...and promise to be faithful,
for richer or for poorer...
...in sickness and in health,
until death do you part?
Yeah, I think so.
And you, Eugenia. Eugenia?
Yes, Father?
Do you take Arturo
as your husband?
Sure. Of course I do.
What God has united,
let no man tear asunder.
Can we kiss now, Father?
My child, you mustn't trust any man.
Not even my husband?
You can't be too careful.
Fine. We'll check it later.
Roll it.
- You start rehearsing.
- Thank you.
Here. Drink.
I'm not thirsty.
It'll help you to sleep.
I already tried it,
and it didn't help.
How many men
have you had to forget?
As many as the women
you remember.
Don't go.
I haven't moved.
Say something nice.
What shall I say?
Lie. Tell me you've
waited for me forever.
I've waited for you
all these years.
Say you'd die
if I didn't return.
I'd have died
if you hadn't returned.
Say you still love me
as I love you.
I still love you as you love me.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
Pepa, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'll be right back.
You've got some nerve.
Call this number, please.
You have no right, Pepa.
Just dial the number.
You're making a fool of yourself.
Well, a little more won't hurt.
- Were you crying?
- Yes.
There! You see? I knew it, Pepa.
Dial! They won't like
you holding up our work.
Yes, right away.
Excuse me! At your service!
My coffee can wait.
I've had enough breakfasts
in my time.
The other woman's number.
She'll never learn. Not her.
She should have by now.
Not her.
No way.
- Who's this?
- Pepa Marcos. Is Ivan there?
- Forgive my bothering you.
- Not as sorry as I am.
I must speak to him. It's urgent.
How dare you call here?
Don't yell at me.
I just had a fainting spell.
I don't care if you drop dead!
Look, Ivan and I are finished.
- Fuck off!
- Fuck off yourself!
Just tell him to call me.
Pepa, I didn't know
you had fainted.
Poor thing.
This is too much!
Don't you dare defend her!
- Mom.
- Yes?
We should talk.
Not now. I'm doing my eye lines,
and you make me nervous.
Okay. Then later?
Later. Later.
What's wrong?
That bitch Ivan sleeps with
had the nerve to call me.
He should be more discreet.
Why haven't I thrown those out?
Dad wouldn't let you.
I could sell them at the store,
you know?
I like wearing them.
It's as if time stood still.
Well, it hasn't stood still.
Don't be rude.
Let her wear what she wants.
Go on. Humor her.
She'll never get well.
Let me help you.
- Hold that.
- Let's see. There.
Like it?
You look terrific.
You're a great liar, Dad.
That's why I love you.
You think it's too dark?
- No.
- Neither do I.
- Am I interrupting something?
- No. How are you?
- Fine.
- How's the penthouse?
- Are you enjoying it?
- It's great, but I'm here to sublet it.
We'll get a good price for it.
Good. I'll want to rent an apartment.
Can I make a call?
I've been out all day.
What type of apartment?
With a terrace, but not so big.
- Yours is number seven Montalban?
- Yes, seventh floor.
220 square yards
including the terrace.
Everybody just loved
your scale model.
It turned out well.
The jerk hasn't called.
- How much is that?
- 200 pesetas.
- Is Isabel here?
- She's busy. Can I help you?
- I have to see her.
- One moment.
Hi.
You want to try a facial?
- I can't now.
- It's free.
They're giving a demonstration.
I need sleeping pills.
I've run out.
- You have the prescription?
- No. I'll bring it later or tomorrow.
I can't sleep without them.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
- She's not much in person.
- She's skinnier than on TV.
Pepa, honey, are you there?
If I can't reach you,
I'm going to get worried.
So am I.
I've had no luck
reaching you today, so...
Well?
I feel you're avoiding me.
Such bullshit.
I'll keep trying until I get you.
- I may get lucky.
- Sure.
I really want to talk to you.
- I miss you.
- I noticed.
Well, take care.
See you later.
Asshole.
This is Juan
at the real estate agency.
Tomorrow I'm sending a couple
to see your apartment.
Try to be there in the morning.
Thank you.
I'm sick of being good.
I shouldn't smoke.
I'm finally getting rid of this shit!
And this dumb flower!
Who'd think of giving a duck
as a present?
Only you.
But now I'll get rid of it all.
And of you!
"Something's come up
that concerns both of us.
I must talk to you before you leave."
Follow that cab!
I thought this only happened
in the movies.
WELCOME TO MAMBO TAXI
MAGAZINES FOR RENT
Help yourself.
It's on the house.
Thanks. Just follow that cab.
Don't worry. It's under control.
Do you mind the Mambo?
I've got everything.
Heavy metal, rock, soul...
...cumbias, even sevillanas.
Salsa, techno-pop...
...whatever you like.
- You really like Mambo?
- I love Mambo.
Yes, the Mambo...
...goes best with this decor.
You're that TV actress.
You play the killer's mother.
How about an autograph?
It's for my girlfriend.
Could you make it personal?
- What's her name?
- Azucena.
THANK YOU FOR SMOKING
- It stopped.
- What's the address?
Thirty-eight Almagro,
but I don't know what floor.
She waved.
Do you think she's on to us?
I don't care.
Where to now?
Montalban, and thank you.
Ladies, there's something
for you to lean on.
Hope it does you more good
than it did me.
Here's your food,
and that's to sleep on.
You can shit on it all you like.
Hey. Jump here. Jump!
She won't jump. She hates it.
Well, back to my waiting.
Number 38 Almagro.
Let's see.
Almagro, Almagro,
Almagro.
Thirty-one, 32, 33, 34, 35, 38.
410-0430.
Of course!
Of course. It's the same one
who insulted me this morning.
Hello.
I'm the mother
of the notorious "Crossroads Killer."
When my son comes home
after one of his famous crimes...
...his clothes are just filthy.
Where are the clothes
your son wore...
At the time of the murder?
Right here. Sparkling clean.
- No trace of blood.
- Or guts.
Unbelievable.
Ecce Homo. It's unbelievable.
A group of armed Shiites
was captured here in Madrid today...
...according to police sources.
A local Shiite spokesman
living in Madrid...
...stated that the commando group
was acting on its own...
...without any connection
to the Shiite community.
The same police sources...
...promise to release
additional information...
...within a few hours...
...after the interrogations
are completed.
Oh, my book!
Ivan, I have to speak to you.
It's urgent.
Leave a message
telling me where and when.
I'm going out
to look for you now. Bye.
It's me, Candela.
I've got to see you.
I'm going out. Call me later.
- I'm in trouble.
- So am I. Goodbye.
Pepa! Damn it, I need you!
- Pepa, it's me.
- That woman!
Pepa, answer.
I'm in big trouble.
"From your dad,
who doesn't deserve you. Ivan."
- What are you doing?
- Making a phone call.
Well, make it!
- Your mother's too much.
- I'm sorry, Marisa.
- And that slut in the window!
- What slut? Where?
Weren't you going to use the phone?
Why don't you use it?
Let's go.
Gather everything and let's go.
"Something's come up
that concerns us both.
I must talk to you
before you leave."
Throw that away!
God, I hope he called.
Pepa, it's 5:00 A.M.
I'm across from your place,
and you're still not home.
I don't know which end is up
anymore!
I can't explain over the phone.
What a pest!
I'll tell you one thing...
I don't understand,
because if you had a problem...
You'll feel guilty about this!
- It's you.
- I called a million times.
You're a drag!
Don't say that, or I'll leave.
Come on in.
I've been out all night.
So have I.
Let's have some coffee.
- Going somewhere?
- No. Ivan's leaving me.
- We're doing great.
- My life's a mess.
Mine too.
- Problems at work?
- No. I couldn't tell you on the phone.
The phone! I just ripped it out!
Damn! I'll have to call
the phone company.
Can I stay here?
I'm in big trouble, Pepa!
Fix the coffee, then we'll talk.
You're a pain today!
What?
Don't call me a pain!
I'm feeling very vulnerable.
My God.
Looks like the work of terrorists.
Oh, the phone...
This just isn't normal.
God, the cops. I'm dead.
Hello.
Open up.
We know you're in there.
- What do you want?
- To see the apartment.
- Which one?
- This one.
- Why?
- To rent it.
The real estate agency sent us.
In that case...
Come in. The owner
will be back in a minute.
- Carlos.
- Yes, honey?
It's too high.
Darling, it's a penthouse.
- And expensive.
- Super-expensive.
But it's a great location.
I want a real house,
and this is not a real house.
The girl is right.
Don't call me a girl.
Carlos.
Yes, my love?
You call this great too?
Christ.
Pepa is really something.
Let's go. Come on.
Drop that! You're a cop, right?
My Carlos a cop?
Very funny!
I'm no cop.
Isn't that your father?
Nice people don't touch
what is not theirs.
Why is this here?
I don't know.
- Do you know her?
- That's Pepa.
You know Pepa?
Not personally, no.
Well, here I am.
You know who I am?
Did you see the bed?
I think so, ma'am.
You know who I am?
Since last night.
But don't call me ma'am.
Ivan sent you for his bag?
- No, the realtor sent us.
- What a coincidence.
I'm glad to meet you anyway.
- This is Marisa.
- Who?
Oh, hello.
I'm his fiancée.
Very nice.
I'm his father's ex-lover.
Pepa, listen...
This is Candela.
Pleased to meet you.
Carlos, please.
Pardon the mess.
My life's been hectic lately.
Can you fix telephones?
I can try.
Come with me.
This one's out of order...
...and I'm expecting a call
from your dad.
Candela, make some coffee.
We have to go.
Yeah. Good idea.
Don't be rude.
This is my house.
We've got to talk.
It can't be that urgent!
- Have you any tools?
- Yes, in the kitchen.
I'll go get them.
Is this any time for repairs?
Don't you recognize her?
She was in the phone booth
last night.
I hadn't noticed.
If you don't want me here, say so.
Who says I don't?
I just learned
that my ex-lover has a son.
And he's here.
Shouldn't he come first?
But I've got a big problem.
Okay, we'll talk.
Let me know when we're leaving.
It won't take long.
Here.
Where's Ivan?
I don't know.
Why doesn't he call?
I need to talk to him.
I don't see him very much.
Don't lie.
He's taking a trip with your mom.
My mother thinks
he's going with you.
Then it's someone else.
So that's why
he didn't sleep at his studio!
- How do you know?
- I spent all night keeping watch.
You must think I'm crazy.
No. You're just nervous
from a lack of sleep.
You didn't know about me?
Never. I had no idea.
Ivan never tells me anything.
I just find things out.
Last night,
when I saw your picture...
"From your dad,
who doesn't deserve you. Ivan."
- That's how I knew.
He never says anything,
never admits anything...
...never criticizes.
Do you think I didn't know
he was cheating?
Sure, but I put up with it.
I tried talking to him civilly,
but it didn't work.
So I begged him not to lie
about important things...
...and to tell me
if he stopped loving me.
Last week, I finally got him
to admit he didn't love me.
It was like pulling teeth.
Thanks for listening,
since your father wouldn't.
Waiting for his call
had me ready to choke myself...
...with the telephone cord.
- So I ripped out the phone.
- You did right.
She's gonna jump!
Your friend's jumping!
She jumped!
Help!
Carlos, be careful!
Don't let go of me, Pepa!
Oh, my God! I can't do it.
Come on! Pull!
You could have killed yourself!
That was the idea!
I'm desperate.
So am I, and I don't go
jumping off terraces.
Young people don't know
how to fight for things.
You think life is all pleasure.
Well, it isn't.
You have to suffer a lot.
Pepa, please.
This isn't the right time.
Yes. I'm sorry.
It's because you scared me.
- Ivan...
- Yes?
I mean Carlos. Bring me
my tranquilizers from the kitchen.
I'm in big trouble.
I can see that.
Carlos, do you love me?
Please, not now.
Okay, what's wrong?
Three months ago,
I spent a weekend with a guy.
I didn't know his name or anything,
but after he left...
...I couldn't get him out of my mind.
What happened that weekend?
Nothing special.
We fucked the whole weekend.
Just thinking about it
gives me goose bumps.
It was like a revelation.
Like making love
for the first time.
I loved it.
Sex means a lot at your age.
Because he's like a terrorist.
He's more intense
than other guys.
I knew he'd be back,
and I'd agree to anything.
He came back?
Two weeks ago,
with two more guys.
- You let them all stay?
- They were with him.
- They took advantage.
- Wait, wait.
I noticed
something weird about them...
...and he confessed
that they were Shiite terrorists.
I flipped. I really did.
I knew it could be dangerous,
but I didn't think about it.
What's worse, they had weapons...
...and were planning
to attack somewhere.
Then I said to him:
"You should have
told me about this."
That's when I realized it was a ploy.
He didn't love me. He used me.
Gazpacho.
You didn't call the cops?
Delicious.
How could I?
I was a hostage in my own house.
- They were arrested yesterday?
- Yes.
- The ones on TV?
- I threw out all their stuff...
...but if they confess
where they were living...
If they're tortured,
they might tell.
They probably won't tell.
But if they do, the cops will
want me for collaborating...
...and you for not alerting them.
In my house,
I collaborate with whomever I want.
I didn't know where to go.
I couldn't face my folks.
It's bad enough
that I became a model.
You need to see a lawyer.
I'll arrange for that.
You can't leave now.
- Go to Paulina Morales.
- The feminist?
A feminist?
As a woman,
she'll take a personal interest.
I'll go change.
Then give me her address.
Why are men like that?
I really don't understand.
I couldn't stand to be
with a man right now.
That's all I needed!
Help me!
- What happened?
- Nothing. She fell asleep.
So suddenly?
The strangest things
can happen suddenly.
You should know, Candela.
It's true.
But a minute ago...
A minute ago
she wanted to go home...
...but since you ignored her...
...she got depressed
and had some gazpacho.
That made her fall asleep?
Yes. It was spiked with barbiturates.
Sorry.
We could call a doctor.
- What kind of barbiturates?
- Morphidal.
- How many?
- Twenty-five or thirty.
She'll have a good sleep.
Why did you do that?
Were you trying to kill yourself too?
It was for your dad.
He loves gazpacho.
It's no excuse...
...but after waiting for hours,
I just lost control.
That's what happened to me.
It could happen to anyone.
Don't get me wrong.
I didn't want to kill him.
Just to make him stay.
I meant to throw it, but...
I understand perfectly.
Thanks. The lawyer's address?
Thirty-one Castellana.
Do you mind staying?
The house is so full of women.
- I'll stay as long as you like.
- Thanks. And fix the phone?
- Are you okay?
- A bit shaken, but...
Don't let her near the ledge.
See you later.
Forget it.
Hi, Ana.
Look what fell down from the sky.
It's mine. Thanks.
It seemed strange. Just one.
Be more careful!
Ana was arguing
with her boyfriend...
...and it almost hit her head.
- You again!
- Hope you don't mind.
Thirty-one Castellana.
I'm glad to see you.
My girlfriend loved the autograph.
When I tell her I saw you again,
she'll think we...
Do you have eyedrops?
No. Sorry.
We could buy some.
That's okay.
Why didn't I think of eyedrops?
What a dope!
It's working.
Forget about them.
But they're hijacking
the 10:00 p.m. Stockholm flight...
...and taking it to Beirut
to free some Shiite prisoners.
That flight will be fully booked.
We must report it.
Then the cops will get me too!
I'll talk fast
so they can't trace the call.
Yeah. You have a way with words.
Police precinct. Hello.
Tonight's 10:00 p.m. Flight...
...to Stockholm...
...will be hijacked
by Shiite terrorists.
Thanks.
Here we are.
Don't tell anyone I cried.
It'll be our secret.
Good.
- Here?
- Where it says "sign."
Is Paulina Morales in?
She's not seeing anyone
this afternoon.
It's urgent. It won't take long.
Come on. You can arrange it.
- Okay. Come on.
- Thanks.
See you later.
Wait here.
I'm coming.
Can I use the phone?
Okay.
Is Paulina there?
Ivan?
I'm going crazy.
"Stockholm."
You can go in.
- Of all the nerve!
- She said I could come in.
I'm in a hurry.
Don't worry.
This won't take long.
May I sit down?
Go ahead.
What's the problem?
A friend of mine is in trouble.
A "problem."
She got involved
with a Shiite terrorist.
I'm dying to smoke. May I?
The shoe is hers.
Anyway, he showed up
with two more Shiites.
Three Shiites.
All three just moved in.
Now they've been arrested...
...and she's scared shitless.
So she needs a lawyer.
Why come to me?
- You're a feminist.
- So?
This is clear-cut chauvinism.
I'm going on a trip.
I'll recommend a colleague.
There's not much to be done.
She must turn herself in,
go to jail...
...and let the jury decide her case.
- I don't understand.
- She's committed a crime.
Her only crime was falling in love
and being afraid.
I'd do the same.
I'm sure.
I don't believe this!
And whom were you crying for?
Your friend?
Not over her.
You see?
Aren't you the victim?
Yes. I've also been cheated on.
By a terrorist?
You could say that.
But not a Shiite. He's from Madrid.
I don't give advice to the lovelorn.
You're certainly no lawyer,
you bitch!
Leave, or I'll call the police!
Was it helpful?
Yes. I feel much better.
Good.
What's this doing here?
A kid brought it
and said it's for Mr. Ivan.
If he wants it, let him come upstairs
and show his face!
Fine. Do you need some help?
No, I don't!
Pepa, I'm here in Madrid with you.
That's all I need.
I'm also with you, and I'm so happy
to see you write this card. Pepa.
He called?
Yeah. I answered.
Well? Give me that!
- I shouldn't read your postcards.
- Never mind. What did he say?
He's too embarrassed to see you,
because...
...you know who I am.
How sensitive of him!
I don't want to see him either...
...but if he wants
his damn suitcase...
...he'll have to come and get it!
- How are the girls?
- Fine.
Where's Candela?
In your room.
Did anything happen?
No, no. Did you see the lawyer?
Yes. I'll tell you about it later.
You mind my wearing your dress?
Keep it. It looks nicer on you.
Don't lose it again.
My shoes don't fit you.
- You saw the lawyer?
- Yes.
We're taking a trip.
Running from the law
like two fugitives?
It's best if we take a vacation
away from Madrid.
I sure need one.
I knew they'd lock me up...
...and get you for hiding me.
Nothing will happen.
We'll come back in a week.
You'll go to court
and tell everything...
...except for the fucking,
and that'll be that.
Really? Don't lie to me.
You know I'm naive.
The lawyer said not to worry...
...just to stay in touch with her.
I'm causing so much trouble...
...as if you don't have
enough of your own.
Let's water the plants now.
Then we'll pack our bags.
"Dr. J. Pardo.
Test results
on patient Pepa Marcos."
Christ!
- What about the animals?
- I don't know.
Your stepson was
snooping around all day, spying.
It's quite natural,
but he won't find much.
Relax. Let me do that.
Why?
- You feel okay?
- Sure.
You two clean the cage
while I water.
Poor things.
You're going to miss me.
You're depressed.
Just like me.
But you'll come along when I move.
I won't leave you alone.
I'd be a fine one to abandon you.
She's out cold. Let's see.
Anyway, who cares?
Too bad for her.
Poor bunnies!
Look. Totally dry.
Pepa just has
too much on her mind.
Did you ever have rabbits?
Back home I had many.
I know lots about them.
Look how they love turnips.
Carlos, I'm sorry I teased you
about your stuttering.
- Sometimes I'm so dumb.
- Forget it.
But you went a little too far.
You didn't behave properly.
Men keep taking advantage of me.
I always realize it when it's too late.
Look how the Arab world treated me.
I sure didn't deserve that.
This is Lucia.
I need to see you.
I can't. I'm leaving town.
We have to talk.
About something
that concerns us both.
If you mean Ivan,
I'm not interested.
Then why are you
going away with him?
Lady, you're nuts!
Between Ivan and me,
there's nothing but pain.
I'm coming anyway.
I know where you live.
For two days everyone
has been saying "no" to me.
Now it's my turn to say "no."
I must see Ivan
before he leaves.
Look somewhere else
and leave me alone!
- That was Mom?
- Yes.
Don't be too hard on her.
The way she talks...
She's mentally ill.
She threatened to come here.
- She shouldn't see you.
- And me?
Fix Marisa some coffee.
We need to talk.
The lawyer didn't work out.
We got into a fight.
She won't defend her?
She'd rather prosecute her.
How'd you meet her?
She was Mom's lawyer.
I'm not surprised
your mother is sick.
They split up before I was born.
After my birth, she went crazy...
...and was placed
in a mental institution.
My grandparents raised me.
They wouldn't let Ivan see me.
You can look now.
Mom was released a year ago.
When she got out,
she wanted to go back to Ivan...
...but he was with you.
Can you zip me up?
So she sued him for millions...
...for all the time
she'd been locked up.
Paulina was her lawyer.
Your mother doesn't mess around.
Paulina tried to sue Ivan,
but it didn't work.
What an insane story.
Mom hates me.
I represent all her years
without Ivan.
Well, I love you.
You're the only good thing
Ivan ever did.
- Oh, it's you.
- I didn't want to interrupt.
- Why so dressed up?
- I'm going out.
Don't mention the lawyer.
- What?
- See if you can wake up Marisa.
- And if not?
- It's up to you.
- Anyway, we're leaving.
- What?
- On a trip.
- Where?
- It's a secret.
- We're fugitives.
It's better if you don't know.
- But he knows everything.
- Come on.
What if Ivan calls?
Tell him I expect nothing
from him.
All I have left from him
is the suitcase...
...and I'm getting rid of it now.
No. Don't say anything.
Don't get the phone...
...or the door.
Fine.
I'll be right back.
I overheard about your mom,
and I'm really sorry.
You're a kissing fanatic!
Let's give her some coffee.
What's wrong?
Nothing. She's having fun.
I've never seen her like this.
Don't wake her.
She's having a great time.
See her face?
She's having a ball.
Her face!
Look at her lip!
Hi. I've come for my bag.
Pepa said it was here.
That's strange.
A kid brought it down earlier...
...but when Pepa saw it,
she threw a fit.
- So where's the bag?
- She took it and she said:
"If he wants it,
let him come and get it...
...and show his face!"
That's what she said.
She's upstairs now.
I'm in a hurry.
She's probably calmed down...
...but you never know.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Don't tell her I was here.
Sir, I'm a Jehovah's Witness
and cannot tell lies.
Only the truth,
and nothing but the truth.
But if she doesn't ask...
If she asks,
I have to tell the gospel truth.
Goodbye.
I'd like to lie!
The bad thing
about my religion is...
...that we can't.
I love the sound of the trumpets
on Judgment Day
Ivan, I have to speak
to you immediately.
Leave a message
and tell me when and where.
I can't pick up my bag.
I wanted to talk to you...
...but I see you're avoiding me.
I'll try again in a few days...
...when you're a bit calmer.
I want you to know
that our years together...
...were the best of my life.
I'm not going away
with any woman.
Goodbye, sweetheart.
I wish you the best
with all my heart.
I'm so unhappy
Because you no longer love me
Why should I try
to change your mind
Be happy, my love
For I'll never forget
the love you gave me
I'm so unhappy
Look at him!
He's nuts!
I'll show her, all right!
Pepa, you'll pay dearly
for those three Shiites!
I'm not going away
with any women.
Goodbye, sweetheart.
I wish you the best...
Liar!
Maybe it's true.
He can fool me with everything
but his voice.
I know all his intonations.
I worked long enough with him.
Goddamn phone!
What were you doing?
That damn fucking bitch!
What did you see in her?
Let's get your luggage.
- You did it again.
- Forget it.
Calm down!
Just look at this place.
- The cops!
- Take it easy. Come on.
It's Ivan.
I knew he's no coward.
It's your mother.
- Let's play.
- I can't!
- Should I let her in?
- Yes.
- Read the instructions!
- "Strategy is..."
Not out loud!
What are you doing here,
traitor?
- Well...
- Carlos, who is it?
I don't know.
It's the police.
What do they want?
We understood.
- Come on.
- Right.
Shut up or I'll smack you.
Good evening.
Is she with you?
We met in the elevator.
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
- Just discussing the lady's dress.
- It's awful.
- It's just a dress.
- But it's awful.
Maybe she likes it.
Stop acting like a kid
in front of the policemen!
"I love you, need you, want you."
"Your Ivan."
May I ask why you're here?
A call was made
from your telephone...
...about some terrorists.
Pardon?
Someone called from here
about the Shiite terrorists.
See! I told you!
Those kids!
There's been some mistake.
My phone's been out of order all day.
She just now pulled it out.
I called her 20 minutes ago.
Ignore her. She's a bit crazy.
- What am I charged with?
- Nothing.
We just wanted information
about who called.
Who ripped out the phone?
I did. This morning.
So nobody's called
from here today.
Pepa's some talker!
Why?
I was expecting a call.
They didn't call, and I got upset.
Who? Ivan? Where is he?
Shut up. I'll ask the questions.
Well, we will.
Go ahead. Ask her who Ivan is.
- Who's Ivan?
- The cause of this mess...
...and of the mess
your partner's about to see.
He's going to find Marisa.
All right. Explain.
May I sit down?
If I'm to bare my soul,
I'd rather be comfortable.
I've had a hard day.
Are you comfortable?
I'd be more comfortable
alone with my friends...
...playing Strategy.
You can't always
have everything.
We agree on that.
Who is this Ivan?
He was my lover.
Before that he was with her.
He's my son's father.
Him?
What's he doing here?
He came to rent my apartment.
I didn't know.
I get the feeling
you're pulling my leg.
You think I like
baring my soul to strangers?
Well, you're wrong.
It's humiliating.
Damn it, Mom!
- Candela, get me a drink.
- What kind?
- There's gazpacho.
- Right! Gazpacho!
Let's go.
- Where are you going?
- For gazpacho. Want some?
We're on duty,
but we don't want to be rude...
Gazpacho for everyone.
Is she sleeping?
Like a log.
She's Carlos' fiancée.
She was tired.
You want me to wake her up?
Not yet.
Why don't you sit down?
I'm getting a stiff neck.
We have nothing against you...
Thanks a lot.
Without being inquisitive...
...you must admit
this is a little weird.
A charred bedroom...
...a broken phone,
a smashed window...
It's been weird, all right.
Okay. Start at the beginning.
And make it clear,
concise, and fair.
I don't know if I can.
I'm too hurt to be clear,
concise, and fair.
Words!
- Just the facts.
- Okay.
I lived here with Ivan.
We loved each other.
At least, I loved him.
After months of trying
to keep our love together...
...we split up a week ago.
He told me to pack his bags.
He'd be taking a trip...
...with another woman.
- He said that?
- He never travels alone.
Remember, these two
for the cops. An extra dose.
Careful.
This is too warm.
Carlos, my God!
In front of your mother,
the cops, your fiancée!
Aren't you afraid?
Go on, please.
So I packed up his stuff
and went to work.
When I came back,
the house was like this.
Except for the phone,
which I did.
The suitcase was gone...
...and the bed was all burned.
They're taking very long.
Go. Check.
They're probably kissing.
- What about Marisa?
- She'd better wake up.
Takes after his father.
- Now, who's that?
- Yeah?
- Telephone repair. And you?
- Police.
- Your I.D.?
- And yours?
Are you the lady
who called this morning?
Yes. Here's the phone,
and here's the plug.
I reached her here by phone
20 minutes ago.
There she goes again!
Not on this phone.
Let's get to the point.
Do you know
any Shiite terrorists?
Shut up! He's asking her!
I didn't know Madrid had any.
Do you know them?
Not me. I'm not into politics.
Sure, man.
They were on TV today!
- Shut up!
- You want the TV on?
I'm not interested in Shiites.
Ma'am, what about you?
Pepa and I have
important things to discuss.
Men, right?
What's more important?
Fine. We'll talk about men.
Is Ivan involved
with these terrorists?
- Relax.
- Ivan?
I don't know.
He's hidden so many things from me.
Can you give me his address...
...or phone number?
He has no phone.
And he's not home.
I told you he's leaving town.
Try the airport.
The airport? Where's he going?
Where is he going?
To Stockholm. Tonight.
With Paulina Morales.
Stockholm!
Why didn't you say so before?
Because I just figured it out.
Now I understand it all.
The phone call.
What an idiot I am!
Why didn't I see it before?
Your lawyer
played it beautifully.
You didn't know
they'd be hijacking that flight?
The Shiites?
The whole country knows.
It was on TV.
But the tip
came from this phone.
I want to know
who the hell called...
...or I'll haul you all in!
Why aren't you at the airport?
There are more cops there
than passengers.
I don't know what's going on...
...but if you don't start talking...
Chief, this stuff has been spiked.
What's in the gazpacho?
Tomatoes, cucumbers...
...bell pepper, onion...
...one garlic clove...
...oil, salt, vinegar...
...some day-old bread, and water.
The secret's in mixing it right.
Ivan loves the way I mix it.
I made it for him.
You collect weapons?
Get back!
Move back. I don't want
to hurt the kids.
Is Ivan really going
to Stockholm?
It's just a hunch,
but I'm pretty sure.
What did you have to tell him?
Nothing, now.
I just want to forget him.
And you should do the same.
In the hospital,
I had forgotten him.
I didn't remember anything.
Until suddenly...
...one night,
I heard his voice on TV.
I didn't recognize his face...
...just his voice.
He was telling a woman
he loved her.
I felt a spasm inside me.
I remembered all the times
he's said that to me.
I regained my sanity
and my memory.
From that moment on...
...I acted as if I had been cured...
...and they released me.
If you're cured,
stop aiming at me.
But I'm not cured.
I faked it, and I fooled them.
I can only forget him
by killing him.
How will you do that?
At the airport.
The airport is full of cops.
You heard him.
I'll manage.
Now that you know...
Let's drink a toast.
Drink!
You too.
Oh, my eyes!
My eyes!
She left the door open!
The door!
Take me to the airport,
please.
Sorry. I have a date.
Take me!
- What the hell is that?
- A gun. Let's go.
My girlfriend will be mad.
Not as mad as I'll be.
Quick, to Stockholm!
Right under my nose!
Did you see that?
Come on. After them!
You again! Great!
We're meant for each other!
Whom do we follow today?
- That motorcycle!
- That Harley!
I'll do my best.
To the airport!
Blow on my eyes.
That lady is crazy,
and she carries two guns.
- Why did she take Ambite?
- Because she's in a hurry.
Ah! Eyedrops!
Anything else, ladies?
No. Just step on it.
That lady is dangerous.
No lady's dangerous
if you know how to handle her.
- There they are.
- I've got them.
I can't see.
He can never say "no."
Ana, that lady has two guns,
and she's a nut.
Look what she did to me!
You think I go around
like this for fun?
She's capable of anything!
My ass is the only one
allowed on that bike.
I'm fed up.
I'm gonna get myself
some quick cash...
...buy myself his bike and split.
With a bike...
...who needs a man?
Learning mechanics is easier
than learning male psychology.
You can figure out a bike...
...but you can never
figure out a man.
She's going for his balls!
I think she's just
trying to hang on.
Fresh out of the mental ward...
...and she looks
like a professional biker.
Be careful! She's crazy!
And she has a gun!
Bitch!
Get down!
Shut up, idiot women!
Leave my man alone!
Can't you go any faster?
Lady, this thing is a relic.
A relic?
Just remember this gun!
Okay! Don't shoot!
Don't you sell guns?
I don't need them.
What if you're held up?
I avoid danger, just like now.
Sorry, ladies.
The chase is over.
Please, just take us
to the airport somehow.
I'm a taxi driver,
not a bounty hunter.
I warned you
she was a dangerous woman.
He said he could deal.
Right here.
Thanks.
Stockholm, please?
International flights
are over there.
- You're weak, Ivan.
- Yes, sweetheart.
- Don't agree with me!
- But you're right.
Sometimes I like to be wrong.
Take me back to the hospital.
That's my home.
Are you all right?
Let go.
You saved my life, darling.
Don't worry.
I don't want anything in return.
Just one thing.
Tell her to go away!
Go away!
Pepa, I'm ashamed.
I've treated you so badly.
All I wanted was to talk to you.
I've spent two days waiting...
...looking for you,
leaving messages.
We can talk tonight.
The trip to Stockholm can wait.
No. It's too late now.
Don't hold a grudge.
Let's have a drink,
now, in the cafeteria.
Yesterday, this morning,
or even at noon today...
...we could have.
But now it's too late.
It's been too late
for the past two hours.
Then why did you come out here?
Lucia wanted to kill you...
...and I came to stop her.
Since you're out of danger,
I'm leaving.
Goodbye.
Home at last!
The visitors...
...are comfortable.
And the kids?
Candela really manages
to recover quickly.
Hope he's luckier for her
than the Shiites were.
God, what a mess!
The maid comes tomorrow.
Better wear shoes
with this mess.
I wonder which is better...
...slipping on gazpacho,
or cutting myself on the glass.
The repairman is a doll, but
I'd better save him for Marisa.
I fell asleep.
How do you feel?
Like new. But you don't look so hot.
Well, I'm going to have a baby.
I didn't know.
You're the first person
I've told.
Congratulations!
You should sit here.
I'll explain tomorrow.
- But...
- Sit down.
You just woke up,
but I haven't slept in two days.
I won't sublet it.
I love the view.
Yeah, it's gorgeous.
How long was I asleep?
Hours!
You have beautiful skin.
I had a dream.
- A good one?
- I think so.
I was a virgin this morning...
...but I don't think I am now.
- Don't tell me one of these jerks...
- No. It was in my dream!
Great!
Actually, you've lost...
...that hard look
that virgins have.
Virgins are awful.
%% If you were onstage
faking a cheap pain
%% Don't bother to act
%% I know that play
%% Liar
%% How well you fit that part
%% It would seem after all
%% That's the way you are
%% I was blinded
%% By your passionate kisses
%% You lied coldly
%% But the curtain
finally came down
%% Playacting
%% That's what you do best
%% A finely rehearsed lie
%% A well-turned mockery
%% You outdid yourself
%% Destroying my heart
%% And now that your tears are for real
%% I only remember your lies
%% Forgive me
if I don't believe you
%% But I think
you're putting on a show
%% Don't forget that after all
%% I'm supposed to be in the wrong
%% Playacting
%% That's what you do best
%% A finely rehearsed lie
%% A well-turned mockery
%% You outdid yourself
%% Destroyed my heart
}}