- Want a hot dog?
- No, thanks.
Just ketchup, please.
Thanks.
Listen, I've got an errand to run.
Kind of skimpy on the ketchup.
Duncan, I've got to do this alone.
What?
Wait, wait, wait.
You called me in Paris,
and you said we have to meet.
Now suddenly you've
got an errand to run?
What's going on?
I don't know.
It's...
...nothing.
You OK?
Yeah. I'm OK.
Really.
I know you better
than that, Connor.
Haven't seen you like this.
People change, Duncan.
You'll learn that.
Fine.
You can tell me
all about it tonight.
8:00 at the bar.
And you're buying.
Right.
8:00, and I'm buying.
You sure you
gonna be all right, Connor?
Of course. Duncan...
...watch your back.
Connor?
'OK.'
'What is it, Connor?'
'Open it. '
'Oh, a ballerina.
'Wow. She's beautiful.
'Thank you. '
'Mmm, my angel. '
'Oh, my God,
I'm so proud of you. '
'I love you, Connor. '
'I love you, my Rachel.
'Oh, God,
I'm proud of you. '
'Thank you. '
Hello?
Rachel!
'Rachel.
'My beloved Rachel.
'How long has it been
since she died?
'A year?
A century? More?
'My mind keeps slipping,
'but some things I know.
'I am Connor MacLeod
of the Clan MacLeod,
'and once,
a very long time ago,
'I was a Highlander.
'Born of this land,
'and like this land, immortal. '
Witch!
You brought
this plague on us.
You damned us all,
Connor MacLeod.
You sold your soul!
You're a witch!
You child of Satan!
They drove you from your home,
cut you off from your own people.
What else do they want?
Someone to blame.
Your mother will burn!
Connor.
Rot in hell!
Get in the house.
Get off my land!
Leave us in peace!
Connor, please.
You're not going back to Glenfinnan.
I have no choice.
Connor, please.
They can't hurt me,
and they know it,
but they can still
hurt the ones I love.
I'm afraid.
I love you, Heather.
More than anything in this world.
Do you believe me?
Yes.
Then don't be afraid.
Nothing can keep me from you.
Nothing.
Connor.
I thought you might be
the water horse...
come to take me on his back
and drown me in the loch.
No one comes
to take care of you?
Not in years.
They think I bedevil
their children
because my own was banished.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Tiny mites
and soured dispositions.
I've no need of them, Connor,
any of them.
Then it's settled.
You're coming with me.
Connor!
Connor, what is it?
I'm not sure.
It happened once before.
Connor!
In the name of the Holy See
and the rule of law...
Jacob?
...you are hereby charged,
Connor MacLeod, with heresy
and the practise of black magic.
We were friends, remember, Jacob?
I stood at your ordination.
I vouched for you.
You shouldn't have
come back, Connor.
Take him.
The ties of blood
cannot be severed by word or deed.
Mother.
Due to the infinite compassion
you are entitled
to one final opportunity
to renounce all that is unholy,
and declare Connor MacLeod
not of your loins.
How say you,
Caiolin MacLeod?
If your God
should persecute me
into the next world,
then I shall simply have
to find myself another.
Burn her!
No! No! No!
He is your son.
I am silent for you.
Black powder.
It will ease your suffering.
Mother!
No!
You're next, you demon!
My water horse.
The Devil's come back to life!
Let her be, Connor.
Father?
Please.
Do not leave me.
Father.
Connor...
'My endless days
are filled with memories of the past
'and the death of my mother
by Jacob Kell. '
Boy, you people are
extremely difficult to find.
We like it that way.
Go ahead, man.
Take your pick.
Take their heads.
They might be Immortals.
Yes, they might be.
Don't be long.
The Sanctuary.
So it's true.
What sacrifices
they have made of you,
warehoused like
rotting pieces of meat.
Tell me,
is this the better way?
I'm sure you've had
time to reflect upon it.
What you need to understand
is that I don't care
about the game.
I don't care about the rules.
I don't even care about
these pathetic souls
you keep locked away
as a barrier to the prize.
Which one is Connor MacLeod?
Well, what do we do now?
What we always do.
We're Watchers, not cops.
We'll find another volunteer.
'Whatever you fear
about Connor MacLeod,
'fear the worst. '
Who is this?
A friend.
'Don't bother looking for me, Duncan. '
He's on the move.
Duncan MacLeod
of the Clan MacLeod.
Hello, Methos.
What brings you
to my humble abode?
Need your help.
Why me?
You've been around
for 5,000 years.
I want the benefit of your experience.
And I thought it was a social call.
You ever had nightmares?
What kind of nightmares?
Bloody images
powerful enough to even
break your meditation.
We live violent lives, MacLeod.
Some of that's
bound to stay with us.
These ones came 10 years to the day
that Connor MacLeod disappeared.
Connor had good reason to go.
He told me how much
Rachel meant to him.
There was more to it than that.
I was with him that day.
The day Rachel was killed?
Something wasn't right.
'Connor, you OK?'
'Yeah. I'm OK.
Really. '
'I know you better
than that, Connor.
'I've never seen you like this. '
'People change, Duncan.
'You'll learn that. '
I need to know
if he's still alive, Methos.
You know a little
about Buddhist monks.
Some of them come
to cherish life so much
that to step on an insect
or harm a blade of grass
becomes a violation
of their creed,
so they place themselves under
an extreme form of protective custody...
A Sanctuary of sorts.
Well, for an Immortal
who comes to abhor the bloodshed,
there's a similar solution...
A way to be removed
from the game forever.
The price is unimaginably high,
but you are, for all practical purposes,
protected from the violence within you.
And it's called The Sanctuary.
Connor would never do that.
Are you sure? It's been around
since before you were born.
At least until last night.
What happened last night?
It was annihilated.
'Hey, Duncan,
what's the matter?'
'The British
destroyed the clans, Connor.
'Scotland's finished. '
'Scotland will always
be Scotland,'
and someday you'll go back.
You can bet on it.
- How much?
- Aw, come on.
Does everything have
to be a wager with you?
Well, you're the one
that keeps telling me
our lives are nothing
but a boundless game.
Good morning, gentlemen.
What seems to be
the problem here?
They refuses to pay her toll, sir.
Really? How dare they?
These men are rogues.
These men are
liars and scoundrels, sir.
They've done nothing but prey upon us
three years running,
right at this very spot.
And by whose authority
do you act?
By Deed of the King.
There is a little 'X' down here.
Does the King always
sign his name with an 'X'?
Excuse me. Sorry.
I think these gentlemen
should be paid.
That deed is a fake.
That's a matter of opinion.
You, sir,
are no better than they.
That is also a matter of opinion.
Here you go.
Ladies.
It's gold!
Why not... It's gold.
Hey, wait a minute.
They took my money!
Oh, it's here.
Let's go get 'em!
Shall we?
Aye.
Heh heh.
Not bad.
All right boys, time to go.
Let's go!
Come on!
Oh. Cuckoo.
Oh, looks heavy?
Looks like
you lost your edge, lad.
Really heavy.
- Or could he be lass?
- Could be.
Could be.
Hyah!
Come on!
Hyah! Hyah!
Hyah!
'Corporal Duncan MacLeod,
sir.
'I've come to pick up
the wounded. '
You've improved greatly.
Ah, you really think so?
No.
I'm just being gracious.
Now, remember.
You are only immortal as long
as you can keep your head
on your shoulders.
Duncan, what you give up
to your adversary in defeat...
...is everything.
I know. And at that point,
I'm very, very dead. Come on!
Not just dead, Duncan.
Empty!
Aye, Connor, I know.
It's called the Quickening.
Our strength and knowledge,
our life essence,
flows into the victor, feeds him,
and makes him stronger, yes?
It's what drives the other Immortals
to kill us,
and what forces us to be smarter,
better than the rest.
I understand.
You do?
Good.
I slipped.
Listen, soon you
and I will have to part.
There is one more thing
I want to give to you.
Va via. Va via!
Oh, aye!
Oh, aye.
This is much more to my liking.
Good.
Attack me.
But you've got your back to me.
It's not always
about strength, Duncan.
Attack me!
It's about manipulation of the mind...
...as well as the body.
Aye, but now I'm in control.
Are you?
Remember well, my friend.
Properly executed,
this move is unstoppable.
we'll now have this talk again.
Who are you?
A friend or a lover.
Or a wife.
- Kate?
- Atta boy.
Except I'm Faith now.
Part of the makeover.
What are you doing here?
Remember our wedding day,
Duncan?
I do.
The way we danced.
I felt like we were flying.
Of course, we did come down,
didn't we?
Crashing.
Oh, shit.
It's time to show
our Immortal brother a thing or two.
Somebody order a club sandwich?
He's funny.
Nice outfit, too.
Faith, I told you
I look like a fuckin' orange!
I'm not dressing you black, Bob.
Trust me.
- Who are they?
- Friends.
What, it's a team sport now?
What, you didn't know?
It's a whole new ball game.
Hey!
Nice bat.
Told you I was gonna cut you.
Let my man Jin Ke
deal with him.
Jin Ke...
...who served
with the Emperor Chin.
The same man.
Some people say
you're a man of honour.
What do you know about honour?
Oh, great.
Yah!
Honour's not in a weapon.
It's in the man.
Enough!
Boys, boys.
I do apologise.
When it comes to discipline,
the first hundred years
are the hardest.
Guess I'm not much
of a swords guy.
I thought I told you to stop.
Yeah, well, I stopped.
Tell me, Carlos.
How much is your life worth?
Don't start this bullshit, man.
'Cause the only way
to win your freedom
is to kill me.
- You're crazy.
- Am I?
Then go ahead.
Stop the madness.
Can you live with the fear?
Can you live
with the weakness?
Weakness, Carlos.
I call this
decap with a twist...
No sugar.
Watchers?
Watchers observe Immortals.
They're not supposed to interfere.
Unfortunately, our role
has changed somewhat.
Why?
Because the rules have been broken.
One of your kind has gone renegade.
In doing so, he's gained
himself a sizable advantage.
One that'll be
impossible to overcome.
Nobody's unbeatable.
Oh, yes, Duncan.
He is.
Unbeatable.
No.
Sorry about that.
There must always
be two of your kind.
As long as there are two,
and you're kept from fighting,
then the prize is safe.
The Sanctuary must not fail again.
You're insane.
Get yourself another volunteer.
We had a number of volunteers!
Sadly, that's no longer the case.
You'll be warehoused, hidden away.
Go to hell.
Don't worry.
The drugs
will kick in momentarily.
Get up.
Get up!
You have better things to do
than lie there on your ass.
Who are you?
Someone who knows more about you
than you know about yourself.
Are you a demon?
I've been called that
and worse.
I'm Connor MacLeod
of the Clan MacLeod.
Connor MacLeod?
And like you, my friend,
I have a hard time dying.
Dawson?
You look like shit.
Thanks.
How long have I...
We'll talk about it later.
We gotta get outta here.
Come on, can you walk?
Yeah.
Go. Go!
What are you doing here?
Keeping tabs on you.
Yeah?
Well, someone should keep tabs
on that psychotic asshole back there.
Didn't you get it back in London?
These guys don't play by the rules.
You don't know what
you're up against, Mac.
So people keep telling me.
Stop the car.
I managed to liberate
that from their lost and found.
There's blood on it.
I didn't say it was easy.
- Pull over.
- What?
Pull over.
MacLeod, tell me something.
Mac, hear him out!
Mac! Will you tell me something?
Now, how many Quickenings
have you had?
How many heads have you taken?
I don't keep score.
Well, we do.
'MacLeod, Connor. '
What's that?
The Watchers' version of a résumé.
'262 confirmed Immortal kills. '
It's a bit like handicapping horses,
but it's part of the gig, all right?
'MacLeod, Duncan.
'174 confirmed Immortal kills.
'174 confirmed Immortal kills. '
Sound about right?
So, what's your point?
Here's the gentleman
you met in Connor's loft.
'Kell, Jacob.
661 confirmed Immortal kills.
'661 confirmed Immortal kills. '
Welcome to your worst nightmare.
Sanctuary wasn't shit, pal.
This guy is way out of your league.
I want to see
Connor MacLeod's body.
Why?
Something doesn't make sense.
What are you saying?
I think he's saying
he wants to see the body.
Well, it's gonna be a rough I.D.
They're all missing their heads!
We gave 'em
a Christian burial, MacLeod.
It was decent, you know.
Said all the right words.
Can't begin to tell you
how reassuring that is.
With all these
unexplained corpses,
well, we had to take it
off the beaten track.
End of the road, Joe.
Thanks.
You watch your ass, MacLeod.
It's not my ass
I'm worried about.
Did I happen to mention
about all this coming to a bad end?
No, Methos.
I don't believe you did.
You were gonna stay and dig.
Dig? Oh, yeah!
'I need to know
if he's still alive, Professor.
'I want to see
Connor MacLeod's body. '
'One of your kind
has gone renegade. '
'People change, Duncan.
'You'll learn that. '
No.
What are you doing here?
You walked out
on your life, Connor.
Why?
I had my reasons.
Reasons?
Every life I touch ends...
...brutally and for no reason.
It's a curse that's followed me
for centuries.
I can't outrun it,
and I can't outlive it.
Rachel's death made you
the last soul on this planet
that means a damn to me.
I thought there was a way out.
The Sanctuary?
Yes.
The Sanctuary.
So, how did you escape?
I didn't escape.
I was let go.
I couldn't see the slaughter...
...only heard it...
...and felt it.
Jacob Kell.
So, here we are.
Both Immortal.
Missed the signs,
didn't we?
But we were both
so new at the game.
Connor.
What a glorious sight.
Just look, Connor.
Look back at the endless
travesties of your life,
and you'll see me, always there
waiting in the shadows.
When friends and lovers
are wiped from your sight...
...I'm there.
When those you cherish
die abruptly and for no reason
I'm there for you.
And when your cellmates
in their so-called Sanctuary
are left twitching
like headless chickens...
Guess who?
Connor.
Stay out of it, Duncan.
Would you kill
an unarmed man again, Connor?
You didn't know, Duncan?
Because you didn't tell him.
Would that finally put the agony
in your soul to rest?
Then go ahead.
Send me home.
What's stopping you?
Honour?
Guilt?
The nagging sense that maybe you,
more than I, deserve to die?
Or somewhere along the way
did you just lose your nerve?
It's holy ground, Connor.
Yes.
Take your shot.
What better chance than now?
Do it.
Do it for your sweet mother.
Or the sweet little war orphan
Rachel Ellenstein...
...who, if I'm not mistaken,
you raised
as your own daughter.
Tell me, do they even begin
to equal for the murder
of a man of God
who raised me as his own son?
Slow...
...close...
Feels good, doesn't it?
But look at you.
Even now, you're afraid,
afraid you'll lose.
That's your true fear, isn't it?
The thought of giving up
your essence to me,
making me
even stronger by it.
What's wrong?
Don't you want
to be inside me?
I want you to think back
to this moment, Connor!
In the endless nights ahead!
And know...
...that every time
you close your eyes
from now to eternity,
I'll be there!
Ripping apart the ones
you care about most!
It's never over,
Connor MacLeod.
Living is what matters.
And you will live with this.
Count on it.
One far-off day, you and I
will be the only two remaining.
You will look back on this
and know you had
one chance to stop me.
You failed.
But until that day,
I will take my vengeance
on those you love.
Your living has been my prize.
For old times' sake.
'He is your son. '
You, on the other hand...
...are on borrowed time.
Call you.
Is what he said true?
Is it?
Believe only what your heart
and conscience tell you.
Connor, with time,
anything can be forgiven.
You taught me that.
Did I?
Oh, look at Dave. Dave!
Behave yourself, Duncan!
No more talking!
May all your hardships fade away.
Till night becomes morn,
let love remain
to guide your way.
Till the day we are reborn.
Kiss her, won't you?
Connor?
I thought you'd never get here.
Connor!
You know
Kate is like us, Immortal.
Aye. I sensed something
the day we met,
but I wasn't sure.
Well, now you know.
And you know as well as I do
that her immortality
can only be triggered
by the shock of a violent death.
Yes, I do.
And without such a death,
she will simply grow old and die.
Yes, I know, Connor.
Is that what you came
to tell me on my wedding day?
Come on.
Drink up, man.
No.
I was wondering.
Does she know?
Why?
Many years
after I was married...
...one night...
...I found Heather
in front of the house.
She had a knife in one hand
and her hair in the other.
When I asked her why she
had done such a thing to herself,
she said it was
the one part of her
that would never age.
It would forever
remain the same
as when I first
fell in love with her.
That's how she wanted me
to remember her.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I once loved a woman
more than life itself...
...and I watched her die.
Unlike me, you have a choice.
What would you have me tell her?
I'd tell her nothing.
She wouldn't believe you anyway.
Then I can do nothing.
She's in the flower of her youth.
Enjoy the moment,
and let it pass.
And if it were you in my place?
I was in your place!
But I thank God
I never had the choice.
I love Kate,
and I will hold on to her
as long as I can.
And that is all I can do!
'Forever, my love. '
'Until the day we are reborn. '
- You haven't lost your touch.
- What do you want?
- To talk.
- Oh, that's a first.
I've tried to talk to you
a thousand times...
Get to the point.
- I was wrong.
- Oh, no, no.
Stealing is wrong.
Lying is wrong.
Killing's wrong.
What you did
goes well beyond wrong.
Fine. I deserve that,
but I want a chance
to make it right.
You want to make it right?
Then give me back the ability
to have children,
to grow old
with the man I love.
How about anything that
resembles a normal life?
And you took it all
away from me.
Those things I can't give you.
Oh, something else
you forgot to tell me.
Goodbye, Duncan.
Kell can't give you those things, either,
so tell me, Kate, why him?
Because I've never known anybody
with such a capacity for hate
except me.
That's what's kept you
going all these years?
Fine.
Go home, Faith.
Take care of what's important.
You were with him.
A woman is a temple
built on a sewer.
Remember what you were
when I first found you.
A whore.
Now, look at you.
A liberated whore.
Fuck you.
Oh, we'll get to that, blossom.
But in the interim, be grateful
I don't take your pretty little face off.
Hurts, doesn't it...
...that there is something
you actually can't have?
I can have
anything I want.
Except me.
I've already had you.
Not really.
Close enough.
Forever.
May love remain
to guide our way
till the day we are reborn.
Forgive me.
I'm sorry.
You had no right.
Kate?
No. Don't be frightened.
You're Immortal, we both are.
I did it for you...
...for us.
Kate.
- Oh, no!
- Oh, my God! What have I done?
Kate!
'You wanted this. '
You forced it on me.
I never asked for eternity.
'I never wanted us to be apart. '
- Would you have really understood?
- Which part?
The endless, numbing
sameness of it all?
Or never bothering
to love someone
because whole lifetimes tick by so fast
they don't even count any more?
Then why did you come?
To see if I could feel again...
...anything.
You're missing the point, Kate.
The difference
between Connor and I
is that as long
as you're still alive,
there's a chance that one day
I might be forgiven.
It may take years...
...centuries, even.
But at least I can carry
that hope inside me.
That's one blessing
of immortality...
...there's always tomorrow.
Even for us.
What are you doing, Jin?
Just thinking.
Men, for the most part,
can mend their ways
only after they have made
a mistake.
One day soon,
we will all serve very little purpose
to Kell, except dead.
A toast.
I see tonight...
...as a celebration of the spirit.
To all of you
who continue to stand by me
even those who might waver
at times...
You are my flock.
You
nourish my soul.
You are all a part
of a great journey,
a 400-year quest...
...for justice.
And here, my friends,
is the instrument of that justice.
The giver and taker
of creation...
...baptised in blood.
It is the living
that matters after all.
It sings like an angel.
Just listen.
Till the day we are reborn.
Kell.
Jacob Kell.
Connor?
We've lived many lives,
you and I.
We've seen things that most people
could never understand.
But now what do you see?
I see someone who would
never kill an unarmed man.
I also see someone
who has lost hope.
Life brings hope and pain...
...but revenge
never brings redemption.
The path and choice are ours.
Connor, what the hell's going on?
I have chosen mine.
What are you doing?
Kell's too strong,
and he's getting stronger.
Neither one of us can beat him alone.
Are you out of your mind?
If we let him win,
it could mean the end.
Connor, no!
Kell is going to kill you, Duncan,
just to torment me,
and there is nothing
you can do about it, nothing!
I don't believe that, Connor.
Neither should you.
Alone, neither one of us
can beat him.
Together, we can.
You know the rules.
Only one Immortal
can challenge another.
And only one will.
This isn't the answer.
Listen to me.
In the end,
there can be only one,
and that has to be you.
No.
We can beat him together.
Then we are in agreement.
Enough, Connor!
I won't fight you.
I will never fight you, Connor.
Then you die!
No!
You're not doing this, Connor.
Oh, yes, we're doing this.
Every day, every breath we took
was for this end.
Look inside
and tell me I'm wrong.
Do it!
I can't.
Remember how
you first found me?
Sitting in that bloody bog,
scared out of my mind?
You taught me how to live, Connor.
You taught me why we live.
Have you forgotten all of that?
No.
Our bonds are all
that hold us in this world.
Don't break this one.
Please, Connor.
I'm begging you.
It's too late.
This has to be done.
No, Connor!
Not like this!
Come on, stop!
- Connor, stop!
- Duncan!
One of us has to die now,
old friend.
No.
And you know it.
Goodbye, Duncan...
...my true brother.
I love you, Connor.
No!
Duncan.
Well done.
I ever thought
you had him in you.
What does it feel like
to kill a brother?
Feels good,
doesn't it?
You'll never know, will you?
Now you'll never have
Connor MacLeod's head.
Are you going to run?
Are you going to hide?
Run?
Brother, come on!
How bad do you want it,
Duncan?
You'll pay!
Duncan!
OK, Kell. Come on.
Let's do this.
Just watch.
Merry Christmas.
A valiant effort, Duncan.
Too bad.
And this is just the beginning.
You see, when you absorbed
Connor's spirit, you inherited his curse.
Revenge is so sweet.
I wonder who we'll start with?
Oh, Kate.
'Forever. '
Oh, God.
Kell!
Jacob Kell!
Revenge will never
bring you redemption,
so I'm going to do it for you.
Is that all you've got?
Duncan, I'd thought
I'd be home for dinner an hour ago,
but this is very impressive.
Come on.
What are you waiting for?
I'd be delighted.
Yah!
Impressive... isn't it?
Duncan!
You see at last your fate!
Yes!
Because this game is done!
Well, look on the bright side.
At least
you went down swinging.
'Jacob Kell.
'Time for redemption.
'The game isn't over yet.
'What's the matter?
'Don't you want to be inside me?
'In the end... '
...there can be only one.
'And you're not it. '
Call ya.
No!
Hope you found peace,
my friend.
So, why are you here?
You hoping you'd find me?
For whatever reason,
Kell made his choice.
So...
...what now?
Trust.
You can always trust me, Faith.
Faith is dead.
I thought we'd give
Kate another chance.
Not yet.
'Till the day we are reborn. '
You hold onto it for me.
We've got plenty of time.