( eIectronics beeping )
( beeping continues )
Prepare Nautilus
for orbit capture.
Computer:
Orbit capture trajectory confirmed.
Engage main thrusters.
Disengaging artificiaI gravity
for Mercury approach.
Someone forget
to secure their tabIet?
Oh.
Remind me to fire the maid.
( sighs )
Computer:
Approaching coordinates.
- Awaiting manuaI override.
- AII right, NataIie.
Manual flight
controIs engaged.
We're going in.
Computer:
Warning, soIar event detected.
- ( eIectronics beeping )
- What's happening?
We have an eIectromagnetic
radiation spike, a big one.
- Are we within safe IeveIs?
- So far.
- Lee, stay on course.
- Entering orbit in 20 seconds.
- ( beeping )
- Computer: Warning...
- radiation shieIds activated.
- What the heII was that?
Radiation levels
are spiking off the charts.
Abort orbit capture.
- Lee, get us out of here.
- Roger that.
Engaging artificiaI gravity.
- ( beeping )
- Computer: AIarm,
- system failure.
- Everything is spiking.
- Heat, magnetics--
- Magnetics, that can't be.
- Are you sure?
- That's what I'm reading.
- Increase thrusters to maximum.
- Come on, darlin'.
Hang in there.
Computer: Warning,
radiation IeveIs at maximum.
My God.
- ( alarms beeping )
- Computer: AIarm, system faiIure.
Damage report!
System faiIures across the board.
l can't hold anything online.
- ( beeping )
- Computer: AIarm, system faiIure.
- Losing power to engines.
- Victoria, check out backup systems.
I'm on it.
There's a fire in the comm.
Computer: Warning,
engine power criticaI.
Come on.
No!
Chaos.
Destruction.
UnpredictabiIity.
Our universe...
is a dangerous pIace.
In our soIar system,
there are over
a thousand asteroids
and comets
that are cIassified
as threatening to hit the earth.
But you shouId aIso know
that those are just the ones
we know about.
Just Iast year,
an asteroid
200 feet in diameter
passed within
40,000 miIes of us.
Now in pIanetary terms,
that is Iike, uh--
it's Iike someone
shooting at you
and having a buIIet
part your hair
without touching your skin.
Now, if it had hit us,
it would have exploded
with the force of a hydrogen bomb.
Do you know how much
advance warning we had?
Three days.
The good news is,
we have the technoIogy
to defIect these objects.
It's caIIed Project 7.
The most advanced,
most powerful,
most ambitious pIanetary
defense system
ever conceived.
It's equipped
with an energy fieId
that aIIows it to defIect objects
many times its size.
The bad news?
- There's aIways bad news.
- ( students Iaugh )
Our government puIIed funding
from Project 7
just before it came onIine.
So right now
it fIoats dormant in space.
The earth's been struck before,
it'II be struck again.
The onIy question
is whether
we're gonna be ready.
Do your part
in protecting the pIanet.
Write to your congressman,
teII your friends.
Spread the word.
Our Iives may depend on it.
We need Project 7.
You.
You need Project 7.
- Thank you very much.
- ( applause )
Dr. Preston, Brad WaIker.
Your Iiaison officer
with Mission Ops.
Can I speak with you
for a moment?
- Yeah.
- As you know, it is our poIicy
to, uh, notify
famiIy members immediateIy
of any situation invoIving
the mission that may arise.
- I know the protocoI.
- Now, I've been sent here
to make sure you don't hear
anything through the media
that may make you worry
unnecessariIy.
Now, having said that, um,
earIy this morning, we did
Iose contact with the NautiIus.
Dr. Preston.
Dr. Preston, wait.
- ( Iine ringing )
- Dr. Preston: Come on, pick up.
- ( phone chimes )
- Recording: We're sorry,
your caII cannot
be compIeted as diaIed.
PIease check the number
and dial again...
- Damn it!
- ...or caII your oper--
Okay.
AII right.
( touch tones beeping )
( Iine ringing )
( phone rings )
- HeIIo?
- Hey, it's James.
I can't taIk to you.
l'm at work.
- lf Edward finds out--
- I'm worried about Victoria.
Today was orbit capture.
They Iost contact with the NautiIus.
l can't reach Mission Ops.
Do you know anything?
l don't, but Houston
doesn't caII the miIitary
every time they have a gIitch.
You know that.
It's probabIy nothing.
I'm sure Victoria's fine.
I know you have eyes in the sky.
Just check it out for me, okay?
CaII me back
if you find anything.
You know I can't taIk to you
about this stuff.
Edward doesn't even Iike
that we're friends.
( modem screeching )
- What the heII?
- What?
Jennifer, did SPEAR
just activate Project 7?
What are you taIking about?
lt's dead.
It's been dead for three years.
Oh, uh, it's sending me data.
Jennifer:
It's sending data to you?
lf Edward finds out that
you've been monitoring it,
he'II throw you in jaiI so fast
that you won't know--
Okay, uh, something weird
is happening.
Project 7
is picking up a strange--
HeIIo?
Okay.
Oh, that's impossibIe.
( sateIIite beeping )
( bridge creaking )
- Status report.
- The EM wave knocked out
virtually every civilian satellite
and most government ones as weII.
We're the onIy major agency
fuIIy functioning right now.
- But that's not our onIy probIem.
- Three sets of images,
aII puIIed from
the deep-sky orbitaI teIescope
before it went down
compIeteIy.
These were all taken
onIy five minutes apart.
What's that spot?
That spot, sir,
- is Mercury.
- That can't be right.
- That wouId mean that--
- Mercury's on the move.
- How's that possibIe?
- We don't have aII the data yet.
We stiII don't know.
( sighs )
Figure out where it's headed.
I want to know if that thing
is coming anywhere near us.
Jennifer:
We're aIready on it.
( computer beeps )
( coughs )
MarshaII?
Oh, thank God.
Breathe.
Check Lee.
( aIarms beeping )
Go, I'II take care of Lee.
- ( eIectricity buzzing )
- ( coughs )
Mercury will miss the Earth
by a distance of 500,000 miIes.
RoughIy twice as far away
as the moon.
- That's not good.
- ExactIy.
Even at that distance,
its gravitationaI fieId
wiII wreak havoc.
Extreme tides,
eIectricaI disturbances at a minimum.
WeII, our primary concern at this point
has gotta be the poIiticaI faIIout.
Put our defense systems
on high aIert.
l've also had Michelle working
to get in touch with the NautiIus,
but we haven't had
any success.
Nautilus is the least
of our concerns at this point.
But they were right there.
If the NautiIus
did manage to puII through,
they may be able
to fiII in the bIanks.
Fine, but you keep
James Preston out of it.
Yes, sir.
( static hissing )
Man over radio: We are continuing
to receive some frantic reports
of massive power faiIures
around the world.
GIobaI communications
continue to be affected,
as most sateIIites
seem to be off-Iine.
All air transportation
is being grounded untiI further notice.
We'II continue to bring you
details as they develop.
Oh man.
l've normalized our oxygen levels,
but most of our systems are damaged.
Communication is down,
as is navigation.
Right.
What the heII hit us?
It seemed Iike a soIar fIare,
but it was massive.
AII of the energy readings
are wrong.
WeII, we'II have to worry
about that Iater.
Right now we've got
bigger probIems.
I've managed
to stabiIize us.
Do what you can with communication.
I'II work on navigation.
Okay.
We need to figure out
where the heII we are.
- ( beeps )
- ( cIears throat )
( footsteps )
- Hey.
Check it out.
A IittIe Sumatra bIend.
You want some?
I need you to take a Iook
at this, okay?
It's about Victoria.
Something happened up there
and l need to know how
it's gonna affect the NautiIus.
WeII, it was a massive soIar fIare
that hit us this morning.
Biggest one on record,
but the NautiIus shouId be prepared
- for that kind of event.
- It's not a soIar fIare.
Okay, Iook.
Its magnetic signature,
it's off the charts.
Oh, my God.
( sizzIing )
Are you okay?
Yeah, just a headache.
Any Iuck on the comm?
WeII, we'II onIy be abIe
to transmit
and receive
on a very narrow band.
But they'II be abIe
to hear us?
If they're Iistening.
Woman on radio:
Power bIackouts.
Communication faiIures.
AirpIanes grounded.
The government wants you
to think it's a solar flare,
but we are here
to give you the truth.
Brooke Adamson's
"Conspiracy Report" is back on the air.
Nice.
- ( static hissing )
- What's wrong?
- ( grumbles )
- ( eIectricity buzzing )
No, it's just, uh,
getting some interference.
- It's not us.
- It's the Feds.
- It's not the Feds.
Victoria over radio: This is
Victoria Preston of the USS NautiIus
making an emergency
distress call.
Can anybody read?
No way.
- What?
- ( static hissing )
This is Victoria Preston
on the USS NautiIus. Come in.
Isn't the NautiIus the spacecraft
that's on the Mercury mission?
- Yeah, yeah.
- WeII, it's gotta be a joke.
WeII, we'II find out.
First we'II Iock on her signaI.
Here.
Um...
copy that, NautiIus.
You're breaking up.
- Do you read?
- Copy that.
This is Victoria Preston on
the NautiIus. We are in distress.
Before we proceed,
please encrypt
this transmission using
security protocoI 27-46-32.
- What are you doing?
- If it's a hoax, they'II pIay aIong.
- How can you be so sure?
- Because that's what I wouId do.
Victoria: There's no such protocoI.
Who exactIy am I speaking with?
Give me that.
This is Christopher Weaver
and Brooke Adamson.
We're seniors
at North Bay University.
You've managed to connect
with our pirate radio station.
Victoria, do you copy that?
Come in.
- What happened?
- We gotta get that signaI back.
Let's go to the car.
We'II try new batteries.
Before my teIescope went off-Iine,
l was able to pull these images.
Look at these sun-spots.
They're starting to disappear here,
and here, here, and here.
- What does that mean?
- Magnetism.
It aII makes sense now.
For one brief miIIisecond,
our humbIe IittIe sun
became a magnetar,
the most powerful source
of magnetic energy in the universe.
A magnetar?
Yeah, it's extremeIy rare,
but it's the onIy thing
that could explain it.
The sun-spots, the bIackouts,
the magnetic wave, everything.
- ( Ioud thud )
- What was that?
Whoa.
This shouId not be happening.
There's no way our database
could have missed
this many meteors
approaching Earth.
Buddy,
either you're wrong
- or that's not a meteor.
- ( Ioud boom )
That impact site can't be
more than a miIe or two, tops.
Let's take my car. I don't want
to have to ride on your handIebars.
Very funny.
- Get in the car.
- I enjoy riding my bike to work.
- It's something that I Iike to do.
- Get in the car.
Uh, this is not good.
Do you know
where we are yet?
No.
But we're acceIerating
without engine power.
Well, you check autopilot and see
if there's been any faIse commands
and I'II see what I can do.
Yes, ma'am.
Wow.
Something's definiteIy wrong.
( expIosions )
- There's stiII no signaI.
- I don't know.
Do you think that
was reaIIy the NautiIus?
Yeah, I do.
I do.
- ( gasps )
- Whoa!
- What the heII was that?
- l don't know,
but there's more coming.
Get in the car.
Get in the car!
- ( expIosions continue )
- James?
Run. Run!
Get down!
Oh, boy.
Is it over?
I think so.
What the heII happened?
( sizzIing )
Matthew: Whoa.
Computer:
Navigation systems initiaIizing.
- ( beeps )
- FIight path compromised.
MarshaII, I've checked everything.
l can't find anything wrong.
Get up here.
I need your heIp with navigation.
We need to figure out
where we're headed now.
- And we are back up.
- Computer: PIotting NautiIus Iocation.
- MarshaII: Wait, this can't be right.
- What is it?
We're not where we shouId be.
Neither is Mercury.
How is that possibIe?
Marshall:
I don't know. It's out of orbit.
No. We're acceIerating
towards the pIanet.
Mercury is dragging us in?
But we're not cIose enough
to be in its gravity.
Whatever it is,
I don't want to be any cIoser.
Computer:
Reverse thrusters engaged.
Victoria, we need
to get a hoId of Mission Ops.
Right.
Okay.
Maybe.
- ( static hissing )
- Ground, do you copy?
Can you hear me?
Ground, this is Victoria.
Do you copy?
Thrusters are at 70%.
I don't Iike this.
- ( static hissing )
- Ground, this is Victoria. Do you copy?
- Yeah, Victoria. We're here.
- Oh, thank God.
I need you to get in touch
with Mission ControI. It's urgent.
WeII, if you're trying to warn us
about meteors,
- you're a IittIe Iate for that.
- Christopher, the NautiIus
has been knocked off course.
I need Mission Ops to guide us.
MarshaII: Come on.
( grunts )
Mission Ops is in Houston.
We're in Oregon and the phones are down.
Oregon, okay.
I need you to get to a faciIity
south of SeattIe caIIed SPEAR.
SPEAR. l know that.
My cousin Iives nearby.
Okay, great. When you get there,
ask for a person named Jennifer KeIIy.
TeII her what I've toId you,
that we need Mission Ops
to guide NautiIus, and give her
this frequency to get in touch.
And, please,
our Iives depend on it.
We're on it.
Let's go.
It has an extremeIy high
iron content.
Way too high for
an ordinary piece of meteorite.
This might sound crazy,
but I think this is a piece of Mercury.
It's a magnetized piece
of Mercury.
lf it was hit
by the magnetar wave,
that wouId expIain
why it's magnetic.
Even so,
how are pieces of it
down here?
I don't know.
- ( beeping )
- Thrusters are at maximum.
- We're stiII being puIIed in.
- I can do a manuaI override
in the engine room
to boost the thrusters,
but it's a temporary fix at best.
- Do it!
- Got it!
This is weird.
You want to read me
those coordinates again?
Yeah. Uh...
- right ascension...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...13 hours...
- ...17 minutes.
- Mm-hmm.
- DecIination...
- Yeah.
..negative-7 degrees...
- ...2 arcminutes.
It's not there.
What are you taIking about?
- It's not there.
- Where is it?
l don't know.
It's just-- it's gone.
- Do you mind?
- lt's just gone.
Okay.
They were right there.
Mercury was right--
they were right there.
All right, that--
that's impossibIe.
A pIanet doesn't just move.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna get some answers.
MarshaII, I got you another 20% ,
but that's the best I couId do.
Let's hope it's enough.
There's not enough power
in the reverse thrusters.
l need to flip us around
and engage the main engine.
That's too risky.
We can't use the reverse thrusters
and turn the ship at the same time.
We'd be puIIed in immediateIy.
- Not if we do it fast enough.
- We?
It's a two-man job, Victoria.
But I'm not a piIot.
WeIcome to your promotion.
Victoria, reduce power by 20%
when I boost the main engines.
Copy that.
Now!
Reducing power.
We're being
puIIed in sideways.
Marshall?
MarshaII?!
( growIs )
Maneuver successfuIIy executed.
Okay, I need you
to take over for a whiIe.
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
I think I might have got hit hard--
MarshaII!
Yes?
We need to see
Jennifer KeIIy right away.
- And you are?
- We have an urgent message
from Victoria Preston
and the NautiIus spacecraft.
- Is that right?
- Yeah, that's right.
- So if you couId just pIease--
- Excuse me, sir,
the NautiIus is having
severe mechanicaI maIfunctions
and they can't
get a hoId of Mission Ops,
but they can
get a hoId of my radio.
- We were sent here to see Jennifer--
- This is a secure facility.
No one gets in without
an appointment or a pass.
- Yeah, I understand that, but--
- That was me teIIing you niceIy.
Don't make me teII you again.
Let's go.
- Great.
- Guard: Let's go.
( ship creaking )
James, I know what must be
going through your head right now.
Then you'II stop
the small talk.
It's just we don't know
anything for sure yet.
There's a very good chance
that she's alive.
Mercury didn't disappear.
It was knocked out of orbit.
- I tracked its gravity--
- And my wife...
probabIy shouId be waIking
on Mercury right now.
Now pieces of it
are Ianding on the Earth.
You understand?
They didn't beIieve us.
- The guard wouIdn't even caII Jennifer.
- Fascist.
What shouId we do now?
Find my husband,
Dr. James Preston.
He'II be at our home
in Pacific Grove.
433 Ocean Beach Drive.
Come on, James.
Look, I don't care if your faciIity's
on lockdown, okay?
Try her number again
'cause I need to taIk to her.
- Sir, you need to caIm down.
- Oh, I need to caIm down?
I used to work here, okay?
l can't call her
because my phone doesn't work.
lt's urgent.
Stand down.
James, you need to leave.
You know you can't be here.
l can't share
cIassified information with you.
What about Mercury?
ls that classified?
- Look, we know aII about Mercury.
- Do you?
Do you aIso know
it's magnetized?
He's with me.
You, stay there.
( woman speaking over P.A. )
- What the heII is he doing here?
- Show him.
Nice trick.
So what?
This thing,
this was attached to Mercury.
You have to recaIcuIate
the planet's trajectory
based on magnetism.
What exactly
are you trying to teII me?
Massive magnetar wave
hit Mercury.
lt is now
extremeIy magnetized.
If it's anywhere near Earth,
it'II Iock on to our magnetic fieId--
it'II come straight for us.
WeII, we've tracked its trajectory,
and whiIe it is headed our way,
we're comfortabIy certain
that it will miss us.
You're not factoring in
the magnetism.
You have to recaIcuIate.
Based on our new data,
the caIcuIations show
the trajectory has changed.
Oh, my God.
Mercury's on
a coIIision course with Earth.
Look at the distance
it's covered.
- lt's moving faster.
- It's Iocked on to us.
Earth's magnetic fieId
is drawing it in.
It's Iike two magnets
puIIing it together.
This is beyond
an extinction IeveI event.
- This is the end of the worId.
- How Iong have we got?
Just over 18 hours.
Okay, people, this is why
we have a contingency pIan.
Initiate Operation Recourse.
I wanna be onIine in 30 minutes.
Jennifer: Yes, sir.
Edward...
Operation Recourse won't work.
Your missiIes aren't strong enough
to stop a planet.
We are not trying
to stop Mercury.
We're gonna defIect it.
The missiIes wiII cause
coordinated standoff expIosions
in front of the pIanet
and drive it off course.
l already know
what your pIan is.
You're assuming
that your guidance system
will withstand
a magnetic interference
and synchronize the bIast.
They can go off course.
They couId expIode
before they get there.
Worse, they get sucked back
into the planet,
they bIow it to fragments,
they wipe us out anyway!
Our missiles
are properIy shieIded.
Not against this.
Going ahead with this Iaunch,
you're choosing suicide
over a firing squad.
Your sarcasm
is reaIIy better suited
to your community
college lectures.
You don't have a say
in what we do here.
We Iaunch as soon as Mercury
is within our firing range.
( technicians murmuring )
James:
Edward, Edward, Iisten.
What about Project 7?
This is exactIy
what it was designed for.
The defIector never worked
in fieId testing, not once.
Without that,
it's just a big rock with engines.
We've been modifying the software,
we've been working out the bugs.
You pulled it so you
can give your contracts
to your rocket
manufacturing buddies.
WeII, if that's the way you want to see
your faiIure, that's your business,
but, regardIess,
we don't have time to dust it off now.
I can get
the defIector fieId to work.
l've been uploading
the software since I Ieft.
l'm sorry.
You've been doing what?
- Hacking into a government weapon?
- That's my weapon.
lt hasn't been your weapon
since I fired you three years ago.
I couId have you thrown
in prison for this.
It'II work.
Just gotta Iet me
upIoad the fixes.
We don't have the time
or resources
to Iaunch two programs.
We're onIy gonna get
one shot at this...
and I am not gonna risk
the fate of humanity
on your unproven technoIogy.
I think you know
the way out.
Okay.
- Chris: Wait.
- ( tires screech )
- Which way?
- I don't know.
Is this North Coast Road?
l don't know.
There's no road signs.
Let's try this way.
And you're sure P-7 is the key
to stopping Mercury?
- Stake my life on it.
- Sounds Iike you'II be staking
- everyone's life on it, James.
- My software updates wiII work.
We just need to upIoad them
to get P-7 fully online.
- That sounds easy enough.
- We just need to go to my office,
get the software, then we need
a secure SPEAR computer.
Did you say we?
HeIIo?
Mr. Preston?
- ( tires screeching )
- ( rumbling )
Whoa.
- Hey, hey, keep the car straight.
- lt's not me.
It's the ground that's moving.
Whoa.
Oh, my God.
( car horns honking )
( car aIarms bIaring )
- It's metaI.
- What?
lt's not trees,
it's not teIephone poIes.
Whatever that is,
it onIy affected metaI.
This must aII be
connected to Mercury.
It has to be.
Jennifer: That's not good.
That's not good at all.
We've just received report--
SeattIe's been devastated
by a massive magnetic event.
- How far are we from Iaunching?
- We've had to recalculate.
Mercury's speeding up and we're having
a hard time keeping a lock on it.
We have a very smaII window
to launch these missiles
and we're running
out of time.
What happened
to your security pass?
- Find Preston.
- Yes, sir.
- Just follow me.
- ( distant dog barking )
Oh, wait.
I read on the Internet somewhere
that you can open up any door
with a credit card.
I think, eh,
yeah, you just--
I don't know.
PeopIe never Ieave
these things Iocked.
Right.
Mr. Preston?
Is anyone home?
HeIIo?
Hey, come here.
God, the phones
stiII aren't working.
There's nothing here.
Nothing usefuI anyways.
( Iights buzzing )
( computer, modem
beeping and buzzing )
- What is that?
- I don't know.
Looks Iike some kind of weapon.
Whose car is that?
What kind of guy keeps pIans
for a top secret weapon on his computer?
Brooke: If he were here right now,
I'd give him a piece of my mind.
What the hell
are you doing in my house?
- Look, your wife sent us.
- What are you taIking about?
We taIked to her.
She's in trouble.
- Brooke: We can prove it.
- Yeah.
What?
WeII, it's just over there.
PIease?
So l used
some of today's engineering
with yesterday's
anaIog technoIogy
with a few experimentaI bits
here and there and voiIà.
lt broadcasts and receives
farther than you can imagine.
WeII, it's a work of art.
lt's how we heard
Victoria's mayday.
- You wanna turn it on?
- Yeah, sorry.
( static hissing )
Okay.
Yeah, cooI.
Vic, you there?
Victoria?
Victoria:
Ground, can you pIease repeat?
Vic, it's me.
Um...
- you safe?
- I'm aIive,
but I'm the onIy one Ieft.
James: What happened?
Are you okay?
Something crazy has happened
and l can't really explain it,
but I'm being puIIed
into Mercury.
Oh, my God,
the magnetism.
Vic, there's been
a huge magnetic event.
Yes, l know.
We were right in the middIe of it.
Mercury's been magnetized
and is being pushed out of its orbit.
Magnetism.
Why didn't I think of this?
Okay,
if I can recaIcuIate,
if l can account
for the difference in force,
I might be abIe to break free
and come home.
Vic, there might not be a home
to come back to.
Mercury's on
a coIIision course with Earth.
Can you keep me posted on this
and just double-check these?
Woman:
I just Iost everything.
What is going on?
This faciIity shouId be impervious
to power surges.
Mercury's interference
is increasing.
It's becoming more
than our shieIding can handIe.
Get the emergency generators
back online.
The moment they stabilize,
I want those missiIes in the air!
Edward,
what if James is right?
Move aside.
Project 7 is the only thing
that can save us from Mercury.
You need to get the heII
out of there before we Iaunch.
Victoria:
Okay, I've done everything I can
to recaIcuIate
for the change in force.
I've tried to boost the engines
as much as possible,
but it's just not enough thrust.
Wait a minute.
What if I Iet it puII me in?
- What do you mean?
- A sIingshot maneuver.
Yes, yes, yes.
She Iets the pIanet puII her in,
acceIerating around Mercury.
That wiII give her the extra momentum
she needs to break free.
That's a suicide mission.
- Magnetism is too unpredictable.
- Victoria: I've been trained for this.
Honey, honey.
You're not a piIot.
You've never done this before.
I have to try.
If I stay here, I'm dead.
It's my onIy chance.
No, no, no, no.
Vic?
Vic?!
- James, can you hear me?
- ( static hissing )
Sorry, it's fragiIe.
lt wasn't built
to be dragged around Iike this.
- Can you hear me?
- ( static hissing )
- Disengage autopilot.
- Computer: AutopiIot disengaged.
Here goes nothing.
- She'II make it, she'II make it.
- ( modem screeching )
She's gonna make it.
She's gonna be aII right.
What is that?
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
- What's wrong?
Project 7's guidance systems
are damaged.
- Can't you fix it?
- It's not a software probIem,
it's hardware.
You can't fix it from the ground.
- So that's it?
- Um, the NautiIus.
The NautiIus has
an amazing guidance system.
If Victoria can piIot the ship
to Project 7,
tether onto its system,
we can then use it to manuaIIy guide
the asteroid straight into Mercury.
We stiII have to do
the software updates.
Without the energy fieId,
you won't have enough force
to knock Mercury off course.
- So send them.
- I can't do it from here.
Can monitor the systems,
but to change anything,
I need a computer
that has top-level
cIassified access.
- And you need to fix that radio.
- ( electricity buzzing )
That's another power surge.
- ( buzzes )
- Come on.
Come on,
come on, come on.
Here we go,
here we go.
- ( beeps )
- l got it.
Whoa.
Yes, Mr. President. Believe me,
we're doing everything we can.
No, sir. These are
Iimited range missiIes.
The timing is cruciaI.
If we Iaunch too earIy
the missiIes wiII faII short,
too late, and Mercury won't be
knocked off course enough to miss Earth.
( feedback )
- Mr. President, are you there?
- ( dial tone )
Mr. President?
- I'm gonna need a new reIay.
- There's an oId airstrip.
One of the radio planes
might have what you need.
Right, I saw it on the way in.
Here, once we get the radio up
and running, we'II caII you on it.
Okay. Is this even gonna work
with all the interference?
Trust me, we reached Mercury
with this thing. lt'll work.
You gonna tell me
where we're going?
The faIIback faciIity.
- Which is what exactIy?
- Designed when I was working at SPEAR.
They shouId have access
to every weapon,
- incIuding Project 7.
- ShouId have access?
The coordinates
are in records storage.
- We don't even know where it is?
- That's why we're hurrying.
HeIIo?
Anybody here?
If we're gonna find
that reIay switch,
- we better start looking for it.
- I don't know. This pIace is creepy.
- l don't like it.
- It's a creepy oId airstrip.
What did you expect?
- Here, this Iooks Iike the hangar.
- Okay.
HeIIo?
- I think this is the hangar.
- Okay.
- Let's check the yard here.
- Anything?
- No.
- Here.
- What exactIy are we Iooking for?
We're Iooking for a radio
that's stiII intact.
Okay.
No, these are aII sheIIs.
- We need to get to that hangar.
- Okay.
Hey.
( rumbIing )
- Quick.
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
- Is it more meteors?
l don't think so.
It feeIs more Iike an earthquake.
- Earthquake?
- Worse, we're being hit by
massive waves
of eIectromagnetic energy.
We still can't risk
Iaunching too earIy.
If this EM interference
increases,
you won't be abIe
to Iaunch the missiIes.
You can't fire
when the interference is spiking.
Okay, then caIcuIate intervaIs
in between the wavelengths
- and we'II fire in between.
- Yes, sir.
- Is it over?
- I think so.
Okay, maybe this plane
wiII have what we need.
Let's find out.
Computer:
Trajectory caIcuIations compIete.
- ( beeping )
- Warning,
possible
coIIision course detected.
Recommend
repIotting trajectory.
Project 7.
Stupid.
What were
Projects 1 through 6?
I don't even want to know.
- Any luck?
- I think I got it.
- ( static hissing )
- Yes.
We're in business.
Okay, Iet's get out of here.
Okay.
Stop where you are
or I'II drop you where you stand.
What the heII are you doing
with my pIane?
- Sir--
- Shut up!
Here's what's gonna happen.
You're gonna drop that,
you're just gonna--
you're gonna slowly
put that down on the ground.
- Yeah.
- And you're gonna put
- your hands in the air.
- Right, okay.
Sir, we needed one part.
We've been communicating
with the spacecraft NautiIus.
Sure, you have.
Hands in the air now!
Brooke: You don't understand.
This is a matter of Iife and death.
- We can't leave without that radio.
- You're gonna Ieave without the radio
because it's my radio.
You know what I mean?
It's my radio.
Hurry!
Go, go!
Say your prayers,
you little bastard!
How are we
supposed to get inside?
There's no way
to sneak around that guard.
- How'd you get that?
- I borrowed it.
- Nice.
- Yeah.
- Morning.
- Hi there.
Hey,
stop right there.
Gonna need to see
that lD again, sir.
Yeah, here you go.
Here you go.
G-g-g-g-gun!
Get the gun!
- ( gunshots )
- Help, help!
( screams )
- ( gunshots )
- Whoa, whoa! Hey, hey, hey.
- Ow!
- Back it up. Over there, over there.
Sorry about that.
You okay?
- Yeah.
- Over there, over there, over there.
What do we do?
What do we do now?
- Give me the gun.
- Okay, huh?
Just give me the gun.
Hey, hey, hey!
Back up!
Okay, there's rope in the car.
Go get the rope.
- Keys.
- The car is open!
- Whoa! Get down!
- ( screams )
Get down,
get down!
Wait, can you just--
Come on,
let's go!
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Okay, he's reloading.
Come on, come on, Iet's go.
Go, go, go!
( metaI creaking )
What?
Brooke:
Oh, God.
We need to get out of here now.
- Brooke, come on!
- l'm coming!
( Iow rumbIing )
Let's go, go, go!
Brooke:
I'm hurrying!
( tires screeching )
Matthew: Whoa.
So, uh, where do we start?
Hang on, these-- aren't fiIe cabinets
supposed to have Ietters on them?
Secret codes, secret fiIes,
they get bar codes.
So how are we supposed to
find the one we're Iooking for?
You take that side,
I'II take this side.
- Okay, aII right.
- Just Iook for things
that have structures, buiIdings,
things grouped together.
- Stuff Iike that.
- Okay.
- Matthew?
- Yes.
- You don't have to be neat.
- Oh, yeah, yeah, well.
Fast.
Just want to keep
some sembIance of organization.
This took somebody
a Iong time.
Computer: Warning, pIanetary gravity
affecting course trajectory.
That's the pIan, girI.
Computer:
Initiating emergency autopiIot
faiIsafe in five, four--
Override accepted.
Impact risk imminent.
I think I got it.
Down on the ground now!
Where's your buddy?
Oh, about time.
Where's the fiIe?
Next time,
I'II tie him up.
I'm sorry, they don't teach you how
to tie peopIe up in astronomy schooI.
I stiII saved your butt.
- Brooke?
- Brooke: Go ahead, James.
I have the Iocation.
Where shouId we meet you?
Take Highway 37.
We'II meet you
at the junction at Highway 12.
- Brooke: Okay.
- Oh, and I picked this up for Iater.
Figured we might need it.
- You want a hug?
- Yeah, yeah, I wouId.
l need those wave calculations.
We're approaching the Iaunch window.
We're working on it.
We just got systems back up.
- We're running out of time.
- l know the time table!
Sir.
Look, Jen,
get a team ready
and take them
over to the faIIback faciIity.
We gotta cover our bases.
If the systems go down here,
l'm not gonna
be abIe to Iaunch.
I need you over there
to Iaunch from there.
I'II get you the Iaunch codes.
Michelle, please stay
on those waveIengths.
MicheIIe: Yes, sir.
Matthew: Whoa, stop. Stop the car.
He looks like he's alive.
- James: We don't have time for this.
- We can't just Ieave him here.
- Matthew, get back in the car.
- We can't leave him here.
- Matthew, get back in the car!
- ( man groaning )
It'II be fine.
- Oh, come on.
- Hey, buddy. You okay?
We gotta get you--
we gotta get you--
- Get up, nice and sIow.
- Hey.
- Easy.
- Step away from the car!
- Take it easy, man.
Just take it easy.
Don't do it, James!
Shut up!
You think I'm kidding around?
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- Huh?!
- Easy, easy.
- Get the heII away from the car!
- Buddy, I can't give you the keys.
- Shut up!
- I can't give you the keys!
- Don't be stupid, man!
- I'II cut his throat!
- I can't give you the car.
Oh, you're gonna
give me the car.
- Hey!
- What's this, huh?
What are you doing?
What's this, huh?
- Okay, okay, okay!
- The keys!
- I'm gonna give you the keys.
- Yeah, you wiII.
- I'II give you the keys.
- Give me the keys.
That's good.
- Don't move.
- Dude.
We need to caII the kids.
The radio's in the car.
It's happening again.
( grunts )
Hang in there, girI.
Computer: Warning,
impact risk ahead.
MuItipIe objects
approaching.
- We're aImost there, girI!
- ( alarm blaring )
HoId on!
Computer: Warning,
heat shieId breached.
Maximum pressure
capacity exceeded.
- ( yells )
- Computer: AII systems criticaI.
Abort maneuver.
Repeat, abort maneuver.
Where's Matthew?
- You get the part?
- Yeah, but we haven't heard anything
from Victoria yet.
Let's hope she's in the middIe
of the maneuver.
We gotta get out of here.
Go!
HoId it together
a little longer!
Computer:
Trajectory compromised.
- Change course immediateIy.
- ( yelling )
l have all
the wave patterns mapped
and the systems are aII up,
and there's stiII a Iot of interference.
Okay, get ready, everyone.
We Iaunch the second
we have a cIear shot.
Computer:
Course trajectory compIete.
CaIcuIating NautiIus Iocation.
( rumbIing )
We'II never get through here.
We gotta back up.
We gotta find another way.
- All right.
- ( engine chokes )
- Damn it.
- You're kidding me.
Okay, we are go for Iaunch.
( buzzing )
- Three, two...
- ( beep )
MissiIes are away.
AIternator's shot.
What are we gonna do?
How are we supposed to
get around this thing?
Guess we have to waIk.
- What are you doing?
- What?
I've aIready been shot at
once today.
( rumbIing )
This thing goes on
for miIes.
Yeah, James.
At this rate, I don't think
we're gonna make it on time.
Magnetism is increasing.
Mercury is forcing
the missiIes off course.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
lt's leaking gas.
- You gotta go across to the other side.
- Okay.
( yeIIs )
No.
James?
James, can you hear me?
- James.
- Victoria: James?
( static hissing )
- Okay, go.
- Hey, Vic.
- It's me.
- Thank God.
- Are you safe?
- I am,
and l'm heading away
from Mercury as fast as I can.
Have you Iaunched P-7 yet?
We can't.
Guidance system's
been damaged.
Hey, honey?
I, uh--
I need you
to do something.
I don't want to ask you
to do this,
but I need you to take
the NautiIus to Project 7
and you have to guide it
to Mercury.
I guess I won't be going home
as fast as l thought.
It's the onIy chance
we have, honey.
I'II do it.
Now Iisten to me.
You have to tether in
the NautiIus guidance system to P-7's.
I understand, James.
Now we stiII have to
do the fixes to P-7.
We have to do that
at the faciIity.
There's really
not that much time.
I'II get there in time.
- I swear to you.
- l trust you.
Go, be safe.
Plot in coordinates
to asteroid 8-7-6-9-5-Z.
- Computer: PIotting coordinates.
- ( air hissing )
- Warning, Iife-support systems faiIure.
- ( aIarm bIaring )
Oxygen IeveIs criticaI.
Estimated Iife support,
15 minutes.
- Brooke: There's a car coming.
- ( sirens bIaring )
Hey!
Hey, hey!
Great.
- Hey, Iook.
- Hey, hey.
Hey, stop!
Stop!
- Get out of the road.
- We need a ride.
Look, l'm not
gonna teII you again.
Listen, I need a ride
to fallback facility.
Edward Rex,
he gave me his ID as proof.
Just take a Iook--
just take a Iook at it.
This ID was stoIen this morning.
Get on the ground, Dr. Preston.
- Hey.
- ( grunts )
Back off!
You heard me.
Thank you.
On the ground.
Computer:
Estimated Iife support, 10 minutes.
( air hissing )
Computer: Estimated Iife support,
five minutes.
- James: We gotta go!
- Yup.
Sorry.
Computer: Estimated Iife support,
three minutes.
No pressure,
thank you.
Here we go.
Come on, NataIie.
- ( beeps )
- ( sighs )
Computer:
Life-support systems back onIine.
( sighs )
We Iost contact
with the contingency team.
It couId just be
communications.
- ( beep )
- Man: Magnetism is spiking.
Reports of magnetic storms
are coming in from all over.
- ( car alarm blaring )
- ( metaI screeching )
- ( cIamoring )
- ( rumbIing )
Oh, my God.
Look.
Not again.
Christopher: Look out!
Oh, my God.
Hang on!
Computer:
Approaching destination.
Nautilus, prepare
for docking at Project 7.
( banging )
- Everybody all right?
- Better than the car, I guess.
Brooke?
Brooke?!
James?
James,
she's not breathing, man.
I'm sorry.
- What?
- I'm sorry.
( murmurs )
Brooke?
Brooke, I'm so sorry.
Christopher, we gotta go.
No.
- Christopher.
- Just wait!
Brooke.
I'm sorry.
Wow.
SPEAR car.
It's Jennifer.
We're close.
We gotta get out of here.
Executing Ianding procedure.
Prepare to tether
NautiIus' navigation system
to Project 7 navigation system.
Computer: Enabling
navigation system tether.
Engaging docking coIIar.
Computer:
Docking coIIar engaged.
- Execute system tether.
- Stand by.
System tether executed.
James, can you hear me?
I don't see a faciIity. Are you sure
we got the right coordinates?
Yeah, we're here.
The dam is camoufIage.
It's aIso the power source
for the faciIity.
Wow.
- Victoria: James, can you hear me?
- Okay.
- ( static hissing )
- Here.
- Vic, are you aII right?
- Yes,
and I'm tethered
to Project 7's systems.
As soon as I get the updates,
l'm ready to launch.
You have to check
the targeting systems.
It'II automaticaIIy be scanning
an impact threat the size of Mercury.
Oh, no.
- What's the Iaunch window?
- If I don't get Project 7 moving,
l'll never close
the gap to Mercury.
Without the updates,
the shieId won't work.
- Then you better hurry.
- We gotta go.
Engaging main engines.
James:
Come on!
( rumbIing, expIosions )
Faster!
We gotta move!
We're aImost there.
Computer:
System error.
Energy fieId inactive.
- ( expIosion )
- Christopher: Whoa, whoa!
James:
Easy, easy.
- ( expIosion )
- Whoa!
- Where's the control room?
- It's directIy underneath the dam.
It's the onIy pIace
safe enough.
Increase engines
to maximum.
What are we Iooking for?
There it is!
- ( beep )
- Computer: System error.
- Energy fieId inactive.
- TeII me something I don't know.
This is it.
( expIosion )
( beeps )
Go.
Come on, James.
What can l do?
What do you need?
l'm gonna get
the system up and running.
- Get Victoria on the radio now.
- Right.
Victoria, do you copy?
Computer: Abort maneuver.
Repeat, abort maneuver.
- Victoria: Go ahead.
- Here, l got her.
Good boy.
Vic, it's updating right now.
James, it's too Iate.
Hey, don't give up on me!
Hang in there, okay?
We need to go!
- James, Iisten.
- We need to get out of here!
Go, go!
Victoria:
Listen to me.
I Iove you.
I Iove you, too.
Computer:
Software updates received.
Energy fieId initiating.
When the shieId activates,
get the hell out of there!
- You hear me?!
- We need to go now!
Let's go!
Computer:
Energy fieId activated.
Impact in 30 seconds.
Disengage docking coIIar.
Computer: Warning,
docking coIIar maIfunction.
( eIectricity buzzing )
This way, come on!
Hey, you okay?
Come on, get up.
We gotta go.
Get up.
Get up, now.
Computer: Warning,
docking coIIar maIfunction.
Time to go home.
Oh, my God.
Yeah!
James, you were right.
About everything.
Victoria knew
what she was doing.
lf it wasn't for her,
we wouIdn't be here, right?
None of us wouId.
Try her.
- What?
- Try her.
- Yeah.
Here.
- ( static hissing )
- Okay.
Vic, you there?
Vic, it's James.
Vic, you copy?
Victoria:
James, do you read?
- You made it.
- ( laughs )
Looks Iike the worId did, too.
Why don't you come on down
and enjoy the view?
Victoria:
I'm aIready on my way.
And for the record,
the view up here
isn't so bad either.
( music pIaying )