\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\NAlert Level 1:
In case of chemical, geological, meteorological or
other than a physical sign of G's action is confirmed.
\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\NAlert Level 2:
Issued when any physical sign of G's action,
such as voice and motion, is confirmed.
\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\NAlert Level 3:
Issued when G has appeared.
\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\N\NAlert Level 4:
Issued when G would certainly
land on a specific site in Japan.
National Land Agency:
Special Disaster Research Committee
"GODZILLA VS. BIOLLANTE"
I've found something!
Who's there? This area is off-limits!!
REPUBLIC OF SARADIA
Where are you going at
this time of night?
I have to go to the lab.
I just received a call saying that
the Godzilla cells have arrived.
They must be quick-frozen.
I'll be back for dinner.
You didn't have to come with me, Erika.
Dad, it's okay. You know you
can't do anything without me.
SARADIA INSTITUTE OF BIOTECHNOLOGY
See you later, Dad.
I'll meet you in the lab.
Erika!
Miki Saegusa, age 17...
She is the best psychic we have at the
Mental Science Exploration Center.
It has been shown
through numerous tests...
...that plants have their own
fields of mental energy.
It comes as no surprise, that we've finally
found someone who can communicate with them.
FIVE YEARS LATER
Tell me doctor,
why do you suddenly wish to
hear the voice of a rose?
I guess it's a sign of old age.
I've lived here alone for
over five years now.
I guess solitude has given
me some strange ideas.
Has it really been five years?
Erika said that one day,
the desert would come to life,
carpeted with all kinds of wild flowers.
How is your father, Asuku?
He's fine.
His latest project is to start a bio-bank.
He's trying to get the Foundation to fund it.
Yes, I've heard of your father's project
and how he wants to preserve the
sperm of Nobel Prize winners
for the production of future geniuses.
There's been a lot of opposition to
his project, but it's still going ahead.
It won't be easy to get
his work accepted.
You see, those same kinds of attitudes
forced me to leave the country.
Some things haven't
changed in five years.
How did you do?
It wasn't any good. I got nothing.
We'll see you later.
Thanks for stopping by.
Did you hear something just now?
A girl was calling you, Asuka.
It was your name, I'm sure of it.
Goodbye...
Have you ever heard of a chimera?
Chimera?
It's a legendary monster
that breathes fire.
It's supposed to appear
from the ocean's depths,
causing storms and
destroying human beings.
It has a lion's head, a goat's
body and a dragon's tail.
But wasn't it a mythical creature?
If genetic engineers
keep playing with cells,
they may create their
very own chimera.
A new like form, totally
alien, and completely
different from what God
intended for earth.
Frightening, huh?
I understand how you
feel about my father's
work and many people are
against it as well.
But I can't help it if my father is the
head of the Ecology Foundation.
I don't see how our relationship
has anything to do with it.
You're right, but I'm still
uneasy about my work.
After all, the Foundation
supports the labs.
Yes, but that doesn't
affect our being together.
You act like Romeo,
from Shakespeare's play.
Well, you won't catch me
portraying your Juliet...
Massachusetts sent me an answer.
They want me to study there.
Asuka, will you come with me?
I don't know what to say...
I can't give you an answer now.
Last night, a series of violent tremors has shaken
the area around Mt. Mihara, on Oshima Island.
Early this morning, smoke has
been seen rising from the crater.
The Central Seismic Bureau is
monitoring the situation...
But at this stage, they are
unsure if a full eruption is likely.
I first heard it from two
children a few days ago.
Now, they all say they had the
same dream last night.
Did you?
It started a week ago,
and every night since then,
it has become more clear.
Well, have you finished?
Yes!
Well then, show us what
you've dreamed about!
Yes!
NATIONAL LAND BUREAU
SPECIAL DISASTER RESEARCH COUNCIL
GODZILLA UNIT
This is Gondo...
It's you, Colonel!
Yes, it's really exciting to wait
for a lizard that never shows up!
You must be joking, Colonel!
They must be trying to replace me!
The most exciting thing
that happens around here,
is betting on who kills
the most mosquitoes!
Sure! God only knows why I
accepted this assignment.
By the way... I called you because I
wanted to conduct some research,
and for that I'll need your cooperation.
I understand, tomorrow at 10:30.
Godzilla's awake!
Alert Level 1:
In case of chemical, geological, meteorological or
other than a physical sign of G's action is confirmed.
PRIME MINISTER'S OFFICE
I don't think the Prime
Minister believes her story.
No, of course not.
She's just a nobody.
If he started believing girls
talking about dreams and ESP...
...he wouldn't be Prime
Minister for too long.
So Gondo, do you believe
what she's saying?
The truth is, I hope it shows up...
If it doesn't,
I'll be out of a job...
Top Secret: First Stage
of Emergency Against G
Robotic engineering...
Computers...
Super-conductivity...
Laser technology...
All of the latest gadgets
are at our disposal...
...including ESP.
The army is really up to date.
- Aren't they?
- You've forgotten one thing.
- What's that?
- You didn't mention our bio-weapons.
Anti-Nuclear Energy Bacteria?
TSUKUBA LABORATORY
OF BIOTECHNOLOGY
Already in the United States...
...they've created a bacteria
that can eat crude oil.
It's been successfully
tested on the oil spills.
Likewise... bacteria that
can eat nuclear material
has been developed by
our scientists here.
In case of a nuclear accident...
...the bacteria would clean
up any radioactive pollution.
It eats...nuclear material?
Of course, and that's why it would work against
Godzilla, who feeds upon nuclear energy.
Well, the situation isn't critical, yet.
True, an orange alert has been issued
and the bacteria must be readied...
But the bacteria wasn't meant
to be used as a weapon.
Not yet...
Well, the problem is that the bacteria can't
be produced in this laboratory on its own...
We need a Godzilla cell to create it.
A Godzilla cell?
Godzilla feeds on nuclear energy...
Somewhere in its cell structure, lies
a nuclear-digesting set of genes.
We need that set of genes
to make the bacteria.
So, you're saying that...
...something taken
from Godzilla's cells,
can be made into something
that can destroy it?
The Godzilla cells were
found five years ago.
They were collected by
an army special unit.
They're stored at the Okochi Foundation.
Will you need anything else, Doctor?
Just a few scientists...
I'm sorry to disappoint you, gentlemen,
but I vowed never to work
with Godzilla cells again.
I understand how you
must feel, Doctor...
...but it's vital for the defense
of our country against Godzilla.
My daughter was more important
to me than my country.
I lost her because of my
work with Godzilla cells.
Now, I have nothing left to live for.
Thank you, but I must refuse.
OKOCHI FOUNDATION
So, you're Dr. Kirishima?
My daughter has told me a lot about you.
I'm glad that we could finally meet.
My daughter also told me that you're
a little critical about our work here.
Extremely...
Well, at least you're honest.
However, I feel that you, like the other
scientists, don't know what I'm doing here.
I do realize the dangers involved,
after all, every coin has two sides...
In that case,
you must realize what kind of weapon
the Anti-Nuclear Bacteria would be.
Are you aware of it?
I know that it could neutralize
nuclear missiles.
Nuclear weapons would be
rendered useless overnight.
If we create that bacteria,
the balance of power...
Kirishima, reality is reality.
This Foundation now has the
technology to make that bacteria.
The superpowers of the world would do
anything to get hold of the Godzilla cells.
If any country succeeded, I'd have
to use force to recover the cells.
The same way the
AmErikan Bio-Major...
...attacked and destroyed
Shiragami's lab, 5 years ago.
The government decided
to store the Godzilla
cells here in this
vault as a precaution.
They would remain in here
and only be used...
...in case of a nuclear emergency
that would threaten the country.
And only under strict control!
But then, Godzilla came along...
...and the rest is history.
As for myself, I hate the idea
of the cells being locked up.
These are the Godzilla cells?
Japan was devastated by nuclear
bombs, and we now have Godzilla...
It's only fair that we use it as a weapon,
that will protect us from our enemies.
An earthquake?
A powerful eruption occurred at Mt. Mihara,
on Oshima Island, a short time ago...
It caused a series of tremors that
were felt throughout the Kanto region.
The eruptions are still occurring...
...throwing lava high into the night sky
and giving the scene an eerie glow...
I must do something, or Erika will die!
I see...
Dr. Shiragami, welcome to the team!
Thank you.
Shiragami has accepted the position?
Really? He's coming here tomorrow?
What?
Yes, on one condition.
He wants to keep the Godzilla
cells in his lab for seven days.
Of course, I told him it was okay.
So, what are you going to be doing?
Will you be creating the
bacteria with Dr. Shiragami?
Yes, to destroy Godzilla
when it returns.
It sounds as if you want
Godzilla to show up.
Maybe, but who knows if
Godzilla will ever appear again...
What if we create the bacteria,
and it's just a false alarm?
I'd be happy if I never
saw Godzilla again!
I'm not joking. We would have created
something as terrible as Godzilla.
I know that it's just a simple bacteria
we're creating via genetic engineering...
But, if the research continues
at its present course...
...genetic technology will produce
something far worse than Godzilla!
Kirishima...
If we don't produce this bacteria,
someone else is sure to do it!
Just look at what humans have done
in the past centuries and you'll see.
I know that! But our responsibility...
Kirishima, I don't believe you
understand science very well.
You can see there's not a lot of movement,
but something is happening down there!
Alert Level 2:
In case any physical sign of G's action,
such as voice and motion is confirmed.
The Super-X2 has been substantially
improved with the installation of...
...the latest on-board supercomputer, that
controls automatic and remote functions.
It's also submersible, capable of operating
at such extreme depths as 10,000 meters.
Its armor is also the latest, TA-32.
It's twice as durable as the
titanium-alloy on the Super-X.
Right. This way, please.
That is called the Fire-Mirror.
It was completely constructed
with synthetic diamonds.
If the mirror is hit with
Godzilla's radioactive breath...
...it will return its
attack a thousand-fold.
Pretty powerful!
Yes, it is.
It's already started.
I've always been fascinated
with cell division.
Two cells in 30 minutes,
doubling to 4 in an hour...
32 cells in two hours.
In one day, 4 million cells.
Terrifying, isn't it?
This is Kirishima...
What?! Dr. Shiragami's lab?!
The bodies belong to two
of Bio-Major's agents.
They broke in to steal the
Anti-Nuclear Energy Bacteria data.
God only knows how they died...
Is this why you've been keeping the
Godzilla cells in your lab all this week?
During the experiment, I thought I
created an immortal plant species.
I gave it self-reproducing
abilities using Godzilla cells.
You did what?!
I thought...
I think I may have made a mistake.
"And demand that you turn over all
Anti-Nuclear Energy Bacteria data..."
"...to us no later than 2:00,
on Tuesday the 31st..."
"...or we will cause an explosion..."
"on Mt. Mihara that will destroy
it completely and free Godzilla."
It was faxed to us.
We received it this morning.
The name of the
organization is "ALIEN"?
Unbelievable...It's Bio-Major!
They're the only ones who would know
about the Anti-Nuclear Energy Bacteria.
Yeah, it's a bluff.
The Prime Minister?
He's been too busy and more worried
about the opposition parties than Godzilla.
Well, they're not bluffing.
That was a call from Mt. Mihara.
There was an explosion,
but it was just a warning.
A warning?
Read the rest, you'll understand.
There's more to the message.
"We've already made preparations
to prove that we mean business..."
"We shall set off a warning explosion by remote
control at 2:00, 24 hours before the deadline."
They're holding the entire
country for ransom!
And Godzilla is their hostage...
Slow down... This looks like the place.
Deliver the bacteria to Bio-Major?
I understand...
If that's what the
government has decided...
Whatever you say, sir.
Doctor...
You see? Science is just
another host for politicians.
So you're going to leave it to them?
We can't just sit here and do nothing!
Dr. Shiragami!
Come to the lake!
I don't believe it!
What you see is no ordinary plant.
That is Biollante.
Biollante?
The spirit of a plant that
appears in Norse mythology.
But that plant, has a human spirit.
A human spirit?
Doctor, I believe Erika's
spirit is in there!
How do you know?
I can hear her calling me.
Asuka, I'll need your help.
You did it.
You spliced one of Godzilla's cells...
...with one of the plant's cells.
Are you proud of this?
What kind of science do you call it?!
What was he doing?
He was crazy to start playing
with the Godzilla cells.
I don't know what scientists
are trying to do nowadays.
It's way beyond me.
You have it?
You'd better get moving, 'ALIEN".
The switch is in the container.
So, it's a double-cross?!
You damned idiot!
We've got to throw the switch!
There's no time left!
Saradia?
We've got to get this open!
I know! The key!
- He got away with the bacteria!
- Forget it! The switch is broken!
Amen!
Alert Level 3:
In case G appears.
Godzilla is back again...
And we lose the
anti-nuclear energy bacteria.
I guess things are about
as bad as they can get.
Well, you miserable people of Tokyo...
I'm glad you tuned in,
because this show has...
We have a special report,
please stay tuned.
In the United States, new laws were...
Just a moment...
This just in...An explosion
has occurred on Mt. Mihara.
Godzilla has escaped
and is still at large.
So, Godzilla is back again?
Doctor, we must return to Tokyo!
Biollante is crying,
I can hear her.
The Coast Guard in the Tokyo Bay area...
...is warning the residents in Godzilla's
path and is evacuating the area.
We have just received these pictures.
Godzilla is slowly on the move.
It has left Oshima Island and is
heading in the direction of Tokyo.
OPERATIONS CENTER SELF-DEFENSE AGENCY
Ansyaki has just been destroyed!
Control on standby,
awaiting instructions. Over.
At this rate, Godzilla will reach
Tokyo in 24 hours.
Super-X2, proceed to runway. Confirmed.
Super-X2, proceed to runway.
Colonel Kuruki reporting for duty, sir!
Super-X2 was assigned to me in
our operation against Godzilla.
I see you're from a
new youth-elite corp.
Yes, sir!
All on-board systems showing
normal speed, Mach 1.
It will be arriving in ten minutes.
Switch to the X2 cameras.
Roger.
Activate the Fire-Mirrors.
Home in on the sensors.
Fire-Mirrors set, on.
Godzilla is turning west!
Colonel Kuruki, a phone call for you.
Seems Godzilla has given
up heading for Tokyo.
Yes, this is Kuruki. Oh, it's you Gondo.
Should we sound the all-clear
for the Tokyo Bay area, sir?
What?! They stole the
anti-nuclear bacteria?!
Close all the airports?
I understand. Alright.
I recommend waiting before
giving the all-clear.
Inform the press that we're still
fighting Godzilla in the Yuraga Channel.
Kuruki, are you suggesting
that we should lie?
This is an announcement for the
airport management office.
The airport is closing down
and shall be evacuated
due to the advance of
Godzilla off Tateyama.
All flights have been cancelled.
We apologize for any inconvenience caused.
Here is a late-news bulletin.
Godzilla has stalled its advance and is
stationary between Miura and Tateyama.
Haneda and the regional airports have been
closed to all traffic further notice.
Standby for the next update in one hour.
The agent's car has been spotted!
He's on the Tomei highway, heading west!
Tomei?
Where could he be going?
Saradian National Oil Corporation.
The only company the Saradians
have in the country
and a front for their spying activities.
Based in Osaka and managed
by an ex-secret agent of theirs.
Every week, a freighter in
Kobe leaves for Saradia.
So you think they'll
smuggle it out by sea?
If we could retrieve the bacteria,
we can defeat Godzilla.
Then, we'll have an almost
endless supply of Godzilla cells.
I see, but Dr. Shiragami is...
Dr. Shiragami...
Excuse me, I'm from TNN TV.
I'd like to talk to you for a moment.
I've heard that your experiment
successfully combined the
cells of a plant with Godzilla
cells to create a super-plant.
Dr. Shiragami!
You people always criticize scientific experiments
without understanding their true value.
Scientists must look toward the future!
It's no longer Erika's spirit, Doctor.
I can't read it anymore. I'm shut out.
Then Biollante is...
Biollante is just a cross
between a plant and Godzilla.
- What is it?
- Godzilla?
Godzilla!
Biollante is calling for Godzilla!
Godzilla is turning north toward Adowara.
What shall I do, sir?
Keep it in the water,
away from the coast.
Understood...
Begin underwater attack.
The mirror's reflection
rate has dropped to 40%.
The Fire-Mirror is melting!
We can't control the lasers as well!
Incredible!
The mirror is heat-proof,
but not like the TA-32 armor.
Switching to missile attack.
It's out of control!
I think Super X-2 is out of action.
Can you bring it home?
I'll try my best.
Godzilla has finally landed on the east
coast and is heading toward Lake Hashi.
Repeating, Godzilla has landed on the
The 31st and 34th regiments have
arrived at the southern end of the lake...
They are taking up defensive positions.
Doctor!
Get inside, it's too dangerous out here!
Miki, hurry! Doctor!
What's going on?
Our opponent thinks it will win easily.
I wonder...
Did Godzilla come to
see Biollante because
it knew they were made
from the same cells?
Yes, it's possible...
They're both from the same family.
More than just the same family...
They're both made from
the same cells.
They're identical, two of a kind.
Not brother and sister,
they're the same creature.
Biollante is dying!
Godzilla's attack must have had an
abnormal effect on Biollante's cell division.
I guess it's not immortal after all.
Godzilla is in Sagami Bay?
So, it's out to sea?
Yes, we're trying to fix it.
Sure...Right.
Well?
The computers tested out okay.
The remote control needs to be
replaced, but that's expected.
However, the fire mirror is out of action.
We can patch up the armor,
but the fire mirror is a problem.
Can't you fix it?
It's badly deformed in too many areas.
Godzilla's melted a mirror
of synthetic diamond!
That's beyond our technological limits!
This is Chopper Three,
no signal on radar or sonar.
This is Chopper One,
Godzilla is nowhere to be found.
Roger...All units standby.
I want another sweep of Saraga
Bay and the surrounding area.
Understood.
If we lose Godzilla this time,
we won't have another chance.
We are currently over the sea...
We will continue to search the bay and
coastal areas for as long as possible.
Roger...
Continue your search pattern
at reference point 4-2-0-9-6-4.
Doctor...
Miss Okochi,
Colonel Kuruki wants you on the phone.
Is it possible that Miki
can detect Godzilla
under water the way she
did at the volcano?
I'm low on fuel. If we go any further,
we won't make it back to Tokyo.
- A little further, please.
- Okay, we'll head for Osaka.
Okay.
It's here, below us! It's moving slowly.
Godzilla is heading west,
100 kilometers off Hamamatsu.
The last time Godzilla attacked,
it ate a lot of nuclear material...
...from an atomic plant to store energy.
This time it doesn't have a
supply of nuclear material...
...and its battles with X2 and
Biollante used up a lot of its energy.
Do you think it will head
for an atomic plant?
Yes. What plants are nearest to it?
There's one at Maizuru, one at Obana,
and there are three at Tsuruga.
That makes five total, a third
of all the plants in Japan.
If Godzilla went that way...
It would be a disaster if even
one of those plants is destroyed!
Judging by Godzilla's latest position,
the nearest one would be here.
Nagoya!
We must organize our defenses.
Send a message...
I want Super-X2 sent into the bay.
I want air cover at
all times, and ground
troops on the three
peninsulas around the bay.
Here, is where we'll launch
our attack against Godzilla.
An all-out attack at Ise Bay?
Godzilla is just as likely to
come from Wakasa Bay.
What if they send everyone
in and it doesn't show?
It's an interesting question,
but an important one.
22nd and 23rd battalion,
prepare to move into position.
- Immediate mobilization.
- Godzilla has surfaced!
It's heading for Osaka!
- Send Super-X2 after it.
- Understood.
Send the fleet to the
channel for battle.
Understood!
We must close the expressway
and send all troops to Osaka.
It's too late. There's no time for that.
I know it's too late,
but what else can we do?!
We must move all troops along
the Mishimi expressway...
...to prepare for a counterattack
in Wakasa against Godzilla.
If we go to Osaka,
we won't have a chance...
But, if we go to Wakasa,
we might be able to beat it.
- What happens to Osaka?!
- My mission is to defeat Godzilla!
Its advance on Osaka
must be delayed.
You'll have to evacuate Osaka.
Contact Miss Okochi in Osaka.
Yes, sir!
KANSAI INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
CONSTRUCTION BASE
Miki!
Leave here, please!
It's too dangerous! Please do as I ask!
- We were ordered to stay with you!
- I insist! Hurry and get away!
What is this, telepathy?
It's all in her mind!
It's absurd to think she
can defeat Godzilla!
This girl has been a great help to us.
She might be able to delay
Godzilla's landing in Osaka!
I trust her ESP ability.
Miki!
The Navy has made it to the channel.
- Sir, the naval force--
- They'll never make it.
It's too close to Osaka for
them to use their cannons.
Alert Level 4:
In case G's landing on any
specific coast of Japan.
Ladies and Gentlemen, we must cancel
the concert due to an emergency.
Godzilla is approaching Osaka!
Please follow the Marshall’s
instruction and evacuate the building!
Godzilla is expected to arrive
in Osaka from Osaka Bay.
All civilians are required
to evacuate in accordance
with the instructions they
receive on radio and TV.
Evacuate calmly and do not panic.
Repeating...
Godzilla is expected to arrive
in Osaka from Osaka Bay.
All civilians are required
to evacuate in accordance
with the instructions they
receive on radio and TV.
Is anyone here?
What do you want?
We're criminals...
Yeah, we're robbing this place.
And you...
There's only one way
to deal with his kind.
Run!
Godzilla is passing the
north side of Osaka park.
It's heading for the business district!
Colonel Gondo has just left
with a loaded ANB Rocket Gun.
- He's on his way, sir.
- Good...
SuperX-2?
It's waiting at the business district.
Let's go!
- Let's go!
- Right!
Attack Godzilla from the front.
Try to lure it over to the
tall building on its right.
Can you do that without
using the Fire-Mirror?
Ready missiles and Gatling-guns!
I'll do my best...
Good! Keep it going!
We're out of missiles!
Colonel Gondo and his bazooka
troop are in position!
A little more...
Ready the Fire-Mirror.
What did you say?
The Fire-Mirror isn't
functioning properly!
Godzilla's not in the
proper position yet!
Fire!
We did it!
Okay, pull out!
Come in, Colonel! Colonel Gondo!
Godzilla is approaching your position!
Repeat, Godzilla is approaching
your position! Come in, Colonel!
All of this intravenous
stuff is bad for you, Godzilla!
Gondo!
After landing in Osaka and
devastating the city...
...Godzilla has moved north
to the Tappa mountains.
She used as much energy as Godzilla.
It's no wonder why she's exhausted.
She shouldn't have done it.
She could have died...
Yes?
- It's a call for Mr. Kirishima.
- He'll be right there.
Thanks.
Oh, Kuruki...
Right...Right...
It's been over fourteen hours now...
There still doesn't seem to be
any change in Godzilla yet.
If the bacteria doesn't work in the
next eight hours, we've had it.
Is that right? I understand...
I'll get a chopper and see you in Tokyo.
The Anti-Nuclear Bacteria should take
effect within six to twelve hours.
On the average, it's only eight hours.
I don't understand why
nothing's happened yet.
Maybe Godzilla is too large
for the dose we gave it.
No, one should have been enough,
and Godzilla got three.
One of them was fired in its mouth!
The dose was lethal...
I don't understand it.
Neither do I...
Just up-- right there.
Get to the biochemistry lab.
Ice blocks...?
The refrigeration is off.
When Godzilla attacked yesterday,
it destroyed the power plant.
The hospital's generators
couldn't handle it.
What's wrong?
I wonder...
Godzilla's temperature?
Yes, I think it has a
low body temperature.
Is that important?
We have no data concerning Godzilla's
body temperature, so we don't know.
But, why?
Bacteria breeds slower
in low temperatures,
so the lower the temperature,
the slower the reaction.
You mean the bacteria won't work
because it's a cold-blooded creature?
Yes, it's possible.
So, if we can raise
Godzilla's temperature...
Yes, but how...?
The M-6000 TC system.
Kuruki!
TC system?
Thunder-control system.
It creates artificial thunder...
...causing high frequency waves
to create clouds, then heat.
Like a giant microwave oven!
Kuruki, we can't use that system
since it's still in its research stage!
Tower One to base. Silver-Iodine
seeding is completed.
Expect clouds in two hours.
The ground troops
are nearly in position!
Go!
B-4 installation, ready!
B-8 installation, ready!
F-2 installation, ready!
Mobile war room...
...installation of all 100 generators
should be done within the hour.
It's hard to believe by
looking at his face...
...that he has such a huge
responsibility on his shoulders.
I guess it's time for my
generation to step down.
From now on, it's up to you guys.
There's nothing special
about our generation.
We make mistakes, just like everyone.
All units now coming out, sir
Godzilla has reached Wakasa Bay!
Godzilla approaching--
The generators have been completed.
Now, they have to be charged.
Good.
TC System, standby.
Godzilla is entering the TC field!
B-2!
You see? That must have raised
its temperature a little!
How hot is that?
So hot, it could melt
an A-1 tank easily!
Godzilla's gone outside the TC field!
Keep it in! It must not escape!
Understood! Commence firing!
- It's back in the field now!
- Good.
G-4!
Doctor?
You better start hoping
this idea will work.
If we can get Godzilla's temperature
high enough, the bacteria should work.
Konaki, what should we do?
Contact Yohama, the nuclear plant.
Yes, sir!
Takahama plant?
This is an emergency.
What are you two doing here?!
Biollante is still alive! Ask Miki!
What?!
- Godzilla!
- Chopper force, maintain position.
Kamatsu Bay, stand by to scramble.
It's working!
The bacteria's spreading!
It's true!
Bring in the helicopters.
This is incredible!
Line three, move in.
Could Godzilla be immune
to the bacteria?
It isn't possible!
Miki!
Hey, where are you going?
- Hey, where is she going?
- I don't know! Come on!
It's dangerous! Stay here!
What's going on?
Something's jamming the system!
Biollante...
She's evolving!
Look at Godzilla!
The bacteria has taken effect!
Congratulations, Dr. Shiragami!
One day, we'll put all of
this to good use.
Now we have to isolate
samples of the genes,
and put them into production at once.
I'm not continuing my work on bacteria.
Biollante has convinced me of that.
What's the matter?
You must continue your work, doctor.
You've got all the Godzilla
cells you'll ever need!
Godzilla and Biollante aren't monsters,
it's the arrogant scientists
that create them.
Biollante!
Thank you...
Biollante said it.
Erika!
Doctor!
It's him!
You look like Hell.
How is the doctor?
The water must have
lowered its temperature!
Godzilla's going back to the sea...
Biollante has gone to the sky.
And this lucky couple
is going to America!
Thanks, but I'm not going to America.
Why not?
Because wherever you go,
people are the same.
There's good and bad in every country.
Then, where will you go?
First...
...to bed, I think.
I haven't slept for days!
Shall we go together?
From here on?
Always!
How long have we been
living in such an age?
Maybe it started when man...
first stepped out of the Garden of
Eden, and left his innocence behind.
Man would do well to
remember this day, forever.