NARRATOR:
Outside of the world you know,
there exists
the Realm Eternal: Asgard.
The shining light of
the Nine Worlds,
Asgard is home to the gods...
all of whom bow down
before the All-Father...
Odin.
Odin's lifeblood
flows through Asgard,
and Asgard is Odin.
His power is all,
and he keeps
the Asgardian realm safe.
But once each winter,
the All-Father must rest
and enter the Odinsleep.
While Odin slumbers,
his absence leaves Asgard
vulnerable...
and this is when
the wicked
descend upon his kingdom.
[#]
Charge!
[YELLING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
For seven days,
an onslaught of trolls,
giants, dark elves and demons
seek to take control
of the Nine Worlds.
But they are eternally
defeated by him.
[GRUNTS]
My arrogant, oafish
brute of a stepbrother,
Thor.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[GRUNTING SOFTLY]
I don't understand.
Where--? Where am I?
[WHIMPERING]
:
Hear me, human.
You have been brought
to Asgard
because in all
the universe,
only you have ever
brought near defeat
to the Mighty Thor.
[WHIMPERING SOFTLY]
What?
I-I-- I couldn't.
[GRUNTS]
Not thee,
Bruce Banner.
You are but a sniveling,
sad creature.
I speak of your other half.
I speak of the Hulk.
[GASPS]
There is one day left
of the Odinsleep.
The cycle is
nearly complete.
As always, the Asgardians
will emerge victorious
against the siege of darkness.
My brother will seek
peace, and then...
Then I shall destroy him.
[#]
[COUGHING, GROANING]
[BIRD CAWING]
Verily, ye must say,
that went far better
than last winter.
Tell us, Volstagg,
are you going to dispatch
that troll beneath you
or are you saving him
for dinner?
[GRUNTS]
That all depends on
how much mead I partake in.
Did my ears
deceive me?
Did Hogun the Grim
make a joke?
And here we thought
you were still in a foul mood
because you didn't get to
slay a frost giant.
I've still slain more than
thee, Fandral.
But we shall see whom
the maidens reward more.
[LAUGHING]
[CHUCKLING]
[CHUCKLES QUIETLY]
In mere hours,
the All-Father will wake,
and then we may rejoice.
[#]
The Lady Sif would know
what vexes thee.
Aye. We won the day.
All is well in
the realm of Asgard,
but only until
the next Odinsleep.
It is as it has always been.
We must
learn to savor
the moments
of peace.
And accept the cycle
of death?
How many of our brothers
and sisters
have fallen to this madness?
Must we be chained
to this eternal struggle?
Be careful what you
wish for, my love,
for when the cycle does break,
when things do change,
then comes the end of days.
Then comes Ragnarok.
Perhaps our fates
are not ours to choose.
But come.
Let us return
to my father's palace
and prepare for
his awakening.
[#]
Please, I'm begging you.
Don't do this.
I've fought all my life
to keep the Hulk inside.
You don't know
the destruction he can cause.
[CHUCKLES]
Don't know?
You fool.
I'm counting on it.
Look at you, so weak.
Were it not for you
inside the Hulk's mind,
suppressing his power,
he would rule Midgard
with his rage.
I won't let him out.
I won't let you do this.
You won't let me?
How amusing
you mortals are.
Now, let me see if
I recall correctly.
It is anger that
unleashes the beast.
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
I seem to have forgotten
the frailty of mortals.
Look, Amora.
I do believe
he's going to weep.
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING]
[ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
[#]
[GRUNTS, PANTING]
No.
It's impossible.
[ROARING]
[GRUNTS]
Now.
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING]
[GROANING]
[GRUNTS]
And so begins the end of Thor.
[GROWLING]
[LAUGHTER]
[DISTANT ROARING]
Yeah. What think
thee, Balder?
One last troll with
dreams of conquest?
Hmm.
Perhaps.
[BIRDS CAWING]
[#]
[GRUNTS]
Come, Hogun, Fandral.
Let us give unto this scoundrel
the gift of battle.
[WHINNIES]
Ha-ha!
[ALL LAUGHING]
Hyah!
[#]
Ha-ha!
[ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
[MEN SCREAMING]
[ROARING]
The creature's power
is incredible.
Take care, Loki.
My spell bonds you
to the creature,
and while you are
master to it,
I can feel him
fighting you.
You have to listen to me.
It can't be controlled!
Do not try my patience, worm,
lest I turn
my attentions to thee.
[GRUNTING]
[ROARING]
[CRIES OUT]
Yah!
[GRUNTING]
Oh!
[#]
[GRUNTING]
[ROARING]
[WHIMPERS]
You are no troll, monster.
[SOUNDING HORN]
[HORN SOUNDING]
'Tis Balder's horn.
But this is
not right.
Asgard's enemies
are all defeated.
And yet the alarm
has sounded.
Stay at Odin's side.
Should I fail to
meet this threat,
you must protect him.
[#]
But if Thor should fall,
what hope has Asgard?
[HULK ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
You will have to
kill me, monster.
For I shall not yield.
[#]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
[GROWLS]
[#]
[GRUNTING]
Thor...the creature.
Like nothing
I have ever seen.
Aye, my friend.
This is no immortal evil
that we face now.
The Hulk has come to Asgard.
[ROARING]
[GRUNTING, THOR CRIES OUT]
Dr. Banner.
Can you hear me
inside the beast?
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
Why have you come here?
Why, to kill you, of course,
dear stepbrother.
Loki?
[GRUNTING]
I have waited
an eternity for this.
To crush you
with my bare hands.
To match your might.
To feel your life fade away,
as my hands wrap around
your throat.
[ROARING]
Never!
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
[ROARING]
Come to your new master,
Mjolnir,
and let us smite
my stepbrother,
Subtitle Created By : Mostofa Kamal™
Mostofa_Kamal_86@yahoo.com
www.Facebook.com/Mostofa.kamal.86
for there are none stronger
than Loki now.
[GROWLING]
Rise, cursed hammer!
Loki, enough. Your own
rage fuels the beast.
I can feel the spell breaking.
I will...
have this hammer!
[GROWLING]
[#]
Nay. You will have
its thunder.
[SCREAMING]
[ROARING]
For Odin. For Asgard!
[CRIES OUT]
[YELPS, GRUNTS]
[AMORA GRUNTING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
The monster...
it is rage incarnate.
It has shattered the spell.
[SIGHS]
The Hulk...
is free.
[GRUNTING]
Will thou yield, Loki?
[GROWLS]
[ROARING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHS]
Truly, this is
the best of both worlds.
I need not control the beast
to enjoy its wrath.
Goodbye,
brother.
This...
This is not
what I wanted.
There's no going
back, Amora.
After all, if not for
your black, broken heart,
none of this would
have been possible.
[#]
You don't know what you've done.
With no one
to reign the Hulk in,
he'll tear down
your entire world.
I find your prattling
useless, mortal,
just as you are now
useless to me.
[SCREAMING]
[#]
[ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLING]
[ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
For Odin.
For Asgard!
[GRUNTING]
[COUGHS]
[ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
[#]
[ROARING]
FEMALE VOICE:
Thor.
[THOR GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
Thor.
My love. I...
I was angered...
when you chose
Sif over me.
I did not-- I wanted
thy love, not your death.
Please.
Please come back
to me.
Mm.
[#]
Amora.
- Yes, my love.
Where...
is Loki?
[HULK ROARING]
[GRUNTS]
LOKI:
What is that monster doing?
It travels
towards Odin.
[#]
Loki.
I would have words
with thee.
No. You were at Hela's
door. I defeated you.
[GRUNTING]
You. You dare
cross the god of--
[CHOKING]
The Hulk will be sent
back to Midgard,
and then you will
answer to Odin.
Fine. Take the creature.
It provided me
with amusement enough
seeing it pummel you
nigh unto death.
AMORA:
Loki, you--
You fool.
You killed him.
Do you know what
you've done?
Because the mortal
died here,
Hela claimed
his soul.
Without his soul,
I cannot return him
to Midgard.
Without
Bruce Banner,
the Hulk cannot
leave Asgard.
[GRUNTS]
[METAL CLANGS]
[HORSE WHINNIES]
[#]
[WHINNYING]
[ROARING]
Valkyries, warriors...
your seats in Valhalla
are promised.
Protect Odin
with your lives.
For Asgard!
[ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
I saw the beast's
eyes, brother.
It will not stop until
all of Asgard is destroyed.
Until Odin
is broken.
You have brought
a new Ragnarok down upon us all.
[GRUNTING]
[CHOKING]
It's possible I made
a poor choice.
Amora, I need you
by Odin's
side.
Protect him, along
with Lady Sif.
[SIGHS]
As...you wish.
Loki,
you will send whatever dark
forces you have left
to battle the Hulk.
Then you and I,
we go unto Hel this day.
[#]
Rest your weapon,
shield maiden.
I have come to aid thee
in Odin's defense
at Thor's
request.
His request, you say?
More likely
his penance, witch.
No doubt he saw your hand
in this attack.
A punishment more cruel
than you can imagine, cow.
[HULK ROARING]
[HORSE WHINNYING]
[GRUNTING]
[ROARING]
[GRUNTS]
Loki, the god of mischief,
bids you death,
mortal creature.
[ROARING]
[GRUNTS]
Long have I wished
never to see this realm.
I always forget
what a busy time
the Odinsleep is
for my daughter.
© MOSTOFA K@MAL™
Dost thou see any newly
arrived friends here, brother?
Have a care, Loki,
lest ye stay here.
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
[GASPS, PANTING]
Wh--? Where am I?
[#]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
No. It doesn't
make any sense.
Huh.
- Bruce?
[GASPS]
Are you okay?
- Huh?
Betty? Uh--
I thought...
- Heh.
I don't understand. I--
I was alone, and then--
- You're not alone, Bruce.
Mm.
Not anymore.
BOY:
Daddy.
Come play with me.
[WHIMPERING]
[#]
Hail Hela, goddess of the dead.
We seek
an audience.
[GROWLING]
The sons of Odin risk much
entering my realm.
The Nine Worlds of Asgard
are in great peril, mistress,
including Hel
and Niflheim.
A new Ragnarok is upon us,
and we need your help.
We need
Bruce Banner.
The mortal's soul is mine,
Asgardian,
as yours nearly was
this very day,
and may well be again.
You would risk everything
for the sake of one soul?
Just as you would, Odinson.
But you do not have
one soul, daughter.
You have half
a soul.
You have
Bruce Banner.
You need the Hulk
to complete your prize.
[HULK ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
[ROARING]
[#]
[SIGHS]
Are you all right?
I feel...
I feel great.
[SIGHS]
I can't imagine
anything better.
FEMALE VOICE:
Bruce Banner.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[#]
Wake from this dream.
BRUCE:
Betty?
Betty? Where are you?
HELA:
The world of the living
has need of you.
[YELPS]
Who are you? What
do you want with me?
Not I. He.
Friend Banner, for
the sake of all of Asgard,
you must become
the Hulk once more.
Betty.
Where--?
Where--? Where's--?
No.
No!
[ROARING]
[#]
[SQUAWKING]
[ROARING]
[MEN SCREAMING]
[GASPS, GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING]
No. No, you can't ask me
to do that.
I finally had peace.
You don't know
what you're asking.
Your time in Hel
certainly has not
made you
less of a worm,
mortal.
[#]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
THOR:
Bruce Banner,
I know thee to be
a man of honor.
I know thee
to be a hero.
The lives at stake
are not your concern,
not even human...
but I ask you anyway.
Be that hero now.
No.
I can't.
SIF:
Die, beast.
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
The Hulk's
soul is
rightfully
yours, daughter.
Take it. Bring
the Hulk to Hel.
Merge the two halves
of his soul...
and claim him.
[ROARING]
HELA:
Bruce Banner,
I will not force you
to forsake
the rewards
of the afterlife.
But you must be whole.
No. I won't!
You don't
understand.
[ROARING]
[GRUNTING]
No!
[SCREAMING]
[ROARING]
Mm?
[GRUNTING]
[#]
[HULK GRUNTING]
Curse you, Loki,
for convincing me to bring
this creature to my realm.
Stay thy hand, Hela.
We shall retrieve
the Hulk.
"We?"
The Hulk's fists have addled
your mind, thunderer.
Fight with me, brother,
or die alone.
Not much of a threat,
considering we're
already in Hel.
[ROARING]
Have at thee!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[ROARING]
[CHUCKLES]
My apologies.
I was enjoying
the performance.
[HULK GRUNTING]
[#]
[ROARING]
Hulk!
Let them go!
I'm the one you want.
[ROARS]
Come on.
THOR:
Dr. Banner.
[#]
Hulk...tired.
[PANTING]
You called him weak,
Loki,
but there is more strength
and courage in that man
than you will
ever know.
- Hm.
HELA:
This soul is too dangerous
to keep in Hel
and too valuable to lose
to Valhalla.
I will return him
to Midgard.
[SPITS]
Enough of this ridiculousness.
To think that Loki,
prince of darkness,
should waste his time
with defending Asgard.
Nay, brother!
We leave
together,
for you still have
much to answer for.
Indeed,
you both do.
For today, Hela has
relinquished a soul,
and she demands one
in exchange.
You may try to
take my soul, death goddess,
but I will make you
fight for it.
And your realm has suffered
much already this day.
HELA:
You speak the truth.
So I shall take
his soul instead.
What?
[WHIMPERING]
Thor. Thor!
I helped you. I--
[MUFFLED YELLING]
I could fight you
for Loki's soul.
Will you?
No.
He is my father.
His stay will
not be eternal.
But know this,
Odinson.
Your soul will be mine.
And I will keep it
forever.
Your fate
is inescapable.
We shall see.
[#]
Thus, the cycle begins anew.
Asgard is safe once again,
defended to the end
by its heroes.
I am proud of each of you
that stand before me.
The day was saved by loyalty
and sacrifice.
We honor those
who fought beside us,
those who are no longer
with us.
And we defy those who would
see us brought to ruin.
And while the rewards
of Valhalla
await all of Asgard's heroes,
this day we honor
a hero of Midgard.
A mortal who
sacrificed everything
for a land
not his own.
This day, a human
showed the gods
what legends
are made of.
Hail the mortal, Bruce Banner.