My name is Wolverine.
I'm the best there is at what I do.
But what I do isn't very nice.
What the?
What the hell happened?
Oh, yeah.
Sir, I know I'm not supposed
to ask questions...
but... who are you?
No one you wanna know, kid.
Looks like someone had a bad day.
Copy.
We're still searching for any survivors.
It happened about four hours ago,
just before dawn.
The creature was sighted
crossing the U.S. -Canadian border.
This is what happened
when it reached civilization.
Creature?
The Americans call it "the Hulk."
Intel's sketchy.
Department H thinks the U.S. military
is covering something up.
It smells toxic.
Gunpowder too.
Well, someone tried to fight back.
Guess they didn't fight hard enough.
Department H wants you to find
and stop the Hulk...
...before he reaches another town
or city.
And if you can't stop it, kill it.
Sounds like fun.
Sir, I think we got something.
- Do you want us to try for a landing?
- Don't bother.
Oh, my God.
Hey, bub.
You haven't seen a big monster
running around anywhere, have you?
No. Stay back.
Stay away from me. Stay back.
Relax, crybaby. I ain't gonna...
You smell toxic.
Who are you?
Please, I'm begging you,
leave me alone.
For your own sake, please, go.
You're in terrible danger.
Here's the deal, misty.
There's a third claw
that's gonna come out...
...if you don't start talking.
Oh, hell.
I don't suppose you got any interest
in talking this out.
What the hell happened?
Oh, yeah.
Let's do this.
Come on.
Hulk smash little man.
Little man, leave Hulk alone.
Hulk is strongest there is!
Okay, bub. Let's try that again.
Thanks, runt.
We've been trying to take him down
for weeks.
Logan, buddy, it's me, Deadpool.
I shot you.
What are you looking at?
Prepare the lab. We're on our way.
His vital signs are increasing.
He's waking up.
Now, Miss Hines,
begin the adamantium bonding process.
- Yes, professor.
- Commencing infusion.
- His vitals are erratic but holding.
- Excellent.
Increase to maximum.
Weapon X's mental conditioning
and reprogramming are at stage five.
Begin combat assessment.
I don't care how long you've had him,
professor.
This is a mistake.
I know him. He can't be controlled.
You have his DNA,
so just let me kill him.
I'll take that under advisement,
Sabretooth.
- Prepare your team for the mission.
- Your funeral.
What do you say after the mission,
we kill all those floating babies?
Do you ever shut up, Wilson?
What? Babies creep me out.
He's fighting the programming.
We are losing control.
Increase the dosage.
Initiate lockdown procedures.
And someone activate Sabretooth.
Guards! Guards!
Wakey-wakey time.
Logan, we missed you.
And Weapon X just hasn't been
the same without you.
Nobody calls me "bub" anymore.
And Omega Red's a bed wetter.
One day I will tear out
your flippant tongue, Wilson.
He's very ashamed.
Despite Deadpool's idiocy...
...Weapon X is indeed pleased
to have you back, Logan.
We put considerable time
and money into you.
- And pointy things.
- You were our best operative, Wolverine.
So disappointing.
But you did lead us to Dr. Banner.
Of course,
you know him better as the Hulk.
I shot him in the ass.
With one of these.
What? I did.
Weapon X has been pursuing the Hulk
for weeks.
Unfortunately,
there was some collateral damage.
If only Department H
had sent you in sooner...
...who knows how much destruction
could have been avoided?
What do you want with the Hulk?
We just wanna help him
find his happy place.
Did you see how angry he was?
I mean, I'm sorry, but come on.
I think his pants are too tight...
We want the same thing
we wanted with you, Logan:
a weapon.
I'll erase Banner's memories
and reprogram him...
...just like I did you.
And then Weapon X...
...will have the most powerful creature
on the planet...
...at our disposal.
You should've killed me
when you had the chance...
...because I'm gonna get out of here...
...l'm gonna kill all of them...
...and then I'm gonna cut out your heart.
Wolverine, after I'm done with you...
...you won't even remember
this conversation.
I've erased your life before,
and I'm going to do it again.
All you'll know
is that you belong to Weapon X...
...now and forever.
Oh, that is so not cool.
I hate that guy.
Wolverine, you look so sad.
Hey, if it makes you feel any better,
Lady Deathstrike tried to kill you...
...while you were asleep.
- Better than having to listen to you.
- Man, does she hate you.
I mean, we all hate you...
...but Deathstrike really, really,
really hates you.
Hey,
still have that unbreakable skull?
Damn it.
You will die today, Logan-san.
It does not matter
what the Professor says.
These are your last breaths.
What are you doing here, Deathstrike?
I'm about to start
Wolverine's reprogramming.
He has to die.
How many times do I have to have
this conversation with you?
He's more valuable alive than...
Sorry, Prof.
Gotta go with the lady on this one.
You've gotta love our healing factors.
I'm gonna enjoy killing you for days.
And then I think we'll drop the Hulk
on an orphanage or something...
...just for fun.
Gaijin dog.
For the dishonor you caused my family,
you will suffer.
And then you will die.
Sweetheart, you and your family
can take your honor...
...and shove it up your bony little...
Deathstrike, don't!
Target located in Cell 23.
Take him down.
Backup. We need backup!
Well, he's alive...
...but I think he's gonna need
some serious TLC.
The last thing the Professor said
before the runt gutted him...
...was for us to kill Wolverine.
Really?
Do you buy that?
Yeah, you know, I would think
the last thing he said was, "Sabretooth!"
We kill Wolverine now.
That is all that matters.
Whatever you say, ponytail.
Who am I to say no to a little murder?
Strike a pose.
Get it together.
We're gonna have company soon.
Please. Please, I'm begging you.
You have to help me.
You have to get me out of here.
If these people turn the Hulk
into a weapon...
...millions of people will die.
So I should just kill you now.
That's what you're saying, right?
Come on, weepy.
You don't know what it's like.
I've been hunted
for as long as I can remember.
And I can't control it. The monster, it...
Look, do I look like I give a...?
Please, struggle.
It will make your death
taste so much sweeter.
- No!
- Yes.
As in, "Yes, you're going to die."
I'm just kidding.
No. That was my favorite gun.
What the hell's the matter with you?
Do your thing.
We need your big green friend out here
right freaking now.
What? No.
What do you mean, "no"?
Even if that was a good idea, I can't.
The transformation happens
when I feel angry or stressed.
No, they must have drugged me.
Something's suppressing
my adrenaline.
It comes from the cortex.
Maybe that will help speed things up.
If you wanna cry now, I'd say go for it.
End of the line, runt.
Got any last words?
Yeah, two.
Let's dance.
I've been waiting for this a long time.
Yeah, well, you can keep waiting.
Dude, that is just not cool.
Look at that.
Could you give me a hand?
I'm kidding. All right, I'll go get it.
There we go. No, that's not right.
What the hell?
Oh, God, now it's upside down.
There she is. Sweet.
You will die.
Gonna kill you.
Hulk smash claw people.
Come on, come on. Come on, now.
Come on, come on, come on.
The next one will be
through your brain stem, Logan-san.
Little man.
Hey. Hey, hey, I'm on your side,
you flaming idiot.
Hey, wait for me.
Who wants snacks? You do.
Logan, I think we lost him.
And they lived happily ever after,
except the Hulk.
Bub, you just made him angrier.
Talking man hurt Hulk.
Hulk rip off talking man's head!
My head? Oh, crap.
He's all yours, Einstein.
No, Logan, we're friends. No. No!
Ugly girl scratch Hulk.
Go for it, big guy.
Tear this whole godforsaken place
down to the ground.
Do it.
Great.
All right, bub. Where were we?
Guys? Red? Deathstrike?
I can't believe it. I'm alive.
I'm alive!
Subtitles by LeapinLar