Uncle Yi, I want an ultraman.
But I want the lemon flavor.
Sure.
That's all right.
Keung, where are you?
Thank you, Uncle Yi.
It's over done!
Leung.
Chief, what's the matter?
See? The pork is over done.
I told you many times.
Pork is the star of this dish.
I... I just went to toilet
for a while, so...
It's ridiculous!
You're not in the mood all the day,
see? You caused trouble at last.
What's the matter with you?
There is only half hour
to the banquet.
Now, the pork is over done.
Can we serve without pork
in the pot?
What we can do now
is to use the ''Blade''.
Leung, borrow the Blade.
The 5th descendant of the
Dragon Head Blade, Wong Bing-Yi,
I'd like to borrow the Blade now.
With the unification of the blade,
we'll do it righteous and filial.
Ah Yi borrows the Blade.
What is it about?
The Chief is holding the
Dragon Head's Blade.
What is it for?
Why did he take out the Blade?
This is my first time to view it.
Wah, this is my first time
to view this Blade.
Don't block my way;
I want to see how wonderful it is.
Bravo!
Woo, it's really wonderful!
Second-Uncle,
you can tell the guests that...
The banquet will be on time.
So, I'll count on you
to make us some tasty pork.
Sure, no problem.
This is a red pocket for you,
for working smooth.
Thank you, Uncle.
Okay, the banquet
will be started on time.
Come on, help me to serve.
Little sis, 5th-Uncle...
We wish you happy birthday!
Thank you.
Good! Thank you for coming.
Thank you, Uncle.
Come on, cheers...
Cheers!
What a smell!
It smells so good!
Give me the salt.
Here it is.
It's done!
Eat more! Come on, enjoy your food.
Come on,
come...
Take it to that table,
and that table, too.
Eat more! Come on...
Eat more.
Cheers!
If Master Joe was here,
we wouldn't have been that messy.
Even he is willing to help,
I won't let him do it.
I promised my brother
to let his son achieve great success.
But he is still a cook out there.
Tidy up now.
Chief, oh no! What a trouble!
Why did you do that?
Don't let him go!
He is the cook!
He intended to poison us!
He should not be the Chief
of our village.
Dare you want to go?
Who asked you to do so?
It's Master Joe.
Wong Bing-Yi,
since you borrowed the Blade,
You must be responsible.
Wong, you are not qualified
to be a cook.
I was being set up!
Did I misunderstand you?
You cooked the pork.
Yi, you don't deserve
to have the Blade.
Master Joe is the man behind...
I decided to expel Wong Bing-Yi.
Wong Kai-Joe will substitute him
for a while.
KUNG FU CHEFS
Tai-tung Martial Arts
Students, before your graduation,
Let's see who can put the emblem
of the school...
Back to its original place.
The one who can do it will be...
The first honored graduate
of the school.
On your mark...
Get set...
Go!
It is with him!
Go after him!
Don't let him go!
Give it to me.
Are you kidding me?
It is with the principal.
Don't come to me...
Respect your principal!
Who wants to be
the first honored graduate?
Move!
Are you serious?
I wanna be!
Me too...
I don't have it,
it's not with me...
I passed it to Ken'ichi.
It is with Ken'ichi.
Where is it? Where is it?
Principal, who did you give it to?
I... I gave it to that jerk!
Where is he now?
You bastard!
Pal, thank you.
Has Ken'ichi left?
I am asking you.
I think he has just left,
maybe, perhaps,
I think so...
It's nonsense to ask you.
I'll go after him.
You don't need to.
He asked me to give you this box
before he left.
How dare he fool the principal!
Watch out, it's breaking!
It's school property.
Principal, I have to leave now.
Politeness, justice, honesty and
honor, patience and self control.
I will never forget
what you have taught me.
I made you these noodles.
This is just a token from me.
It's very kind of you.
Rise.
After leaving the school,
go to this place to look for
master Sum Wai-tak.
What for?
From this great master,
you can learn what you're lacking for.
The principles of gourmandism are:
color, smell, taste, conception and appearance.
Ken has cooking talent.
But he doesn't know much
about the idea of food.
However, we cannot teach
the conception of food.
He must figure it out in his life.
If he can match himself with food,
then, he can make it.
Although Ken isn't a local student,
He has strong passion
on Chinese cookery.
After some time, I am sure...
He can become a great cook.
Sis, do you think the smell of tea
can distract me?
Please wait!
Forget it, Ching,
I am sure you can't get it
just by smelling.
We should get ready
for servicing now.
Come on, just say you can't make it.
Kam-lui, I told you, remember?
I want to serve our guests
nutritious soup,
But not this kind of mixture.
You can smell it, can't you?
This seems to be a nutritious soup,
But actually,
it is medicine instead of soup.
Take it away.
I tried so much time
and effort for it.
What a pity
that you still miss something.
I have already helped you.
But my sister is really great!
Kam-lui, what is this black stuff?
It's disgusting!
Take it away please.
Take it away!
My sister is really great!
Have the goods
we ordered been delivered?
I am now going to check it.
What's wrong with you?
Come and give me a hand.
All right.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Are you kidding?
You messed up everything!
I am sorry...
If any of it breaks,
I'll cut the bill, you got it?
Come on.
Oh my head...
It hurts!
What are you looking at?
Move those stuffs inside, hurry up!
No, I...
I'll check the bill later,
but I must check the goods first
If any breaks, I won't pay the bill.
If one is rotten,
I'll deduct 2 dollars, and so on
Move now!
Hurry up!
You too, move those
near the door way first.
Excuse me, sir...
Do you want to eat in?
This way please.
What did you say?
I said...
First, I am not a coolie.
Second, I didn't mean to hurt you.
Third, I came here for Master Sum.
The forth thing is...
I am really hungry.
Why didn't you voice out?
Did you give me a chance?
I'll make you pay for
hurting my head later.
Please wait for me
right here for a minute.
Since our shop
has just been in service,
If you don't mind,
please sit inside.
It's all right.
You want to see Master Sum?
So, you must tell me
what ingredients are put inside the soup.
Sis.
Thank you.
The water from 3 rivers.
So, you are a gourmet!
I just know something about food.
Did you make this Pu-er tea
with old tangerine peel?
How did you know it?
Old orange peel is as precious
as old ginseng.
To mix tangerine peel
with old Pu-er tea,
It is the best drink to quench thirst
and helps good digestion.
You know much about tea.
However, our food is even better
than this tea.
I am sure you have never
tried that before.
What do you want to order, sir?
What is the signature dish
of your restaurant?
All are signature dishes,
you can order anything you'd like to eat.
''Cabbage in clear water'' please.
''Cabbage in Clear Water''?
So, is it steamed or boiled?
Mind your tongue!
That is the famous Szechwan dish.
Although this is a
Cantonese restaurant,
Since you order it,
we'll get it ready for you.
Have you figured it out?
Are you kidding me?
This tastes like medicine.
But I know there is
something special inside.
This is a soup with 3 snakes
and a turtle. So disgusting!
I can't imagine that
you're really great!
So, do you know how to make
''Cabbage in clear water''?
I am a cook,
Sure I know how to make
such simple dish.
One for me please.
Master, why does he order
Szechwan food in a Cantonese restaurant?
It's weird.
I think this is a cook too.
He wants to try me
with that special dish.
Luckily I am not nobody.
Bro, there is just cabbage and soup,
Why people view this
as the greatest dish of all?
Yi, for we villagers,
cabbage has special meaning.
It is like our family.
Normally, we won't pay
special attention to it,
However, when we lose it,
we will miss it.
You'll understand the warmth
and love of it
Check please.
Sir, is there any problem
with our cabbage?
Be frank...
This is far beyond standard.
I don't understand what you mean...
The cabbage and chicken are not bad.
But the process is wrong.
The cabbage you made here...
Any cook can make it.
The original one
has not been found for ages.
May I know your name?
Wong Bing-Yi.
Master Wong,
if you are a great cook,
Dare you compete with me?
What if we lose,
I will
leave this restaurant forever.
If you lose,
please wash dishes here for a year.
Why should I compete with you?
As a cook,
you have no reason to reject me.
Okay, but I need an assistant.
I can tell it's done by Master Sum
at the first bite.
It's really tasty!
So soft and spicy,
and it's not greasy at all.
This has been the signature dish
of our restaurant.
And, he has a good assistant.
So, to him,
this is just a piece of cake.
Master Wong.
What do you think about his dish?
It's just fair.
Master Wong, it has been put here
for quite a long time, it's cold.
Watch out!
Sis.
Oh no! Why is it so hot?
What's wrong with it?
Actually, wrapping the skin...
It is a thin layer of sugar.
It is for keeping the duck warm.
Although the duck
is put on the table,
Actually, it's still
in the process of cooking.
It is very...
What is it?
I lost.
Why?
It is ''Wu-jo's 8 Treasure duck'',
not any cook has ever made it for century.
I can't imagine that...
It tastes like what it is written
in the cook book.
To make this dish,
we can't use knife.
Not any knife should be used.
Duck's meat is hard to handle,
once it is in touch with knife,
The tissue will go hard and still,
and the fibres will break.
Master!
Don't stop him.
I know very well about Master Sum.
After leaving school, go to
this place for Master Sum Wai-tak.
By the way, he always wants to leave.
Master Sum Wai-tak, please wait.
What did you say?
Sum Wai-tak?
Right, Sum Wai-tak is my father.
However...
He passed away last year.
Sum Wai-tak
was my brother's master, too.
I know.
When I tasted the duck,
I knew who you are.
So, about my story...
Master Wong, I heard something
about you before.
I believe that you're innocent.
Why?
It's basic instinct.
A cook who loves cooking
will never do that.
Have some tea please.
Thank you.
Master Sum left.
We have no cook now.
I just know following cook book.
And my sister doesn't want to
be a cook, too.
If this goes on, our restaurant...
It will be closed sooner or later.
And this family business will...
My brother adopted
your father's cooking skills
And I adopted cooking skills
from my brother.
So, I am obliged to help maintain
the fame of ''Sum's restaurant''.
But I just can't do it alone.
Master Wong, do you want...
The young man I just saw is smart.
He is just a little bit arrogant.
If he is well trained,
sure he will become great.
But he may not stay.
I believe that he will.
But under one condition.
Please go ahead.
Never call me Master Wong again.
Call me Ah Yi.
All right, Ah Yi.
I want to challenge you!
What do you want to compete with me?
Cutting skills.
I am sorry...
It's up to you.
He knows how to cut a globe fish!
No matter why he wants to
compete with cutting skills.
To cut a globe fish,
the cook must be quick and sharp.
There are many thorny things
on the skin of the fish.
You can cut it with the knife.
But it's really difficult.
That's why it can test
the cutting skill of a cook.
Finished.
This is the sliced globe fish.
If you have worries, so...
you can eat it half hour later.
I can't smell the stink of fish
but tastes it so sweet and fine.
It's neither like fish nor meat
This is the top level
of eating globe fish!
It's okay, it's my turn now
It is a bream.
The Japanese take bream as the king of fish.
Its taste is elegant and subtle.
But comparing with globe fish...
This is cold slice of bream.
It doesn't seem to be special.
No matter how skillful is Yi,
how can the taste of bream
be better than globe fish?
You...
What knife did you use?
The knife was cold.
The meaning of ''Sushi'',
that is to keep the fish
at a cool stage.
So, the fish will be tasty
After the sudden cold feeling,
the temperature inside the mouth
mixes with the tasty fish,
it is stirred inside the mouth
and spread outwards.
The frozen bream
seems to have rebirth!
This is the best taste of all.
I am not the loser.
I failed to have a better knife.
You're really great.
Actually, this is the secret
of cutting skills.
Who messed up with my sauce?
Why are all the carrots gone?
The money for paying the vegetables...
I have to pay the supplier now...
All right, don't cry please.
I have got it ready.
Come on, you cry whenever you get
the money for paying vegetables!
8,000...
Your order please.
Who told you to delivery
these things to us?
This is the order of Mr. Wong.
Thank you.
What is it?
Whose stuff is it?
To make tangerine sauce,
using pineapple juice is okay.
But you must add chrysanthemum
and iquorice.
With a green root and tastes ho
you can't say it a radish.
From Wong Bing-Yi.
He must have done something
to my sauce.
He has gone too far!
Master...
Don't greet me master,
I haven't promised to be your master yet.
Master, come on!
I'll do anything you tell me.
When heaven wants someone
to do something big,
first,
the guy will be bitterly trained.
He will be hungry and tired,
he will be trained
to be calm and mild.
So he will gain strength
from his training.
Are you sick?
How can this sharpening these knives...
You didn't sleep but sharpen
the knife in the middle of the night.
And you made it till dawn!
Will you let others sleep?
I can't imagine that,
you're not only selfish,
but also deaf!
You're sick!
What do you want?
Do you think
you're acting horror film?
Who do you want to scare
with these knives?
You know? You made sounds all night,
I just couldn't sleep all night.
Are you crazy?
Are you sick?
Why don't you go for medication?
Master.
I've already done
with the rusted knives.
So, we...
When can we start?
Start what?
Of course, you teach me cooking.
What else do you think?
Since this is sharpened by you,
you'll use it.
What?
Didn't you hear it clear?
I... I want to know...
When will you teach me cooking?
So boring!
Peel it, there are some baskets
waiting for you
Master, I...
Ah Yi.
Tomorrow is the first day
you become the chef,
this is your uniform.
Thank you.
Yi, what is bothering you?
I am worrying about my nephew.
Silky cake.
Greatest of all.
Crab meat in bird's nest soup.
Deep boiled snakes in oil
with ginger and green onion.
Cod fish's face in herbal sauce.
BBQ conch.
Abalones in winter melon.
BBQ goose.
Greatest mouths of all.
Curry seafood.
Roasted pigeon in lavender sauce.
Fried shark-fins.
Seafood in pumpkin.
World's selection of Sushi.
Treasure of the world...
Master Joe.
This is the newly designed menu
for the new shop, are you satisfied with it?
Just follow your idea. Dismiss.
Master, this is the new chef
I hired for the new branch.
Master Sum.
Where did you work before?
Sum's Restaurant.
So, why do you want to work in the
King of Cantonese Restaurant?
Master Joe, actually, I always wish...
to work in such a big group.
I want the truth.
The reason is...
I... I made a small mistake
in a cooking race.
I was defeated by 2 persons, so...
Master Sum is quite famous
in this field.
What is that guy?
What cook can defeat you?
That guy is named...
Wong Bing-Yi.
Pardon?
He is named Wong Bing-Yi.
Wong Bing-Yi.
I won't be merciful this time.
Master Joe, but the Chief has left
the village for ages.
Are you on his side?
I am not!
What I mean is...
I mean, you are his nephew...
Actually, it's nonsense.,,
Why do you treat him as your foe?
Right? Listen to me...
Shut up!
He stole the Dragon Head Blade,
he hurt my father.
At that time, did he remember
that's his brother?
Give it back to me!
Brother, stay calm please.
Why?
That blade is mine!
I am the Best Chef of the World!
You have no right to hide the blade.
I don't need this.
I want the Dragon Head Blade!
Where is mine?
Where is my Dragon Head Blade?
Give it back to me!
He always wants that blade and
to be the Chief of the Village.
Wake up please!
Bro, drink no more!
At the most critical moment...
Ah Yi!
Brother!
I witnessed it.
It's him...
He set a trap for my dad.
My brother got hurt
because of saving me.
It hurts!
My father can no longer be a cook,
all because of him.
He left the village.
Bro!
Stop it, I have no face
to stay any longer.
Please take care of Joe for me.
I promised my brother to
take good care of Joe, God knows that...
He forced by me
to leave the village.
It's a revenge.
How can he do this to you?
Forget it.
Let bygones be bygones.
In fact, your brother...
Won the championship of the
World's Best Chef for 2 consecutive years.
He gained much fame for us.
My brother is really a genius.
Wrong.
Wrong!
Cutting skills is easy to learn
but it needs non stop practice.
For common people,
they just need to cut sharp.
If a cook has better skills,
He can handle chopping, hitting,
mashing and slashing well.
That's already good skills.
But if he wants to be a good cook,
Different ingredients need
different kinds of cutting skills.
So, it'll take much time
for real practice.
Is it really that bad?
I did it purposely for you.
Thank you.
I worked for one whole day.
I already said thank you.
Don't be cocky!
Other than being fresh,
to make great food,
We need great sauce to mix with it.
Saucing is the soul of a dish.
But different people
have different taste.
But you will get bored for eating
same good food everyday.
So,
all good cook can make good sauce.
Try it.
Ying, why the sauce you made...
are of the same taste?
I think so.
Kam-lui.
Actually it's easy to make sauce.
You just need a little patience.
And some interest.
And some imagination.
There are few kinds of taste,
sweet, sour, bitter, hot and salty.
Just keep on trying.
Mix with different ingredients.
Then find out the best choice
of the guests, that's all
Is it tasty, Kam-lui?
It is sweet and salty.
But I can taste sweet and hot
at the same time, it's great!
How did you make it?
I haven't tried
such special sauce before.
Kam-lui, let's use this sauce today.
Keep it well in the kitchen.
Be careful.
Kam-lui, I'll go with you.
Ying, what are you thinking?
I am thinking of a way to
make some delicious bean cube pudding.
You want to make bean cube pudding?
Greet me Master,
then I'll teach you.
But I want the most delicious one.
No problem.
Master!
The ingredients for making
bean cube pudding is simple.
Soy beans, water and some substance
for solidification.
The proportion of soy beans
and water may differ.
Today, I'll teach you frying.
For fried eggs, we love it to be
smooth, soft and with good smell.
But how to make it smooth?
The key point is to let air
enter the eggs.
Bubble it.
This shares the same theory
of making spongy cakes.
I'll show you.
Then, you'll count on yourself.
The key point is to control
the temperature of the oil.
Just one word, don't use boiled oil.
If so, the eggs will be over done.
Come on.
Master, it is not done yet.
Yes, it is to use the remained heat
to make it all done.
So, the eggs will be smooth.
Other than skills of frying,
You need to pay attention
to breaking the eggs.
And, most important of all is
to control the heat.
It is simple to talk,
but it is really difficult.
This is named
''Wong Po thousand layers of egg''
Fried egg is just a simple dish.
But it is really
something interesting!
More simple the dish is,
more difficulty to be handled.
It's really hard to cook great dish.
No. it is not hard to cook well
It's really hard
to perform well in life.
Move now.
This is the home made sauce.
It's tasty!
This is newly made,
hope you all like it.
Boss. I haven't eaten
so delicious chicken.
What is it about?
What is it?
This is...
Obviously, it is a nail.
Nail?
Can you get it? It is a nail.
What is it? What nail
you're talking about?
There are some nails in the pot,
it can kill.
Oh no!
Don't get nervous,
it's just a misunderstanding.
Kam-lui.
What's the matter?
Take a look at yourself.
It is so sharp!
I don't mind nails,
but I want it cooked well.
It's not steak, I don't want it raw.
I don't eat half done nails.
Do you want to kill me?
What do you want?
You've gone too far!
If you want to mess up,
you must use better trick
How can you add so many nails
into the pot at the same time
On one would be so stupid to cook
like this. This is a set up.
It's hard to say
There was precedent from your chef.
What did you say
Wong Bing-Yi, this is the present
from Master Joe
Don't worry.
This is the pork done by Chef Tin,
no problem.
You'd better watch out
Why?
What does that mean?
I can't imagine our business
would become this worse.
Don't panic
Why not?
Now, we have no customers to come.
If this goes on,
our restaurant will be closed.
Who brought this bad luck to us,
huh?
Brother Choi,
are you here for shopping?
Let me handle it.
We'd better not talk behind someone
Don't mess up.
I don't want to be bullied
but say nothing.
Boss, how is it?
How are you?
Bitch! You're looking for trouble!
What's up?
Get lost!
What are you doing?
Stop!
So? Be a hero?
Go!
What's up?
Run!
Stop!
Freeze!
Stay where you are!
Hurry up!
Stop!
Freeze!
What do you want?
No, thanks.
Disgusting! Why did you stop me?
Look, you have flour
all over your face.
Come and join the 7th competition
for the ''Best Cook of China''.
This campaign is held
once in 4 years, the winner...
Will be awarded
the Best Cook of China,
If we win...
then we can save the reputation
of our restaurant.
Let's hurry back to tell sister
about this.
My dad is the best cook,
he is the best of the best.
I can win the cup easily.
No one can compete with me.
I want a revenge.
Hello...
Okay, I'll wait for you.
Sorry, I can't go.
Yes, what's the matter?
Master, please tell us.
Sister and I take you as our family.
We can help you!
This matter bothers me
for a long time, I must settle it.
Master, if you don't go,
we won't go too.
Ken, this is a
very important competition.
What is more important
than the competition?
Yes!
It's you and this restaurant.
I don't care the name
of being the best cook.
For the restaurant,
you must try hard in the competition.
Don't worry, we'll wait for you.
Ken...
Take this with you.
Now, the competition for the
Best Chef of China begins.
All the representatives are now
coming in the studio.
Uncle Yu.
This is a great event
for all great chefs in China.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the 7th competition for the Best Chef of China...
now begins!
Let me introduce the judges.
Mr. Yu Pun-cheong,
the chairman of the China Cookery Association.
Mr. Liu Chi-wing, the famous chef.
Ms Wong Lai-mui,
from the Catering Alliance.
Mr. Wong Wing-chi, the chairman of the
Association For Catering Services Management.
Mr. Yu Wing-man, the honorary
chairman of the Chef Association.
Before the competition,
We'd like to
invite the last champion,
Master Tin Chou-dao from the King
of Cantonese Restaurant.
Hi, Master Tin.
Master.
Is he still your master?
Kam-lui.
He is no longer your master.
Fatty,
I want to challenge you.
Fine, where are you from?
Sum's Restaurant.
Now, I have to tell you the rules.
This is a knockout.
The judgment team will pick
2 teams among the 6.
They will have the final race
in next time.
Now, the theme is knife.
In that case,
other than the outlook and taste,
The chef must express
the skills of cutting.
The cutting skill is a must
of a real chef.
You'll have one hour
for competition.
Now, I declare the race begins.
I want to cook Szechwan's style
of Ox head.
I understand what my master means.
Kam-lui, we must win.
Let's charge up.
But what should we do?
They are all picking ingredients.
Sis, what should we do?
Let's go
''The Four Stuffed Treasures''.
The Four Stuffed Treasures''?
It's more complicated than
''Eight Treasure Duck''.
Don't you have confidence
in your cutting skills?
I got it.
I'll get the chicken, duck,
pigeon and the fillings.
And quail too.
Sis, what is Tin doing?
This is the famous dish of Szechwan.
It pays much attention in cutting.
The competition is truly excited.
Now, we have only...
3 minutes left.
1 minute.
5.
4.
3.
2.
Time's up.
The 6 dishes are...
Grapes and Fish from Wah Shun Hotel.
Clams in chicken soup
from Chai-tai Restaurant.
Golden Ox and Duck,
from Wan's Restaurant.
Phoenix's tail and peach blossom
from Grandma's Restaurant.
Four Stuffed Treasures
from Sum's Restaurant.
Szechwan's Ox Head from the King
of Cantonese Restaurant.
Judges,
What a headache!
The fish and the clams...
The cutting skills and procedures
are all right.
But they picked wrong ingredients.
About the duck,
It tastes well and spicy,
it looks good too.
However, when it is peeled,
the body of the duck was broken.
And the dish from Grandma's
Restaurant, the prawns are fresh,
The outlook is nice too.
But the strong taste of wine..
Just covers the taste of prawns.
For the Four Stuffed Treasures,
The cutting skills are excellent.
The quail is in the pigeon,
then in the chicken,
And finally inside the duck.
It's a mixture of meat,
but with clear and layered taste.
It's really wonderful.
About the Ox Head,
it's really a master piece.
It's a difficult task indeed.
From the cutting skills
and the choice of ingredients,
it's of the top level.
Wonderful!
This ox-head is really wonderful.
Now the judges
are having the final judgment.
The 2 final teams
will be announced soon, they are...
Ken from the Sum's Restaurant
and Tin from the King of Cantonese Restaurant.
Congratulations!
We have made it!
We won!
I wish Master was here with us.
Master, we can enter the final race.
But the other team is...
The Sum's Restaurant.
Master Joe, don't worry.
I can figure it out.
Let me go.
Ken...
Come and fight with me
if you're a man.
Ken, watch out!
Ken.
Nice food can make people happy.
But if the chef isn't happy,
How can he pass happiness
to others through food
When I see you going back
to the village,
I can tell you
finally figured it out.
Thank you.
I must thank you indeed.
If you didn't teach them
whole-heartedly,
They can't enter the final race.
It's all because they are talented.
Ken, thank you.
I am so sleepy...
Are you?
Don't sleep,
I have many places to go with you.
I have so many things to do with...
Why happiness is so short?
Because...
People have many unhappy times.
Ah Yi!
You're something!
Sit down.
What do you want?
Nothing, I just come to see you.
Isn't it too late?
Not late at all.
If you are a bit late,
you will not see him.
Cut the crap, you're not welcomed.
I am your nephew,
I came specially to see you.
Why don't you want to see me?
I think I am not heartless.
Uncle, your student
wounded my fellows.
He should pay for it, right?
You know pretty well
for what you did.
What?
You kicked my father away
for the Dragon Head's Blade.
Now, you want to take my cup
for the Best Chef away?
This should be what I told you.
Your uncle did nothing wrong.
Stop!
No matter you believe it or not.
Your father has his reason to leave.
Okay, I have my reason to...
Fix that bastard and the bitch.
This is between us,
there is nothing to do with them.
Yeah.
I don't want to do anything to them.
I just bring you some present.
Leung.
Master Joe, why not leave him alone?
I don't want to repeat.
Well, my fellows accidentally
locked up your student,
And a young girl inside the freezer.
And they accidentally
locked up the door.
But don't worry.
I've kept the key for you,
do you want it?
I am sorry, I failed to hold it.
The key is inside,
take it or leave it.
You can take time to consider it,
but they just can't wait too long.
I've got no choice.
No!
That key is not the true one.
I've got the right one here.
Come on, it's over
Thank you.
I must thank you indeed.
Master Joe has lost control,
please take care.
Take care.
The next Best Chef
will be found soon.
The theme of this final race is...
Soup.
The Chinese always need soup
in the banquet.
Other than making soup,
the participants must achieve
one more thing.
That is...
Purity.
Sis, what does it mean?
That means, no favour
is the best favour.
So the cook cannot add seasoning
into the soup.
In the arts of cookery,
One way is to cook without seasoning,
it is to let people eat the real
taste of the food.
The best cooks of the Shang
and Chau Dynasty,
They integrated the arts of cookery,
With philosophy.
That is ''Purity is the best''.
I can't imagine
you'd give up the competition
for that rusty blade.
Do you like this blade?
You really like to be Chief.
Don't blame me of being heartless.
I'll let you be the Chief
for one day.
I now declare the beginning
of the competition.
Ken, what soup should we make?
Why these cabbages be viewed
as the best food?
Cabbages mean a lot
to the villagers.
They are like our family.
Normally, you won't feel much.
But when you lose it,
you'll feel how much you love it.
You'll understand it in future.
Kam-lui.
Let's do ''Cabbage in Clear Water''.
Master said, the fame of the
''Best Cook'' isn't important to him
Except Sum's Restaurant!
All right, let's do Cabbage
in Clear Water.
Master Tin, how can you
get these ingredients...
Preparation is always important
to achieve success.
This dish is named with
''Clear Water'',
it is because the soup is as
clear as water.
The method is, mined the chicken,
Then drop them evenly
inside the chicken soup.
When it sinks,
It'll absorb the remained fats
and other materials.
Kam-lui, give me the cabbages.
This is not normal cabbages.
We must pick the heart
of the cabbages.
Then, get some fine needles.
Stab the needles into the leaves
to make numerous fine holds.
But don't ruin the outlook
of the cabbages.
Then, add the cooked soup...
into the pot with cabbages.
And then put it into the steamer
for steaming.
What is it about?
For traditional method,
only the bottom is heated.
All the heat comes from the bottom.
Now, he uses this device,
So it will receive heat evenly
all over the pot.
When it is opened, even the Buddha
is attracted to jump over the wall for it.
''Buddha jumps the wall'',
it is absolutely the best soup of the world.
''Cabbage in Clear Water''
is no match for it.
Wait.
Make it a signature dish
of Sum's Restaurant.
Sis, that's my bean cube.
Dragon Head's Blade.
How come the bean cube disappeared?
Why the Szechwan cook view this
as treasure?
To make great food with some cheap
and common ingredients,
It is the top level of cookery.
And it implies the top level
of life performance.
This is the real taste of food.
Purity!
The result is,
Ken Lung from Sum's Restaurant
is the new Best Cook of China.
Bravo! Wonderful!
Brother.
Since you have come,
why not have a sip?
This is the taste of cabbage.
Who is he?
We haven't seen for ages,
how are you?
I am fine.
Master Wong, how are you doing?
Is she Sam Ching?
Right.
So you must be Sum Ying.
Sis, is he...
He is our father's student,
Master Wong Bing-kei.
Dad...
Dad, please don't leave.
I did it wrong!
Ken, my brother and I think that
you're the best one to have this blade.
We hope you can make good food
with it.
To give happiness to the world!
I will leave tomorrow.
So soon.
This is my plan.
I have something for you.
It's made by me.
Sorry.
Don't be sad.
I've tried it.
What you made is best.
I don't know what sister
is thinking.
Why makes you learn cooking skills
from Wong?
Master is a great cook, it's really
your luck to learn cookery from him.
I don't care.
I'll leave this happiness to you!
No laughing.
Look at you! You're so handsome!
Really?
You have rosy cheeks!
I am sure you don't have
female students in school.
Haven't you been touched by women?
So what?
No matter you're not gentleman like.
And you are stupid!
You are so dull!
You don't understand girls at all!
But I can cook
No need to understand girls