"This movie is based on a true story that happened
after Hong Kong's handover."
Subtitle by PandaRG
"As sensitive information is involved,"
"due to some parties still currently being engaged
in the police force,"
"the names, unit numbers, and the times
and places of the incidents..."
"...have been changed in order to protect
their personal safety."
Please feel free to have a look
at our newest items.
This is our latest collection.
Would you like to look at this one?
This is a robbery!
Don't move!
Lie down!
What are you doing? I said lie down! Are you deaf?
No.
You said don't move, so how can I lie down?
And if I lie down, then why can't I move?
Ah, we have a talkative guy!
You're one smart little monkey,
aren't you?
Aren't you?
Freeze! Don't move!
We're at the scene and need backup!
Stay away!
- Sir
- The suspect is inside holding 50 people hostage.
Call the negotiation team
- and have SDU on standby.
- Yes sir!
Don't come any closer!
Or I'll kill her!
I'm inspector Lau Chi-wai.
Tell me what your demands are,
but don't hurt the hostages.
- Get me a car!
- Wait!
It's horse racing day so traffic's bad...A plane!
Get me a helicopter in 15 minutes...
...otherwise I'll kill her!
Errr inspector...
I'm hungry-
How's it going?
The suspect's mentally unstable.
We'd better agree to some of his demands.
He wants pizza.
Get over here!
Not you!
The pizza boy!
- Which do you want?
- I want the stuffed crust one.
We don't make those...
What do you mean you don't make them?
And you call yourself a pizza delivery?
Well, you didn't order the stuffed crust
in the beginning.
How can it be good without the cheese inside?
No way, I want the stuffed crust.
What's so great about the cheese? It's fattening
and has tons of cholesterol.
I don't care, I'll kill this chick!
Fine, okay.
Don't get so worked up.
I'll order one for you right now.
Hey, where's the helicopter?
There's just three minutes left!
OK, calm down.
Look, I fulfilled one of your demands already.
Shouldn't you let some hostages
- go at least?
- I don't care!
If the helicopter doesn't get here in 3 minutes,
I'll kill this foreign girl!
L...have Hong Kong permanent residency!
- You smart ass!
- Hey!
Go,go,go!
Go where? The guy's already surrendered. Go home!
As long as the helicopter doesn't
get here in 3 minutes, I'll shoot her!
Hello?
Seriously?
The female hostage just now...
...her nipples were hard under her dress.
You see everything!
I don't know why you think it's such a big deal.
I don't understand how women can go out
and not wear a bra!
What's the big problem?
The girls in Boston don't wear bras either.
Without bras,
it's normal that their nipples jut out.
For fuck's sake...
...this ABC can speak Cantonese
but always uses English words.
It's so complicated to use three syllables:
Nip-ple-s.
In Cantonese it's so much easier:
I-I-n!
Hey, what time is
the Portugal vs. England game tonight?
11pm. But why bother, Portugal will lose.
No no, I want to see Cristiano Ronaldo.
What's so great about him?
- His skills with the ball!
- You can watch Ronaldo,
and I'll surf for my porn.
Enlarge it!
No, rotate it, "then" you enlarge it.
Damn dirty horny bastards.
Bro! We're in a police van.
You can drive faster!
You won't get a ticket!
I'll shower first.
Go ahead.
"Regarding SDU Training course in United States."
"Headquarter decided to send A-team to States
in order to unleash their best qualities."
You're looking for me?
Sir, I want to know why you chose the A-team?
You know that SDU hasn't won
a single award in many years.
This year we have a chance...
...since the SAS team isn't that strong.
Don't be like that. You know your B-team
can't even run 10km in half an hour!
Sir, it was raining the last time we ran.
A-team didn't have to face the rain.
This is just one of the problems.
Hey, how's your English?
I dated a white girl before!
OK. How do you spell "September"?
S-E-P...
I'm definitely faster than Joe at loading guns...
...and he can't beat me in close quarter combat!
A team is not just about one person.
You gotta have team spirit!
Josh told me that he wants to move to A-team.
- Huh?
- If you were a good leader...
...then your team members wouldn't ask for that.
Josh wants to transfer to A-team?
I was working, how can I answer the phone?
Of course you can answer your phone anytime.
You're a receptionist!
I thought if one person signs then it's okay?
No.
I used to deal with your father as well.
This is a long-term contract...
...I must have both signatures.
You should speak with him quickly.
This is a
good buyer...
- Shall I...
- No, definitely not. Let me think it over.
Hey, is there anything else?
If not then I'm leaving.
Who said we're done?
Let me take a shower, then we'll go for a drink.
Who's more attractive to you
girls with big chests.
Or girls with flat chests but no bras?
What the fuck is up with your question?
Why can't big-breasted girls also not wear bras?
Why should I choose?
Yeah, your question already has problems.
But if I really have to choose?
OK, then...
...big-chested girls.
You're totally shameless!
Hey Missy, I can't always be around you 24-7...
...I need time for myself too.
Never mind, if you're not happy being with me...
...let's break up.
I tell you this, Cheung Suk-yee...
...it's not that I don't understand you.
You don't understand me either!
Maybe we should've gotten to know each other
better before we started.
No need.
Just throw them all away.
But that's really how she asked!
What?
They are talking about the other departments
going out for "special massages".
So I went in...
...and she asked me if I wanted a facial!
Fuck no, I didn't come for a facial.
I came for a...
Thanks!
So I told her I didn't want a facial.
And I still regret it to this day!
Why?
Do you know what a facial is?
They mean using this pair...
...right over here.
Then she pushes your face into them...
...and then the facial begins!
Hey, hey!
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry! Speaking of which,
why don't we get going already?
Are you sure? If you're up for it,
then I'm in!
I'm ready anytime!
Right now?
I'm watching the game...
Umm...yes, it's about to start.
Watching others score...
...while you yourself can't score is just stupid.
Come on, let's go!
So this is serious?
If so, then I gotta call my morn to
tell her I'll be back late.
Fucking hell, you're a mama's boy?
Will you ask for your mom's permission...
...before shooting a robber?
What the fuck are you doing?
He's called Dried Shrimp,
so of course he's gonna be wimpy.
By the way, why are you called Dried Shrimp?
Just say it. You'd tell it sooner or later anyway.
- Fine, you're the one who OKs it.
- Well?
You didn't join the team yet...
...but during Chinese New Year last year
there was a big case.
I've heard of it.
...and our Dried Shrimp here gained
his fame as a hero.
We received some intelligence...
and the two teams set off for
the criminal Wang Tao's den.
Got to the target location,
carefully standby at the back door.
First broke the through the front door, then light bomb
and barged in the house.
Dried Shrimp was guarding the front door,
we got in and there we see someone
lying on the floor...
...as we moved closer...
...they opened fire at us...
...it was definitely "let the bullets fly".
It was so small and crowded...
...just had to carry on and fight.
They fire, we fire.
We fire, they fire.
Suddenly..."boom", the ceiling came crashing down.
It was Wang Tao, he blew up the wall
so that he can escape.
Dried Shrimp received call and chased after him...
...he got shot twice.
Luckily he wore bullet-proof vest.
Wang Tao walked up to him
and open fired at his head.
He was shit scared and curled up into a ball.
The lucky boy, the bullet got caught
and didn't hit him.
Wang Tao then ran off.
The ambulance came
and he was still curled up like a Dried Shrimp.
And you know what? The name Dried Shrimp
is now renowned throughout the police force.
Fuck you man!
If it wasn't for you, no one would call me that!
Hey, but no one is lying here.
When we got there,
he really was curled up
like a dried shrimp.
To be fair, I think it's OK. At least you tried.
Exactly! If I see him again,
I will personally arrest him!
Now this is a perfect example of...
...all talk and no action!
Hahaha.
So what do you think of the match tonight?
You're nuts! Portugal's
bound to lose England has Beckham!
I don't think so, I think England will fuck it up.
Portugal...will lose for sure.
It's just a matter of by how much.
- Are you so sure?
- Totally sure!
Then why don't we bet on it?
$2000. We just bet on
- who wins and loses.
- Hey, I want in on it too!
This doesn't involve you!
I will only bet with one other person.
You're not scared, are you?
Shall we listen to my suggestion?
What now?
Instead of wasting money on a bet...
...why not spend it on a blowjob instead?
Let's go!
You're a fucking pervert always talking
about kinky subjects.
If we hurry up then we can still make it
to Shanghai Street.
Instead of Shanghai Street,
why don't we just go to Macau?
There's a new place that just opened
there called "No. 1 Clubhouse".
- Really nice.
- What is it?
A nightclub and the girls are sizzling hot.
Going to Macau is not a bad idea.
We can eat crab congee there too!
Fucking dumb-ass!
We're talking about call girls
and you talk about crab congee!
Come on, if we hurry we can also
catch the game as well!
Stop. You guys remember what's in PGO?
SDU is a sensitive unit...
...we must register before we can leave
the territory.
Then call the boss
and tell him you're going
to Macau! There, registered!
Are you nuts? It's 8pm on a Friday night...
...and you want to call the boss
and tell him we're going to Macau!
Why not just tell him that
we're going for prostitutes!
- Then just say it. What's the big deal?
- You guys call him then.
I'm not doing it.
Someone told me there's an exhibition
on relics going on there.
Let's just tell our boss we're attending that!
Actually, I'm a devout Buddhist.
But how do you say the word in English?
I know!
She-le-chi
Fuck you!
It's not that hard, is it?
It's considered rather blasphemous, but let's go.
Wait wait, this really doesn't work.
The four of us going together
to Macau on a Friday night...
to see relics?
Seriously?
He has a point.
Forget about it. Let's just watch the game.
It's not like we don't have other solutions.
Really?
Before I was in SDU...
...I was part of an operation in Pak Nai.
We detected a speedboat gang
smuggling illegal immigrants into Macau.
Seriously? Smuggling people into Macau?
Sure! For example, some are out on bail...
...but want to go gambling.
At Pak Nai, you pay,
and then they bring you over to Macau.
When you're finished...
...you just catch a ride back!
Sounds exciting! Then we can even go
and eat crab congee.
Yes, you're right!
Wow you really do love crab congee!
That's because it's really good!
If you're there, how can you not try some?
Like I said, if we want to go,
we can already be on that boat.
What's everyone's opinion?
I just follow the others.
Look, we're police officers and SDU members.
You're seriously suggesting that
we illegally smuggle ourselves
into Macau to look for prostitutes?!
It's so ridiculous.
If you're that desperate...
...I'll go with you to Shanghai Street instead.
OK?
Girls we will definitely get...
...but how often do we have
the whole B-team together like this?
Why be such cheapskates?
Let's be sugar daddies together!
That's right,
we'll be the best team ever!
It's too dangerous!
If you don't even have the guts
to face such dangers...
...then why are you still with SDU?
We've handled much riskier missions before.
You aren't afraid to shoot guns...
...but you're scared to shoot your load?
It's not that I don't dare, but do we really
have to smuggle ourselves across?
Why don't we ask everyone in the team?
If you agree to go, raise your hands.
Forget it, you guys go ahead.
I'm gonna stay and watch the game.
- Let's go! what are we waiting for?
- Sit down!
We're a team, that means we stick together.
This is called "team spirit"!
If even one of us won't go...
...then the whole operation is called off.
So now we all watch the football match together.
What the fuck? This is ridiculous!
I need to fuck, he doesn't.
So why don't I get to go?
Come on, let's all go together.
To be honest, I've never hired a hooker before.
When it comes to call girls...
...you just need to know two words:
...in and out.
It's either going in or coming out.
If you choose someone right for you,
then you lie down.
Whoever finishes first and gets up, wins.
- Isn't that right?
- But isn't there
an easier way to do this?
Nope.
Desperate times require desperate measures.
I christen this operation...
..."Sex War"!
This is for the unity of our B-team.
Josh Chan, whether this operation succeeds
or not depends on you!
You know I've had this flu for over half a year.
Maybe if you let me sweat it out...
...I'll get better.
So help me out here, okay?
- Fine, whatever.
- Good going, men! Synchronize watches!
Dismiss!
We go immediately to get ferry tickets!
I thought we're sneaking across,
so what's this about tickets?
You still gotta act smart.
Sergeant, you sort out the tickets.
I'm gonna quickly pop over to Yuen Long.
Then we meet at Pak Nai.
No.1 Clubhouse, it's here.
Hey, big guys! Come in, come in.
We don't have time. We need 4 tickets
to No.1 Clubhouse immediately.
But there are many different packages.
Tons of choices,
like the "Environmental Blowjob".
Come in and we'll chat!
- Wait, what's an "Environmental Blowjob"?
- Just come in
- and chat first.
- Wait, what's an "Environmental Blowjob"?
What would you like, boss?
Some "magic water".
What brand?
The strongest one.
Okay, please wait.
So this is what you need to buy?
It's much more fun with it.
Oh! The "Environmental Blowjob"
The "Environmental Blowjob" doesn't use condoms.
Less condoms used means less rubbish.
So it's more environmentally friendly, hooray!
So what does "Best Young Selection" mean?
- It means little girls.
- Fuck off!
- ...How little are you talking?
- Minors!
No way, that's messed up!
...Are you serious?
Of course not.
You go ahead and buy it. I'm good.
Why are you so difficult?
Asking what this is and how much it costs...
Once we're there,
every second costs money.
With this medicine...
...it basically guarantees your money's worth.
Do you really need to go to such extremes?
Our money is earned through our sweat and blood.
So I'm not gonna waste even a cent of it.
There are lots more selections here.
What's up your alley?
Do you prefer
chest or ass?
You can double up overnight by
starting at No.1 Clubhouse...
...then we go for a Darling massage
and finish off with a night's stay.
All for $3800 per person. What a bargain!
It's too expensive. Got anything else?
Ah I understand.
I'll introduce something else to you then.
Let me introduce these to you.
This oil comes from India.
This is called "Never Gonna Fall".
And this new product from Taiwan
is called the "101 Tower".
These aren't right for you?
How about this one: "The Weeping Woman".
The Weeping Woman?
Dad! Sorry...Why do you still want to sell these?
The last time you used it,
the women still haven't fully recovered!
Don't you feel bad for them?
Yes, that's right, this one is too strong!
Girls aren't right for you?
Then how about muscled guys?
Why would I want guys?!
And why do the men look kinda dark?
They are Thai!
Thai boys are more popular these days.
But hustlers are a bit more expensive
than hookers. Yeah!
How much more?
One cock equals three chicks!
Hey, don't waste time talking about this!
No need to be upset.
We have plenty to choose from.
Just give me a minute!
Hold on.
Everyone's bodily needs is different.
I'll take this one!
No really...This one is too powerful,
and it's expensive to boot.
Expensive means that it's effective. I'll take it!
These three are $300 each. But this one is $1000!
- Give me 4 bottles.
- Wait a minute none for me,
so just 3 bottles.
3 bottles!
Dear, please get 2 more of these.
Dad!
Just listen to dad!
Mules!
They are a big hit recently.
But you need one week of advance booking.
Not to worry,
horses and sheep are readily available!
Stop telling me about animals!
Just give me 4 tickets to
No. 1 Clubhouse, that's it!
Fine, fine. But you're sure
you're not into animals?
You're thinking I've done it before?!
No...Anyways, let me make a call first.
Yes...we're paying now.
Oh, thank you!
Just a friendly reminder, only two drops.
Don't go overboard.
Just give them to me.
- No need for bags.
- Thank you!
- Let's go.
- Hey, you hold it!
See,dad?
I told you this is how to sell them!
Your acting classes are really proving useful!
We earned another $3000.
Big Fei-Lung? Yes, Peter referred me to you.
You got a boat going to Macau?
4 people, 15 minutes...Wait for us,
we're on our way.
You're kidding, they say England will
win the cup this year!
Why is it surprising?
They have Beckham and Rooney.
Beckham? When do they ever do well when he plays?
Football is all about teamwork.
What's up?
The car is stalling. Should we check it first?
Is it the car or is it you who's stalling?
They said in 15 minutes.
Fine.
Take all your money out!
Ka Ho, you take care of the cash.
So we put our wallets, IDs and keys into the bag.
Lock it inside the car.
It's not safe to leave it here.
Yes it's not safe, but it's still safer
than taking them to Macau.
If we get searched there,
at least they won't know we are SDU.
This time we just take the cash
and our phones. Are we clear?
No problem.
B-team, ready?
Yes sir!
Let's go.
Hi, Mr. Lee! Hello everyone.
I just need to put some goods on board
then we can take off.
Hey, there's four of us, so here's $4000.
No rush, no rush! Please board first.
- Alright, everything's sorted.
- Good.
Here's some lemon tea. It won't be long now.
- Thanks.
- Here!
- You're not sitting with us?
I get sea sick.
What did he say?
He gets sea sick.
He's afraid of seasickness?
Then why doesn't he just walk to Macau?
Maybe walking there will make him even sicker.
Hey, it's Friday night, so there'll be
lots of people at N01. Clubhouse.
Do you want me
- to call you a taxi?
- No need, it's fine.
But this No.1 Clubhouse place, is it any good?
- I've never been there.
- What?
You live in Macau...
...and you've never been there?
I've been to enough of those places
when I was younger. My daughter is almost 3.
You guys have fun.
I'll be at the bar at the end of the street.
When you guys finish, call me.
When will you be done?
Oh...in 5 hours.
Don't leave without us, ok? Give him $1000.
No problem.
We must leave before sunrise,
otherwise too many marine police around.
We'll call you then.
Thanks, and have a great time!
Welcome!
Please hold on, you'll be up soon.
OK, OK.
Sir, did you make a prior reservation?
Reservation? I have tickets!
Please wait.
Even with tickets, we have to wait?
I'm wilting here!
Welcome!
Wow, you're getting hard already?
Please come in, handsome!
So what?
You're so horned up already,
and we're not
even close to getting laid yet!
Mind your step.
Hey lady, why do we have to wait, and they don't?
They are our VIP guests!
You gentlemen just have tickets,
so you'll have to wait!
She looks friendly on the outside,
but inside she's full of disdain!
Do you have rooms now?
Yes, straight away!
Please come this way!
This way please.
Bring us some fruits!
- Just a second.
- And ask the mama-san to come!
Welcome, good gentlemen!
My name is Andy, Andy Ho...ho. Hahaha!
Hold on...why is the mama-san a man?
Sigh, we're a single-parent household,
so I have to act as both mother and father.
Plus, you're not messing around with me...
...you're messing with my girls, right?
Anyways, welcome, welcome...
Welcome!!!
Any special requests?
Due to my religious beliefs, I don't eat pork.
So you can kindly skip your first round
of the "pork chop" types.
What makes you think the ladies
in the first round will look fat?
It's to make the girls
in the second round look better.
Just skip the nonsense and get to the point.
You guys are veterans!
Hold the pork chop, hold the pork chop.
OK! Any other requests?
One word:
they have to be "experienced".
No problem! Older women, right? Hahaha,
the older ones are more experienced...
Are you making fun of me?
Relax! Haha...
I know, you want big tits! Go!
This guy's pretty wacky.
Haven't I seen him
at another club before?
People like him, they just go
from one place to another.
Here we go, boss!
Congratulations and welcome.
Welcome to Andy Ho Ho's "tit" art exhibit.
I'll let them introduce themselves.
Hello, I'm Mani, from Heilongjiang.
Hey long what?
Hi, I'm Linda, and I'm from Dalian.
Big Linda!
Hello, I'm San San from Tsingtao.
Tsingtao beer?!
Hi everyone, I'm Siaoyee, from Chengdu.
Seoul and Chengdu?
I'm Dalina, and I'm from Mexico.
Mexico!
I'm Jolin from Fujian. Pick me!
Pick you? Hahaha!
Hi boss, I'm Sze Sze from Guangxi.
Guangxi?
What's with you?
Umm? Dunno, suddenly I feel scared.
Oh yeah! Aren't the ladies pretty?
Gentlemen, please select your choices.
Hey Dried Shrimp, you go first since
you're the most desperate.
Hurry up! You're not trying to choose a wife here!
Andy?': Z f
Do you have anyone with short hair and no chest
but is good at massage therapy?
No way, you come all this way
just to look for a tomboy?
So you'd prefer the girls from the first round?
Ask a pork chop with no tits to come.
Ok, please wait a moment. And you three?
Fine, you! Since you were so enthusiastic.
Jolin!
- Second from the left!
- Linda!
Are you okay?
- First left.
- Sorry?
- First left!
Mani!
- Did you need to be that loud?
- He can't hear me!
Congrats! Wow, I can't believe that in just the
1st go all the clients have made their choices.
This is truly amazing!
Andy, do we pay $200 extra for a trainee?
Of course! We have trainees. Who wants one?
- All of us.
- Not me.
This isn't just about you.
These girls came all the way to Macau
just to make a bit of money.
But once they arrive here, they realize that...
...they don't yet have the skills
to do their job well.
So for $200, you can help them out.
This is what you
call helping those in need...
...to learn valuable skills in life.
I mean, $200 is nothing to you, right?
Fine, fine, I'll have one.
I'm so touched! I'm so grateful to all of you.
So, shall we get ready?
The 4 trainees, stand by.
Sit back for a bit, ok? See you shortly!
Now let's tie up some loose ends.
You sure you don't want this?
If you don't, then I'll take it.
Hold it, hold it. Two drops only!
First, I want to explain to
you the upcoming procedures.
You take care of the front;
you help push with your boobs.
After showering, both of you
then come at me together. Understand?
Sounds good! I'll go strip.
Go, go. How long have you been a trainee?
Get you fucking clothes back on!
What's wrong? Aren't we doing the boob push?
Boob push needs boobs to be able to push!
You're all bones. You're lying!
You're probably not even from Dalian!
But I'm really from Dalian!
But you just conned me into believing you
have a big rack!
You'd get arrested if you were in Hong Kong.
Get me the mama-san!
Hurry up! Come on in, you hunk! Sit down!
- Is this your first time?
- Mmm.
Wow, you have really big feet!
You know what they say,
big feet means other parts are big too.
Mmm.
Hey sister, bring the stuff over here.
Oh, you're so nervous!
Please have some tea.
Thank you.
That's not for him to drink.
It's for me to use later on.
Have some candy then?
That's not for him either!
I'm going to use it on him later.
Hey, it's cold, why don't you wear something.
Corning, boss!
Hey,hey,hey!
- What are you doing?
- I'll do it myself.
You're cheeky!
Hey,hey,hey!
I like it!
Thank you! But just massage is ok,
no need to fondle.
You're so sensitive!
Hey...don't move, don't move!
I just want massage, nothing else.
Good idea!
- Good evening boss!
- Let me help you.
Good!
Boss, I'll start stripping then.
No complaints from me!
Wow, I didn't expect that you not only
have a small mouth...
...but also a small rack!
What's your name?
I'm Ling Ling.
Ling Ling good name!
Why is a beauty such as yourself
working here at a brothel?
It's because I'm new
and don't have much experience.
Exactly, you're just lacking some experience.
But here's your chance.
Why don't you gulp down some tea first?
Boss, I can't do it.
It's company policy we can only fondle...
...but no mouth.
I understand that it's a big company,
and rules cannot be broken.
That much is certain.
Boss, you're such a good person!
Yes, I'm a very good person.
The other clients
wouldn't think about your future...
...so they would never help you.
But I think we share a similar fate...
...so I will help you.
Boss!
Sorry for the misunderstanding...
You're full of shit!
You give me fakes and expect me to take it?
You waste my time and spoil my mood as well!
What now?
It's a misunderstanding.
I'll get you another and promise
that the next one will be a home run!
Hurry!
Come in!
Boss!
Wait, let's check the goods first.
Stand over there.
Sure, no problem.
Jump up and down 1O times.
See? This is what you call the real deal.
No way!
She's got fake ones too!
Why choose her and not me?
Because at least with her it's injected
inside her boobs...
...unlike yours which is
falling out everywhere! Go home!
Hey handsome, do you want to shower first?
No need.
Then I'll take one!
Wait a sec.
Do you need to use the mouth wash?
This stuff is all for her use later.
Oh.
Had dinner yet?
Yes.You?
Me too.
You just joined?
A few days ago.
Have you gone out and looked around yet?
Not yet.
But want to go see the ruins of St. Paul's.
The ruins of St. Paul. Nice place.
Have a candy.
Do you want me to do massage first?
Let's finish this first.
Hey, hey! What are you doing?!
What do you mean? This is normal.
I'm famous for my magic hands...
...and my special massage.
There's really no need.
I don't need a "happy ending".
Just a normal massage, okay?
You're so thoughtful! Alright.
- Thank you!
- Come on!
Company policy says you can't suck, right?
But you can instead use your mouth to "fondle".
That won't break the company policy...
...surely?
Oh ouch, ouch!
Boss, sorry, are you okay?
Shit, that really hurts!
You give me back my own pubic hair?
Hey good-looking, did you wait long?
Hurry and get undressed!
You need a massage?
Sister, sit over there.
Do you need a massage?
No thanks.
What does this mean?
It's a normal random police check.
Just show your ID to the officer
you don't even need to leave.
Oh Shit!
Boss, I can't! Just now you already went way
over the line.
Hey, just let me taste it once.
- I cannot!
- Boss, phone call.
Yes?
Dried Shrimp!
There's no Mainland police officers here,
just Macau ones. They don't arrest clients.
I cannot...
A bit, just a bit.
- I really cannot!
- Just a touch?
Boss, your phone!
- What now?
- Keung, we really need to leave now!
I told you, they are not here to arrest clients...
...they just check IDs.
Exactly they check IDs!
Oh Shit!
You call Josh, and I call Ka Ho.
We leave in 1 minute!
Bloody hell, what oil did you use? Is it expired?
No, I just opened it...
What the fuck?! You can't even tell
the difference between water and oil?
- And you call yourself a massage therapist?
- Sorry...
What's up?
Captain, what's going on?
Police check! Be outside in 45 seconds.
No fucking way!
- Here's some tips.
- Thank you sir.
Thank you.
What's your name?
I'm Lily.
Lily, bye.
Everything's fine.
Enjoy. enjoy!
Hey boss, the police check is nearly finished.
You can have more fun soon.
Go,go,go!
YOU, stop!
It's a dead end!
- Here, this way!
- What?!
They're coming! Don't think, just jump!
Ahhhh!
Yahhhh!
- Jump!
I can't, my legs are like jelly
and my dick is hard!
Normally you can do it, so just go for it!
Quick! They're here, quick!
Hurry!
You guys go. Just leave me!
Then let's go.
Let's run first, then think of a way
to rescue him.
No!
We came together as a team,
we'll leave together as a team!
If you move, I'll shoot!
Stop, don't move!
Run! Don't worry about me!
Hands UP!
Wow, the station is packed today!
The four of you, get in there.
Thank you sir.
Shall we call a doctor?
No need.
Please take out your wallets, keys, mobile phones.
Everything in your pockets.
- Hey, let's go!
- What's the matter?
Beckham is injured!
You can do this later let's go now!
You guys stay put!
I told you Beckham will leave the field.
There's still Rooney that's enough.
Can one guy like Rooney save the whole team?
I don't know if one person can
save the team or not...
...but now I know one person
can harm the whole team.
Why do you keep on groaning?
No...the thing is so stiff, it's painful.
I told you two drops only!
You had to be greedy...
It wasn't me!
The chick didn't know
and used half the bottle!
Fine, fine! Why don't you turn around
and sort yourself out?
Can you be quiet afterwards?
Don't look, guys!
Fuck!
I told you we shouldn't have come.
Look at what's happened!
Even the name of the operation is stupid.
What the fuck is your problem, huh?
Huh? We all decided to come together...
...but now you're fucking blaming me?
You forced me!
I forced you? If you weren't horny as well...
...how in the world would I force you?
This "Sex War" operation was
agreed upon by everyone.
Where's your sense of shared responsibility?
You shouldn't even be in the SDU!
Now you're talking about the SDU?
Do you know how many rules we broke tonight?
This "Sex War" operation...
- I'm the commander of this operation!
- We left Hong Kong
- without approval...
- I didn't say
this operation has failed,
- so it will continue!
- ...Illegally entered Macau...
- This is an order!
- ...hired prostitutes, resisted arrests.
- I'm the commander of this operation!
- Any one of
- these could get us fired!
- Are you challenging me?
Keung, let's forget it...
You finish your jerking off!
None of your business!
Come on...
This fucking bastard has looked down
on me for a long time!
You want to transfer to another team?
We're harming your career, right?
I'm not a good enough leader for you, is that it?
You're the leader, right? Let me ask you this.
What should we do now?
Shall we go out there and tell them we're all SDU?
Let the papers put us on the front page?
SDU members going to Macau to look for hookers?
As the leader of the B-team
and "Sex War" operation commander...
...after assessing our current situation,
I have reached a conclusion.
Our best move is to...
escape!
You mean altogether?
Because I heard "everybody"
I totally agree with you, but how?
Got any small change?
Hold on.
Go, go, go...Come on...
Come on...Oh crap!
Trying an overhead kick?
OK, back to business.
Hey, let's finish the second half first.
Nah, you guys carry on.
Oh shit! The suspects escaped!
They took this all down?
Hello? Sir...
sorry...the four suspects got away.
What were you doing? You didn't cuff them
and didn't put them in a cell?
The cell is already full, sir.
Three days ago, we received
classified information.
Wang Tao brought more men
to Hong Kong via Macau.
From the method they used in their escape...
...we believe your four men
may be part of Wang Tao's gang.
Everyone get ready for a briefing in 10 minutes.
We must arrest them! Understand?
Yes sir!
Shit!
Give them a call. Tell them
to turn around we'll pay them extra!
- I don't have the phone on me.
- What?!
It's in my trousers.
Hey guys, heading back to Hong Kong?
- You want to leave right now?
- Yes, now!
$2000 each. We leave now.
Give it to him.
My money is in the trousers too.
What?!
If you don't have the money, don't waste my time!
No no...here, take my watch!
I'll withdraw money
from the ATM once we land.
I don't have time for this nonsense. Assholes.
Go back and get your trousers.
You must be kidding we just got out!
You have a death wish or something?
And you call yourself a cop? They just checked
the place why would they go back?
Fine, whatever you say.
Give me 10 seconds.
What's going on?
Nothing. Shall we go?
Hurry up!
What?
Fuck, the flat-chested girl stole all my money!
Get the mama-san, quick!
Why would I have the mama-saws number?
Oh Shit!
It's Lily.
It's a friend.
Friend? What kind of friend?
She's the trainee in my room.
She can be trusted, it's okay.
Where's the flat-chested girl?
She stole all my money!
How would she know which flat-chested girl?
Police! Open the door! Police! Open the door!
Coming!
Have you seen any suspicious men around?
- Yes!
- Where?
While I was walking past,
I saw 4 guys over there arguing...
Oh, the sound proofing here isn't great.
They should be over there.
Why don't you have a look?
You'd better not be lying.
If we don't catch them, we'd have to punish you.
Sir, you're on duty.
Who's your mama-san? What's your name?
I don't have one. I'm Nancy.
Nancy?
You can flirt later. Over there, right?
Thanks.
Thank you.
God, I'm in pain.
Hey! She's getting changed, don't look!
- I'm not looking.
- Yup!
Turn around, for fuck's sake!
Ow!
Where are you guys going?
I'll leave you guys here...
Please be careful.
Thanks a lot. Let's go!
Hey, you'd better take this with you.
No way, that's your money.
You'll need it for the taxi.
Fine, I thank you on behalf of
Hong Kong residents. Let's go!
- Hey, I really can't stand it anymore!
- Hurry up!
Can I find somewhere to relieve myself first?
Hold on, hold on! Almost there! Hold on!
- I'll go and sort this out now.
- Quick! Quick! Quick!
Oh!
Sex War operation commander, what do we do now?
Let me think it over.
Think it over? By then we'll all be arrested!
I told you we shouldn't have come!
Why do you always have to be so negative?
When I was a kid, I watched those SDU movies,
and they had a saying:
Confidence does not make you a winner.
But with no confidence.
I believe in our captain,
and I believe in our "Sex War" operation!
We still can get out of this mess!
That's right
True, although we didn't get to sleep
with the girls...
...at least we fondled them!
That's better than nothing.
Fuck it! So now what?
I'll tell you after I take a piss.
Of course you say you want to come!
Dried Shrimp!
What?!
What were you doing just now?
Nothing.
- Nothing?
- What now?
What are you hiding there?
Nothing!
Take it out.
- Take it out now.
- You go outside first!
Come out! Take it out!
"Thai Style massage"
You were using this to jerk off?
L.
I'm asking you...
...why were you jerking off to
an ad for male hustlers?
I'm actually gay.
You're gay and you came here for prostitutes?
What a waste of money!
I wanted to tell you guys earlier.
But I was worried that you guys
wouldn't accept me.
We're a team
why wouldn't we accept you? Right?
Yes!
Yup!
I was scared to come out...
...since everyone thinks SDUs are so manly.
I was worried that if I didn't
come with you guys...
...you'd look down on me.
Why would we look down on you?
Which century are we in now?
You ask Josh
this kind of thing is normal
in other countries, right?
It's no big deal. It's pretty normal in Boston.
It's a screw-or-be-screwed world anyhow.
Exactly, why would we treat you any differently?
You really won't?
Of course we won't!
But if we shower together,
I will pick up my own soap!
A lot of people think like you.
That's why they invented liquid soap.
I use them!
You're so smart!
You bastards!
I wouldn't do that I'd just stick
close to the wall.
I'm gay.
But it doesn't mean I want to screw just any guy.
You guys don't need to freak out.
We aren't freaking out.
We all treat you as a friend.
But you can't bring your gay friends
- over to bully us!
- Why not?
Then we'd be the ones who are called shrimps!
Fucking hell.
See, that's why I didn't want to tell you guys!
Just joking don't be like that!
We'll get use to it soon!
Come on!
Ah, is Fei-Lung still at that bar drinking?
Hey, I go this way, you go that way.
OK.
This is good stuff, and it's for you!
Hey!
You can apply it to your nose, or even the mouth!
Eh? Why are you here?
Well, the trainee job pays too little,
so I need to find a second job.
I see. By the way, do you know
any speedboat drivers?
Those guys over there by the door should be.
- Here?
- Yes
OK, thanks.
What do you wanna drink?
San Miguel.
US$40
Hey, you look familiar.
I think I've seen you on TV before.
Would you happen to be referring to Tony Leung?
No way!
Breaking news,
around 1am this morning...
...four male Chinese suspects escaped
from the police station.
According to police sources
they are considered to be extremely dangerous.
Hey buddy.
4 people going back to Hong Kong tonight.
Will you take us?
How? My boat has been detained by the police.
I can%leave!
We'll pay you more if you agree.
No really, I can't help you.
Your hand is colder
than the beer! Look! No, look!
Your fucking mother is even colder! Go back
and fuck her instead!
Wow, what the fuck?
Hey, where are you taking me?
Oh, so no wonder the boss is always
praising your cheery attitude.
So he means that you're happy. Like, gay happy.
You understand, right?
Don't get me wrong,
it's that you're gay I mean happy!
- You still have to rub it in?
- Oh, sorry! Sorry!
Hey, what are we doing?
Keep quiet.
Breaking in is illegal!
Police officers entering Macau for
hookers is already illegal.
Might as well go all the way.
Hey, what are you looking for?
Cash, of course! Hurry up and help!
Burglars!
Where?
Huh? You know each other?
- Ah ho? What you doing here?
- My friend's in trouble,
so I came to get some cash.
You're really something.
I've moved here for almost a year...
...and you didn't even visit me once.
And on your first visit, you tried to rob us.
Kwan, call the police! We have burglars here!
Come on, this is just a father-son argument.
No need to call the police.
Uncle, uncle...
This ungrateful son of mine
deserves to be punished.
I told you that we have an emergency,
otherwise I wouldn't need the cash!
Ungrateful bastard!
Do you think I know nothing after I retired?
I still have friends in the force!
The money you owe outside is already on record
for internal investigation.
So what if you made it into the SDU?
It's not like you're moving up any higher
in the ranks. You're useless!
You like gambling so much,
you should feel sorry to your morn.
I quit gambling a long time ago.
So what? You still owe
few hundred thousand dollars!
The money I owe is from the cafe business
I started with friends.
The force pays you well enough.
You know nothing about the cafe business...
...so of course you're losing money!
You don't even know how to fry an egg!
Come on, you're both father and son.
Don't be angry, you can resolve this peacefully.
What a stupid fool, loaning money
from loan sharks.
Even if I ask loan sharks
and they don't lend me...
...they still wouldn't treat me
like shit the way you do!
I started the cafe business for my own future.
I don't want to end up like you!
- Like what?!
- You can't afford the rent
in Hong Kong after retirement.
So you have to move to Macau
while your own money is running out!
What a failure.
How dare you call me a failure?!
Put it down!
Don't, he's your father!
Uncle, let it go!
Call the police!
Hey!
- Are you okay, uncle?
- Call an ambulance!
Look after him.
Hey, how's it going?
Ka Ho's father is in the hospital.
I thought you guys were trying to get money?
How did you end up here?
It's a long story...Let's just say it
turned into a domestic drama.
Where's Josh?
I lost him at the bar.
Tried calling him but no one answers.
Maybe he's dead?
Where's Ka Ho?
Over there.
He said he goes jogging and swimming...
How could he end up like this?
You haven't visited in a while.
Your father had an operation not long ago,
but he wouldn't let us tell you.
I do call him. He always say he's fine!
You owe people money and you didn't
tell him either!
You both are like two peas in a pod.
I started the cafe business
so I could make more money...
...was hoping to move him back to Hong Kong.
I know he doesn't like living here.
Aiya...Look at you.
You're a big boy now, don't cry.
You really think we moved here just
because of the cheap rent?
Dad also...
Your father is a man too.
Who here is the patient's family?
The patient is fine, he just got too worked up.
He should rest for a few days, then he'll be fine.
Thank you, doctor.
Let him rest.
You guys head to Hak Sa.
Plenty of speedboats back to Hong Kong there.
- Thank you sir!
- Thanks uncle.
Hurry up if the report gets back to Hong Kong,
then you're in big trouble.
Let's go.
I just got the message. ls everything okay?
We understand.
You were busy with the girl, so why would you have
time to answer your calls?
What are you talking about? She saved us before,
and now she's in trouble.
We understand. We don't have time, let's go.
Already?
Take care, uncle!
We're leaving, bye bye!
Hey, watch this!
This one!
Hurry up!
Wow, this is it! This is the place
that has the best crab congee!
Boss, what would you like?
- Crab congee for me.
- OK, crab congee!
What's going on?
Don't know just eat
and watch the unfolding drama!
This dish is really famous here.
Why don't we share one?
Sure.
Huh?
Why are you here?
Ah, I didn't know you got knocked up.
I normally hate kids, they're so much hassle.
It's all his fault
I thought we were being careful.
But we did it once, then suddenly
I end up like this!
Of course, I have good genes!
My sperms are active!
Ewww, don't say dirty stuff like that!
You sure did change quickly. Before,
you didn't like younger, more immature guys.
He treats me very well.
Sure he does, otherwise you wouldn't be
so quick to have his DNA inside you.
Where's the ring?
I was thinking of us going on a holiday
together for our wedding.
Holidays are good. When?
No way!
He still isn't financially ready yet.
Better wait until he becomes the company's boss...
...it's not too late.
Good thinking. Good plan!
Why don't you leave me your number.
Next time I'm in town I'll give you a call.
Isn't he your friend?
We're very good friends!
We even share the same ride.
Since when do I share my ride with you?
Then why can't I get her number?
0h, I get m!
I should call you sister-in-law! Sister-in-law!
Hey, stop it.
Then why not?
Hey, why did they divorce?
I don't know. He hardly talks about his wife.
I just know they had an argument
then got divorced.
Not surprising.
As SDUs, we have to wear protection
on every mission.
But once you're at home in bed, you don't want
to wear protection anymore.
So when she does, it leads to arguments
and then divorce.
Chan Siu-ching...
...what game are you playing?
Yes, I like playing games!
Even when I give birth,
I wouldn't say that
I'm married on his birth certificate.
I'm never giving up on your alimony money.
The money I get from you now...
...I can even support
another man.
I wasted so much of my youth
being with you...
...now it's time I
get my revenge.
I provided everything for you
when you were with me!
What rubbish is this about you
getting your "revenge"?
You haven't changed one bit.
You forget that I'm not part of your "team".
I don't need to follow your orders!
And stop going to my mother's
and say that I cheated on you.
We got divorced before I had someone else!
You're always just thinking about yourself!
You don't take care of those around you.
It's OK, it's OK. Don't be angry
with people like him.
Let's eat.
Are we done? Then let's go.
- Ummm.
- Finish it first. Eat!
Didn't you say you love crab congee?
So finish it!
Otherwise people will say I don't take care
of those around me.
She didn't use to be like this.
Actually, her chest is pretty much
the same as before.
That's true.
She used to be so easy-going.
I don't know when she started changing.
Maybe we were together for so long
Every time we talk, we'd end up arguing.
Relationships between men
and women are never easy,
especially if you see each other every day.
Not like his kind of people.
And what's so different about us?
We have to do things face to face.
But not you guys. Since one of
you always flips over. there's less arguing.
Last joke! Last joke!
You deserve it.
Keung, forget about it.
Just think of it as you donating to charity.
That's right. A few thousand dollars
a month is not a lot.
Captain!
This is a matter of urgency we should sort out
this "Sex War" operation first...
...before getting sidetracked
You're right.
We're representing Hong Kong team,
this operation has to be good...
Sex War operation must go on.
Done yet?
Let's go in 3O seconds.
Yes, sir.
That's crazy painful!
We go to Bing Kee!
I know, smuggling iPads earn more than
smuggling milk powder.
But if all the kids drink tainted milk
and turn into mutants...
...then who's left to buy your iPads?
One ice coffee!
OK, lets talk about this later.
Hello my good man! How about a ride back
to Hong Kong?
Call me Brother Eagle.
I can usually detect the presence of cops.
Is this a bait-and-hook operation?
Maybe you think I'm a cop...
...because I watched too many cop movies
when I was younger.
We just came over for some sightseeing.
I'm just asking. You can't take me to court...
...if this is a trap I know my rights!
Wow, Brother Eagle is a very learned man!
Hah, I also watch a lot of cop movies.
How many of you are there?
Four.
$8,800, paid upfront.
We only paid $4000 to come over!
It's riskier now. Take it or leave it.
Here's $4000.
I'll give you the rest when we board.
Come back tonight.
What?
That's ages from now!
It's daytime now.
Who is stupid enough to smuggle
during broad daylight?
Give me your phone!
OK, it's done call me when you get here.
1' 2:
You said you didn't know how to play!
Don't blame me it's only
because you're bad at it!
I was just making you happy by letting you win.
I gotta go.
To where?
My friend found me a job,
so I need to go to an interview.
Umm...
Goodbye.
See you.
Why did you say "See you"?
Don't you guys usually say "Bye bye"?
It's because I think I'll see you again,
so I said "See you".
Well?
How was it?
Done. We leave when night falls.
Where's your girl?
She had to leave.
Dried shrimp?
Jerking off again.
Dried shrimp!
Are you OK? Seems like you're still struggling.
Yeah, my hands are crazy tired!
Looks like I need to help you.
Thanks Keung.
But can you do it gently? It's a bit raw now.
Ow!
That's not what I mean! Follow me!
Captain, you pawned off your Tudor watch?
But it was from your ex-wife!
Exactly, so why keep it around?
Dried Shrimp.
Captain, you should save this money
for your own use instead.
We're a team, and we've decided you need
it the most right now.
Instead of us three having fun,
why don't you have yours?
That's right.
If this "Sex War" operation only allows one person
to spill their load...
...then I think that person should be you.
Thank you Captain!
Thank you Ka Ho!
You can thank me, but move back!
I can feel you poking into me!
Sorry Sorry Sorry!
Let's find a way to find him
a male prostitute in this place.
"Thai Style massage"
"Thai Restaurant"
Keung, I'll pay you back
when we get back to Hong Kong.
Then you can get your watch back!
How can we ask you for the watch money back?
You know it's better to give than to receive...
...Because if we receive it would mean
we're on the ones getting cornholed!
Hey!
So sorry, that was really the last joke!
Don't be a sissy...
...hurry up and go inside!
We'll wait for you downstairs.
Can you come in with me?
I'm really nervous!
I've never been to places like this before.
- So we do the fucking for you too?
- Hey, just forget about it...
Sawasdee-ka! Hello handsomes,
are you looking for Thai delicacies?
The three of us are not, but he is.
We are his bodyguards.
Wow, Mr. Bodyguard, you have such a big chest!
Do you want to do part-time here?
Aren't there just Thai delicacies here?
Thai food can also be adapted for Chinese
or Western tastes! So are you interested?
I may be fit, but I can't handle it
when people pressure me.
So...do you have any preferences?
Don't underestimate him, he can handle it all!
Wow...Thai happy ending, priced $6969!
Zesty young meat!
So? Decided yet?
I don't know what to choose.
Too many choices confuse you let me help.
Try this one: Spicy Royal Rack!
Hey this one's OK!
Mama-san, this one please!
- No problem.
- Hold on.
The pictures are always different
from the real thing.
- Let's have a look first!
- No problem,
I'll put the order through right now!
Sawasdee-krub!
What? You call this Spicy Royal Rack?
It's more like Spicy Royal Fat!
You shouldn't judge by looks alone...
...service is more important in the end, right?
For fuck's sake, with all that fat...
...you'd sooner die of high cholesterol
after trying him!
Usually the ones with some fat are tastier!
Forget it, let's not argue.
Just bring us another one, OK?
This one?
OK.
Hot and sour tender mix!
Coming!
Hi Baby!
Exactly what kind of mix is this?
A mix of northern and southern India.
I usually don't discriminate, but...
- ...I'm afraid of the dark.
- But the dark ones have the most experience!
You know he is the best in getting people off?
The god of prostate massage!
Guaranteed instant erection!
Don't worry about that, he's already up for it.
Seriously, no more fooling around.
This is the last chance. This one!
Thai-styled roast beef.
Hahaha“.
This is our other special.
Was gonna save him for myself tonight...
But seeing that you like quality,
I'll let you guys have him!
Let's have a look first.
Sawasdee-krub!
Wow!
No need to look like you're starving for it.
Like what?
You already look like you're sucking him off!
Fuck you!
Go take good care of our guest!
Yes sir!
He'll get milked dry!
There's the saying "the ball is round",
This year another surprise.
Portugal beats England on penalties
3-1 and progresses to the semi-finals.
I told you, football is not a one-man game.
In the end it's all about the strategy.
Got the $2000 that you owe me?
How would I have it?
Hey, have you guys finished arguing?
We lost the game already.
The flat-chest bitch?
You bitch, you stole my money to come here?
Where's my money?
What are you doing! Let me go!
I don't even have enough money
to buy make-up yesterday!
And my mobile?
I dropped it.
- You dropped it? Fuck you!
- What are you doing?!
What is this then? You dropped it?
Why are you guys here?
Oh, nothing, waiting for the boat and my friends.
Why? You came here to fool around?
No!
Did you find speedboat?
- Found him.
- Wait a second...
...is the Big Fei-Lung you're talking
about the one who looks like...
Anthony Wong?
More like Simon Loui.
Why didn't you talk to him when you saw him?
When did I see him?
I said hi to you last night...
...but you turned around as soon as you saw us.
What are you talking about?
The place was so dark did you get
the wrong person?
I didn't even say where, how did you
know it was dark?
Josh, what is up with you?
Talk!
Big Fei-Lung isn't the only one with a boat!
We have one now, right?
No, I want to know why you saw him
but didn't say anything!
How can I?
I arrested him before!
So how should I go over and say hi to his face?
Bullshit!
He's driving a speedboat now so what if
he knows you're a police?
As if he'd go and report you.
I didn't just arrest him.
I framed him too!
Serious?
You're always so righteous
you'd do such a thing?
I've always wanted to become a part of SDU.
So back then, I wanted to prove myself
in front of my seniors.
Big Fei-Lung was still dealing drugs at the time.
I went to a disco and saw him,
but didn't find anything on him.
So I planted some drugs
which I found earlier in his car's backseat.
No wonder you wanted to sit in the back
when we came over! Just checking, right?
I always think back on this and regret it.
I always wanted to be a good policeman,
a good SDU...
...but this is always at the back of my head.
When I saw Big Fei-Lung, I was scared shitless.
I wasn't afraid of him calling me out.
I was scared of him looking at me.
Do you understand?
Once you're a cop for a while,
you're bound to have a few regrets along the way.
It's OK, if you cannot face up to others...
...as long as you can still face up to yourself.
I used to look down on other people...
...but then I realise that everyone
is about the same.
You can't say that I'm not like you...
...I'm not from Boston!
And I don't know how to say "nipples"!
We just call it "lin"!
Oh yeah, where's your flat-chest bitch?
Fuck, she got away again!
Next time, I'll burst her boobs!
How can you burst someone with no boobs?
I'll squeeze it!
What's with the wind suddenly?
Is it from a hairdryer?
Wow, you look like you're glowing!
Was the sucking and blowing good?
I just know one thing: all's right with the world.
Congrats!
Good, "Sex War"
operation is complete,
with Dried Shrimp as our rep!
It's about time let's go!
Go!
MY legs are wobbly!
How are you? You only just came,
but you're hard again?!
That medicine is really strong!
I didn't mean it to happen.
You guys head in first,
I'll find somewhere to sort this out.
Hurry up then.
- Fuck!
- There's no one!
His cell number's dead.
What shall we do?
What are you worried about?
You have a mobile, just call Big Fei-Lung!
Hey hey hey!
- Hey.
- Big Fei-Lung.
Why are you guys here?
I was looking for you yesterday.
Weren't you looking for hookers?
Why are you everywhere on the news?
Hey, let's not talk about it now.
We need your help to get back to Hong Kong.
- Today?
- Yes.
But I already have 5 other clients.
Surely your boat is big enough to fit us too?
OK, OK...gotta wait for one more client,
come on in...
You're very lucky!
Tonight I have a big client he's really nice.
Good, OK.
Oh, Brother Tao!
Oh, Brother Tao! Brother Tao.
Sit sit sit. Just wait a bit won't be long.
OK.
Please sit.
Brother Tao. Sorry but there's a surprise tonight.
What surprise? It's surprisingly crowded haha...
With Sir Chan...and them.
Right, just let me finish loading,
then we're ready to go in 10 minutes!
OK.
Sir?
Yes, we teachers...
...are always called "sir"...
...this, "sir" that, ain't that right Sir Lee?
That's right, Chow Sir!
Hahahaha.
Well, "Sir", which subject do you teach?
Human biology.
But it's tough to live in an expensive place
like Hong Kong. Our pay is not great...
...so that's why we came over to Macau
to earn some extra cash doing massage.
In Kowloon City I'm known as...
...the Hands of God.
You know how many people I have
to jerk off in a day?
- Heard of it before?
- Nope.
Oh too bad.
Sometimes you really can't tell
from just appearance alone!
Look at my size...
I also have my secret techniques!
- That's true pride!
- Sorry, sorry...
And you? What are you good at?
I'm...
known for my "motor tongue".
Hahaha.
What are you doing with your hand?
Huh? My hand?
Haha, good question, what am I doing with my hand?
Let me tell you...
...I help clients jerk off...
Since I've been doing it for so long,
my hands get cramped up and they twitch.
See?
To stop the twitching?
I just need to keep doing what I'm good at.
Don't believe me? You wanna try?
- No thanks.
- Are you sure?
Looking at your build,
hard to believe you are a teacher.
- OK.
- I never did study much...
But my English...l can spell
at least all 12 months.
My son, he's in high school...
...and can't even spell them sometimes.
Isn't it ridiculous?
Exactly.
Hey, Why don't you try spelling one?
Spell September.
S...e...p...
...t-e-m-b-e-r. September.
Haha, I'm the one teaching English,
not him. You got it wrong.
Haha.
Teachers like us know
so little nowadays.
We have plenty of school holidays,
meet a lot of
school girls, that's about it...
Learning all the extra stuff isn't
so useful in the end.
Let's go...
Bye...
You sons of bitches don't move!
I've seen plenty of cops in my life...
...but never have I seen such disgraceful ones!
Pretending to be teachers is bad enough...
...but pretending to be male prostitutes?
Fat boy!
You! Don't you have mirrors at home?
Before I started using AK47s...
...I once ran a male hustler club.
Hands of God? How about I show you
God with my gun!
Fucker, I'll shoot you in the head.
No, don't! Sorry.
Yes, we're cops. But we're just cops
who are passing by.
Look, we don't know each other, nor do we have
any grudges between one another.
Let's just pretend we've never met...
...and nothing happened, OK?
Don't move.
Hold your hands up.
I told you I would personally arrest you!
Well done!
Good job.
- Can we go now?
- Not yet.
Four more are coming.
Four more?
Don't move or I'll shoot him.
The police are here!
- Run!
- Hey, where's Brother Tao?
Arrested! Hurry and move
or we'll get arrested too!
Hurry up!
Police, don't move!
Doesn't seem to be these four.
Yes, it's them!! Don't you recognize them?
Oh yeah, guys, move in!
Yes sir!
I'll give it to him.
Kwong, wrap it up!
You probably recognise me.
You're a handsome guy, it's hard not to.
Sorry!
Thank you!
But don't worry, after you framed me,
I went to prison.
Then my boss thought that I was a traitor.
So I escaped to Taiwan...
But it was a good thing since I met my wife there.
I'll show you something.
Look, my daughter! She's three. Isn't she pretty?
Yes!
Every day after work, I'll go over her
English courses with her.
Sometimes things are meant to be...
When you think that
there's no way out, think again.
Josh!
Yes!
Thank you.
If you want your daughter
to learn English, call me.
You know, I'm from Boston. Bye now!
OK.
Come on! We gotta get back before seven!
What's the rush, there's plenty of time!
Why did you stop? Where are we?
Hi, I need to call a tow truck!
We're in San Tin...We'll pay you extra, OK?
...OK, thanks.
Call a taxi, Dried Shrimp.
What time is it?
- How far is it from here?
- 6:20!
1O kilos.
Why don't we run back?
Are you serious? Captain, a taxi is better.
The last time we trained, it took us longer than
half an hour to run that distance.
But the last time we had our full gear
on plus equipment!
But we haven't slept for two nights!
Shouldn't we think of something else?
I remember what you said last time:
confidence does not make you a winner.
But with no confidence, you'll definitely lose.
I believe in Captain,
and I believe in this operation.
Hey, your hard-on finally went soft!
Hey, it's gone!
Yes, I'm not hard anymore!
I can't go on.
Come on!
Time!
6:55!
Now who'll dare say...
that B-team can't finish 10K in 35 minutes!
Captain! I'm so happy to be a part of
the "Sex War" operation!
I think it was a success!
I'm also very happy to be getting prostitutes
with everyone else!
Next time, include me as well!
This part...
...is a bit harder to say!
Just like, "What happens in Vegas,
stays in Vegas"...
what happens in Macau,
there won't be a second round.
In the end, our "Sex War" operation was
just a waste of money and sweat.
For example, Ka Ho's under investigation
and even got his dad into the hospital...
But in the end the two of them patched things up.
Strangely, they both previously went
for that flat-chest bitch...
...and they both promptly rejected her.
Ho said that when his father gets better...
...he'll take him to No.1 Clubhouse
for a family trip.
As for Josh, you'd never guess.
For someone so uptight who has never been
with a hooker...
...he finally goes out and sleeps with one...
...even telling her later on to move to his flat
and become a trainee.
Everything's been so clear...
...starting from the beginning...
...it definitely shows that he's from Boston...
...buttoned-up on the outside,
but open-minded on the inside.
And what did I gain from this "Sex War" operation?
Two syllables:
Respect.
Weren't we going to a buffet? Why Japanese food?
After all that...
...we should remind ourselves of
the taste of some raw tuna.
How's it down there?
My flag's still at half mask...
...as if saluting some soldiers
who were killed in action.
What? I'm just copying him.
You learn from him,
and you'll also get our death stares.
Fuck.
Shame on you, asshole.
Cheers.
Josh, cheers.
Seriously, if you don't want
to stay in our B-team...
...I'll inform the head
and transfer you to A-team.
What now? You wanna kick me out?
OK, I did once think that you were rubbish...
But now I discover that you are a great leader.
Thanks for the flattery,
but I'm not as good as A-team.
But I don't think you were right about something.
What?
You said one guy alone cannot save a team...
...but this "Sex War" operation
was successful...
...because of you.
You always said you wanted to be the best
of the best within the SDU...
...You're now on your way.
The most important skill is flattery.
Am I good enough then?
Just right.
Hong Kong's most wanted criminal Wang Tao
has been arrested by Macau officers.
According to leads, this is the biggest
and longest search operation...
...made by Macau authorities.
The police spokesman also said that
one of Wang Tao's accomplices...
...was working undercover with the police...
What the hell, I arrested him!
Forget it.
In other news,
Hong Kong police force's
Special Duties Unit...
known as SDU...
beat 16 other countries to claim 1st place...
in the International American
Special Forces competition.
Can you tell us the secret to SDU's
success this time?
Team spirit, that's the most important thing.
Team spirit!
We always get along well as a unit!
So what if you're good at shooting...
...you can't beat us at ejaculating!
Good one. How'd you say it in English?
I am proud of you!
Proud!
Have we had enough? If not, we change venues.
But we just sat down.
There's a new place in Macau...
where you eat abalone on top of
a real woman's abalone...
...And you eat without chopsticks...
Each piece must be eaten using only one's mouth.
Gosh! Just thinking about it makes me wanna...
I am ready!
Really? Again?
We just got back.
OK, sorry, I didn't say anything.
We can think about it.