Falling in love is not allowed in school
Tonight at 11 p.m.
A No. 3 alarm fire broke out
at the Narranmoda Memorial School
One of the 2 casualties
is the wife of the school Principal
Someone is still up there!
Sir...
You can't go up there
Someone is still up there!
Sir
Calm down!
There's no one up there. The firemen have checked
Was in the office...
Trust me!
The school is haunted!
Ho Yiu Leung please report
to the school office now
I was a student of Narranmoda Memorial School
That night I was preparing for the School Open Day
We were working late
Suddenly a student was summoned to the office
I have never seen that office before
It doesn't exist
20 years later
Are you sure? How of them?
How many of them are accepted?
Got four
My God! That's not enough!
Wait! Are they in boarding school?
I think so...
Shit! I need time to get ready
What for?
I...
Don't you dare!
Yat-Man
Is it true? There will have 4 boys in our school?
I'm on duty now. Don't be silly!
Come on! Please tell me, I can't wait
Yes!
Are they cute? How do they look like?
Go check by yourself
Let's go!
Where are they?
In the school office
We have an impeccable record all along the time
If now we have the 4 boys in our school
I can't imagine what is going to happen
Nowadays many schools have gone co-ed
Why can't we do the same?
We just can't
You're over reacting, Miss Fong
We need students to keep the school going
I'm putting you in charge
Please keep an eye on them
I'd better get ready
Bye!
Call me!
We're roommates again!
We're in the same room!
Me too!
Your skirt is more than 2 inches above the knees
You broke the school rule!
How about this?
What are you eating?
Nothing
Miss Fong...
Ho Yat-Man, please come with me
Good morning teachers and students
Welcome to a new school term
This year is our school's 30th anniversary
I hope you'll adhere to the school's motto
Confucius once said...
Shit!
Mobile phone is not allowed in the classroom
Put it away!
My name is Dick, and you?
Let's get to know each other
My name is Lau Chek-bun
Ko Hon-keung and me were old classmates
What's your name?
Li Kwok-chung, call me Charlie. And you?
Ho Yat-Man
That's a nice name
Where are you going? To the toilet!
Wait for me!
Let's go!
Why must you follow us to the toilet?
Hurry back!
It depends...
What the heck! Where is it?
This is a girls' school
Not anymore
We're like unwelcome here
I won't be leaving
Hey, let's take a look over there
Alright...
Let's look at the menu
What menu?
Come on, idiot!
Thanks principal for giving
a significant instruction
Now I have an announcement to make
Our school will be different this year
We will have 4 boys in the school
Quiet... please be quiet!
I'm sure you'll remember
Our school main objective is to have
a good learning atmosphere...
Over here!
Keep a simple school spirit
and carry out our motto of pursuing the truth
You cannot...
You're not allowed to...
Quiet please!
I know him! It's Ben!
Our school rule Fong-fong
Falling in love is not allowed
$1,000 for this dorm?!
The girls' dorm looks much better
Are there any vacancies?
That's none of your business
The girls' dorm is off limits to you
You'll be expelled right away
if you break the rule
The superintendent must sure go to sleep...
That's me!
Normally I sleep late
Dare you to try?
Is there any boys' toilet here?
Yes, but not in use for a long time
We're cleaning it up now
I heard there's a haunted toilet here
It wouldn't be the same one, right?
Don't be stupid! That's nothing to do with us,
The school is not haunted
Here's a copy of the school rules
Memorize them by heart
Don't be late for class tomorrow
Any question?
If not, I'm leaving
Goodbye, Miss Fong
Have you heard any stories of this school?
Well no need to worry! Let's go!
Where are we going? What do we do next?
During lunch, there must be
lots of food in the canteen
Cool! Let's go!
Wait... let me put this down first
OK...
Before I forget
Your meals will be brought to you everyday
The canteen is also off-limits!
What? That's a jail sentence!
You either choose to withdraw or go by the rules
Better not break the Rule No. 2
I don't want to kick you out so soon
Let me out...
Come on! Tell me or I will
make you drink this shampoo
No...
Have you held Ben's hand before?
Or kiss him?
No!
He's just a classmate from grade school
Were you in love with him?
Tell me the truth or eat this soap!
You're so vicious!
I have never in love with him before
Fancy meeting you here
We have to prepare something for it, right?
See, here you are,
Spiral style sensation
This is from the U.S.! Thanks!
You knew it well,
You seem like the first one to use it
Why?
What about that Fong-fong?
She's my classmate from grade school
Didn't expect to run into her here
Do you have large size?
You don't need a large!
Give me back, idiot!
Hey, catch it!
You...
Try this, Yat-Man
It's an essence mask
I don't need it
Look! So dehydrated you are!
Use it after you shower, it's moisturizing
Cat puts this on her buttocks too!
I don't!
Try it!
Why were you with those boys today?
Miss Fong asked me to keep an eye on them
You were blushing
No, I was not! I just fell down
Did they touch you?
What?
It's normal, especially when you all fall down
I think Ko Hon-keung is cute
I'll take him if you don't
I'm interested in him! Just leave him to me
You can't compete! With what?
What's wrong with you?
Please don't force me to do anything to
you as you keep smoking over here!
Yat-Man, please don't do that!
Don't let her copy homework anymore
Ben, I need the laptop for my notes
Can I have it back?
School starts tomorrow!
Lay off your studies!
Have you ever been in love, Charlie?
You want a good start?
I don't mind to have a try
Practice makes perfect!
Then you must follow our words to do
Come here! Learn this good stuff
This was really an unbelievable movement!
That's nothing special
I have something better
Let's watch it together
Really? So Dick,
from now on other than Ko Hon-keung,
You're my buddy
Same here!
You can't smoke in here!
Mind your own business!
Please! I can't take smoke
Please smoke outside
Please...
We can't go out
after 11 p.m.
I'm already taking it outside
Shut your mouth!
My nose...
Miss Chung will be your home room teacher
Miss Fong, why are there only four of us here?
Because you're the only ones in the class
4 is good
We can focus on our studies
Next class is PE lesson
I'll be your PE teacher
Great!
Let's go
Where are you going?
Look at them
They are fumy
I go to toilet
Make it quick!
Why hula hoops? We should play volleyball
Shit!
Who is it?
Did you drop your cigarette?
Which one of us
is in the wrong toilet?
We're only in here to take a drag
Here, have one on me
I'm Dick, you are...?
Call me Si. You're from the boys' dorm?
That Miss Fong is a maniac!
Here you go!
I said it's my treat
I didn't ask for your number
Call me when you want to have fun,
Will see then...
Give me your number too
We can chat or SMS for keeping in touch
Si...
Go...
Are you alright?
Damn! Just left without a word!
Wow! So muscular and handsome
Miss... Let's go! The Head prefect is coming
That petite one is cute
Too short!
She suits you, Charlie
Go get her number...
What? Now?
Where are you going? Time for lunch!
Very well!
Let's eat!
What the hell is that?
Don't waste your food!
No, Keung
This pork chop is awful!
It's cold, stiff and salty!
You try this!
We have to complain to Miss Fong
Let him do the talking
Keung, you must talk to her
I really can't take this pork chop
Sometimes I really feel like we're in a zoo
It's alright! Just take it easy!
Who threw me the banana?
Fong-fong? You want me to eat this?
No! Look at it!
I'd rather look at you
Teacher is coming No
Call me!
What were they doing when you arrived?
Waiting for their food
Remember! From now on
I want to know
all their moves
I'll expel them
if they break the rules
I don't think it's a good idea...
Listen to me, Ho Yat-Man
There's a reason for every rule
You must listen to me, understand?
It must be 4, alright?
I'm going to practice boxing
She's gone!
Take your buddies to the forest
Let me talk to him!
Please do it with low profile,
If Keung can't make it,
the deal is off! Bye!
Don't say that! It's misleading!
You'll thank me for it!
Show me the stock!
You'll get fat, stupid!
That's not enough for you!
I'll go out for a smoke
Don't forget to dress up yourself nicely,
See you later! Bye!
OK
Are you coming?
You'd better not go
The deal will be off if you don't go!
Fong-fong is bringing 2 girls
to our welcoming party
That's a great chance
Don't screw it up please!
They're being friendly
Don't be such a prig
I'm talking to you
Please look at me!
Don't be such a party pooper
Take it easy
Keung, I ain't with Dick on this
But we just want some fun
It's not a crime! Come on!
Do you have a DC?
Yes
What are you doing here?
I didn't set foot inside
and it's before 11 p.m. I didn't break any rules
What do you want?
I came for you...
What for?
I wanted to tell you something
But didn't get the chance
612 I have nothing to say to you
Stay right there or I'll get Miss Fong
I'm here to talk to Ho Yat-Man
Listen up, everybody!
Just say what you want!
When I first met you
I felt you are pretty
Although you're pretentious
I knew you didn't mean to be
That's none of your business
Everyone also wants to get out
of that hideous uniform
And put on make-up to meet guys, right?
Are you done?
We can give it a try
What do you mean by that?
It means I hate snitches
I heard what Miss Fong and
you were talking in the forest
If any one of us gets kicked out
Everyone will get a copy of that picture
Don't you dare!
Want me to try?
Let's go!
Where are we going?
We're having a party with your pals
I'm warning you, Cat and Fong-fong are nice girls
Leave them alone!
They won't leave us alone!
I'll feel safer if you join us
Forget your punching bag
Do what normal girls do
You only live once!
There was a big fire 20 years ago
The disciplinary master died in the fire
but they never found her body
Soon after that, the Principal
hung himself on a tree
Which one?
That one right there!
Why did we still come here?
The most dangerous place is the safest
No one will look for us here
And it's just a rumor
Who knows if it's true?
Don't be scared!
I want to know more. Please carry on
Since then, the intercom kept summoning someone
to report to the school office
People who went there
either disappeared or were
found dead in the toilet
Some even jumped down from the school building,
Cat please report to the school office now!
You scared me!
Let's go if you scared!
You're late!
I brought you something
What?
Yat-Man!
Shit!
We ran into them
And just looked for a late snack
Don't tell Miss Fong
Please...
Why so scared? You see ghost?!
It is great that the head prefect comes to join us
So let's have fun!
Ben, what have you done to her?
She'll be taking my orders from now on
Let's take a picture for proof...
No, I mean as a souvenir
Take a photo
You didn't take that right, did you?
You told me not to, it was just the flash
Get in line!
1... 2... 3
You broke the rule, go!
Hurry up!
Come on...
10 All
5... 10
What do you want?
One more time...
I go first, listen
10... 5
Forget it, I'll take this swig
Cool! What a drinker!
I never thought of doing this
by challenging the school rules over here
The most dangerous place is the safest
Don't you know that?
There's a girl jumped down from the top and died
Even Miss Fong wouldn't come here
Is that true?
Of course! Do you know where she died?
Where?
Right here!
Don't scare me!
Hey! Stop... it's late, let's go
No, I'm just getting started
Let's go, before you get out of hand
Let's stay for awhile more
No, let's play that again tomorrow night
Hey! Stop it...
You expect me to hit the brakes now?
I have a boyfriend! Stop it!
You're lucky I fancy you, bitch
I maybe a slut, but I draw the line with you
Crazy
Come back!
Don't fool me around, bitch!
Go, hurry up!
Dick Chi-hang, report to the school office
School office! There is somebody there!
Hello! I'm here!
Dick Chi-hang, report to the school office now,
Dick Chi-hang
Come in
Principal
Thank you
About Dick Chi-hang's disappearance
I hope you'll keep it to yourselves
These officers are from Missing Person Unit
They want to ask you a few questions
It's odd, Dick left his things in the dorm
Where did he go?
No need to care about him
The officer also said that he's a druggie
Maybe he's too high and sneaked out
until he couldn't find his way home
Step aside...
Ben! Call an ambulance!
Sure...
Help me
Patients who are in a coma for over 20 years
seldom regain consciousness
You have to prepare
She's still in a bit of a daze
There she is!
Auntie!
It's me, Siu-yee!
Talk to her
It might be helped
Excuse me
Are you alright, Auntie?
Why so secretive? Exchanging gifts with Charlie?
No! I just borrow reference book from him
Just don't want anyone to misunderstand
You two are being naughty!
You're always on the phone! It must have something
It's the Head Prefect!
Did you get it?
Told you he's dedicated!
What a surprise...
They're not match at all! Let's go
Yat-man
What is it?
Look!
I'd like to hear what you have to say,
the school is...
Cut the bullshit!
I knew you want to expel me
It's all my faults
I'll take the fall, OK?
You think this is the triad deal
Even the triad can be reasonable!
Call up the Education Board
Is it a crime to take pictures
with a fellow classmate?
Look at this picture!
I didn't kiss her
She'll never let someone like me to kiss her
I want you to mop the floor after school
I'm not punishing you for the picture
It's your attitude
I have no right to stop you from taking pictures
I just don't want you to be regretful
This is obviously a prank
I'll punish whoever sent this
I wanted to see you because
I want to know who did that
Do you know?
Yat-man, tell me!
You'll be punished for withholding information
I don't know!
I thought you'd named Si
Miss Fong is very nice!
I was even worse than Si
before Form 3
I almost got kicked out for picking a fight
But Miss Fong was on my side
So you practice with a punching bag?
I need to ease my stress
Some people really had it coming
Thanks!
For what?
For taking the fall!
That's the least I can do
I don't want to be punched by you
Were you in the triad?
I don't know about before
But now I'm definitely not
You handle this floor
I'll take care of the downstairs
Rule No. 2, no smoking and drinking
Light out and in bed by 11 p.m.
No loitering
Rule No. 3, the following are off-limits...
Rule No. 4...
Dick!
What are you doing?
Help...
Dick!
What are you doing?
Yat-Man, Miss Fong expelled Si
Help...
Si, don't
Yat-Man has nothing to do with this
Nothing to do with her?
She's Miss Fong's running dog
She blabbed about my smoking,
drinking and my skirt
And I am the person who sent out that picture
Get out of the kitchen if you can't stand the heat
What you want to play on?
I'll go all the way with her
I'll strip her clothes and take pictures
Leave her naked on the stairway
Let people have a feast tomorrow
I want to scare her up only
Are you crazy?
Leave me alone!
Don't do this!
Stay out of this!
Stop it!
Lai Hei-si, report to the school office!
I thought you said the school is empty
It should be no one here
Lai Hei-si, report to the school office!
Who is it? Come out!
Man... we'd better go
I've never seen this school office
Are you crazy?
That was just a story!
Man, let's go!
Get lost!
It's just a room! How scary could it be?
Si! It's me!
Sorry! I was just kidding
You brought me here?
Don't take me to the school office
What school office?
No! The school office... no!
Calm down!
Follow me!
Sit down!
Wait here! Don't go away!
Don't go! Someone was calling my name
I told Man not to go, but he didn't listen
Wait here! I go get you some water
Who's Man?
My boyfriend...
Remember, don't open the doors
Don't go to the school office
What did you say?
Si...
Why are you here?
I saw someone coming in, so come and check it out
Did you see Si and her boyfriend?
No!
What happened?
I don't really know
They're missing
Help me look for them
Why there's two more shadow here?
Haunted Tales of Narranmoda Memorial School
Fong-fong couldn't find Si
Her mother hasn't seen her for the last few days
You saw her that night?
I don't know, I only know one thing
Someone knocked me out while I was boxing
and took me to the sick room
Then whoever did this disappeared
Every time someone disappeared
there will be a new shadow on the wall
Did Si see that missing school office?
What did you found from the internet?
Just some old stories
Shadows on the wall
and the hanging... wait!
Abide by school rules within the school
Falling in love is strictly prohibited
Run away if summoned to the school office
Whoever finds the inexistent school office
Burn it down at once
Chapter 20 of the "Book of Revelation"
And the devil that deceived them was
cast into the lake of fire and brimstone
where the beast and the false prophet are
and shall be tormented day
and night forever and ever
A Narranmoda Memorial School former student
I heard about this website before
but it was terribly done
Everyone thought it was a joke
We'll find out soon
Time to eat!
He has a sweet lunchbox
We have pork chops everyday
Thanks, Yat-man!
I don't feel like eating
Let's eat, I share mine with you
That's better
You don't want this, let me have it
Whatever...
Shit!
You have sashimi for lunch!
I meant to share it, but not now
This is from Cat!
Thanks
Cat is a smart girl
I know, Honey
No matter what
I'm doing this for her own good
I understand. She gets distracted easily
She should focus on her studies
I found her a school in Canada
Why is this happening?
Let's go...
Go
Why?
He's still crying. Ben is with him now
How's Cat?
She's packing up, and crying too
I told Miss Fong about them
I know
Am I wrong?
I'm scared! I don't want anything to happen to Cat
Will they be summoned to the school office?
I've never believed in it
But now I realize it has something wrong
I just want to tell you something
Sometimes things have happened
No one or nothing can stop it
So just don't let it happen
It's totally out of control
Maybe you don't even know it has happened
Charlie went to the girls' dorm,
Cat!
It's Charlie!
Cat! Come out!
I need talk to you!
I don't care if Miss Fong expels me
I really need talk to you
All I did was just study
I haven't tried anything at all
I don't know what's going on
for the past few months
But I know now
That's something happened between us
Or else we won't play, laugh and cry together
If nothing happened between us
a simple goodbye is good enough
Why did you just write me a letter? Why?
Come out, Cat! I'll pretend
I've never read that letter
Come out and tell me what's going on
Come out and say goodbye!
I don't know
I just know
it was something very, very special...
I mean it
Cat
Shit! Don't make it public!
No...
Charlie...
Where are we?
I don't know!
No gambling, drinking or smoking
Lights out and in bed by 11 p.m.
No loitering
Why are you here, Si?
You two are well behaved,
why both of you were here?
We also don't know
You both must have broken the rules
So did I... The disciplinary master said
I can go if I copy the rules 100 times
I'm working on it
I can go soon
Rule No. 4, school uniform is a spiritual symbol
All students must be neat and tidy
The skirt can't be more than
two inches above the knees
Anyone who broke the rules will
need to face the punishment
The skirt can't be more than
2 inches above the knees
I broke the rules
Run!
I'll never do it again... I broke the rules
Why you come back?
What now?
No...
No... I've been copying the rules...
Why did you break the rules?
I didn't... I really didn't
I didn't...
Yes we did
We broke the Rule No. 1
We have fallen in love
Don't be scared!
Cat
Come down!
Cat, don't scare me!
Please come down!
I broke the rules,
The disciplinary master wants to punish me
No, she won't! Please come down!
Come on!
No, she's standing behind me...
She's standing behind me...
Cat
Call the police!
Please don't die! Ben, call the police!
Do something!
Charlie
Why?
She's back!
Who killed Charlie and Cat?
Miss Fong, on that night
I heard you said "She's back"
Who's back?
The psychiatrist has already explained
You're all under too much pressure
It was a collective hallucination
Bullshit! Cat and Charlie were dead!
Right in front of us
That's not a hallucination!
Please, Miss Fong!
My Auntie was the school's music teacher
She was also the Principal's wife
She set the big fire 20 years ago
Because there was a new disciplinary master,
Yuen Si-yum
She set all the rules
She used to summon the
students to the school office
Nobody knows what punishment they'll face
My Uncle never interfered
You seduced my husband, bitch!
I'll burn you alive...
Let me out! Help!
What are you doing, Ping?
Open the door!
You broke the school rules, too!
You're screwing around within the school
They'd never found her body
No one knew if she was dead or alive
When the school re-opened,
weird things began to happen
I discovered the inexistent school office
I was secretly admiring a boy
but he liked another girl
That girl died one night
It was then when I found out
whoever broke the rules would
be summoned to the office
According to a website created by a former student
The only way to stop the curse
is to find the right location of the office
and burn it down
Was that you?
A priest taught me that
But after the renovation
Nobody knew where the original office was
Anyway
The school board has decided
to close down the school
That should be the end
Goodbye, Miss Fong
I hate that disciplinary master
Me too!
You're lucky you don't remember anything
I'll never forget that day
I really want to burn her again
That's the only way to save the students
Time for your medication!
Sit down! I'll take you for a walk later
Dick, Si, Cat, Charlie
Watch over us
We'll avenge your death!
Ho Yat-man, Ko Hon-keung, Lau Cheuk-bun
Plan A
Law Siu-fong, report to the school office
I have more if you need it
It's the holy water from the Cathedral
We'll finish her off!
Remember this
Mind your safety
Before we burn that school office
Don't open any door
Any door may lead to the office!
Ho Yat-man, Ko Hon-keung, Lau Cheuk-bun
We're here. Come and get us
We're already over broke the
rules by dress up like this,
Come and get us!
Behind you, Fong-fong!
Don't let go!
Help me!
Fong-fong! Let her out, bitch!
Calm down, Ben!
Go to plan B
What do you want? Stay away...
Remember how I used to pull your braids?
That's because I want to stay close to you
Ben!
Do you know when I was young
I didn't dare to tell my mom though I had a fever
I worried I couldn't see you
if I missed the school
When I met you again over here
I was so excited
I want to tell you
I'm really in love with you! It's true!
Follow me to the school office now!
I'm counting on you, Keung!
Fong-fong!
Yat-man!
Hurry up, Ko Hon-keung!
Run along!
Where's the lighter?
Look for it! Hurry up! She's catching up with Ben!
Shit! I can't open all the doors!
Did Keung get her?
The lighter!
Are you alright, Ben?
We burned the office!
I'm in the Biology lab
I'm coming to you
Sorry! Wrong one!
She's still here!
How did that happen?
Ben's walkie talkie!
What now?
Miss Fong said if we burn the office
We'll finish her off!
What now, Yat-man?
I don't know! Maybe that wasn't it!
Where's the real school office?
Fong-fong! Plan B!
Ben, I knew it
You were in love with me since grade school
I made sure Mom gave me braids
so you could pull them
Then I'd have an excuse to talk to you
When I found out you're coming
I was really happy
See? She's crazy about me!
Fong-fong, say it again!
It won't work! She'll know I'm lying
I hated him for pulling my braids
I was never in love with him!
Yuen Si-yum, come out!
Calm down, Ko Hon-keung
I was sent to a boys' home in Form 1
Everyone thinks I'm with the triad
Pick on a rotten student like me. Why Ben?
Let him go!
Calm down...
I don't want anyone to get hurt, especially you
We'll be fine
Are you alright?
Yat-man!
Calm down...
Follow me
Stay where you are! I'll go back for Yat-man
Ko Hon-keung
Yuen Si-yum, let her go!
She's always abided by the rules
She didn't do anything wrong
Why her?
I broke the rules
I fall in love with her
I'm saying this again,
I fall in love with Ho Yat-man
I have broken the cardinal rule
Come after me!
Don't believe him! He's lying
That was me falling in love with him! Was me!
Leave him alone! Punish me!
Run! Ko Hon-keung, run!
Yat-man!
Please run!
Come out! Yat-man
I won't love you
Yat-man!
No need to worry about me
Miss Fong, Yuen Si-yum got Ben
Only Ko Hon-keung is left to save Yat-man
Why did you come back?
Auntie, we're here
Do what you have to do
They took down one floor during renovation
Miss Fong!
Where is Yat-man?
Inside the school office
I won't let you harm my students
Yat-man... wake up
Yuen Si-yum, I hate you!
Don't mind us, run!
Are you alright?
Watch out!
Cat, Charlie
Keung, Yat-man, run!
Come one, Fong-fong is waiting outside
Is it true, what you said?
What?
You said you fall in love with me
It's true! What about you?
Are you telling the truth?
Yat-man!
You break the Rule No. 1
Falling in Love is not allowed