"Our adolescence is the season of love."
...is what everyone says.
Our hearts flutter. We feel restless.
And we're curious about boys.
Yes, we fall for someone.
That is the greatest mission for us girls.
But for girls, life is more complicated than just love.
And that's why...
I focus on friends instead.
Futaba!
- Good morning!
Long time no see!
Your seat is here.
- Here?
- Right behind me! Lucky!
Isn't she cute?
- She's cute!
- Right?
Who is it?
What was her name?
H-Hold on... Yoshioka. It's Yoshioka.
- Yoshioka?
- Yoshioka.
Our eyes met!
- Go talk to her!
- Me?
Hey!
- Oh, there it is.
- What are you doing?
Thaaat's not going to work.
- Isn't that Makita Yuuri? The girl you mentioned?
- Good morning.
Hey, Makita. You were in class 1-5, right?
You were Mikami's friend, too.
He said there was a really cute girl named Makita in class 1-5.
I'm not that cute!
That was so cute just now!
He even said she's--
Did you see those puppy dog eyes?
Why do guys like girls like Makita Yuuri?
It's like... she's stupid, or simple...
It's not like she's cute enough to say it, right?
Futaba, if you put a little work into being girly, you'd be popular.
Actually, you're just not feminine enough.
It's fine, it's fine!
I'm bad with boys, anyway.
- What's with that way of putting it?
- Right?
Futaba, have you been in love with someone before?
No! Never!
Hey, don't laugh! Don't laugh!
I just lied to them.
I think friends come first.
But this is the second year of high school!
In truth...
You've got no manners.
Tanaka-kun?
Huh? He's the transfer student in our class, right?
What is it, Futaba?
Sorry, go on ahead!
Hey!
- Tanaka-kun!
- Mabuchi!
- Hey.
- "Mabuchi"?
- School supplies?
- Yeah.
Then I guess I'll go with you.
That was close!
Somehow... I thought he looked like
the Tanaka-kun I knew when I was 13.
The rain started pretty suddenly, didn't it?
Tanaka-kun?
My name is Mabuchi.
I'm sorry! I made a mistake.
The rain started pretty suddenly, didn't it?
I knew it!
You're Tanaka-kun! Tanaka Kou-k--
I'm telling you, my name is Mabuchi.
I'm Mabuchi Kou now.
My parents got divorced.
I've been in Nagasaki ever since.
You're as dull as ever, aren't you?
I wondered when you'd figure it out.
Yeah, but... Tanaka-kun...
- you're completely different from bef--
- Again, I'm Mabuchi.
Well, how about a reunion hug?
I won't! I will not do that!
Tanaka-kun wouldn't sa--
He's gone.
Huh?
Tanaka Kou isn't here anymore.
Why has he changed that much?
Tanaka-kun wasn't the type to come on so strong...
He smiled a lot, and was very kind.
The rain started pretty suddenly, didn't it?
Ever since then,
whenever our eyes met, we'd look away.
What's going on?
Cops and robbers. Want to join?
Girls are playing, too?
...and look again.
And in the first summer vacation of middle school...
Summer Festival
7 o'clock.
At the clock in Sankaku Park.
At the clock...
in Sankaku Park.
I'm pretty sure that's what I heard.
But...
Tanaka-kun never came.
He never came to Sankaku Park, or to the festival.
Just like that, he never came.
Not even to school when the new semester started.
It'd be better if you had a bag, right?
It looks like I'm all out right now, hold on. Sorry!
It's okay!
Hey, you!
Hold on! Money!
Money!
I paid, though.
Don't try to fool me.
You were just trying to run off.
No!
Seriously, what a slimy person.
Hey, someone call the discipline officer!
No... I did, right?
Give it up, Futaba.
Just apologize and pay her.
Uh...
- Um...
- She paid.
Huh?
I saw it, too.
Get out of my way.
Mabuchi is right. I saw it, too!
Yeah?
She paid me just a second ago.
- What? Did she?
- Yeah.
How could I have known? Then you can go.
You're so mean, old lady.
Terrible.
Are you letting out your stress?
That's not what you should be saying.
You lot, and you too.
Apologize.
S-s-s-sorry.
Excuse me!
Thank you.
It's nothing.
That wasn't right no matter how you think about it.
Yeah.
But you got mad for my sake, so I feel better.
If something that small makes you
feel better, then you come cheap.
Being like that would make your friendships come cheap, too.
Friendships are more important to me, anyway.
That would be making pretend friends.
They're trivial.
Mabuchi! Mabudachi!
[pun - mabudachi means "a close friend"]
Thanks to you,
I got to talk to Murao Shuuko!
Thanks!
But... even if they're pretend friends,
it's a lot better than being on my own.
Hey.
If you'd like...
Thank you!
I'm sorry about back then.
I was the closest to you, and even saw it...
It's okay! It's fine!
But thanks for this.
It looks good!
Hey, why are you getting involved with someone like her?
Eating her bentou on her own is so strange.
Wouldn't it be nice if the boys talked to her?
And you know, a heart being on that cake...
is so pathetic.
["itai" - "hurt" has been taking on a slang meaning]
Seriously.
She's just putting on a cute act for the boys.
- She's pretty sly.
- Isn't she?
Being like that would make your friendships come cheap, too.
But being sly...
wouldn't that just mean that you want people to care about you?
If so, maybe we should act that way, too.
That's not the point.
I just hate girls like her.
If you hate her, you can just ignore her.
You're just so envious of her you can't ignore her!
What is this? I'm in such a bad mood now.
Where are your friends?
Tanaka-kun, you... !
Is it my fault?
No.
It's my own.
I was venting just now.
Sorry.
Actually...
in middle school...
just like Yuuri right now...
I was left out.
After you were gone,
I was always alone.
That's why
I thought I'd make high school better.
I have been...
lying to myself.
So that I can get along with people.
And that's why...
things ended this easily.
-- homework isn't done!
Seriously? It's due tomorrow!
Hurry up and finish!
Look at that.
Don't get all flirty in the school.
Are you stupid? Nothing is over yet.
You haven't even started yet, have you?
Also, give it a rest. Stop calling me Tanaka.
Kou!
You're dropping the honorific that suddenly?
Thank you!
The 5 students selected as the class leaders
are expected every year
to participate in the spring's leader orientation.
Tanaka-sensei will explain the details of the orientation.
Okay.
In Leader Orientation, the leaders of each class lodge together
to strengthen their interpersonal networks
and create a plan for the year's events.
The athletic festival, school festival, field trips...
One year of life in high school is busy and will pass quickly,
but what kind of life it will be is up to you all.
On that note, is there anyone who is up to the task?
Right.
I haven't even started anything yet.
In that case, I have to try starting something!
Yes!
Yes! I'll do it too.
I will, too.
Yes, yes! I will also do it!
And Mabuchi-kun, too!
- Hey, what are--
- I already said it!
Seriously?
For two days, starting today,
you will be sleeping and eating
together as part of Leader Orientation.
Listen up. You are preparing to be able
to help everyone in your classes.
Okay!
- I'll carry that! Your hands will get dirty.
- I'm wearing gloves so I'll be fine.
Thank you.
I know the thing that you're hiding, Sensei.
Hm?
The mole in your double eyelid.
This?
You're the first one to realize it, Murao.
Then... don't tell anyone but me about it.
Ever.
I can't make a promise like that.
Here, head back over to where everyone else is.
Mabuchi.
What was that?
Wouldn't it be... that?
Hey, help me... with this.
You can handle that just fine, Yoshioka.
Ow!
You alright?
It's okay, I'll do it. Have a seat.
Thank you.
What's with him?
Kominato-kun, carry the firewood.
And at tonight's meeting, we're going over
"the significance of school events"
so we'll all do the sheet together.
Murao-san! Later on--
I have a bit of a headache.
Are you alright, Yoshioka-san?
I'm Kikuchi from class 6.
Class 2 seems to be difficult.
Yeah.
But I volunteered to do it, so...
It's one of those "if I don't give it my all, what then?" things.
I don't think carrying all of the burden is all there is to leadership, though.
I'll carry these, okay?
Class 6.
Yes.
The significance of school events
is to set up plans for events that cannot
be completed except as a group.
We need to improve the sense of belonging that everyone has.
In relation to the sense of self, doing things with others
will help reshape each person's
position, responsibility, and behavior.
If we consider that the desired result of the events,
then this will lead us to far better school events.
- Crap...
Wonderful!
Then next will be class 2.
Yes.
Uh...
The goal of school events...
is...
to create memories... of fun times.
That's all.
Are you an elementary student?
You came up with that yourself, right?
Class 2 is starting out like that, then.
Today you will have no free time. Be sure
you think of something together.
Present something before orientation ends.
Okay, class 4 next.
Yes.
The significance of school events
is to hold events that give us the ability to adapt to society--
Her writing is messy, too.
It's pretty.
It's hard to tell if it's morning or night.
Kind of like you.
Huh?
Whether you're mean
or kind.
I can't tell.
You're the same, aren't you?
Weak or strong-willed.
But I think...
being a leader is too much for me.
Isn't that just fine?
Nobody will be troubled if you feel defeated so soon.
I think that was good.
Creating memories of fun times.
School events are... you know.
Long after they're done, when you remember them,
and the things you experienced with everyone else...
It's just fine if you all make those happy memories.
Something like that.
I see.
Right!
Huh? Where's Futaba?
Oh, you did one.
Hey, do you know where Mabuchi went?
Hey now. Aren't you guys being too distant?
It's so pretty!
Here we are. The start of a new day.
Yeah.
I...
will never forget this sunrise we're all seeing together!
Me neither!
This is "Aoharu"! Aoharu.
We'll ride out adolescence together!
["aoharu" is another way to read "seishun", adolescence]
Hey, you guys...
You're done if this makes you embarrassed.
Things like growing cold can wait until we're old men and women!
You don't seem like you'll change even
when you're an old man, Kominato-kun.
You're really loudmouthed in that way.
Hey, wait... can you not say loudmouthed?
Being called loudmouthed is painful. But right now--
Would these be pretend friendships, too?
After that, the leadership group fell under Kominato Rule.
Whether there's something to do or not,
we get together once per week.
We did say that, right?
You did all on your own.
Anyway, come without missing any.
Your attendance is too low.
Coming or not as you please...
are you a kindergartener?
Okay, on that note, just like it says
- there are meetings everywhere.
- You're all really at it.
Hey.
The orientation report for the school's newsletter...
I want to have one of you do it. Anyone?
I have cram school...
Then I'll--
Kou! You're good at writing, right?
Huh?
This is my chance to walk home with Shuuko. Let it happen.
I'll handle it.
- I've got it.
- Thanks.
No, if you do it, it will be like an elementary student did it.
I said I'll do it, so I'll do it.
No, your writing is messy too.
I can write clearly.
- You won't finish it before the end of the day.
- I will! Give it back!
- Forget it! Lend me your lead pencil.
- Futaba-chan.
- Hm?
What do you think of Mabuchi-kun?
I...
think I've fallen for him.
Oh, I see!
I have a feeling that you like him, too.
No, no, no, no!
We just went to the same middle
school. His attitude is so poor...
He has that air of, "Aren't I so cool for not putting in my all?"
So now I don't...
Just now?
Not then and not now.
Never. At all.
Really? That's good!
I was scared.
I had no idea what I'd do if you were a rival.
- I won't be! Oh, hey, you're going to be late for cram school.
Yeah.
Right,
it's not that I like him.
Just...
His bony hands...
and his fairly clear handwriting...
and being able to barely see his eyes behind his bangs...
these are all more interesting to me than they were before.
That's the same habit you had before!
Do you...
like me?
What are you--
That's not what I mean! You're so different from before
so I wonder why you've changed so much.
Sorry.
Don't try and find the old me.
That would be seriously annoying.
You'll be a loser forever if you clutch your memories like that.
I definitely do not like him!
- Where's Mabuchi?
- I made him go home.
Why are you here?
You said...
you're going to hand that in, and to go on ahead.
I meant for you to go on home, though.
Are you thinking that I thought I said
too much and would wait for you--
I'm not.
Well... whatever.
We're going.
I'm sorry, Yuuri.
I, too...
like Kou.
At first, seeing him again...
I thought that I didn't like the new Kou.
But I realized that I was lying to myself.
Thanks to you, Yuuri.
I knew it! You too, Futaba-chan.
I thought so.
Then... no matter who things go well for,
let's not hold it against each other, okay?
But I don't think it'll work out for me if it's you.
Yuuri...
Oh, I'm going to the bathroom.
I was... actually scared to say it.
I thought that if I said it...
I'd lose a precious friend I'd finally made.
But I also thought that I have to say it
precisely because she's a precious friend.
I'm back.
I'm feeling hungry... maybe we should eat something.
I like Tanaka-sensei.
Why are you... so suddenly...?
It's just...
I thought that I could say it if it were to you two.
Well, Mabuchi is the one who has to decide, though.
He might even turn you both down.
And if it goes well for one of you...
I'll always be neutral to both of you.
Both of you, do your best.
So you see... the problem is Tanaka-sensei, after all.
I don't understand the feelings of women who fall for older guys!
I'm the one who has tighter skin! Right?
Hey, are you listening?! Hey!
Hey, Kominato.
You're as loud as ever.
Stop messing around and study a little.
You'll bring down the number of graduates.
The guy next to him... he was at Nagasaki Seiran High.
Really? Coming here from that Seiran isn't special at all.
Did something happen?
- Like he couldn't keep up?
- Seiran isn't a big deal, either.
Hey.
You guys need to get a grip.
He had nothing to do with it.
And why are you the one getting mad?
What are you talking about?
If your friend were getting spoken
to like this, you'd be pissed too.
Get out of here.
Hey, let's go.
What's with him?
Kou!
What is it?
Nothing.
I...
have given up looking for the old Kou.
Huh?
I want to get to know the new Kou.
Everything that I don't know from the
4 years you were in Nagasaki.
Hey, why did you come back here?
This and that.
Are you living in the same place?
Yeah.
With your mom?
No.
- Why?
-It doesn't matter, does it?
It has nothing to do with you.
It doesn't have nothing to do with me!
Suddenly going away, and then suddenly reappearing...
There are actually so many things that I want to ask you!
I'm asking you because I haven't sorted it all out in my head yet!
Please just... don't step into other people's
space any more than you already have.
Sooo hot!
Is Kou ditching the meeting again?
Forget that... why in summer vacation, too?
And at your house.
You know, the festival and field trip are soon
after the new semester starts.
What will happen if we don't do this now?
I wonder if something happened to Mabuchi-kun.
He hasn't replied on LINE, either.
[Japanese messaging app]
It's like he's avoiding us.
Tanaka, Mabuchi
Yes!
Yoshioka!
Tanaka-sensei!
Why...?
Kou is actually... my little brother.
Your brother?!
We're trying to keep life simple at school
by keeping it secret from the students, though.
But I want to ask about Kou, too.
He shows you a little bit of expression, after all.
Here.
In his first year of middle school,
our parents divorced, and I stayed here with our dad.
Kou went to our mom's parents' place in Nagasaki with her.
Why did he come back here?
Last year... of an illness.
He came back here because of that.
I couldn't be with him when life was at its hardest.
How about some other family?
I'm the only one who can be with her right now.
Her lung cancer is progressing.
We can consider it to be in its final stages.
Her back pain is most likely due to her bones changing.
I'm sorry to say it, but...
The results seem to have been good.
Oh?
How is your back pain?
It's alright.
Don't worry about me. Get home and study.
Kou is hiding it,
but I might not make it.
If something happens, Youichi,
take care of Kou.
I...
couldn't handle seeing her emaciated body.
I made excuses like work, or Nagasaki being too far.
I pushed everything onto Kou.
I'm sorry!
But it seems...
Kou couldn't forgive himself for being unable to help.
Mom!
He got absorbed in other things,
and started thinking that he just isn't allowed to enjoy himself.
He's been
carrying feelings like that the whole time.
He's actually a kind, good guy.
That's why--
I know.
I see.
My brother told you.
When I left for Nagasaki,
I made him a promise.
A promise that I would take care of our mom.
I gave him my word that I'd support her. Like a child.
I put my all into my studies, too.
So she could live in comfort once I became a doctor.
I didn't even realize that she was ill.
It's laughable.
At the side of my mother growing thinner and thinner,
every day,
as if she were already prepared to leave this world...
what was I thinking?
You don't understand, do you?
You don't need to understand.
You get tired of a lot of things
when you find things important to you.
Kou!
I don't understand!
I don't... not one bit! But...
Is wanting to understand from the bottom of my heart not okay?
Being scared of losing what's important to you
is pointless if you distance yourself from us all!
Because...
for us, you've already...
become someone really important!
That's why if you get absorbed in something,
and someone gives you
a hard time for enjoying yourself...
We can't forgive him!
If there's someone like that,
even if it's your mom,
I'll beat that person up!
Kou?
Don't pull away yet.
Then...
Yeah.
Summer Festival
7 o'clock.
At the clock in Sankaku Park.
You didn't say anything except that, so...
I thought, "that wasn't a date..."
and sobbed at the park.
7 o'clock.
At the clock in Sankaku Park.
Yeah, that.
That was...
meant as a new promise to you.
Shall we go this time?
To the summer festival.
Okay!
I can rewrite what happened that day 4 years ago!
I'll tell him!
This time, I'll tell Kou that I like him!
Hello, Kou? Where are you?
Sorry.
Something came up that I can't get away from.
Uhh... what time can you make it?
I'll wait until whenever that is!
Can't make it. I'm actually in Nagasaki right now.
Nagasaki?
Kou-chan? What is it?
I wasn't able to get a hold of Kou after that day.
I was just wondering, "Is it second semester yet?"
and was scared that Kou would disappear somewhere again.
Kou.
Hi.
Um... about that.
We have... a meeting today.
I'll pass for today. Can't make it.
Mabuchi seems strange since second semester started...
He doesn't even come to our meetings at all.
I've been saying we need to prepare
for the culture festival, but it's all on LINE.
Kominato, do you know if he's seeing someone?
No... if I ask him, he just dodges the question.
But it does sound like it's a girl. One from his time in Nagasaki.
These are cute!
Hey, Futaba-chan.
I actually confessed to Mabuchi during summer vacation.
I thought I'd try and get a leg up on you, but he turned me down.
At that time, he told me there's someone he can't leave alone.
I was convinced that it was you...
Your nails are so small.
How about having a seat?
Okay.
You don't need to answer that?
There's a lot going on with an old classmate from Nagasaki.
The calls just keep coming.
Oh.
To make up for the summer festival,
want to do something now?
If you don't want to, it's okay.
Let's do it!
Narumi
Hello?
Now?
Sorry... it's that classmate.
Another time, okay?
Kikuchi-kun?
Are you okay?
Your boyfriend just left... was there a fight?
No, no. He's not my boyfriend.
That so?
It turns out I'll be living with my mom.
So I'll be heading out your way.
We can see each other again.
Oh? That's good.
Yeah.
Oh, right. That DVD I borrowed from you before--
Sorry.
Can we talk about that later?
I'm going to give priority to that friend
I made a promise with first.
Everyone, are you having a good time?
The theme for this year's Sakigaya festival is markets.
Please enjoy all the stalls representing
countries from around the world!
Want to try doing a before-and-after comparison?
[makeup]
The match to decide the best arm wrestler is right here!
Welcome back, Master!
[intentionally sounding cute]
You speak out, too!
Kominato, you need to put on some pants. It's creepy.
I can't let myself lose to Shuuko.
Is this the same as what you ordered?
- Yes.
- Yes!
Thank you very much.
Please enjoy yourselves here.
Shuuko-chan suits the masculine clothing too well!
This is such a success!
Kominato's idea of doing reverse maids and butlers is such a hit!
- One waffle...
- One waffle!
Kou-chan!
You didn't get lost on the way?
I didn't. That's some outfit you're wearing!
- Come in.
- Okay.
I'll introduce you.
She's a middle-school classmate from Nagasaki.
I'm Narumi Yui.
Hello.
Hi.
Sit over there.
Sure.
The appearance of a girl from his 4 years away, then.
I'll show you around later. Want a drink?
Something that you recommend.
Oh, but you have a sweet tooth, right?
Yoshioka.
She'll have one Kominato Special.
Okay.
Yuuri, can you hold this?
Yoshioka-san, you look great as a butler!
Oh, well, that's because I'm not very feminine.
But, Yoshioka-san, you're such a girl.
Here.
Come to the stage at the end. We're
just a thrown-together band, though.
W-What? What is this? These people jumping into the picture?
[a cover of My Favorite Song by Ellegarden]
I had fun today.
Thanks.
Do you have class tomorrow, too?
Yeah.
Yoshioka-san!
Crap, the mic was on.
Nice, Kikuchi!
Kou-chan.
There's a train. I need to hurry.
Then we'll stop here.
[cover of Kaze no Hi by Ellegarden]
That--
Like I said,
I had to cancel our summer plans at the
last second, right? To make up for that.
Kou!
You still have cleaning up to do! Kou!
Again, about back then...
Please take the filled boxes of equipment to the leaders' room.
Why are you running away from me?
Don't worry about that. It was an accident.
What?! What is it?!
- Why are you mad?
- I'm not!
You are!
I'm not mad...
It was... meaningless...
Neither of us meant to. It was an accident.
It's the same as if it never happened.
Then...
is it okay if it isn't an accident?
If you don't want to, you can pull away.
For canceling our plans at the last second...
I'm sorry.
That night
was Narumi's father's wake.
Her parents are divorced as well
and her dad had been looking after her.
Telling something like that to you would be... you know.
Is Narumi-san
someone special to you?
A friend.
But I understand how she's feeling right now better than anyone else.
Yeah. You would.
It's... space I shouldn't step into, right?
What do you mean, "space"?
You know... before you get all soaked in sentimentality, help with cleaning up!
Seriously... thanks to your slightly triangular relationship...
Hello?
Kou? Do you know a girl named Narumi Yui?
Yeah.
Narumi is a classmate from Nagasaki.
The police were asking about her at school.
It seems she came here to visit
in order to run away from home.
Run away?
She's been staying with a relative since her father died, right?
But she told me she's going to live with her mother here.
No.
Her mother seems to have said no.
Her mom has a new family.
She was taken into custody.
Since she had something from our festival, the police called us.
I listened to the story, and she says she's a friend of yours.
The police.
Let's go.
If I said it was all...
on purpose...
what would you do, Kou-chan?
It's okay.
I understand.
Kou!
It's red.
It seems that until her family decides where she'll
be staying, her mother will take care of her.
I'll take her there.
Thanks. Please do.
Go ahead.
Why...
did you kiss me?
Sorry.
I got caught up in the mood.
Liar.
Right now is the time when the season is changing,
so I think there are people here who can't quite get in the mood.
What happened to Mabuchi-kun?
He's been off for a week already.
Narumi-cchi seems to have it pretty
rough staying with her mother.
So he's taking care of her.
Her relatives are still arguing over who is going to keep her.
I wonder what Mabuchi-kun will do if she has nowhere to go?
He might feel he has to take care of girls who feel that weak.
Their circumstances are even similar.
I...
want to take back Kou's smile.
This is about Kou-chan, right?
I would like you to let him go.
I know that you are having trouble right now,
and that there is a pain only you and he understand.
But...
When he is with you,
time stops for him.
We had finally started making progress, and...
I don't want to.
I don't have anyone but Kou-chan.
I want him with me no matter what.
I'll do anything if it's for that.
If acting all righteous to try and trick us
is as far as your feelings go, then you
are the one who needs to give up.
Yoshioka-san.
You only came to complain to me out of desperation
because the thought of losing Kou-chan is too painful, right?
This delusion that time stops for him when he's around me
is to try and push me away!
I...
just wanted to come up with a
reason not give up on Kou.
I'm pretty stubborn, aren't I?
Futaba.
Don't go thinking strange things.
Today, I was dropping off some papers
and a guy saw me opening a door with my feet.
Another person driven away by my mannerisms.
Habits are really hard to get rid of, aren't they?
You're missing a button there.
I like you.
Kou,
I came to you so you could clearly turn me down.
So that I can come to terms with a broken heart,
I want you to turn me down properly.
I... can't date you, Yoshioka.
That clears it up.
Thank you.
But we'll stay friends after this, too, okay?
Are you having flashbacks?
Yeah.
For no reason.
I just suddenly remember things.
I remember things I hate like sounds,
and places,
and they're in color.
What about you, Kou-chan?
Does something like this not happen to you?
Oh.
That's good.
Is he going to pick you up?
Your uncle in Nagasaki.
He's going to look after me until I graduate high school.
Don't worry about me.
Listen,
Narumi...
Kou-chan, I'm the only one
who understands you.
- Morning. - Morning.
Morning!
- Morning.
- Morning!
Yoshioka-san, the aura around you
has changed lately, hasn't it?
Or is it... you're changing it?
Yeah. I've decided to graduate from being the way I was.
I'll lose 1.5kg, stop running with huge
strides, and stop my bursts of laughter.
I'll be more feminine so that I'm more popular.
Is this to spite Mabuchi?
I thought that if he clearly turned me down,
I would be able to move forward.
But I'm not doing that at all, am I?
Actually,
I don't know
how to move forward.
Or what to do.
You finally looked at me.
Looking somewhere is what it is to move forward.
That's fine, isn't it?
I don't think you need to force it.
Because there's someone right in front of you telling
you that Yoshioka-san is fine the way she is.
What I'm saying is that I like you, Yoshioka-san.
But... I don't really know you very well.
You can get to know me starting today.
I'm saying this about myself, but... I can recommend me.
Are you okay?
That's the first time anyone has said they like me.
So?
Do you think you can come to like him, too?
I'm not sure.
But when I'm with Kikuchi,
I can feel a little progress.
Also,
I think that if I'm with Kikuchi-kun, I can
get rid of Kou's memory sooner.
I see.
I'm not very confident about it, though!
Kikuchi is going to take Yoshioka away from you.
He can do what he wants.
There isn't anything
between Yoshioka and me.
How's that? You were just grinding your teeth like crazy.
Don't make yourself match Narumi-cchi's moods.
- I'm not matching or feeling for her.
- Then what is it?
People who can't consider their own happiness
shouldn't be proud of supporting other people.
You're such a nice guy it rubs off on people.
Being with you, I had a feeling I could go back to the old me.
But then things came up with Narumi.
I then realized I really couldn't forgive myself.
That's why, until Narumi can stand on her own two feet,
I decided I'll be responsible for her.
Thanks for being concerned.
The only one getting heated up was me.
To the point our moods were so
different I couldn't get anything across.
I'm seriously lame.
I don't think you're very lame at all.
Are you saying I'm coo--
I'm not.
Right.
It's frustrating.
I wonder how things would be if we had met sooner.
If we did,
I could have been around when things were hardest for him.
I wanted to do something for him.
You still can, can't you?
There's still something you can do, right?
[plan outline for a free day during field trip to Kyuushuu]
This is a field trip that will round out the year,
but to keep you from first saying "Kyuushuu
is large, fun, and has delicious food!"
and then letting loose, every class must follow
the plan that they submitted for their free days.
Okay?
Sensei!
What is it?
Can I change our plan right now?
Nagasaki?
Don't be suspicious of it.
This isn't about what happened there for you.
This is about your knowing good places to go for a date there.
Huh?
If you're thankful for anything I've done, help me out.
So that things start going well between Shuuko and I.
Please!
Narumi: Is class done?
Are things going well with your uncle and the others?
Narumi: They're alright.
How's the new school?
Made any friends?
Kou-chan: We're going to Nagasaki for our trip. Let's meet up.
Yui, what is it?
What, a boyfriend? Good for you!
- Bye.
- Byebye.
Good work!
Byebye!
Do you need something?
Here.
Thanks.
Sorry to have bothered you.
Unlike him, I won't let go of you.
When I'm in a large group of people,
I always end up
unconsciously trying to find you.
Even if I get the wrong person, I look for you.
And when I'm trying to find you,
no matter how big the group is,
I somehow find you first.
I wonder if that's what it is to fall in love.
Good morning, Yoshioka-san.
Good morning, Kikuchi-kun.
The first day of our trip! Let's get really into it!
Have we finished changing seats around?
Have your expectations been met?
This time, for our trip,
we'll be shuffling around the seats!
We'll be shuffling!
You may not know who you'll be sitting next to.
Does his little trick seem like it's on purpose?
He's doing the best he can in his own way, I'd think.
But...
I wonder if it will go well.
Welcome!
Kominato-kun.
Is Kou alright?
With Nagasaki.
I'm counting on you to take care of Kou.
You plan to sneak out to see Narumi-cchi?
What the hell is with you?
That hurt.
I didn't go through the trouble of getting us
to Nagasaki so you could do that, you idiot!
You're an idiot. Seriously. An idiot.
What do you mean, "the trouble"?
The trip's plan.
The reason that I had it changed to Nagasaki.
No, I can't do it.
If we're going to fight the past, you're
the only one who can take that place.
You're the only one who knows the old Mabuchi.
But I have plans with Kikuchi-kun.
And...
Kou going to that place...
It'll never work.
The one who can get him there
is the class leader. You, Yoshioka Futaba.
You said that you want to take back Mabuchi's smile, right?
Was that a lie?
We feel the same way.
Hey, Kou.
Can you really not forgive yourself?
How about making sure of that?
Before meeting up with Narumi-cchi,
at least kick away the past first.
That's what we're asking of you.
Okay, don't be late for meeting back up!
Everyone, make sure you come back!
Please let me take Futaba-chan for the day.
If one of your friends was sending out a distress signal,
you would go save that friend, right?
Kou.
You're late.
Kominato...
I'm leaving.
Spineless.
You've only grown taller. How sad.
You really don't look like, and aren't like, Tanaka-kun.
I said Tanaka is--
Always dragging along and whining about stuff in the past...
You're a loser yourself, Kou.
What do you think you--
Bedsores that got worse every day
and so much vomit you know the end is coming.
In the end, she couldn't even remember
your name, let alone your face.
After hearing about your mom,
I've studied a lot about her illness.
I asked Tanaka-sensei a lot of questions.
And after all that, I still couldn't get
any closer to the severity of your sadness.
I didn't understand. I was frustrated.
My desire to understand still hasn't changed.
I said you don't need to know these things, didn't I?
Her voice was getting hoarse back then.
Kou, how about eating together downstairs?
It's fine. I want to finish this.
Then... I'll leave it here.
Don't work too hard.
Okay.
I...
wonder why I didn't realize.
I wonder where I went wrong.
Is everything over after only one mistake?
There aren't any people who take the right path every time.
Come with me
and make sure...
of whether or not you really did make a mistake.
Come.
I said come!
That hurts!
You're alright!
No matter what happens, I'll help you.
I promised you, right?
That if there were somebody giving you a hard time,
I would beat that person up.
Come on.
This is the area I lived in for 4 years.
Yeah.
When I first came here with my mom,
I didn't speak for a long time.
Kou, it's heavy, right?
I'll carry some.
But she kept talking to me.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Actually, I'll just eat here.
There wasn't a girl you liked there?
How is it?
This is strange.
I wonder why,
but I can only remember her smiling face.
Mabuchi-san?
You've come back?
He's the priest.
My mom came here a lot.
In hopes she would get better.
Your mother
never once prayed for herself.
Every day,
she came here
to pray for you.
I pray that Kou has fun at his new school.
I pray that Kou remains healthy.
I pray that Kou grows to be a kind-hearted person.
I pray that Kou finds people important to him.
I pray that Kou...
lives his life with a smile.
Not asking for her own sake...
is what it is to be a mother.
Sorry.
It's okay.
You did come, after all.
I...
couldn't move forward, after all.
Kikuchi-kun, you said...
that you see me first
no matter where we are, right?
Yeah.
But...
Back then and even now, what I see first
has always been Kou's back.
I'm sorry.
I knew that.
I knew that you, without hesitation,
would always go straight after Mabuchi.
But that being the way you are
is exactly why I fell for you.
This is me being a bad loser.
Kikuchi-kun...
I...
I wonder if those two are okay.
Hey.
- You lot.
- Crap.
What is it?
Leave the rest to me.
Come back before breakfast.
Kou: I want you to come out with me one more time.
I want to see the sunrise with everyone.
We'll make a good memory!
[Number withheld]
Yes, hello?
Yoshioka-san?
When Kou-chan transferred here 4 years ago,
he was wearing a uniform that was different from everybody else's.
He was short, too.
He was always alone, and never fit in with other people.
After school, he would stay at his art class desk
and write graffiti on it while he was alone.
He wrote so many girly things.
Sankaku Park.
7 o'clock.
Start his clock up again for him.
Yoshioka Futaba
Even if we just stay friends!
As long as Kou will smile for me, it's okay!
One more time...
If all of us can just see
that sunrise one more time!
Everyone's pretty late.
Yeah.
Was it really okay for us to not go?
This, too, is what friendship means.
Here.
Thanks.
Coming all the way here might have been a pretty big detour.
Detours are what makes this Aoharu.
Yeah, loudmouthed.
This is cold!
No, too loud.
Look! It's getting bright!
Hey, look! Kou!
Kou?
Are you cold?
Are you okay?
I might die like this. Leave me here.
Ow!
I give! Uncle!
Sorry.
In the first year of middle school,
I liked you.
When I was in the jail in cops and robbers,
you ran straight to me to get me out.
Tanaka-kun!
I'm getting you out!
But before you could, you fell straight down.
My sides hurt just remembering it!
Like you said,
I'm the loser for desperately clinging to my memories.
I love you.
I did then, and I do now. Always did.
You're okay with someone like me?
I don't know.
I've never liked anyone but you,
so I don't know.
But you're, you know...
my...
hero.
Euphoric Translations
Translation/Timing: Stythe
QC: Thule
www.euphorictranslations.com
We'll be at the airport soon.
Make sure you're not leaving anything behind!
Okay!
Also,
Mistakes are always made in our adolescence,
but...
it's adolescence exactly because there are mistakes.