The Japan Broadcasting System hired Android Announcer: Maico.
Her voic gives love, courage, and life to the dwindling 21st century radio scene.
Things are only at the beginning!
Man, STAR's autograph is so cool!
So groovy!
So quick!
It's just writing, yet it's still great!
Hey, don't you think so?
Quit goofing around and finish up the script, please.
I know.
Leave it to me.
I will quickly write a shining script like STAR.
STAR, STAR, STAR...
Suga is finally getting serious.
Maybe I can expect the replay of that legend from 10 years ago, Live! from the North Pole Crossing!
There's one unfortunate woman over here too.
Don't mind her.
They were in completely differnt universes.
Time will solve the problem.
But it was still cool.
Since STAR came in, the program has been getting record-breaking listener ratings.
I'd like to be like STAR-san too.
Yeah, that's the spirit.
Yes.
STAR, huh?
He was absolutely real.
Like Suga, we need to shine too.
Man, I'm bored.
It's too early!
Ouch!
Gentlemen, quit fighting and get back to work...
Yes?
This is Kacchin, elite member of the Japan Broadcasting System.
Oh, Katsumi.
Who would say that about himself?
Don't say that.
I'm telling you, we'll talk about that later.
I don't care which.
I know! I do think about it!
I Want to See You Right Now
It was my fault.
I'll hear you out later.
I'm hanging up, okay?
Yes, I love you too.
Now, I should organize my papers.
Was that your girlfriend, Kacchin?
Oh, uh...
So Kacchin-san has a girlfriend?
I'll input that in my memory.
You actually got one?
Don't underestimate me.
That woman must have given up on life.
What is that supposed to mean?
Falling in love with a man who has no self-direction and who is always sucking up to other people will only make her unhappy.
She'll be crying later on.
Well, sure.
The number of women I've forced to cry number as many as there are stars.
See? There's another one.
Quit lying!
Kacchin-san, you're terrible!
Hey, that's...
Maico-chan's "Don't be naughty" system!
Nice punch.
Kacchin-san, you're awful!
Well, you're a rude android.
I was actually well-known as "Fast-Eater, Kacchin."
What, Kacchin? You got a woman?
That's cool.
Well, yeah.
People call her shy and cute.
You're lying!
Don't say that while smiling.
Well, that's okay.
Kachi-ko, that phone call earlier was from your woman, wasn't it?
Well, that's...
She's shy and cute, so she's popular, right?
Of course.
She's wonderful beauty, who would even trigger the STAR detector.
That's great.
Our almighty elite P.R. officer.
Ume-san, give him a big one.
Congrats!Congrats! Congrats!
Congrats! Congrats! Congrats!
That's great.
Yes, it's great.
Well, I guess.
I was already popular with Hana-chan and Kiku-chan during kindergarten.
My locker was full of love letters in my elementrary school days.
It was so bad that our homeroom teacher had to tell the girls to save their paper!
Do you think it's real?
During my junior high years, I got fell into a small slump.
He is slightly stuttering.
So he is lying.
It really was nothing, though.
Of course.
Interesting.
I got over it quickly.
In that case, I want to meet this fictitious girlfriend.
Oh, yes, I joined a voluntary services club then.
Wouldn't that be too mean?
I never was too fond of him.
I really didn't like that too much, but I did the work.
It was out of luck that he got assigned here during the staff reassignment.
Then I showed off what I did, so I got really popular again!
It's a good chance to show him who is really the man behind all of our braodcasts.
I'm like a hot rod, an ultimate lady killer.
Right, Ume-san?
You know what I mean?
I sure would like to see Kacchin-sama's girlfriend.
I sure would love to see that wonderful beauty.
I wanna see!
I wanna see!   I wanna see!
I wanna see!   I wanna see!   I wanna see!
I wanna see!      I wanna see!      I wanna see!
But she's a working woman too.
I really can't make her come here so suddenly.
Isn't she totally devoted to you?
That's right.
Of course she is.
Then you should be able to do it.
Alright, then.
Please leave a message, then press "#" twice.
Oh yeah, she only has a pager.
Well, I'll leave my number, but I don't know if she'll call back.
W-what?
I want to see you right now.
The message has been accepted.
Please hang up now.
!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
Communication
Ended
Let's wait around, then.
In the middle of the day?
She will come, if she's totally devoted.
Oh, she's not coming, no matter how long we wait.
She's not coming!
Since it's Kacchin's girlfriend, put "-ko" on it,
would ka******* be her name?
I wonder?!
I believe.
I really believe.
She will come.
You really don't have one.
Even if that's true, I still believe.
He's so desperate.
It's the same thing as saying he doesn't have one.
My writing gets better when I see other people's misfortune.
I think I can write a good script.
Now it's been 2 hours.
Spill it.
You'll feel better.
So? P.R. Officer-san?
I...
I can't hear you.
I...!
What is this music?
Is it you, Ume-san?
It's from the STAR detector.
What?!
It's responding to something.
Is STAR's official coming?
Is that Kacchin-san's girlfriend?
Impossible!
Now you see that my girlfriend is a wonderful beauty.
I was jsut playing around, trying to create the mood.
I don't believe it.
I absolutely don't.
I don't know who you are, but thank you for coming!
Now I can keep my pride as a P.R. officer.
Shkow it to that Forehead Man,
Macho Mixer,
Android,
Dumped-by-STAR,
Useless A.D.,
and Idiot Script Writer.
I can stick it to them!
He's saying it out loud.
He's really out of his mind.
I'm stuck all of a sudden.
Welcome, my honey!
I see! It was you, Masudamasu-san!
You always acted cold, but deep inside, you were always...
Masudamasu-san!
What's going on?
Who knows?
I... I...
I am a lady killer!
It's getting so pathetic.
Now you see?
You are not a miracle man.
You're a no-good man, who doesn't even have a girlfriend.
No! No!
Massan, keep going.
You don't have a girlfriend, do you, Kacchin?
Do you?
How terrible...
Isn't that enough, Matsu-san?
There is no giving in in radio broadcasting!
We're not on the radio!
Shut up!
Am I not right, Kacchin?
You're a liar, aren't you?
You're righ...
Kaccin-san!
I'm sorry I'm late.
Are you my girlfriend?
Yes, I am, Kacchin-san.
You really came!
Yes!
Oh, thank goodness!
You don't need to cry.
I am your girlfriend, you know.
Jeez, this is so cheesy.
Yes, it it.
But Maico-chan is so sweet.
She was concerned about Kacchin-san.
Oh, man, I'm back in a slump again.
What's your name?
I'm Maico.
S-s-s-see?!
I have a wonderful girlfriend!
Am I great?
Y-yeah, you're great.
See? See?
Yes, I see.
My bad.
It's so pathetic, I just can't go on.
Good for you, Kacchin-san.
It's all because of you, Maico.
Congrats.
Thank you! Thank you!
I love you all!
Thank you!
Hello.
K-Katsumi?
Jeez, brother, what's going on, calling me out with the pager?
I sneaked out of school, since you said you wanted to see me right now.
Don't you dare smile and say this was just a prank!
Uhhh, I called my girlfriend, and then...
That's why Maico came, and... then I...
I just...
What's going on, brother?
Hey, everyone, what just happened?
Maico!
I'm happy for you that your real girlfriend came.
This script came out nice.
Today's show is going to shine, I guarantee it.
Yay!
Maico's Diary
I'm Masudamasu, a Chief Director for the Japan Broadcasting System.
In other words, I'm the most supreme being among the staff.
Today, I become Kacchin-
san's girlfriend.
I became one, since
Kacchin-san said he wanted
a girlfriend.
I don't think the staff
didn't notice that I was
his girlfriend.
Hey, you come to me if you are interested in the radio industry.
If you want, wearing a million dollar dress is possible.
Or you meet the nice STAR too.
So? Are you getting excited?
Next time - Android Ana Maico 2010
Tenpoin S Akira
Huh? It must be our guest's name.