A letter from radio-name Ten-chan:
I don't think bullying is a good thing.
I agree, Ten-chan.
Bullying is uncool.
Kissing in Love
Good morning.
Umm?
It's 30 minutes before airtime.
Yeah, you're right.
Where's Ume-san?
Who knows?
Maybe he's crying like a wimp in his apartment.
If you know that, why don't you give him a call?
You aren't very enthusiastic.
Can't you see?
I'm only here to witness how this cheap program falls apart like a dying flower.
I'm done for.
My career is falling apart like a bowl made out of sand.
How could I tell Mom or Katsumi about this?
I should never have participated in such a program.
It's no use crying!
Let's go on the air!
Izumi-san, what about the CDs?
Where are the CDs?
I didn't get them ready.
Why are you here then?!
Because I haven't found a new job yet.
A henchman's struggle, huh?
Like you can do anything by yourself.
It's not my fault!
I've submitted my report to the manager.
I beg you, please at least reassign me somewhere else.
Oh, no, it's nothing.
Let me get him, but would you keep that a secret?
Matsu-san, it's Isozaki-san.
From public relations?
He's saying to hurry your ass up.
Fine.
What do you want, Isozaki?
I'm rotten?
Of course.
Did you call just to mock me?
That's so mean.
Good going, Isozaki!
There's 10 years worth of public relations.
You're so different drom the wimp I just kicked.
Let's have lunch some day.
It's on me, of course.
Roll that deal along. Thanks.
Finally, luck is coming my way.
What's up, Massan?
It's nothing.
Good morning.
I brought the requested CD's from the library.
Thanks Maico, for even covering for the A.D.
I was asked by Masudamasu-san.
I see.
You can't disobey your master, right?
Since you're so honest, I'll give you a special prize today.
I'll put you in charge of today's program.
Do as you like.
Really?!
Yeah!
I doubt you can do it.
OK!
I'll try, try, and try hard!
What are you saying?
Don't accept so easily.
Ume-san isn't here.
Izumi-san isn't cooperative either.
Nobody is doing anything for us.
All we have is Suga-san's script.
There's no way we can go on the air like this.
Why?
Do you have no intention of going on the air, Densuke-san?
Of cource I do!
That's why I'm here.
Then let's do it.
Do it? Me?
Yes.
Fine. I'll do it.
I'll make the listeners say that it was better that ever.
Densuke-kun, you're shining!
It's so not good!
There's no other way!
It's impossible with you!
I'm still doing it!
Have fun.
A no-good A.D.'s direction, huh?
This should be quite a show.
So, the special death metal CD by our guest from 2 weeks ago...
goes out to pen-name.... from Tokyo.
Dang!
Oh, again...
Nice! You're shining!
Isn't this a bit too harsh for training?
A hard lesson is needed from time to time.
You're right.
Hard lessons are needed.
Director Densuke-san, the chief, Masudamasu-san, is here.
Would you work hard and show how good you are?
Damn!
120,121...
Keep on going!
Shut up!
After the commercial, we'll go to our usual corner.
Oh, how scary.
Stay tuned.
A street interview!
We've already messed up 123 times after just the first corner.
It's beautiful mathematically, but, man, that's not the point!
Densuke-san, please relax.
You just have to run it according to the cue sheet.
I will finish the talk as directed,
so you just have to properly run the tapes and songs...
Don't tell me that! You're a robot!
And I'm only a human!
I can't help but make mistakes!
And now you're whining.
Densuke-san, everyone makes mistakes.
But you should be able to put forth an effort so you don't make mistakes.
Let's keep trying.
I know that.
And I am trying.
Oh, the commercial is over.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Please pardon our mistakes.
Now I would like to get started with our usual corner.
OK, the CD...
Maico's That's Nice!
I'll take letters from the listeners,
and we'll see what you want to say, or what you want me to do.
Why?
Why is this CD here?
Try whatever you want to make my CPU overheat by putting me in a bind.
How dirty of you to play it like this.
The first one is a request.
Requesting Sato Machiko-san's "Kissing in Love".
Wait a sec, Izumi-san!
I played this in the Oldies Special once before.
Where are you...
This time, the letter is from Los Angeles.
What are you doing?
A staff member just came in.
We are still on the air.
I'm asking you, why are you putting this song on?!
That's a huge accident.
We are on the air.
As an android personality, I must continue the broadcast.
The requester from Los Angeles is...
This letter...
Do you want me to do it again?!
This letter is from the popular producer, Takatou Kenzi-san.
Good evening, Maico-chan.
Yes, good evening.
The song I request, "Kissing in Love", is the first song I produced.
Stop it.
What right do you have to do this?!
When I heard her sing in the studio,
I was confident that she was once-in-a-decade material.
I still believe that, too.
Stop it!
But the office I belonged to demanded I start promoting her as soon as possible.
They didn't care if she only lasted for a short time.
I resisted as much as possible.
She might be talented, but she was still immature as a singer.
So I had to nurture her, take time.
I really believed that.
I ended up almost being chased out of the position as the producer for Sato Machiko-san.
After that, I tried to contact her several times, but I have never seen her since.
I still think about her every time I hear "Kissing in Love".
The other day, someone from Japan Broadcasting told me that
Sato Machiko-san is working as a stuff member on your program.
To Sato Machiko-san...
no, to Izumi, I want to say, "I want to see you again."
"And I want to dedicate this song to her one more time."
That's the letter.
This is a song Takatou Kenzi-san is dedicating to Izumi-san.
Enjoy.
Sato Machiko-san's "Kissing in Love".
The CD!
That's so incredible, Maico-chan.
Matsu-san?
This is why you're scum.
Who would turn down the volume during such a good scene?
Izumi-san, a program that allows me to lie doesn't exist within me.
I can only act honestly.
So, when I read this, I wanted to tell, on the air...
All the listeners, and you, Izumi-san.
You could have spoken with me directly!
But this is a letter intended for this program.
What an inflexible android, really.
So embarrassing.
I've always thought I was betrayed.
I've always hated him.
Were you listening?
Well, then we don't need to explain.
This is the spot for the seasoned mixer.
Go for it, Ume-san.
Sato Machiko-san, please take this letter.
It's so shining.
Maico's Diary
This is elite public relations officer, Kacchin.
The other day, I went to play a survival game with friends from my college days.
I was very happy to get a letter from overseas. Izumi-san was very happy too. But something is strange. The illumination settings haven't changed, but the studio seems brighter.
I'm good sniper,
so I hid behind some object, and was waiting for them to move.
But nobody came around even after 3 days.
I thought my plan was perfect!
And it was so mean that they all left for somewhere else!
Next Android Ana Maico 2010
You are so meek.
People tell me that all the time too.
You are so meek
That you're so honest with yourself.