A question from radio name Ai-chan of Okayama-ken reads:
What is Maico?
Shut up and watch!
But you know, that pizza guy grom the other day was so bad.
I know.
But now we could refresh the studio, and it feels good.
Ouch!
What are you saying?!
Suga's script was all burned and couldn't be read,
it was a wasted effort.
Morse!
Oh, you're going out too?
Yes. Masudamasu-san wants to see me.
OK, I'm shutting it.
Oh?
Gone home already?
Everyone?
Geez, why couldn't they wake me up?
Could it be that they actually hate me for real?
That's impossible.
I'm a popular guy, liked by everyone.
I'm sure that they just couldn't wake me up after looking at a sleeping angel.
Now, time to go home.
Oh yeah, they put in the card reader.
Huh? It won't open.
Strange.
Oh?
HA!
I got locked in!
No need to panic.
I just need to call someone on the phone.
HA!
Oh, hello?
This is Kacchin.
The door won't open.
Hello? Hello?
What's wrong with the phone?
Does it hate me?
Oh, no, that's not it.
I'm a nice guy, loved by all.
I'm sure it's a simple mistake by the switchboard operator.
I'll forgive them with my ocean-sized heart.
If the regular line is useless, I still have this.
Oh no! I've gotta hurry!
Man, that scared me.
Hello? This is Kacchin.
I'm in big trouble, so can you call me back...
Oh, it's just you, Katsuo.
I'm busy right now.
Let's talk later...
Oh, that?
I say, you know... Flowers are fine.
No, that's not what I mean.
We'll talk when I get ho...
Hey! Katsumi! Hey!
Calm down... Stay calm, Kacchin.
I'm not wimpy enough to be scared by this.
That's right, I'm a world-renowned Kyushu boy!
What am I saying?
Is someone getting close?
Is it STAR?
That's it. STAR is walking outside this door.
I must tell him.
I must tell him that I'm in a dire situation!
But how?
Oh, Morse!
Yeah, knock on the door and use Morse code.
I didn't expect the knowledge from boy scouts would be useful here!
Please notice!
Wait...
Was that really the code for SOS?
Now I'm worried again.
Back then, I was so fascinated by Yoritsune-kun's story about how offspring between a rhinoceros beetle and a stag beetle would make a rhinostag beetle.
This is no time to be nostalgic!
What now? What now?
What if I'm actually sending a message saying "I'm not here"?
Oh my Morse!
There's no other choice.
I'll stay here for tonight.
Why won't it turn on?
I'm getting hungry.
Is there any food?
But whose is this?
Masudamasu-san doesn't eat chocolate,
and Densuke is too poor to leave some behind.
Maico doesn't eat to start with,
and Suga didn't even show up today.
Moreover, I highly doubt that the Ume-Matsu brothers would eat chocolate.
Therefore, this chocolate is Izumi-chan's!
That means this is an indirect kiss!
This is an emergency situation!
I'm not excited about it!
Were... you... watching?
What's the matter with you?!
You could have told me that you were here!
Why isn't he here?
It must have been an illusion.
That's it. That must be it.
Pizza! Yes! Food!
But did we order pizza today?
That means... this is from that violent pizza?!
But I don't have any other choice.
But how many days does pizza last?
It's been... umm...
Well, I'll check the contents first.
I'll forget that I even saw it.
What do I do?!
What?
There's a giant mushroom here.
Yeah! I'll have a big laugh with this tomorrow!
I'm not hungry.
Because I'm a healthy nice guy, who eats full meals everyday.
My body is filled with energy,
since I am such a musclemand, totally different from my wimpy past,
my height equals five times that of Tokyo Tower,
and I weight 40 grams on a table spoon, a super bargain size.
Take me for your picnic, for your kids' snack.
Kacchin for all your snack needs!
What's wrong with me?!
Damn! Damn! Why do I have to suffer like this?!
God, what'd I do to deserve this?!
Well, I really can't answer that...
Are you a god?
Yes, though I'm still only an A.G.
A.G.?
An assistant god.
You're useless.
No way!
Help me, Buddha!
What do you want?
I'm in dire trouble right now!
Please help me!
What's your name?
I'm Kacchin.
Wrong religion.
Oh, don't say that!
It's not my job. See ya.
There's no God, no Buddha...
But there're more religions.
Well...
Damn, I can't remember!
This is all Yoritsune-kun's fault for talking to me in class!
Achoo!
It's getting cold.
Oh, it's warm.
Yeah!
Smokey!
And it stinks!
Yeah!
Now I'll be saved!
Now, security guards should be...
Why?
Could it...
Impossible!
Why didn't they wake me up?
If they had, I would have been rolled up in my blanket, sound asleep by now.
They must all hate me.
That's why I was left alone.
I'm...
I'm the unneeded person in this program.
That's not true!
without you, Kacchin-san, we couldn't continue the program.
I can keep going only because you're watching after me, Kacchin-san.
Maico-chan...
No, my sweet honey!
Same here!
Kacchin-san, get up!
My little lover!
Kacchin, I know I don't show much emotion, but I actually...
My queen!
Kacchin! Kacchin!
Everyone!
Thank you! Thank you!
I love you all!
Maico's Diary
I received a letter from a listener,
asking "what does Maico-chan do after the show?"
(It feels like I'm rechargin.)
I'm getting a tune up by the maintenance department!
The secretary, Katagiri-san, tells me a lot of things going on in the company.
Like who and who are dating,
or which manager's son had a perfect grade...
Just listening to her is so fun.
Next Android Ana Maico 2010
Flowers? Or Kokeshi?
"Flowers? Or Kokeshi?"
I love them both.