Maico, aren't you in a slump lately?
If you're ticked, say it out loud!
So, let's get loud today too!
Kodomo, Drama, Maico,
Kodomo, Oyaji, Shacho, Oyako,
CoDoMo,
CoDoMo, CoDoMo, CoDoMo, CoDoMo,
What do I do?
What do I do if the sponsor quits on us?
CoDoMo Group
Tell me, what's going to happen to me?
All right,
now that we've worshipped the great sponsor who funds this program,
let's forget all about last week, and start our recording session.
Roboco,
Yes?
Have you finished
reading through my poems?
I'm inputting them right now.
Please give me a bit more time.
Hurry up!
OK.
"Our mother is gone,"
"Leaving me, Jiro, and Ichiro behind."
"We can't eat the pot roast that mother made anymore."
It's a serious poem.
Suga, are you sure this is good?
I guess it's good and depressing.
I didn't write them anyway.
Good morning.
Yo, yo! How have you been?
I guess you've been busy recently?
Kume-san was surprised too.
You're shining.
Not really.
By the way, have you had the new nutrition supplement drink?
It's really good.
It makes your insides hot.
What's that called?
You mean, Matbat Gold?
Yeah, that's it!
So you're drinking it.
No wonder you're shining!
Even the Star Detector doesn't know what to do with you.
Don't bring in an outsider.
Who's that?
Your lover?
Some stranger.
I guess the conversation flows naturally.
That's the standard conversation in the industry.
Groovy, yeah!
Roboco, can you tell who that is?
There is no matching image in the Idol Database.
Wasn't there an athlete that looked like that?
I thought there was a woman, no, artist that looked like that.
Excuse me, can I have some tea?
Oh, yes, right away.
Densuke-kun, right now!
Uh, sure...
Wait!
Why do we have to be nice to some stranger?
But remember last week?
What if he's some very important person?
It'll be just like with President Kodomo.
It was so rogh after that.
President Kodomo made me play horsey for 20 hours,
and my knees got so torn up!
Oh yeah, I've got scabs now,
but they're in a "G" shape.
Wanna see?
Hey, I want to.
I want to see them too.
[G-Shaped]
Ta-da.
So what?!
Does looking at them change anything?!
But they're so unusual!
See? See?
I'm going to input them.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Excuse me, but can we hurry?
Excuse me.
I see, he's the guest.
Don't see it!
Why would a guest be here when it's not an airdate?
I'm sure you mis-scheduled.
Who is he?
Answer me!
Uh... I don't know.
Then I'll ask him.
Hey, who the hell are...
What the hell are you doing?!
You can't do that, Matsu-san!
What if his pride gets hurt by us asking "Who are you"?!
He might be someone from CoDoMo Group.
My knees are completely shot already!
I can't be a horsey anymore.
Roboco, carry on an ordinary conversation and figure out who he is at the same time!
You're a robot, so you can overcome this dire situation!
We will support you as much as we can.
Look!
That is the wall that stands in front of you.
Okay.
I'll try hard, and overcome it.
Now, let's start.
You guys ready?
Yes.
Sure thing!
Now, it's time for our guest of the day.
Anyone will be able to tell who he is just by hearing his voice.
Good evening.
You all got it, right?
Nice start, Roboco.
You're doing so well recently.
Yes, I won twice.
You won twice?
They were toughy opponents, but I was still victorious.
By the way, when is your birthday?
June 21st - Capricorn.
It's someone who has won twice, and was born on June 21st.
Some astrologists say June 21st is Gemini, but I wonder who's right?
Matsu-san, the people listed with that birthday are a singer, a bicycle racer, and a shogi player.
Winning twice means he's not a singer.
Maybe it's the number of times he won the Idol All Star athletic event.
Roboco, the guest is either a singer, a bicycle racer, or a shogi player.
Limit the conversation topic.
Will you be facing a touch opponent in your next game?
Next game?
Isn't it hard to keep up with the training?
Training?
I mean, when are you going to release your next new album?
New album?
They're all wrong!
Sorry, I was looking at the July 21st page.
You dumass!
I'm sorry, but can we take a break?
Can you make it short?
Of course.
June 21st...
I'm guessing he's around 20 years old.
What?!
A piece of the scab came off my left knee, and the G became a C.
Cool!
Shut up!
What is it trying to tell me?
It bothers me.
G and C, huh?
Isn't G for "Ganbare" (Good luck)?
C is for Cacchin?
That's me!
I see.
Who is it?
The mystery is solved!
Ganbare Cacching! (Go, go, Kacchin!)
YES! Go, go, me!
But, about what?
Give it a rest!
Densuke, look it up.
Okay.
It's burned from the smoke!
Um, are you done yet?
I have other appointments after this one.
Roboco, we have given all the support we can provide.
It's now all up to your talk.
I'm trusting you, Roboco.
You chickened out.
Uh...
Um...
Um..
What is it?
Um...
In Let's Go Trio, do you know the third person after Chun-san and Chosaku-san?
Shoji. What about it?
Nothing.
Um...
If you drop water on a shrunken straw wrapper...
...it expands, right?
Yes, you're... right...
It's hopeless.
It is.
Go! Go! Kacchin!
Go! Go! Ka-
Gome on, Maico-chan.
Um, do you like to collect crown caps?
Go! Go! Kacchin!
Huh?!
I'm impressed with your android skill, Maico-chan.
I've never told anybody about my hobby.
It's been 20 years since I started collecting crown caps.
I started collecting after I found out that the designs differ depending on the year or the locality.
It's the same...
It requires a delicate technique to remove them from the bottle without damaging them, doesn't it?
Yes.
I bought a special bottle opener from India for that purpose.
They have that?
You're very fastidious.
Sure.
I carry my treasure everywhere I go.
This one is from 1948, but there is no rust!
W-wow!
That's one of a kind.
Yes, people tell me that a lot.
One of this program's staff collects crown caps too.
I would love to meet that person.
I'm sure you will get along very well.
Thank you for the fun time.
Today's guest was...
...guest was...
...-san.
Please come again!
I would love to.
Nice one, Ume-san.
Sorry for Roboco's dumbo talk.
Oh, it was fun.
So, who's the one collecting the crown caps?
It's me.
I screw a lost of things up,
but I'm confident about crown caps.
T-that's...
the legendary piece that was only sold at the Adachi Tobacco Shop in 1959!
Where did you...
I got it from Adachi-san himself.
I see.
You must have been recognized by Adachi-san.
You can have this.
I can't take that!
It's such a treasure.
I believe that it's best to be owned by you, who was recognized by Adachi-san.
I'm sure you can become the crown cap master.
Thank you.
It was very fun today.
Please have me over again.
I would ask you to come back too.
Bye.
We never learned who he was in the end.
Don't know.
Oh, Tenpoin-san!
It's been a while.
It was a pretty fun talk, Masudamasu-san.
You have such nice staff.
Could he be...
Look, look, everyone!
The right one is now "C" too!
Yeah!
What does it mean?
C and C...
One is Cacchin, and the other is...
For Corosareru. (will be killed)
The mystery is over.
Kacchin will be killed.
By whom?
Maico's Diary
This is the A.D., Densuke.
The other day, I used Shinkansen to go pickup a part for Maico-chan.
Suga-san told me about this secret way to ride it.
Tenpoin S Akira-san was
a very wonderful person.
But, after that, kacchin-
san screamed "I will be
killed!" and ran away
somewhere.
Kacchin-san was
weird again today.
My ticket was for the non-reserved seats,
and I was drinking coffee in the buffet car the whole time.
It was a comfortable ride, but for some reason, I wasn't comfortable being there.
Everyone was starting at me real hard too.
Next Android Ana Maico 2010 - Fly
When I was a kid, I squished one, thinking it was a mosquito.
Next Episode
Fly
It was so gross.