Note: Kokeshi is a traditional Japanese wooden, decorative doll.
Katsuo, turn off the TV.
Oh, come on, the Monday Warm Fuzzy is just starting.
Record it on the VCR.
You can watch it after the meeting.
Man...
How's our brother doing?
They said that he'll recover in a couple of days.
I'm glad it wasn't serious.
Well, anyway, let's get started.
Hang on.
[Flower? of Kokeshi?]
The 427th Katsumata-Family General Assembly.
Today's topic is the 79th session of...
Do we put flowers or a kokeshi at our entrance hall?
Let's finish this quick.
It's a waste of time assembling for such a silly reason so many times every week.
But, Katsuo, you usually read manga or sleep anyway.
What?!
Enough, Katsuo.
Now, for a start, let's hear opinions from each of you.
Who thinks we should put a kokeshi on the shoe shelf?
Mom.
Oh, it broke.
Mom!
Yes, yes.
What about flowers?
That's 3-2.
What did Kacchin say?
He said flowers.
3-3! Now we're even!
The majority doesn't rule.
We must come up with a solution that everyone will be satisfied with.
Dang.
Then let's decide it quickly.
Katsuo, you're not serious enough.
What?!
Quit that.
What's the matter, mother?
I'll go get some tea.
Oh, mother, I'll go, so would you remain seated?
Oh, don't worry about me.
I can't do that.
Just let me.
OK?
You don't twist enough.
The twist.
Mom : lost 62.
Would you win for once already?
Now, let's hear the reasons why both teams push for their opinions.
First, the Flower Team.
Come on, Katsuo.
Me?
But I went last time.
Kacchin isn't here, so we don't have any other choice.
Well...
Like, when someone comes to visit us, it's embarrassing to have a kokeshi at our entrance.
How is it embarrassing?
It's like a grandpa fashion.
I really don't get it.
I do.
He's saying that he doesn't want the mood to be destroyed when he brings home a girl.
Hey!
Hey, Katsuo! When did you find such a girl?!
No! You're mistaking me!
Then, what kind of relationship are you in with Urajima Katsuko-san,
whom you broght home on the 18th of last month?
We were brainstorming on ideas for our school's open house.
Then why did you lock your door?
What the hell are you checking out?!
Quit it, both of you.
We never come to a conclusion because we always go off a tangent like that.
Keep your mind on flowers and kokeshi for now!
However, Katsuo, come to my study after this.
Next, the Kokeshi Team!
Me! Me! Me!
We must change water or switch flowers often.
Well, yeah.
My point is, either mom or I would end up doing those chores.
Sure. It's a woman's job to take care of flowers.
Brother, that's gender discrimination.
Anyone who's not willing to take care of them doesn't have any right to voice their opinion.
On the other hand, you don't have to take care of a kokeshi.
We just need to dust it once in a while.
With the above points, I strongly, strongly push for a kokeshi.
Very good, Kacchan.
Here.
Ha!
Katsuo, say something back.
She's so logical that I can't say anything back.
You can't even say anything back to an elementary schooler?!
What the heck, you dump everything on me.
Looks like the Flower Team can't even respond.
Here's the tea.
All right, let's take an interval.
Both teams, scramble for strategies.
So, how is it going so far?
Don't worry, mother.
Kokeshi Team has a big lead.
Already?
Man, they'll outrun us at this rate.
I would hate to have a kokeshi be the first thing I see when I step into the house.
I don't like it either!
After overtime, tired and beaten, opening the door...
Can you imagine meeting your eyes with a kokeshi?
Those cold eyes,
nihilistic mouth,
expressionless face...
The exhaustion from the day would double!
A smiling kokeshi would be weird too.
Anyway, is there any good way to break their arguments?
What if we attack mom?
Mom?
Yeah!
I'm sure she doesn't have a reason.
If we convince her, we might be able to pull her to our side.
I see.
Second half!
Now that we've heard from Katsumi and Katsuo, can I hear an opinion from mom?
Me?
Yes.
Why did you want a kokeshi in our entrance hall?
Why a kokeshi over flowers?
Why a kokeshi?
So, why?
Do you not remember?
This.
That's...
Oh yeah, from back then...
Yes.
Yeah. Come to think of it, this family started with that kokeshi.
Hey! Dad!
Sorry, Katsuo.
I'm betraying my team.
What?!
A kokeshi is like a cupid for mom and dad.
Wouldn't it be great to be greeted by it?
That's not what you said erlier!
So, there's two left in the Flower Team.
What the hell! The adults are not fair!
You change your minds so fast!
Then I'll never give in!
I'll have roses in our entrance hall, and show them to Urajima!
I knew it.
Katsuo.
Don't stop me, grandma!
I won't stop you.
I'm on your side.
Mother!
You can't blame Katsuo for getting upset.
I'm disappointed...
about forgetting Katsue-san's kokeshi, and about changing your opinion so quickly.
Grandma! So...
I'll side with flowers too.
I have lots of free time anyway.
Taking care of flowers will be nothing.
Grandma!
Mother...
Katsukichi! Are you really a man?!
Changing your opinions so quickly!
Aren't your ashamed as the head of the household, and as a husband?!
Well, um...
I will never give in!
We will have flowers in our entrance hall!
Kokeshi!
Oh my. What do we do now?
Listen up, both of you.
The discussion will not end at this rate.
You're to blame too.
If we can't talk about this, let's have luck decide the matter.
Let's have a bet and the winning team will put up whatever they like.
Is it a fair bet?
Of course.
The radio program that Kacchin works for starts soon.
Will the first letter that is read come from a man or a woman?
Let's decide with that.
Fine.
All right, which do you want?
A man.
A woman.
All rihgt then. Turn it on.
Roger!
Good evening, everyone.
This is Maico, back from my weak of resting.
Let's spend our time together until our time is up.
Now, for a special treat, let me read a letter.
From pen name, Kacchin.
Please listen to me, Maico-chan.
For a long time, my family has been having a small problem.
It's about whether we should put flowers or a kokeshi in our entrance hall.
I am siding with flowers for now, but I'm not very particular about it.
If my mother or sister wants to put a kokeshi, I don't have a strong reason to disagree.
But I don't want to hurt my father or my brother by siding with them.
I just can't stand the fact that this friendly family is fighting.
Maico-chan, what should we do?
...there we go.
Hmmm...
Then why don't you combine both sides?
I mean, put a kokeshi holding flowers in your entrance hall.
That way, everyone's wish will be kept, and I'm sure you can all see it with a smile.
How's that, Kacchin-san?
Anyway, I can see how much you care about your family, Kacchin-san.
Kacchin-san's family, stop fighting and have a peaceful time.
Now, let's get to it!
Jump ou...
That Kacchin... that's pretty good.
Brother...
Yup, that's was pretty good.
A kokeshi holding flowers, huh?
Yeah, that's a thought.
But where would we find such a kokeshi?
Well, I'll start by asking at the dolly stores.
I'll ask at the seniors club too.
And if all else fails, let's ask some artists and have them make one.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
I have a hidden stash of money.
Honey, you really...
Of course, I will have you help me out too.
Oh, come on!
Man...
Oh yeah, I need to stop the VCR.
I'll go see Kacchin tomorrow again.
Hey, there's chabashira.
Chabashira - a stick of tea leaf, floating vertically inside the teacup - a sign of good luck/godd fortune
Maico's Diary
This is Izumi.
The other day, I found this really good "wanted" ad!
I only have to work for 5 hours a day, and get paid 30,000 yen per day!
I read Kacchin-san's
letter today.
I tried, tried and tried
to come up with my answer
but I'm not sure if it
helped Kacchin-san's family.
Once he's out of the
hospital, I'll ask him.
The transportation fee and uniforms will be provided.
I can even pick my uniform from nurse style or police style...
I know what kind of job it is.
But the pay is so good!
The next Android Ana Maico 2010
Je teame
I wish someone would say that to me.
Next Episode
Je teame
I will only accept from a man 25 years or older, with an annual salary of 30,000,000 or above.