Anroids are machines that are modeled after humans.
That's why Maico cannot become human.
She can't. Not ever.
It's no good.
This one has stopped too.
What happened to make both of them stop?
This place is just crappy.
Hey, turn up the volume.
It's estimated that 4,000,000 will be affected by this.
The National Weather Services has issued a flood Warning in addition to the Wind Warning.
How much longer will we be stuck here?
I guess we just have to wait here.
We have a live report from Noritake-san in Odaiba.
Oh, man.
I wonder when they're going to start operating the trains again?
Noritake-san?
I can't reach him.
The next typhoon report will be at 1.00.
The next traffic report will be at 1:00.
Oh, Izumi-chan, weren't you commuting in your car?
I'm having it repaired.
Everyone's stuck, huh?
Shit out of luck.
Then why don't you take a taxi?
I can't afford that with my small-ass salary.
Maybe the taxis are stuck too.
Damn, why did we get a storm now?
Well, the trains will start moving at some point.
Let's just wait patiently for the storm to end.
Storm...
Maico,
Yes?
go ahead and recharge yourself.
Yes.
Sleep well.
It's not the best view...
Well, would you just leave her alone for a while?
I'm going home.
How are you getting there?
It's storming outside.
However I fell like it.
I just go home whenever I want to.
Sometimes I envy her attitude.
Well, let's just wait around.
Suga-san, this is a non-smoking area.
You'd better quit smoking.
Why?
We're done airing already.
You'll get cancer.
There's no way I'll get it.
That's just a superstition.
Oh, Izumi-chan, did you catch a cold?
No, I didn't.
Good.
You'd better watch out for your health.
Maico-chan, please cheer me up, because exams are getting close.
Maico-chan, please cheer me up, because I broke up with my girlfriend.
Damn, what a lousy bunch of letters.
What do you expect?
They were sent to the life advice corner.
They aren't worth advising about!
Right, Ume-san?
If you just sit around and wait until you hear the answer on the radio,
there's something wrong with you.
That's a worrisome comment, coming from from a program director.
Who cares?
We're not on the air right now.
Hey, they're here again.
What is?
You know, those poems.
Oh, those My My Poems.
One of our regulars.
The hell with the regulars.
He's the only one who contributes to that corner.
What's matter with that?
I don't have to write up some fake talk due to that.
It's so depressing each and every time.
Can't we do anything about it?
But that depressing feeling is also a source of my creative energy too.
What's it like this week?
Read it.
Mother, I can see your gentle smile every time I close my eyes.
Mother, neither Jiro, Ichiro, nor I have ever forgotten about you.
Mother, I want to eat the delicious sukiyaki that you made again.
Mother, I want you to clean my ears in your lap again.
Mother, Mother...
Mother, I can't stand the Earth without you.
It's getting really desperate.
It's really getting intense.
It's shining.
This is just a dude with a Mother Complex.
They are all so messed up.
What happened to them? Heita and the woman he brought with him?
I guess they're holding the ceremony next month.
That's sudden.
I guess they want to get married fast.
Anyway, Maico really was out of line.
Can't she fell the atmosphere? Damn.
She can't help it.
After all, she's just...
a robot.
There's no way she can fell a human heart.
And yet we're having a robot advice humans.
In a way, this program is full of deception.
You're going too far.
Everyone's working hard.
Of course. It's our job.
I just want this program to be a little more serious.
And we can't be serious with Maico-chan?
After all, her words are nothing more than mechanical data anyway.
She can't understand the fundamental part of humans.
That's why she would try to say something that would interrupt the mood.
Aren't you saying too much?
I know she can't hear this!
What's wrong, Macchan?
What's up with the irritation?
It's nothing.
Hey, isn't the train moving yet?
I guess not.
Damn.
What's the matter with you?
Shut up!
Hey, Izumi-chan, give me a tissue.
Izumi-chan!
Did you hear me?
Give me a tissue.
They're right there.
And I'm asking you to hand it to me.
Please help yourself.
Are you talking back to me?!
We're not clocked in right now.
What?!
Would you stop fighting?
We better clean up the mess quickly.
Jeez.
Oh man, we can't read this poem anymore.
Who cares?
Throw it away!
Yes.
Ume-san?!
What is it?!
Mother, the gloves you made are wearing out.
Hey, this in the My My Poem!
What? Are these poems written by you, Ume-san?!
What?
Why didn't you say so in the beginning?
You didn't have to hide it like a wimp!
You're horrible.
What?
You're so horrible.
You snap about your own irritation,
and rather than apologizing, you become defiant.
What about you?
You're reading the want ads ostentatiously.
If you want to quit that much, then quit now!
I will!
I'm so tired of this place.
The android, and you too.
You're all so insensitive.
"You"? Does that include us?
Yes!
You smoke so brazenly.
If you want to die from cancer, then die alone!
Why are you laughing?
That's why I'm saying that you're insensitive!
Well...
What's this?
Why is this happening?
Stupid A.D., get lost!
Go to some corner and cry!
You can't ignore me!
I've worked hard for this program!
Don't make me laugh.
Nothing has changed from your hard work.
You're just an A.D.
What's that supposed to mean?!
I know you were thinking that way too!
That's why you couldn't say anything to that woman.
Well, that's different...
Man, you're all rotten!
Why do I have to work with them?
Hey Roboco, answer me.
Management is totally wrong to, trying to let a robot run a show.
Weren't there any better ideas for catching peoples' attention?
There's no way a robot's voice can reach a listener's heart.
I can't stand this.
I quit.
Are you running away?
Are you really quitting?
Are you giving up this program?
To hell with this program.
It's been failing the whole time.
Gathering all the junk together only produces trash.
I was too late in noticing, that's all.
That's not fair!
Why did I get yelled all this time, then?!
Because you're not talented.
You're scum because you don't get that.
It's a good opportunity.
Why don't you quit too?
Don't be rediculous!
If you want to quit, then quit by yourself!
Yes, I'm planning on it.
It's getting better.
Oh come on you all. Don't be so selfish.
This is why I didn't want to sit for all these babies.
When did you take care of us?
You were only selling yourself to management!
I'm going home.
I'd much rather go out in the storm than stay here with you.
How dare you run away, Matsu!
Maico-chan, are you awake?
Densuke-san,
Densuke-san, I'm not a robot, but an android.
Were you... listening?
Yes.
Maico-chan, well...
Why am I crying?
Why am I sad?
We were having so much fun on the air.
Was that all a lie?
Yes, it was.
Humans are like that.
Maico-chan, you can stay honest because you are an android.
And you hurt other people's feelings by being insensitive.
This is not right.
Why is it wrong to be honest?
I don't understand.
It's 1:00.
Here is an update on the typhoon and traffic information.
There is no sigh of the storm beginning to weaken.
This storm is expected to last longer than the initial estimate.
Maico's Diary
This is Maico.
A sparrow made a nest on a factory chimney which I can see from the studio.
I heard everyone's words as I was recharging. Why am I crying only after hearing when people are stating what the think and feel? Someone, please tell me. It's storming outside.
The parent bird is flying in and out to feed the chicks.
She's flying so busily.
If I were a sparrow,
I wouldn't have time to recharge,
so I would fall at some point.
Next Android Ana Maico 2010
Kissing in Love
Those feeding sparrows look like they are kissing.