In the year 2010, a girl appeared in the low-rated radio world. Her name is MAICO.
She is the first android announcer in the radio world.
...
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Mi
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Fa
ReReMi ReDoMi
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Mi
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Fa
ReReMi DoRaDo
DoReDoReDo DoMiDoReDo
SoRa SoRa SoShi
RaShiRaShiRa RaShiDoShiRa
RaShiDo ReReReRe Fa!
SoRaShi ReDoShiDoMiRaMi
RaShiDoMiReDoReFa DoShi
SoSoSoSo ShiReSo FaMiFaMi
MiMiMiMiRaMi SoDo
Alright, are you all here, you boneheads?
As I'm gonna be a director an all...
I want a rating of
over 20% so work your...
asses off...
Geeze, we are starting the show in half an hour, why isn't anyone here?
Even though we got our notices
2 hours before the show.
It's unbelievable that they all are so unmotivated.
Oh, Ume-san! It's you.
You're assigned here too?
Aren't we the lucky ones?
I was reassigned to this crappy show after directing a high-rated show which I worked on for the last 15 years.
Huh?
Good morning.
Hey, Izumi-chan! You were put here too?
They ordered me to...
These are the CDs we're airing today.
I wrote the name of the songs and the timings on the cue sheet.
What an unmotivated girl. She didn't even apologize for being late.
But I can't complain because she's cute.
What should I do with this
unfocused rage?
Good morning!
I've decided to turn my anger towards you!
What was that for?
Good morning, huh?
Densuke, aren't you suppose to say
"I'm sorry for being late"?
You've made a quite an entrance
for a clumsy Assistant Director.
I'm.. sorry for being late
Wanna know the kind of
person I hate the most?
The person who's late for a work?
Wrong.
The person who is
handsome but useless.
It's better than being ugly
...wish I didn't hear that.
Please, stop!
Shut up! Quit complaining!
You're just an A.D.!
This is just plain rude!
I can see how unmotivated you all are!
You can complain when you've
become a real director!
Ouch ow!
Morning! Whoa, Mattsuan's director?
Guess this show is going to be a hit!
Densuke, you're being picked on
as usual. Looking good!
Ume-san is the mixer?
Being reticence makes you look sharp.
Come on, make some noise.
Wow, nice sound effect!
With my script, Ume-san's sound effect, and Mattsuan being a director,
we will win this year's Pulitzer award which has got nothing to do with it though.
This is so exciting.
Izumi-chan, wanna go out for a
drink after the show?
No
Ume-san~
Nice timing!
Hey, Suga! Is the script done?
Oh, come on. Who do you think I am?
I am Suga-chan,
the legendary scenario writer
who had success in the "Live to the World! From Across the Antarctic" .
That's the program you
worked on 10 years ago....
Anyway, Just take a look at this. It's the revival of a legend. It's shining brightly.
"Jump Out, MAICO!!"?
Who the hell is MAICO?
Oh, please. She's the DJ of the show.
And I did it without even
meeting the DJ, It's brilliant!
Did we have any
announcer named MAICO?
I know her! I think the name of the lady from the cigarette store across  from my apartment is...
"Good evening, everybody. My name is MAICO, the DJ of this show."
"I'm an android working for the Nihon Broadcasting Corporation."
"Two thumbs up for an android. An android is the greatest. An android,
gotta catch' em all."
What the hell is THIS!?
Ain't it cool? A show that's run by an android. The first revolutionary show in the radio world.
This is where the legend begins.
Who came up with
this crappy idea? Who!?
Of course Masuda Masu,
the chief director.
She's also legendary, isn't she?
What's so legendary about this?
For the last 15 years, I've been solving thousands of people's problems.
Even if it's the company's orders, I can't make a fake show for all the listeners.
I'd prefer raising tomatoes back at home.
This fraud is inexcusable. How can they come up with such a radio talk show!?
Think I would come up
with a nonsense project!?
This is the project Nihon Broadcasting Corporation is giving everything they've got
to survive through the low-rated radio world of the 21st century.
That's this show using an android as DJ, "Jump out, MAICO! 2010".
This android will decide the future of Nihon Broadcasting Corporation.
And you guys are the best of the best to make the show succeed.
A capable director who ran the life consultation show for 15 years.
The reticent mixer with
many different techniques.
The scenario writer with
many great ideas.
The specialist in song and sound selection. The useless assistant director "AD". And...
Why aren't you saying anything about me, Masuda Masu-san?
Please say I'm the program coordinator who pushes the show with revolutionary idea.
I don't feel like it.
God, no....
Uh, so you're saying that
a robot is in this box?
It's not a robot. It's fully automated intelligent android. The name is MAICO.
This is an android...
She's cute...
Don't tell me you got a crush on her.
MAICO, you're awesome!
She looks so real! This is great!
How does she look underneath?
Ya wanna look?
It's like looking at the
doll from a low angle.
I know what you're saying man.
Men, what a foolish existence.
The secret of MAICO will be revealed. It must be brightly shining.
Ta-da!
S..she's not complete...
We didn't have enough time to finish her up. The bottom half will be completed in 2 weeks.
We only have 10 minutes
till the air time. Get to work.
Hey hey! Are you saying that we must air the show with this freak!?
Why are you picking on me?
No way! I'm going home!
And Densuke, you are fired as well!
Give me a break...
Wait Matsu-san, if we don't start the show, I'm gonna be the one in trouble.
Just write up your resignation!
I don't want that!
You are so easy to give up.
Even though MAICO is not complete,
we can still activate her.
Don't you think this is the part to show the ability of a capable director?
Hey, Densuke!
Yes?
That robot broad...
She's an android.
She's nothing but a robot broad to me! So just activate that robot broad Densuke!
Me?
Why do you think you are an assistant director? We don't have enough time.
Yes, sir...
We have less than 5
minutes left! Move your ass!
OK
Let's start the show
with S-2 as usual. And....
Please hurry up for my sake!
First turn the main switch on...
Huh? Why isn't she moving?
She won't move unless you install the OS! Don't you know that, you idiot.
These 50 CDs are the OS application discs! Hurry, up the show's gonna start!
What did you do that for?
Are you saying it's my fault? You, an ordinary AD, are blaming me, the program coordinator?
Move your ass, Densuke!
We only have 3 minutes left.
But still....
Use that.
MAICO Activation Disc                                                 for Word Processor
It says "for Word processor"...
What time do you think it is?
Densuke, is that robot broad active?
Seems like it....
Seems like it isn't good enough! Don't tell me she can't read the scripts!
It's looking good. It seems that she recognizes optically with CCD cameras.
She's got a data modem, exciting talk system, emergency shutdown system, and an emotional response control system.
Quit your techno-babble. Densuke,
place her in the studio.
How am I..?
Use your brain! Just carry
her in or something!
She's..heavy...
Having trouble, Densuke-kun?
Can't..you help...me....?
MAICO is in the studio!
10 seconds left.
No rehearsal but, we have no
choice! You got that!
She's ready to go.
Ume-san...
Please...
What the hell are you doing!?
Shoot...
E...English...
She's not fluent at all...
That's why I can't trust a machine
with more than four frick'in buttons!
Okay, MAICO. You're doing
fine, you're beautiful.
The show... the show is ruined...
It must be from the show's sponsor.
Please answer the phone,
Masuda Masu-san.
Sorry.
No...
She's...heavy...
Are you sure this show is
going to work out...
Hello, everybody! I'm Densuke, the assistant director of
"Jump out, MAICO! 2010" for the Nippon Broadcasting Corporation.
Most of the radio shows are live so we can't let our guard down.
The director will discipline
(beat) you if you do
I try not to let my guard down
but it seems that I can't help it.
If you know a good way to keep you
guard up, please tell me.
Next show
"Android Announcer MAICO 2010".
"Adachi-san in Danger"
Adachi-san is the one in danger.
I hope I'm getting this right...