You know it, right?
The world will keep turning even without Maico.
It's a minor detail. Don't worry.
But... it's lonely without her.
Good morning.
Densuke!
Why are you there?
What do you mean, why?
Then who did I tie up?
Let me go!
Or else I'll report you to the authorities!
Who's that kid?
He just came in a few minutes ago, and messed the studio up.
I thought the only useless person around here was you, the no-good A.D...
He doesn't look anything like me!
In my head, useless equals you.
Would you judge people more by their looks?! By their looks...
Then who's that?
Dunn...
Anyway, it's not cool to tie up a kid in a chair.
Oh, idiot!
Are you all right?
You twit!
Wide open!
Please stop.
Violence is not nice.
Why are you being so bad?
[Je t'aime]
Okay.
Let's get married.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Now, Ume-san!
God, what a messed up twit.
But really, who is thid kid?
I don't care. Would you just kick him out already?
I can't work with him.
I can't do that.
I'll get his parents, and give them a word or two.
Hey, brat, who are you?
Why are you here?
Where are you from?
Listen to me, damn it!
K-k-k-k-k-k-k...
Kick him out! Get rid of him!
What a little shit.
He's light years away from being cute.
Why couldn't the front desk hick him out?!
But really, what was that all about?
Maybe he got lost during a school trip?
Don't wander all the way up here!
This is an adult work space.
It's our battleground.
He's really gutsy today.
Probably because we get visited today.
By that sponsor's agent.
You know, Hara... Horo... Hire... Hare...
It's Hirata Heita-san.
Yeah. He's coming.
Is he trying to fire someone again?
No, I guess it's not like that.
But I can understand why Massan got so irritated.
That quiz thing didn't go well, after all.
If that's the case, we better keep a low profile today.
I don't like him eighter.
Really?
Really!
He probably doesn't think of A.D.'s as human!
I agree with him too.
What are you doing?!
Hurry up and get ready! Sheesh.
Damn you all...
Densuke, open the door.
OK.
Who is it?
W-what?!
Don't come this way!
That's so mean!
Thank you for waiting, señorita.
Let's go to Tahiti for our honeymoon.
It's a short trip on my private jet.
What dou you mean?
Oh, come on.
It is an unspoken proposal from a shy guy like me.
Je t'aime.
What the hell?!
Who the hell are you?!
Why do you try to obstruct me?!
K. Taro?
So what?
You shouldn't be violent.
K. Taro...
There are too many matches.
I heard that you have implemented a cutting-edge-technology robot.
I would very much like to see it.
Will you go home once you see it?!
Go home right away?!
Go home immediately?!
Calm down!
Shut up!
Then I will let you see it.
Hey, Roboco!
Yes.
See? This is the robot-sama you wanted to see.
Huh? Who is?
Her! Look!
How dare you act like that to my fiance.
Fiance?
We're not engaged.
You're right.
But we're tied already heart to heart!
Now you've done it...
My most-precious-next-to-life ... 26 of THE HAIRES!
Absolutely unforgivable!
Roboco! Show him proof that you're a robot!
Yes.
You must not, señorita!
Such adult pleasure is too early for me!
Oh, but the sweet scent of the forbidden fruit taunts me.
Idiot! See?! See?!
See?!
Why do you have to bully him at his level?
Are you really a robot?
No, I'm an android.
This is a fraud!
Robots must have square bodies, with lots of lights,
and they've got to launch lots of missiles!
She's not a toy, you idiot.
Ha! You even proposed to this Roboco.
How pathetic.
Guys like you are called Robo Fetish.
They're the lowest beings of the human race, worthy only of shame!
It actually means such a crual thing?
Ha, you Robo Fetish!
Go home and go suck on your mama's boobies!
It even hurts me too.
Now you've done it.
It's okay.
Is it really okay?
I'm an android.
Who cares about him crying?!
You're not Robo Fetish, Taro-san.
But things could happen... like he could be the son of our president.
And he tells his papa about all this, and we all get fired...
No way...
How could that be...
Oh yeah, but I've heard...
that our president only has daughters,
and our sponsor is still single.
See?! Seeeeeeee?!
Don't make me worry, damn it!
You Robo Fetish Brothers!
You guys are the enemy of the human race!
Go home to Robo Fetish Planet, and dance your Robo Fetish Dance.
That's mean!
You're groovin, Massan.
So pathetic.
Long time no see, everyone.
Heita-san.
Neigh whinny whinny!
Long time no see!
Kacchin-san! What are you doing?
Neigh whinny whinny!
We just happened to run into each other out there,
and he begged to be my horse.
Oh, I'm really just like a horse to the sponsor.
Neigh whinny whinny!
That's the worst comeback to the workplace ever.
Don't look at me like that!
What's the commotion about?
Well, some stupid brat wandered in, so...
Bullying a kid, huh?
No, not really bullying...
Stupid brat, huh?
Would you like to too, Heita-san?
Ah, well...
I like these too.
Kids make me cry too.
Get ahold of yourself, Mister President!
President?
President?!
Presi...dent?
Heita!
That's right, it's Heita.
I'm your faithful secretary, Heita!
Nice to meet you.
They...
They bullied me!
What?
What's going on?!
How could this be?! Unforgivable!
Absolutely unforgivable!
Who do you think he is?!
Kodomo Taro...
CoDoMo Construction, CoDoMo Shopping, CoDoMo Bank, etc.
He is the General Executive of CoDoMo Group, consisting of 103 companies,
and the world's best child president...
Right!
He is...
the head of CoDoMo Group - a child president, Kodomo Taro-sama!
Good evening, everyone.
This is your android host, Maico.
With the generous help from our sponsor we're planning a special CoDoMo program.
Our correspondents from New York, London, Beijing, Shanghai,
Paris, and Berlin are catching the newest CoDoMo scoops.
Stupid AD
Today's program is filled with news that will satisfy your CoDoMo Life.
We call this Maico's CoDoMo Paradise!
Our guest is...
I'm Kodomo Taro from the company who looks at our future, CoDoMo Group.
Je t'aime.
Maico's Diary
This is the legendary script writer, Suga-chan.
When I woke up this morning, I was sleeping on a bench in a park,
and my wallet was gone.
What a surprise
to have a child president.
With this important fact,
Maico's memory stays
busy too. But was
this really okay?
I would like for our
staff to come up with
more clever ideas.
On top of that, my nose was covered with dried blood,
and my body ached all over.
It's such a mystery.
I tried to solve it myself, too...
Something must have happened while I was sleeping!
Yeah, I'm getting close to the truth!
Grooving!
Next Android Ana Maico 2010
Next Episode
G-Shaped
G is English. Actually, a letter.
I'm groovin' so high!
I'm cool!