The sudden tragedy that hit the studio.
Will Maico be able to continue the program without the script writer?
Come on, Maico!
fax: Aren't you airing Yukie-chan S.O.S.?
Why...
Vampire Unit
Why didn't you tell us anything?
It's because he's a radio artist.
Because he was, he wanted to stay on the scene until the last minute.
Why?
Is this program really worth that much?
Whether it is or not is up to Suga himself.
Nobody has any right to stop him.
Densuke!
Yes?
What can we do for Suga?
It is to carry on with this program.
It is to let Suga-san have the best program in the hospital.
Well done.
I won't forgive even the smallest mistakes.
So be prepared.
Yes.
The song is ending.
Maico, it's almost time.
Ume-san, give me the best jingle ever.
Maico-chan...
What's the matter, Maico?
Why aren't you talking?
Look at me!
I don't care what. Just talk, Maico.
Suga is listening.
Speak for him, damn it!
Please don't break. Not today.
Not today...
We can't goof up today, Maico!
The radio drama, Yukie-chan S.O.S., will be off the air this week due to certain circumstances.
In its place, let me talk.
Let's me talk for the sake of my precious person.
Please.
Last week, we had a serious problem in the studio.
The script writer, Suga-san, vomited blood and became unconscious.
All the staff members ran up to him, and took him to the hospital.
But I just stood right where I was.
I wasn't too shocked to move.
I'm sorry, Suga-san.
I was measuring you with my built-in sensors.
I was recording the dropping surface temperature and the heart rate on my hard disk.
Why didn't I run up to you, Suga-san?
What are you talking about?
I heard that Suga-san's life was saved because of the data I provided.
My specs as an android came in useful.
But, if there is a person falling unconscious nearby,
isn't it better to run up to that person?
At least other staff members did that.
I tried to simulate which was the better action to take,
but the logic fell into an eternal loop, and I couldn't come up with a solution.
Was I wrong?
I plan on asking Suga-san when he comes back.
But since he was hospitalized, no visitors have been allowed,
and I can't even see him.
According to my data, he has weakened significantly already.
I'm worried about Suga-san.
I'm very worried.
It has been only 5 months since I have been booted up, so I do not know much about Suga-san.
The Suga-san I know wears glasses, has a physique that has taken in too many calories,
and always liked to stick his thumb up for anything, and say "You're shining" and "You're glowing."
He liked to smoke,
and liked to drink, but couldn't drink;
he's Star-san's fan,
and he's a bit slow at writing scripts,
and the finished scripts usually contained 6% misspellings.
He also has a unique quirk that makes him write scripts faster when he sees other other people's misfortune.
When this program got started, teamwork among the staff members didn't exist.
Quarrels never ceased,
and at times we got violent,
and we have even boycotted the program.
But only Suga-san was always smiling.
I can remember his words...
That "I'm going to write as good and legendary of a script in this program as the one from 10 years ago,"
"for Live from the North Pole Crossing."
That "I'm going to rise up and shine!"
And Suga-san was...
Suga-san was...
I don't enough information.
I want to talk more about Suga-san,
but there is not enough data for it.
I want to tell him why I, an android, can be here.
It came across well enough.
Yeah.
No.
Even if it's faltering, she wants to say more to Suga-san.
The feelings inside of her.
Don't we want to let her?
Isn't there...
Isn't there something?
What the hell's that reaction?!
Think more about that person!
This Vampire Unit-kun is always alone, and feeling down!
I don't remember reading such a letter.
I wrote it.
Isn't it shining?
Maico-chan, Vampire Unit-kun!
Remember that letter.
Vampire Unit-kun?
Remember it!
Try hard and remember it!
Try hard and...
Keep trying, Maico-chan.
I can't do anything,
other then cheer for you.
Keep trying.
There is one!
My favorite memory!
It was a letter sent to Maico's 30,000 Friends corner,
sent by the pen-name Vampire Unit-kun.
The handwriting was that of Suga-san.
I have it in my memory.
Back then, I advised Suga-san through the microphone with my own words, as I thought on my own...
I kept making mistakes too, and got yelled at by the director every day.
I make mistakes all the time, but I believe I can put forward an effort not to make mistakes.
Everything ends if you give up.
So...
Suga-san, please keep trying.
Please get healthy, and write the script for the program again.
I don't like not having any more new data about Suga-san.
The radio drama isn't over yet either.
I also want you to create a new corner.
Suga-san, don't get defeated by the illness.
Keep trying, trying, and trying!
Suga-san, are you listening to me?
Can you hear my voice?
There is a nice poem written by this program's mixer, Ume-san.
I would like to dedicate it with my own arrangement.
Suga-san is gone,
leaving me, Densuke-san, Director-san, and all the staff in the studio behind.
We don't have any scripts written by Suga-san in today's program.
We can't hear the next episode of the radio drama either.
But, Suga-san,
neither Izumi-san, Ume-san, or Kacchin-san need it.
We just want to see you.
I know that the stars are just burning matter, like the sun.
But still let me wish upon you, dear stars.
Please let me see Suga-san.
Please let me...
Densuke?
Yes?
Maico's voice is reaching Suga, isn't it?
Yes!
She's the best personality!
I don't care if you're a sponsor or the agent. I won't hear any complaints!
What's wrong with this broadcast?
It's so great!
It's shining so brightly!
Kacchin-san!
N-no way...
What's the matter, Kachi-ko!
Right now, Suga-san just...
At the hospital, Suga-san just...
Suga-san just...
Suga-san, please try, try, and try hard.
I'm cheering for you.
I'm praying for your safe being.
Maico's Diary
This is Suga-chan, leaving you with a glow!
You know, it was bothering me when I entered Heaven.
Today sorry there's nothing really nothing
Shimane and Tottori, which was which?
They both look alike, and they're both near each other.
It's so confusing.
Shimane was known as Izumo a long time ago,
but knowing that doesn't tell me anything.
Haha! Haha! Haha!
Now, I'm going to go flirt with the cute angels.
Next Android Ana Maico 2010
Super Maico
Maico, I'm cheering for you from Heaven!