This story is about Maico and her surrounding staff.
It's a neo human drama...
Are you shitting me?!
You're Evil
That's cool.
That's fun.
Then let's try something a bit perverted, with two of these next.
What's that one like?
Idiot!
Are you in grade school?
Are you bored?
Are you bored gradeschoolers?
Huh?!
We are none of those.
She's right.
We are the radio staff, delivering dreams, hope, and love to all the good kids around the country.
So, radio staff, is Yukie-chan's script ready?
Sorry, Massan.
Why am I the one getting hit?!
What would you do if I hit the precious scriptwriter's head and something went wrong?
And you don't care about the A.D.?!
So, Suga, when's the script gonna be ready?
Sorry, but I've hit a wall today.
I can't see ahead. Man, how troublesome.
Do you realize when the recording is?!
It's today!
We have less than half a day!
We have no time to goof around!
You might not believe me, but I'm thinking hard too.
Man, how troublesome.
What a difficult man.
What are we going to do?
We have no other choice.
Let's use the trump card.
The trump card?
Well, what are we holding back for?
Then I wouldn't have been hit meaninglessly.
I'm glad you agree.
Your cooperation is indispensable for this.
Wait a minute!
Why are you hitting me?!
Suga has this attribute that makes him write faster when he sees someone else's misfortune.
That's so twisted.
It's all for the script.
Get hit by me, and stay unhappy for now.
It's hard for me too.
But it's all for the script!
Hold your tears and endure this.
Ume-san, give us a big one.
So noisy!
Now look, Suga!
Top it with seafood and nattou on a regular crust.
Thanks.
Now what, Massan?
You! Weren't you watching me beat Robo Fetish up?!
I was.
Don't you feel anything after watching that?!
Don't you get any creativity from his patheticness?!
But you know, it happens every day.
Man, I'm also in trouble.
I see.
For him, seeing Robo Fetish get beat up is already a part of daily life.
What do I do now?
You're so useless!
That's so mean in more ways than one.
So that means we have to come up with a new misfortune, right?
Aren't you getting smart, Roboco?
Thank you.
Man! Even Maico-chan doesn't hold back the cruel thoughts!
But what would make him suffer without using violence?
What now?
Slip.
Huh?
Slip on this.
Step on this banana peel and slip on it like a dumbass!
Nobody would fall for that!
Everyone except Suga and Densuke, come here.
Yes.
Hey! Why aren't you calling me too?!
Izumi-chan, you too.
Don't you want to finish up this script and go home?
Now, listen...
What's going on?
All right, get to your positions.
Yes.
What are you plotting?
Hey, what's going on?
What's going on?
Welcome to our exciting event!
The rolling splash on the banana!
The challenger is...
Mister Robo Fetish!
Thanks.
Are you ready?
Sure.
Now, go!
What now?
Is seeing me slip really that fun?
It is so wrong,
to enjoy someone else's misfortune!
I won't slip!
I won't slip like a dumpass for this cruel staff!
Listen, everyone...
You really slipped!
You're such a dumbass! Robo Fetish!
It's so pointless.
That's so mean.
Robo Fetish-kun, you were shining.
I have never seen any human being trip so stupidly in my life!
Sure...
Your tripping showed the misfortune you were born with.
Indeed, it is the natural-born misfortune!
I'm starting to get my creativity back!
Just watch me! I'm gonna write!
Good luck!
Leave it to me!
Well done.
Matsu-san.
Densuke-san, that was very cool.
Maico-chan.
Man, I'm stuck.
It's too soon!
You only wrote the title down.
Well, this is about if for a banana misfortune.
What did I trip for?
There are a few more left.
It'll go nowhere at this rate.
Isn't there any other fresh and powerful misfortune?
By the way, didn't we have another misfortune expert?
Man, I'm late.
What the hell! You're late, Kacchin!
Sorry, I've been pretty busy.
What's that?
I was asked to give these to Masudamasu-san.
Are these nutrition supplements?
Hello? This is Kacchin.
Are you supposed to take one?
It's me.
I need one to survive this though job.
Oh, Masudamasu-san.
Did you get them?
The nutrition supplement, right?
Yey, I did.
Can we take two or three?
Matsu-san looks pretty exhausted.
You can, but those are nitro.
Nitro?
Yeah. Nitroglycerin.
I ordered them to demolish my house.
I'll come get them later, so keep them there for now.
See ya.
Nitro...
That's nitroglycerin...
What's this?
What is this?
It's nitroglycerin.
It is a liquid you get from a chemical reaction between glycerin, nitric acid, and sulfuric acid.
Extreme caution is needed for handling it due to its hight vulnerability to any shock.
It's also known as one of the ingredients in dynamite.
D... dynamite??
Idiot! Don't shake it!
I don't mean to!
Please put the lid on.
It'll go BOOM if I spill it.
Why did you throw it?! Would you put the lid on?!
Maico-chan, can you?
Sure.
What are you doing?
You're shining.
Suga-san?
This is so unlucky.
This is such a shining misfortune!
Suga!
Massan! I'm so grooving right now!
My creativity is overflowing!
Would you give me a break?
This could be life or death!
15 minutes!
Give me 15 minutes, and I'll give you the best script!
Matsu-san!
Massan!
Densuke!
Yes?
Hang on.
NO!
Thank you, Massan!
So evil.
You're so evil!
I'll gladly be evil for the sake of the program!
Oh?
What's the matter?!
Right here, Yukie-chan dives into the sea,
and the dolphin, Willie, comes to the rescue,
umm...
We need a bit more.
Hey, Roboco!
I'm an android.
Watch out!
I hate this job!
I'm going home.
You can't.
I'll lose my balance if you move now.
I don't want to die here with all these scumbags!
I'm elite! And being elite is great!
How's that, Suga?
So good, Massan!
I'm sure, I'm sure...
It'll be fine. It'll be fine. It'll be fine...
Stop that.
Hello.
I have your pizza.
We're busy right now!
Come back later!
I can't do that.
It'll be over 30 minutes soon.
Excuse me! Please open!
What a forceful pizza delivery guy.
Man, I'm really getting the head!
That's the spirit, Suga!
I have a delivery for you!
Hold the door, everyone!
Who called for him?!
It was Suga-san.
Right here, Yukie super action!
I'll kill him.
I swear I'll kill him!
Hey! Watch out!
Bravo!
So great!
Thanks for waiting.
Here's your delivery from Pizzadnald.
Please take this.
Oh, sure.
Massan, this is a masterpiece.
It's too bright, I can't read it...
Maico's Diary
This is Kacchin.
Do you know the cucumber pack?
Just slice them up and put them on your face,
and the nutrition soaks into your skin, and your skin gets so smooth.
I learned today that
nitroglycerin is
a very dangerous
matter.
Everyone was surprised
too, except for Suga-san.
Shy was he not hurt?
Humans are very mysterious
I have my mother have some sliced everyday, and I never miss it.
Since I'm the elite P.R. officer, I must watch out for my looks.
Next Android Ana Maico 2010
Morse
To tell you the truth, I was a boy scout once,
so I know all the Morse code by heart.
Next Episode
Morse
CQ CQ CQ...