Numerous problems fall upon the android, Ana Maico.
Use your robot powers and slove the mysteries, Maico!
You are the star, perhaps!
MAICO 2010
It's very special tonight.
Jump Out Maico 2010!
Sorry I'm late.
Fly
Good evening. This is Maico.
Here, these are all the CD's that we had requests for.
We have a special program tonight.
Thanks.
We are filling the programm with all the requests oldies from the listeners.
Did I goof up?
There are many oldies out there too.
Izumi-san?
It might be a special song just for you,
or it could just be a very old song.
Did I goof up?
Oh, I guess they're fine.
But what's important is that the song is important to you.
By the way, where's Kacchin?
I heard he took a vacation.
I guess he got scared of the invisible assasin.
Now, let's start with this first letter.
What's the matter, Ume-san?
This is from pen-name, Ame-Hitode-san Saitama.
And, then?
There is a fly...
This song is from when I was in the 8th grade.
in the booth?
I sang this song at a karaoke place,
How can he tell?
and the girl who I liked told me that I sounded good.
I can hear...
This song has been my favorite since then.
Yeah, I can too.
Don't just hear it!
Why is there a fly in the studio, you dumb ass!?
There we go.
The requested song is Travel Kibun de Trouble Night by THE  Kanpouyaku.
Isn't it because we were eating in the studio?
I know that!
I'm upset about the lack of your studio maintennance!
Roboco, you can see a fly buzzing around you, right?
Yes, I can.
There is one.
It's a male Lucilia caesar.
Then here's my order.
Smash the fly.
Smash it?
Right!
But the fly will break if I do that.
That's fine!
I don't care if it breaks or dies!
Do it now!
I can't.
What?!
Destruction of a living organism is prohibited by my programming.
You are a robot build for broadcasting, right?
Yes, I'm a broadcasting android.
A broadcasting robot would be a pro.
It's common sense for that pro to eliminate that fly!
Now, kill that fly!
No! I can't violate the programmed commands.
Um, the song is almost over.
Right, Izume-san?
Oh?
Yeah...
Roboco, the song we be over soon.
Do it right.
I can't.
Idiot! Not the fly!
The song is almost over!
Um, did you like that?
It was Travel Kibun de Travel Night by THE Kanpouyaku.
She's so inflexible.
The next song is Tsunamigui Rock n' Roll Sarukuma Inuo-san.
Densuke, you do it!
Me?
Of cource.
This song was requested by pen-name Iwa-san from Aichi,
It's your fault for not checking up on the studio properly.
pen-name Tsuki-no-Uta-san from Kagoshima, and many others.
Right, Ume-san?
Ume-san is a first-class mixer.
So, let's hear it.
Tsumamigui Rock n' Roll. Here we go!
Even the slightest noise can obstruct his work.
Here, we're on a song now.
Go!
Densuke-san...
are you going to break the fly?
Uh, well...
Sorry, Maico-chan!
Robo Fethish!
Ouch!
Can't you kill a dumb fly?!
Huh?!
It's rather quick.
No wonder!
I was the idiot who asked YOU, a man who gets excited by looking at Roboco's legs,
a man who's lower that a fly, a Robo Fetish.
Right?!
Please, don't blame yourself so much.
I'm blaming you!
You dumb fly...
DIE!
Give that to me!
You damn fly!
Oh, the song is ending!
There, that was Sarukuma Inuo-san's Tsumamigui Rock n' Roll.
The next request is from pen-name Peko-san of Tokyo.
She requested Donchaka Yuki Matsuri and Ski de Pururun by Russel Josetsutai.
Let's hear two songs with no breaks.
What are you doing?!
Get up!
Before yhe fly flies away!
All right, already.
I can't reach.
Densuke, jump!
OK.
Are you all right?
Don't you know how to control yourself?
Sorry.
Damn!
Densuke! After it!
OK!
This on-air is so shining!
If we can have programs like this every time, I'll go way past the best in the world,
and I will be he best in the universe!
Densuke! Over there!
OK!
Ack! It flew away!
If I don't break the fly, it will disturb the broadcast.
All right!
I swear I'll get it this time.
There!
But I can't break the fly.
Don't be so slow!
Run! Jump! Do it now!
But it's disturbing the broadcast.
Quit panting and move!
It's all your fault!
But I can't break the fly.
But it's disturbing the broadcast.
But...
You're so useless.
Don't move...
Damn!
Watch out!
But it's disturbing the broadcast.
But I can't break the fly.
Why is it so heavy?!
But it's disturbing the broadcast.
This damn TV!
But...
Man, it hurts!
All right, go get that box.
OK.
But I can't break the fly.
But... But...
Here you go.
This box contains Ume-san's 7 tools of the broadcaster.
Does this work on flies too?
Densuke,
light this and set it up.
OK.
A blow gun?
Ume-san, I don't understand your intention.
This is it.
Densuke! Use this!
OK.
But... But... But...
Don't you get that that's dangerous?!
Oh, I just...
Just what?!
Ouch...
Are you OK?
Just go kill that damn fly!
OK.
But... But... But... But...
Maico-chan?
B... u... t...
Maico-chan, what's wrong?
Come on, Maico-chan!
My, this looks fun.
It's the best!
Oh, my.
Ume-san, we'll segue into the next song.
Izumi-chan, get ready.
OK...
Hurry.
The song is ending.
Where's the fly?
Use the spray, Densuke!
But you just said it's dangerous.
You sprayed it on me with no hesitation,
but you can't do it to Roboco?!
If you wanna claim to not be a Robo Fetish, then spray!
Spray right now!
My lover's today's everything...
Sukina hito no kyou no subete...
Kill the fly!
Idiot!
What's the matter with you, Densuke-san?!
Uh, um, no!
Densuke was trying to spray you!
This is spectacular!
I was trying to stop him.
What the hell?!
That's so mean, Densuke-san!
That's not it, Maico-chan!
Forget about that! Now, the fly!
Yeah! It's the fly's fault!
Izumi-san, I was just...
The fly...
So gross...
Hey! The mic is on!
How are we doing, Ume-san?
Wha?! Uh! No!
What am I doing?
Yes, it's time to say goodbye as we listen to Sato Machiko-san's Koi Shite Kiss.
I guess the airtime passed by quickly today.
I heard that fun times fly by more quickly,
but, as an android, I don't understand that feeling.
Izumi-san,
What?
I don't know anything about the fly.
No, not about that.
I found this out by accessing the Idol Databank...
Sato Machiko-san is actually...
It's so shining!
Why did you do that?
An android would not understand.
Maico's Diary
This is the chief director, Masudamasu.
Do you know totocalcio?
It's legal gambling on the soccer games.
A fly wandered in during the airtime, and was a mess. Am I the only one who thought we could just open the door and let it fly? Is that why I was scolded by Izumi-san? I can't understand.
I've been playing it for 5 years, but I've never lost so far.
People call me the God of Gamblers.
The Japan Broadcasting System is so lucky to have me!
Next Android Ana Maico 2010
I don't understand.
Say what?
You still don't understand?
Next Episode
I don't understand
Like I said, totocalcio is...