Maico.
That's the name of the android announcer that the Japan Broadcasting System has hired to make the best radio program!
Can You Hear Me?
Sup?! Are you all here, you useless bunch of junk?
Now that I'm director of this program,
we will aim for a listener rating of 20%!
So get... ready...
Hey, hey, hey, the broadcast starts in 30 minutes.
What the hell?
I told them to do the usual,
but I wanted to see them show up early on the first day at least, damn it.
Good morning.
Hey, I thought some super hot chick showed up.
Are you setting up new sound effects for the new program?
Yes.
Good work, Ume-san.
But, hey, the hard days start again today.
How long will my hair last?
Good morning.
Hey, long time no see.
Are you done listing up the CDs?
Of couce!
Since there are no requests, I picked the songs I like.
I will list the songs and their timings on the cue sheet.
She's participating in this, even though it's delaying her wedding to K.T.
Really, she's become such a good woman.
And there's the man who hasn't changed a bit.
Good morning.
You really haven't changed.
Heh?
What?
You just ruined my good mood.
We must have some history between us in our previous lives.
Just like a cobra and mongoose.
So, which pf those were you reincarnated from?
Maybe the mongoose?
Then I would lose every time!
I'll take the cobra, then.
You just admitted that you're the loser.
That's why you're a good-for-nothing.
You sound like a father and son.
That's so mean, Izumi-chan.
That hurts.
Shut up!
Would you please stop?
Let me hit you more!
I've been so stressed because I couldn't hit you for a long time.
I did my prep yesterday!
That's good.
That's commendable progress for you.
Would you please stop hitting me while you compliment me?
At about this time...
he always showed up, like Densuke's savior.
Sup!
H-hello!
I'm Saito. I was promoted from part-time to full-time today, and was assigned here.
It's like a dream that I can create a program with you.
I am still inexperienced as a script writer, but it's nice to meet you!
Yeah, let's do it.
Nice to meet you.
Man, we got a completely different type of guy this year.
Eh, Suga?
Excuse me.
Hello.
Saito-kun, is it?
I know you're nervous, but is the script done?
Of cource!
I've been writing the script for 5 days without any sleep!
Today marks the start of my career as a legendary script writer.
Legendary, huh?
To match the broadcasts you've been making,
I tried, tried, and tried hard, and wrote this.
Let's Go Maico, huh?
Yes.
I wanted Maico-chan to go through even further improvement, and picked this title.
I couldn't decide between this and "Go! Go!" for a couple af days...
That sounds good, Saito-kun.
I really think it's cool.
Don't act like the boss!
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Maico, the personality of this program.
And I'm an android that belongs to the Japan Broadcasting System.
Wow!
Yay!
Long live the androids!
Androids are the best!
Androids are so cool!
What the hell's this?
Well, the beginning is very important,
so I wrote this, weaving in a self introduction and some light French jokes.
How is it?
It's pretty good for a rookie.
There are no misspellings either.
Thank you.
You just gave me the confidence to make it as a script writer.
I'm going to hold your words in my heart for eternity.
The hell with the legends!
Matsu-san, don't do that.
Shut up!
I thought I'd be friendly at first, but this is my limits.
Is management trying to make us produce a stupid program again?
I'd rather go back to the country and raise tomatoes.
How is this reality?
Is it really fine, oh God of Radio?!
I think it's the worst program too.
But this is just the kind of program that will allow us to survive in this 21st Century media bubble.
Long time no see, everyone!
This androids should be able to aid and heal people's fragile hearts.
And you are the worst-of-the-bunch staff, sure to cause more problems.
The stubborn director who handled a life advice program for 15 year.
A muscular mixer who became silent because of a complex against his own voice.
The script writer who has never written anything before.
The former idol whose heart was broken.
The good-looking but useless assistant director...
And...
Why aren't you saying anything about me?
Please tell them that I'm the no-good P.R. officer who confuses them...
with cheap sense of planning and an off-the-wall feeling.
I don't want to.
That's cruel!
And that's the M Plan, right?
Yes.
We let the android experience many different situations,
so the beta test program could be tweaked to make it act more human.
That was our last radio program.
Because of you, 97% of the objective was met.
But something was different.
Was there a miscalculation in that 3%?
There was something in Maico that we could not get just by transferring the data to Super Maico.
No, that's not it.
That was the difference between the perfect and imperfect android.
Humans are imperfect too.
I'm missing something as well.
That's why I make an effort.
Maico-chan tried, tried, and tried hard for this missing screw.
A non-human can even get in touch with a human.
Actually, she could touch people's hearts because she was imperfect.
That's the ultimate android personality.
Her name is...
Her name is Maico.
Maico-chan...
I'm happy for you, Robo Fetish-kun.
Oh, don't say that, Izumi-san.
So this is really Maico-chan.
This is the first time I've seen the real thing.
What's in here?
What?
Actually, I've never seen it clearly either.
I can... open it, right?
No...
It's like peeking at a doll from below.
It's exciting, isn't it?
Underneath lies everything about this android personality.
My dear Maico-chan's everything will be disclosed!
Tada! Tada! Tada! Tada!
My dream is...
This is the reality of life.
Besides, it's the second time for me.
Masudamasu-san, why aren't the legs attached?
She got sent to the junkyard by mistake.
I rebuild her with all my effort using all the remaining parts.
No way...
The new legs will be build and will be here in two weeks.
I've been writing my script without sleep for this day...
I know how you feel.
Oh, no!
We only have 5 minutes before airtime!
Damn!
Densuke! Boot Maico up and put her in!
Got it.
Quit whining.
It's showtime now!
Yes!
We have less that 3 minutes left. Hurry!
Ume-san, give me the usual.
Hurry up, everyone.
Hurry up for my sake!
....
Densuke-san...
Maico-chan!
This is no time to be reminiscing, Densuke!!
We have less that 1 minute left.
Hurry up and get her in there!
O-oh, okay!
What is going on?
I know this is sudden, but we're about to go on the air.
Please!
Okay.
Maico is in!
50 seconds left.
No rehearsals! Got it?!
Okay to go.
What's up?
Densuke-san, please take these back.
Oh yeah, I have something I want to give you too.
That's...
This is yours, right?
Yes, it is.
Where do I need to put it?
No, I don't need it anymore.
I can continue to broadcast without that function as Maico, an android.
I see.
What's taking so long?!
Sorry.
Okay to go.
Maico.
Maico-chan.
Can you hear me, everyone?
Can you hear my voice?
Let's keep trying, trying, and trying!
The end.
Thank you. I will continue to speak to your hearts for ages to come, so my voice will keep reaching you. So it will reach you forever. I'm praying.
Thank you for your support all this time.
I'll be looking forward to the next time...
Matsu-san!
I came up with a shining new project!
I call it "Maico-san Select 2010"!
It's not just Maico, but I put "-san" on it to make a point!
The shining new project, "Maico-san Select 2010"!
Now, which one should I pick first?