An android announcer that the Japan Broadcasting System has hired: Maico.
Her voice gives love, courage, and energy to the depressed 21st century radio scene.
Things are still only at the beginning!
[Kaitai Shinsho = translation of Anatomische Tabellen by J.A.Kulmus]
Who are the three men that translated the "Kaitai Shinsho"?
Maeno Ryotaku.
Sugita Genpaku.
Who's the third?
Who is it?
It's Nakagawa Juuan.
How do you know this stuff so well?
Well, he's like the third one of "Let's Go Sanbiki".
So I guess nobody knows him.
Who's the third person?
"I'm Jun!"
You Know
"I'm Chosaku!"
"Minami Haruo!"
...is actually wrong.
Maico-chan, do you even understand what's going on?
I'm sorry.
I don't have the show biz database loaded, so I don't.
Who is it?
Who was it?
Shut up!
Quit goofing off.
We're not goofing off.
We're coming up with the questions for Million Dollar Quiz Hunter.
I told you that I don't approve of those stupid ideas!
Hello, this is Kacchin.
Oh, Katsumi.
I told you, I'm at work.
It's an important day today.
This might be our last.
I really don't care.
Right, cherry tomato?
What's the matter?
The sponsor's agent will be here shortly.
And is there something wrong with that?
We might get written up,
or someone might get fired,
or worst case scenario, the program might get cancelled.
I told you, I came up with a shining idea.
Yes?
A letter!
LIFE!
Listener Ratings Are
Listener ratings are life?
Absolutely!
No good!
On hold.
Super no good!
Absolutely no good!
OK!
No-good with a score of 82.6%.
Ouch!
Um, who might you be?
Who are you?
I'm A.D., Matsuo...
I refuse to talk with an A.D.!
P.R. officer, step forward!
Yes.
I'm the chief secretary of the CoDoMo Group, Hirata Heita.
Nice to meet you.
I have a pen.
Now.
Where's this much talked about android personality?
Oh, here. She's the one.
Hello. I'm Maice.
Umm...
The android is hard.
It's true.
She's rock solid.
It hurts.
Correction!
She's super okay, yeah!
What's up with him?
How come the listener ratings are so low, even with this diamond in the rough?
I don't get it.
You're absolutely right.
Actually, you can't really help it with such a no-good for nothing staff, doing a no-good carnival.
You're right!
How about we replace the entire staff, and refresh it with some new faces?
How dare you!
You traitor!
I'm a P.R. officer!
It's my duty to reflect the sponsor-sama's opinion!
You're the lowest.
Shut up!
Right?
Beautiful.
Your attitude towards your work has a certain beauty to it.
Well, thank you.
You could be the role model by sacrificing yourself.
Me too?
I won't let your effort go to waste.
Now, let's create a new future!
Just you and me.
Forget about the no-good programs of the past.
Until yesterday, you were a crane in a dumpster.
But you will be soaring into a beautiful sky from now on!
The sky is where the listeners are waiting!
Heita-san!
Please quit criticizing us before you've even seen us work.
Everyone is working very hard.
Don't put a no-good label on us yet!
Japan Broadcasting System policy clause 423:
The A.D. may not give advice to the sponsors!
Stop it!
Isn't a tad early to reach a conclusion?
And you are?
I'm the director, Matsu.
I'm the man who leads the group.
I see.
So you're responsible for the low listener ratings.
W-we're still getting there!
So you have a plan?
Well...
Do you?
Dooo you?
We do!
This is it.
Hey, that's mine!
Shut up!
Ume-san!
We call it a Million Dollar Quiz Hunter!
Million Dollar Quiz Hunter?
Million Dollar Quiz Hunter!
In this corner, I will ask questions to the listener over the phone.
It's a wonderful idea, giving out a million dollars,
if you can answer 5 questions in a row.
So who's the lucky person who will be the first to take the challenge for a million dollars?
Wonderful!
It's shining!
It's not!
Who's going to get a million dollars?
This is Adachi.
We'll go into the red if you pay up!
I'm so excited!
What the hell were you thinking?!
Oh, Adachi-san from the other day?
It wasn't my idea.
Stop this!
The first challenger is Adachi-san of 3rd street.
Quit it!
Quit!
Sit down.
This is a live broadcast.
Yay!
Now, question number one.
What is the proper name for a FAX?
We might be a no-good staff,
A Facsimile!
but we still put our spirits into it, and make it the best!
Bingo!
Now, question number two.
That's the spirit of the radio artists!
What is the capital of Slovenia?
Ljubljana!
Bingo!
Wow!
Question number three.
It'll be fine.
What is the next smallest unit from Micro?
I made the questions hellishly hard.
Nano!
Bingo!
Answering all five correctly would be nearly impossible.
Question number four.
What is the name of the director of this show?
Fine.
Let me watch until the end, then.
Are you sure?
Don't worry.
Matsu!
Bingo!
Congratulations!
You've answered four questions right.
You are one question away from a million dollars, Adachi-san.
Of course!
What's going on?!
Good luck.
She said one more!
One more!
So, here is the last question.
How do fireflies make their tails flash?
You better get the entire amount!
Tic, tic, tic, tic...
With a battery!
Bzzz!
Too bad.
The fireflies make their lights with luciferin and luciferase, reacting to a metallic phosphate and oxygen.
W-we're saved.
How the heck would I know that?!
That was too bad.
You were so close to a million dollars.
What's going on, Matsuo-san?!
Matsuo?
Ma-Matsuo?
You mean our A.D., Matsuo Densuke-san?
Just as I thought!
Yes.
Adachi-san, do you know Densuke-san?
What was that?
I expected some of the staff to get excited about a million dollars, so I swapped the last question.
This is not fair!
I heard I was guaranteed a million dollars if I called this number at this time.
And you fell for it!
That's cheating!
After all those speeches, you still had doubts about us?!
And now what, is this some kind of joke?
Of course!
And you fell for it too!
I couldn't help it.
I'm sorry, but I can't help you.
As a low-paid A.D., I can't miss such a chance!
This is so rude.
Wait a minute.
I can't believe you all would do this!
So the questions on these sheets are fake?
That's right.
This is only a game, you know.
This is unforgivable.
As a member of the broadcasting staff, I can't stand to be misinformed!
It's still incredibly rude!
Good bye, Adachi-san.
Why are you acting funny?
Have you leaked it to someone as well?
N- no way.
OK, who's next?
What's your name?
I can't say my real name, but let's just say I'm Kacchin-mama.
That's absurd...
Hang up!
Goodbye, Kacchin-mama-san.
Oh, hey, Kacchan?! What's going on?!
I'm sorry. It's an order from the director.
How could you do this?!
Who's next?
Don't be ridiculous, Kacchin-san!
This is Vampire Unit.
You're abusing your power!
You're at fault too!
Oh, Vampire Unit-san! Can you do the back flip on the bar yet?
Y-yes!
After hearing your encouragement, I practiced a lot.
Izumi!
We're still on the air.
It took me a while, but I can finally do it!
What are you doing?
Just a faxing.
It's an emergency.
That's wounderful!
Let me see it!
You're violating my privacy.
So how did it feel?
I don't care!
Really good!
Matsu-san! Let it go!
Maico-chan, you helped me so much.
I'm glad to hear it.
So, how are things with your classmates?
Yes. Now that I can do that back flip, nobody is mocking me anymore.
So now I'm really shining!
Change of plan.
The rain in Spain
falls mainly in the plains.
Izumi
Izumi.
Oh, th-that was nothing.
Anyway, I hope you try hard for the quiz too.
Damn you, you even encrypt your message?!
Damn you, all.
Sure!
Now, question number one.
Since we might get fired, I'll take that as my retirement fund.
What is the definition of NAT?
Eh? Uh...
You're all so unfair!
Let me think here,
Your really change that much when money is involved?!
How pathetic...
I have heard this somewhere...
Geez! All of you!
Pathitic.    Pathetic.     Pathetic.
Pathetic.     Pathetic.    Pathetic.
Pathetic.     Pathetic.     Pathetic.
How could this be be happening?!
I know!
What do you know, here's just how bad this no-good staff really is.
It is the computer term, Network Address Transferring!
Bzzz! I'm sorry, that's not it.
Oh, that's not it?! Oh, man!
I'm sorry.
Goodbye.
OK, that was too bad for him.
Director?
And our next challenger is...
Cut it out, already!
Oh, Masudamasu-san!
What's the matter?
How pathetic!
Well, what else?
Is a million dollars more important to you than this program?
I'm calling in for the million dollars.
Don't you have any pride?!
I wasn't expecting to hear from you.
To have more people listen to this program.
There's no rule against me.
To have them enjoy the show!
Then let's go.
Isn't that our duty as radio artists?!
Question number one.
What color is a giraffe's tongue?
No matter how badly people talk of me, or no matter how much they mock me,
Black.
Bingo!
if there is even one listener who enjoys the show, I don't need any money!
Question number two.
What comes after Jurassic period?
Cretaceous period.
Bingo!
Director...
Massan...
Question number three.
Whe were this year's Nobel Peace Prize winners?
Sorry, Heita-san, that you had to see this.
John Hume and David Trimble.
Yes, it was bad.
Bingo!
Question number four.
But it's no use to move this no-good staff to any other assignments.
What was Sylf's college major?
Music.
For now, we will change our plans to do a buy-back.
Bingo!
Now you're off to the final question!
I can handle any kind of question.
Heita-san...
The staff is all third-rate, all a bunch of no-goods,
For "Let's go Sanbiki", who is the third member after Jun and Chosaku?
but your spirit is first rate.
So I'm going to bet on that for a while longer.
OK?
Tic toc tic toc...
Oh yes.
Don't forget about the listener ratings either.
O-of course!
Massan, you're really shining today!
Oh, I know!
It's Onoda-no-Dai!
Oh, stop that.
Bingo!
Wow!
You got them all right!
So, when do I get the prize money?
What's the matter?
We will deliver it to you in just a few days.
But I'm impressed by you again for answering all of them right, Masudamasu-san!
There is no question that I can't answer.
Congratulations to you!
Now, let's break for a CM.
Maico's Diary
Yo!
I'm Suga-chan, the legendary script writer, who made the live broadcast of the North Pole crossing!
Masudamasu-san
is amazing!
She answered all of
the questions easily!
But, I don't understand
why all the staff was
looking at me so weird,
including the sponsor...
You know, show biz is so fancy and shining.
The other day, I stayed up all night, drinking with a new rising singer.
I ended up paying a 120,000 yen bill!
Man, being a lady killer isn't easy either.
So my lunch today is just a peanut butter sundwich and milk.
It's a bit bittersweet.
But they're shining on their own too.
Next time - Android Anna Maico 2010
Miso Cucumber
That's yummy too.