An android announcer that the Japan Broadcasting System has hired: Maico.
Her voice gives love, courage, and energy to the depressed 21st century radio scene.
Things are still only at the beginning!
Let's start, already.
How can we start a party without booze?
Our mid-term party!
Why are we doing this at such a weird time?
To raise our spirits!
Roboco's suckage really decreased recently.
The Lowest
I'm trying my best.
Hey, I like that smile.
Maico-chan, you're shining.
Suga,
quit saying "shining" all the time.
It's annoying.
Why?
I hate words like "shining", "smooth", yadda yadda.
I've never said "smooth".
I don't care! Just keep smiling like an idiot!
Oh, it fell out.
I'm back.
You're too slow!
Give me a break!
These are hellishly heavy.
Pick them up before making excuses!
As if this was my fault...
She's an android.
I know.
How did she know?
Here.
Thanks.
Oh? Aren't you gonna drink, Izumi-chan?
I drove.
You could take a taxi tonight.
We can share one.
We live in opposite directions.
Don't mind the minor details.
Let's drink up.
No thanks.
You sure?
She's got someone.
How come you're so optimistic?
Maico can intake 500 g of food and 500 cc of liquid, and store it temporarily for socialization purposes.
Why would only mine explode?!
You can use it as a carry-out bag as well.
Everyone get some?
Ume-san.
This untactful program is finally starting to go smoothly.
All thanks to the team's effort.
47% due to my skill,
35% due to Ume-san's technique,
10% due to Izumi-chan,
8% to Suga,
5% to Roboco, I guess.
Well, let's keep...
Why wasn't I included?
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
Um, me too...
Kacchin, I'll share 10% of mine.
The way you say that is not nice.
Adding it all up comes out to 105%.
And... me?
I'm glad you pointed that out.
Don't you get it yet?!
You're the -5%.
That comes out to 100% even.
No way...
That's mean.
Don't get so depressed.
I will share my points for 20,000 yen per each percent.
I can't accept sympathy percents.
No, you need to buy it, at 20,000 yen each.
That's even worse!
I can give 3% of mine, if you'd like.
Are you sure?
I really don't need it.
Then why are you keeping 2%?
So how many percents do we have now?
Enough!
Quit playing the math game.
What I was saying is...
Now that things are falling into place,
let's keep up the good work.
Got it?!
Answer!
All right.
Cheers.
Cheers!
I'm gonna drink 'til dawn!
Cheers.
So good!
What's up with this wimp?
You don't have to force yourself.
Oh, I'm fine.
I don't mean to stay pissed all the time.
It's just the way I am.
I wanna feel good too.
Right?
Same here.
Honestly, how are we?
People do talk about us.
Actually, the violent woman in glasses is meeting with the company director.
Is she doing some show for the director?
No way.
But I don't think it's a bad talk.
You're right.
You gotta be right!
Our efforts gotta be recognized.
You're right.
We're workin' hard.
Ya, we are.
Yes.
Let's keep going!
Yes, let's!
What is it, Director?
Increasing our budget?
Eye!
My eye!
What?
You irritated?
Is the listener rating going down?
Maico's ability improves I step each day,
3 setps in 3 days.
Steps forward 3 steps, then 2 extra steps too!
Why would it go down?
Then why are you looking so disappointed?
The rate of growth is too slow.
Listener Rating
Zoomed In View
This is more than enough.
This micro growth isn't enough for management.
Our sponsor's agent is coming to see us next week.
That means...
Yup.
It's a performance review.
Unless the rating goes back to 1% within 1 month,
there will be a staff reduction.
What?!
If you have time to party, come up with ideas to put the rating back to 1%.
Come up with what?!
And what about you?
I have a secret meeting with the general manager.
What secret meeting?
Take care.
Hey!
What a selfish woman!
She must have been Queen of Planet Selfish.
What are we gonna do?
We gotta come up with something, if you don't wanna be laid off.
Suga!
Damn it! Wake up!
Come up with some idea!
So is it gonna be me? I'm gonna get laid off?
Why can't you be useful for once?!
Yeah, who else?
Don't say that!
Why won't you give up?
Suga-san!
Give us a great idea!
Any idea!
Massan, you're shining.
What about me?
Am I not shining?
Give it a rest!
Am I not shining, Suga-san?
And what are we going to do today?
Who knows!
Booze!
Gimme some booze!
Sure.
This is the worst.
How could I not drink in this situation?
I'm troubled too.
And suffering.
Lost 26 yesterday.
18 today.
I'm not losing them willingly.
I want them to grow!
You understand that, Ume-san?
You're the best, Ume-san.
I say "Hey!" and you say "Yo!"
Damn, I wish you were a woman.
We could have build a happy family together.
Stop!
I'm Kacchin!
Yes, this is Kacchin.
Oh, it's you.
Please get off.
Oh, it's nothing.
It's part of work.
I told you, I'll let you decide.
No, I'm not being careless!
I...
Alright, flowers.
I'm fine with flowers.
No! I didn't do that!
That was...
Yeah, that's an elephant.
We only had 3 channels!
We couldn't even receive Japanese programs on the radio.
Who could possibly blame me for wanting the glory in mass media?
No, you don't understand.
You don't understand at all, Suga-san!
I had to write home that I was already a top notch director.
Am I wrong, Suga-san?
Am I not good enough?
Hey, Suga-san!
You're shining.
This really is the worst.
No wonder this program's going to fail.
That's not good.
I was just getting better at my job.
I don't want it to fail now.
Wouldn't you be disappointed, Izumi-san, if something failed halfway?
I...
I'm used to being cut off halfway.
But how can you know if you're right if we quit halfway?
Are all androids insensitive like you?
I'm going home.
See you tomorrow.
See you.
Oh, you're heading out?
Hey, Robocco, I'm out of booze.
Isn't there anymore?
Would you like mine?
I don't care.
Just give me.
Sure.
Here.
I'm not gonna drink that!
It's morning already?
Good morning.
My head hurts...
Don't talk so loud...
It hurts my head.
You scumbags!
Die!
Just die right now!
Good morning!
What a super, ultra good awakening.
Oh?
I'm SUGA...
Super Ultra Good Awakening...
Good one!
You die too!
What a violent wake-up call.
I just came up with a super ultra wonderful idea in my dream that would raise our listener ratings.
Super ultra...
wonderful idea?
Yup.
Ume-san.
I call it A Million Dollar Quiz Hunter.
Maico's Diary
Good evening.
I'm an elite P.R. officer, Kacchin.
You may call me Kacchin.
If you're younger than me, or positioned lower than me, add "-san".
Today, we had fun
with the mid-term party.
People said many things,
and did many things.
But there is one thins
I don't understand.
What really is the
mid-term party?
Yes, "Kacchin-san."
I'm not a girl, so don't add "-ko" at the end.
Now, I need to lead this no-good staff with my elite skills.
This is so full of challenges.
Next time on Android Anna Maico 2010
You Know
Next Episode
Oh, what?
You have something agains me?
That's so mean!