Super Maico:
That's the name of the new model of android announcer that the Japan Broadcasting System has hired to make the best broadcast.
Good evening, everyone.
I might sound the same, but I'm not the same.
My name is Super Maico.
I'm the new 5th generation android personality, starting on this program as of today.
I'll help
I have prepared many entertainment programs that are different from before,
There's nothing to do.
so please sit back and enjoy.
No.
I promise to bring you a fun program.
It's good and easy.
You never did anything anyway.
So let's get started.
Jump Out Super Maico 2010!
This program is brought to you by CoDoMo Group; we bring a new tomorrow for the human race.
She says,
"I only look childish on the outside,"
The commercial changet?
her eyes full of tears.
It's kind of cool.
It's Super Maico.
I've never seen it so big and hard.
She's ad-libbing the CM on the spot.
That's impressive.
Of cource.
You can't find such big, hard...
Super Maico!
She's the 5th generation of android personalities,
build on the data gathered from the prototype Maico
and the technology provided by CoDoMo Group.
She's loaded with twin 1-megabit CPUs and 32 terabytes of memory,
fortified with anti-terrorist arms;
and armor that can withstand an explosion from nitro-glycerin.
This is the final, most advanced from of a 21st century android!
Wonderful! Fantastic!
Ha! Ha! Ha!
I understand it's impressive.
But why does it look so dumb?
Don't you understand his fashion sense?
What a shame.
The design concept came from Dungam.
No way!
Do your best for the radio industry, Super Maico!
I'll try, try, and try hard!
She's discharging!
Super Maico's latest movie rankings:
This ranking is based on real-time tracking, using Super Maico's build-in communications and statistics systems
So, Matsu-san,
What?
is this program reaching Suga-san?
to track moviegoers' numbers all around the globe.
Maico-chan, too?
Who knows?
But still, that android is doing pretty well.
And look, the STAR detector is reacting too.
What's the matter, Katagiri-san?
I'm sorry. You're in the middle of the program.
Well, I forgot about this package that was sent to Maico-chan, care of maintenance.
I thought it could be important, so I brought it now.
I see.
I heard about Suga-san.
He was a really fun person...
Well, excuse me.
What is this?
Maybe a gift from a fan?
What?
It's Suga-san!
It's a package from Suga-san!
What?!
Really?
Hand it over!
Yukie-chan S.O.S
Final Episode
September 1
Suga-san, you really were listening.
Maico-chan's voice really reached him!
Yeah.
Yeah!
What's the matter, everyone?
Can we have a minute?
I don't mind.
Can you hang on?
I will separate my normal mode from my on-air mode.
What are you doing?
Super Maico has 2 CPUs.
I can interact like normal while remaining on the air.
There is no need for you to go back out even after the commercial.
That's impressive.
So, what is it that you need?
Sorry, but change today's air schedule, and put this drama on the air.
This is the radio drama you were doing on the previous show.
Okay, I will switch with the next corner and put it on the air.
Good!
Thanks.
Don't you need the scenario?
No. I've already saved it.
Can you hear this, Suga?
Can you hear this, Maico-chan?
Isn't it a bit different?
enuresis = bed wetting
Right. Yukie-chan is suffering from enuresis.
And weren't they facing the crisis of destroying Earth?
According to this script, the Hong Kong mafia comes over to help Yukie-chan.
Phillips the Dolphin, too.
What the hell is this?
I can't air straight from that script.
The story is full of contradictions,
and there are 12% misspellings.
I rearranged it to make it enjoyable even for 5-year-olds.
How do you like it?
It's not good!
Why?
Suga-san wrote this script on his deathbed.
I understand how much you are saddened by the loss of Suga-san.
But isn't it our job to make a high-quality broadcast?
You are right.
But this is his final legacy that he's left behind with us!
Please, air it as it was written.
Please.
What you are saying contradicts broadcasters' ideals.
Well, fine.
Matsu-san?
No!
Ume-san, shut off the program.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm saying, we don't have to air such a stupid program!
What's so stupid about this?
The rating is over 3% right now.
This is not the program we've been building so far.
There are listeners who look forward to the next episode of Yukie-chan!
The listeners rating of the past radio drama was 0%.
Calculated numbers aren't everything!
I understand how you feel.
Then, please!
But it still doesn't change the fact that only a few people have heard it.
My current program is more accepted by the listeners.
Please understand.
Well, you might be right, but...
Ume-san!
Damn you! You tricked us!
Matsu-san!
I won't let you interfere with the program.
Damn!
This is...
Get out of this room.
No!
We can't reach anyone with such a program!
We can't reach Maico-chan!
You get out!
Please stop, Densuke-san.
Don't say my name with that voice!
You're not Maico-chan!
How dare you even say that?!
I'll help!
Take her out!
Maico was stupid.
She could only do what we told her to do.
But she was at least honest with us.
She was even honest about things we might hesitate to say.
Without even the slightest hesitation!
The robot here is just a mechanically smart object!
Maico might be inferior to you,
but she reached people's hearts far better than you!
Why?
She was so imperfect,
so the listeners were just worried about her.
Maico-chan was making an effort.
The effort you're making is completely different from Maico-chan's!
She was so earnest.
She never lied!
The hell with the ultimate personality.
Nobody is sympathizing with your words!
Don't boss me around after making the worst program ever!
I knew you were gonna say that.
But those are taboo words for scumbags like us!
You're not earnest.
You aren't conveying anything!
I'm making the best broadcast!
Why?
You don't get it?
I don't get it.
Because you are the one who built me.
That's right.
I build you to save people's fragile hearts.
To prevent a repeat of that cursed incident from 4 years ago.
The incident where one of the listeners took his own life after listening to the radio, right?
I know.
That's why I'm doing the perfect...
That's not it.
Why?
I'm doing so well.
This is not right.
An android incapable of sensing the feelings of nearby people isn't capable of working as a radio personality.
Stop it.
If you don't, I'll punch you.
If you don't...
I must fight... back...
This is...
This android is a failure.
Maico's Diary
Hello, this is Maico.
The other day, there was nobody around, so I answered the phone.
With all the sensors and the I/O devices unmounted, I am no longer an android, but a piece of junk. But, I'm sad. Even though I am only machine parts.
He wanted an order put in for some ramen to be delivered.
I made the noodles and soup according to my data bank, and delivered it.
But the man who ordered had a very puzzled look on his face.
Did I do anything wrong?
Next Android Ana Maico 2010
Can you hear me?
You can hear me, right?