Maico: That's the name of the prototype andoid announcer
that the Japan Broadcasting System hired to rejuvenate the dwindling radio scene of the 21st century.
What's wrong with it?
My back is all charred.
Next time...
The story doesn't stick no matter how many times I hear it.
What are you saying, Massan?
My hunch will be right.
People want it cool and violent,
Lolita and Space Jack!
It's shining!
Don't say shining!
Oh yeah, I'm thinking about making Yukie-chan's dad wear a wig.
What do you think?
Don't do it!
Don't ever do it!
Actually, why are you even asking me?!
Make Yukie-chan's dad full of hair!
Densuke, where's the guest?
Ah, yes!
I checked with the manager a minute ago, so I think it will be okay.
Would you all listen to the show?
It's just getting to the climax.
Izumi-chan, how much time is left?
There's 3 minutes.
Would you listen?
This is about the limit.
I did check with them.
First of all, I haven't even heard who the guest is, Densuke-kun.
I don't know who either.
What?
Kacchin usually takes care of...
Man, I'm late.
Didn't you forget to put "-san" just now?
No, I didn't Kacchin-san.
That's good, then.
You know, I'm sensitive, so...
Oh? Isn't the guest here?
Can't you see?
Kacchin-san, who is our guest?
Don't you know?
It's Tenpoin S. Akira-san.
What's that "S"?
How ignorant.
That's the middle name.
I don't know what kind of person though.
I just got the person shoved onto me from the talent office.
Don't brag about something like that.
How dare you talk to me like that!
I'm the P.R. officer!
Watch what you say!
There is no matching name in the talent database.
Maybe an athlete?
Wan't there a potter by that name?
Do you know, Ume-san?
What a mystery.
I don't care if he's in there or not!
The problem is the guest not being here!
Absolutely!
The person is going to have a gap at this rate!
It's your fault.
I swear it's not my fault.
No way!
Oh yes. I have some good news for you.
I heard there's a terrorist around this area.
They're blocking streets all around here.
What?!
Densuke, call them, and check where that "S"-san is now.
Immediately!
Okay!
Is this Big Geino-san?
Ah, yes, it is.
Thanks for the other day.
Yes, um...
Tenpoin S. Akira.
Um, has Tenpoin-san left your office?
But you said the schedule was okay a few minutes ago.
Huh?
"Isn't it the 20th of next month at 8 PM?"
No! It's today!
Huh? Still in America?
I see.
Thank you.
I'm sorry!
You scum, you can't even make appointments!
When are you gonna start working?!
Are you an agent from some secret organization sent in to kill me by overworking me?!
Get out!
Turn around and get out of here right now!
I'm sorry.
An apology won't do!
Roboco, beat him up!
Densuke-san, you impeded the workflow of this program.
That is unworthy of production staff.
Maico-chan...
That's right, Roboco.
Beat him!
Beat him, and make him regret.
If you can't, I'll give him the beating of love.
I am actually a certified karate master.
This is an alarming situation.
How are you planning to handle this?
If the guest isn't here, what can we do?!
In broadcasting, you never give in.
Isn't that what you say all the time?
The drama is ending soon.
The guest is here.
Yes, we'll make one up.
Today's wonderful special guest is...
YOU!
Let's do it, Densuke-san.
Matsu-san!
It's your own fault!
Go and die for the program!
With no rehearsals.
Let's do it, Ume-san!
That was the 5th episode of "Yukie-chan S.O.S."
What is going to happen to Yukie-chan?
Now, for our special corner, we have a special guest.
It's Tenpoin S. Akira-san.
Hello, I'm Maico.
Nice to meet you.
Uh, uh...
I don't even know whether this guest is a man or a woman.
What do I do?
Just say something!
Good evening.
Nice to meet you.
Akira-san, what is your job?
I am an A.D. for the Japan Broadcas...
I mean, singing!
I'm a singer.
But, according to my memory, your name is not listed on the artist's database.
Well, umm...
Don't make things difficult!
It sure is a mystery.
I'm sorry!
Don't talk back!
Ask him about his hobbies.
OK.
Don't talk back, damn it!
What's your hobby, Akira-san?
My hobby?
Note: Crown caps are the old style bottle caps for things like Coke bottles.
Collecting crown caps.
Like, the ones that are decorated with jewels, that kings wear?
No. I mean the caps for glass bottles.
Nowadays, the market is filled with cans and plastic bottles, and these are rare finds.
I really think glass bottles are chic and trendy.
Besides, by comparing the crown caps, we can tell the differences in the year and locations of the production,
it really is pretty deep.
Really?
Yes.
Also, it's pretty hard to get them off of the bottles without damaging them.
Regular bottle openers can bend them.
That sounds fun.
Well, yeah.
Is he Nobita-kun? (Another Doraemon reference)
My neighbor, Adachi-san helps me too.
Roboco, ask him what his type is for girls.
Love talk maight fill in some time.
OK.
Don't talk back! Damn it!
I'm sorry.
Akira-san, what's your type?
Um,
I like kind girls.
Kind?
Yes.
I goof up a lot at work, and get yelled at all the time, so I want someone who treats me gently.
Wimp.
That sounds troublesome.
You're right. It is a lot of trouble.
Like what?
Miscommunication,
copying the wrong documents,
mistyping receipts,
getting guests upset...
I do a lot.
I just made another mistake while making appointments, and got yelled at a minute ago.
People tell me all the time that I'm not suited for this job, and that I should quit.
That's one helluva singer.
I thought I might get better in the beginning.
I might get a chance one day as long as I do the job I'm told to do.
But I realized that's not good enough.
I make goof ups all the time, I get yelled at...
I'm trying to get better, but it's really not working.
I myself think it's really pathetic.
There's no way that such a goof like me can have a girlfriend.
No woder everyone gets tired of me.
Now they both got quiet.
Izumi-chan, put a song on.
Continue.
This is an order from the chief director.
What the hell?!
Shit. Do as you want.
That's not true.
You haven't given up yet, Densuke-san.
I make mistakes all the time, and I get yelled at too.
But I never give up, and always try harder.
Maico-chan...
I would like to back up the people who continue to try hard.
So, Densuke-san, please don't give up.
Try, try, and try hard.
Thank you, Maico-chan.
I'll try hard.
I'll really try!
You're so kind.
You're just my type.
It would be the best if I had someone like you as my girlfriend.
Oh, man, what am I saying?
So, back to the crown caps.
The lady across the street from me gave me a great one.
It's really rare find, with the design printed off-center due to a printing error.
That's great!
I'll bring it by next time.
I'm sure you'll be impressed.
Yes, I'll be looking forward to it.
It's done?!
I'm sorry, Matsu-san, for having such a weird conversation.
I'm really so...!
I'm impressed you could keep on talking in such a situation.
Well done.
Thank you, Matsu-san!
No, I must thank you.
The show was great with that conversation between you and Roboco.
Thank you.
Oh, would you quit that?
But I think I've grown a bit.
I see, I see.
Everyone! We shall call this special A.D. "Robo Fetish" from now on!
What's that?
Ume-san!
It would be the best if I had someone like you as my girlfriend.
You've got some guts to announce that in public!
I didn't know that Densuke-sama was in love with Roboco.
That's not true!
It's the same thing as confessing your love.
Right, Robo Fetish-kun?
You're shining, Robo Fetish!
Ume-san, would you give a big blessing to this Robo Fetish guy?
Congrats!
You've finally done it, Robo Fetish-kun.
This isn't right, Izumi-chan.
That was just a spur of the moment thing!
Robo Fetish-kun! That's too cruel!
Maico is my lover!
When did all of this happened?!
I don't know either!
Robo Fetish-kun,
I will deduct the fee from your paycheck for using company equipment for your own personal use.
What do you mean?
Now, everyone, start using the new name!
Robo Fetish!
Would you stop?
Enough!
Robo Fetish!
Stop!
Please stop!
Maico's Diary
We've got a problem, boss!
What's the matter, Hachi?
They found a drowned body in the alley between Echizen-ya and Kikyou-ya!
I think my CPU is
a little hot today.
Since Densuke-san
told me he likes me,
I cannot bring down
the temperature no matter
what. Am I broken?
What?!
How could there be a drown body in the alley?!
I thought it was strange too,
but the desk drawer in Echizen-ya was open.
Aha, now it makes sense.
Wait, what the hell are you talking about?
Next time - Android Ana Maico 2010
What, that's the title?
Bam!
Are you sure this is right, Ume-san?
I guess it is.