Maico: that's the name of the prototype android announcer
that the Japan Broadcasting System hired to rejuvenate the dwindling radio scene of the 21st century.
Take me to Beirut!
That's impossible! This is a radio studio!
You can't do it?
It's impossible!
Do it, even it it's impossible!
If you don't, I'll kill you!
No way!
Man, I'm late.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
Um, maybe I'll be a bit more late...
Don't move!
I'll kill you if you move.
What's going on?
That's my question!
That guy just came out of nowhere a minute ago.
With a pistol?
What are the guards doing?
That scum has donee nothing but point the gun and say 'Take me to Beirut'.
This is crazy.
What are we gonna do?
There's less than 20 minutes until air time.
I know!
Anyway, don't irritate him.
I don't want him to start shooting.
It was you who yelled, Massan!
Take me to Beirut!
Do you want him to die?!
Man, I love Beirut!
If you are a man, you've gotta go to Beirut at least once!
Tired of living on the small island of Japan, right?
By the way, where is Beirut?
Beirut is the capital of Lebanon.
It is located at the bottom of the Lebanon Mountains, and it faces the Mediterranean Sea.
The population is approximately 1,500,000.
The main industries are silk and cotton textles, and the processing of gold and silver.
Impressive, Maico-chan!
Now that we know, let's go! Beirut!
Massan, take it away.
Damn you!
Don't shove me into this position after you made all the noise!
That's the lowest!
Take me quickly!
Go hijack airplane if you wanna go!
What the hell are you doing at in studio?!
Don't make excuses.
Go now.
Go immediately.
Go this very moment!
Damn, are you listening to me?
Um, may I ask you q question?
What?
Why do you want to go to Beirut?
I need surgery.
Surgery?
Are you sick?
Then go see a doctor, not us!
I'm not sick!
But you said surgery...
I need the sex reassignment surgery!
I want to become a cute girl.
Don't move!
There's a man I love.
But he is only interested in girls.
That's why I need a sex change.
Take me to Beirut now!
You're wrong in many ways!
That's right!
The novice should start with cross dressing first!
Robo Fetish-kun, that's pretty wrong too.
Anyway, it's your freedom to love whoever, and do whatever,
but, would you do this somewhere else?
Radio studios can't fly.
We can't take you to Beirut or Shanghai.
Then take me to the Sahara.
I'll walk from there.
Don't you get it?!
You can't do it after I've asked you so many times?!
This is not good.
Did we piss him off?
Are you...
Are you trying to break me up with him too?!
Stop it! Watch it!
Shoot him, if you want!
Matsu-san! That's no joke!
The hell with jokes!
It's part of the A.D.'s job to protect the director!
When did that become my job?!
Do it, damn it!
I don't want to!
Hold it!
I heard your story.
Masudamasu-san.
Don't mind me. Carry on.
OK.
You were just listening?!
Oh, no... it's nothing.
So pathetic.
H-Hey! What now?
I don't wanna die!
Don't move!
I'll shoot if you run!
No!
I don't want to die before becoming a director!
Alright, Robo Fetish, you're a director from now on.
For real?
For real.
Yey, director!
Congrats!
So die without any regrets!
I don't want that either!
Then you're stuck as an A.D.
Die with regrets!
Isn't there a choice where I can survive and b a director?
Idiot!
Nothing will ever go that well!
Don't underestimate the harshness of the world.
Shut up!
You all mock me!
Think about it again!
You're still young.
You're pretty handsome too.
Let's enjoy the days of youth with healthy man-woman relationships!
Those words don't mean much, coming from Robo Fetish.
Would you shut up?!
Please? OK?
Man-to-man love is a waste.
What?!
Uh, well...
You said waste?
You say my feelings are a waste...
Note: "Ke ga nai"  can be interpreted as "Have no sense" or "Have no hair"
That I have no sense!
That's not what I meant!
Don't let your mouth get you in trouble!
Unforgivable!
#10   [     !     ]
Ro...
Robo Fetish!
Densuke-san!
Hang in there, Densuke-san!
I'm done for.
Maico-chan.
Yes.
Become a good radio personality even without me.
How dare you do that?!
Stepping on a dying young man?!
Idiot!
Do you see a bullet hole in you?!
Huh?
You're just fine.
But there was a gunshot.
Ume-san!
That isn't funny!
It scared me a bit.
That was beautiful timing.
It's a work of art.
I really thought I was shot.
Thank goodness.
It really scared me.
You really are robo fetish.
Yay! Let's love love!
I told you I'm not!
The situation hasn't changed a bit!
Damn you, ignoring me all this time!
I'll kill you all!
That's enough!
Move!
I won't!
Then I'll shoot you first!
I don't get it!
What good does this do?
I can't imagine that this will solve anything.
What would you know?!
I'm really in love with him!
But he...
Why do man like women?!
I can only answer biologically...
Shut up!
Cute girls like you will never understand my feelings!
I'm not a girl.
I'm an android.
W-What...
It's been a short time since I was built, so I really don't know much about this world.
I cause trouble for everyone here all the time.
But I do my best with what I can do.
Then, well, from time to time, they congratulate me.
And that makes me feel like the feelings from those times I get yelled at just fly away from me.
I really love that feeling.
Maico-chan...
Have you ever told your feelings to that man?
No.
Then!
Then tell him first.
I believe it isn't too late to consider other options after that.
But I'm not good enough...
Don't hesitate!
Please show your earnestness to him first.
Then I'm sure...
You're sure...
I'm sure...
When does this show air?
At 20:10.
I'll start listening to it next week.
I'm saved...
Oh, yeah, the police...
Quick! Report this to the police!
What was that for?!
There's no need to report it.
That was only a model gun that was stored in the station's inventory room.
Huh?!
You knew that from the beginning?!
What are you talking about?
Anyway, don't you have work to do?
Oh, shit!
Hey! Get ready!
We're going on the air?!
Of course!
Get to work, Robo Fetish!
Ume-san!
OK! OK!
Man, that was fun!
Sheesh, this studio has so many problems.
I can so use this in Yukie-chan SOS!
Get inside.
Right!
Good evening, everyone.
This is Maico.
We had so much trouble right before our air time today.
Well, as we were getting ready, a man burst into the studio...
She's finally reached the optimum state.
Actually, I'll tell you more about it later.
Let's try, try, and try hard this week too!
Jump Out Maico 2010!
Maico's Diary
This is Densuke.
On my day off, I took a walk to the river bank,
and out of the blue, a man who looked exactly like me showed up.
On top of that he said, "You will die soon!"
I met a man with a gun
today.
Japanese laws prohibits the
possession of guns, but he
still had one.
But after we talked, he was
a good man. He said he will
start listening to my
show.
I got upset, and replied "I won't die!"
And he just grinned, and then disappeared.
It was a mysterious incident.
Someone who was standing nearby called it Doppelganger.
Is that a food or something?
Next Android Ana Maico 2010
"You're evil!"
Next Episode
You're Evil
I'm gonna get yelled at!
Somebody, help me!