In the year 2010, a girl appeared in the low-rated radio world. Her name is MAICO.
She is the first android announcer in the radio world.
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Mi
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Fa
ReReMi ReDoMi
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Mi
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Fa
ReReMi DoRaDo
DoReDoReDo DoMiDoReDo
SoRa SoRa SoShi
RaShiRaShiRa RaShiDoShiRa
RaShiDo ReReReRe Fa!
SoRaShi ReDoShiDoMiRaMi
RaShiDoMiReDoReFa DoShi
SoSoSoSo ShiReSo FaMiFaMi
MiMiMiMiRaMi SoDo
I credit you all for completing the show last week even though we went through all that trouble.
It's a miracle that we
didn't cancel the show.
But look at this!
You know what these are! These are the complaints from the radio listeners!
After going through all that adversity, they aren't giving us any credit!
The complaints are for airing
the show in English!
...and these are the fan letters from US.
That's great, MAICO!
You are the Tokyo Rose of the 21st century! You're international already! This is great!
Don't change the subject!
That's right.
How many times do you
think I was scolded by the
sponsors through out the week.
That's because you are useless!
How dare you! The way you
talk will only hurt others!
Anyway, the reason why the last week's show sucked, is because this robot girl spoke in English!
How rude to ignore me....
Don't you think so, Ume-san?
Don't ever screw up like that!
You want it in English?
No mistake! Do you understand?
I understand.
She spoke in Japanese...
I reinstalled the proper OS
but, it took me all week long.
Densuke-san had to reboot me 20,000 times but now I'm fine.
The Japanese encoding
program is also installed.
Don't give me one of those seducing looks! Do you understand what I'm saying?
Stop smiling and cry!
Reconsider what you have done!
I'm sorry...
I didn't mean that way.
I'm sorry for being rude so... I mean!
You, robot broad, crying like a human.
I'm an android.
You are fine just being a robot broad!
It's poor to blame her cause she didn't have the proper OS installed last week.
I'm the one who is poor...
At this rate, they will
cancel the show anytime.
Right, Ume-san?
It's better than struggling so fruitlessly.
I'll throw this anger...
this furious anger... at you!
Izumi-chan, how can you be so calm?
The failure of the show is the
staff's joint responsibility.
I do what I'm suppose to do.
That's right but...
I guess I will throw this pent up
anger... towards you, after all!
I said that hurts...
Densuke! I can find a
replacement  AD easily!
So you must instruct that robot broad well! Understand?
Suga, the script.
Oh, here you go.
Again, this week's script is shining!
The 2nd most common question
from the listeners were
"Is the robot girl really a robot"...
I'm an android.
Anyway, they don't believe
the show's host is a robot!
In today's show, we'll appeal that point strongly. Got that, you numbskulls!
GOT THAT?
Use S-5 for the jingle here
We don't have much time left.
IRoHaNiHoHeTo...
Please hurry up, everybody.
Is there any problem?
I can't feel the lower half of my body.
They will finish it up by next
week so please be patient.
Matsu-san is frustrated,
so try not to mess up.
I'll try my best.
That was the most pitiful
"I'll try my best" I've ever heard...
I'll try my best.
Cranking up your volume
doesn't help it.
She's an android after all.
Guess she's got no heart...
Move faster, Densuke.
I'm sorry.
Izumi-san!
Could you throw that out?
She's doesn't  even give me any support...
Densuke-san
Huh?
I'll try my best.
Lowering your volume
doesn't do any good either...
All right! Here we go!
Good evening, everybody.
Were you surprised when I
spoke in English last week?
It was because the Japanese encoding program wasn't installed in my main memory.
Starting this week, I'll try my best
of the best of the best.
"Jump out, MAICO 2010"
This program is brought to you
in part by the Kodomo Group,
the company that keep's an eye on the future of Japan through out the day and night.
Alright, switch to commercial!
Densuke, how's the response?
Let's see... We got about 6
responses from the listeners.
let's see...
I say this and this..and this.
They are all shining brightly.
Densuke, give it to the robot broad right now. We got 20 second left.
Yes, sir.
These are the faxes from the listeners. Introduce them after the commercial.
I understand. Are you all right?
Seven seconds till the end of commercial!
Got that, robot broad?
I'm an android.
Now I'll introduce
messages from the listeners.
First up is a message from nick name "[Peeee] an in a man's genitalia of course"-san.
Nice job, Ume-san
"Good evening MAICO-san.",
Good evening to you too.
"Are you really a robot?"
"It's hard for me to believe."
Actually I'm not a robot, I'm an android. Let's move on to a next message.
She's not going into enough depth...
"If MAICO-san is really a robot, please self-destruct in 5 seconds after this message."
Suga! How could you pick out
that kind of message!
Eh? Aren't they superb?
What are we going to do?
This has no Guts or Feeling to it.
By the way, I'm an android, not a robot. If I self-destruct, I can't continue the show...
Matsu-san!
Huh?
Why don't we let her
describe her abilities?
For you, that's not a bad idea, Densuke.
Hey robot broad! Introduce your abilities! Tell them how amazing you are!
Move your ass!
Yes...
I'll introduce my superior abilities so everyone will believe that I'm an android.
I'm installed with the latest sensors which are 5 times more sensitive than a human's.
For example if I concentrated
on hearing...
Oh, I just heard the sound of a pin dropping on the floor in the hallway of
Adachi-san's house on 3rd avenue.
This slowly moving footstep
must be Adachi-san's wife.
Watch out! Don't step on it!
Thank god, she dodged it. I'm glad.
Does she believe that the
listeners are gonna buy this crap?
Hey, robot broad! Play the CD!
Introduce the songs!
I'm an android, not a robot.
So do I have to play the music?
Don't answer back! We are on the air!
I'm sorry but I'll move on to the song
list because the director told me to. Kouragi...
You read it Araragi.
I'm sorry. Here's "Don't go, Don't stop" by Mitsuru Araragi.
That shortened my life span about one hundred days.
What a good song...
Hello, this is Studio One.
Yes? Oh, I'm really sorry. We'll be more careful from now on. I'm really sorry.
That was the complaint from the advertisement agency.
What are we going to do?
Who's gonna take the responsibility.
I have no clue ...
I say it's not a problem. Isn't the program organizer the one to be blamed.
Let's have a huge
farewell party for Kacchin.
You devils...
Here's more responses from the listeners.
You read it.
OK
ummm...It says,
"Please read this with some enthusiasm."
"Hey Matsu, in your face! I can see you losing more of your precious hair!"
What did you say...
I didn't write it...
You are being too cordial.
I'm... I'm...
It's not my fault! It's not my fault!
The song will end soon
That was good, MAICO! You're the best!
This must be a nightmare...
So next week my bottom half will be completed...
I'd like it better if I broadcasted
the show in perfect condition.
Please look forward to it.
This program is brought to you in part by  the Kodomo Group,
The company that keeps an eye on the future of Japan through out the day and night.
Ume-san, cut the audio please...
I tried my best to not make a mistake.
But, I don't think people get
that you really are an android.
I'm disappointed.
I can't tell such a simple
thing to the listeners?
Nooooo! My hair!
By the way, I did my job.
I'm the one who's going to be blamed. What should I do?
That was a pretty good show.
I tried my best to warn them!
I'm not the one to be blamed!
Masuda Masu-san, please inform
this to the head. Please?
Where is this robot DJ?
Could you give us a comment?
What a great project, Masuda Masu-san.
She is the first robot DJ hired by Nippon Broadcasting Corporation in the radio world. Her name is MAICO.
I'm not fully finished yet though.
We would like to have
a comment from the DJ.
Never thought about introducing
her using other medias...
Matsu-san, why didn't we
do this in the first place?
You idiot! We work in radio, we make our living with sound and music!
I can't allow such a thing. Right, Ume-san?
...I'll do my best of the best of the best.
Can you look over here?
Sure.
Nice to meet you, everybody. I'm MAICO, the DJ of "Jump out, MAICO! 2010"
I'm an android built just for this show but everyone calls me a robot.
But, I wish everyone would
accept me as an android.
Next episode.
"Android Announcer: MAICO 2010"
"Punyoon!"
I'll do my best of the best of the best (punyoon). Huh?
Did I just say something awkward (punyoon)? Huh?