In the year 2010, a girl appeared in the low-rated radio world. Her name is MAICO!!!!.
She is the first android announcer in the radio world.
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Mi
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Fa
ReReMi ReDoMi
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Mi
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Fa
ReReMi DoRaDo
DoReDoReDo DoMiDoReDo
SoRa SoRa SoShi
RaShiRaShiRa RaShiDoShiRa
RaShiDo ReReReRe Fa!
SoRaShi ReDoShiDoMiRaMi
RaShiDoMiReDoReFa DoShi
SoSoSoSo ShiReSo FaMiFaMi
MiMiMiMiRaMi SoDo
I'm done.
1 hour 23 minutes 45 seconds. Do you understand what this time represents?
1,2,3,4,5. All the numbers are in an order.
Idiot! I means it took too long
to clean up the studio!
Do you understand? Hello?
That hurts...
Ume-san, say something to
this extreme idiot.
I'm doing my best.
Please stop it.
Morning.
Why are you turning your face away?
Do you hate me that much?
Nobody likes you.
What an insult! I'm a nice guy who has always been picked as the class rep. since the 1st grade up to college.
That's because no one
else wanted to do it.
That can't be...
Matsu-san! I got another great inspiration!
Today's talk will go with
"MAICO flys in a Kimono!"
What the hell are you thinking!?
You mean you didn't plan anything?
I'm so unpleasant...
Bunch of monkey's...
What? What was that gay screaming for?
I'm an elite program organizer...
Not a fag...
Good morning
Are you the ...Robot Broad?
Yes. The bottom half arrived yesterday.
So Katagiri-san from
maintenance, put me together.
Can you stamp this reciept please?
How about a signature?
Sure
Here...
Thank you. Now I'm a perfect MAICO.
This is good. MAICO-chan, you are brightly shining. This is great.
Oh, this is absolutely great!
Please don't Suga-san.
That is embarrassing.
But in that clothing, I can't
imagine you as a robot.
Of course, I'm an android.
Ohhh....
Quit it, Kacchin-san. It's embarrassing.
Robot broad..
Because you went on a TV and newspapers, the show is being noticed more.
So today we are going all the way with your talk and no music, got it.
Yes, sir. I'll do my best
of the best of the best.
That's it, MAICO-chan.
And also, you clothes
compliment you nicely.
Thank you very much.
All right! Let's get ready for the show. If we make a mistake, I'll resign right away.
Got it? Densuke, if you don't want to get fired, go copy the script!
What are you doing?
I don't know.
Wow, she's shining.
Test, test, mic test. Red, blue AEIOU.
Peter Parker picked a peck of pickled peckers....
Damn. After being completed, finally she's motivated.
That is not a tongue twister, by the way.
Are you done with copying the script?
Uh..not yet.
We'll be on air soon, you idiot!
Are you alright?
What the hell is this?
It's a screw.
I know that. What I'm saying is
how can you miss this after...
spending 1 hour 23 minutes and 45 seconds to clean this studio!
I thought it wasn't a big deal...
If you'd had "Thought" you'd
have put it in a safe place!
When are you two going
to stop playing this skit?
2 minutes left till we go on air.
That's right! We better get going or I'll be the one who gets scolded.
Test. Test.
Good evening, everybody. I am MAICO.
Last week, I was interviewed by the TV reporters and It was exciting.
Izumi-chan, start the commercial after this, give her the scripts during the commercial and read the letters from listeners...
So everyone, please look forward to it.
Huh? What's that sound?
WHAT!?
Here we go with
"Jump Out MAICO!! 2010."
Wow, she got the beat.
She's brightly shining!
No, she's not!
We must stop her...
This program is brought to
you in part by Kodomo....
Punyoon... Punyoon... Punyoon...
No, the sponsor's are...
I'm done with the copying! Woah!?
Oh, it's  the "Happy Yappie Talking Ability" which was written in the manual.
It's neither happy nor yappie at all!
I can't speak well punyoon. The
program is bugged punyoon.
What the hell is this!?
I don't..know...
It's your fault! Do something!
What?
Here it is! Let's see... It says "When MAICO starts to talk with 'punyoon' at the end of the sentence,
it may be because the plug-and-play system of the additional hardware is not configured right.
The best solution is to reformat the hard drive and reinstall the OS."
It must be because we added the bottom half of her body. Now, let's get moving.
Do it, now!
It's impossible to
reinstall 50 CDs right now.
Wonderful punyoon! Pretty punyoon!
This is the most annoying kind
of "happy" talking I've...
The commercial will end soon.
The music! Play any kind of music!
I didn't prepare it. It said
"No music, just talk today"
on the cue sheet.
Don't you guys have any other music? Anything!
I have Star's CD
Sounds good. Let's go with Star.
It's amazing. Each song
lasts 150 minutes.
That's over the CD's recording limit.
That's why it's big. See?
How the hell are we
suppose to play that!?
What are we suppose to do?
Use that tape.
Huh?
It's an opening of "Yukie-chan SOS", the radio drama airing in 2 weeks.
Well, we were able to buy time somehow. Let's say the song is 4 minutes long, meanwhile, we'll...
The song only lasts for a minute and a half.
Well, it's an opening
so it's a short version.
I see.
Don't be persuaded yet.
I'm in trouble punyoon.
The shutdown program is activated so my system will shutdown in 80 seconds punyoon.
What is it this time?
Don't tell me that robot broad
is gonna shut down.
Shutdown... shutdown punyoon
How are we suppose to carry the show without the DJ talking?
If the silence continues
for 15 seconds, the air time will...
The air time!? Yet again, my show will...
Why do I have to face all these troubles? I quit... I'll quit and become a tomato farmer back home...
Come on, Matsu-san.
From now on, call me Mr. Tomato...
Matsu-san...
Can't we do something, Izumi-san?
Ume-san?
No. No. No.
Suga-san?
Good job, MAICO. You are the best.
Kacchin?
You are an ordinary AD.
Don't forget to add "san" on my name!
Kacchin-san...
We're doomed!
Masuda Masu-san?
Looks like the show will
come to an end this week.
No...
No!
Oh, hi Densuke-san punyoon.
MAICO-chan! How can we
stop the shutdown process.
The shutdown program is on the chip of sub-motherboard so, by cutting the wire, the process will be terminated punyoon.
I don't understand any of that!
Please push the mole on my back punyoon.
A mole on the back?
Excuse me for this.
No problem punyoon.
A mole... a mole... I found it!
Geeze its all analog...
The program will stop by
cutting the wire punyoon.
Which one am I suppose to cut?
I'm sorry but the help file you're looking
for doesn't exist punyoon.
No way!?
The way it's set up, it's gotta be
either the red or blue wire.
But which one? Which one could it be?
They want to talk to you punyoon.
Leave it to me.
Kacchin...san.
I've been practicing fortune telling secretly, for just such an emergency.
Oh spirit of the great fox
god, please show us the sign.
Cut the yellow wire.
She doesn't have a yellow wire!
That can't be! Alright, I'll try it one more time. Oh the spirit of the great fox god, please show us the sign. Please! Amen!
Everything is over... It's the end...
What should I do... What should I do... What should I do...
Densuke-kun, it's either red or blue.
Is it red? Or blue?
5 seconds left punyoon.
4 punyoon.
3 punyoon.
2 punyoon.
MAICO-chan...
1 punyoon.
The song you've just heard is the opening of "Yukie-chan SOS", a radio drama which will start in 2 weeks.
Thank god...
Damn, I missed the chance to quit.
The contents of this drama will
be a secret until it airs.
In this drama, it will be MAICO's first challenge as a voice actress.
Please look forward to it punyoon. Punyoon, punyoon, punyoon....
Of course the problem still won't be solved... Even if you stop the system, the bug isn't fixed.
The sponsors... are mad!?
Punyoon, punyoon, punyoon, punyoon, punyoon....
I'm Matsu, the director of the show.
Do you know how to raise tomatoes?
It's very simple. Just plant the seeds in the a flower pot and give it water.
I'll just become a tomato farmer, recieve a relief subsidy from the government, and make a living out of it.
Isn't it a wonderful retirement plan?
With this, my life after the retirement is secured. Now all I gotta do is get rid of that annoying robot broad.
Next episode.
"Android Announcer: MAICO 2010"
"Useless"
By the way, there are 5 useless staffers in this show.