For the listeners of this program,
for the staff of this program,
MAICO 2010
Maico starts up again today.
Android Ana Maico takes off!
Tokyo - to Nerima-Ku Nerima 6-2-1
Matso Densuke-sama
Den...-chan...
Maico-chan!
Sheesh, you scared me.
I don't understand
Is Den-chan you?
Did you read it?
Yes.
Would you stop that?
It's an invasion of my privacy.
I'm sorry.
Oh well.
It's much better being read by you than by anyone else.
I found this when I was cleaning my room.
I got it from a classmate at my high school.
Was she your girlfriend?
Well, yeah.
Her name was Hiraguchi Naoko.
She was cute.
What are you going to do after we graduate, Den-chan?
I'm gonna go to Tokyo and work in mass media.
And I'll become the director for TV and radio programs,
and produce many fun shows!
What?
What's so funny?
Because you look like you're having fun when you're talking about that.
And you always sleep through class.
What?
But... I want to see the shows you make.
I'm sure they will all be happy and full of energy.
Naoko...
Then what happened?
Nothing much.
I came out to Tokyo, and Naoko went to the local juco, and that's it.
We exchanged letters for a while after that,
but I got busy trying to get jobs in mass media.
So, I couldn't keep up with replies.
Why don't you go back to see her?
Because I'm still only a no-good A.D. after all these years.
So, you can't see her if you are an A.D?
Well, that's not it...
What is it, then?
Well, enough of this.
'Sup?
Morning!
Oh, good morning.
Densuke-kun, that's my seat, you know.
Oh, well, this is...
It's a million years to early for you to take my seat!
Your idiocy is gonna infect me!
Get out of my seat!
That's so mean.
Good morning.
Morning.
About last week...
Sorry, but I'm busy getting ready.
Don't bother me.
Oh, okay...
I see.
What?
Ouch!
How dare you try to get this mature body at your rank!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Oh!
Unforgivable!
It's unforgivable that you were looking at me like that!
From me to you with love...
A love letter from Densuke to Massan?
I think you're totally misunderstanding this!
That's really the worst.
That's not it!
Don't look at me so eagerly!
You all are misunderstanding it!
That's Densuke-san's...
Maico-chan, don't tell them!
Why?
If those cruel people find out, they'll make fun of me!
I want to keep this letter from Naoko as a part of my pure memories from my younger days.
I don't want it to be violated by those dirty people.
But...
Ume-san! No way!
You're so shining.
Also, Den-chan, did you really get hired by a TV station?
You were lying like that?!
I'm impressed that you were assigned as director of that popular program, Suttoko Quiz.
It doesn't air over here, but I wish you the best.
Good luck.
Oh, man, it's full of lies.
I know how you fell.
You wanted to look good for her, right?
Of cource you can't tell her how bad you were doing.
And you're no longer in touch with her, huh?
Of cource.
You couldn't dare go meet her as an A.D. after lying so much.
Either way, you kept such a letter after all these years?
You're such a wimp.
I sure don't wanna be like that.
Um, I think you're going too far with this.
Hello.
Oh, Hey-san.
Are you happy?
Are you lucky?
What do you want today?
Don't look so scary.
Smiles are the energy for tomorrow.
Nothing good happens when you come around.
You have a point!
I lose!
Sorry, sorry.
I am getting married soon.
Well, it's a destined encounter.
What luck!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
I'm glad for you.
The thrill has come, you know?
So, what kind of woman is she?
She's here with me.
Hey! Come on, my angel.
Neigh whinny whinny!
Thank you.
No problem.
How was the ride?
Well, it wasn't bad.
I'm sorry I made you be a horse again.
Oh no, it's fine.
You kept me at your place for 2 weeks.
I didn't get killed because of you.
Oh, come on we're always friends.
Oh, what the hell?
Oh, Hei-chan!
No, no, people are watching us.
We'll have our love-love time after this.
Here.
Let me introduce her.
She's my fiance, Hiraguchi Naoko.
Hiraguchi Naoko?
Thank you for taking care of Hei-chan all the time.
Naoko...
Hey, hey, I'm the one who's taking care of them.
Oh, Hei-chan!
I don't like them.
Really?
But they're shining.
Naoko...
I thought you were a crawler, but you're trash, Densuke-kun!
Densuke?
Naoko!
Den-chan!
Hey, is she...
Looks like it.
Den-chan, what are you doing here?
I thoughy you were a director at a TV station.
Well, um...
Naoko, Densuke-kun is no-good A.D. here. The lowest position.
A.D...
I see.
Actually, are you acquaintanted with Densuke-kun?
Well, yeah...
Hm, like how?
We were in the same class in high school.
We were just classmates.
That's all?
Yes.
She's right!
Densuke-san...
Naoko was popular in school.
I tried for her too, but I got dumped.
Oh, come on, Den-chan!
I see.
Well, you need to be at least my level to balance Naoko's beauty.
Congratulations.
Well, this is fun.
Densuke-san...
Good, good!
I'm really glad for you.
You found such a good husband.
Thank you.
Good luck.
Good luck to you too, Den-chan.
But I'm only an A.D.
Right.
Work hard as housekeeper.
This is not right!
You're not right, Densuke-san!
Because...
What's going on?
Oh, it's nothing.
By the way, where did you find such a beauty?
We had a marriage arrangement this morning.
And you proposed already?!
Why aren't you telling them anything?
You're contradicting the truth!
It's okay.
It's really okay.
Please, leave it alone.
But she was your girlfriend!
You need to tell him so!
Enough!
Sorry.
But it's really okay.
Heita-san is a good person... or maybe not.
But he's rich,
and he won't cause any trouble either.
But she lied.
It's not a big deal.
Are you okay with that, Densuke-san?
I'm only a lowly A.D.
I don't have the right to disturb her.
I don't understand.
How is that related to this?
Well, yeah.
I guess you don't get it.
It's okay.
Just keep all of this a secret.
Please.
Densuke-san!
You're only an androd after all.
They're going to hold the ceremony next month already!
That's so sudden.
I'm a love express.
Oh come on, honey!
I don't understand...
Maico's Diary
It's the director, Matsu.
The other day, my friend gave me this hair stimulant that's a gamble.
I don't know how it works,
A mistake needs to be corrected. But Densuke-san told me, "You're only an android after all." Yes, I sure am an adroid... I don't understand.
but it's supposed to make it grow a lot, or make me lose it all.
Even I got scared a little.
I'm afraid of losing my precious hair...
Hmm, what should I do...
Oh my God! I lost four already while thinking about this!
Next Android Ana Maico 2010
Storm
What? The perfect storm?