Congratulations, Izumi-chan.
Congratulations, KT.
For the special couple,
Japan Broadcasting System is having a special 5-hour program...
NOT!
Popular music producer, Takatou Kenzi, a.k.a. TK, proposes on the radio show.
Man, it's so flashy.
What would we expect from a popular producer?
He's so fast to act.
Izumi-chan, have you kissed him yet?
Oh, come on, Matsu-san!
Pretty funny, Massan.
I'm glad for you too, Izumi-chan, for finding a permanent job,
though I'm a bit sad too.
It's such merry news.
Ume-san, give her a happy one.
Congrants! Congrants! Congrants!
Good  for her.
Yes.
Also, sorry about the other day.
I said something horrible about you.
That's right.
You were wrong.
I'm not a robot, but an android.
That's right.
Sorry.
Yes, this is Studio One.
Yes.
Matsu-san, it's Isozaki-san from public relations.
Yeah.
Hey. What's up?
Before tomorrow?
That's so sudden.
All right.
It's airtime soon, so I'll call you later.
Yeah. Later.
What was that about?
What is it?
How old are you?
I'm 24...
Still too young.
For what?
Life advice program, huh?
Yukie-chan! Don't die now!
You are so sincere
How could you even say that?!
After her repeated battles against the Ora-ora Aliens,
Yukie-chan's Nanyo-syndrome got worce,
and she'll lose all of the liquid in her body within a few hours!
But what could I have done?!
The ice cap from the North Pole has covered the Northern Hemisphere,
Izumi-san...
Good work.
and the Western Nations are almost completely destroyed!
Thanks.
Yukie-chan is our last hope to save the world!
We can't help it!
This is our destiny.
What will happen with the drama after this?
Don't say that.
There will be a miraculous turnabout in the story. What else?
Destiny is something we create with our own hands.
Get up, Yukie-chan!
Yukie-chan's mother comes back from the 23rd century.
Don't shake her!
Oh no!
Isn't it shining?
Why is her mother coming from the future?
What will happen to Yukie-chan next time?
Don't be so picky.
Right, Kacchin?
To be continued...
Oh? Where's Kacchin?
Story, planning, script, editing - Suga-chan.
Maybe he took a day off?
Maybe he's being followed by someone again.
Music - Arimono.
That's not something you should say with a smile.
Producer - Matsu.
SFX - Ume-san.
Oh, the tape is near the end.
Starring Maico as Yukie-chan,
Matsu-san, the tape is ending soon.
Yeah.
Kiminobu-san as Kiminobu-san,
Ume-san, give me the S-21 jingle.
Ijuin-san as Ijuin-san.
Thank you for listening.
Wrap it up with the drama synopsis, then we'll go to the next corner.
Don't mess this up.
That was Yukie-chan S.O.S.
Will Yukie-chan be able to save the Earth from destruction?
Please look forward to the next episode.
Now, the next corner.
Maico's Life Advice Against Your Will!
I will call a number randomly,
and try to give advice for whatever problems the recipient may have.
Last week, nobody answered even after 20 calls.
I will try to advice people on their problems this week.
Now, let's start the tel-tel-call!
I wonder if someone will answer this week.
Looks like they're not home.
On to the next tel-tel-call.
Congratulations!
I'm an android radio personality for Japan Broadcasting System, Maico.
O-OK...
I know this is very sudden,
but would you share a life problem with me?
I wiil use the enormous amount of data I carry as an android to solve your problem.
Is this really radio?
Yes. Your voice is being broadcasted nationally over the radio waves.
That's so sudden! I can't do this.
That's so rude.
Excuse me, but let me hang up.
Oh, please hang on!
Would you at least answer one question?
Eh?
Are you suffering from anything?
Huh?
Any anxieties?
Something that's not going well, or something that you are troubled about. Is there anything?
There is.
I do have a problem.
It's been 10 years since I started living separately from my husband.
What kind of man is your husband?
He's normal except for his hair.
It's just... he works for a mass media company.
He used to come home in the beginning,
but since around the time our daughter was born, he quit coming home.
That's nice.
That's so sad.
Shut up!
He kept himself busy.
He even got himself involved with projects not assigned to him,
while leaving the family alone.
Even when I asked him to watch after our sick daughter,
he just read one letter, and headed back to his job, leaving her behind.
My daughter nearly had pneumonia by the time I got back to her.
That day, if I didn't get back, that listener would have...
Or just the other day, he disregarded te monthly day they've set up to meet with each other.
She told me that she waited at a restaurant for him for a long time.
But he wouldn't even keep that promise.
But it was storming that day.
This is not acceptable.
I hate him.
But it's still troubling you, right?
Eh?
You just said that you hate him.
But there should be no need to be troubled if you really hate him.
Well...
Do you hate your husband?
Well, no...
So you love him?
That idiot.
How could you ask such a question to a woman approaching 40?
Do you hate him?
No.
I'm proud of my husband, who can be so caring to a total stranger.
But that's no excuse to leave his family behind.
Have you mentioned that to your husband?
No.
Why not?
He wouldn't listen.
Actually, that's not it.
I wanted him to notice my feelings and our daughter's feelings.
I'm only an android, so I cannot comprehend people's feelings.
But there is one thing that I've learned after working as a personality.
Sometimes, there are things that cannot be communicated unless you verbally say them.
Please tell your husband what you just said.
It's okay! I'm sure he'll catch on.
But...
Fight!
Please try, try, and try hard.
I would like to think a little.
Good!
To hold on to such troubles for 10 years...
Humans are truly amazing.
I believe that she truly loves her husband.
I hope she can talk with him.
We'll be back after these messages.
That's too much.
Leave me alone.
Damn, that stings so much.
Good job, Maico-chan.
Good job.
Yes, thank you!
Um, did I make any mistakes?
Just as you told me before, I thought hard in my own words.
You said that you can't lie the other day, didn't you?
Yes.
But that's not true.
You're just sincere.
Right, Maico?
Matsu-san, did you just say Maico?
Of cource.
I'm an android after all!
You really are sincere.
Yes!
I can't believe it.
This cheap program could still solve a 10-year-old problem.
This is why I can't quit the radio biz.
Hey, Isozaki.
About the life advice program,
cancel that.
Why?
Weren't you just listening to the show?
Matsu-san!
You guys are the worst bunch of junk imaginable.
But I'm the only man who can manage this bunch of junk.
Right, Densuke?
Yes, you're right.
Ume-san, let's go out for a drink someday.
Izumi-chan, would you stay with this program even after you get married?
Suga, give us good scripts.
Of course!
Densuke, don't goof up.
Sure!
Maico,
Yes!
You...
you...
Everyone! Look! Look!
I finally got this all the way out in Tibet.
Isn't it the best?
That's so nice, Kacchin-san!
Of cource.
My family will finally be happy with this.
Hurray! Hurray!
Right here, I'll make Yukie-chan's dad the boss of the villains!
Yeah! It's shining!
Suga, we're already off the air.
Hang on!
I'm almost done!
That's weird.
What is?
Suga-san told us that he falls into a slump unless he sees people's unhappiness.
He sure did.
I have that in my memory.
Done!
This just surpassed the script for Live from the South Pole Crossing!
It's truly a legendary script!
It's super shining!
S-Suga-san...
Suga-san!
Hey! Are you okay?!
Come on!
Suga!
Suga-san!
Hang on!
Why?
What do we do?
Suga-san...
Densuke! Get an ambulance!
Hurry! Now!
Yes!
Suga-san...
Maico's Diary
This is the A.D., Densuke.
We went out for a drink yesterday with the staff members.
There, a store worker came over to me and handed me a piece of yellow paper.
Suga-san fainted unconscious. Matsu-san, Izumi-san, Ume-san, Kacchin-san, Densuke-san, they all ran for him. As for me... I could only just stand there.
It said free beer ticket.
I've never been treated so well by a total stranger before.
I swear I'll go back to Bar Mugendai again!
Next Android Ana Maico 2010
Vampire Unit.
I know!
Vampire Unit
A pack of vampire bats are coming!
I'm scared!