In the year 2010, a girl appeared in the low-rated radio world. Her name is MAICO.
She is the first android announcer in the radio world.
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Mi
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Fa
ReReMi ReDoMi
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Mi
SoRa SoRa SoRa SoRa Fa
ReReMi DoRaDo
DoReDoReDo DoMiDoReDo
SoRa SoRa SoShi
RaShiRaShiRa RaShiDoShiRa
RaShiDo ReReReRe Fa!
SoRaShi ReDoShiDoMiRaMi
RaShiDoMiReDoReFa DoShi
SoSoSoSo ShiReSo FaMiFaMi
MiMiMiMiRaMi SoDo
The first week was 1%, the second week was 0.5%, and the third week was 0.1%.
Even though her interview went on TV before the third week show, the rating still plummeted.
I wonder why?
She's trying her best but...
I've done my job.
It's obvious why the rating is so low. This robot broad is ruining the show.
She's slow, her tongue's not smooth, not flexible, and she breaks and stops too often.
And worst of all, she goes "punyoon".No wonder no one listens to it punyoon.
Right, robot broad?
I'm an android, not a robot.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Now, now Matsu-san. Now that MAICO-chan's bug has been removed, the situation should start to improve.
Right, MAICO-chan?
Yes. I'll do my best of the best of the best.
Uh-huh, let's do our best.
What's with your fresh attitude?
A robot should always do their best.
And robots always have a mysterious pocket that can grant wishes.
That doesn't make any sense...
How's everyone doing? I came up with an excellent project by listening to the last week's show.
I name it
"MAICO and the Flying Punyoon".
That was a great reaction, Masuda Masu-san.
Your late, Suga! By the way, where is the show's dork program director?
Oh yeah, Katsucchin.
Where is that stupid grunt?
Ah, he gave me a call earlier. He said that he performed too much Kokkuri-san last week and thinks he was possessed.
So he went to visit an exorcist.
What do you mean he felt possessed?
How convenient. Let's
start the recording.
Eh? But the show airs tomorrow.
We are going to prerecord the show today. If there's going to be a lot of mistakes, it's a staff's duty to correct them. Am I wrong?
I see, prerecording the show.
Why didn't we come up with that till now?
Ume-san, shall we give it a shot?
Alright, get ready for the recording! Robot broad, be prepared cause I will haze you a lot today.
Yes, I will do anything even squatting or crawling through the mud. I will do my best of the best of the best.
That's not the kinda
hazing I'm talking about!
I'm sorry...
Hello, everyone. This is MAICO. I'm sorry about last week, my program had a bug.
I was just scolded by the director...
What the hell are you thinking? It's "good evening" not "hello." And don't say anything about stuff behind the scenes.
Can't you show some sense of humor like using that "punyoon" to surprise the audience?
I understand...
Alright, then.  Start over
from the beginning.
It's ready.
All right.
Good evening, everyone.  I'm sorry about last week, my program had a bug.  This is MAICO punyoon.
Did I surprise you? It was just a joke. The director told me that it would be an useful technique to surprise the listeners.
Well then, let move on to the show.
"Jump Out! MAICO: 2010"
Excellent, MAICO.
That's a wonderful beginning.
That stupid robot...
"Got Problems? Leave It to MAICO and her 30,000 Friends". First up is a letter sent by Bloodsucking Batallion-san from Tokyo county.
"I am isolated in the class
because I'm not athletic."
"I still can't do pull-ups on a horizontal bar even though I'm a high school student."
"MAICO-san. what should I do."
Say something, robot broad.
I guess you can't help it.
What's with that reaction!
Think more about the person!
This Blood Sucking Batallion-kun has been worried for a long time because he's not athletic!
He wrote that he's isolated, but he may be getting pushed around! He might start skipping school and in the end, he might even drop out!
I was in charge of a show to solved people's problems for a long time so I know!
When did we start getting letters like that?
I wrote it. Isn't it brilliant?
Come up with some type of solutions like your style of improvements!
But there are personal differences in athletic abilities so I think he can't help it.
Think that kind of a material makes a good show? Say something. Answer Blood Sucking Batallion-kun's question.
Blood Sucking Batallion-kun, I think there are many problems in people's life.
You robot bitch!
Matsu-san, violence is bad.
You worthless stupid robot...
I'm sorry...
I can't feel any emotions from your apology! You aren't apologizing at all!
I am programmed to
apologize when I'm scolded.
What did you say!?
Matsu-san, don't!
Please hit me instead of her.
I understand...
You call yourself the very first robot DJ in the radio industry? Radio shows can't be run by a mechanical doll like you!
Just go throw yourself in the waste disposal right now and become some scrap metal slag!
Tears?
I'm trying to come up with the best words based on my emotional program. I'm trying to the best of my potential.
Your tears are fake. You aren't sad at all.
Matsu-san!
You can't come up with the responses just by linking them with your on-line dictionary!
Think! Think harder and sooth the pain Blood Sucking Batallion-kun is having!
That's what the radio DJ suppose to do.
I'll leave the tapes running.
Listen well, robot girl!
Speak with your own words!
My own words...
I think your athletic abilities would improve if you ask your friends for help and practice together...
Not good enough!
I think jogging in the morning
would have an effect.
Do it over!
Do push ups and sit ups
before you go to sleep...
Again!
Building your muscles is the best way to improve you athletic abilities...
Again!!
What's wrong, robot broad? Speak!
Matsu-san, isn't it enough?  Why don't we compromise at this point?
Densuke, don't you want to be a director?
Yes, I do.
Then never say the word "enough" again! There is no compromising in a radio show.
M..Matsu-san...
This is the last tape.
Keep on rolling.
Ume-san, am I wrong?
Am I a terrible man?
I got a position at the mass media company. I might be in charge of popular shows and end up marrying an actress.
Hang in there.
Hang in there, MAICO-chan.  I can't do anything but cheer you on. Hang in there.
Hang in there. Hang in there.
I...
I also screw up all the time and get scolded. But I keep trying, and try not to make another mistake.
It will be over if you give up. So..so please do your best, Blood Sucking Battalion.
I will cheer for you.
Please do your best of the best of the best...
T..that was a great response, MAICO!!!
Alright, I'm giving you an okay.
I'm glad, MAICO-chan.
Thank you... Thank you, Densuke-san...
Robot broad, move on to the next letter.
Next letter was sent by YuiYui Special-san from Okayama prefecture.
MAICO-san, which do you like better, Ten-don or Katsu-don?
I'm not sure since I have never ate it before.
Who the hell picked this letter?
I did. Isn't it great? It's brilliant!!!
The tape has ended.
Thank you, MAICO...
I am Izumi, the sound mixer of Nippon Broadcasting Corporation.
The other day, I received an invitation to my friend's wedding but I still haven't decided whether to go or not.
Because I wore all my favorite dresses to other formal events. If I buy a new dress and give a wedding tip, I'll be broke.
I thought I might meet a wonderful man if I worked for mass media but...
Next episode:
"Android Announcer: MAICO 2010"
[The Worst]
The worst show, the worst staff.
I'm thinking about changing my career seriously.