This script writer put in his all during his life,
and even put in his after his life!
Oh, Suga-chan forever!
It's done.
Good job.
Did you see the number of wreaths?
He really bad a good network of people.
And yet there weren't too many people there.
They are all busy people.
The moderators handled the whole thing so well that it felt like I was watching a show.
How much did you put?
In the offering.
I put in 500 yen.
That's so stingy.
It's right before payday.
I can't help it.
I put in 33,000 yen myself.
We were praying for him in this studio, where he stayed until his last minute.
So don't talk so dirty in here!
Sorry.
Suga-san died!
My voice didn't reach him, and he...
Calm down, Maico-chan.
But...
The funeral is over.
Your battery ran out in the middle of the service.
But... Suga-san was right there just 20 seconds ago.
There were flowers, and a picture of Suga-san smiling,...
My voice didn't reach him...
If you think so, then pray for him.
But how?
Just remember things about Suga.
And talk to the Suga that's inside you.
Okay.
She must be in shock.
No doubt about that.
She tried so hard, and it still didn't help.
Raise your chin!
We produced the best broadcast that we could send to Suga.
He must be smiling in Heaven too.
Right, Ume-san?
Close your eyes.
Say farewell to him.
It's shining.
I send my condolences to the lost, great script writer.
Where have you been all this time?
In the executive management meeting.
Talking about the existence of this program.
What does that mean?!
Existence? You mean you're canceling us?
Why?
Numerous problems have surfaced.
The situation is at its worst.
What have we done?!
The chronically low ratings,
a broadcast in English, a buggy broadcast, destruction of the studio,
insulting the sponsor, boycotting the job,
infringement on publicity rights through the use of a false guest,
and use of the public air waves for a private matter.
I've been stopping all the complaints from above so far,
but last week's broadcast really killed us.
What was wrong with that?!
Maico-chan worked so hard.
If you think about social common sense, then it was inevitable.
You understand that, right?
B-but...
I have an announcement from the Japan Broad-casting System's executive management.
Since there is a critical defect with Maico, she will leave the personality position.
And the program will be renewed with a new personality.
Don't give me that crap!
Why only Maico-chan?
I'm guilty too!
Me too. I intruded mid-air.
Oh, good.
I thought I was gonna get fired...
This is unacceptable!
I protest!
To keep the rest of you here, we had no choice.
Then that's even worce!
Take me out, not just Maico!
Mee too!
Well, I...
But...
Everyone, thank you for all of our days together, though it has been short.
Why are you talking like that?
I'm an android personality.
If I cannot keep airing, then I am not qualified to be here.
Are you giving up?
My voice didn't reach Suga-san.
I failed as a personality.
You can say no if you want!
I am programmed not to disobey the company's orders.
Why are you so unable to adapt?!
Director, you called me sincere.
There is one thing I understood as I worked with you.
It's the meaning of the word 'fun'.
Maico-chan...
This is the best one.
Take it.
Matsu-san...
I can now be happy because of you.
Izumi-san...
Ume-san...
It's shining.
I want you to have it.
I heard Ume-san's voice for the first time.
It's a pretty voice.
Take this with you.
It's the best, happiest photo ever.
Kacchin-san!
You!
Densuke-san...
These are your precious...
I'm such a goof, so I lose them all the time.
So would you keep them?
Okay.
Take care, everyone.
Maico-chan!
Densuke!
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Was it okay?
Was it really okay?!
Maico would have left even if we stopped her,
just like Suga stayed in the studio until the last minute.
I think so too.
But...
It's not like Maico will cease to exist.
Densuke. Just as Maico did for Suga,
it's now our turn to let Maico hear our voices.
We're radio artists, so we'll do it over the radio.
OK.
We're now down to 5.
I guess the replacement is coming today.
We have to let Maico hear our broadcast.
We have no choice but to accept whoever comes.
Get ahold of yourself, Robo Fetish!
I missed you calling me that.
That's so messed up.
Who's that?
Is it the replacement?
Everyone, line up.
We have to get along as soon as possible tomake this broadcast a success.
Teamwork is critical.
Densuke.
Okay.
Smile.
All right, let's make the greeting gorgeous with STAR's stuff.
Roger.
Welcome!
Miso cucumber!
xie xie = Chinese for 'thank you'
Xie xie, miso cucumber.
I'm not STAR.
Don't make that mistake.
Ha, look at all of you.
So bad.
I'm not in the mood for your bad jokes!
Is it that you are the new personality, Heita-san -san -san -san -san?
No, and I hate how you're talking.
Then why are you here?
Of cource, to accompany our president.
I'm Kodomo Taro of CoDoMo Group, who looks at our tomorrow!
What are you doing?!
Mr. President!
I'm in pissy mood today.
Take him out before I make him cry like a baby!
Try insulting me some more!
What?
Beat him up!
Are you okay, Matsu-san?!
What was that punch?
Jose = Jose Mendosa from Ashita no Joe
It was like Jose's.
Come, Maico!
Mai...
co?
Is that...
Super Maico
Hello, everyone.
Your voice...
Maico!
I'm the android personality, Super Maico.
I will try, try, and try hard!
Maico's Diary
I'm Super Maico.
I'm a 5th generation android personality, created with the cutting-edge technology of CoDoMo Group.
This is sudden, but I am leaving the personality position as of today. All my listeners, all the staff, thank you for everything. good bye.
I am loaded with twin 1-megabit CPUs and 32 terabytes of memory,
and I am able to access information over the Internet 2.
I am the ultimate creation for broadcasting.
Next Android Ana Maico 2010
I'll Help Too!
I'll help too!
Would you help me continue this broadcast?