An android announcer that the Japan Broadcasting System has hired: Maico.
Her voice gives love, courage, and energy to the depressed 21st century radio scene.
Things are still only at the beginning!
Star
What the heck are you doing?
Can't you see?
Getting ready to greet STAR-san.
Welcome!
STAR-sama!!
Don't even try with your awful hand-writing!
Oh, man, my artwork!
Violence is not good.
Are you okay?
Izumi-chan! Well aren't you dressed up today!
Not really.
A chance to marry into wealth...
Is that STAR guy that good?
Star
You don't know him, Massan?
He's kept 1st place the weekly ranking for the past 12 weeks in a row already.
How in the world did we manage to get such a star as our guest?
Well, you know, I think he's interested in Maico.
In me?
Yup.
I think he liked the fact that you're the world's first android personality.
So, you being a robot actually is useful once in a while.
Thank you very much.
Well, then, let's hit it big, and aim for the company director's award or something.
I like that, Massan.
Of course.
Ume-san.
By the way, Suga,
What?
Who's that?
Isn't he your friend, Massan?
He was already here when I got here.
I don't know him.
Ume-san?
Hey, who are you?
If you are not a staff member, get out of here.
This is not a playground.
)(*&!@$^!@#!
&@#*@#$(*^!(*!
What the hell are you saying?!
If you're in Japan, speak Japanese!
@@#$!
@#$#@#)   !@$(*!#$*(!!
Damn you! We're busy here today!
We don't have time to play with some mystery foreigner!
Oh, I'm late.
Hey guys, have you seen our guest?
Who's that?
He's STAR's manager.
I've been asked to be an interpreter...
I heard he's a difficult man to handle.
I've been threatened that he might cancel STAR's visit, if we don't treat him right.
Really?
We better be careful, then.
What are you doing, Massan?!
What, Kachi-ko?
I'm busy trying to kick out this weird foreigner!
Do you know who he is?
He's STAR's manager, Mr. M!
What?!
!@#)(*)(*)(%&!@#
!@#&@$)(@...
!@)$(*!@#!!!
He's really upset.
He said that he can't allow STAR to make an appearance on such a rude show!
How could you do this to us now?!
!@#)(*   !@#&!(@#!@00.
Make this man apologize.
Am I that man?
You want me?
Massan, please, for our sake!
Why do I have to apologize?
It's all for our program!
Aren't you the director?!
!@#)(!@*#   !@&#*!@#.
Be more humble, and apologize with a smile, he says.
Massan! Think about our program!
I'm very sorry.
(*&@.
Well, all right.
You're the man, Massan!
I was touched too, director!
Let me stay with...
Then let me smack you!
I'm sorry.
So, I'm not supposed to touch this?
So, this is STAR's poster.
Hey, why are you putting it upside-down?
But this is right-side-up.
This is STAR's face.
What are you talking about?
This is the shadow.
Isn't this tiny thing standing here STAR?
But would STAR have a crew cut?
(*&^@.
Yes, right away.
((*&&@#$   #$@#$   @#$@#$$#.
Oh, yes, yes.
My name is dog.
@#$(@#$(   @#$&(*#   #$#   !@#$5.
Oh, I know.
Everyone, get over here.
What?
Hurry.
According to him, STAR has a very delicate character.
He needs our cooperation so he can work in the best environment.
Well, as long as our program gets better with that.
I would do anything for STAR.
For a start... Maico and Izumi-chan.
Yes.
Put these on.
Okay, no problem.
I refuse.
Please give us a moment.
What?
Izumi-chan, put it on.
Please.
Yup.
Be a man, and just do it.
It's for the program.
Please.
No.
Maico-chan accepted it.
She's not thinking at all!
What? STAR likes women with facial hair?
Facial hair is life?!
@#(*&!!
Marrying into wealth...!
@#(*&@.
@#$@#$,   @#$@#$.
Thank you.
Man, you are both shining!
!@#@)_)(*&.
We have to do something too?
@#$@#$098   @#$@#   @#$   !!@#   #$(*&@#$.
STAR trusts a man with one eyebrow shaved off?
W-wait a minute!
Does STAR really...
Are you serious?!
Mister, can he represent the group?
That's so not fair!
Damn you!
Eyebrows are like relatives of hair!
How could we do that?!
I'll refuse too.
Man, you look so stupid!
You actually look pretty good, Kacchin-san.
What?!
@#)$(*@#$,   Kacchin.
Yes, right away.
Now what?
STAR likes nature.
He will be happy to see flowers on our heads during his breaks.
Does he really say that?
I'm sure!
I think.
We need to put this on?
On our head?
That's pretty.
That's not the point.
Man, this stupidity is so shining.
Stop bitching!
There's no shame here anymore!
I'm putting one on.
I'll welcome STAR with one of those on!
I hate dendelions, since they fly away later on.
I'll take... this!
Check this out!
That's so bright, Massan!
Don't say bright!
Now, you all hurry up and put one on!
Now.
NOW!
Now, now, now!
Looks like he's finally liking us.
Well, no wonder.
He's been playing with us so much now.
You all look wonderful.
@#$)(*@#$.
Yes, what is it?
Now what?
There is one thing you have to be careful about when we talk with STAR.
What is it?
The words for greeting must be "Miso cucumber."
Miso cucumber.
You gotta be lying!
I'm just relaying his messages to you!
@#098@   @#$   "Miso cucumber!"
Is he serious?
Oh, come on! It's fun!
Now, let's all practice.
Line up!
Now, 1, 2, 3,
MISO CUCUMBER.
@$@#$   @#$@#$%%!!
Izumi-chan, Ume-san, you have to say it too.
#@#$   )(*)(*)   @#$@#.
You better take this seriously.
But...
Don't talk back!
It's all for STAR.
Alright.
Ume-san too, do it next time.
MISO CUCUMBER.
No good.
"Cucumber" is okay, but "Miso" is still no good.
Now!
MISO CUCUMBER.
It's getting much better.
Now, with more feeling,
put the feelings of respect, love, and loyalty towards STAR.
Now!
MISO CUCUMBER.
Oh.
@#)(*@#$   @#$@.
What now?
Is STAR here now?
It's still early!
@#$)(#@   @#$%.
Get ready to greet him.
MISO
Masudamasu!
Price Tag: A Million Dollars
Mi!
@#$@#$)(*@#$...
Is he her friend?
Looks like it.
That's good timing.
Let's ask her to stop this idiocy.
I like that!
Listen up, everyone.
Today's guest, STAR, is a V.I.P.
We must not have bad manners.
Obey all orders that M gives to us.
Got that?
YES.
There's not much time.
Let's hurry.
)(*4   @#$@#$@!!
MISO CUCUMBER
Maico's Diary
Man, I fall in love with your sound effects every time I hear them, Ume-san.
With that, Ume-san was trying to say that he's quiet, but he's a qualified mixer.
Since STAR-san is coming
to our program today,
we got ready to greet
him.
STAR-san is really big
and very much shining.
It was fun talking with
STAR-san today.
Oh, I'm wrong?
I see.
Sorry about that, Ume-san.
He meant that Ume-san's family owns a sushi restaurant,
and the Chef is a karate black belt.
Next time - Android Anna Maico 2010
I want to see you right now
Next Episode
Saiko! Come back!
Is that right, Ume-san?