I'm in a dream, of which
I can't escape.
Time flies. Eternal silence.
The eternal light flickers in my heart.
The body became meaningless.
The world is far away.
Silence becomes darkness
that covers everything.
The only thing that is important
is happiness.
The happiness of being together.
The problem is grouping the DNA.
Could you please die once more?
Mr Karawaza?
You are looking for something, don't you?
I don't have a lot of time
that's why I'll cut it short.
Who are you?
-Excuse me,
I didn't introduce myself.
Let's say my name is Kato.
Why did you dial this number?
-I know exactly what you are looking for.
I know everything you ordered last year...
such as clothes, food, household goods,
medicine
and animals for laboratory purposes.
And of course the re-numbering
of the Haidon company
for the development
of the super-computer software.
I know everything. I see everything.
It is about the time, isn't it?
It is about the time to give medicine
to your sister.
How do you know about my sister?
-I'll come back to it later.
I will give you what you need
and you pay compensation.
That's how the business works.
Business?
A 21 year old woman.
Price: 10 million yen.
You received that amount
from the Haidon company.
It's a deal.
You can pay after you received the goods.
I'll explain later.
Please transfer the money
to three different accounts.
You'll receive the Guinea Pig
tomorrow afternoon.
Sister, it's time for you medicine!
Thanks.
How are you?
As usual. Always the same.
It's getting worse.
Don't say that.
Don't give up hope.
Yes, but...
Surely I know my body best.
That's true.
Are you ok?
Sorry. It's better now.
My sister's heart is
becoming weaker.
It's being attacked by her own
white blood cells.
I have to find the missing link
in the wonder of birth of mankind.
She's dead for five days already.
You work hard.
What's that?
I found an oil source.
Can you keep that for me?
Whatever happens, don't
loose it.
Ok.
Sister, time for your medicine.
Thanks.
I put it here. I count on you
that you drink it.
That's no good. It's too old.
What's going on here so late at night?
Sister, her wrist is torn off.
Give me yours.
It's for your best.
Sister, did you know that the
Hunchback of Notre Dame
was an android?
No, I didn't.
Sister...
My research is soon finished.
Then your disease maybe...
That would make me happy.
Who's there?
It's me, Kate.
I have transferred the money already.
I have to have a serious talk
to you.
You'll surely let me in if I
say: "missing link".
How did you get this?
Our computer is linked with the department
of molecular biology in Boston.
My partner has the rest.
I would like to give this information
to you.
I think it's not a bad deal.
-I don't want to.
Why? Your medical research...
I don't want to be used
for money making.
First you kill,
then you save a life.
You kill a woman
and save your sister's life.
Please go!
Look at these data!
A virus has already invaded
your computer system.
Don't worry. I and my partner know
the password.
Now you have to show me your laboratory.
Finally you woke up, Mr Kato.
It hasn't been easy.
But I got hold of important
data.
I kept your emotions and your memory
before you were brain-dead.
But I had great difficulty
in wiring your nervous system.
Is it too close?
I wonder if you live or not.
You died three days ago.
Then I revived you.
But only your head.
I found it.
Yes, that's true.
He isn't here, honestly.
That was your partner.
I want to know the rest.
I want her address.
You can talk, can't you?
Soon.
It'll happen soon.
That's good.
Is that your partner?
-Keiko.
Ah, her name is Keiko.
You won't manage to do that.
Mr Kato, I will implant a new
memory.
I understand. Yes. Yes.
Mr Kato,
I will now enter new data.
Please, come here.
It won't take long until you
live again.
Sister.
Why did you bring me back to life?
Finally I found peace.
The world is far away.
Silence becomes darkness,
that covers all.
So many decades have been gone
since then.
I created God,
the devil and myself.
And I'm still there. Alive.
My body still hears
the bells for my sister.