Hello.
Hiroshi, look at.  It always has his notebook.
It is strange since that his woman left it.
Ca does now a month that she left.
I wonder where it goes with his wipes.
Awaits, Hiroshi!
THIS IS my secret hiding place.
All my lost treasures are here.
All the beautiful things that I lost are here.
the whole times that I lost is here.
All is hidden in the darkness.
When I was again child, there was a river.  I came to play here.
Fish, friends, dragonflies...
They all disappeared.
Chibi, this is you?
You disappeared so suddenly!
And I rediscover here in this dark place.
small Poor thing.
I am a painter.
I must paint you Chibi.
You?
I already met you.  Before, when there was a river here.
IT WAS well you?
Yes, I am a siren.
When the river drained itself, I failed here.
I hear you.  Your voice resounds in my heart.
You lived here in the darkness...
for this whole times...
Since that I met you, I love this place.
I come here since years to paint.
Now I understand why.
Why?
Just to review you and paint.
all that I lost, I rediscover it in you.
HAS to leave now, I will not stop painting you.
That Is this that this is?
You had to catch a strange thing.
let us Go at my place.
One will take care of this infection.
let us Return.
Thank-you.
Leaves me to see.
Ca should help you.
This medicine can heal all the evil.
You would do better to paint me.  This is your mission.
Yes, my mission.
completely.
I am a painter.
I will paint you.
HAS to leave now, I will spend my time to paint you.
Hiroshi, does what arrive to the painter that lives up there?
It goes out everyday with his sketch notebook.
How wants you that I know it?  - I related you that it was himself
done book a bathtub last week?
Why, it interests you so as that?
Stops that.
Then stops, you!
You are really stupid!
That Is this that this is?
You go well?
Holds good.
Go.
Thank-you my God.
Ca stopped itself.
Thank-you.
This medicine has not the air to walk.
Good...
well by where to begin...
The corpse must be the one of his woman.
THIS IS a terrible matter.  She brutally was mutilated.
know You, she was pregnant.
Nothing that of there to think...
How that goes?
I am frightened!
It killed his woman.
Leave to pass us.
His woman was nailed to the bed since a times end.
IT WAS a drawing professor.
A very kind man.
That goes it t to arrive for him?
No idea.
Magnificent...
Here the results of the investigation.  According to the autopsy report,
it would have dismembered his woman.  She was pregnant of 8 months
and was in final phase of a cancer of the stomach.
The fetus is dead inside the mother.
The painter asserts to have killed a siren.
The psychological tests concluded that it was schizophrène
and it was committed little time after.  Here the results of the search.
scales were rediscovered in his bathtub.
But the origin of this fish remains
to this indeterminate day.