- What was that?
- Please remind me, never to go out with you.
- Fine, you don't have to.
- I won't.
Shut up! Stop laughing,
it's not funny.
- Are you okay?
- No.
Stupid shoes.
The fuck are you looking at?
But seriously, I've never seen
so many douchebags in one place.
- I don't know, that tall one was kinda hot.
- The Marilyn Manson?
- Hot!
- Gross!
- You take this, I'll take the next one.
- You little freak.
- You're gonna go back in there, aren't you?
- Huh, no.
- Whatever.
- No.
- Bye, Judy.
- Bye, Stephanie.
- What the fuck?
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry. You look so pretty.
- I had to just to scare you a little bit.
- Don't touch me.
I'm just trying to say hello,
you have such a pretty dress on.
Check it out, check it out...
We got a limo, we got weed, champagne.
Just come hang with us.
Leave her alone.
Why are you in a such a bad mood?
Can I have a cigarette at least?
Or something, a smile?
Fuck off.
She just threw a cigarette at me.
Bad vibe, bro.
- Not very nice.
Hi! Can you-
The fuck?!
I see you too.
That late and still out?
Better go home.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
I know where you live, Judy.
See you later.
Yeah, I just got home.
God, I'm glad that's over.
I know.
It was just some old truck driver.
Yeah.
Ugh no, I didn't.
I just...
No, it freaked me out.
I know.
Yeah well, I blame you.
The stupid places you take me to.
Oh crap.
The lights are out on my floor.
Ok, bye.
- Where'd you park the car?
- It's downstairs.
- You got the address?
- Yeah. You better hurry, we're gonna be late.
Please don't scream.
You're so beautiful.
MANIAC.
Hello, Redlucie86.
Truly timid?
It's my first time on a dating site.
There's a reason
I'm called timid man.
Picture...
That sounds lovely.
Why didn't you agree?
Of course I have.
- Lucie?
- Frank.
- Hi.
- Hi. It's very nice to meet you.
No charm, I'm sure.
- You are totally not what I imagined.
- Really? What did you imagine?
Umm, like fat, with long black hair
and just greasy skin full of acne.
Huh, you should've seen the other photo
I was going to send you.
I mean people always post
the best pictures of themselves
and then that's what something
is like when you meet them.
I ordered some wine.
I hope you don't mind.
No, I like a man
who takes control.
Thank you.
- Cheers.
So, how long have you been using
the website?
Uhh, like six months, maybe?
But this is my first dinner date,
usually it's just for drinks.
Although I can already tell that
you are a breath of fresh air
for the jugheads I deal
with at the bar every night, ugh.
See, it's really easy to get over
with the testosterone at work, you know?
Yeah.
So, why don't you have
a girlfriend?
- I...
- Are you okay?
I just...
Frank, are you okay?
You look pale.
Is everything okay?
Well, excuse me, I-
I need to find the restroom.
Did that waiter even look Indian to you?
I think he looked more Mexican.
He was such a tool.
You know, it was really sweet
of you to drive me home.
I'm happy to do it.
I had a very lovely evening.
Did you wanna come up
for a drink?
Are you sure?
Uh, like I said -
begging really isn't my thing, so...
Right. Okay then.
Sounds nice.
So what's all that stuff
back there?
I thought you were a journalist
or something.
It's for a fashion shoot.
I'm just doing a favor
for a friend.
So where do you live, Frank?
Probably in some trendy loft
or something.
I mean my place isn't much
but it's all mine, so...
I'm done with roommates.
No, thank you.
I still have to drive home.
Yeah, but not now, right?
You should take off your coat
and stay for a little while.
Want me to put on some music?
I love this song.
Dance with me.
I think you're cute.
I'm gonna be right back.
You don't go anywhere.
You take a lot
of pictures of yourself.
Hi...
I wanted to slip into something
a little more comfortable.
So how about that coat?
Now it's your turn to do me.
Why... Why are you hiding?
I don't know.
They're little.
What do you think?
You wanna touch them?
You shouldn't be so scared,
timid man.
Your hands feel warm.
Squeeze them.
You can do it harder.
You wanna get rough playing?
Is that what you're into?
Are you gonna fuck me?
I can't. I can't.
Don't be a pussy.
You like it?
I like to keep the lights on too.
Don't be so horrified.
You just relax.
Why can't you leave them alone?
Why can't you leave any
of them alone?
Can I have just one
without you getting in the way?
Now look...
Look what you made me do.
Look what you made me do!
I hate you.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I'll make it better.
I'll make it all better now.
Sorry I missed you today.
I have a surprise for you.
Are you asleep already?
I'm sorry but I just can't wait.
Alright.
Take a look.
I saved the best for last.
Here we go.
Oh, that's nice.
Perfect fit, right?
Okay now, this might
sting a little.
Okay, good.
Good.
Just one more...
Perfect.
Meet Redlucie86.
Redlucie 86,
this is my girlfriend.
I know the two of you will
get along just fine.
Don't worry.
It's fine, it's fine.
What?
She's beautiful.
Why are you ignoring me, huh?
No, wait...
This is impossible.
No!
Why are you doing this to me?
What? You too?
Why?
You're just like her!
You two are the same thing as her!
Why are you doing this?
Why?
Hey.
I'm sorry to disturb you, uhm...
I was just taking pictures
of your mannequins in the window.
I hope that's okay?
- It's fine, I guess.
- Yeah?
Do you mind if I take pictures of them
with the gate open?
Okay, sure.
Yeah? Cool, thank you.
- What's this for?
- Oh, it's just fine art, I guess.
Here, take a look.
- Is that French? Your accent?
- Oui.
You have a good ear.
- What do you do exactly?
- I take pictures of mannequins.
I try to bring them
to life with light.
Okay, cool. Thank you.
Sorry to have disturbed you.
I'm not usually opened on weekends.
Well, thank you
for opening up for me.
Bye.
Would you like to see my work?
What do you do?
Are you an artist?
I don't know about all that.
Come in, maybe you can tell me.
It's amazing.
They're from all styles and eras.
I've restored most of them myself.
She's beautiful.
I love her.
- What year is this from?
- Thirties.
She's in great condition.
You know what...
I'm having a show for my photos
in a gallery downtown.
Maybe I could use some of your
mannequins for my photoshoot.
That would be incredible, I mean...
They're so much more unique than
the ones I've been shooting with.
- Is this your place?
- Yes.
- You bought it?
- It was my family's.
Been restoring them
for three generations now.
Who's Angela?
The name on the sign.
It was my mother.
She's gone.
I'm sorry.
- Do you live here?
- Thank you for coming.
Sorry, I'm a little nosy.
I mean this place is so special.
So what do you think
if I rent them?
Uh, I'm not sure...
I usually try to find permanent
homes for them.
You're funny.
Well, I can adopt them.
What about that?
I'll give you my number.
So if you change your mind, I promise
to have them home before midnight.
I can be a good mother.
- My name's Anna.
- Thank you.
Call me, please.
Oh and by the way...
You have lipstick on your face.
Have a great day.
Oh no. No, no, no.
No. Get out.
Get out.
Get out. Go.
Go.
That's disgusting.
- Move it!
- I'm just waiting for my wife.
You have ten seconds
before I give you a sanitation.
Let's go.
Come on, let's go!
- You ready?
- Yeah, let's go.
I got my stuff.
Ugh, can you turn this on?
- I'm sorry!
- Shit, you scared me!
I forgot my tights.
- Hey, do you mind waiting for me, please?
- Sure, yeah.
Thanks.
I can't believe you shoved me in my locker.
Don't be tight.
- It was just a joke.
- Come on...
I could've broke my ankle.
- It still hurts.
- You're such a prick.
- But seriously.
- Tough it up.
- Come on girl, just come out with us.
- One drink.
- No.
- Come on, hun.
- Why don't you wanna come out?
- I'm going home.
- You never come out with us.
- What's up with that?
- The car's right up there.
- No way.
- You guys, I think I really hurt
my leg bad today. - Really?
- How?
- I went so fast with that twitch at.
I really don't think those tights
are any better.
- Good night, girls.
- Good night.
- Get home safe.
- Bye.
Text me, let me know.
Good night.
Oh, fuck.
- You're so beautiful.
- Shit.
Oh, shit.
What the fuck?!
Leave me the fuck alone!
Get away from me.
Somebody! Help me!
What the fuck?
Where is everyone?
Please, help me!
Please! Help me.
Help me!
Somebody! Open it!
Please!
Hey!
Please.
Open the gate, come on!
Oh fuck.
No, no.
Shit.
Oh, shit.
Fuck!
Oh, fuck.
No! No!
Please!
No!
Please.
Stop looking at me,
focus on your work.
- Anna, can you give me a hand?
- Yeah, sure. What do you need?
A hand, behind you.
- Which one?
- Second row.
- This one?
- The one on the right.
Oh, sorry.
Doctor Frankenstein, I presume.
- Are you a fan of those old films?
- For sure.
Okay, so what do you think
about my idea
of putting the mannequins among
the guests at the show?
You could see them mingling,
like they're real people.
Sometimes I think they have
more personality than most people.
I think we may have some
of the same friends.
- So, what do you think?
- I think you're incredibly talented.
- Well, that makes two of us then.
- Not really.
- I'm just a restorer.
- That one's my favorite.
Okay, now you show me.
It's amazing.
- It's gonna be perfect, Frank.
- I'm glad you like them.
- I love them.
- Why did you want them to be faceless?
Oh, I have a little idea for the show.
You'll see.
Okay, I'm starving. Are you hungry?
You wanna grab some lunch with me?
It's my third exhibition since
I've graduated from art center.
But it's my first with this gallery.
If it's successful they'll give me a show
in their other galleries in New York.
If something was missing...
Something tangible relating to the concept-
The installation of your mannequins
with create the ambiance I was looking for.
You know, when you came into my shop
you looked at them
like no one else ever did.
You seem captivated.
- You must have thought I was crazy.
- No.
You were so soulful with them.
So present.
When my mother died last summer,
I wasn't so sure what to do with our shop.
Most stores couldn't care less about restoring
antiques. It's cheaper to buy them new.
And if I closed the shop
I would've had to abandon them.
It's like me and my old negatives.
I have boxes full of them but I could
never see myself getting rid of them.
Sometimes it's hard to move on.
So what does your girlfriend
think of your work?
- I don't have a girlfriend.
- Really? Okay...
I thought you lived with someone.
Frank?
- Are you okay? - It's nothing.
- It's just a migraine. It'll pass.
- Should I call a doctor?
- No, no, no-I'll be fine.
I just need my meds.
I'm used to it.
- I'm sorry, I have to go.
- Are you sure you don't need help here?
No, thanks.
I just need to be alone.
Watch it, fuck face.
Are you suffering from a migraine?
This will have a similar effect
but you won't need a prescription for it.
- And it comes in a nasal spray, so it'll work faster.
- Thank you.
We have found links connecting
the two victims in mid-town.
But as our investigation
is still developing.
I can not give you
any more details.
All I can say is that all
of these women were Caucasian,
between the ages of 20-30.
They can talk all they want.
But they will never understand.
As long as you keep a secret.
But if you can't, it'll find you...
and you'll be alone.
You hear that?!
The lot of you.
Alone.
- Now promise me you won't tell.
- Franky?!
Hey, it's mommy.
Franky, honey, where are you?
Franky!
Come here.
Shh, momma loves you.
Hey.
The necklace is beautiful, Frank.
Thank you so much.
- Did you make it?
- I did.
That's original.
Where did you get the stone?
It's something I found
in a thrift store.
Is that real hair?
What is it?
- I believe it's horse hair.
- That's interesting.
And what about you?
Are you feeling better?
Oh, sure.
I've had migraines since I was a kid.
I forgot to take my medicine, so...
It's really nothing.
Sorry if I've frightened you.
- It's okay.
- I just finished on-
Um, you know-Sometimes I feel like
you come from another era.
I love it.
It makes you very different.
One second, Frank.
I'm sorry.
Thank you so much.
- I'll see you.
- Yeah.
Sorry Frank, a friend of mine
was helping me and I had to say goodbye.
I sometimes feel like
a slave-driver, you know?
- I hate it.
- I can't say I know what you mean.
I've always worked alone.
- You never feel lonely?
- Yeah.
That's why I was calling.
I thought if you weren't
doing anything...
I would love to.
But I have so much to do tonight.
But what about tomorrow?
We could do something.
Okay, yeah.
Tomorrow night works.
- What time?
- Nine?
- Is that okay?
- Nine is perfect.
- I'll pick you up at the gallery?
- Yeah, super.
Cool.
Good night, Frank.
Good night, Anna.
Stop staring.
You're missing a movie.
Franky? Hey, it's mommy.
Franky?
Franky, honey, where are you?
Are you alright?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm fine.
So what'd you think?
You know, Caligari is -
to be the first horror movie.
I really thought she was gonna
get killed at the end.
I'm glad that she didn't.
Yeah, but they all end up living
in a mental hospital.
I know but at least
it was a happy ending.
I may have just found
the last romantic.
Sorry.
Hello?
Yeah.
Where are you?
Yeah, okay. Cool.
Yeah, I would love to.
Okay, I'll call you back
in five minutes. Ciao.
It's my boyfriend.
He's at a bar having a drink.
You wanna have a drink with him?
Frank?
Are you okay?
- It's okay. I'm tired.
- Are you having another migraine?
No, I'm fine.
I just have some more work
I have to do at the shop.
Have fun, though.
- Let's have one drink.
- No.
- Just one.
- Really.
Come on.
- I had a very nice evening.
- Okay.
Another time, I guess.
Good night, Frank.
Goodbye, Anna.
The Cabinet of Dr. Caligari.
Go wait for me in the car, Franky.
Don't just stand there.
Do as I tell you!
Go wait for me in the car,
goddamn it. Franky!
- Hey guys.
- Hey. Good show.
- Do you think?
- Absolutely.
- Really?
- It's great.
Are you serious?
One second.
- Hey Frank, I'm so happy to see you.
- Hello Anna.
- You look stunning.
- Thank you.
- Really, you're beautiful.
I just feel like I'm in
a carnival costume.
This heels make me walk
like an ostrich.
- I'm happy you made it, though.
- Me too.
- Your photos are breathtaking.
- Thank you.
The way you made the mannequins
come to life at the projections.
- Yeah.
- It's you, right?
Yeah, it's me.
My face on your mannequins.
- Will you excuse me for a moment?
- Yeah, sure.
You lose something?
Anna loves to hang out
with her gay friends.
I guess it's a way for a man never have to
worry about trying to fuck her.
You're the mannequin guy, right?
Lemme ask you something.
Did you play with dolls
when you were a kid?
- I'm not gay.
- What?
Good talk.
A famous person once said:
An artist is somebody
who produces things,
that people don't need.
You know...
Your work might interest
another client of mine,
whose general theme is destruction
of completely useless objects.
I'm sure he'd love to smash up
some of your mannequins
at his next photoshoot.
I'm in restoration.
So tell me, Fred-
How does the restoration
process take place?
Do you go dumpster diving,
department stores garbage bins
in search of used parts?
They're antiques.
You wouldn't find them in dumpsters.
Honestly, I just find
the whole thing really creepy.
You and Anna are the perfect fit.
- Do you have a card?
- No.
- Let me see if I have a pen.
- Dominique!
Gorgeous!
- Any buyers?
- A few offers.
But don't worry, the real money's
in New York. Okay?
- Okay, should I call you a cab?
- No, I don't live far. I think I'll walk.
- I can call you a cab.
- No, no, no. You go have fun, fun, fun.
- Okay.
- And congratulations.
- I'll call you tomorrow.
- Bye, sweetheart.
- What's wrong with you?
- I guess I...
Why do you always
have to do this?
- Welcome back.
- It's nice to see you.
- Hey Jimmy. Have you been good?
- Excellent.
Changing your makeup
and hair style didn't fool me.
You didn't think I'd recognize you?
Why?
'Cause you think I'm stupid?
Why do you act like
I don't exist?
I never wanted to hurt you.
But you made me.
Didn't you?
Yes.
Yes, you did.
Did you need to be
with all of them? Huh?
Did you?
Was it the money?
Answer me!
You knew, they didn't love you.
Not like I loved you.
Not like me.
I still love you.
You know that?
Please don't kill me.
- Please don't kill me.
- Oh. I'm not gonna kill you.
I'm gonna keep you.
Mommy.
You will not go out tonight.
Is that clear?
You will stay home with me.
Hey, it's Anna.
Leave a message after the tone.
Hi Anna. It's Frank.
I'm sorry to bother you
at this hour.
I just wanted to know how long
you wanted to keep the mannequins.
I have another client...
Anna? What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Rita, my agent...
She was murdered last night
in her apartment.
Murdered?
Oh my God.
Police just called me,
asking me so many questions.
Someone broke into her place.
They must have been
waiting for her.
Frank, it's awful.
I can't believe it.
I swear it's a nightmare.
You shouldn't be alone now.
Is your boyfriend with you?
No. He's back in New York already.
Do you need company?
- No, it's okay.
- No, don't be silly.
It's no bother.
That's what friends are for, right?
- I don't wanna trouble you with this.
- Anna, I'll be there in 30 minutes.
I know.
Me too.
I miss her too.
It's been a long time.
I'm gonna get her back.
I promise.
Come in.
I didn't hear the intercom.
One of your neighbors
was walking out when I got here.
I saw your name on the mailbox.
I hope you don't mind.
I'm happy to see you.
Oh, I didn't know you had company.
I don't mean to intrude.
Martin lives next door.
- Did you guys not meet at the show?
- No but I've heard a lot about you.
- Martin Nunez.
- Frank.
He's a stylist.
He's helping me with the mannequins.
Yes but I'm really an actor.
I actually just booked
my first national, so...
I don't know what that means.
It's a national commercial.
For Sparkle toothpaste.
- See.
- Ding!
Alright well...
I'm gonna leave you guys.
I actually have an audition
first thing in the morning.
So, if you'll excuse me...
- Oh honey. It's gonna be fine.
- Thank you.
Take good care of her, Frank.
See you.
It must've been
a very long day for you.
I know what it feels
like to lose someone.
I'm here for you, Anna.
Why would your boyfriend leave
for New York now?
Oh, we got into such
a fight after the show.
It's always about him and...
I don't even know what I was thinking
hooking up with that guy.
Really. He's such a music guy.
Huh, they can be very pompous.
Yeah.
I'm gonna make us coffee, okay?
That was the first day we met.
I didn't take care of her.
I was too busy talking to other people
and she left by herself.
Don't blame yourself.
It's really not your fault.
Just try to let go.
I know what you need.
I'm so tense.
You know, hair is the only part
of the body that lasts forever.
I'm sorry, I can't.
- I should've sent her home.
- Anna.
She knew what she was doing.
She lived three blocks away.
What were the chances
of her getting attacked?
Other girls were killed
and you had nothing to do with them.
Believe me, it's not your fault.
I asked Rita needed a ride
and that's when she told me.
- Told you what?
- Where she lived.
Isn't that what you were wondering?
How I knew?
I was just wondering what other girls
you were talking about.
The girls that were mutilated
and murdered.
It's all over the news.
Rita had the same profile.
Don't you think?
The police never mentioned anything
about other girls.
It's probably an ongoing investigation.
That's why.
Anna, you need to relax.
- Let me massage you again.
- It's okay.
I- I would just
rather go to sleep, okay?
And we talk tomorrow.
I'm very tired.
Wait!
I came all over across town
to be with you in your time of need.
Well, I would rather be alone.
Please.
Being alone isn't going
to help you.
Believe me. I know.
I'm just gonna ask you
to leave now. Please.
What's the matter, Anna?
I thought we've become friends,
you and I.
You sound like a stranger.
Why are you scared?
Anna, come.
I think we need to
have a little talk.
Get off me.
Just calm down.
What are you doing?
It seems that we need to
iron a few things.
You know what I mean, don't you?
Come, I think we need
to have a serious talk.
- Get off me!
- Let me explain it to you!
Get off!
Martin! Help me!
Help!
- What's the matter, Anna?
- Leave me alone.
Go away.
Please, go away.
Anna, it's me, Martin.
Open the door.
Anna, what's happening in there?
Is everything alright?
Anna, open the door.
- Anna?
- Martin!
- Anna, where are you?
- In the bathroom.
Anna, open up.
I'm sorry.
Open the door.
Open the door! Anna!
- Martin?
- No, it's not Martin.
It's just you and me.
Now open up and let me explain!
- Martin, are you okay?
- Anna.
It's me.
What's happening?
I came all across the town
to be with you in your time of need.
I'm sorry. Please.
Let's talk first.
Leave me alone!
- Just go.
- No.
- You need to understand.
- Go, please.
Put the knife down.
Put the knife, Anna.
Put the knife down!
Just calm down.
Calm down.
Just relax, just relax.
It's okay.
Okay.
Patrol 19, stand by.
Code 4-8.
Possible suicide.
Marian Avenue 728.
This is 19, we're on our way.
It's gonna be okay.
Anna, please!
Help!
Anna!
Somebody?
Wait!
Anna!
- Help me!
- Anna.
- Stop the car!
- What are you doing?
- Help!
- No.
No! No, no, no!
Oh, no!
Anna! Why did you do that?
Didn't you understand?
I just wanted to be with you.
I just wanted to be with you, Anna.
I never touched you.
Not once.
Anna, I want to introduce you
to my mother.
We'll be together forever, Anna.
I promise.
No one will separate us again.
Hey Frank.
- Do you like my nipples, Frank?
- Shut up!
God, your hands are so warm.
- I'm gonna get you back, Frank.
- She's lying.
Please don't listen to her.
Don't listen to her.
Did you play with dolls
as a child, Fred?
You wanna take a bath?
- No.
- You wanna take a bubble bath?
No. I do not.
Now leave. Leave!
Oh, Frank. What happened?
I knew you were in the locker,
you naughty boy.
Did you like what you saw, Frank?
Don't listen to them.
They're lying.
Frank, don't bring
any other girls home.
I get jealous.
I'm gonna tear you to pieces, Frank.
I don't even know them.
They're lying.
This is our home, Anna.
Welcome.
This is where we live now, Anna.
No, not you! Get out of here!
You hear me? Get out!
Don't come near her. She is mine!
Do you hear me?
Get away!
She belongs to me!
You will never understand
what we feel for one another.
Where is she? Where is she?
Answer me!
Get your hands off of me!
Please. Let go.
Ah, my leg!