Revised Subtitles By: DJPS
It's cool!
Let the singing begin
Sing it out loud
I'll sing it to the entire town
Panpipes and lutes get me in the mood
Every time I hear it, it makes me move
From your voice heard through the roof
My folk-girl, you are amazing
Your moves are groovy, oh my darling
I'm a city rocker in town...
When I saw you, my heart melted
Your crystal voice grips my soul
Singing with you would make me whole
I'm right here hoping you'll look at me
Seeing you'd make me very happy
I'm falling head over heels, or so it seems
I'd do anything
to see you in my dreams
Superb. I'll get it for you.
Cheers! Cheers!
Great!
Tao!
Hey Tao!
My turn!
I have no fear of rain or sky!
Always stand tall... up to the sky!
Thunder crashing!
Lightning flashing!
I still stand tall!
Against them all!
Hey!
What the hell?
My name is Tao.
I love singing "Lightning Rod".
But I don't know why my singing
annoys some people.
Sir, please...
Please don't make this ugly.
Who's ugly?!?!
Get out!
This is Tun, a good friend of mine.
We've been friends since primary school.
His dad's name was "Tai".
I've never seen his mom.
According to his dad, she ran off
with a guy when he was young.
His dad was a well-known amulet expert.
Everyone in the country knew him.
But after Guru Tai passed away...
Tun ran his dad's amulet store,
halfheartedly.
He's never had faith in the legacy
his dad passed on to him.
Instead his faith was in a shell of lust...
The thing which romantics
have beautifully labeled as "Love".
Tun had a deep belief in love.
His belief was beyond faith.
But one day his faith was
destroyed by a girl.
A girl named...
"Maew"
He was devastated,
and has since then kept to himself,
disconnected from
his social life and friends.
If he isn't possessed by his dad's spirit,
it must be the environment.
Since then, he has become
an expert on amulets.
And turned himself into an amulet guru...
widely respected in Pattaya,
just like his dad.
He makes a living from people's beliefs.
Frank Edward Muller used to say...
"Belief is the cause of faith".
And faith is the thing
that makes miracles happen.
Sometimes there is a fine line
between miracle and coincidence,
as thin as the line between
faith and obsession.
It's real.
Can you sign to authenticate it?
I can.
Thank you.
See you then.
Good luck.
Not working today?
It's a holiday.
Actually...
it's a rich man's holiday.
What's this?
All the money I owe you... 30,000 baht.
Where did you get it?
Oh?
you won the soccer bet.
Why? You thought I was
gonna lose forever?
Tonight, I'll take you out
for a Thank You Party.
Thank You Party?
Like the other night?
No, thanks. I don't wanna get hurt.
This is a hi-fi karaoke bar
with a great sound system.
It's cool, man.
I've already asked Ped and Kai.
No, man.
Don't be a prisoner in your own home.
Just get out and see the world.
Maew isn't the only fish in the sea,
you know?
Okay. I just wanted to invite you
to a karaoke bar.
You always stay at home.
Last time you didn't have
a chance to sing, right?
Come on. It's my treat.
Where?
Pattaya Karaoke.
Can you promise me one thing?
What is it?
Don't sing "Lightning Rod".
What if I get lost, going alone?
I can't fulfill dreams on my own
When I'm blue I want someone to talk to
The big question is who.
I don't have a clue
Would you be my guy,
if you don't mind
I have had a crush on you,
since forever
If it's no trouble,
let's put our hearts together
Just think of it as a favor
Your voice is terrific.
No "Lightning Rod"!
Okay, bro.
That baldy has bad taste.
Oh, your taste is fucking good.
Who requested this song?
My song.
Fucker.
This damn song again?
Big boob girl, dancing, dangling.
What a beauty!...
What the hell is this?
Actually, "she's" a "he" with HIV!
A troublemaker's song.
Gets his dick cut off.
Trying to be a heart-throb
Hate fagots!
Ahhhhh!
Did your father die?
I'm just getting in the mood here.
Stop it!
You're scaring the customers away.
Or you want to get me fired?
There'll be no more songs for any of you.
Serves you right.
It's your fault that
I haven't sung yet.
I didn't sing "Lightning Rod".
No, you didn't.
This is nastier.
That's not it.
Chang is prejudiced.
If I sang the National Anthem,
he'd still pick on me.
Damn it. Let's get out of here.
Whoa! I haven't sung a song yet.
If I can't sing, neither can you.
Oh!
You're an asshole.
This song again?
Can't you sing any other songs?
No, I didn't request it.
If it wasn't you, then who?
I don't know.
Maybe you?
Not me
Then who?
I'm right here waiting for you
Whenever she makes you so blue
Whenever I see your heart broken
My heart's also drowning in pain
If her love is mean and unkind
I'll wipe your tears away until they dry
Give me your bruised heart
Let my true love heal it fast
Have you never seen
an airplane before?
What do you mean?
Like a dog's eyes on an airplane.
Don't you get it?
Beauty and The Beast.
Do you know her?
Your stupidity cannot be cured.
Her name is Nok. She's high-class.
The daughter of a Pattaya Godfather.
Disappointed, huh dog?
I'm not. Cause I'm not a dog.
I'm Ped the duck, with my wings...
I'll fly there to quack-a-boom-boom her.
Hey, where're you going?
To quack-a-boom-boom her.
Her father is mafia, remember?
So what? He isn't my father.
You fucking duck, you've gone too far.
If her love is mean and unkind
I'll wipe your tears away until they dry
Give me your bruised heart
Let my true love heal it fast
If her love is too mean and unkind
I'll wipe your tears away until they dry
Give me your bruised heart
Let my true love heal it fast
I'll cherish you with all my heart
Can you take me home?
What did she tell you, Tun?
Tun, what did she say?
She asked me to take her home.
Cross it! Cross it fast!
Cross what?
The bridge of love!
It's the bridge of love
that she's extending to you.
What the hell are you waiting for?
Nok...
I want you to know
that I was AWOL.
I mean...
I just wanted to let you know...
You are such a fantastic singer.
You like this song too?
I really like it.
I've never seen any girl sing...
...as well as you do.
What's your name anyway?
It's "Tun", like a mole, living in a hole.
And do you have a car, Tun?
For Tun, the "mole in the hole", no.
But for this Tun, yes.
It's a motorcycle, not really a car.
Here it is.
It's an old hog, as you can tell.
On the journey that we've taken
Tons of life stories have happened
I've chosen this path as my destiny
It's fresh, like teen spirit
Though from time to time it can be hectic
It's the path of mind I chose myself
That's gross.
How is it gross?
I didn't ask you how you did it.
I just wanna know if you did it.
Well, Tao has a good point.
I saw you and Nok
on the motorbike together.
Why are you talking
like sex is a big thing?
If it isn't, I wouldn't have been born.
This mofo comes up with
another lame quote.
Whose quote is it this time?
Aristotle.
Well, is it a "yes" or "no"?
Yes?
Voila! That's it!
And how'd you do it?
You're getting too nasty.
Which one of you is Tun?
Chief Mhee wants to see you.
Her name is Nok,
the high-class daughter of a Godfather.
Is it you who screwed my daughter?
I didn't know she was your daughter.
Put it down. I'm getting a raw deal here.
How dare you step on my toes?
I didn't mean it. Besides...
Your daughter started it
What's wrong with you?
Didn't you hear what he asked?
Are you Guru Tun?
Yes.
Yeah, it's genuine.
That's what I wanna hear.
I knew your father, quite well.
If he wasn't such a skirt chaser,
he wouldn't have died so young.
What about you?
Are you a wolf, like your dad?
No, not at all.
Klae. Bring my daughter out here.
Do you know him, honey?
Bang! Bang! No, I don't.
Is that your daughter?
Yes.
She's nice.
I thought you were gonna get zapped.
Why was I gonna get zapped?
There's no reason for him to kill me.
Don't you know Chief Mhee kills people
for no reason.
How do you know, Ped?
Well, that's what people say.
People say again?
What if they said
your mom was a crocodile?
Fucker.
So, I'd run away from home.
Enough! Enough!
OK guys, let's get
our asses back to work.
What's our position tonight?
What do you mean?
Usually, we do it missionary style.
You think that's funny?
I asked if we're going out tonight.
Do you believe that?
Guru Tun asked us to go out.
I made some money
authenticating amulets.
Just wanna give you guys a treat.
A treat?
If it's on you, it's your call.
Pattaya Karaoke.
Oh Honey, I've already come to see you
I'm here right now.
Come closer to me (A-la-wa)
Oh Honey, we're soul-mates
I don't lie when I say I love you,
oh my dear (ta-la-la)
Oh Honey, I've already come to see you...
I'm sorry. Please come back later.
Oh Honey, we're soul-mates
I don't lie when I say I love you,
oh my dear
I promise I'll love only you,
really only you
I even talk in my sleep about you
Yeah only you
I don't believe you
You're a liar baby, a liar talala!
A liar baby, Ahhhhhh!
Hey!
What the hell are you singing?
It's "My Honey".
My Honey?
I thought you were singing "My Ass".
You barked and chased
all my customers away.
That's it!
Fuck off!
Any problem?
When I get rich you'll see!
See what?
I'll open up my own place
and you'll be sorry.
I guess I'd be happy.
Thank you.
When you happen to get rich,
give me a call.
But for now, get the hell out of here!
Get out!
Here, take this number.
Whose number is it?
It's Nok's, your babe.
Where did you get it?
I just got it, okay?
Happy Birthday, dude.
I'm really jealous of you.
The entire hectic story starts right here.
This girl Nok,
was neither high-class...
nor a daughter of a Pattaya Godfather.
May I speak with Nok, please?
Nok?
Who's calling?
I'm Tun.
Tun who?
I'm Tun, Tao's friend.
I see. Tao, friend of a toad!
Listen, that bitch no longer works here.
What do you mean?
What do you think I mean?
She doesn't work here anymore.
What kind of work?
Goddammit!
She's a hooker.
Why did you call her anyway?
A hooker?
Hello.
How can I get to mount her...
uh... meet her.
Just give me 100,000 baht...
I'll deliver her to your bedroom.
People are trying to sleep here!
100,000?
Who would have thought
that love could happen in one night?
What is it, Pla?
But... it actually did.
Uh Nok, I need a favor from you.
Can you do one last job for me?
Another Job?
I can't do it. I told you...
Kamnun Moo has already hired me.
Three million baht per year, remember?
Yes, but I... uh...
I can't!
All right. How about you just go meet him?
It's Kamnun Moo we're messing with.
Do you want me to get killed?
I really can't. He's already paid me.
And even worse...
I've spent it all. Got to go now.
Tao, the police are here.
Hey, stop!
Hey you.
Yes, officer.
I'm a security guard.
Great.
What movie are you looking for?
"Scent of the Night Flower 3".
Oh, c'mon.
Part 2 is still in production.
How can I get part 3 for you?
How about this one instead?
"Sex of the Night Fondler".
Guaranteed orgasm.
Guaranteed orgasm?
How much?
Hey, where the hell is Tun?
Why hasn't he opened up his stall?
He might have gone crazy by now.
Maybe.
He may not know what
"hooker" really means.
Right! Rotonour Sigford once said...
Sometimes, it's hard to tell the difference
between a genius and an idiot.
Who was this Rotonour Sigford?
Bullshit. This moron doesn't know anything.
Fucker!
Why are you closing your stall up so early?
Heading home for a soccer game.
I have a lot of money on the line.
How much did you bet?
100,000.
What?
100,000?
Fucker! Trying to get a new bike.
What happens if you lose?
Lose?
Impossible.
Tonight ManU is gonna win.
I'm sure of it.
Kenny Miller is dribbling past Wes Brown.
And he kicks it in! One-Nil!
Miller had a chance and scored.
No chance whatsoever for Tim Howard.
The Wolves had waited for this
counter-attack, and they did it.
Finally, the referee blew the whistle.
I don't have it.
If I did, I'd lend you some.
What did you spend all your money on?
I transferred 100,000
to a person named Pla.
I have just a bit left.
Who the hell is Pla?
Oh,
you gave me his number.
Why did you have to give him that much?
Tun... Talk to me!
Because I wanted to meet Nok.
That girl Nok?
Why did it cost so much
to meet that slut?
I don't know.
Pla said it's a security deposit.
Security deposit my ass!
You are such a comic genius.
I only paid that whore
10,000 baht to do you.
You hired her?
I thought you knew,
since I gave you that number.
How could you do this to me?
I just returned the favor.
What's wrong with that?
Well, did you finally see her?
I didn't fucking see anyone.
Don't tell me you got conned
by that ladyboy.
If you want that money,
go and get it back from that queer.
How dare you trick my friend?
Give the money back now!
Hey, what's that? What's happening?
What's happening, Poupee?
I don't know.
I thought I'd make money from this shit
and pay him off.
I wasn't trying to cheat your friend.
Sell it then.
I want that money right now.
Well, you follow him upstairs.
And where are you going?
I have to pee. I'll come later.
Come on.
Just wait here.
Never seen a woman before?
Don't you have homes to go to?
I really feel sorry for your parents.
Bring it out.
Give me a knife.
Hey!
I've got a knife.
Gotcha.
I got you.
I fucking crack myself up.
My joke rocks.
Hey bro.
I don't think I can
give you a refund.
Why not?
It's fake.
How come?
Pla said he got these drugs from you.
Taste it for yourself.
Hey.
How can you be sure he didn't fool you?
Dumb ass. He doesn't know anything.
Free coke for me.
Keep it, Kraroak.
What a sucker!
I got him, that knucklehead.
Tell your friend to put her hair up, bitch.
It gives me the creeps.
Have you ever seen 'The Grudge'?
It's me.
P'Arng?
I thought you got whacked.
Y-y-you think t-t-t-they would
recognize me?
Yeah.
I could hardly recognize you
if you didn't stutter.
About your soccer-bet debt...
Who's your bookie?
My b-b-bookie is Moo.
Oh! Same here!
How much did... did you owe him?
100,000.
Look!
Who's this?
The plastic s-s-surgeon...
h-h-have your face made over...
Then you can get away from them.
Change my face and look like you?
While you are living,
your looks aren't i-i-important.
Don't cling to them.
Who said such a thing?
Err... Franco.
Anthony Hawkins.
Stravinsky.
David Fisherman.
Next time get your
stammering voice done too.
Hey Tun.
Can I crash here tonight?
Tun!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Are you wasted?
Leave me alone!
Who the hell are you?
I'm Tao, the turtle, your pal.
A fucking turtle that talks?
Have you been drinking?
Hell yeah. You think I drank sea water
and got drunk?
Moron!
What part of your fucking brain
gave you that idea?
Asshole.
Who did you call asshole?
You!
Ouch.
My dad never even called me that.
Who the fuck do you think you are?
Oh, you wanna play rough?
How about a fist fight? Muay Thai?
Hardcore wrestling? You name it.
Or you want my sidekick to whip your ass?
Who are you talking about?
Kit Silencer!
Pew!
Take this!
Knocked? Knocked out?
Bleeding... I'll call Gatorade to pay you.
All right!
Do you want a piece of me?
Come on.
I'm gonna whip your ass.
When you're drunk, you are a shit.
This amulet model is no longer collectable.
You should keep it for yourself.
It's dirt cheap.
Fuck! I stole it for nothing.
Sorry. What did you say?
Nothing.
Hello. Are you guru Tun?
Kamnun Moo wants to see you.
I don't have any business with Kamnun Moo.
If it's about Tao,
I don't know him personally.
He bought an amulet
and we had a little chit-chat.
And I never bet on soccer games.
- Let me go! I said let me go!
- Where are you rushing to?
I said let me go!
Did you just punch me?
Why did you knock him out?
He was trying to run away.
Run away from what?
Wake him up.
Hold up...
What the hell is that bucket for?
To wake him up.
Fucking idiot! You watch too many movies.
You're gonna end up drenching him.
I hire henchmen to back me up.
But look at the way you all dress.
You make me look like a dumb-ass jerk.
Koong and Kung,
let me ask you something.
Why do henchmen have to wear wacky outfits,
and goofy black sunglasses?
And those stupid hats?
Wanna be a hip-hop star?
Why not pick red, white, orange
or other damn colors?
He is awake now.
Put that damn bucket away.
Hey bro...
You checked the amulets
for Chief Mhee, right?
Yes.
A honey tongue, a heart of gall.
I won't buy it
I had been warned
to not fall for your bullshit
A honey tongue, a heart of gall,
a hypocrite
How many hearts have you broken
to bits and pieces?
When can I take this damn thing off?
My voice would sound a lot better.
Are they all real?
Yes, sir.
Terrific. My own collection,
the Sacred Seven.
You have all seven models?
All but one. Could you find it for me?
Which model?
A Supermodel.
Give me the envelope.
Well, I bid you farewell, sir.
Hold on, bro.
Go tell your buddy Tao that...
Don't even think of running away from me.
Hey.
Show the guru out.
Nok.
Let go of me...
Do you know him?
Let me go.
Hey.
Do you want to die?
That's Kamnun Moo's chick.
Get out of here. Move it!
Come on!
038-225476.
Your father owns a crocodile farm, huh?
Yes.
So he is rich then.
What's his name?
Poo.
Your dad's Poo. You're Pla.
Your mom'd be 'Puke'?
Puke your mother!
Such a dogbreath.
Hello?
May I speak to Poo?
Speaking.
Listen! I've kidnapped your son, Pla.
If you don't want
something tragic to happen,
Pay me a ransom of one...
two...
300,000!
Huh?
Hey! I only owe you 100,000.
How'd you hear that?
The speaker's off.
Good ears.
Hello?
Do you hear your son crying?
Guess what.
I'm not giving you three million!
There's no love lost
between me and that sissy.
What the fuck bit you?
A film clit-tick.
A clit-tick?
They normally tick. They don't bite.
Yeah, but this damn clit-tick bites.
Hello?
What a fucking father!
How could you disown your son?
Why shouldn't I?
He disowned his own dick.
Listen up.
I'm neither a saint nor a
soft-hearted dad of a fag on TV.
That type of father surely has
nothing to do with me.
Cold-blooded motherfucker.
Did you really cut off your fuckstick?
None of your business!
Bitch!
If I don't get my money back,
I'm gonna kill you.
Come on! Shoot me!
I might look like a ladyboy,
but I know that gun is fake.
If I noticed it yesterday,
you wouldn't have snatched me.
Oh yeah? Why don't you try this shit first?
Alright. Keep laughing.
Hello.
Tun is hitting the bottle again.
Again?
Was it my fickle heart, my fault?
Or was it your gullible ears?
Whatever pulled us apart
I just want to tell you the truth
I want you to listen to me for once
I'm confused, going down
because of your changing heart
Your buddy's up there.
What is going on?
He said he's heartbroken.
Heartbroken?
Which bitch was riding
past his house this time?
That whore, Nok.
What?
Told you! That candy-ass
is too sensitive with women.
How much did he drink?
About half a bottle.
Why didn't you guys stop him?
How could we?
We got here too fucking late.
Just be honest and say
you didn't dare to.
All right. I didn't dare to.
You know he's a Mad Max
when he's tanked up.
Even Chang wouldn't dare to mess with him.
Take it easy, man. Easy.
I've found out Nok is
Kamnun Moo's kept woman.
Hey Tun.
Don't talk bullshit.
That's not funny.
Who the fuck is joking here?
Huh?!
Now...
Kamnun Moo said
don't you even think of escaping.
Hey! Look!
Holy shit! He said that?
Tun! Tun! Don't!
Please.
For my life's sake.
You are on your own!
But I'm your best friend.
Sit down, you jackass!
No!
Tun...
Please.
I'm so sorry. It's all my fault.
He already said sorry.
Let bygones be bygones.
No!
There's much more between Nok and me.
What the hell is it?
It's what you don't have.
And what is that?
True love.
Blow me, Tun.
What kind of love grows in one night?
It's something you guys
wouldn't understand!
I'd like to hear you sing.
Where are you going, Tun?
Didn't your friend tell you?
He did.
Didn't you say you loved me?
Are you stupid or what?
Is there a guy who still
believes in such a thing?
Yes.
No, there isn't.
Men don't have the word "Love"
in their hearts.
Meet 100 guys...
and they are all the same.
I'm just one of the love choices
she discarded
To her I'm only a useless cigarette butt
She inhaled all the sweetness
and flicked me away
Left me crushed under her feet
I'm just one of the love choices
she discarded
It feels like being hit on the head
with a mallet
I'm too sensitive and naive
Sir!
You've just interrupted
in the middle of my song.
I butted in because I'm a dipshit.
I'm an idiot who
doesn't know what love is.
But honestly...
I...
have sincere feelings for this woman.
This son of a gun is a sweet talker.
Award-winning poets should call you daddy.
Are you drunk?
I might be drunk.
But I know what I'm talking about.
Do you know him?
You really love this woman?
If "love" means sincerity,
Then the answer is Yes!
Can you put a price on your sincerity?
No, it can't.
Then your sincerity and love
are not the same.
The love of this woman is worth 3 million.
You have it?
If you do, go ahead
and take your love back.
Or, is your love worth less than that?
Deal!
I'll give you 3 million baht.
All right. You're the man!
But now, get your ass out of here.
Whenever you have the money,
You can come and get your love.
Alright.
No need to drive me away.
- I'm just one of the men she discarded
- What are you gonna do?
Can't do anything until those pricks leave.
She inhaled all the sweetness
and flicked me away
Left me crushed under her feet
I'm just one of the men she discarded
It feels like being hit on the head
with a mallet
I'm too sensitive and naive
I'm nothing but a novice
in this game of love
Hey!
Is he dead?
How much did you pay for it?
3 million baht.
It's a fake.
What?
Really?
Yes, Sir.
There're only 9 genuine ones in the world.
Three belong to Mr. Por, Chief Kwang,
and Big Mod.
One to Tri-Croc Temple.
One to Father Sua.
One to Dr. Keng.
And the last one...
belongs to me.
All besides these, are fakes.
Where did you get it?
From someone I know.
The one that belongs to you...
Can you sell it to me?
It was passed down to my dad
from my grandfather.
Actually it belongs to my family.
Three million Baht.
Agatha Kinsky once said...
Love makes you do stupid things.
And so does greed.
Hey!
What's your name?
Nhoo.
You are Nhoo.
You look like a half-breed.
Where do you study?
Bangkok.
What're you doing in Pattaya.
My parents live here.
"Great Butt-siness Company".
It's "Business".
What the fuck are you laughing at?
Butt-siness?
Who's your father?
Mickey
Mickey Mouse?
Since you think your English is good.
I tell you what...
I'm going to call her father,
and you talk to him.
Tell him that his daughter
has been kidnapped for ransom.
Hello.
Hi.
My name is Pla.
Uh... Pla like a fish... Uh... your...
Right now... your daughter...
you know, uh...
Your daughter like a... like a kidcracker
Kiss my ass.
What the fuck are you laughing at?
Kidnapper!
Kidcracker?
And you think you're so cool.
My father isn't a foreigner.
My father can speak Thai.
Why didn't you say so, bitch?
You're a bitch.
Want your ass kicked?
Oh! You're going to get it, you skunk!
You bitch.
Shut up, faggot!
Hello.
Mr. Mickey?
Listen to me.
This is a ransom call.
Your daughter is beside me right now.
If you don't pay me a ransom of...
of...
of three million baht...
Greedy asshole.
Why not?
Her dad is richer than yours.
Hello. Do you hear me?
If you don't send me 3 million,
I'll cut your daughter into pieces
and send her to you.
What the f...
If your father skips out on me...
Hey.
When are you going to release me?
When I get the ransom.
And when?
Seems like her father is ditching you.
Shut up, you monkey's ass.
You skunk.
Your mother.
You bitch.
You fucking monkey.
Why don't you hit her too?
Serves you right.
You're getting on my nerves.
I can't help it.
Your father is aggravating me.
You're dead meat, bitch.
Cut her saucy tongue out.
I'd love to see you in pain.
I thought you were kidding.
Is it in full?
Yes, Sir.
Ok.
I'm a man of my word.
Can I pay you only 2.9 million?
Why?
I want to pay my friend's debt
of 100,000.
What a macho man.
Don't you think you drink to much Red Bull?
Anyway you dare to ask,
so I dare to give it to you.
You have the guts
to bring me three million.
I respect you.
-Koong?
-Sir?
Do your job.
Miss Nok.
Now you've got your love.
Why did you do this?
What did you want to prove?
Nothing.
I just wanted you to know
that all men are not bad.
Are you sure you'll set me free?
Yes.
So somebody has already settled my debt?
Yes, but there'll be no next time.
No, not anymore.
That was my last time. I'm out.
Shit. Only 3 Million.
Why don't you give it to them?
How could you let them cut off
your daughter's finger.
I'm broke because of that card game,
remember?
You're damn right.
I came here to borrow money from you.
Mickey, how long have you known me?
I've known you... for one year.
Just one year, and you dare borrow money
from me.
Koong.
Sir.
Get Tun's money out here.
There's three million in here.
Take this money to the designated location.
Thank you very much.
And my henchmen will
take care of those creeps.
Hello
It's me, Chief Mhee.
I know your amulet is fake.
If I don't get my money today,
you are dead!
You cruel, evil-minded son of a bitch.
Alright. I'm sorry.
Your apology can't
make my finger grow back.
Why didn't you cut that skunk's finger off?
Well, I wanted a human finger,
not a skunk's.
Bastard! You trouser snake!
You already had your dick cut off!
This is just a pinky.
Stop screaming like you're gonna die.
Fuck you!
One more word,
I'll also cut out your tongue.
I'll let you go.
If you tell anybody,
I'll cut your lips off.
Understood?
Go home now.
Your car's at the back of the building.
Why? Don't you need the money?
Not anymore.
By the way,
it seems no one's coming to help you.
I knew it.
Please don't cut the rope.
Just leave it like that.
It really turns me on.
Hey, bro.
Bro!
Your phone's ringing.
Tun, where are you?
I can't stay in Pattaya.
Chief Mhee will kill me.
Why does he want to kill you?
He found out I sold him a fake amulet.
Why did you do that?
How much did you get from him?
Three million.
Three million?
Fuck you!
Yes, fuck me!
I have no idea how
to return his three million.
He wants his money back today.
You spent all three million on what?
I paid your debt of a 100,000.
Oh, thank you.
What about the other 2.9 Million?
Tun.
Hello.
Hello?
Mickey speaking.
I have the three million.
Where do you want it?
Yes, yes...
the same place in half an hour.
Hello.
Is that Nhoo?
It's me Tao.
What's up darling?
Where are you now?
I'm in front of my house,
about to drive in.
Has anyone seen you?
Not yet.
I've just arrived.
-Leave now!
-Where to?
Anywhere.
I'll come to see you
Really?
Yeah. I miss you already.
I'll be at my friend's condo.
OK, you go wait there.
Don't go anywhere until I call you.
Hey, where is my daughter?
You could call her cell phone.
Do you know why your father died?
Because he was a ladies' man.
But you are going to die...
...because of your trickiness.
Whose phone is that?
Is it yours?
No. It's his.
Why did you take his phone?
Damn. Get it.
- Hello.
- Tun, I've three million baht for you.
Sir, the caller said
he has three million.
Give me that goddamn phone.
- Hello.
- Who's that?
I'm Chief Mhee.
Where's my friend?
He's about to die.
Wanna say some last words to him?
Please don't hurt him.
I'm on my way
to pay you the three million.
You'll bring my money?
Alright.
I'll give you 20 minutes.
Send her in.
Klae!
Yes, sir.
Get her something to drink.
It looks like nobody's coming.
Honey, let's go.
Phra Rod.
Oh shit!
Where do you think you're going?
I'm taking the money to your boss.
You are hours late.
He doesn't want it anymore.
What happened to my friend?
Tell me that you want to die!
Tell me!
Tell me, son of a bitch!
Say it!
What's the matter?
I'm sorry.
I really can't do it.
If you can't, then
give my three million back.
You saved my life, Tun.
But, I...
Hey!
Did you steal my amulet?
You're still alive?
If I had waited for you,
I'd have been dead by now.
How'd you escape?
I beg you. Please don't kill him.
Suppose a woman sells herself
as a sex slave for one year...
just to save a guy's life.
If you were that guy,
what would you do?
What would I do?
What?
Three million baht.
If I were that guy...
I would give her this money.
Where did you get this?
ManU.
Someone once said that love only begins
when you have faith.
And where there's faith,
there's always a miracle.
Sorry. I thought it was Nok's car.
But now it belongs to Chief Mhee.
What do you mean?
I guess cars are more valuable
than girls.
So he chose the car instead.
Miracles don't always happen
to people with faith.
Because, since that day
Tun has never seen Nok again.
We're gonna drink and get drunk to eternity
- No check, no chase, no end of me.
- Take your bitch home. It's closing time.
Get up!
His crying and babbling may sound annoying
But nobody knows my friend's heart...
is broken!
She's way out of his league
Hey, the pub is closed.
What's your problem?
It's your friend's birthday.
My friend, not yours.
You're drunk. Buzz off.
Get out of here!
I told you to invest in something else.
What're you looking at?
She's my girlfriend.
Oh?
He stares at me like this everyday.
Right. Why don't you get used to it?
Fucker.
Get out.
I'm closing the place.
Some fucking owner,
always driving customers away.
Look at Chang over there.
Do you believe in destiny?
I've quit singing.
I know.
Think of it as a birthday present
from me.
I'm right here waiting for you
- Whenever she makes you so blue
- Happy birthday, dude.
Whenever I see you heartbroken
My heart is also drowning in pain
If her love is mean and unkind
I'll wipe your tears away until they dry
Give me your bruised heart
Let my true love heal it fast
When two people love the same song,
it shouldn't be called "destiny".
And as for the return of Nok,
it shouldn't be called a "miracle".
Einstein once said there's no such thing
as miracles.
Everything that happens
has a cause and effect.
The repercussions of an action,
that some religions call "Karma".
If her love is mean and unkind
I'll wipe your tears away until they dry
Give me your bruised heart
Let my true love heal it fast
Why don't we use real guns?
That's too merciful.
The airguns will give him
a slow and painful death.
Ready?
Ready!
100,000 to the first person
who cuts off his finger!
Yes!
Charge!
Yeah!!!!
Revised subtitles by: DJPS