Deck the halls
with boughs of holly
Fa-la-la-la-la
La-la-la-la
'Tis the season
to be jolly
Fa-la-la-la-la
La-la-la-la
Don we now
our gay apparel
Fa-la-la, la-la-la
La-la-la
Troll the ancient
Yuletide carol
Fa-la-la-la-la
La-la-la-la
Whoa!
Deck the halls
with boughs of holly
Ha-ha. There must be
much, much more holly.
Tis the season to be--
Wh-What's this? There's too much holly.
Whoa!
Slow down, lad.
Don we now
our gay apparel
No, no, no,
no more mistletoe.
Chip, away from
those presents, dear.
Mama, I found one
for me!
Can I open it, Mama?
Can I?
- Well, just one.
- Oh, boy!
It's good to see the boy
having a proper Christmas.
Not like last year.
Yes. This is much
more agreeable.
Well, I thought last year
was quite nice.
Yes, well, I suppose I--
I did manage to save Christmas.
- You?
- Yes, me.
If not for my skilful
and decisive leadership,
all would've been lost.
Leadership? Ha! You could
not lead a horse to water.
What are you yammering about?
It was all my idea.
Your idea? Everyone
knows it was mine.
Heavens. How many times are we going
to have to go over this story?
- Story?
- Until someone gets his facts straight.
- Why don't you tell it, Mama?
- Capital idea.
Well, I don't know.
Come now, Mrs Potts. Surely you
recall how I saved Christmas.
Tut-tut-tut-tut.
No leading the witness.
Please, Mama,
tell the story.
Oh, all right.
Ahh, now we will hear
what really happened.
Well, let's see.
Belle, terrified
by the master's anger,
ran away
from the castle...
straight into
a pack of wolves.
But the master saved her.
- They began to be friends.
- Ah-ah-ah.
That's where I came in.
- Where could he be?
- Goodness knows.
We've searched
every last corner.
I'm beginning to think
he's not in the castle at all.
Voila! There he is!
- Wonderful!
- No time to waste.
We must find a way
to get them together.
Let's go!
Love will not wait.
You really think she's the one?
Will she break the spell?
I knew it from the moment
I set eyes on her.
If anyone can reach the master,
Belle can. Such a kind soul.
And her looks don't hurt either.
Wait for me! Uh, eh.
- Hi, Belle.
- Oh, hello.
Chip, do you know
what day it is?
Well, it's not Tuesday--
No, silly.
Today is December 24th.
- The day before Christmas.
- And what a beautiful day it is.
A wonderful day
for a morning stroll.
Yes, yes. Nothing starts the day like
a brisk walk around the grounds.
Yeah! or you could
go ice-skating.
Yes, fresh air, exercise.
In moderation, of course.
Come along, Belle dear.
The great outdoors awaits.
Yeah, let's go!
Mer oi, monsieur.
Oh. Good morning.
Huh?
Oh, dear.
Are you all right?
I fell and I landed
on my-- on, on the ice.
It's pretty slippery.
Yes, it's slippery.
This is a perfect day
for skating.
Come on.
No.
- Go on, Master. It might be fun.
- Go for it!
- Come on!
- Not so fast.
Come on. Why don't you
try it like this?
One, two, three.
One, two, three. See? It's easy.
Yes, I think
this may work.
Bravo! Bravo! Encore!
Fife, you approve?
Oh, maestro,
it's magnificent!
Oh, come along.
It's merely an opera...
to bring the house down.
Is there a part
for a piccolo?
Absolutely.
Solo for Fife,
in B-flat.
- Ooh. I'd do anything for a solo.
- Yes.
I know. Now, Fifey,
in the midst
of my crescendo...
I thought I heard merriment
outside the window.
Have a little look-see,
will you?
Wow! Would you
look at that?
Well, I think I might. I'll
just pick myself up and-- Oh!
What's this?
Heavens, look.
I'm bolted to the wall!
Oh, right.
Urn, the master
is skating.
Skating? Why on earth
would he do a thing like that?
Probably because that
pretty girl is holding his hand.
- What? Belle?
- Hey.
Maybe if she falls in love with
him, the spell will be broken,
and we'll be human again!
Trust me, Fife.
Humanity is
entirely overrated.
Before the enchantment,
there was no need...
for my particular
brand of genius.
But now the master
needs my melodies...
to feed
his tormented soul.
I am his confidant...
and his best friend.
And I won't let some
peasant girl ruin it for me!
Fife, see to it that
this blossoming love...
withers on the vine.
Yes, Maestro Forte.
One, two, three.
One, two, three. One,
two, three. One, two, three.
I think I've got it!
Hey, down in front.
I wanna see.
Let me see.
I wanna see too!
- Quiet.
- Oh, this is very promising.
Ah, yes, there is
something in the air.
Could it be love?
Love?
I've got to stop them.
Help!
What's that
little toot up to?
Aah! Whoa!
Stop!
It's a Christmas angel, see?
This is no angel.
It's the shadow
of a monster.
Oh, Forte is going to be
so proud of me.
I don't know
why I bother.
Now he's worse
than ever.
Don't lose heart,
dearest.
I hate Christmas.
The music helps?
Your music is the only thing
that helps me forget.
Don't worry,
old friend.
I'm here for you,
just as I have been,
just as I always will be.
Why is the beast
such a grump?
I don't know.
He's always like that.
- Even at Christmas?
- Yep.
Belle, what's Christmas?
Oh, Chip, you must know
about Christmas.
Stockings in front
of the fire? Tree?
Tinsel? Presents?
Presents?
Do I get one?
Of course. Everyone gets
a present on Christmas.
- Oh, even the master?
- Yes, even the master.
- What are you gonna get him?
- I don't really know him well enough...
to know what he would want.
- What would you want?
- Well, what I love most...
in the world are my books,
my stories.
Why don't you get
the master a story?
You're right, Chip.
A story.
When I get to know him
We'll find more things
to say
One day
I will reach him
There has to be a way
Everyone needs someone
He must need someone too
When I get
to know him better
Here's what
I will do
I'll read him stories
From picture books
all filled with wonder
Magic worlds
where the impossible
Becomes the everyday
We'll find
a mountaintop
And some moonbeams
to sit under
I'll lead because
I know the way
So much to discover
I do it all the time
I could live
inside bright pages
Where the words
all rhyme
We will slay the dragons
That still
follow him around
And he'll smile
Yes, he'll smile
As his dreams
leave the ground
Stories and stories
About mermaids, kings
and sunken treasure
Magic worlds
where the impossible
Becomes the everyday
I know a tiny place
Just a dot
too small to measure
I'll take him there
I know the way
Stories about heroes
Who overcame
their deepest sorrow
They'll put hope
into his heart again
He'll cherish every day
He'll find
a better world
And the strength
to face tomorrow
I'm sure that
when he knows the way
He'll want
To stay
Do you think the master
will like his gift?
- I do.
- So does this mean we're gonna have a Christmas?
Uh-huh. Absolutely.
Absolutely not.
Why not?
Out of the question. Not a chance.
Dream on. An impossibility. Forget it.
Aw, come on!
- Suck in that gut.
- Mon ami. Get with the spirit. Unwind.
- Oh, dear.
- Come on, love. Have a heart.
Yeah. Come on.
No, no, and-- let me think--
No!
This is where
I put my foot down.
Wait. Get outta-- Uh!
The master has
forbidden Christmas!
- Oh, dear me.
- Forbid Christmas?
No one can forbid Christmas.
He doesn't wish to be
reminded of his past,
and Christmas is
a most painful reminder of it.
I, for one,
do not wish to torture him.
I, for one, think a little Christmas
cheer would do him some good.
- Yeah.
- 0h? Hmm.
The girl is right.
It is up to us to do something.
Uh! It's not our place
to get involved.
No, no, no, no! We just can't
mind our own beeswax, can we?
Just have to stick our wick
where it doesn't belong.
- Oh, humiliating.
- Pish posh.
I think it's
a wonderful idea.
But the master doesn't want it.
His castle, his rules.
It's not fair.
He's right.
It's not fair!
Don't whine, glasses.
Sorry.
Look at us,
squabbling and bickering.
Breaks my heart
to see it, it does.
And we used to be
at our very best at Christmas.
Why, we used to prepare
a feast for the entire castle.
Ah, you could have
some stuffed turkey.
- Cranberry sauce.
- Shortbread cookies.
- Mince pies.
- Potatoes.
- Gravy.
- And Christmas pudding!
Uh, pudding?
With, with custard?
What do you think we are, barbarians?
Of course with custard.
And raisins
and brandy...
and all those things
you like.
- All right.
- Yes!
But if the master finds out
about this, he will be furious,
so, everybody, keep quiet.
Come on! What are we
waiting for, Christmas?
Good heavens, we don't have
much time. It's Christmas Eve!
- I'll see to the dinner.
- I'll get some mistletoe.
We need to brighten
this place up.
Belle, I know someone
who will help.
Now, now, wait for me. I'm
in charge here. I'm in charge.
Wait for me!
One-thousand one,
one-thousand two,
one-thousand three--
- Are we there yet?
- Not yet.
Oh, boy, there sure
are a lot of stairs here.
One-thousand seven,
one-thousand eight,
one-thousand nine,
one-thousand ten--
Hello?
Do not be afraid,
mes amis.
It is I, Lumiere. We have come
to pay you a little visit.
- Lumiere?
- Angelique.
Ah, Lumiere,
finally.
I thought we were to be locked away
in this dusty attic forever.
Ah, Angelique,
mon amour.
Your eyes are still so lovely
after all these years.
Lumiere, please!
You'll tarnish
the halo.
Oh, yes.
This is Belle, our guest.
- Pleased to meet you.
- And this is Angelique.
She is the
castle decorator.
You mean was
the castle decorator.
I am not responsible
for this baroque atrocity.
When I was in charge,
the castle was full
of light and beauty.
Ah, but, cherie,
that is why we have come.
Gather around,
mes enfants.
We are planning the greatest
Christmas celebration ever.
- No, stop!
- What is it, cherie?
Why do you raise my hopes--
I, I mean, their hopes
only to have them dashed?
Well, no more.
But it's Christmas Eve. Without you, we'll
never get the castle decorated in time.
Ha! Christmas? Hmph!
I refuse to hope for it any more.
I will not
be disappointed again.
But this is to be the
greatest celebration ever.
We cannot do it
without you.
Well, but of course
you cannot.
Christmas takes planning
and organization.
No. No, I won't do it.
It won't change anything.
I believe it will.
There is more to
This time of year
Than sleigh bells
and holly
Mistletoe and snow
Those things come
and go
Much deeper than snow
Stronger than the
strongest love we'll know
We'll ever know
As long as
there's Christmas
I truly believe
That hope
is the greatest
Of the gifts
we'll receive
As long as
there's Christmas
We'll all be just fine
A star shines above us
Lighting your way
and mine
Just as long as there's Christmas
there will be Christmas pud
- Tons of turkey
- And cranberry sauce and mince pies if we're good
- Lots of logs on the fire
- Lots of gifts on the tree
All wrapped up
in red ribbons
Wonder if there's
one for me
We're due for a party
Where on earth do we start
I may wear my tiara
you brought me in Montmarte
All the silver
will sparkle
And the china
will gleam
And we'll be as shiny
as a brand-new centime
- After dinner we'll play games
- Till the morning breaks through
Then we'll meet
in the garden
- This is what we shall do
- We will build
We will build a snowman
that'll reach to the sky
It will stay up
until July
What are you doing?
Stop, stop, stop.
Put me down. Put me down.
Uh, this is ridiculous.
Everyone knows that
the lights go on first.
I don't want to go
all the way up there on the top.
As long as
there's Christmas
I truly believe
That hope is
the greatest
Of the gifts
we'll receive
As long as
there's Christmas
We'll all be just fine
There'll always
be Christmas
So there always
will be a time
When the world
ls filled with peace
And warmth
We're gonna have
the greatest Christmas ever.
Oh, I hope so, Chip.
You on the left,
you on the right, follow me.
There is decorating
to be done.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. But keep in mind,
the master mustn't find out.
Oooh, yes.
Christmas?
She's planning Christmas?
Yes. Awful, isn't it?
Perhaps she doesn't know
how I feel about Christmas.
But she does know.
She just doesn't care
like I do.
She's actually trying to bring
Christmas back to the castle.
And you know how much
we despise Christmas.
The day my life ended.
- Bring me my presents!
- Your Highness,
please accept this humble gift
as a token of our appreciation.
I know I speak
for everyone when--
Ah, just give it to me!
A storybook?
You call this a present?
I hope you have something
better for me, Forte.
Yes, sir.
Urn, of course, Master.
What is that?
A small piece
in your honour, Master.
Eeew! I hate it.
Forte, that stuff is gloomy.
Who disturbs my Christmas?
Please, take this rose...
in exchange for shelter
from the bitter cold.
I don't need a rose.
Go away,
you wretched old hag!
You have been deceived
by your own cold heart.
A curse upon your house
and all within it.
Until you have found one
to love you as you are,
you shall remain
forever a beast.
But we've come so far
since then.
We've risen above
the tragedy.
Where is she?
I believe she's gone
to the boiler room,
or so a little birdie
told me.
Hey, hey, hey. Come on.
Get outta the way.
We're workin' here.
- Excuse me.
- Let's go. Let's go.
All right, you guys. Now, get back to work.
The castle doesn't heat itself, you know.
Aye, gevault.
So, what can I do you for, lady?
- I'm looking for a log.
- All right. Logs we got.
What do you want? Hard wood?
Soft wood? We got it all.
We got birch, maple,
pine, oak--
Doi! Concrete.
My head. Don't worry.
It'll pass.
So, make up your mind
already.
Is it all right
if I just browse?
Suit yourself. Take your time.
Me, I got work to do.
Hey, what am I payin'
you for, being boring?
Do that on your own time.
Get outta here!
Yes.
Oh!
What are you hiding?
- It's a Yule log.
- Huh?
A-A Yule log.
It's a wonderful
tradition.
One log is chosen and everyone
in the house touches it...
and makes a Christmas wish.
Wishes are stupid.
You made a Christmas wish
last year.
Is this what
you wished for?
No.
But I will keep wishing.
- And when the log is burned on Christmas morning--
- There won't be no Christmas.
- But--
- No! I am the master here.
How can you be
so selfish?
You cannot possibly
understand.
You have no idea what
it's like to lose everything,
to be trapped
in your own castle,
to be, uh, uh, uh--
Prisoner?
The only one holding
us prisoner here is you.
Well, I'm not giving up.
Prisoner.
Hiya, Belle. You should
see the ballroom.
It's all decorated and pretty
and there's garlands everywhere.
I think the master's gonna be really
excited when he finds out about Christmas.
Well, he, he already knows.
Really?
Was he excited?
Actually, Chip,
he's forbidden it.
But I thought
he couldn't forbid Christmas.
You know, Chip, he can't.
We'll have Christmas
with or without him.
Hurray! Can we get a tree now, Belle?
It's the only thing we're missing.
All right, then.
Let's go get a tree.
But first--
Belle.
The master. Hurry.
What about this one?
Nah, too skinny.
Come on.
- Ohh, Lumiere.
- She's beautiful, no?
Yes, and I'm hideous.
Not to mention
ill-tempered.
What? What is that?
Ooh, it looks like
a Christmas present.
Oh-ho-ho.
It's for you, Master.
It's from a girl.
- Mrs Potts?
- No. From Belle.
Belle?
Uh-uh-uh. Master,
you can't open it.
Well, why not?
It's for me, isn't it?
Because it's
not yet Christmas.
Master, we all understand
how you feel about Christmas.
But when a woman gives a man a gift,
she's saying, "I care about you."
Hmm. But I don't
have a gift for her.
It is not too late.
Well, I guess I could
get her a little something.
Forte, stop the noise!
Noise? Noise?
This is my masterpiece.
Master.
I, I want you
to compose a song.
- It's a present for Belle.
- What? Belle?
And make it happy!
Oh, but happiness
is so depressing.
What's next?
Love songs?
Wedding marches?
It's all that girl's fault.
What about this one?
- Hmm, too wiggly
- Too wiggly-
Fife!
Pay attention.
I need you to pace when I think.
The girl is evil, I tell you.
She pulls him
from my grasp.
She fills his head
with dreams of love...
and hope and Christmas!
Well, what you gonna do?
You can't stop Christmas.
No, but I can stop
the girl.
Chip, this is
the last one.
That's not it. That's just
a weed wishing it was a tree.
Chip, we've looked
at every tree on the grounds.
But it's more
this way than that.
It will have to do.
- What a headache I have.
- I'm sorry.
L-- I'll get a saw.
No, that's fine. I don't want
I should put you out.
Oh, all right.
Do you have some oil? I just
thought a little massage--
But if it's no, it's no. Go on.
What are you waiting for?
Knock yourself out.
You never get headaches,
I guess. Lucky you.
- Really, I can get a saw.
- Who wants a saw?
I said go ahead with the whacking
and the hitting. Who's stopping you?
Shh. What is that?
It's beautiful.
And now for
a little Fife.
Sultan, wait!
Don't worry yourself about me.
I'll just sit here. Snow is fine.
A little wet,
but who's complaining?
Yes, my dear.
Come to me.
Come here, boy.
Come here.
Good doggy-
Nice doggy-
- Sultan?
- Back off, doggy.
Oh. Hello?
Hello?
Well, maybe there's
nobody here.
Maybe we should go.
What's the matter, Sultan?
Oh, hello. I don't believe
we've met. I-I'm Belle.
- And you are?
- Fife.
Down, boy, down.
We heard the most
beautiful music.
- Was it you?
- Me?
You thought
that was me?
Mademoiselle, please.
I am Maestro Forte,
court composer and
your most humble servant.
Pleased to meet you,
Monsieur Forte. I'm Belle.
Yes. The entire castle
is talking about you, child.
They say you're planning a
Christmas gala. Marvellous idea.
The very thing to shatter the
master's dark and gloomy past.
But you must make this
the grandest celebration ever.
- Have you gifts?
- Yep.
- Food?
- Garlands, ribbons, wreaths?
- Check.
Spangles and "fandangles"?
The trinkets, the trimmings,
the trappings?
- Yep, we got 'em all.
- A tree?
See, Belle?
I told ya.
Well, we found one.
But it was on the
piddlin' side of puny.
N-- But did you look
in the Black Forest?
There you will find
a tree...
better than any
you can dream of.
Better? We gotta go, Belle!
- We gotta!
- Chip, we can't.
L-I promised your master I wouldn't leave
the castle grounds. I gave my word.
Chin up, son.
There's a profound lesson here.
Keeping your word is much more important
than bringing joy to another.
You're twisting
what I said.
Not at all.
I agree with you.
Look after yourself.
Let the master do the same.
Never mind that the tree...
was always his favourite
part of Christmas.
Please, Belle? Please?
It looks dangerous.
Mademoiselle, you are
in more danger...
- in this very room, I assure you.
- All right.
- Yes!
- We'll take Phillipe.
If we hurry,
we can be back by nightfall.
- Hurray'.
- Au revolt, Monsieur Forte.
You'll keep my secret,
won't you?
Of course, mademoiselle.
The master will remain
completely in the dark.
Au revoir, Fife.
Fife! I want you
to follow her.
Make sure they don't
come back.
Oh, yeah, but, uh,
maestro, she's so nice.
When you're finished
fawning, Fife,
perhaps you can recommend
someone else to play your solo.
No! I'm going.
I'm going.
- Cogsworth!
- Oh, dear. Yes. Oh, oh, coming. Corning.
Cogsworth!
Running, running. Almost there.
You bellowed, sir?
Find Belle. I, uh--
Well, I--
She has to hear a song.
Yes, sir.
Right away, sir. Uh, uh, yes.
Splendid.
Yes, well-- Splendid.
Belle. Belle?
Where is she?
Belle?
Careful, careful.
Too fast!
Get out of the way! Stop!
Huh! Amateurs.
Belle? Here--
Excuse me. Hello?
Has anyone seen Belle?
I can't find her anywhere.
And the master is demanding to see her now.
He's got a song he wants her to hear.
C'est magnifique!
Last I saw of her, she was going with
Chip to look for a Christmas tree.
Right. We must conduct
a search of the grounds.
- Lumiere, you're with me.
- Cogsworth!
I'm waiting!
0h, dear. Uh, running, running, running.
I'm almost there, sir. Uh, uh--
Mrs Potts, stall the master.
All right, Lumiere, we're--
Lumiere?
Wait, I'm leading.
Me first,
you second.
Belle! Belle!
Where is she?
Belle? Belle?
Belle,
where are you?
Lumiere, wait.
The Black Forest!
Come along. Hurry now!
Oh, no.
This is catastrophic!
Cogsworth, quit dawdling.
I'm not dawdling.
I'm waddling.
Well, don't waddle then. We're
in a hurry, you lazy old clock.
Why am I still waiting?
- Mrs Potts!
- Corning, sir! Corning!
What a brisk day!
Why, you look positively
chilled to the bone.
Where's Belle?
How about a nice cup of tea,
sir? Just a spot.
Hmm. Forte,
play Belle's song!
Hot.
You're not singing!
Deck the halls
with boughs of holly
Fa-la-la-la-la
- La-la-la-la
- Louder!
'Tis the season
- A bit more tea, sir? Good for the heart, you know.
- No, thank you.
- Just a spot?
- No more.
- Well, there's always room for tea, love.
- I said, "No more."
- Oh, dearie me!
- Mrs Potts,
are you trying
to distract me?
Goodness, no, sir.
Heavens. Is that a yellow-bellied,
double-breasted sapsucker?
- Rare this time of year.
- Enough! Where's Cogsworth?
- Where's Belle?
- Belle?
- We can't find her, sir.
- What?
Leave me!
Show me the girl.
- I will bring her back!
- No!
Urn, she's abandoned you.
Listen to your old friend,
won't you?
Have I ever steered you wrong?
Led you astray?
No. But the girl--
The quickest way
to break your heart
Make you depressed
and ill
ls to get tangled up
inside
The side effects
could kill
All passion
is a waste of time
A deadly game pour vous
I am your friend
Your cher ami
I wouldn't lie to you
If you must love someone
may I suggest
You love yourself
Just think it through
You'll never leave and you
will find you'll get more rest
You'll always feel
as good as new
Your freedom is the most
important thing, my friend
You must be strong
You mustn't bend
Don't talk for hours
Don't send flowers
Don't write poems
Don't sing songs and dance
Beneath the stars
that shine above
Don't fall in love
Oh, don't do it.
As soon as your heart
rules your head
Your life is not your own
It's hell when
someone's always there
It's bliss to be alone
And love of any kind
is bad
A dog, a child, a cat
They take up so much
precious time
Now, where's the sense
in that
Love takes the wildest heart
and makes it tame
If you're turned on
then just turn off
Emotions are a thing
all great men overcame
Please, don't make
this grande catastrophe
Don't get attached
to anyone or anything
There's nothing worse
than things that cling
You'll go to pot
You'll turn to drink
You'll never rest
You'll end up mad
And looking like
some poor demented dove
Don't fall in love
Don't fall in love!
No, no, no,
"0, "0, no, no.
They cannot mix bells
with holly.
Still, I have to admit,
not bad for amateurs.
I knew this was hopeless.
There. That's it!
That's it!
Oh, Chip, it's perfect.
- Do you see her?
- Not yet. Now, come along. Hurry!
You go on.
I'll never make it.
Save yourself.
- Ah, it will be summer before we reach them.
- What the--
- Whoa'.
- Mons'.!
Oh, dear!
Allez! Allez!
Faster! Faster!
I think we finally
found a use for you.
Clock boarding!
No, snow clocking!
Whatever!
- It's the best tree ever!
- Chip, you're right.
Merry Christmas!
And a happy Hanukkah!
We better hurry.
It's getting very stormy.
Again with the chopping.
Oh, I gotta do something.
Forte's counting on me.
Timber!
Take it away, Phillipe!
Oh, no!
- Fife?
- Uh, hi, Belle.
Uh, nice tree.
What are you doing
way out here?
Uh, nothin'.
I just was, uh, walkin'.
I mean, uh, I love
the bitter cold.
I mean, uh--
Phillipe!
Oh, no!
The tree, Belle!
We're gonna lose the tree!
Whoa !
Chip! Oh!
Where is he?
- Hold on, cherie. I will save you!
- Oh, dear!
Oh, no. Oh, gosh. Oh, no.
Oh, gosh. Oh, no. Oh, gosh.
Oh, no!
- Oh, Chip, thank goodness you're safe.
- I wasn't scared.
Oh, no! No!
Belle!
Oh, no, what have I done?
It's all my fault.
We all share
some blame, mon ami,
for daring to hope
for a Christmas.
You said you'd never leave.
I wasn't trying to leave.
I just wanted
to make you happy.
You broke your word.
And for that, you will rot
in this dungeon forever.
I should have known you'd
never be anything but a beast.
Midnight.
Merry Christmas,
Cogsworth.
If only it were.
Oh, my dear old friend,
I told you not to feel for her.
Things were so much simpler
before she came along,
before we dared to hope.
Oh, I thought
she was the one.
- Belle?
- Allo, cherie.
There she is.
- Merry Christmas.
- Doesn't look so special to me.
Oh, Chip, I'm sorry.
Nothing's changed.
I told you
nothing would change.
I told you the master
would not allow this.
I told you Christmas
was a hopeless folly!
But...
I was wrong.
When I felt lost
And lonely
Not a dream in my head
Your words
lifted my spirits
High
Remember what
You said
As long as
there's Christmas
I truly believe
That hope is the greatest
Of the gifts
we'll receive
- As long as
Our guiding star
Shines above
There'll always be
Christmas
So there always
Will be a time
When the world
is filled with peace
And love
Ah, it tears me up
to see you this way, Master.
Why do you torment yourself?
There's the symbol
of your curse.
Destroy it, and end
these adolescent notions...
of love and redemption.
End your pain forever.
Yes! Do it!
Smash it!
Belle?
What are you doing?
What is it?
Oh, a storybook.
Does this one have
pretty pictures you can color?
Utterly dreadful, Master.
No! This one's different.
It's from Belle.
Well, that would account
for the creative wrapping.
Quiet! I want to read.
"Once upon a time,
there was an enchanted castle.
Its master seemed as cold as winter.
Deep inside his heart--
His cries of anger echoed through
the stone wall of the castle.
Though surrounded by servants,
he was all alone.
And in that
simple act of kindness,
he knew someone cared.
Christmas that year was spent
exchanging humble gifts.
But the greatest gift
that anyone received...
was the gift of hope.”
Hmm. Hope.
No, Master!
Come back!
She'll only prolong
your torment!
You know what, Belle? I don't need
a tree to celebrate Christmas.
And I can do
without mistletoe.
- Well, I don't need tinsel.
- Oh, I don't need holly.
- And I don't need a wreath.
- I don't need ornaments!
- And I don't need turkey!
- I don't need stuffing!
I don't need pudding!
To each his own, my friend
You know how to get me stressed
But when it comes to
making Christmas special
I'm a cut above
the rest
If you could see things clearly
you would say that I've been blessed
You can't hold a candle
to my timing
I'm a cut above
the rest
You belong side by side
You should never be apart
'Cause when you're both together
you're really twice as smart
"Twice as smart."
She does have a point.
Yes, well, two heads
are better than one.
They say that as a team
we have got to be the best
Now we found something
we both agree on
We're a cut above
the rest
There's no doubt that as a team
we two are the very best
Everyone who knows us
must agree
We're a cut above
the rest
There's no doubt that as a team
you two are the very best
Everyone who knows you
must agree
- We're a cut
- A cut above
Above the rest
Uh-oh! It's the master!
Uh, Belle--
Can you forgive me?
Of course.
Merry Christmas.
Let's give Belle the Christmas
she's always wanted.
So, Beast gets girl,
and it's a happy ending
for everyone.
Enchantment lifted,
and Forte fades
into the background.
No longer important.
No longer needed.
I think not!
What is it, Mama?
What's happening?
Watch out!
Forte!
- Whoa!
- Hurry, now. Hurry.
Can you believe
I never took a lesson?
Belle!
- Oh, no!
- Belle!
- Help!
Oh, no.
Maestro! Stop!
- What do you think you're doing?
- Don't you see, Fife?
They can't fall in love
if they're dead.
I'll tell you what I see.
A big, old windbag!
You could've joined me, Fife,
but I see my triumph
is a solo act.
My solo-- It's blank!
So naive.
- No! N-N-No, no!
- You're second fiddle, Fife,
and that's all
you'll ever be.
Forte!
We can remain as we are...
forever and ever!
Forte!
Enough!
Heavens! Master.
You're not singing.
Careful.
Oh, no, the bell jar!
- Got it. Got it.
- Oh, careful.
Is this happy enough
for you, Master?
I know I'm downright giddy!
Master, the keyboard.
- You got it?
- Got it. Got it.
Whoa, whoo!
Ooh, help!
No!
Forte.
Oh, yes, it is lovely.
And you said it was impossible.
I said it was impossible
without me.
- Everyone, shh, shh, shh! Here they come.
- Wow!
The setting is perfect.
Oh, aren't they beautiful?
It's wonderful!
Hurray!
And what a wonderful
Christmas it was.
I suppose if anyone
saved Christmas, it was Belle.
Merry Christmas, one and all!
- Merry Christmas.
- And merry Christmas to you, sir.
- Merry Christmas, everyone.
I believe we have a little
something for you, Chip.
A present? Oh, boy! Thank you.
Open it!
Look, Mama! A storybook!
Would ya read it to me?
- I'd love to, son.
- Oh, boy!
Maestro?
- Yes, Master?
- Would you do us the honour, old friend?
I'd be delighted.
There is more
To this time of year
Than sleigh bells and holly
Mistletoe and snow
Those things
Will come and go
Don't look inside
A stocking
Don't look under the tree
The one thing
we're looking for
ls something we can't see
Far more precious than silver
And more splendid than gold
This is something to treasure
But it's something
we can't hold
Oh, as long as
There's Christmas
I truly believe
That hope is the greatest
Of the gifts we'll receive
We'll receive
As we all pray together
It's a time to rejoice
And though we
may look different
We'll all sing
with one voice
As long as there's Christmas
I truly believe
That hope is the greatest
Of the gifts we'll receive
As long as there's Christmas
We'll all be just fine
A star shines above us
Lighting your way
And mine
Light my way
You know I will
As long as there's Christmas
I truly believe
That hope is the greatest
Of the gifts we'll receive
As long as our guiding star
Shines above
There'll always be Christmas
So there always
will be a time
When the world
is filled with peace
And love