One time a year,
there's a marvelous night,
When enchantment and wonder
spark and take flight
Each home fills with joy
on this grand holiday,
With hearts growing warm
in a magical way
The rooms are all covered
with garment and wreaths
The mantel is ready with stockings beneath
Lights twinkle and glow
and bells brightly chime
The moment's arrived, it's here,
Christmas time
Three precious gifts
lie under this tree
What secrets they hold,
Let's look and we'll see
The first tells a story
for us all to hear
About laughter and family,
and those we hold dear
We love Christmas so much,
we want it to stay
But what if we wished
it was here every day?
Anchors aweigh
Full steam ahead
Swab the deck, you
All aboard Next stop, Funnyville
It's here
- The one
- The only
best day of the year
It's Christmas
Oh, boy Just what we always wanted
- Hey, look at this
- Cool
Merry Christmas, boys
You know we have to wait
for the family
Sorry, Uncle Donald
Ah, it's Christmas,
and I've got a special surprise
for you
But you didn't even
read the card
We'll read it later
- Merry Christmas, everybody
- Merry Christmas, indeed
Where are my boys and my kisses?
I could just eat you up
Oh, Donald?
Oh, boy
Aunt Daisy, catch ya later
Last one down the hill's
a rotten egg
Not me
Boys Dinner
The one thing better
than presents
is Christmas dinner
Isn't this lovely? All of us gathered
for a wonderful meal
It's my favorite part of Christmas
- Turkey
- Donald, would you like to carve?
Boys Where are your manners?
- This turkey is so good
- Your gravy never has lumps
We love your cooking,
Aunt Daisy
Donald,
they're just enjoying my dinner
I don't want any
All right, who's for carolling?
We don't wanna sing,
Uncle Scrooge
We wanna play with our toys
- Bedtime, boys
- Not yet
Christmas can't be over already
Good night, boys
What a great day
We should do it more often
Yeah Once a week should be enough
It'll be another 365 days
until we get more Christmas
Star light, star bright,
first star I see tonight,
I wish I may, I wish I might,
have the wish I wish tonight
We wish it was Christmas
every day
All aboard Next stop, Funnyville
Boy, those guys
sure like that choo-choo
They're gonna
play with it again today?
Let's play with our new toys
They're gone
Hey, what is this?
Didn't we open these yesterday?
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
There's only one way to find out
We're gonna have to open
these presents
Merry Christmas
- Uncle Donald, we did it
- It's Christmas again
It's Christmas again, Uncle Donald
Two days in a row
You boys must have been dreaming
We almost forgot
about our special surprise
Where are my kisses?
I could just eat you up
We should have seen that coming
Last one down the hill's
a rotten egg
Again
Boys, dinner
Isn't this lovely? All of us gathered
for a wonderful meal
This is my favorite part
of Christmas
Turkey
Boys Where are your manners?
Donald,
they're just enjoying my dinner
Good night, boys
- That was great
- Double great
All aboard Next stop, Funnyville
Merry Christmas, boys
Look out, Uncle Donald
- Merry Christmas, everybody
- Merry Christmas, indeed
Where are my boys and my kisses?
No, you don't
I think this is my favorite part
of Christmas
Merry Christmas, boys
- Merry Christmas
- I could eat you up
my favorite part of Christmas
All aboard Next stop, Funnyville
You can stop Christmas now
Please
Where are my kisses?
Funnyville
my favourite part
Who's for carolling?
Looks like the end of the line
Until tomorrow,
when it happens all over again
You're right Yesterday's today,
and today's tomorrow,
and it's gonna be the same thing
day in and day out
Get a grip
I'm sorry, fellas
That's OK. We know how you feel
If I see the same toys again,
I'll go out of my mind
Yeah, and if I eat any more turkey,
I'm gonna need new clothes
We got to do something
to liven things up
Green leader to red leader
Initiate pancake intercept sequence
Roger
Donald, stop playing
with the boys' presents
Where are my boys, and my kisses?
Right here, Aunt Gertie
Isn't this lovely? All of us gathered
for a wonderful meal
It's my favourite part of Christmas
Oh Turkey
Not the piano
Not my beloved carols
Well, we still have the tree
Let's run
before Uncle Donald gets mad
We'll be outside
if you need us
Donald, are you all right?
"To Huey, Dewey and Louie,
Christmas isn't about candy canes,
holly or lights all aglow,
it's about the hearts that we touch,
and the care that we show"
"Wishing you lots of love,
Donald and Daisy"'
Some Christmas
this turned out to be
Gee, I don't know about you guys,
but I don't ever
wanna do that again
Me, too
Me, three
Tomorrow, let's have
the best Christmas ever
We're putting
these sleds to good use
Incoming
Merry Christmas, fellas
Look, we made you breakfast
Isn't that nice?
You want to open presents?
No way We've got to
wait for the family to get here
- Merry Christmas, everybody
- Merry Christmas, indeed
Don't forget our kisses,
Aunt Gertie
What are they up to?
You boys are so wonderful
- That looks heavy
- Let us help you
Why, isn't that sweet?
Thank you, boys
Ham
Uncle Donald,
would you like to carve?
Something's up for sure
Nothing better than gathering
for a wonderful meal
It's our most favourite part
My feelings exactly
Carols, Uncle Scrooge?
Why, boys,
it's like you could read my mind
What's the big idea?
What are you boys up to?
Donald Duck, you're spoiling
a perfect Christmas
No, Uncle Donald is right
We are up to something
Merry Christmas
See, it's your dream boat
Thank you, boys
How beautiful
Some Christmas this has turned out
to be I'm just so happy
Boys?
Come gimme a push
It's over
Christmas is really over
The day after Christmas
I understand, boys
You must want Christmas every day
No
Anchors aweigh
Full steam ahead
Man overboard
So Christmas was meant
to last just one day
And maybe it's better that way
It's a time to be treasured,
it can't always be here,
But the feeling it gives us
can last the whole year
Now this gift holds a story
both wondrous and rare,
About a father and a son
and the love that they share
This Christmas they'll learn
before the night's through,
If we care for each other,
our dreams can come true
Come on, Maxie,
at least hum a few bars
Dad, hurry up
The mailman comes at noon, Dad
Let's see, now
- How about an electrical recliner?
- Yeah, Dad, whatever
Don't want to turn
into a fancy pants
Yeah, Dad, but Santa won't get
our letter if we don't leave
now
Hold on, Dad
We're taking a short cut
We ought to slow down
before we break the sound barrier
- What?
- We're headed straight for the mall
Great idea
- Low bridge
- Really? Where?
Go ahead and stop the mailman, Son
I'll be right behind ya
Don't worry, I won't let you down
Excuse me
Pardon me, ma'am
Didn't mean to get fresh
Wait
There's a madman
on the ornament
Sorry
Wait Stop
You have to mail our letter
to Santa
Get out of the road, kid
Do you have anything bigger?
I have an empty space right here
I'll take it
My dad'll be here
any minute, honest
Sorry, kid, gotta go
Special delivery
for the North Pole
You really think Santa
will get the letter in time?
Sure as I stand here
Slippery
I gotta get it, I just gotta
My own one-of-a-kind, carbon fibre,
torque rod, snappy flex,
tip-to-tail, rail-to-rail, wood core,
twin-directional snowboard
That's a mouthful
With adjustable
forward and high back
skid plate step-in bindings
Look at this! All nice and neat
and ready for ol' Santy
Merry Christmas Eve, Pete
Why, if it ain't
the goof master himself
Say, we got us
some more work to do, Max,
or Santy won't find our chimney
Ain't that quaint? The goof brain
thinks there's a Santy Claus
There isn't?
Like father, like goof
Kid's got the goof gene
in his bloodstream
There is too a Santa
Now, son, come here
See, it's an urbane myth,
like that Locked Ness Monstrosity,
and the fella with the sweets
takes cheques
Well, think of it
An old guy in a red suit
cruising the entire world
in one night,
using reindeer what fly!
Why, it's impossible.
Look, kid, I've been around, see
I've been to foreign lands,
like Brooklyn,
and I've never seen,
nor met a soul who's seen,
this Santy Claus fella
Look, Maxie, I found the front door
So long, neighbors.
Have a very merry Christmas
And a happy New Year
Hey, how about giving
your old man a hand?
What is it, Maxie?
Why, you look like Santy Claus
put a lump of coal in your stocking
I heard there isn't any Santa Claus
Who went and told you
a silly thing like that?
Mr. Pete
Well, that figures
Of course there's a Santy
Or we'd have out-of-work elves
You think?
Think? Heck, I'm sure
Son, have I ever been wrong?
A broken clock is right
two or three times a day,
and this time I'm right.
Believe me, Santa won't let you down
- You really think he'll come?
- Why, as sure as pigs fly
Hey, Dad,
what did you ask for from Santa?
You know, just the usual
What's that?
It's a surprise
Now, plug her in
and let the joy of Christmas shine
That'll put
the spirit of Christmas in you
Course there's a Santa
Believe me,
Santa won't let you down
An old guy in a red suit,
cruising the entire world in
one night, using reindeer what fly
Why, it's impossible
Hiya, Maxie Wanna help?
Did you know that there are
two billion children in the world?
No wonder
I keep tripping over roller skates
That means Santa would have to make
800 visits a second,
not including bathroom breaks
I guess old Santy's
been at it so long,
he figured out the short cuts
Looks like it's gonna be
a white Christmas
Dad, this is serious
I know, son, but
Gosh
Something sure smells mighty tasty
But how can a reindeer fly?
That's easy,
it's those antlers, they
You know, with the wind
and all, that creates lift
Hot
Still, it's a lot of work
for one guy
That's why we leave him cookies,
for a pick-me-up
But it just doesn't quite make sense, Dad
Chestnuts
Where are we going, Dad?
To share the joy of Christmas
with those less fortunate
Shouldn't Santa be doing this?
Santy's on a tight schedule
this time of year,
so we're helping him out
Looks like
I might need one, too
Wanna play toy carses? All I got's
two, but you can have one
Santa gave me this one last year
This year, I hope he's gonna
give me another one
Kid, I ain't so sure
there is such a thing as
Christmas Eve dinner is served
- Mr Goofy, that's incredible
- Like magic
Christmas magic
Thank you so much
With things being so tight,
without you, we wouldn't have
Don't mention it
You'd do the same for me
But have you ever really,
actually seen Santa?
He's got a big white beard
But have you ever
actually seen him in person?
Where?
- Merry Christmas
- Santa
Santa?
You made it
Who wants to be the first
to sit on Santy's lap?
Me, me Over here
I'm so glad you came
I almost didn't believe any more,
but now
Everything's OK So
I want my own one-of-a-kind,
carbon fibre, torque rod,
snappy flex,
tip-to-tail, rail-to-rail,
twin-directional snowboard
Please
Dad?
You tricked me How could you?
Santy's got a problem with one
of his elves, but he'll be back
Gosh, Maxie I'm real sorry
I was just trying
to make those kids happy
Remember my tradition of eating one
of Santy's cookies before bedtime?
What's the point?
Remember how we always open
one present on Christmas Eve?
Hiya, Maxie
Lookee here,
it's your old stuffed bear
- Remember what you named him?
- Old Stuffed Bear
- Remember who gave him to ya?
- Yeah Santa
But that's when I was little
No, he's not
Trust me, Max
You just gotta believe
- Santy's real
- No, he's not
- Yes, he is
I promise
Then prove it
When Santy shows up,
we'll be here to greet him
I'll snap a picture of him
so you'll have
photographic evidence
Yeah You'll fall off the roof first
I won't fall off the roof
You just watch
Santy Claus is coming to town
Bright
Told you you'd fall off the roof
I didn't fall off the roof
Where's Santy?
I didn't miss him, did l?
Nope
Then where is he?
I don't know about you,
but I'm cold and tired,
and Santa Claus is not coming
Why doesn't he just grow up
and face the facts?
"Don't forget
Max"'
Oh, Dad
Max, wake up. Look, son.
It's him, it really is
Do you see him, Maxie? Do ya?
Over here
- Almost forgot Smile, Santy
- Dad, the lens cap
I'll get it right this time
Come down with your hands up
We have you surrounded
What in the name of Pete is going on,
for Pete's sake?
Maybe he's running a little late
Dad
Are you OK?
You were right about everything
I even fell off the roof
Hey, Dad, it's OK
Santa didn't show. No biggie
Well, since he's not coming,
at least we can eat
all his cookies
Not hungry
Hey, Dad,
here's one from me. Open it up.
Maybe later
Max?
Burglars
Santy
Merry Christmas
Santy, I'm so happy you came
Gosh I thought you'd be taller
And you look trimmer
than your pictures
Well, you know
camera adds 50 pounds
You have to meet Maxie
Yeah, love to,
but gotta get going
Two billion kids, 823 a second
Very tight schedule
Wait, Santy,
he's around somewheres
Wait Santy
Santy
- Maxie?
- Hi, Dad
What are you doing
dressed up like Santy Claus?
I just wanted to make you happy,
like you did for our neighbors
Maxie, I might have let you down,
but you sure didn't let me down
Could it be? Do you think?
Gosh It sure looks like
Santa Claus
I believe it is
Wow, my own one-of-a-kind,
carbon fibre, torque rod,
snappy flexed, tip-to-tail,
rail-to-rail, wood core,
twin-directional snowboard
- Thanks, Santa
- What's all the commotion?
If it's another robber,
I'm gonna get him
Santa?
Well, hey, Santa,
I believed in ya all along
For real and for true
So, where are my presents?
Merry Christmas
But what about my squirty gun
and my yo-yo?
I know you can hear me
Santa didn't forget your gift,
did he?
Every year, I ask for the same gift,
and every year I get it
What's that?
Your happiness
What is it, son?
Got you the same thing
Merry Christmas, Dad
Merry Christmas, Max
Where are you going?
To share my present
with little Jimmy next door
That's my boy
So, Christmas is found
in the way we live,
Not what we receive,
but what we can give
Our Iast present may seem small,
Not fancy, flashy or special at all
But this gift can be given
by the rich or the poor,
It's a gift of the heart,
and it means so much more
Thanks, Joe Merry Christmas
Merry Christmas, George
You working?
Not tonight It's Christmas Eve
There it is, Pluto
The perfect gift
to go with Minnie's watch
My Minnie
They close at five
I'm a little short now,
but you and I are gonna make
lots of tips today
- Aren't we, fella?
- Yeah
After work we'll pick it up
Let's get this tree to Minnie's
Figaro, there's nothing but bills
How am I going to afford
to get Mickey a present?
Oh, Mickey
When you play your harmonica,
my heart sings
An instrument like that
deserves a special case
Yeah Some day
Come into the kitchen
Breakfast is almost ready
I'm not eating you
out of house and home?
Course not, silly I have plenty
For me?
Have you got the time, Minnie?
- Let's see, it's
- Gosh, sure is a beautiful watch
My one heirloom
It'd look nice with a gold chain
around your pretty neck
Oh, Mickey My goodness,
I've got to go to work
Madam Your sleigh awaits
Oh, how wonderful
Giddy up, Pluto
See you tonight
Fella, we got work to do
Welcome to Crazy Pete's tree lot
Hurry, folks, only one more day
till Christmas
Easy credit No money down
This stuff works pretty good
Merry Christmas
I'll be merry when
I've sold all those ten-footers
Why are you standing there with
your face hanging out? Get to work
OK, fella You know what to do
Shake a leg
Quit slacking
There's a customer waiting
Do be careful of the paint
- Yes, ma'am
- Such a nice young man
Here's a little something for you
I don't expect anything
I'm just glad to help
Oh, boy
Thank you, ma'am, thank you
Hot dog We'll be able
to get Minnie that watch chain
- We'd like to buy a tree
- You folks are looking for a tree?
Boy, oh, boy,
is this your lucky day
This here's what you folks need Ten
feet of towering Nova Scotia pine
Wow It's bigger than our house
Well, it's a little more
than we need
Missus, I've got to be honest
with you,
this is all
I've got left on the lot
The others have been reservated
You don't want these kids going
without a tree now, do you?
We are gonna get a tree,
aren't we, Daddy?
This is all we have
Well, that'll be just fine
for a down payment
I'll set you up with a nice
installment plan. Just sign here.
We're gonna get a tree
Foot off the brake,
the kids are waiting
Hey, how about this tree?
I found it out back
It hasn't been reservated
It's beautiful
- Perfect
- We'll take it
Merry Christmas
Thank you again
Merry Christmas. So long!
Merry
Christmas
I had them on the hook
for a ten-foot tree
I'm taking what I would have made
from you
- But I...
- Now, get out of my lot
Chumps
Somebody's burning their ham
More than warm. It's hot!
Not my ten-footers
Attention, holiday shoppers. Don't forget
to bring your last-minute purchases
to our gift-wrapping department
I've never seen it so busy
Who made you
Santa's number one helper?
I want to get Mickey
something special this year
Without that Christmas bonus,
I'm sunk
Hello. Okey-dokey. Bye.
Mr Mortimer wants to see you
in his office right away
My Christmas bonus
- Ginny
- That's Minnie
Right, I've been making a list
and checking it twice,
and I found that you have been
Santa's best little helper
this season
Your hard work
is about to be rewarded
Close your eyes
and hold out your hands
Mr Mortimer,
I can't thank you enough
Yes, I know Don't interrupt
- Penny
- That's Minnie
Whatever On behalf of the store,
it gives me great pleasure
to present you
with your Christmas bonus
A fruitcake?
No need to thank me The expression
on your face is thanks enough
Scoot along to the gift-wrapping
department where you belong
And, er, Winnie?
Merry Christmas
Oh, Mickey How am I ever
gonna get your present now?
There must be a way to get Minnie's
present by five o'clock
You got any ideas, fella?
Don't worry We'll come up
with something, we just gotta
Do you think the band
will ever show up?
I don't know They're putting out
a fire at Crazy Pete's
It went up like a Roman candle
Chief, looks like the toy drive
is a big fat bust
Listen That music
Come on
Where are we going, fellas?
A concert in the park
Look, Bub, we're desperate
We need music for the toy drive
You're our only hope
I don't have time, Chief!
I gotta get a gift for my girl
Look, pal, don't do it for us,
do it for the kids
- But l
- Son, to these kids,
the only difference between
a broken heart and a smile is you
You're on Break a leg, pal
Look, I'm really sorry,
but I can't stay
I got Christmas shopping to do and
Gosh
- The band
- Must have been hot at Crazy Pete's
Guess I'll be showing up
at Minnie's empty-handed
Terrific Thanks to you,
this was our best toy drive ever
You and that harmonica
make a great team
She's worth her weight in gold
Holy cow That's it
We've got two minutes to get
to the shop. Come on, Pluto.
- Thanks, fellas
- Goodbye
- Thanks
- Merry Christmas
Sorry
Hey, what's going on?
This is our stop
Look, there's the shop
Excuse me, sir I was just hoping to
trade this for a gift for my girl
Sorry, that harmonica
isn't worth much
Well, merry Christmas
You're worth a lot to me,
old friend
Say, maybe that harmonica
is worth something after all
Come on in
Can't wait to open your present?
I know how you feel
I love Christmas so much
Say, Mickey,
why don't you play some music?
Isn't it time
we were opening our presents,
and speaking of time,
what time is it?
Well, I think it's time
for you to open your gift.
A case, for my harmonica
A chain for my watch
Mickey, it's beautiful,
but I traded my watch
to get you that case
I traded my harmonica
to get you a watch chain
Oh, Mickey,
I can't believe you gave up what
means the most to you, for me
Minnie, you're all the music
I'll ever need
- Merry Christmas, Mickey
- Merry Christmas, Minnie
Want some fruitcake?
A gift from the heart
is cherished and true
A present is best
when love's given, too
So in the end, love is the reason
that Christmas is more
than a gift-giving season
It's a time with our loved ones
to show that we care,
When families and neighbors
come together to share
So, this Christmas season,
let us all do our parts
to keep Christmas spirit
alive in our hearts.