Hayes:
But you weren't actually there
when your daughter died,
were you?
No.
You said yourself,
Frank has a temper.
(Sighs) Everyone gets
frustrated sometimes.
Not everybody punches walls.
Tell me again,
why did your husband
punch the wall?
He was tired.
It was work...
He was tired like the night
that your daughter died?
I didn't say that.
And he was alone
with your baby.
She was crying,
she wouldn't stop.
Now, isn't it possible that,
in his frustration,
Frank picked up
your baby girl...
(Whimpers)
That he picked up Taylor
and he shook her?
(Sobs)
Now, isn't that possible
Mrs. McCormick?
(Quietly) Yes.
Yes, what?
(Heavy sigh)
Yes, it's possible.
Darren: Listen to me.
Frank: Son of a bitch!
Frank!
He twisted everything she said!
It was a mistake
to put Kerry on the stand.
She's my wife!
It hurt the case!
Look, you need to start
preparing yourself.
I am not going to jail!
You need to get
your head together,
show some remorse.
Frank: I'm not gonna let you
do it, you son of a bitch!
Guard:
Let's go.
Kerry! Kerry!
Guard: C'mon on, sir.
Come on.
Kerry!
(Frustrated grunt)
It gets easier,
being separated from your girl.
Yeah.
Conjugals, right?
Voss, no talking.
How long you goin' away for?
Guard:
Voss, what'd I tell ya?
Hey, my buddy here's upset.
(Wheel blows out)
(Hard impact)
(Tires skid on pavement)
Guard 2:
Anyone hurt?
Guard:
What happened?
Open up!
(Pained grunt)
You made it.
Have I ever let you down before?
Whoo!
You comin'?
Ed: Really?
I bought ice cream last night.
Sophie, I'm not giving you
a hard time.
Look, you are pregnant,
you are beautiful,
and you should eat
whatever you want.
Send Clark out
to get some more.
I gotta go.
I gotta go, I gotta go.
Parker:
You talking to Sophie again?
How many times
has she called today?
I lost count.
Wordy: Which stage is she at
The "get me this" stage,
or the "do you still love me"
stage?
Parker: Or the "I'm fat and
it's your fault" stage?
Wordy:
It's worth it,
once you hold 'em in your arms
for the first time.
Winnie: (Over P.A.)
Team One, hot call!
Armed prisoners escaped
from a transport van.
Ed: Where?
Winnie: Leslie and Eastern.
Ed: How many on board?
Winnie: Two prisoners.
They escaped with an unknown
accomplice.
Issue a citywide alert
and get me a manifest
for that van.
We need to know
who we're dealing with.
Winnie: Getting that
for you right now.
Winnie: (Over radio) The escaped prisoners
are Frank McCormick and Carl Voss.
McCormick.
Isn't he the airline pilot?
The guy accused
of killing his baby.
Winnie: He was headed
back to city jail.
His verdict
isn't until tomorrow.
What about Voss?
Winnie: Voss.
Voss committed armed robbery,
assault with a deadly weapon...
He was being transferred
back to Kingston Pen.
Maximum security.
Thanks, Winnie.
Tires are shredded.
Might have something
to do with this.
Spike strip.
This was planned.
Do Voss and McCormick
know each other?
Guard:
It sure seemed like it.
They were talking.
Thanks.
You think Voss and McCormick
are in on this together?
Well, they're both lookin'
at serious time.
Hey, Spike, you got anything
on the van's camera?
Screening the footage now.
Okay, here we go.
The three men left the van
heading in the same direction.
You get an image
of the accomplice?
Spike:
Just the back of his head.
Wait a second.
I got a late-model sedan
leaving the scene,
heading south.
Spike, are all three men
in the car?
Tinted windows.
Hard to tell.
I do have a plate number
though.
Registered to?
Spike: Rick Marinelli.
Career criminal.
Did some time with Voss.
B&E's,
two armed robberies...
Okay, any connection
to McCormick?
Nothing I can see.
McCormick's record's clean.
This is Voss' breakout.
Parker: He had his buddy
Rick help him out.
Yeah, and took their new buddy
Frank with them.
Winnie, alert the airports,
train and bus station.
Emphasis on airports,
both private and commercial.
Our guy's a pilot here.
And let's get an APB out
on Rick Marinelli's car.
Copy that.
Ed: Spike, look into
Voss and Marinelli.
If this thing is planned,
somebody knows
where they're headed.
You got it.
Ed: Let's get these guys.
Parker: Okay.
Ed: We're gonna start
at the courthouse.
(Sirens wailing)
Hey, Winnie, can you patch me
into McCormick's lawyer?
Comin' right up, Jules.
Parker: McCormick wasn't
expecting to be free today.
He's thinkin' on his feet.
He could have jacked a car.
Winnie's checking
for any vehicles
reported stolen this morning.
Jules,
any luck on Frank's lawyer?
She's on the phone
with him now.
Winnie, patch me into Jules
and the lawyer.
You got it.
Jules: Any idea where
he might've gone?
My guess? As far away from here
as possible.
He did not want
to go back to jail.
How did Frank's daughter die?
Darren:
She was six-months-old.
Frank thought it was sids.
He went to check on Taylor,
found her dead in the crib.
But the coroner ruled it
a homicide.
Shaken baby syndrome.
Would you say Frank
has a temper?
Look, the guy is angry,
all right?
He feels like
he was railroaded.
This prosecutor,
Adrian Hayes, he's a pitbull.
He's got a perfect
conviction rate.
Do you think Frank's angry
enough to want to hurt him?
After this morning,
I wouldn't be surprised.
What happened this morning?
Darren: I put Frank's
wife on the stand.
I thought if the jury
could see her
standing by her husband,
it would help our case.
But Mr. Hayes ripped her apart.
Frank must've been upset.
Bailiff had to restrain him.
Spike:
Boss, I've got a lead.
Yeah, Spike?
Found a boat registered
to Rick Marinelli's brother.
He keeps it docked
at Ashbridge's Bay.
Good way to get outta town.
Dump the car,
head for international waters.
Ed: (On headset)
Change of plans.
Team one,
head south to the lakeshore.
Ashbridge's Bay Marina.
Sam:
Taking Leslie Street.
Wordy:
Following you, Sam.
Ed: Stay alert.
Eyes sharp.
Sam: We're coming
in from the south.
(Sirens wailing)
Sam:
Got a sighting on the vehicle!
Where?
Cherry Street, southbound.
All right, we're coming north.
(Sirens wailing)
Sam:
Ed, he's heading right to you.
Ed:
I'll try to head him off.
(Brakes squealing)
Wordy: Heading for the lake.
They've got nowhere to go.
(Tires squealing)
(Sirens blaring)
Ed: (lnto bullhorn) This is the
Police Strategic Response Unit.
Turn off the engine
and step out of the car now!
(Engine revving)
Ed: Turn off the engine, and
step out of the car, now!
Let's do it.
Step out of the car, now!
Jules: Out of the car!
Sam: Turn the engine off!
Ed:
Out of the vehicle now!
Wordy:
Hands where we can see 'em!
Jules: Open the door!
Ed: Get out of that car now!
Sam: Here he comes, Jules.
Jules: Open the door, now!
Parker:
Open the door, slowly.
Ed: Out of the car now!
Get out! Get out of the car!
Hands were I can see 'em!
Parker:
Do it now!
Ed: (lnto headset) We got Voss
and Marenelli in custody.
Wordy:
McCormick's not in the car.
Where is he?
How the hell should I know?
He didn't go with you?
No, but I'd give you a ride.
These cuffs tight enough
for ya?
All right, you let McCormick
out of the van,
then what?
He took the guard's gun
and he ran off.
All units be advised
Frank McCormick is not yet
in custody.
He's assumed armed
and considered dangerous.
♪ Flashpoint 3x17 ♪
Collateral Damage
Original Air Date on January 4, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
(Telephone ringing)
Frank?
What're you doing here?
Why do you have a gun?
You're packing up
all my stuff already?
It's not yours.
You're getting rid
of her clothes?
I can't keep it here.
I can't...
I can't look at it
every single day.
It's been six months,
Frank.
We should be going through
all this stuff together.
We shouldn't be
doing it at all.
Sorry.
You think I did it.
(Dialling 9-1-1)
Ed: I got Sam and Jules
on the main floor,
Wordy and Spike
sweeping the second.
If Frank's here,
we're gonna find him.
That's good.
Ed:
There's the prosecutor.
(Calling out)
Mr. Hayes.
Hayes:
What's going on?
Parker: Frank McCormick
escaped earlier today.
Yeah, they told me.
Sir, we need to put you
in protective custody.
Okay, fine.
I get it.
Thank you, sir.
I understand McCormick
threatened you
in court today.
He wasn't happy with
how things turned out.
His lawyer claims
he's innocent.
Innocent men don't run.
I got the top coroner
in this country telling me
that this guy shook his baby.
Even McCormick's own wife
thinks he did it.
McCormick's lawyer said
she testified on his behalf.
Yeah, didn't turn out that way.
Kerry:
He was tired.
Did your husband
want this child?
Of course he did.
Was he happy when you told him
that you were pregnant?
Was he happy?!
Mrs. McCormick,
tell me again,
why did your husband
punch the wall?
He was tired.
It was work...
he was tired like the night
that your daughter died?
(Muffled cry)
The seed of doubt
was already there.
I just exposed it.
Sam:
He's not in the building.
Thank you,
Mr. Hayes.
Ed: Mr. Hayes, we're gonna
get you to go
with these two officers here.
All right.
What's going on?
McCormick's wife turned on him
in court today.
Ed: Okay, Team One, let's move.
Frank's wife may be in danger.
(Sirens wailing)
Kerry: (Answering machine)
Hi, you've reached the McCormick's.
Leave us a message
after the beep.
(Disconnects call)
Winnie, I can't get through
on the McCormick's home line.
It keeps going to voicemail.
I know.
We got a 911 in progress.
Parker:
Patch it through.
Coming right up.
This is Sergeant Greg Parker
with the Police Strategic
Response Unit.
Mrs. McCormick?
She's not responding.
(Sirens wailing)
Ed: You got it?
Parker: Yup.
Ed:
Bravo team, in three...
Two... one.
(Ram smashes door)
Ed: Police! Police!
Jules: Police!
Sam: SRU!
Police!
Clear.
Clear!
Eddie.
Yeah. Yeah.
Garage is empty.
He took her.
(Tires squealing)
Frank:
Just keep going straight.
Frank, the police are looking
for you.
You should turn yourself in.
They stack us three to a cell,
three feet wide.
I get the floor.
My head's next to a toilet,
but that's not why
I don't sleep at night.
You know what they do
to people
that are accused
of killing kids?
The thing that kept me going
all this time...
Was knowing that you
still believed in me;
That no matter
what anybody else said,
you believed in me.
You knew the truth.
What I said in court...
Frank: Wh-what you said in
court, you can't take back!
(Takes steadying breath)
Sam: Winnie, we need
to put out an APB
on Kerry McCormick's car.
Winnie: Copy.
Jules: If he was gonna hurt her,
he'd have done it here.
Unless he caught her
dialing 911.
Spike, you pick anything
off that 911?
Spike:
Working on it.
(Cell phone ringing)
Everything okay?
Soph, you need to rest.
You shouldn't be on your feet
so much. Look...
Sophie, I gotta go.
I'll call you later.
Okay, bye.
Kerry didn't talk
to the operator,
but she left the phone on
the whole time.
I've boosted the gain,
so we got something.
Jules: Can you turn it up?
Spike: Yep.
Kerry:
What was I supposed to think?
Frank:
I told you I didn't do it!
Kerry: What about what
the doctor said?
Frank:
You believed her?
Kerry:
She's an expert!
Frank:
Where are your car keys?
Kerry:
Here. Just take them. Go.
Frank:
You're coming with me.
Kerry:
No, Frank.
Kerry: Let go!
Frank: Come on!
Jules: Frank's lawyer said
that there were two doctors
involved in the case.
There was the uh...
The ER doctor who pronounced
the baby dead
and the coroner
who performed the autopsy.
And both lawyers mentioned
the coroner's testimony.
The wife called her an expert.
Jules: The top forensic
pathologist in the country.
Parker: Yeah, and her testimony
helped turn his own wife against him.
Maybe Frank's looking
for payback.
What's the name
of that coroner?
Dr. Roberta Fenton.
Her office is
at the city morgue.
All right, let's get moving.
Winnie, patch me through
to security
at the coroner's office.
(Phone ringing)
Security.
Ed:
This is Ed Lane
with the Police
Strategic Response Unit,
is Dr. Fenton
in the building?
Yes.
Okay, we have reason to believe
that an escaped prisoner
named Frank McCormick
may be looking for her.
I see.
Ed: Subject's a
white male, 30s,
maybe accompanied by
a white female of the same age.
Any sign of them?
Have you seen them?
Security guard: Actually,
I think I see them now.
Ed: Okay, stay calm.
If you can stall him, do so.
But the priority here
is to cooperate.
He's armed
and emotionally unstable.
We're on our way.
Thank you very much.
Can I help you?
(Police sirens wailing)
Wait a second,
what's down here?
Security guard: Oh, nothing.
It's uh... It's just labs.
You know, uh, maybe we should
check out the third floor.
It says autopsy.
Sir, we uh...
We don't even use...
Autopsy. Now!
That's her.
That's Dr. Fenton.
Open it.
Open it!
(Keys jangle)
(Indistinct chatter)
Dr. Fenton:
Frank McCormick?
Frank:
Back away from the table.
Dr. Fenton:
Oh my God.
Just do what he says, please.
Dr. Valo: What's going on here?
Dr. Fenton: Just stay calm.
Dr. Valo:
Sir, could you please-
Dr. Fenton:
Try to stay calm.
My wife thinks
that I killed my daughter...
And you're gonna show her
that she's wrong.
Mr. McCormick,
I know you're upset...
don't patronize me.
Sorry.
I want you to go and find
my daughter's autopsy report,
I would you to take
a very good, close look at it,
and I want you to find
the mistake that you made.
(Shouting) Do it!
Frank, please.
You don't need to do this.
This isn't-
(Scoffs)
Frank: Let me see it.
Bring it over here.
It contains autopsy photos
of your daughter
that I didn't show in court.
It could be very upsetting
for you,
and for your wife.
(Sighs heavily)
How many people we got in here?
More then a hundred.
We got offices
on the upper level,
and the autopsy suites
in the basement.
Wordy:
We need a full evac.
It's underway.
I'm bringing in more uniforms
to lock down the perimeter.
This is the guard.
Hey, we talked on the phone.
Where's Mr. McCormick now?
Autopsy one,
with the woman he came with
and another coroner.
Ed:
Sam, Wordy, with me.
Parker:
Spike, set command post up here.
We'll need blueprints
of the building.
On it.
Parker: And a way to communicate with Mr.
McCormick.
The building's equipped
with an intercom system.
I can hook it
into the headsets.
Okay, it'll have to do.
Let's hurry up, guys,
McCormick's hanging
by a thread.
He's just lost his child,
his wife,
and now, he's about to lose
his freedom.
(Door squeaks open)
Boss, we got a visual.
Got a cam on the window.
Parker:
Entry options?
Wordy:
Door's stainless steel.
Too heavy for a ram...
We can't risk a charge,
not with the chemicals
in there.
There's an extensive
air vent system.
One in every room.
You wouldn't know it
from the smell.
Breathe through your mouth.
I'm uploading blueprints
to your PDAs.
Okay, there's a duct above
the autopsy suite.
Best entry's through the roof.
You're gonna have to rappel.
Ed: Okay, Sam, this
can go both ways.
Bring a strobe and CS gas.
I'm on it.
I'll spot him?
Let's do it.
The C.T. scan
of your daughter's brain
indicated severe swelling.
See this area here?
There's a pooling of blood
at the base of her skull.
You must've mixed up the scans.
This is-
this is someone else's.
It's got her name on it.
Dr. Fenton: As I said in
court, those symptoms,
along with retinal hemorrhages
comprise something called
shaken baby syndrome triad.
No.
I'm sorry.
I'm very familiar
with the syndrome.
I did not shake my baby!
I wish I had
another explanation.
(Heavy sigh)
Parker:
Frank McCormick,
Greg Parker,
Strategic Response Unit.
I need to make sure
everyone in there is okay.
Talk to him.
He can hear you.
I don't need a SWAT team,
i just need some answers.
Parker: Okay. Okay, Frank.
I understand that.
But in the eyes
of the law right now,
you're still an innocent man.
You still stand a chance
at trial.
Nobody believes me.
They only believe the expert.
Sir, is it possible
to get copies
of the McCormick files?
Yeah, they're in the archives.
Okay, great.
Can I see them?
And everything you have
on Dr. Fenton!
'Kay, Spike, we're on the roof.
Which vent is it?
You want the main intake vent,
south side.
Copy.
Sam, in position?
We see it.
(Drill whirs)
All right.
(Sighs heavily)
I know it's hard
to lose a child.
Frank: It's even harder
having everybody thinking
that you killed her,
including your wife.
Parker: Hard time for
both of you, Frank.
You've both been through...
A lot.
Line secure?
I got ya.
(Rope straining)
Parker: I mean, how long
have you been together?
Five years.
Parker:
Five years?
Five years you get
to know someone.
First night we met,
she looked me right in the eye,
like she already knew me.
And then today on the stand,
she says she doesn't know
anymore.
You think I wanted
to believe that?
Parker: Kerry, I think Frank just
wants a chance to be heard here.
You made them think
I didn't even want her!
You didn't!
Like I didn't want
to get married?
Not at the beginning.
You didn't tell them
the next part.
The part after I held her
in my arms for the first time
and saw her little chin,
and her...
Eyes that looked
just like yours.
I loved her.
I know.
Sam:
Almost there.
Hey, Frank,
I can tell that you love
your daughter.
I'd like to hear your side.
Can you tell me what happened
the night your she died?
(Sighs heavily) I-I was looking
after Taylor because uh...
Kerry was with her mom
at the hospital.
(Taylor crying)
I'd just come off
a fourteen hour flight.
I didn't realize
how exhausted I was.
Taylor was...
She had a cold.
She wouldn't stop crying.
I tried bouncing her
because she always loved that,
but it didn't work.
(Taylor crying)
Nothing worked.
(Crying)
So I tried to put her
in her crib.
Uh, let her cry it out.
You know, that's what
you're supposed to do, right?
You, you let 'em cry.
But she wouldn't stop.
I was a wreck -
from the crying,
from the flight...
and uh...
I-I had a glass of wine.
I dozed off for, maybe,
half an hour.
And when I woke up,
it was quiet.
As soon as I went in
to check on her,
i knew that there was
something wrong.
I mean...
(Exhales sharply)
She wasn't breathing.
I called 911, I tried CPR.
Her little lips were... cold.
(Exhales sharply)
She was gone.
My little girl was gone.
(Sucks air in through his teeth,
huffs out)
She just stopped breathing.
It had to have been SIDS.
Dr. Valo: SIDS doesn't cause
the brain to swell and bleed.
Well something does, right?!
Something does!
And it wasn't me!
Spike, we've got a problem.
What's that?
Sam: The vent to the
autopsy room is blocked.
He'll hear me
if I try to cut through it.
That wasn't in
the original blueprints.
Where else can we gain access?
Spike:
There. Histology.
Ed:
What is that?
It's where they store and test
blood and tissue samples
for ongoing cases.
Which way, Spike?
Spike: Sam, make your way
50 feet along the duct
to the next shaft.
Copy that.
He's questioning the evidence
in his daughter's case.
We tell him to go to histology
so that Fenton can retest
the samples...
And make Frank feel like
we're on his side.
And what happens
when the tests are done?
Parker: He's not gonna find
what he's looking for.
He's gonna be a danger
to everybody in there,
he's gonna be a danger
to himself.
Okay, boss,
let me do a face-to-face here.
I can connect with him,
I can keep him grounded.
All right, Eddie.
Okay, I'm gonna go in unarmed.
Parker:
No, I don't think so.
Ed:
Greg, you know how it works.
I'm not gonna earn his trust
walking in there with an MP5.
I can cover him, boss,
and Ed can give you eyes in.
Okay.
Sam, you don't take
your eyes off of him.
Sam:
Copy that.
Which way, Spike?
Spike:
Turn to your right.
Copy that.
Yeah, how do I know
you're not gonna just shoot me
the second I walk out the door?
Parker: We wanna resolve
this peacefully, Frank.
Okay.
Thank you, Frank.
Dr. Fenton can handle
the retesting.
So why don't you let Kerry
and Dr. Valo go?
No, I'm gonna make everybody
stay with me.
I want him to check the results
'cause I'd like
a second opinion.
They're coming out.
'Kay, I'm in position.
Frank:
Stay back!
Jules:
This is just procedure, Frank.
It's right there.
Frank:
Get in, get in. Go.
(Slams door)
Frank, I am unarmed.
What are you doing here?!
My name's Ed Lane.
I just want to talk.
I don't like Ed being in there
unarmed.
I can't see him,
my view's limited
against the wall.
Parker: Spike, we have to
get Jules in position.
Jules, I can get you an angle,
give you more access
to the room.
Show me.
Spike:
Here's Sam in the air vent,
and you'll get a view
to histology
through this window.
Got it?
Got it.
All right, Sam,
Jules' on her way.
Copy that.
Seconds away.
Okay, calm down.
Just calm down.
I want you outta here now.
Frank, take it easy.
Frank:
Get out now!
This is not what we discussed.
Jules: I can see him, Sam.
We're covered.
Frank, I'm a father,
just like you are.
Okay?
Just like you are.
Now, believe me,
if I were you,
I would want answers too.
Now, doc,
where are those samples?
(Stammering) Uh, the freezer.
Let's test them, please.
Spike: Ed, camera's
in a good position.
Ed: That's it. That's it.
Thanks, doc.
Eddie, make sure he sees
the slides are Taylor's.
I don't want him thinking
we're pulling a fast one.
Sam: This is a problem.
I'm 20 percent blind here.
Jules:
I got him, Sam.
All right,
let's hold one second.
Let's make sure that those
are the right samples.
Okay, Frank?
Fenton:
Taylor McCormick.
(Sighs) That's my little girl.
That's all that's left
of her.
Ed: Frank, they're doing
what you want here.
Do you think you can go ahead
and put that gun down?
Not until these tests are done!
Ed:
Okay.
Well, let's let 'em
do their thing, okay?
Let's let 'em do their thing.
Doc, go ahead.
Fenton:
Try this.
Spike: This doctor's not used
to needing second opinions.
She's a gold standard
in forensic pathology.
Frank's theory that
she might be wrong...
Parker:
Wishful thinking, I know.
Eddie, find common ground;
I'm worried what happens
when they finish those tests.
I bet she was a good mom.
Frank:
Yeah.
She was beautiful.
Patient.
(Sighs) She fed her
and she changed her...
Got up in the middle
of the night.
She always cried
when you gave her to me.
You were away.
She didn't know your smell,
so she wanted me.
Ed:
Those first few months,
it's all about mom.
Kerry:
You got it, though.
In your own way.
He sang to her.
Frank:
She liked classic rock.
Stones, Eagles...
Good taste.
I always thought I'd take her
to her first concert and...
(Takes deep breath)
Teach her how to play guitar.
I didn't even get to go
to her funeral.
Ed:
You know, Frank,
whatever those test results say,
they're not gonna bring
Taylor back.
Wanna have a look?
Okay.
(Takes calming breath)
Dr. Valo:
Okay.
This is an image
of Taylor's brain cells.
There's evidence of edema,
hemorrhage.
Consistent with injuries
sustained
during a violent trauma.
There was no violent trauma!
We could retest the samples
a thousand times,
the results won't change.
Science doesn't lie.
Frank: B-but I do, that's
what you're saying?
Ed:
All right, look,
is there anything else,
anything at all,
that would've caused
these symptoms?
Yes.
Uh, a vitamin C deficiency,
Barlow's disease...
But those all came back
negative.
Run the tests again.
Dr. Fenton:
There's no need.
Frank: Nobody's leaving
until you test it again!
Get back!
Ed: Frank! Frank!
Put the gun down now!
Put it down!
I did not kill my child.
Ed:
Let's slow it down here.
(Shouting) I was there!
Sam? Jules?
He's out of range.
I'm out of range.
Adjusting position.
Ungh!
(Thud echoes through ducts)
Frank:
What was that?
(Alarm blares)
Jules: No solution.
I've got no view.
Parker:
What just happened?
He hit lockdown.
It activates
the ventilation system.
Sam, get outta there now!
Frank, take it easy.
Frank: You had a guy up
there this whole time,
pointing a gun at me?
Jules: Ed's not covered,
guys, come on.
Frank:
You lied to me?
(Struggling grunts)
Sam, status?
He's still on the line.
(Grunting)
I'm okay.
But I don't have a view.
Spike, can you try to override
the ventilation system?
Spike: There's do or do
not; There is no try.
Can you kill the alarm?
Security guard:
Yes! Yes, sir. One sec.
Frank:
What are they doing up there?
You said you were
just here to talk!
Ed:
Take it easy, Frank.
He's here to keep me safe,
he is not here to hurt you.
You had a guy in the ceiling
this whole time?!
Frank, just stop.
Stop fighting.
Dr. Fenton:
Listen to your wife.
Don't you talk to me.
Keep testing.
Dr. Fenton:
The facts don't lie.
Frank: I know what
happened that night!
I could never have hurt Taylor.
You loved her so much,
you couldn't live
with the memory
of what you did.
N-no.
No, no, I couldn't.
I couldn't have.
Parker:
Eddie, this is delicate here.
He needs to know
he's not alone.
Spike. I know, boss.
I know.
Kerry, Frank said that
when he met you,
that you could see
right into him;
That you knew him.
Can you tell him
what you think
may have happened that night?
You were exhausted.
You got home,
you just needed to...
Lie down,
close your eyes, rest.
But she was crying and crying
and your nerves were raw.
You had a, a drink.
You tried everything
to make her stop crying.
So you bounced her
'cause that worked
most of the time,
and she loved that,
and maybe you bounced her harder
than you realized.
No. No, it was...
It was the normal bounce;
The way I always did it.
(Cell phone vibrating)
Kerry:
Dr. Fenton, is it possible
that that could've
caused those...
Those injuries that you saw?
Yes, it's...
It's possible,
Kerry:
Then if that's what it was,
then maybe
it was just an accident.
And accidents just...
It happened,
and now...
And now it's over.
(Choked sob) Oh, God.
Kerry:
It's finished.
(Sobbing) No, no, no, no, no...
Ed:
Frank,
Frank, maybe it's time
to get some closure on this.
You, you and Kerry both.
Maybe it's time to try
to say goodbye to Taylor.
Frank?
(Tearful) I'm sorry.
Ed: Frank, listen to me.
Frank...
Spike, where's that override?
I know, I know!
Frank, give me the gun.
Frank?
(Sobbing) Look away.
I've got a distraction.
Don't do this!
Kerry: Frank!
Ed: Don't do it to your wife.
Spike...
I'm in.
Overriding lockdown now!
Frank:
Look away.
Ed: Put the gun down!
Kerry: No!
Sam, now!
♪
Subject in custody.
I got you, buddy.
(Sobbing) I can't go on.
You should've let me...
Ed: I got ya.
Frank: I can't go on.
It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
(Gasping for breath)
Frank: (Sobbing)
Ed: Just take one breath,
then you take another.
That's it.
You're going to be okay.
(Breathing deeply)
Kerry:
Hey.
(Dialling phone)
I gotta go.
What's up?
Sophie.
Go.
(Sharp exhale)
(Panting)
Are you okay?
You okay?
How you doing?
There was so much blood.
I was scared.
You did good.
You were the man
of the house today.
I'm so proud of you.
Jules:
3:31 pm, officer Lane:
"Maybe it's time
to find some closure.
You and Kerry together."
(Cell phone vibrating)
Carry on, Jules.
(Into phone)
Hello?
Jules: What would you
rather live with...
believing you're innocent
or knowing you're guilty?
Nah, you don't forget
you killed your kid.
Oh, I think he did.
I think that he blocked it out.
Sam:
He was as good as convicted.
He had a ticket to freedom,
but instead of running
he turned around and went home.
Spike: 'Cause it wouldn't
have been freedom,
leaving behind a wife
who thinks you're a killer.
(Disconnects call)
Parker:
Dr. Valo on the phone.
Reporter: Although the baby
had all the classic symptoms
of shaken baby syndrome,
the coroner neglected
to administer a test
called a "gram stain,"
which would have led
to a different diagnosis:
Bacterial meningitis.
The baby had a cold
that caused an ear infection.
Dr. Fenton overlooked it,
but Dr. Valo didn't.
Taylor wasn't shaken.
Reporter: Dr. Fenton, why
didn't you run the extra test?
There was no need.
The evidence was conclusive.
Reporter: How do you feel
about the suggestion
that your other cases
may be reopened?
The sample was contaminated.
There's no other explanation.
(Turns off TV)
So Frank was innocent
all along.
Tell me we haven't had days
when we wanna cut to the chase.
Frank and Kerry get
a second chance today.
♪ What is this road? ♪
♪ what is this journey? ♪
♪ and where does time go
so slowly? ♪
♪ love may be the end of us ♪
♪ but why,
why should we fear? ♪
♪ because with all
the wondering ♪
♪ I'm weightless here... ♪
Sophie:
Hey.
You didn't answer your phone.
I'm sorry.
Soph, I am so sorry.
You okay?
Doctor said there's something
wrong with the placenta.
It's partially separated,
so they put me on bed rest.
I know.
I know, he told me.
He said the baby's
gonna be fine now.
Yeah, she'll be okay.
A she?
Did you know that?
Yeah.
(Laughing)
You guys don't tell me
anything.
No.
(Laughing)
♪ But why, why should we fear ♪
(Whispered) Okay.
♪ Because with all
the wondering ♪
♪ I'm weightless ♪
♪ in my dreams ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==