Okay, team,
officer's wife is targeted.
Let's find her
and keep her safe.
Honey,
we gotta go!
What?! What's wrong?
I'll explain later.
Come on.
Just be quick!
We'll meet out here.
Okay.
Leah, you're with me!
Spike, Sam, north side!
No!
Okay, Dean,
this assignment
is threat level one.
Means it's the lowest level.
Trust me,
it took weeks to convince my dad
to let me come on a ride-along.
When he finally said yes,
I knew it'd be something
like this.
Okay, Winnie,
Data Logger 8033
just passing Waypoint 3.
Copied and logged,
Team One.
Two minutes ahead of schedule.
Hmm.
How's the package?
Oh, he's lively as ever.
Check if he's breathing.
So you report in along the way?
Well, Winnie charts
our progress,
and then if we were
to miss a call,
she would know
where to send backup.
Like if we're ambushed?
Yeah.
Cool.
You know we're not gonna be
ambushed though, right, Dean?
Yeah, I know.
Dad told me that escort calls
are pretty quiet.
What did you say
to convince him anyway?
I told him how much Clark
wanted to come;
how he really wanted
to ride with him.
You got any questions, Clark?
I'm good.
You sure?
Just feel free to ask.
Clark
nah, it's cool.
I'm just uh...
Picking it up as we go along.
Man of few words,
like your dad.
Yeah. Yeah, right.
No?
Me like my dad?
Nope, not at all.
I don't know.
I wouldn't be so sure.
I see a lot of Ed in you.
Yeah, you want
a police question?
Here's a police question,
all right?
Parker all right, go ahead.
The guy we're taking
to the hospital,
he defrauded people
out of millions of dollars,
ruined their lives.
That's right.
He's a douchebag.
I believe that was
the court's finding, yes.
Okay. So why are you
going through all this trouble
to help him?
I mean,
he gets a security detail,
medical treatment...
It's our job.
To be bodyguards for some jerk?
We're not judges, Clark.
We're police.
We uphold the law.
Get down!
Get on the ground!
Get on your knees!
On your knees!
Get down!
Down on the ground!
Come on, get down!
No funny business!
Hands behind your back!
All right, get up!
Up! Up!
In the other room!
Get in the other room!
Go! Go!
All right, let's do it!
Uh-oh!
Look what I got!
Jackpot! Got it!
Whoa!
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
You guys got an arsenal
in here!
Give me a hand with this.
Look at this stuff!
Hey! Tally it up!
Damn...
About a pound and a half.
Twenty-two an ounce
times twenty-four ounces...
That's...
That's over 50k!
Whoa!
Fifty thousand dollars.
Well, you guys are more
important than you look.
How much is there?
A little over $2200.
- You know how much this cost?
- $3.99.
You're crazy...
- Yeah, I know.
- I coulda got it cheaper, but...
I like to shop local.
Do you guys have any
idea who you're messing with?
Yeah, we do.
Christopher Gearing, your boss.
Tell him we came.
Yeah, I'll tell him.
You think those masks
will protect you?
You know the best thing
about you guys?
No matter how big the talk,
you all get real quiet
at this point.
Let's go!
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
Get back! Get back!
Take cover!
Come on, get down!
Get down!
Okay, guys, if this was
a high-risk scenario,
the most likely place
for an attack is right here...
The transfer point
between a vehicle
and the building.
Can you tell me why?
More exposed.
Right. Good.
Can you be more specific?
Uh, what else do you see?
Parking garage.
Could be a sniper perch.
Right. Now, what we do
is take a diamond formation
around the subject.
We'd have a spotter on overhead
to check the threats.
What else?
Those garbage cans -
could be concealing an IED.
This hospital serves the prison.
They've got a bomb unit
doing regular sweeps.
And we'd clear all that
stuff out ahead of time...
The garbage cans, mailboxes,
all of it.
What else?
Uh...
Clark, you wanna chime in?
On what?
Well, threat assessment.
Threat assessment?
Like from here to the door?
That's right.
Uh... shin splints?
Team One, hot call!
Shots fired -
519 Sackville Street.
Multiple gunshots.
Repeat, multiple gunshots.
Winnie, we're on it.
Let's move.
Okay, boys, you're with me!
Come on!
Hey!
I got an exit.
Come to me.
Aghhhh!
Team, let's hold up here.
Okay, stay in the truck.
Lock the doors.
Oh, come on!
But dad...
Do not move,
you hear me?
What's going on?
What can you tell us?
Shots came from inside
that building,
but it's been quiet
since we arrived.
All right.
Seal off the block,
the whole area's hot.
Keep everyone out.
Yes, sir.
Sam, Leah -
move up recon.
Copy.
Spike, give me floor plans.
Coming up.
Hey, Greg.
How come every time I see you
someone's shooting up
the neighbourhood?
It's your division, Matt,
you tell me.
Staff sergeant Matt McGrath,
Ed Lane, my team leader.
So what are we
looking at? Domestic?
It's not domestic.
911 said there's
more than one gunshot here.
And now quiet...
Maybe the shooters
got what they came for?
Or it's a stalemate.
We should move up,
see what's going on.
Dude.
Come on. Why not?
You heard my dad.
We were told to stay.
Uh, we were told we were
going for a ride-along today.
I'm pretty sure this doesn't
feel like a ride-along.
What do you care?
This is just supposed to be
a day off school for you.
Exactly! So shouldn't it suck
a bit less than school?
You wanted to see
police work up close,
didn't you?
Right! Well, the way I see it,
Dean Parker,
there are two types of people
in this world:
the sitting in
the truck type...
- Yeah...
- And the other type,
and I don't think
you're the sitting-
in-the-truck type,
I really don't.
Come on.
We have to keep
a safe distance.
Absolutely.
And we have to get back
before they are.
- Okay.
- Here.
We'll need these.
So we can hear what's going on.
Make sure you turn off transmit
so they can't hear us.
- Clark...
- Yeah...
You do know how pissed
my dad's gonna be
if he knows that
we're gone, right?
Yeah, about half as pissed
as mine.
Let's go.
Window broken outward...
Looks like our hot zone, Ed,
second floor, east side.
Residential suite floor
plans coming your way.
Main entrance has cover;
That's our approach.
Sam, let's form up!
Hurry!
Spike, Jules,
sweep and clear.
- Got it!
- Sam, Leah - with me.
Hey, look.
There's a guy coming out
of the building.
On point. No surprises.
Use extreme caution.
Let's move.
Ted... Ted...
Ted, come on,
stay with me, man, stay...
Oh no...
Team, 10-33 inside
the building.
Repeat, 10-33.
What does that mean?
It's 10-33...
Officer down.
Ed;
Team, new deal.
Hard entry now!
Let's move! Move!
They're going in blind?
They don't have a choice.
Officer down.
Flashpoint 05x09
Lawmen
Original Air Date  November 15, 2012
==sync, correction by dcdah==
www.addic7ed.com
Hard entry,
let's go now!
Police! Right there!
Drop it!
Down on the ground now!
Get on the ground now!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Two in back!
- Shooter, red wall!
- Leah, with me!
- Sam, now!
- Police! Drop your weapon!
Police! Drop it now!
Get down!
Get down on the ground
Drop your weapon now!
Drop it!
- I'm a police officer...
- Drop it!
Okay, okay, okay.
Clear in the front.
Ed?
Eddie!
Ed, status?
All clear!
I need EMS now!
Please, you gotta help him.
What's the status
of the downed officer?
Gunshot wound to the chest,
but he's still breathing.
He's critical.
All right, man.
Let's go.
Hold on.
Look.
Is that the guy who came down
the fire escape?
Yeah. I think it is.
Let's get outta here.
You were just walking by?
We heard shots,
we intervened.
They just opened up on us.
I should go with him.
No, he's in good hands,
and we need you right here.
Nobody on that side's talking.
Why didn't you call
for backup?
It all happened really fast.
So you broke protocol?
Look, we reacted, okay?
I mean,
in case you hadn't noticed,
my partner just took one
in the chest,
so maybe you could just...
just back off an inch or two,
okay?
Okay, okay.
Sit tight.
Boss, something's
not adding up.
Two plainclothes officers,
guns in hand, no ID.
So what, they just happened by?
That's the claim,
but the officers are pretty deep
inside the apartment.
Bad guys got between them
and the door.
All right, keep at him.
I'm gonna see
if there are witnesses.
We have to tell them
what we saw.
Oh no, no, no.
That's not gonna happen.
We're just gonna
let that guy get away?
Well, we don't know
anything about that guy.
He left a crime scene
and he's evading the police.
That look like
a good citizen to you?
Look, you were right, okay?
Leaving the truck
was a really bad idea.
Hey, boys.
Anyone see this thing happen?
Come on, who was here
when the gunshots started?
Hey, Dylan.
You remember me?
Uh, yeah.
Last year, from practice.
Yeah, I'm thinking about helping
coach out again this year too.
Officer asked you a question.
Ah, we didn't see anything,
Sarge.
Well, if you think of anything,
call it into the station, okay?
This is not the best place
to be hanging around, guys.
They're good kids.
I don't blame them
for not wanting to talk.
My guys at division tell me
this is a stash house
for Christopher Gearing.
Drug trafficker?
Meth, mostly.
Not the kind of guy
you wanna snitch on.
You know him?
Ted Salansky.
Look, I uh...
I have to call his family.
I'll be inside, Matt.
Look, we weren't supposed
to be there in the first place,
so let's just leave it at that.
What if it's evidence?
What if it's hockey gear?
Look, for all we know,
they're already
on top of the guy.
So let's just...
keep listening.
Okay.
We should wait inside though.
Ed! Boss!
It's methamphetamine
and money...
- Who burns money?
- Destroying evidence?
They didn't know
the cops were coming.
I found this ski mask.
These guys aren't bank robbers,
they're dealers.
Okay, officer,
you need to tell us exactly
what's going on here.
A little off-the-books
police work?
I wanna speak to my union rep.
I'll tell you what,
we'll get SIU down here.
You can talk to them.
No, sir,
we're not done.
Boss, you need to see these.
Jake, looks like
they know you here, buddy.
Hey, who's this?
The third member of the crew?
The silence isn't
helping, Jake.
Gearing's men are onto you.
We can take care
of ourselves.
Can she?
Oh my God.
Talk to us.
It wasn't supposed to go
like this.
No one was supposed
to get hurt.
Go on, Jake.
Third guy in the crew,
his name is Cam Weyler.
That's his wife Marcy.
Winnie, get me
Staff Sergeant McGrath.
Copy that.
Boss, there is only
one reason why they'd
- have a picture of the wife here.
- I know.
What do you got, Greg?
Still sifting through this,
Matt,
but we've got reason to think
Gearing might retaliate
against the officers
involved here.
How can you tell?
Surveillance photos.
They've been tracking
the officers
and one of their wives -
Marcy Weyler.
I mean, does that fit
in Gearing's MO...
A hit against a cop's wife?
He-he's got no rules.
No code.
That's how he rose to power;
by being more brutal
than the competition.
Look, Greg...
Greg,
Gearing's got eyes everywhere.
By now, he knows you busted up
his stash house.
Yeah, and found his plan
to retaliate.
Eddie,
if he's gonna strike back,
he's gonna do it now.
Let me call division.
You get eyes on Cam, okay?
Okay, team, all hands on deck.
Winnie, we need to find
Marcy Weyler.
Let's get unis to her home
and to her work.
Copy.
Jules, stay here.
Don't take your eyes off him.
Just keep on Jake, Jules.
If there's a vigilante plot,
we need to get on top
of those involved,
how long -
all of it.
Copy.
Okay, guys,
I'm cutting you loose.
Taxi'll take you.
So it was cops
that started all this?
What?
We were just listengg
on the headsets.
We wanted to know
what was going on?
Some officers crossed a line,
Dean.
We'll talk about it later.
Are they in trouble?
It doesn't look good, son.
Get in.
517 Belmont.
Thank you.
Okay, team,
officers wife is targeted.
Let's find her
and keep her safe!
You ready?
Team One, we've got unis
at Marcy Weyler's
home and work,
but she's not there.
Okay, Winnie,
just keep digging...
friends, neighbours -
this woman's in danger.
We need to find her now.
Okay, I got something.
Surveillance photos were taken
at home, at work,
and at a third location,
and the building's got
a distinctive facade.
You recognize it?
Nope. But someone
somewhere does.
Reverse image search engine...
It takes a photo
and compares it
to every picture on the web.
Looks for similar shapes,
colours, patterns.
Barrington Community Center.
North end of the neighbourhood.
Guys, let's move.
Staff, ride with me,
I'll fill in.
Perfect.
Winnie, call ahead.
Anyone sees Marcy,
lock her up in a back room.
Copy that.
I can't do it, Clark.
Dean, what are you doing?
We can't just drive off.
It's not right.
We're supposed to go home.
It's not right!
Like, Clark,
people could get hurt.
It's not our business, okay?
In or out, boys?
I gotta go.
Just hold on a sec,
please.
Okay, tell you what.
Why don't we call 911?
- Anonymous tip.
- No, can't do it.
We're dealing
with corrupt cops;
we don't know who we can trust.
Look, if you don't want
to do this,
I'll understand.
I'll just tell them
I got out of the truck alone.
- Really? You'd do that?
- Yeah.
Making me the biggest dink
on earth. Yeah.
Thanks.
We're good.
Okay, here's what we do.
We go back and we check
what's in the duffel bag
before we make
any decisions, okay?
And if it's not important,
then we can forget all of this.
We can just walk away.
And if it is important?
Then we tell our dads.
And I prepare for life
in the toolshed,
where I'll be locked
until I'm eighteen.
All right, let me know
if anything changes.
Cam's not on duty
and he's not answering his cell.
APB's gone out.
We'll find him, Matt.
He's my officer, Greg.
They all are.
I just can't believe
they went rogue.
We don't know the whole story.
It's this neighbourhood.
Tie you up in knots.
You remember what it was like,
5, 10 years ago...
Overrun by gangs,
drugs, poverty.
I had my share of calls here.
It's changing, Greg,
it really is.
You can feel it on the street.
People are fighting back.
School enrollment's up,
crime's down.
I mean, it's fragile,
you know, it's new,
but it's there.
Boss, no answer
at the community centre.
I'm trying
neighboring businesses.
Okay, keep at it, Winnie.
This animal, Gearing,
he gets his way,
this whole place will slide back
into the dark.
So you're really into
this cop stuff, huh?
Let me ask you something.
Why?
I wanna help people.
Like your dad.
Well...
Not if he can help it.
He's against it?
He doesn't think
I've thought it through.
Right. He knows what you want
better than you do.
You know what it's like
to have the city's top
crisis negotiator
as your father?
It sucks.
Yeah, well, at least he talks.
These days,
my dad hardly says a word.
So you break in,
you destroy drugs and money,
and then you leave.
That makes sense.
You wanna disrupt business,
stop the flow.
What about weapons?
What do you do
when you find weapons?
I'm just gonna keep
asking you questions, Jake.
You're doing your job,
I get it.
And you're just looking out
for your brothers,
but the more information
we have,
the more we can help them -
you know this.
I've told you
what you need to know.
You still haven't told me why.
Why?
You wanna know why, SRU?
Because you blow into
the neighbourhood every 6 months
and you make a big show.
We live here.
Honey,
we gotta go.
What?
What's wrong?
I'll explain later, come on.
Just be quick
and I'll meet you out here.
Okay.
Leah, you're with me.
Spike, Sam, north side!
Nooooooo!
No! No!
Marcy!
Noooo!
Boss?
Winnie, EMS,
women's change room, right away!
Copy.
He killed her...
Sergeant, he killed her...
Baby...
Move!
Stop! Police!
Subjects sighted!
North exit!
Stop right there!
On the ground!
Stay on the ground!
Right there!
Oof!
Get up! Get up!
How old are you?!
Dean...
You sure about this?
Clark, we agreed.
That's not what I mean.
It's just...
The guy with the bag,
what if he's one of the cops?
Yeah. So?
So they busted up a drug house.
Maybe that's not
such a bad thing.
There's a right way
and a wrong way.
You have to obey the law.
Yeah, the law...
What is it?
My dad shot a teenage girl,
did you know that?
Yeah, she was protecting
her mother,
trying to stop a violent man.
She didn't deserve to die.
No...
Everyone knew it, Dean -
he knew it...
But he followed the law...
Did he tell you that?
Of course not.
Mom did.
She had to say something.
Something to explain...
The mood swings,
the silence.
I mean, sometimes
you'll just find him
and he's in the middle
of something...
just getting a glass out
of the cupboard...
You know, it's just like
someone pressed pause.
He's just dead still,
staring at the countertop.
And worst part is,
when I look at him now,
that's all I see.
The guy who had to do that,
the guy who put a bullet
in that girl's head.
I mean, what kind of guy
even does that, Dean?
Oh gee...
Get down...
We're good.
Wanna go get the bag?
Yeah.
Let's go.
How is she?
Cam?
I've got two unis on him.
Something's not right, Eddie.
How did Cam know his wife
was being targeted?
Good question.
He took off before
he even discovered the photos.
And that's before
there was any indication
that Gearing was after Marcy.
And yet he came directly
to the community center
to protect his wife.
So who told him?
Well, it wasn't Jake.
He's been with me
the whole time.
Well, it's not hockey gear.
Serial number's are filed off.
These belong
to the drug dealers.
Boss, there's only
one other person
who knew that Gearing
was after Marcy.
Yeah.
Anyone have eyes
on Matt McGrath?
- No, boss.
- Negative.
Hey!
I'm gonna need that bag.
Winnie, put an APB on
Staff Sergeant Matt McGrath...
The whole city -
and top priority.
Copy that.
I'm a police officer.
That's official evidence.
Hang on...
Son, this is a serious matter.
I'm not gonna ask again.
Can I see your badge?
You're smart.
Now, did you, uh,
know what's in the bag?
Yeah.
So you understand
this is a dangerous situation?
I'll tell you what.
There's some cops
just over there.
How about we take it over
together.
I tell you what,
give me that bag
and I won't arrest both of you
here and now.
I don't believe
I caught your name, officer.
Hey! Hey! Stop!
Just take it! Take it!
Take it!
Just take it!
That guy's not right.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, we just let him walk off
with a bag of guns.
No, I didn't.
No, I put my cell phone
in the bag.
Boss, I got Dean on the line.
He says it's urgent.
All right, put
him through, Winnie.
Dad...
We're in the middle
of a call here, son.
Are you all right?
Yeah, we're fine.
Dean, is Clark with you?
Yeah, we're both fine.
It's just...
We have some information
about the shooting this morning.
What about it?
We saw a guy running away
from the apartment
and we saw him stash a bag
in the alley
after you guys went in.
You saw all this
from the truck?
Uh, no. See, that's the thing.
We got outta the truck.
We wanted to see
what was going on.
You did what?
I specifically told you
to stay inside that truck.
Okay, just listen
and then you can freak out,
okay?
Clark put you up to this?
We both did it.
Just please let me explain.
We came back to see
if the bag was important
and that's when we found out
it was full of...
well, it's full of guns.
Guns?
With their serial numbers
filed off.
Gotta be from Gearing's crew.
Cam must be the guy they saw
pulling the guns out
during the raid.
Okay, Dean,
you do not touch those guns,
you understand?
That's the thing,
we don't have them anymore.
A cop came and took them.
What cop?
Didn't get his name
off his badge.
He's about 6'1", brown hair,
gray suit, white shirt.
About 50 years old.
That's Matt.
Only one reason you'd need
a bag of untraceable guns.
He's going after Gearing.
Uh, dad...
Winnie, put out an APB
on Gearing,
all known locations.
Dad...
Associates, friends, family.
He's in grave danger.
We need to bring him in.
- Copy.
- Dad, can you listen to me?
Oh, son,
I've been listening to you.
you disobeyed me;
you moved into
a live battle zone;
you withheld key information
during an active investigation,
and then you exposed yourself
further to danger
by returning to the scene
of the crime.
Have I missed anything?!
Yeah, we put a cell phone
in the bag.
You what?
We didn't trust the cop,
so Clark planted his cell
on him
so you could track it.
I'm on it!
Dad?
Do not think
you're off the hook.
I want you and Clark
to stay where you are.
We're sending Jules to you.
Okay.
Do not move!
Are we clear?
Yeah.
I'll be right there, boss.
I just need a sec
with Jake first.
Piece of cake.
Marcy's dead.
I know.
I'm sorry, Jake.
Listen, we're gonna need
your help.
Matt's missing.
What?
When he saw Marcy shot,
he took off.
We think he went after Gearing.
Now, listen,
I can either hand you over
to SIU,
or you can come with me
and you can help us
stop your sergeant
from doing something
he might regret forever.
It's up to you, Jake.
- Let's go.
- Okay, let's go.
Got him.
He's moving east on Lakeshore.
Right behind you, Spike.
He's continuing on Lakeshore.
Make a right on Jarvis.
Jules, does that ring any bells
with Jake?
Distillery district.
Gearing have any ties there?
Koolhaus Night Club.
It's part of his
laundering operation.
Did you guys get that?
Yeah. We copy, Jules.
This is crazy...
When I joined the force,
Matt was everything
I wanted to be in a cop.
Tell me about that.
He was smart, brave.
He cared about the work,
cared about the people.
So what happened?
Few years ago,
Gearing and his crew
move into the neighbourhood,
start pushing all the other
dealers out.
Full on turf war.
Things just blew up on us.
One day, out on patrol,
shots-fired call comes in.
Middle of the day...
Matt's first on the scene.
Two victims, 10-54.
No need for EMS.
First one was fifteen.
The other was twelve -
twelve years old.
Just kids.
That's how Gearing
won the war;
using child soldiers.
We're taking him down, Jake.
He's done.
After that, Matt put
together a task force.
Me, Ted, Cam.
We spent months
investigating Gearing.
Stakeouts, surveillance,
undercover...
we poured everything
that we had into it.
Thousands of man hours.
Cracked his distribution
chains,
infiltrated
his laundering operation,
and the day we arrested him...
that was my proudest moment
on the force.
When the case went to court,
the whole thing
just fell apart.
Half our evidence got
thrown out on technicalities.
Some witnesses recanted,
others didn't even show up
at all.
Gearing made
our whole task force
look like a joke.
The only thing that stuck
was an unlicensed
weapon charge.
Six months probation.
So you changed tactics.
Matt formed a new task force -
off the books.
If we couldn't get him
in the courts,
we were gonna get him
in the streets.
Whenever we heard
of a stash house,
we wouldn't wait
for a warrant...
We'd crush it.
We take their guns,
we destroy their product.
Zero tolerance.
And it was working.
Did you ever use violence?
We thought about it...
about cutting the head off
the snake,
ending it once and for all,
but Matt said no.
Greg, he's a good man.
We gotta get there
and we gotta stop this.
Keep quiet,
you might survive this.
Gearing!
Am I under arrest?
I should've done this
years ago...
Dylan...
Right there! Right there!
The signals coming
from the parking lot.
Son, listen to me...
What're you waiting for?
You're not gonna do this.
I know you...
Aghhh!
Dylan, you okay?
Stay there!
Boss, Spike, with me.
Sam, Leah, main floor.
Let's move now!
We've got a couple
of kids here.
They're tied up.
We'll come back for them.
Let's move!
Greg...
You all right, son?
You okay?
Hey, it's Dylan, right?
All right, you hang tough.
I couldn't do it.
Couldn't do what, son?
The sergeant...
I didn't shoot him.
I... I couldn't do it.
Stay here.
Agh!
Up on your knees!
Sergeant, right there!
Put the gun down!
Put it down now!
We've got the subject
on the lower level.
Put it down now!
Sir...
Clark, what you said earlier,
about your dad
killing that girl...
He had to do it.
It was the right thing.
Yeah?
When we were in the Lane,
talking to that sergeant,
he was messed up,
you could see it.
He was just so lost.
That's why your dad
followed the law;
he knows what happens
when you don't.
He knows what you become.
He is so torn up, Dean.
What your dad had to do
was terrible,
but he made the right call.
What're you doing, Matt?
Walk away, Greg.
Let me do this.
I can't.
No one's gonna miss him.
No one's gonna mourn him.
I know...
He puts guns in the hands
of children...
and sends them out to kill
other children, women...
I know that.
And we play by the rules,
we fight fair...
Why?
Huh, Greg?
Why does this monster
deserve your protection?
Do I need to answer that?
We're not here
to protect him, Matt.
We're here to protect you.
No.
Well, I tried being
a good cop...
doesn't make any difference.
Doesn't make a difference?
Excuse me?!
The kid upstairs says otherwise.
Dylan was supposed to kill you,
but he didn't.
Because when it came
down to it,
he knows good from bad.
And you know how?
Because you took the time
to get to know him.
You took the time
to be a part of his world.
You did what a good cop does.
You cared...
you care.
He knows the difference
between you and this murderer.
You gonna prove him wrong?
Don't prove him wrong,
come on...
Come on.
Let it go.
♪Men with guns ♪
♪ took our young ♪
♪ then begun to start killing
everyone ♪
♪ took the lives ♪
♪ of our wives ♪
♪ now we hide in the dark
and wait to die ♪
- You all right, Eddie?
- Not even close.
You know, what Clark did
with the cell phone...
we wouldn't have come in time.
It's a pretty smart move.
It's pretty brave.
And what, that makes up for it?
No. Sometimes Dean
drives me crazy,
won't listen to a word I say,
and other times
he does something
that makes me so proud
I think my heart's gonna...
just burst.
Thing is that, more and more,
both happen at the same time.
Clark's a great kid.
He's got a lot of you in there.
What do we do?
I know.
How bad do you think
this is gonna be?
I don't know.
Let's just get it over with.
You know,
if you wanna be a cop,
you gotta learn
to follow the rules.
Yeah, we get it.
♪ Life is a pending funeral ♪
♪ the holes that we dig
will be our own ♪
Wanna grab a pizza?
Uh, sure.
See, that's the other thing
about being a cop...
ten percent discount
at Vanelli's.
Okay, let's go.