Subject's in sight.
We are in pursuit heading
South on cherry street.
We need back up.
On our way.
Sergeant Robert
Gray, step out of the vehicle!
Hands where we can see them!
That's it,
slow and steady!
Spike, grenade!
Pull back!
So?
Here, here, here,
have a seat, have a seat.
I can sit.
Do you want me
to get you a tea?
Like an herbal tea
or somethin'?
I don't need an herbal tea,
I can sit,
and you're not allowed
to do that,
treat me like I need
bubble wrap or something.
I'm the same, okay?
I don't want you
to change on me.
Everything is the same.
So the doctor's sure.
There's...
Yeah, she's sure.
I can't even believe it.
I mean, like,
what are the chances?
We were so careful.
It's like...
Point zero-zero one per cent.
You've always been exceptional.
I don't wanna
let the team down.
Hey, don't worry
about the team, okay?
This is bigger.
How do you feel?
I feel really scared.
What else?
I can't believe...
Believe what?
I can't believe
how much I want this baby.
Me too.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah!
Hey, it's me again.
So, this is the colour
you picked.
Personally,
I think your taste is awful,
probably from looking
at camouflage all day.
So, I picked something else.
Warm,
strong,
and complex.
You're probably wondering
how the other project is going.
Six months.
It's amazing.
He's moving so much.
I wish you could feel him.
Six months.
I miss you so much!
I can't wait till you're home.
Sorry to interrupt,
but it's 0800.
Round everyone up?
Not a problem.
Briefing's in five minutes.
Camp and the others?
Picking up supplies;
They won't be back for an hour.
Good.
So what are the rules?
Well, officially,
I can stay on the force
right up until the end.
Yeah, sure, if
you're on a desk, but...
When are we gonna tell them?
Sam, it's too soon.
I'm only seven weeks.
Most people wait till after
the first trimester.
Most people don't
have your job.
I don't want
to say anything yet.
I don't want people
checking in,
getting all over-protective.
I don't want to throw anybody
off their game.
But you can't just pretend
nothing's changed.
Sam, look at me.
I'm just as qualified
as I was two months ago.
So this is just another day?
Yes.
Ready to keep the peace?
Let's do it!
Then gear up! We
hit the road in ten!
Let's let 'em know
we're out there!
Kondraski?
Caps, c4, plans, all set.
Bishop?
It's all locked up.
They'll be in position in 30.
Let's get there in 29.
What's up?
Are you sure?
What about?
Me.
Kondraski and bishop are solid,
but if this operation
goes South...
We need you.
I know you're gonna do your job
and keep us safe.
I wouldn't have asked you
if I didn't think so.
You know that.
But what you also need to know
is that you will always
have a place here.
I will always be here for you,
whether you come now or not.
I just don't wanna
let you down, sir.
Doug, what's the first thing
I told you in basic training?
Sergeant's always right.
Well, right now
the sergeant's telling you
whatever choice you make,
that's the right one.
Let's go.
We take care of our own, right?
Right.
Sid ah, traffic's bad all
the way out of town.
Red lines are bad, right?
Yeah, either way,
we still get a layover.
A six-hour drive,
a night at a crap hotel,
followed by another
six-hour drive home.
Livin' the dream.
Geez.
Sir, I need to
know how long you're gonna be.
Uh, it's a fire Lane.
I'm just waiting for my guys.
Three minutes.
Ah!
How about less
than three minutes?
One daley 13...
We're all clear.
- Officer...
- Don't move!
No alarms!
Get down!
Do what we want,
no one gets hurt!
Team one, I got
a nervous dispatcher
over at Charleston security.
They're trying to get in touch
with one of their crews
downtown,
but it's gone quiet.
Charleston's got a whole
fleet of armoured trucks, right?
Yeah, this one
was out on a bank run.
They're supposed to be in
contact every 15 minutes,
but this one's running silent.
Dispatcher can't raise 'em.
Protocol is to call us.
Is this their route?
No, this is their last contact.
Their final stop
is supposed to be here.
439 Pearl.
Pretty narrow street.
Couldn't have picked
a better spot for a robbery.
Okay, spike, Sam, let's
start at temperance,
come in from the east.
We'll come in from the west.
Boss, check in
at the last bank.
They gotta be somewhere
in between.
Sarge, we gotta double time it!
Cops are on their way.
Charleston got in touch
with them
looking for the truck.
Okay, there's still time.
You know where to go.
Distract and
disable - on it!
This truck remind you
of anything?
A Humvee.
All it needs
is a turret on top.
You got this?
Yeah.
Just not a fan of tight spaces.
Drop safe walls
are three inches thick.
I won't go any
deeper than three and a half.
It's the wonder of c4.
Cops are on their way.
We've only got
a couple of minutes.
That's all we'll need.
Bishop, I need
you on the roof.
I'm good.
E-A's are set and ready.
In position for pick-up.
Status?
We're in.
In position.
All clear.
Hang on, we got trouble.
What do you see?
Sam, how close are you?
Cops.
Tops and tail.
Alley's packed tight.
In position.
Approach on foot?
No, let's take the trucks in
as far as we can.
If we run into any problem...
bottle 'em up tight.
Copy. Leah?
Nothing yet.
Kondraski?
Almost done.
Almost is gonna
have to be enough.
As soon as cover starts...
Back the way I came.
Ready.
There's supposed to be
two guards in that truck
at all times.
Cab of the truck looks empty.
Wait a second.
A single guard.
Not moving.
What, is he injured?
I don't know.
Bishop.
Ready.
Sam, spike,
let's move in fast!
Ed, we're movin' in now!
Nothing from the rear.
We'll...
Engine's cut!
Power's totally gone!
Incoming!
Taking fire!
We're taking fire!
Ed, we're blind here!
We got multiple gunshots!
We're under attack!
== sync, corrected by Martzy ==
www.Addic7ed.Com
Winnie,
we need UNI's down there!
Tight perimeter!
No one approaches
until we've locked this down!
You got it, boss.
We're still blind.
Can't spot the shooter!
Spike?
Nothing!
Eddie, we're on
your end of the alley.
We've got your six, Ed!
Where are the shots
coming from?
Can't tell.
No muzzle flash.
No one's approaching!
Weird offensive strategy,
surrounding your targets
in smoke!
They won't be able to see us!
They haven't
targeted the windows,
they're just firin'
at the roof!
No intent to injure.
An elevated
sniper pinning us down.
Okay, guys, this is delay.
It is not an attack.
Smoke works both ways.
We've got cover too.
Let's not give
'em any more time.
Shields up.
Let's close in. Boss!
In position.
Right there! Don't move!
Freeze! Don't move!
Freeze!
Hold fire! Hold fire!
Come on! Move!
Keep going to
the end of the alley!
Boss, the guard's
coming your way!
Rear of the van is clear.
Okay, remaining
guards are okay!
Come on, you're all right.
You're all right.
What's going on?
There were three
of them at least.
They blew the safe.
Yeah, but where'd they go?
It's a clean job.
Looks like they used c4.
These guys knew
what they were doing.
What was in there?
This was our last stop.
What we already had
in the drop safe,
what we picked up here...
Little over two million.
We were supposed to take it
out of town,
up to the federal bank.
Doesn't the money usually flow
the other way?
It's all used bills.
The feds are rolling out
a new design for the twenty.
Today was our last collection,
gettin' all the banks to give us
the rest of their old bills,
get them replaced with the new.
Until it's destroyed,
it's still legal tender.
Guys, I know why
your truck shut down.
Electrical arrestors.
They short-out
a car's electrical system
when you drive over them.
It's temporary though.
But effective.
It was a trap.
They lured us into the alley
and made sure
they had a way out.
Professional, prepared...
And they're long gone.
Well, the day's not over yet.
Let's scour the alley.
Let's get these guys before
they really hurt somebody.
The security camera's gone.
The e-a is definitely homemade.
We could source the parts
if we had a couple of days.
Gotta be faster than that.
We gotta pick up the trail.
Sam, what do we got?
There's a perfect alley
back here,
lots of concealment and access
all the way to king.
The smoke covered them.
They get out through
there with the money.
Sid...
Did you get a look
at these guys?
Just the cop.
A cop?
Yeah, he said we were
blocking the laneway.
He got me out of the truck
and he pulled a gun.
Well, whoever these guys
are, they got connections.
Along with everything
you find in c4,
I'm getting traces of motor oil
back here.
Yeah, the military bakes that
into their c4 as a marker.
In case it ever gets stolen,
they can always track it.
Every base uses
a different signature.
I'm gonna run it
through the database
and see what I can find.
- I got a visual.
- Where?
One of the cruisers
that responded on king.
Their in-car camera got lucky.
We're under fire in the alley
and these "cops"
are going the other way.
One cruiser, one cop,
three passengers,
and two big bags of money.
Any way we can clear
that image up, spike?
Let me give it a try.
Ed, I ran down the tracer
in the c4.
It's local.
It came from downsview.
Okay, let's find out how
the army lost enough c4
to blow up a safe
in an armoured truck.
We'll stay here,
figure out how to find a cop car
in a city full of cop cars.
Spike, get me that picture
as soon as you have it
cleaned up.
Let's find out if he served.
Eddie, I'm gonna try to smooth
the way for you at downsview.
Everybody okay?
Yeah.
We still on plan?
With a wrinkle.
We have to lay low for a bit,
get out of town.
It was always our fallback.
I just gotta make the call.
Sergeant,
there's no way that...
I know what I'm saying.
Military ordinance
on the street,
explosives from your base
used to rob an armoured truck.
If we don't find it now...
But what you're asking for...
may save lives.
Gotta be a whole lot better
than a flock of reporters
camped outside your gate
asking questions
you don't wanna answer.
I understand.
Your officers just pulled up.
I'll give you
whatever you need.
Thank you very much.
Captain Ruscitti, you
know why we're here?
Yeah, your
sergeant can be very persuasive.
He's right.
I'll do whatever you need
to find this stuff
and figure out who has it.
Okay, good. We're
gonna need log books;
we're gonna need
security cam footage
of the warehouse
where the c4 was kept,
and we're gonna need to talk
to the guy in charge.
I'm setting you up with
master corporal Ronnie birch.
He counts our boxes
and bullets.
If anyone can help you,
it'll be him.
What else you got?
Well, since
a bunch of army explosives
are out on the streets,
I've already given your team
access to something
that should help you
track these guys down.
What do we got, spike?
A very strong
desire to join the army.
I've got some programs
cleaning up the car-cam footage
of our suspects.
That shouldn't be long,
but this...
The M.P. At downsview
patched me into the army's
military satellite system.
It looks at police decals
and the light bar on top.
Cross-referencing that
with the transponders
in all our cruisers
and we find...
The one cop car
without a transponder.
Our suspects.
You know, boss, if we had
this stuff all the time...
What happened?
I don't know. They
must've gone under cover,
like a parking garage
or a tunnel.
Satellites can't track
what they can't see.
Where, spike?
That's the address right there.
I'll send it to your PDA's.
Sam, Jules, let's go!
You all know what to do.
I'm gonna make sure we're set.
Trash all identifying evidence.
Hey, the cops got too close.
What do you think?
I think we have to move.
Whatever you got.
Forbes, we're gonna
have to lay low awhile,
make sure our tracks
are covered,
wait for this to blow over.
Guns? Not yet.
Won't it look bad
if we all just disappear?
Only if they're already on us.
It's just that limb
that we're out on, it's...
It's a little thin.
That's all I'm saying.
No, we're good, we just...
We're in this together.
We're all in this together.
This isn't just about
the four of us.
You know that, Doug.
We'll be there at 1600.
Right, four o'clock.
We all good?
Forbes, you're not still afraid
of the water, are you?
Let's go.
It's straightforward.
Every time ordinance goes out
it has to be signed
by the officer who ordered it
and me...
hard copy, and the computer.
But once it leaves here
it's harder to track.
And this is the
last couple of months?
Last two weeks.
Training exercises,
overseas deployments...
We send a lot
of this stuff out.
Ed, trying to track
all these people down,
it would take days.
All right, these
stretch back the last couple of months.
Anything else you need,
we're on it.
Okay.
Ed, I just cleaned up
the image as much as I could
and I just sent it out.
Okay, spike, thank you.
Sir, maybe you can help us
narrow this down.
You recognize this man?
He was involved in the robbery
this morning.
It can't be.
What're you saying?
That's sergeant Robert Gray;
He's one of our best.
He was here between
combat tours.
Honourable discharge
just last year.
Master corporal birch
can tell you all about him.
They were in basic together.
So you know this man?
And you sign for everything.
- Yes, sir.
- Where is he?
I don't know, sir.
Do you have an
address for Gray?
Yeah, it's a quick phone call
to personnel.
Boss, we got a positive I.D.
On a sergeant Robert Gray,
former army.
The address is coming your way.
Thanks, Eddie.
Hopefully we won't need it.
Spike found the car.
Spike, there's nothing here.
Satellites haven't picked up
any cruisers
leaving the area.
It's 'cause it doesn't
look like a police car anymore.
I got fake decals
and light bar.
Back to square one.
So now it's just a white car.
The city confirms the
house belongs to Robert Gray.
All right, let's
knock and announce,
give him a chance to surrender.
Who robs a bank
and then comes home?
Someone who thinks
they got away with it.
Robert Gray,
this is the police!
Strategic response unit,
open this door!
Robert Gray?
He's not here.
Mind if we look around, sir?
Why?
We think he committed a
serious crime this morning.
No, no, no, no, no.
No way.
I can readjust the
parameters of the search,
get the satellites lookin'
for a white sedan.
Well, they couldn't
have gotten far.
Dialling it in.
Six million
people in the G.T.A.
And we gotta find
one white car.
Good news is white's
not the most popular colour.
What is?
Silver.
- But?
- White's number two.
Where's sergeant Gray?
You should just let him go.
He robbed an armoured
car with stolen explosives.
Did anyone get hurt?
There's a guard
in the hospital.
They fired on my men.
Yes, someone was hurt.
It wasn't supposed
to be like that.
So you knew what
they were up to?
It's all about being there
for the next guy.
No one cares more for his men
than Gray.
When he left the army,
he came back
and his life was falling apart,
but he pulled it together
because he knew there were
soldiers that needed his help.
So what, so that's what
the money was for?
It's not just about the money.
When was the last
time you saw Mr. Gray?
Never heard anyone
call him mister.
It's always been sarge.
This morning.
He and a couple of other guys
staying here
left when we were out.
Boss, Gray's not comin' back.
His closet's half-empty.
Any sense that
he was taking a trip?
He said he might
be gone for a while.
It depended on a meeting
he had this morning.
How well do you know him?
He saved my life.
On duty?
No.
When I got back.
Let me show you something.
Did you find the car?
Uh, not yet.
I was just checkin' in.
You need to talk to sarge?
Your radio broke?
No, I mean with you.
No, no, no, no.
Sam, this is not
how this is gonna go.
Jules, I just...
I'm fine, Sam.
I just wanna know
how you're doing.
I'm doing my job.
Sam, I got somethin'.
Yeah, me too.
What have you got?
White sedans,
former police cars,
are rarer than I thought.
We got two,
three possible targets.
Can you tell
how many passengers?
Sadly, satellites
cannot see through steel yet.
Where's Gray now?
I don't know.
He didn't tell me the plan.
Plausible deniability he said.
Ed, we need you
guys back downtown.
Spike's found a few vehicles
that need tracking.
That one's closest to him.
Okay, Ed, there's a
possible suspect vehicle
heading in your direction
we need to get eyes on.
Spike's sending you
the coordinates now.
Copy that. Leah, let's move.
Winnie, I got a job
for some UNI's.
We got a white sedan
heading east on Danforth.
We're gonna need eyes in.
Send me the details.
I'll have them track it down.
Thank you, Winnie.
And that one is ours.
Let's do it.
They live here?
Yeah. All former army,
all just like me - struggling,
trying to find a way
to fit back in.
Injured or not, you live here,
Gray expects you
to do your part.
Rebuilding his deck?
Taking pride,
making a difference,
helping each other.
You said he saved your life.
Have you ever
served, sergeant?
No. Been in
uniform 25 years though.
You see a lot of stuff,
things nobody can understand,
things you can never forget.
I was in Afghanistan.
We were called in
after an I.E.D. Went off
in a market place.
My job...
My job was to find
all the arms and legs,
match them up,
so we could figure out
how many casualties there were.
How do you tell that story
at a cocktail party?
How do you stop
remembering that it happened?
And that's where Gray comes in?
When you leave the army,
lots of guys don't
have a problem
and the army helps
with the reintegration.
But guys like me,
I'm on medication for the pain,
for, for, for my depression,
for my dreams,
for just about everything.
I'd been home more than a year
living in my parent's basement,
drinking too much.
When I called sergeant Gray...
Without a question,
he came, picked me up,
invited me to stay with him.
I don't have a lot of rules.
This isn't your mother's house.
There's no curfew.
Which one is it?
The door will always be open.
You'll always be welcome.
Getting there,
that's up to you.
This is the address?
It's about five blocks away.
It flattens out at the top.
This place wasn't
exactly accessible,
but we'd work on it.
The bathroom, the doorways.
He'd provide all the materials,
expect me to get to work.
It's tough love.
He's a sergeant.
They know how to push
your buttons.
Guys saw what it was doing
for me,
they wanted to come too.
And he was happy to have them?
He never turned anyone away.
Hey, boss, camp's right.
Gray's being flooded with emails
from all over.
Army, marines...
They have all heard of Gray
and they're asking for help.
He's taking them in,
but it's costing him.
I have a request
for a second mortgage,
overdraft...
He doesn't have enough money.
We should be two
blocks behind our target.
Left, right up there.
Spike, I just got a call
from the UNI's.
They located your white sedan
on the Danforth.
Are you looking for a woman
in her thirties
going to the gym?
I'm not the gym type.
Thanks, Winnie.
So we're sure
it's one of these two?
Yeah, unless they painted
it when they stripped it down.
We should be able to see it.
You think camp knows?
No. Gray wants to keep
his circle small.
Protect his men.
Take the money
and keep putting it
into this place.
You know, they come from
all over the country.
He flies some of 'em in,
puts them up,
never even asks for a penny.
And there are more than 8 vets
who could use his help.
Maybe he's looking
for a bigger place.
That's what I was thinking.
I asked the bank
to look into it,
see if anything's underway.
Ed, how close are we?
Sam, there!
The white car
we're lookin' for.
Can't see inside.
Just like our suspects,
there's four occupants.
Subject's in sight.
Ed, stand down on the search
for your white sedan.
We are in pursuit,
heading South on cherry street.
We need backup asap!
Sarge.
What's the plan?
Sarge?
Highly motivated people here.
They've already taken
a lot of chances today.
We're almost there.
We just have to lose 'em.
No way that happens.
They're too close.
This still works.
I stay behind, I keep 'em busy.
Kondraski no, that doesn't work.
We're not leaving you behind.
No way,
sarge, let me stay.
I keep 'em busy.
You three get across
the finish line.
Sarge-
You heard me!
Now, Forbes,
hand me my bag.
They're gaining on us!
Sam, we got movement
in the front passenger seat.
What's he doin'?
Sergeant Robert
Gray, step out of the vehicle,
hands where we can see them!
That's it!
Slow and steady!
Spike, grenade! Pull back!
Sam, what's goin' on?
He's got a grenade.
No pin in it!
That's not all.
He's got c4 strapped
to his chest.
On our way.
Ed, Gray's blocking our way.
The others went South
of the bridge.
If he drops that grenade...
c4 goes off too.
Takes this whole bridge down
with it.
Sergeant Gray,
you need to stand down!
This is over!
I don't think so.
Spike, we're almost there.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
No, as soon as we get
there we're trapped too.
Leah, give me a target.
Where else could they be going?
Down cherry street,
there's nothing but the lake.
Okay, that makes no sense.
There's gotta be another way
out for them.
Commissioners takes
them back downtown,
but they have to know
we'll block it.
Why would they
box themselves in?
Especially if
Gray's stallin' us?
Ashbridge's marina.
That's it. They jump on a
boat, they cross the border,
they disappear.
That's it.
Or stash the money and
come back to get it later.
Okay, give me the
quickest route to the marina.
Sam, this is a man who's
used to being in control,
setting the pace.
I know this guy, sarge.
I know where he's comin' from.
That's good.
Build on that,
but don't force it,
and let's get this guy
off that bridge.
I'm movin' in, spike.
Sergeant Gray,
my name's Sam braddock.
I was hoping you could tell me
what's going on today.
Call it a humanitarian mission.
Firing on police,
stealing money from banks?
You were never at risk.
The money was gonna
be destroyed.
The banks were insured.
The only real victims here
are the men and women
I'm tryin' to take care of.
Spike, is there any
way to take this guy down?
Can't get close enough.
Taser, shields -
whatever we use...
he'll see us coming,
drop the grenade and...
That's the car!
We're closing in! Let's go!
This is it.
Where's the guy
who's supposed to meet us?
Sarge said sixteen hundred.
He's on his way with the keys.
Today, my teammates
spoke to a lot of people
who think you're a great man.
They're wrong.
I'm just doing my job.
That's what sergeants
always say.
Folks, clear out of the way.
Leah, right there.
Go around, get behind them.
Ma'am, clear out of the way,
please.
You serve? Yes, sir.
I never met a sergeant
who didn't impress me.
Today, you gotta lead
by example.
Don't put your team at risk.
Let's end this.
It should have been me.
What?
Look, I'm the expendable one.
Give me a chance to prove myself
on that bridge
doing something.
You heard sarge.
Let's just get this done.
Leah?
Almost there.
Go now.
S.R.U.! Police!
S.R.U., don't move!
Don't move!
Hands where I can see them!
Don't!
Don't make me.
Just let us go!
Can't do that.
Forbes.
Look, I don't like
what you did today,
but I understand it.
We do our duty,
we serve and protect,
and we're there for each other.
I get that.
Yeah, when no one else will.
Come on, buddy,
step away from the bag.
Just step away.
Doug, don't!
It's over.
Thank you.
Leah.
Subjects contained.
I've just been told
we've captured
the rest of your team.
You're lying.
No, sir. All three
of them at the marina
and they're unharmed.
All I wanted to do
was give 'em a chance.
I understand,
but there's gotta be
another way.
You're right, there is.
Sam, what's goin' on?
How's sergeant Gray?
We're workin' on it.
I really let him
down, you know that?
You did the right thing.
No, he needed to make this work.
It was the last chance we had.
What are you sayin'?
Sergeant Gray,
that's not a good idea!
Sam, body language.
He's not surrendering,
potential suicide.
Okay, let's just keep talking,
all right?
Those men and women,
they're gonna need you.
Don't come any closer.
Boss, I just got off the phone
with Gray's bank.
The death benefit, the pension,
it all goes to camp if he dies.
It doesn't matter
the cause of death,
it still pays out.
How much?
About a half a million dollars.
Sam, knife's edge here.
This isn't who you are!
This isn't how you want people
to remember you.
Yes it is!
- This is exactly-
Doing what needs to be done.
Look at me, sergeant Gray!
Sammy, get back.
Too close!
Sergeant Gray, listen to me.
You tried to do
a good thing today.
You've been trying to help
for months.
He's within twenty feet.
Even with body armour,
he's way too close.
Sam...
You need to stay back.
Even with the money,
I don't get it.
His pride, his honour...
He's not the type of guy
to kill himself.
I know. We're missin' something.
Eddie?
I hear you, boss.
Look, you wanted to help
sergeant Gray,
now's the time to do it.
What do you mean?
He's not giving up.
His life is in danger.
Seconds count.
We gotta move fast.
Okay, what can I do?
Give us a way in.
Now I heard Gray's life
was falling apart
when he left the army.
What happened?
It was his wife.
She left him?
She was pregnant
with their first kid.
He was so happy.
It was great to see him smile.
We were supposed
to get a leave,
but then we got extended.
It was an accident.
She fell.
She hit her head.
Nobody thought anything
was wrong,
but then the next day
they found her.
She died in her sleep,
some sort of rupture
in her brain.
The baby died too.
He felt that if he'd...
if he'd have been there,
he could've found her,
saved her life.
- Sam, you get that?
- Yeah.
He feels like he
can't fail at his mission.
Without it...
He'd have to think
about his past,
all the people he's lost.
Sergeant Gray,
you say you've been doing this
for all the men and women
who need help,
but it's not just about them.
It's about you, too.
When I was a kid,
my little sister was killed
in an accident.
I was there, I saw it happen.
Ripped a hole
in the middle of my life,
but it's not like I could
talk about it at home.
My dad's a general,
my mom's a good army wife.
The orders from the top
of my family
were to deal with it
and move on.
So my dad dove into his work -
longer tours, longer hours.
My mom did
the civilian version...
P.T.A., volunteering.
And I thought...
"How can they get over it
so fast?
How can they not even
talk about her?"
'Cause it hurt too much.
They were just trying
to do anything
but spend time in the house,
anything but be reminded
of what happened.
It's a noble cause
you're fighting for, sergeant,
but it also keeps you
from thinking about
the people you've lost,
the people
you couldn't protect.
All I can picture is...
My wife, Kathryn,
alone...
Lying there,
no one to help her.
Without this...
What do I do?
You forgive yourself
and you remember her...
not for the soldiers,
not for them,
for you.
Thank you.
♪ It seems like the world
has come undone ♪
♪ and so much is said
so little done ♪
♪ it's in the hands of you
and me ♪
♪ to leave behind a legacy ♪
♪ a home for those to come ♪
♪ the politicians of this world
don't own ya ♪
♪ they're breedin' lies
it's their disguised persona ♪
♪ it's up to you
to make a choice ♪
♪ so go ahead
and use your voice ♪
♪ the time to stand is now ♪
♪ 'cause there's still fields
that cover up the pain ♪
♪ it's where
the children play... ♪
The latest news from Italy.
Your mother is single-handedly
keeping the post office
in business.
This time she waits
till the third line
to ask before
I'm coming to visit.
Aw.
You wanna be my wing man,
keep all my aunts from wondering
why I'm still single?
What's in it for me?
All the homemade wine
you can drink.
I'm listening.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
Jules.
Hey, boss...
Yeah?
You're a father.
I am.
Do you find it hard
being a cop?
You mean not knowing when
you'll come home at night,
if you'll come home at all;
trying to stay involved
in your kid's life;
trying to protect 'em;
not being able to arrest
the kids
that are mean to 'em?
It's a piece of cake.
You and Sam thinking about it?
It's come up.
You'll make a good mom, Jules.
Do you think
I'll still make a good cop?
Do you need me to answer that?
Uncle spike, Uncle Ed,
we'll have that kid's back.
Yeah, you too.
Okay, dinner it is.
I'll give you the rest
of the details then.
Thanks.
That was my dad.
The army knows guys like that
are still slippin'
through the cracks.
Any way he can help 'em out?
Well, he's gotta wait and see,
but he thinks maybe
they can buy the house,
leave it in Gray's name.
It's a small price to pay.
That's what he thinks.
Nice work, Sam.
Hey.
What's wrong?
You were right,
it does change things.
I could've lost you today.
Jules, you could
lose me any day.
I know. I get that part.
Though the two of us
could've lost you today.
How do you think
I would have feel
if that was you out there?
I can't tell you
not to do your job.
And I can't tell you either.
We gotta tell the team.
Tomorrow.
♪ It's not so hard
to realize the truth... ♪
Go to the store
and get bubble wrap?
Yeah? And some tea?
Herbal?
I could use a cup.
Okay.
== sync, corrected by Martzy ==
www.Addic7ed.Com