Kate!
I need you to open this door
right now!
Ungh!
Don't do this!
You're too close to this thing!
You're not seeing this right.
A couple more of those,
detective...
And I'll open right up.
Now I need you
to open the door.
Boss, visual's up.
No, Kate!
Sometimes I wonder
what you would think
about this.
You would make a joke,
that much I know.
You'd tease me about it...
about me being here,
talking to a hunk of stone.
I know people talk about grief
and...
They say that it takes time.
I'm waiting, Evan.
It doesn't seem fair though,
right?
That the 3 years
you have been gone
take up so much more
of my heart
than the seventeen
we spent together.
You shouldn't be here.
No one knows I'm here.
He'd be 21 today.
It doesn't go away, does it?
You know what I miss?
Luke, please.
We can't do this.
You know,
I have something for you.
That bike chain bracelet
Evan made,
it's been broken
for the longest time.
I finally got around
to replacing the pin.
He wore it every day.
He'd want you to have it.
You keep it.
It's yours.
Mrs. A, I think...
this can't happen again.
Where is he?
Briefing room.
Hold up. Take a breath.
A street fight, Ed?
We don't know the details.
I spoke to Terry from 52.
He took the call,
a bunch of kids fighting.
Someone swinging
a hockey stick.
Apparently. What's he
doing getting mixed up
in stuff like that? Greg,
you're gonna ask him.
You're damn
right, I'm gonna...
All right, hold up.
You go in hot right now,
it's not gonna help
the situation at all.
Well, I don't wanna help
the situation.
I wanna take a paddle
to the little punk.
When does this get easier?
Well, I hear that they become
a little more manageable
when they're... They're 40.
Hey, you know that
beemer that came in yesterday?
The Enduro?
Yeah. Got it running.
The engine was full
of sand, it was shot.
- It was.
- That's it, sweetie.
Now it's not.
You're a genius,
kid, you know that?
When I was your age,
it would've taken me weeks.
'Course things were
different then.
Yeah. Horsepower
was actual horses...
Coal was the way of the future.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't get cocky, smartass.
Sorry, honey.
You didn't hear that,
all right?
Hi. Steven.
Boss?
Look, uh, sweetie,
I want you to go out
in the backyard, okay?
Play with the other kids,
all right?
You have fun.
Hey, I hear there's a meet
and greet in Chatham.
New clients.
Yeah? Where'd you hear that?
All I'm saying is,
now that I've been promoted,
maybe I should come.
Yeah, we'll see.
Luke, get back here!
Come on, Luke!
Hey.
Ahh...
You okay?
I didn't start it.
Team one, hot call!
Look, go home.
Ice it, all right?
We'll talk later, all right?
Dad, I didn't start it.
Dean, you know what?
The older I get,
the less that matters to me.
Just go home. Now.
Car bomb,
284 Mapledawn Road.
Suspect fled on a motorcycle,
last seen headed eastbound
on Bloor.
Reports of a blue El Camino
in pursuit.
Spike, Jules, scene
of the explosion.
Sam, Leah,
let's find that bike.
There you are...
Winnie, how far away is EMS?
They just passed east mall.
Over here, please!
My daughter...
What's her name?
Alex. It's her leg.
Alex, can you hear me?
Clear back! Stay back! Back!
That's shrapnel
from the explosion.
Looks like she twisted it
when she fell.
Vehicle spotted
at Queensway and Kipling.
We're close.
Sam, come north;
We'll close him in.
Copy that.
Yeah, it's me.
Listen, there was a bomb.
They got Steven.
Yeah, I'm on the Queensway
following the guy.
Ah, dammit.
What's happening?!
Alex, can you hear me?
Alex?
Hypovolemic shock;
She's lost a lot of blood.
Just hold this down here.
Okay...
Keep the pressure on.
Okay!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
Alex?
1, 2, 3...
Boss, the bomb went off
at a children's birthday party.
Two deceased -
Mary-Ann and Steven Miller.
Alex! Alex, can you hear me?
1, 2, 3...
Keep the pressure on!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
Come on, Alex.
Alex, can you hear me?
Can you hear me, Alex?
What... what happened?
You're gonna be okay.
Thank God...
Ma'am, she's in good hands,
okay?
Can you tell me
what happened here today?
Sorry. Ma'am?
I can't.
Team one, another sighting -
Queen East.
Heading north -
we're blocks away.
What did you get, Jules?
It doesn't add up.
Assassination, broad daylight,
a house full of kids.
Like someone's making a point.
Yeah, but to who?
This place says
welcome to Mayberry.
Did you get anything
from witnesses?
That's the other thing.
A house full of people
and nobody saw a thing.
Yeah, I got the same thing
from the kid's mom.
Something's not right.
Think it's a hobby?
No. I think we're
dealing with bikers.
Boss, the hosts of this party
are members of the Brigadier
Motorcycle Club.
Okay, team, extreme caution.
Copy that.
Boss, I got a call
from detective Kate Andrews,
organized crime division.
Not a good time, Winnie.
She says it's urgent.
Direct order;
You're to take the call.
Sergeant Parker?
Listen, detective,
I'm in the middle
of a bomb investigation
and chasing two
gangland soldiers.
No, one gangland soldier.
The young man in the car
works for me.
He's a CI. He's my asset.
We got gunfire.
Agh!
== sync, corrected by Martzy ==
www.Addic7ed.Com
Sam, Leah, go
direct to gunfire,
we're coming north.
Stop! Right there, stop!
Sam, we've got an active
shooter coming your way.
Ungh!
I think you got him.
You doing all right, son?
Yeah.
Winnie, I need you
to connect me to...
Luke! Luke!
Never mind.
Detective Andrews?
Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I'm fine, Mrs. A.
What the hell
were you thinking, huh?
You could've been killed.
Well, I was trying
to keep eyes on the guy,
like you said.
I said stay clear.
Get intel, but stay clear.
Mrs. A, he ambushed me.
Detective
Andrews, I'm Greg Parker.
This is Ed Lane.
How're you doing?
That man killed
in the explosion...
Steven Miller...
is he a member
of the Brigadiers?
He was the leader.
What does that
tell you, detective?
Is this a war? Looks that way.
The Brigadiers have been
expanding their operations,
they've been encroaching
on rival turf.
Which rivals?
Another bike
club - Devil's Guard.
They run a lot of meth,
weapons, extortion...
all areas the brigs
have been getting into.
Detective, the bomber
didn't have any patches
or any gang markings
or anything.
Now you're thinking old-school.
Nowadays, these guys keep
a white-collar profile.
They mow their lawns.
They send their kids
to French immersion.
The hogs and the leathers,
they only come out
on special occasions.
The shooter's not talking.
No ID.
I'm sending you a photo now.
Devil's Guard?
Could've brought him in
from another chapter,
hired someone unaffiliated.
I found something
in the bombers jacket.
An IED detonator.
It's rf controlled.
Short range, maybe 200 feet.
Why a kid's party?
Send a message.
Devil's Guard letting us know,
"we can get you any place,
any time..."
It's Brian.
Hey, Brian.
Yeah, I know, I'm sorry,
I just, I...
I wanted to get the guy,
but the cops showed up.
No, no, no. I got outta there,
made myself scarce.
Okay. Yeah, you got it.
Walter's called
an emergency meeting,
right now, at the clubhouse.
They want me there.
Well, that's not
happening, so relax.
You know the dynamics,
detective,
what's your guess?
They're gonna hit back.
Walter McHale was
second in command.
Now he's the lead,
and he is not one
to back down from a fight.
Then we get ahead of it.
We bust open
their headquarters.
We don't have the evidence.
These guys are pros.
They don't store weapons
on site,
and they keep
their noses clean.
8 months I've been
all over them...
not one single piece
of actionable intel.
Send me back in.
I mean,
if we're gonna hit back,
I can get a time and place,
that's actionable, right?
Detective, I don't...
I don't wanna step
on your case here,
but you can't be
considering this.
Everyone in that clubhouse
is going to be amped up
and on high alert.
In his state right now,
can your CI keep playing the part?
What do you say, Luke?
You up for this?
Look, this could be the chance
we've been waiting for.
Get Brian, Walter, all of them.
You gotta let me try.
'Kay, let's wire him.
He's going in.
It gets hot, we can
bust that place wide open.
Spike, Jules,
all hands on deck.
We got razor wire,
crash barriers,
cameras at every entrance.
Door's reinforced steel.
Yeah, no
element of surprise.
Unless we make
our own doors.
Okay, the north
wall's got no cams.
We stay out of line of sight.
Breach charges. Jules with me.
Sam, Leah, up top. Let's move.
Luke's belt buckle comes
with a mic and a GPS tracker,
so we can hear everything
and know where he is
at all times.
It doesn't show.
Not unless you're really,
really looking for it.
They'll ask you what
happened with the bomber.
You keep your story simple,
stick as close to the truth
as possible.
Distress code is "bad deal."
Okay, yeah, I got it.
Bad deal.
Oh, uh, check,
check, check, hello, goodbye.
Good to go.
Luke,
my team will be outside.
If anything goes wrong,
you just stay down,
we'll get you out safe, okay?
Do you know what your job
in there is, son?
Bring down the Brigadiers. No.
You get us a time
and the place of the retaliation
and that's it.
You get out, all right?
You don't go anywhere else,
you don't take any assignments,
understood?
Understood.
All right.
Okay...
So far so good.
We need to talk.
Now.
I'm not liking this.
He's okay... He's okay.
Luke.
We got a problem.
Eddie, standby for my go.
Alpha team in position.
Bravo team in position.
Walter, what's the problem?
Shut up.
Brian, come on, what
the hell's going on here?
The man told you to shut up,
Luke.
Brian gave
you a direct order to stay,
so you take off.
That guy killed Steve,
I had to try and get-
- Alpha team...
- Wait!
He hasn't given the signal.
He's fine.
He gave you an order!
Are you a brigadier, Luke?
Are you one of us?!
Look, I know I screwed up.
But I did this for Steve,
for the Brigadiers.
You don't like that,
you better kick me out now.
Because if someone
comes at us again,
I'm gonna do
the same damn thing.
All I needed to hear.
Get the guys together.
That's a brave kid.
Yeah, he is.
Look I was meaning to ask...
"Mrs. A?"
Luke called you that
in the alley.
I've known Luke
for a long time.
Friend of my son's.
Luke didn't have
an ideal family life,
so he came over a lot.
You know how that can be.
Sure.
What's your son think of this...
you and his friend
working together?
My son died three years ago.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Was he ill?
Boating accident.
Well, that must've been
difficult.
It was.
Walter you've all heard
what's happened.
It's a real shame.
It's a tragedy
that it had to come to this.
This club is at a crossroads -
you all know that.
We all loved
and respected Steve.
He was our president,
our friend, our brother.
But he was blind...
Blind to our enemies,
blind to our opportunities...
Doesn't sound like
a war speech, does it?
This is the point I
was trying to make with Steve
for months now.
Many of you have.
Sorry to say...
He never did see the light.
I wish that he had,
I really do,
but take a look around you,
gentlemen.
See who's here, who isn't here.
These are your real brothers,
the ones standing beside you
right now.
Everybody else...
Like I said, crossroads.
Some of us will be going
in one direction,
some of us in another.
Anybody got a problem
with that?
He's not talking about
going to battle.
He's talking
about taking over.
He's talking about a purge.
If he's announcing it,
it's already in motion.
How many targets
are still out there?
And where?
Geez, Brian...
Just keep your mouth
shut and your head down, okay?
You'll be fine.
Karl's not here. I know.
Dennis, Richard...
Are they all dead?
Good work, Luke.
Karl Borance, Dennis Barber,
Richard Breed.
Who are they?
Loyalists - of Steven Miller,
the assassinated
Brigadiers leader...
and now marked men.
Okay, team,
you heard the news.
The Brigadiers are
cleaning house.
We've got three targets.
Spike's sending you photos.
Spike, home
numbers, cell phones.
On it.
If you wanted to
take out three guys
without tipping your plan...
Make sure they're together.
And we know these guys
love bombs.
Spike!
No answers
at home or at work.
Cell phones are off,
but I'm getting a GPS ping back
from Karl Borance's phone.
He's southeast from here.
That's Dennis Barber's
restaurant.
It's downtown, lunch hour.
Pretty brash move.
Not if they're trying
to play it off as a gang war.
Gives them deniability.
Well, they've
shown they're not worried
about collateral damage.
Let's move.
Hey, I'm gonna stay back,
make sure Luke gets out
all right.
What's going on?
I don't know,
something about this...
Ed, you go. I got it.
Go.
Winnie, detective Andrews' son,
what can you tell me about him?
Evan Andrews.
Died at 17
in a boating accident.
The file's sealed
because the parties involved
were minors at the time.
'Kay, contact the officer
that was there.
Maybe he can give us
some more information.
Sure.
Team, schematics of the
restaurant coming at you.
Spike, break this down for me.
If we're dealing with
the same tech,
how's this go?
Real simple;
Bomber plants the device,
waits for the targets
to show up,
presses a button.
It hasn't gone off yet.
What does that tell us?
Best case,
someone had a change of heart.
More likely...
All three of the targets
aren't in place yet.
So we call ahead,
start clearing the place.
Unless we supervise
the evacuation ourselves,
it's too risky.
Patrons start running
out of there,
it's gonna cue the bomber.
He's gonna take out whatever
target's are already there.
And we show up with
the sirens blaring...
same story.
You all right?
Yeah.
These aren't easy times.
Had to be done, right?
Okay,
let's bring your guy in.
Hang on. Something's up.
Tell you what...
Walter and I have a loose end
to tie up.
You wanna be part of it?
I mean, you said you wanted
to step up.
Well, today would be
a good day for it...
chance to prove yourself
to the new regime.
Luke, no. Say no.
You know what? Never mind.
You've had a hell of a day.
Yeah.
I'm in.
No. No, no, no.
What's he doing?
He's giving us Walter;
That's what he's doing.
Not the plan, detective.
Listen to me.
This is our chance.
They're going on
an assassination run.
Which is why we
have to let it play out...
to protect the target.
You mean arrest your man.
Yes! Yeah, that too.
Sergeant,
nothing that happened today
can be traced back to Walter.
So far he can just walk away
from all of it.
If he orders this hit,
then we've finally got him.
My investigation, my call.
Eddie, CI's on the move
and we're following.
What's your twenty?
Boss, we're almost
at the restaurant.
Hang back, sergeant.
Tracking signal's strong.
We'll follow at a distance.
I know you think
I'm pushing him,
but you really have
to trust me.
He knows what he's doing
and this is what he wants.
Yeah? How can
you be sure of that?
Because I didn't recruit him.
He came to me.
He wanted to be a CI?
No, he wanted to change
his life around.
He knew I could help.
Well, you were the parent
in his life.
You had mentioned it earlier
that he didn't have
a very strong home life
and that he was
at your house a lot.
I helped out where I could.
He must have been grateful.
Sometimes.
Okay, team, listen up.
Sam, you're on the trigger man.
This guy's gotta have
a sight line to the restaurant.
I want you to find him
and stop him.
All right, I'm on it.
Leah, you're with me.
Back service door.
Let's clear the place out
quick and quiet
without tipping him off.
Got it!
Jules, you're out front.
No lights, no sirens.
You're looking for
the targeted bikers.
Keeping 'em out
buys us more time inside.
Copy. Spike?
Let me guess. I'm on bomb?
You're on bomb.
There was one summer where
Evan and Luke got jobs at a garage.
Brian Novak was their boss,
and when I got wind
of his affiliation
with the Brigadiers,
I... I just hit the roof.
I went driving over there,
and I marched
both those boys out,
one in each hand.
I guess I thought
Luke got the message,
but um... A few months ago,
in the middle of the night,
Luke showed up at the station.
Luke, it's 2 in the morning.
What're you doing here?
Whose is that?
Mine...
How long?
Couple years...
I got patched in this week.
No, no, don't do that.
You just joined
a violent criminal gang...
these are the people
I spend my whole life
trying to put away.
Look, I'm in over my head,
Mrs. A.
It's not...
It's not at all
what I thought it would be.
Okay...
Look, I'm a fully patched
member of the Brigadiers.
I've got names, locations,
jobs.
I can give you all of it.
He wanted out...
He realized he'd made
a mistake,
and he wanted my help
making things right.
You gotta
be clear about this, Luke.
You go through this door,
you can't come back.
You understand that, right?
I'm ready.
So who are we gonna see,
anyway?
Ron.
Who is it?
Ron McHale.
Walter's own cousin.
Not a full-time member,
but still involved.
Always got along with Steven,
and I should have
seen this coming.
Yeah, I need
units at Ron McHale's house...
plain clothes, unmarked cars -
right away.
No. Go!
Yep.
Walter, it's Ron.
You were right.
Okay. Got it.
That was Ron.
He's got company.
Luke's cover's blown.
What're you talking about?
It was a set-up, it was a test.
They suspected he was wired
and they fed us bad intel.
No! They would've searched him
in the clubhouse.
And we would've busted in
and saved him.
Oh my God.
Let's move! Go, go!
Everyone, can I have
your attention please!
This is a police emergency.
I need you to stay calm
and exit through
the back door, please.
Exit through the back door!
Let's go, folks!
Folks, please, now! Do it now!
Let's go, ladies, let's go!
Here we go!
Through the back
of the building!
It's an emergency, folks!
If I can have you up and out!
Up and out!
Let's go, people, let's go!
Spike - there!
Mr. Barber? Yes.
- This your restaurant?
- What's this all about?
- This your usual table?
- Yes.
You need to get outta here,
right now!
Your lives are in danger.
Go! Go!
Okay, two of
the targets are coming out.
Got the bomb!
Jules, the missing
target is Richard Breed.
The bomber's waiting
for Richard Breed.
Copy.
Where are you...?
Okay, they're headed
north - just up there.
Okay, turn right.
Leave it! Drop everything!
Now! Come on!
Let's go! Let's go,
gentlemen, let's go, now!
Ed, he's here!
He's down the block;
I can't intercept him
without the trigger man
seeing me.
How long?
Sixty seconds - he's
halfway down the block.
We're not clear yet!
Sam, anything?
Nothing.
Oh God...
I got him.
Thirty seconds, Ed.
Ed, when you clear out
the restaurant,
clear out the kitchen
and the street out front.
Fifteen seconds, Ed.
Digital counter-measure;
I'm not gonna be able
to move it!
Ten seconds, Ed.
I gotta go.
Richard Breed!
Let's go! Stay down!
Take cover!
Detonator... charges...
Do not go in there!
Stay where you are!
Power supply.
Drop it!
Bomb defused!
Keep your hands
where I can see 'em!
There!
Show me your hands!
Do it now!
Luke!
Where is he?!
Ungh! Where is he?
I'd like to
talk to my lawyer.
Ungh!
Where is he, Brian?!
Detective, you
need to step away.
Not now, Parker!
Kate, I know this is hard.
But we need clear heads
right now.
Keep him
inside and watch him.
You got it.
Okay, Eddie, talk to me.
Boss, we're clear.
The targets are safe,
bomber's in custody.
Okay, new priority.
Walter's got Luke.
He knows he's been working
for the cops,
so we need to find him,
and find him fast.
Let me see what I can get.
Where's Walter?
This is time sensitive!
Where is he?
Save your breath,
it's not gonna happen.
Hey, we can
protect you from him.
Ed.
Getting nowhere
with the targets either.
Just saved their lives,
and they're still not talking.
Okay, okay.
Boss, you getting that?
We got a whole lot
of nothing here.
Anything?
No.
Okay, spike, let's run down
brigadier properties,
known hideouts,
business affiliations.
On it!
Out!
No, I don't need you. Out.
You don't remember me, do you?
The Andrews kid.
You're his mom.
You stormed into my shop
that day.
That's right.
You should have told me
you were a cop.
I was there as a mother.
Oh, so you're the one
who turned Luke?
Oof!
I'll take that as a yes.
She inside?
*** you know, Luke
could be dead.
Are you good with that?
He'd be safe
if he'd stayed in line.
I need you to
open this door right now!
A couple more of those, detective...
And I'll open right up.
Tell me where Luke is!
Spike, the internal
command truck camera...
can you patch it to me?
On it, boss.
Kate?!
Don't do this!
You're too close to this thing.
You're not seeing this right.
Now I need you
to open the door.
Boss, visual's up.
No, Kate!
Tell me where Luke is,
or I will end you.
Kate, you harm him,
we're no closer
to finding Luke!
Come on, lady,
listen to your boss out there.
I don't have a boss, Brian.
In case you haven't noticed
I just love to force.
Boss, I got that
information you asked for.
Fast, Winnie.
I spoke to an officer
who was on the scene
the night
of Evan Andrew's death.
Luke Mathers was there.
Okay...
He was the one
driving the boat.
Look, I have a
family, all right?
It was a freak accident.
A piling had broken free
and drifted out into the lake,
but alcohol was a factor.
If I cross Walter,
then no one's left untouched,
and you know that!
When help arrived,
they found Luke
near the overturned boat.
He was half-drowned,
hypothermic,
diving down over and over.
Trying to find Evan,
trying to save him.
Don't you dare
talk to me about family!
I have a kid!
They had to forcibly
pull Luke out of the water.
He's blaming himself...
And maybe now Luke's
trying to make amends.
Yeah.
Thanks, Winnie.
Kate, I'm coming in!
Kate!
Kate...
We still need
answers; Give him some air.
Okay, the Brigadiers have
ties to two construction companies,
some commercial real estate,
a demolition business.
Gives them access to properties
all over the city.
Okay, let's start
crossing them off.
Winnie, I need every
available unit!
Copy that.
Just lower the gun.
Let's talk about
what's happening here.
Come on.
I have to save Luke.
He wanted out,
I pushed him in further.
No. No, you didn't.
He didn't come to you for help.
Yes - to get outta
the Brigadiers, he'd...
No. He came to get
you back into his life.
What?
That night at
the police station
wasn't a plea for help.
That was a gift - all of it...
it was a gift.
Joining the Brigadiers,
getting patched in,
he did it all for you -
to serve them up.
Now why would he do that?
To give you
something that you wanted.
To atone...
The only way he knew how,
because he blamed himself
for Evan's death,
because he felt guilty
for surviving,
and because he wanted you back.
No...
Let's try this again.
You need to tell me exactly
what the police know.
It's over, Walter.
You're done.
I pushed him away.
You were grieving, Kate.
You were facing a pain
that no person
should have to endure.
What you did was natural.
I let him endanger himself.
Hey, and now we're gonna
find him, all right?
Do you wanna do right by Luke?
Then you'll be there
when we do.
Give me the gun. Come on.
Come on.
Let's go find Luke.
Thank you, Kate.
Thank you.
You see that cruiser, Brian?
Yeah.
We're gonna walk to it,
which means you've got
30 seconds to change your mind.
Or what? You gonna
wave a bigger gun in my face?
Just be quiet, Brian.
This is a listening walk
for you.
Richard Breed is alive.
So is Karl Borance
and Dennis Barber.
Your coup failed.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You backed the wrong guy,
Brian.
Walter's going down,
I promise you that.
We will get him,
and when we do...
Where does that leave you?
That's a hell
of an enemies list:
Brigadiers, Devil's Guard,
and us - the cops.
Now, if I were you,
I'd think real hard
about which one of these groups
is least likely
to kill your family
in the night,
and then I might try
to ally myself with them.
Walk's over. Get in.
Wait...
You'll protect my family?
We will.
- The Matador Ballroom.
- Eddie, Batador Ballroom.
Spike?
Got it.
The old Windemere hotel...
one of the brigadier's
demolition contracts.
4108 Dovercourt.
We're close.
Winnie, have all
units fall back,
wait for the SRU to approach.
Copy that.
Based on the floor
plan, three points of entry.
Spike, Sam, take the west
wall; Leah, take the east;
Jules and I'll take the South.
Good to go.
All right, enough.
We're done.
Two armed subjects,
threat level red.
Breach on my go.
Three...
It didn't have
to go like this, Luke.
Two...
Do it.
One.
Go!
Right there! Put the guns down!
Police! Drop your weapon!
On the ground! Do it now!
Get on the ground now!
Drop your weapon now!
Drop it!
Now! Down on the ground!
Down on the ground! Get down!
All right!
Gimme your arm, put
it behind your back.
Behind your back!
Subjects secure.
We have Walter McHale
in custody.
We got you, buddy.
We got you.
♪ it's not safe here anymore ♪
♪ there's too much damage
to ignore ♪
♪ I've spun in circles,
I'm confused ♪
♪ if no one wins,
does no one lose ♪
You got them, right?
The Brigadiers...
you can take 'em all down,
right?
Got 'em.
Okay.
Luke, I need you to know...
I never blamed you
for Evan dying.
Mrs. A, I was the one driving...
no, no, no, listen to me,
please.
Luke, I pushed you away.
- I am so sorry.
- You're sorry?
I was in pain,
and I was confused,
and I turned my back on you...
Luke, you've got nothing
to make up for.
We both lost someone
that night,
and now I know
what you've always known...
The only way through this
is together.
I'm ready now, Luke. Okay?
♪ we never learn to bend ♪
♪ so we break and break again ♪
♪ and now we're broken in ♪
Well, thank you for
calling, I appreciate it.
Oh yeah, will do.
'Kay, bye.
So a 14-year-old kid's
walking home through the park
when he gets jumped
by four older guys.
Do you know how
this story ends?
I have some idea.
With a good samaritan
stepping in
to fight off the attackers.
Who told you that?
Kid's mom.
She called you a hero.
Is he all right, that kid?
Yeah - a couple broken ribs,
but he'll be fine.
How does that feel -
being called a hero?
Okay, I gotta ask you, Dean.
Why?
Why step in?
This kid's a stranger.
Those guys might've had knives.
Why take the chance?
You need me
to explain that to you?
I do.
I dunno, I guess it was...
Something I saw
in the kid's eyes.
Kid on the ground?
No. One of the guys
doing the kicking.
I could tell he was...
Confused or...
Afraid.
Like it was all just happening
and he was caught up in it.
Anyway, I just...
Kinda felt bad for him.
Does that make sense?
Yeah, it makes sense.
Hey...
You know, that's gonna
look worse tomorrow, right?
That's what they say.
Yeah.
♪ We never learn to bend ♪
♪ so we break and break again ♪
♪ and now we're broken in ♪
♪ too many pieces to mend ♪
♪ oh, too many pieces to mend ♪
== sync, corrected by Martzy ==
www.Addic7ed.Com