We need to go now.
The vents aren't on.
Spike: The venting system
must've been knocked off-line
when Xavier sabotaged
the power generator.
Woman:
My leg!
I can't feel my leg!
(Pained cry)
Sam: The pathogen meter's
900 and rising.
Woman:
Anything over 2500's fatal.
2500...
Sam: She needs medical
attention, okay?
You all do.
You need to let everybody out
now.
Jules?
Jules!
Jules! Jules!
(Bag rustles)
(Door beeps)
That's a test subject?
Yes.
It's not contained.
I did.
I double bagged it.
You double seal it,
and then you put it
in a container.
The subject may be dead,
but the pathogens
that killed it
are very much alive,
understand?
- Be careful.
- I'm sorry, sir.
(Keypad beeps, airlock hisses)
(Phone rings)
Greg Parker.
Dr. Toth, hello.
Very well, thank you.
How are you?
Okay.
You wanna a tell me why?
Yes, I know what it's in there.
Ben, incident report last
month, the 17th.
No, that can't be right.
Hey.
Set it up in the briefing room.
Ben:
You got it.
Yeah, I'll be here.
(Lock clanks)
Gunman: Down on your knees!
Don't turn around!
Hands behind your back!
(Exhales)
Dammit!
What's going on?
Parker: They forgot
to turn their mics off.
Jules and Sam.
I thought they were done.
Well, they're not.
That was the condition,
when she rejoined the team.
- I know.
- Priority of life.
I gotta tell you, Eddie,
I knew it was happening.
How long?
Two months.
And I made the choice
to let it go on.
What happened to
no mo secrets, Greg?
This way, it's just on me.
It's not your job, it's mine.
It's your job?
What do you mean?
When Dr. Toth put this team
on probation
I gave him my word
that Sam and Jules
wouldn't cross the line.
Well, what's he gonna do?
Greg?
(Keypad beeps)
Gunman:
On the ground!
Turn around!
Hands behind your back!
All right, up! Up!
Come on, move it!
Move it!
Ben: Team one, hot call.
Gear up.
- Go.
- What do you mean? What's going on?
I got no choice.
- Greg!
- Go. Just go.
I don't want the team
distracted by this.
Go!
(Hot call siren blares)
(Sirens wail)
Ed:
What're we looking at, Spike?
All right, it's a level three
biohazard research facility.
Meaning what?
Spike: Well, meaning it's classified.
But hold on.
Okay, here we go.
Private company,
study biological agents
and develop vaccines.
Terrorist target?
Spike:
It's on the watch list.
Oh man...
Viruses, toxins, pathogens,
all kinds e exotic bacterias.
This stuff gets out,
it's like biological WMD's
with mass casualties.
Ed: Okay, okay. Ben?
Ben: Go ahead.
We need a Hazmat team
with a decontamination unit.
Full community evac...
Uh, Spike?
Spike:
Uh... two kilometers.
Ed: Two kilometer radius.
EMS on scene, please.
Ben: Got it.
And I've got RDA's CEO,
Dr. Henry Bergan,
on the line.
Ed: Okay, Ben, thank you.
Put him through.
Ben:
Patching him in now.
Doctor, it's Ed Lane, SRU.
Bergan:
Officer, I just heard.
I was on my way downtown.
I'm at least 40 minutes away
from the lab.
Ed: Who's in charge
of the facility now?
Rose Gilvrey.
She's our CFO.
Rose is extremely capable,
she can give you
everything you need.
Okay, thank you.
Appreciate it.
Officer,
I don't know if you're aware,
but our facility...
If the wrong person
were to get their hands
on our materials...
Ed:
We're aware.
Bergan: All it would
take is a subway car,
an office building,
a vent.
Ed: Doctor, best thing
you can do right now
is to let us handle it.
Keep your phone handy,
we'll call you if we need you.
Thank you.
(Sirens wail)
Rose: Officer. Rose Gilvrey.
Rose, is this building
fully evacuated?
Apart from
the central personnel.
We need everybody
outta there now.
Tests are still in progress
in the lab.
Samples of sensitive materials
have to be properly contained.
Well, how many people
we talking about here?
Two: Our chief scientist
and his second,
and they'll be done
as soon as possible.
Ed: Okay, any word from
the security guard?
Rose: No, but one of our
workers was found tied up
in the waste disposal lockup.
Okay, did he get
any descriptions?
No, he was attacked
from behind;
he didn't see a thing.
Sam: Can you confirm
how many intruders
we're dealing with?
(Gunshots pop)
Sam: Shots fired!
Jules: All right, get back!
You guys, back, back, back!
Ed: Ben, we got shots fired.
Active shooter.
Ben:
Copy.
Ed: Let's get ems down
here immediately.
We're gonna try to locate
and extract any of the victims.
Rose?
Can you help us out
with staging area inside?
Rose:
I've brought you passcards.
Keep them on your person.
These give you access
to the entire building.
I would advise that you don't go
into the clean room
until they're done.
Ed: Okay. Spike, you ready?
Let's move.
Sam...
Let's do it.
Power's out.
Rose:
This shouldn't be happening.
We have precautions
against blackouts.
Sam:
You have backup generators?
Rose: Of course, but every
second of downtime's dangerous.
What's going on, Ben?
Ben: Active shooter.
No confirmed victims yet.
Just keep me informed,
all right?
Sure thing, boss.
Greg, I'm sorry to do this.
Do what?
I'm here to suspend you
from duty.
Sync and corrections by
www.addic7ed.com
Rose, where was the gunman
last seen?
Right there.
And he took the guard
in that direction.
Essential personnel?
There, in the clean room.
Laboratory one.
Okay, Jules, head to the lab,
escort those workers out.
Rose, tell your team
we're on our way.
Guys, with me.
Let's move.
Spike, get Rose to help us
into the mainframe.
Parker:
Suspended.
I was expecting
a bigger reaction.
Parker:
Conditionally? Permanently? What?
Toth:
That will depend on you.
Team one's probation period
is now over.
But...
I'm left with two
major concerns.
One is your judgment
as sergeant,
regarding the relationship
between Callaghan and Braddock,
which you made the choice
to conceal.
That's right.
The other concern,
equally critical
to your team's safety,
is your judgment
of your own judgment.
Second guessing,
self-doubt...
This is the subtext
of all your reports,
transcripts,
self-evaluations.
You openly question
your own decision-making.
How can you captain a ship,
if you've lost
your own compass?
Any rebuttal?
Or am I right...
that you're relieved
someone else
has finally made the choice
for you?
So...
Please sign here and here
and I'll need you to relinquish
your badge and sidearm.
What about Braddock
and Callaghan?
They will be reassigned
to different teams.
(Pen thunks on table)
That's not gonna work.
Northwest hallway clear.
Lab three clear.
Sam: No sign of a gunmen,
no further shots fired.
Copy that.
(Rose's phone rings)
Dr Bergan.
Dr. Bergan:
Rose, fill me in.
Rose:
The police are here.
They haven't located
the gunmen as yet,
and we lost power.
Bergan:
How long?
If refrigeration's down...
Rose, you know what
that material's worth.
Of course I do.
But with armed intruders in,
there seems little point...
Power's back.
We're good.
I'll be there as fast as I can.
Spike: Ma'am, I'm gonna need
access to your computers.
Rose: I'll call you back.
Spike: Passwords please.
Rose: Sure.
Spike: Now.
(Computer keys clack)
(Lights click on)
SRU. You guys okay?
Uh, fine.
It's probably best
if you stay outside the lab
until these samples
are secured.
Logan: Is that bogeyman
still on the loose?
We're working on locating him
right now.
We need you guys to evacuate
as soon as possible.
Applewhite: Well, we need at
least another 20 minutes.
Some of the samples
started to thaw
when we lost power.
Filiform gets real cranky
at room temperature.
Guys, we need another
20 minutes in here.
Okay.
What's filiform?
Rose:
It's a strain of anthrax,
refined and weaponized
during the cold war.
We're working on a vaccine.
Parker: If I had told them to end
it, they would have listened,
but I didn't.
It's on me, not them.
They made their own choice,
after already having been
granted a second chance.
Parker:
Come on, doctor,
look me in the eye
and tell me if you've ever,
in all the calls
we've had this year,
seen their judgment
or their performance
impaired by their relationship.
Not yet.
But it's only a matter of time
before their instinct
to protect each other
overrides the safety
of a citizen.
This is why we have
the priority of life protocol.
You like assuming the worst,
Larry?
Don't lecture me, Greg.
Imagining I could've
kept someone safe
but didn't?
That's what keeps me up
at night.
(Clang in the distance)
Here we go.
Police!
Raf: Clear!
Sam: Clear!
Ed:
You all right?
Raf: We have the
guard, unharmed.
He just left through that door.
He took my gun.
Ed: One guy?
Guard: Yeah.
Go! Go!
Sam:
We've lost visual.
Raf:
Spike, you seeing him?
Spike: I got nothing.
He's avoiding the cameras.
(Computer key clacks)
We heard gunshots.
Any wounded?
He shot out
the power generator.
Power generator?
Guard: I didn't have the passkey
to get him into secure storage.
He must have known this building
has electronic locks.
So he knows the place.
Yeah. He was looking
for something
in the deep freeze.
When he couldn't find it,
he lost it.
And what'd he say?
He said he wasn't gonna let 'em
get away with it.
Spike, gunman knows the place.
It sounds personal.
Gonna bring the guard
to you right now,
see if he can id the subject.
Spike:
Copy that.
Rose, we're gonna need photos
of all RDA employees,
past and present.
Rose:
Of course.
Gunman:
No, I couldn't find it.
No, the police got in the way.
Look, you gotta come here.
That's not...
Look, that's not gonna...
No, it's not gonna work
and you know it.
I know what to do.
They're in lockdown.
I know where Applewhite is.
You just need to get here
as soon as you can.
Spike: Employee personnel
files are up on that monitor.
Ed:
Jules, you good?
All clear.
That's a lot of turnover.
Rose: Yeah, one of our
senior operations managers
moved on last year.
Got a better offer
and took his team with him.
That's him.
Rose: Xavier Dodd.
Ed: Let me see, let me see.
We had to let him go
four months ago.
Poor performance,
mental health issues.
Spike:
Sam? Raf?
You getting this?
Sam:
Copy that.
Xavier: Nobody move!
Jules: Subject's in the lab!
Applewhood: Jesus! Xavier?
What're you doing?
Xavier:
I'm looking for answers!
You're gonna help me find them!
Xavier, I need you
to put the gun down now.
You, back up, or I'll shoot!
Tell those guys to stay out!
I can see them!
Tell them to stand down!
Jules:
Sam, Raf, stand down.
We're gonna work this out,
okay?
Female scientist: We' I in
mid-process here, okay?
We're dealing with filiform,
we need to reseal these...
Hey! Don't tell me
about filiform, okay?
I know about filiform.
Then you know that
at room temperature
filiform starts to vaporize.
Look.
Look at the pathogen meter.
We're already inhaling spores.
If the exposure in here
crosses threshold level,
it's untreatable.
Then I guess you'd better
help me soon
rather than later.
We need to seal these samples
immediately.
Hey! What did I say?!
Nobody moves,
nobody leaves
until I get what I want!
That includes you!
Ben:
Sir.
Jules is in the line of fire.
Subject has two hostages.
Parker: What does he want?
Ben: No clear demands yet.
He was fired
for psychological reasons.
All right, I'll get a headset.
Greg, we are going
to the gun cage.
No, these are my people.
I need to know what's going on.
There's an exposed pathogen
that could become airborne.
What kind of pathogen?
Anthrax.
All right, forget the headset.
Have Spike patch audio/visual
into the briefing room.
Do it now. Right now.
Ben: Yes, sir.
Toth: Don't make me call for
an escort off SRU property.
Back off, Larry.
You know you're officially
under suspension.
Then I've got nothing
left to lose, do I?
If you do that,
you know your chances
of returning to duty...
My team needs me.
Spike? Eddie?
Can you hear me?
Boss.
Parker:
Okay, I've got visual and comm,
I'm with you.
Jules: Xavier, can you tell
us what you want here today?
How do you know my name, huh?
What did they tell you?
What did they say?
They said that you worked here
and you were let go.
Spike: Four months ago.
Mental health issues,
unreliable work habits,
disparaging the company.
Xavier:
Did they say I was unstable?
Huh? Paranoid?!
They said you had
mental health issues.
Xavier: Ah! Physical health
not so much concern, huh?
Rose: He was an excellent
employee, at first,
but then later
he became convinced
that one of our vaccines
was making him sick.
His performance suffered,
his behaviour became erratic,
and then he threatened
litigation.
Dr. Applewhite had no choice
but to let him go.
Ben, I need everything
you can find on this guy...
family, home life,
medical records.
Copy.
Spike:
Boss?
Hey, Spike, let me talk
to your contact there.
Rose, it's my boss.
Hi, Rose, my name is
Sergeant Greg Parker,
I'm at the SRU.
Is the man actually sick?
Rose: His symptoms were
found to be psychosomatic
and stress-related.
Parker: Then why would
Xavier take RDA's vaccine?
Rose:
Standard precaution.
He worked in
our biosafety zones.
Spike: Xavier was a
disposal specialist.
Yes.
It's a high-risk position.
He worked with infected
animal carcasses.
It says he was given
VVA-50,
a three-in-one vaccine
for anthrax,
botulism and smallpox.
Rose: Yes, all safe, approved,
and sold all over the world.
Okay, thank you, Rose.
Jules: Do you think
the company's vaccine
is what made you sick?
I know it did.
Jules: And that's
why you're here today.
Xavier: I'm here to get a sample
of the vaccine I was given.
I want my doctor to analyze it.
Applewhite: VVA-50 has a shelf
life of one year, Xavier.
There won't be any samples left
of the ba...
Xavier: You're lying!
You're lying!
He's a liar!
He's the chief researcher here;
He designs these vaccines.
He fired me personally.
He's accountable.
He has every reason
to cover it up.
Maybe I can check it out.
No offense, you I don't trust.
Them I don't trust.
All right, Dr. Ouellette's
gonna be here any minute,
then we're gonna
get some answers.
Spike: Do you know this Dr.
Ouellette?
Rose: Jack Ouellette.
He's an activist scientist.
Been crusading against
vaccine manufacturers for year.
And there's no remaining samples
to analyze?
No.
Ed: Ben, let's get
Xavier's wife down here.
We need to talk to her.
Ben:
Copy that.
Jules: Xavier, there's no
sample on the premises.
We checked it out.
No...
No! Why should I believe you?
Applewhite:
You can check the records.
That entire batch
will have been used
or discarded by now.
It'll be in the records.
I wanna see those records.
I want Ouellette
to see those records.
I want him to see everything!
I wanna know exactly
what I was given!
what was in it!
Something you put inside me
made me sick.
I hear you.
Look at me.
I hear you, all right?
Now, if RDA gives
Dr. Ouellette addresses,
will you please let these people
finish their work here?
You make that happen,
you got a deal.
Spike:
Boss, Xavier's wife is here.
Valerie Simmons?
Okay, we need to talk
over here.
No, no. This shouldn't be
happening.
They forced him
to take the vaccines.
You know that, right?
It was a condition
of his employment
when he started here...
for his "protection."
Compulsory vaccinations.
Just like the Gulf War soldiers.
Parker: Didn't work out too
well for some of them either.
Soon after that
he started getting
these muscle cramps,
spasms in his arms
and shoulders,
migraines.
RDA's in-house doctor
said that...
It was all in his mind,
like what he needed
was a better attitude.
But Xavier kept getting worse.
After they fired him,
we tracked down this doctor
who studies vaccines
and their side effects.
And this was Dr. Ouellette?
Yeah, and we went for
a second opinion.
Lou Gherig's disease.
I've ruled out pretty much
every other possibility.
Now, the EMG confirms it.
What is that, like a...
(Clears throat) Brain disease?
Over the next few years,
your motor functions
will continue to decline,
you'll lose control
of your movement.
Valerie:
And there's...
No...
Ouellette: The ALS runs its
course in two to three years,
sometimes more.
Um, then respiratory failure
sets in.
But his mind will be normal?
Even though you can't move
or speak,
it's still you in there.
Xavier:
Three years...
So let me ask you this,
this in-house doctor,
why didn't he discover the ALS?
Convenient, isn't it?
And you tried legal action?
Three different lawyers.
They all said sorry
for your luck,
there's no proof
the vaccines made him sick.
That's why Xavier was trying
to get a sample for testing.
Why the gun?
He had no choice.
They weren't exactly
gonna let him
walk in the front Dr.
Oh, and he's dying.
You got that part, right?
Okay, I need to go to work here
and I just need you
to wait outside
with this officer, please.
It's okay.
Parker: Xavier doesn't
have a lot to lose.
It's gonna be tricky
working him down from this.
(Door closes)
Ed:
Dr. Ouellette?
He just called me on the phone.
I have nothing to do with this
man's actions here today.
Well, that's good.
So let me cut to the chase.
Could the vaccine have
caused Xavier's illness?
There's a preservative
that's used in some vaccines,
squalene,
that's recently
been linked to ALS.
I know RDA has experimented
with squalene in the past.
Rose: None of our squalene
vaccines ever went to market.
Okay, look, here's the deal.
Xavier wants you to go
through RDA's documentation
and to tell him whether or not
that vaccine is safe.
Can you do that?
If RDA will allow it,
absolutely.
Rose, you made that call?
Yes, I've cleared it
with our CEO...
but no documents
leave this building.
Ed:
Okay, Jules.
Xavier,
Dr. Ouellette is here.
RDA gave him access
to their files.
How do I know?
Ouellette:
Xavier, I'm right here.
I'm gonna check into this
for you, all right?
Make sure they gave you
what they said they gave you.
Xavier:
Okay, good. Good.
Ed:
Okay, let's go.
Raf, see if you can find us
some different eyes in.
Raf:
On it.
Do you remember our deal?
Thank you.
Applewhite: Okay, we've lost a lot of time.
We have to move fast.
We need to put these babies
to bed.
Ed, got a window
behind the subject.
Ed: Now, stay ready,
in case things go sideways.
Rose: You can search our inventory
on the computer over there.
Backup hard copies filed under
vaccine number over there.
Ed:
Fast is good, doctor.
Facts don't lie.
This won't take long.
Jules:
How you holding up?
Xavier:
(Sighs)
I'm dying.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Xavier: You know, first,
it was just small stuff.
My muscles started twitching
for no reason.
I got a little numbness
and tingling.
Didn't think anything of it.
But this disease,
it moves fast.
Soon, I'm not gonna be able
to feed myself.
I'm not gonna be able to move,
or dress,
or swallow.
Or speak.
I can handle it, so can Val.
I mean that's...
That's the way it is.
But Gracie...
(Tearing up)
She's gonna grow up
watching me lose control,
one piece at a time,
and waste away.
She's not even gonna remember
the sound of my voice.
You have ALS?
What?
Like you didn't know.
Als is very difficult
to diagnose.
I'm sorry our doctors
missed it.
I really had no idea.
It's hereditary, right?
Is there a member
of your family perhaps who...?
There isn't.
I thought you had work to do.
Parker: Jules, Xavier's
living under a death sentence.
He's waging war against RDA.
Is the only thing
that's keeping him going.
He needs validation.
Xavier, between me and you,
you don't strike me
as an unstable, paranoid man.
More like somebody
who's trying to make sure
other people don't get sick
like you did.
If I can prove that I'm right,
then the money from the lawsuit
will help take care
of Valerie and Grace.
There's nothing else
that I can do for them.
Do you have a picture of her?
Of Grace?
(Machine beeps)
Look at those cheeks.
How old is she?
Xavier:
She just turned three.
Jules:
Aw, that's such a great age.
She's adorable.
Parker: De-escalating.
Nice, Jules.
Facing the end of the road.
Sound familiar?
Ed:All right,
we've got an answer.
Xavier's not gonna like it.
Jules, you're in there,
it's your call.
If he escalates,
Sam and Raf move on your order.
Copy.
(Phone rings)
(Phone beeps on)
Yeah, Ouellette.
Dr. Ouellette:
Xavier.
I know this isn't the answer
you're hoping to hear.
The vaccine is unrelated
to your ALS.
(Breathes heavily)
That was, uh...
That was so quick.
I checked everything,
the ingredients list,
phased trial results,
safety records,
chain of custody
right down to your dose.
I don't think the vaccine had
anything to do with your ALS.
What're you saying?
You think there's no link?
You're telling me
there's no link?
I'm afraid not.
I'm sorry, Xavier.
That's impossible!
Come on, there's gotta be
some kind of mistake,
or they doctored the results
or something!
Right?! Ouellette?!
Sam:
Jules, I'm coming in.
Okay, just give him a minute.
This is a lot to accept.
It's the only explanation!
Jules: Xavier, there is nothing
that happened here today
that cannot be undone.
No, no, no!
Listen, I'm not paranoid.
Okay, I've read about
these cover-ups, right?
They doctored their file
or they deleted something,
or they paid people off.
Applewhite: Xavier, you
got what you came for...
VVA-50 was his baby,
of course he's gonna try
to protect it.
You've got the answer,
you need to face...
We can check it out, Xavier.
Drop your weapon.
Xavier: There's no way
I would've got through
if they knew the real truth.
Jules: Xavier, put
your weapon down now!
Xavier:
You did this to me.
Jules: You drop your
weapon right now!
Xavier:
You lied to my face!
And you can lie to me,
to my face?!
Jules:
Drop your weapon right now!
Jules: Drop your weapon!
Logan: You let him go!
Drop your weapon right now!
(Weapon fires, loud explosion)
Spike?
Lockdown should happen
automatically.
(Locks beep and clank)
Sounds like it just did.
Sam:
Jules! Jules!
Jules!
Jules, status!
Sam:
Come on, Jules.
Jules, status.
What's your status?
(Moans) I'm okay.
(Moaning)
Puncture wound.
There's a piece of shrapnel.
It hit an artery.
Sam:
Keep pressure on it.
We got injured,
I need to get in there now.
Ed:
Easy, Sam, easy.
We gotta know
what we're dealing with here.
Parker:
What the hell happened?
Team?!
Sam:
Logan fired.
We got a major spill.
The refrigeration unit
broke open.
Rose: The bullet must have
hit the HP vapor generator.
How much filiform
was stored in there?
Rose:
At least twenty units.
And at room temperature
it thaws, right?
And the spores become airborne.
Sam: The pathogen
meter's 900 and rising.
Rose: The good news is the
lockdown itself accelerates the vent.
It should bring the pathogen
levels down under control.
No, it won't.
The vents aren't on.
Spike: The venting system
must've been knocked off-line
when Xavier sabotaged
the power generator.
Ed: 'Kay, Raf I need you
in that vent room now.
I'm on my way.
Sam:
Ed, we gotta go in.
I'm suiting up now.
Spike: 1200 parts per
million and climbing.
Come on, come on, come on.
Logan:
My leg!
I can't feel my leg!
Applewhite: It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Logan:
(Whimpering)
Xavier and Applewhite:
(Grunts of effort)
Logan:
(Screams in pain)
(Gasps for breath)
Applewhite: We're going
to have to reset it.
Okay, keep her leg steady.
Hands here.
Here!
Okay...
Logan:
(Shrieks from the pain)
It's gonna be okay.
I need to find something
for a splint.
Jules, can you hear me?
Mh-mm.
Sniper breathing, okay?
Slow it down, and hold.
Lower your heart rate,
you'll lose less blood.
We're coming right in.
We'll get you soon, okay?
Ed: If filiform's inhaled,
what happens, Rose?
If it's under a micron,
hits the bloodstream
with every breath.
If you inhale
over the threshold,
there's no going back.
There's no real symptoms
at first, but...
But what?
Ultimately?
Severe respiratory problems,
your skin turns blue,
you vomit blood.
It's terminal.
Okay, under that threshold,
is it treatable?
With antibiotics.
Spike:
The threshold is?
Rose:
Anything over 2500's fatal.
2500.
Xavier, this is Ed Lane
with the SRU.
I need everybody
out of that room immediately.
Let's just get you
some fresh air,
and then I promise you
we will resolve
anything you need.
Where are you doing?
She needs help
to get out of here.
Jules: Xavier, we're
all leaving right now,
through the decontamination
chamber,
one at a time.
Xavier:
No! (Fires gun)
Nobody's leaving here
until I get some answers.
Jules:
The venting system is off-line.
You know the damage
that filiform does.
Xavier:
Why won't you admit it?!
Applewhite: I'll admit anything,
anything that you want...
Xavier:
I want you to tell the truth!
But the truth is
you just got sick, Xavier.
It's terrible, it's unfair,
but it's not my fault.
He can't face the truth;
means accepting his own death.
Toth: Now the crusade
he and Valerie are on
was all for nothing.
(Whimpering)
Jules:
Maybe it's hard to hear,
but maybe the vaccine
didn't make you sick.
How could you possibly
understand this?
This is your last chance!
Jules:
Do not raise your weapon!
Raf:
Ed, I'm in the vent room.
Talk to me, Raf.
It looks like
the whole thing's shut down.
Our best bet is to reinitialize
the system manually.
Ed: Doctor, I'm going to
ask you one last time
before I put any more
of my team in danger,
is there any possibility
that Xavier could be right.
Dr. Ouellette only if squalene were
present in the VVA-50's composition.
But I'd have seen that
in the records.
Spike: And hypothetically,
if there had been a cover-up?
Ouellette:
No. Not possible,
not without doctor in
the records.
Not without employees
being aware.
Or employees being let go?
What kind of employees?
Depends on the nature
of the cover-up.
What are you doing?
Spike: Operations manager?
Safety supervisor?
Quality control inspector?
If it were
a contamination issue,
definitely.
There is no cover-up.
That many people were let go?
Spike:
Last year.
The entire safety
operations team,
just before Xavier was hired.
Rose, you replaced
your entire safety department?
What, did you get a result
you didn't like?
As I said before,
our safety operations
manager left
and took his entire team
with him.
I was sorry to see them go.
Huh.
Spike, Eddie, think we need
another angle on this.
Spike:
Copy.
Ben, get me RDA's CEO
on the line.
Copy.
Ed: Rose, if you're
protecting someone,
now is the time to come clean.
Ben:
Boss, Dr. Bergan's on the line.
Patch him through.
(Phone beeps on)
Bergan: Sergeant, I understand
the situation at the lab
still isn't resolved.
Parker: Yeah, your former
employee remains convinced
that one of RDA's vaccines
made him sick.
That's just not possible.
Doctor, I'm telling you,
a minute ago,
I would've agreed with you.
Excuse me?
Parker: Dr. Bergan, are you
aware of any problems
with operational safety at RDA?
Bergan:
Absolutely not.
So, you're not aware
that your entire safety team
was replaced last year?
Bergan: Rose told me
they moved on by choi..
Parker: And so she replaces
an entire safety department,
and you don't even raise
an eyebrow?
Bergan:
I trust Rose implicitly.
Her vision and leadership
have single-handedly made
this company profitable again.
Dr. Bergen, I've got four lives
in jeopardy at your lab,
I'm gonna need
your full cooperation here.
You have it, I promise you.
I'm taking you up on that.
(Warning meter chimes)
(Jules whimpers)
Jules, slow your breath, okay?
Count it out,
keep your heart rate real low.
(Short, shallow breaths)
Applewhite:
Shhh! Hang on, hang on.
(Shortened breaths,
gasps for air)
Xavier we're running
out of time.
Sam:
Jules?
Jules!
Okay...
Is she okay?
Applewhite:
She's lost a lot of blood.
You've gotta apply
constant pressure,
Applewhite: Okay?
Jules: Okay.
Applewhite:
All right, keep your head down.
Jules:
Okay.
Sam: Xavier, she needs
medical attention, okay?
You all do.
You need to let
everybody out now.
Xavier!
How can this possibly help you?
Okay! Okay! Okay!
They can go, but he stays.
They can't walk, Xavier!
They need our help.
Xavier:
You're staying!
Jules, I'm on my way.
Are you hearing
what I'm hearing?
A civilian's at risk.
Parker:
He knows what he's doing.
Rose: The decontamination
chamber's effective
for only two people at a time.
Rose, can he take an oxygen tank
in there with him
for the others?
Too risky.
The air's thick
with hydrogen peroxide vapors.
Introduce enriched oxygen
and the whole thing
can blow up.
♪
Did you see that?
You wanna write that down,
and put it in your file.
Priority of life is observed.
Noted.
Sarge... is that you?
Hey, Jules, you stay with me.
Yeah, you hang in there, okay?
I couldn't get through to him.
Riker: No, you did
everything you could,
you hear me?
You did everything you could.
You do me proud.
You just hang on.
Jules, you just hang on.
Raf, come on, buddy.
Anything?
Doing everything I can.
He's here.
Let's do this.
(Pathogen alert beeps)
(Rose's cell phone rings)
Rose: It's my boss, I
need to take this.
Yes?
Bergen: Rose, I was just
questioned by the police.
The less you know the better.
I appreciate that.
But just so it's clear
moving forward,
the safety team you replaced...
They found irregularities
in the tank cleaning system...
The presence of squalene
in a large batch of VVA-50.
We disagreed about the risk,
and I gave them
a generous incentive to move on,
and then I cleared up.
I see.
And that batch wasn't destroyed?
Rose:
Henry,
you know how much a batch
that size is worth.
It was our entire margin
for the year.
I couldn't just throw it away.
I didn't realize.
So we've distributed
a tainted vaccine,
and Xavier was one
of a number of people
who received it?
Rose: We've had no
customer complaints,
and there's no actual proof
that our vaccine made him sick.
It was my call, Henry.
Bergan: Your call pulled
us out of the red.
Rose:
Yes, it did.
Bergan:
It earned you a bonus.
Yes, it did.
Thank you for your honesty,
Rose.
Yeah,
thank you for your honesty.
Jules, you get that?
Spike: Your boss was
calling from our station.
The miracle
of the modern headset.
The whole team's connected
to one set of ears.
Xavier, it's done.
Help me up.
Xavier!
(Grunts in pain)
Xavier, Rose confessed.
She confessed!
She confessed.
There were safety issues.
RDA gave you
a tainted vaccine, okay?
Gave you a tainted vaccine.
She, she admitted...
She admitted to the cover-up.
She did.
Now you have to go.
The decontamination chamber
only works for two,
so I want you to go now.
We have to get outta here.
We have to go.
You go first.
Xavier: You go first;
I'm already sick.
Come on. Come on.
God, I'm so sorry.
Jules:
(Breathing heavily)
Raf, Xavier's still not out.
Raf:
Almost there.
Ah, come on, come on.
(Computer trills)
(Meter beeps)
I love you.
(Jules gasps in pain)
Come on.
Be ready, guys,
she's lost a lot of blood.
(Computer trills)
I got it.
(Levers clank)
(Ventilation system whirs)
(Relieved breaths)
(Decontamination chamber beeps)
Ed: Get her outta there.
Let's go, let's go!
Ed: Come on, Jules, come on.
Paramedic:
We're gonna give you an IV
and then we're gonna get you
to the hospital.
♪ So down it seems ♪
♪ the reassuring dream ♪
♪ I will let you hold onto me ♪
♪ always knowing
what it means ♪
♪ 'cause falling down ♪
I love you.
(Muffled response)
♪ Is what I found ♪
You're gonna be okay, Jules.
♪ But wait ♪
♪ 'cause I can see the silence ♪
Toth: I confronted you
with your suspension,
you agreed to it.
But when you saw your people
out there were at risk,
what'd you do?
You went high-noon on me,
at great risk to your chances
of getting your job back.
Now, why is that?
Ed: You saw what
happened out there.
Priority of life was observed.
Today it was.
We don't know about tomorrow.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
Your sergeant's
suspension orders.
Ed:
You don't get it, do you?
Toth: I've seen this team,
I've read the reports...
You don't see
what this team does,
you don't live the job.
If it wasn't for him...
Eddie...
Sam and Jules?
That was the right call.
You can't say that.
(Ed slaps the table)
It was the right call
because it was your call,
and that's why we're here,
and that's why we're team one.
So don't come in here
and tell me otherwise.
Toth:
Okay.
So here's the thing:
I like this team.
I like your sergeant,
I trust him.
The problem is
he doesn't trust himself.
Team one is off of probation
as of today.
Regarding Callaghan
and Braddock,
based on what I've seen today,
I will make a personal appeal
to the chief
to reverse his decision
to split them up.
Until that time,
they will remain on team one.
Thank you.
How is she?
She's stable, sir.
She'll be all right.
I'm glad to hear it.
Sergeant Parker,
you have some thinking to do.
I'm gonna give you one week
to decide
if you wanna continue
to lead this team.
Your team trusts your judgment,
so do I.
One week.
Ed:
So...
Go to the gun range,
use this for target practice?
What do you think?
No, Eddie.
Not just yet.
Sync and corrections by
www.Addic7ed.com