(Sirens wail)
Ed:
What're we looking at here?
Jules:
System's gone haywire.
Unit commander:
It's been hacked.
The alarm's on
a perpetual loop;
you don't even know
what it's flagging.
Parker: Most secure building
in the city, Eddie,
and someone just
cracked it open
like a science project.
This had better work.
Male:
You do what I tell you?
They won't even know
what hit them.
(Velcro rasps, weapons click)
'Kay, listen up,
it's the last time
to review this.
We are a full escort
for a high-risk target,
Karl Morse.
He's en route
to metro courthouse three
for sentencing
after a plea deal
for drug trafficking.
Ed: Okay, I just sent everybody
the final route plan.
It's on your PDA.
Now, there's a lot of chatter
on the jungle telegraph.
A lot of people wanna
get to this guy.
Think he'll try a jailbreak?
Jules: If he took a plea bargain
, he must probably talked.
Sam: Meaning the
people he talked about
aren't too happy.
Ed:
Okay, here it is.
Whoever gets to Morse
makes a lot of friends.
We're gonna stop that
from happening.
(Spike's phone rings)
Spike:
Meet you in the truck.
Hey, Natalie, not a great time.
Natalie: Hey, sorry
, it won't take long.
I just wanted to get back
to my friend
about what we talked about
last night.
Yeah, yeah. You know,
I thought it about it a lot,
and, uh, the things is,
uh, think right now
is not a good time.
Natalie:
It's just a weekend, Spike.
She's got the cottage
all summer.
I didn't mean it
to be some big thing.
No, no. Of course not.
You know, I...
Honestly, Nat?
I-I like you,
and I think you're great.
But, um, thing is,
I don't think I'm ready
to be going to cottages
for the weekend right now.
So you like me,
you just don't "like" like me.
Gotcha.
Is it my brother?
Did he say something?
No. I haven't talked to Sam.
Please don't say,
"it's not you, it's me."
Okay.
Natalie:
But it's not me, right?
It's not you.
Still friends?
Okay.
(Phone line beeps)
Um, other line.
You go.
Spike: Okay.
Uh, call me when you get back?
Natalie:
You got it.
David.
David: Nat, I'm sorry.
Last phone call, I promise.
But...
I have to see you today,
face to face,
just this one time.
I'm not sure
that's such a good idea.
David:
(Sighs) Don't worry.
I know you're serious
about this guy.
I just...
I need to say goodbye to you
in person.
Ed: Okay, we're about 15
minutes from target.
Status report?
Secondary clear.
Sam?
Primary good.
Spike?
Surveillance all clear.
Let's keep it that way.
Is everything...
Good with you, man?
All clear.
I mean...
Okay, last night,
Natalie came home
from coffee with you
and she seemed upset.
She was upset?
Well, she was trying
to hide it, yeah.
She asked if you ever stop
with the "kidding around."
I don't know, I make jokes,
it's what I do.
You usually your sister's
wing-man?
I'm not her wing-man,
okay?
You know what?
Never mind.
We're not dating.
Well, that's good
'cause that would be weird.
Trouble has a way
of finding her.
David:
Yeah, bank foreclosed.
A friend of mine
told me about it,
I got it for cheap.
It's gorgeous.
David:
You look good.
So do you.
(Chuckles)
Don't sound so surprised.
I just mean considering...
Considering everything?
Yeah.
Well, I'm really glad
that you're doing well,
I mean it.
David: Yeah.
Speaking of which, this is my uh...
My business partner, Albin.
Hey.
Natalie, right?
David: Oh, yeah, he knows
everything about you.
How you, uh, dazzled your way
into my life,
made yourself at home
in my villa,
drank my booze,
swam in my pool...
You were my personal
house guest
for, what, two months,
and then you threw me
to the dogs
and breezed away.
Wait a minute, I threw you?
What would you call it?
You packed the bag.
I trusted you.
You have no idea!
David: You know, there's no
rules in Colombian jails.
No, um, guards to keep one guy
from doing whatever
to another...
Unless you've got something
to bribe 'em with.
No one to turn to.
You can beg and you can scream,
but nobody hears you.
Every night, I go back there.
I can still smell them
on my skin.
I am so sorry,
but I did not mean
for any of that to happen.
Aggghhh!
(Whimpers)
David:
You owe me, Natalie.
You don't just get
to walk away.
You're gonna do something
for me, Natalie.
(Natalie whimpers)
Ed:
Okay, guys, stay sharp.
Four more blocks
to the courthouse,
we say goodbye to Morse,
we head home.
Jules:
Ed, city van, dead ahead.
Team, let's pull over.
Didn't the word go out,
no work on this route?
Well, it should've,
that's for sure.
Jules, call the city,
see if this is just
a miscommunication.
Let's check it out.
(PDA beeps)
Raf.
What is it?
Spike:
It's a fake!
Pull back!
It's a fake.
Spike:
It's gotta be up high.
Wherever that signal's
coming from,
they want direct line of sight
to the explosive.
I've just jammed
a high-level frequency.
It's got no business
being in this area,
might be an IED on that truck.
You sure?
There's a lot of news
satellite hookups
for the Morse hearing.
It's too high for that.
It's very specific,
so it can't be triggered
accidentally.
Spike, you find the location
of the trigger man?
Spike: West from here...
It's close.
I can't be more specific, guys.
Ed: Got it.
Raf and I are heading west.
I got it jammed for now,
but if he switches signals...
Copy that, boss.
I'm trying the nearest building
with a good vantage.
Copy that.
Jules, let's clear those people
outta here.
All right, let's move away
from the truck immediately.
Move away from the truck now!
Ed: Right there. Bad idea.
Freeze right there.
Really bad idea.
Turn around.
Put the phone on the ledge,
no fast moves.
Raf: Subject secured.
We got the detonator.
Parker: That's great
work, Spike, everybody.
Now, let's get Mr. Morse
to his court date.
Parker: Morse is en route to the
rear entrance of the courthouse.
Raf: Hey, wasn't Morse the
guy you bagged last year
at the Lakeshore warehouse?
Yeah, three million worth
of heroin.
Jules: Yeah. Now we just risked
our butts off to save his life.
So we can safely get
his sorry butt back in jail.
Must be nice
to get a little closure.
Justice league!
(Spike's phone rings)
Oh... hold on a sec.
Sorry, I gotta take this.
Hey! It still isn't you.
Spike, I'm sorry.
I know what you said,
but I really need to see you.
Spike: Uh, okay,
I can come by after shift.
No! Spike, please come.
I'm with David,
and he'd really like
to meet you.
Well, who's David?
He's an old friend.
Just please come get me.
Spike: "Get you?
" Nat, you in trouble?
Mm-hm.
Okay, you know what?
I'll get Sam.
No! Don't. Just come.
Please, I really need
your help.
Spike:
Okay, where are you?
Hey, guys, I got a bit
of a personal thing
I gotta take care of.
If we're all done here,
I'll just come back after
to debrief, okay?
Holleran's gonna wanna hear
about the IED, Spike.
Yeah, I know,
and I'll be there.
Just...
Your mom?
Uh, it'll be quick.
You do it in an hour?
Half that.
See you at the barn.
All right.
(Doorbell buzzes)
David:
Spike.
Yeah, hi, is this David?
I'm here for Natalie.
Come on in.
(Buzzer buzzes)
(Door buzzes open)
David:
Officer Scarlatti,
Natalie has told me
so much about you.
Spike: There's not that
much to tell. Hey.
Natalie:
Spike, I'm so sorry.
Hey, don't worry about it,
just get your things
and let's get going.
David: See, we knew you
were the type of boyfriend
who'd answer a distress call,
no questions asked.
Natalie?
What's going on?
Albin:
We're on.
She's done.
Tie her up.
Let's get to work.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Michelangelo Scarlatti,
badge number 3496.
What're you gonna do
with Natalie?
Joined the Police Strategic
Response Unit in 2005,
specializing in bomb disposal
and crazy "mad"
computer skills.
David, you got me.
Let her go.
Albin:
He's off the grid.
Got everything
with a GPS trace,
including the SUV's tracker.
David:
Special citation last year
for "bravery
in the line of duty,"
one of the best cops
in the city,
and you're gonna help me
get something from...
(Computer beeps)
There.
Are you serious?
David! David, stop!
Stop! David!
I don't know what Natalie
told you I could do,
but the evidence depot?
That's what people
are talking about
when they're talking about
something being "impenetrable."
Alarms at every entrance
and exit,
key cards and passcodes,
not to mention
a dozen armed guards, 24/7.
Now, I don't know exactly
what you expect...
Albin: We expect you to hack
into the security mainframe
with a spoofed ID
to cover your tracks,
override the ID line system
and keep any traces
off your line
while you're doing it.
Now, I've already got you routed
through an encrypted VPN.
Okay.
So it sounds like you know
exactly what you're doing.
You don't need me.
Or Natalie.
Here's the deal,
two men waiting
on my signal to enter.
They have ID's,
they have uniforms,
they know the layout.
Albin:
But we don't have passwords.
So you gotta get them
and handle any curve balls,
David:
And you gotta move fast
because we are fighting
the clock.
What's the rush?
Evidence protocol.
What we want gets destroyed
end of shift.
That is at 4:00.
David: You have to get
them through three gates,
and to the main evidence depot.
Now, if you need
more persuasion...
Natalie: - Agghhh!
Spike: - No! Okay, okay!
Okay!
No. We're good.
(Phone beeps)
Man 1:
So?
Man 2:
The wheels are turning.
It's not gonna happen.
Man 2:
It'll happen.
I trust these guys.
Do you trust me?
Yeah.
So we sit tight?
Hurry up and wait.
Albin:
Using a packet sniffer?
Yeah.
Got me the admin password.
And now...
We're into the main security system.
And we've got two guys
at the front door.
I'm ready for them.
You used to be a blue hat?
Albin: Yeah, but the money's
better on this side of the computer.
Stand by.
Spike: Okay, first
gate's a standard ID check.
I set them both up
with a dummy number;
it'll check out.
That's the easy part.
But once they're in,
if I can't move fast enough,
there is no turning back.
Then you better move fast,
Spike.
Man 2:
Bagged and tagged.
Down from 52.
(Id card beeps)
In and out, home for dinner.
No turning back.
Get them in and out.
(Snaps fingers)
(Spike types furiously)
Hurdle number two.
(Keys clack, computer beeps)
(Beep)
(Computer trills)
Dammit.
What?
They found the hack?
No. To get through
the second gate,
you need the latest password.
You usually get that
via secure email,
but I can't find it.
If I had more time...
We don't have more time.
Well, here we are...
They're at the gate.
I told you, once we're...
They're at the gate,
get them in.
Albin:
David, this hack,
the cops will be on us
if we don't move fast.
We're moving fast.
This is risky.
This is our shot.
Spike:
Okay, I got an idea.
I'm sending them a password
right now.
It's gonna be wrong,
you tell 'em to punch it in
anyway.
Why?
What're you trying to do?
An incorrect password'll set off
an alert in the server.
It'll try to verify
the number...
Spike: Yeah.
Three times before sounding an alarm.
The system's open
during the verification.
And I wanna jump in
during that pause
and reset the password.
That way the system will think
it's correct.
What kind of pause?
How long?
Spike:
Half a second.
That's the best I can do.
(Keys clack)
(Sighs)
He's sending a password,
but there's a catch.
(Phone beeps)
(Keypad beeps)
(Keypad buzzes)
(Computer trills, keys clack)
(Gun thunks heavily on desk)
(Keypad beeps)
(Buzzes)
Technology, huh?
(Keys clack)
- Last chance.
- I can count.
(Keyboard keys clack furiously)
(Keypad beeps)
(Keypad chirps)
(Locks click)
Let's go.
(Sighs and breathes heavily)
(Keys clack)
(Door clicks shut)
All right.
Two down, one to go.
We've got 24 minutes left.
So from here...?
Albin: From here,
it's just a straight shot...
Then back out the same way?
David:
Simplest and fastest.
Spike: That's the plan.
So, listen,
once you guys find whatever
it is you're looking for,
you're gonna let me
and Natalie go, right?
David:
(Laughs)
Wow.
You hear that, Nat?
Even after you trick him
and you lure him here
and he's handcuffed to a chair,
he's still worried about you.
How do you do that, huh?
David: See, Spike, with
me, it was like, uh...
You know, everything's great,
she's all happy-go-lucky,
let's live in the moment,
right?
Next thing you know,
I'm in a Colombian jail
and she's on a plane
right back home.
Dave, focus.
See, lucky for me,
I had a good friend,
who, after 10 months,
tracks me down in hell
and persuades the devil
to save my soul
with some serious cash.
And when he starts planning
this little project,
I tell him,
I can make that happen...
Because that's what friends do.
Spike:
David, it's working.
Your idea, it was smart.
It got me here,
we got them inside.
Hey...
Just let her go.
No. She doesn't get
to walk away.
Not this time.
Spike's voice mail: Hey, you've reached me.
Leave a message.
Anything from Spike?
Parker:
No.
Winnie, call Spike's mom.
I need him to check in.
Winnie:
Copy that.
Last gate...
Man 2: - How are ya?
Officer: - How're you doing?
(Keypad beeps and buzzes)
(Keys clack furiously)
Uh-oh.
(Alarm blares)
What's up, guys?
Albin:
What, secondary firewall?
Spike:
System overrode the relay;
it has a built-in fail-safe
if you try it more than once.
Albin: No-no-no!
My sources said there wasn't one.
Spike: Okay, then you
tell me what happened!
What's the plan, Scarlatti?
Spike:
Ungh!
(Natalie gasps)
What is the plan?
Tell him to fire his weapon.
What?
Spike:
Your guy on the inside,
tell him shoot
at the fire alarm.
If he shoots at the fire alarm,
the doors will open
and the guards will fall back
when a live round is fired;
that's the protocol.
(Sighs) Shoot the fire alarm!
Do it!
(Gunshot blasts)
Stay close.
Stay down! Stay!
(Alarm blares)
(Emergency alarm blares)
Hot call, hot call!
Shots fired
at the evidence depot.
Ed:
The evidence depot?
Who opens fire there?
That place is like Fort Knox.
Reports say
two uniformed officers.
They're still in there.
Still no word on Spike?
Winnie: No.
His mother hasn't seen him all day,
and his cell phone's going
straight to voice mail.
Okay, track his GPS, Winnie.
We need him.
Copy that.
David: Okay, talk fast.
How does this work?
Spike:
When the fire alarm goes off
it unlocks all the doors
until the all clear.
It's easier now.
David: Except for the shots
fired, the SRU gets called.
Spike:
And I'm SRU,
and I know exactly
what they're gonna do,
and how they're gonna do it.
Team one is a man short,
so there's gonna be a hole
in the perimeter.
We're gonna have a window
before backup shows up.
(Annoyed breath)
David: Hollings, Kenton, listen up.
Here's the...
Oh... hold on.
David, David, David.
Firing shots in a building
full of cops...
How does that not lead
back here?
I have the doors unlocked.
You wanna tell me
how your source
didn't know about this,
uh, fail-safe?
Spike, I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault.
No, it's okay.
It's okay.
I set off the alarm on purpose.
No! No.
Just do what they say.
You wanna ask them
for a plan B?
All right, boys, listen up.
Here's the plan.
Natalie, the second
they get what they want
and they get outta there,
we become a liability
and they are going
to kill us, okay?
I have to draw this out,
and I have to make sure
our team gets here.
They're the only ones
who can help now.
David:
Hey! Hey!
I need you to focus, Spike.
Albin, shut her trap.
Natalie: - No, no! Spike!
Spike: - Natalie, it's okay!
Okay, Natalie, it's okay.
Okay?
Natalie: - No!
Spike: - Get off her!
(Muffled cries)
Spike:
It's gonna be okay.
(Sirens wail)
How many officers
you got in there?
Seventeen.
They know you're here.
They've all got secure locations
to stay in
while you do your thing.
Ed:
Where were the suspects headed?
Unit commander:
The evidence locker.
Parker:
Just two males?
Yeah, but they had help.
Winnie, where the hell
is Spike?
Winnie: There's no trace
on his vehicle's GPS.
This is an all-call
for Officer Spike Scarlatti,
badge number 3-4-niner-6.
Repeat, Officer Spike Scarlatti
of the Strategic Response Unit,
report in.
If you have any information
on his current whereabouts,
you need to report
to the SRU immediately.
Come on, Spike, where are you?
Where are you?
Albin: Okay, Spike,
what's the SRU's plan?
Spike: They're gonna set
up a command post,
then make a beeline
for the evidence room.
David: - Time?
Spike: - Minutes.
Kenton:
We're in.
Even with the number though...
It'll take some time.
This had better work.
Like I told you,
you do what I tell you,
they're not gonna know
what hit 'em.
They're entering
the surveillance room
right now.
But not for long.
David:
Go. Go!
Unit commander: This is what
I mean, they had help.
Ed:
What're we looking at here?
Jules:
System's gone haywire.
Unit commander:
It's been hacked.
The alarm's on
a perpetual loop;
you don't even know
what it's flagging.
Sam: No way we can
see what's going on.
Parker: Most secure
building in the city, Eddie,
and someone just
cracked it open
like a science project.
Okay, okay.
You stay here, boss.
Let's get us back online.
Guys, with me.
Let's move it.
Okay, it's file 24932.
Find it.
Hollings:
24932...
There.
There, go.
Move, move.
Spike:
They're on the move.
David: Kenton, you have
four heavily-armed SRU cops
closing in.
Copy that.
We're good to go.
Okay, pack that bag.
Albin: Quickest way out,
not the way they came.
Albin: - Out the back?
Spike: - Yeah.
Tell me where to go.
David: We can get you out
without them seeing you,
but you gotta move.
Let's go.
(Alarm blares)
Clear.
(Alarm halts)
You got control?
Main board is here,
didn't come from us.
Can you get back in?
Unit commander:
No. The hack's from off-site.
Pretty much impossible,
but somehow they did it.
Maybe they knew the system.
An inside job maybe?
If they're good enough
to do this...
What went wrong?
Why'd the alarm go off?
Unit commander: The alarm
wasn't triggered from inside.
That was set off remotely, too.
What?
Guys, the gate alarm
that triggered all this
was set off deliberately,
from the outside.
Why would they blow the whistle
on themselves?
Sam:
Doesn't make sense.
Ed:
Boss, eyes?
Parker:
Still blind, buddy.
David:
They're not gonna have time.
Albin: You need to
slow your guys down.
I know.
(Alarm blares)
Boss, what's that?
What is that?
It's a number three.
Southwest quadrant.
Looks like an exit, Eddie.
I thought all the alarms
were cut.
There's fifty of them.
Maybe the bad guys missed one.
Jules, Raf, check it out.
Sam...
(Alarm blares)
They're splitting up.
Chasing ghosts.
They won't get anywhere
near your guys, I promise.
(Siren wails)
False alarm, looks like.
(Alarm halts)
Boss, is that you?
Not us.
(Alarm blares)
Another alarm, Eddie.
Looks like the other side
of the building.
What's your take on this?
So far,
the evidence locker's clear.
Sam: They must've split up,
headed in opposite directions.
That would take some serious
coordinating to do that.
Ed.
Coming in here
took that already.
Parker:
So what were they after?
Okay, boss,
we have three evidence boxes
that've been tampered with.
Evidence log.
Stand by.
Go ahead.
Sam:
Case number 25146,
25143.
Sam:
24932.
Three-two...
You got an evidence log?
First one: Gang bust.
We were holding C4 explosive
and detonators.
Next one, 500 rounds,
hollow point rounds.
Ed:
We gotta stop these guys now.
They make it to an exit,
they'll shoot their way
through our guys.
The place'll be a bloodbath.
Yeah, I hear you, buddy,
but you could get that
on the street.
You don't need to break into
a depot for that stuff.
Unit commander:
Last one's Karl Morse's case.
20 kilos uncut heroin.
Big bust from last year.
Scheduled for incineration
today.
(Siren wails)
(Alarm halts)
Raf:
(Snorted breath)
We're going in circles here,
man.
(Multiple alarms blare)
Boss, they're playing with us.
Boss, what is it?
Two exits from here?
Yeah, buddy.
Yeah, the one you came in on...
And one on the other side.
No way they passed us
in the hall.
All right,
we regroup on the far side.
We gotta get these guys
before they make it
to the perimeter.
How're we doing with cameras?
I'm locked out.
Parker: - Eddie.
Ed: - Boss...
Alarms 3, 49, 6.
3-4-9-6.
That's Spike's badge number.
Parker:
And then 10-33.
Officer in need of assistance.
Ed:
We gotta find Spike fast!
Jules:
Unless this is Spike's work,
because only an inside guy
can hack into the system.
Then set off an alarm
intentionally.
To get his team here.
Okay, obviously
he's under duress.
We need to locate him ASAP.
Okay, guys,
who talked to him last?
Boss, Spike had a couple
calls today.
Check the auto-transcripter,
maybe we can get at least
his half of the conversation.
Parker: All right, that's good.
Winnie, you take it.
Winnie:
Copy that.
Police!
Stop right there!
Ed:
Right there!
Hollings:
Come on! Come on!
Kenton: These guys are on our tail.
We gotta slow 'em down.
You heard him,
we don't have time!
Help me with this.
David: Guys, what the
hell are you doing?
Kenton: I grabbed some
C4 from the locker.
C4.
Good idea.
No, that's bad idea.
That stuff,
it's really unstable.
David: He's worked with it before,
he knows what he's doing.
No, listen,
there's another route.
(Stammers, frantic)
Just... close...
They're like almost outside.
Listen to me.
Shut up! Shut up!
David: Guys, just do
what you have to do.
Just do it fast.
Before I got
David, no.
You don't have to do this.
Listen to me, David.
David:
Almost there...
They're just outside the door.
Wait for it.
Ed:
Let's go.
Please, David, no.
David: - Almost...
Spike: - No.
Guys, let's go.
Spike: - David, stop.
David: - One more second.
Spike:
David...
Spike: - No!
David: - Almost...
Ed:
Let's go.
Ed, Ed...
Ed: - Tar!
Sam: - C4! Move, move, move!
Spike: - No!
David: - Do it! Do it now!
Spike:
No! No!
(Explosion booms)
Eddie!
Anyone? Status?
Team one, somebody talk to me!
(Muffled cries)
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey!
Why did you do that?
I did everything
that you wanted!
It's not over yet.
- It is for me.
- Get them out.
Why should I?
You already killed four cops,
what else can you do?!
Go ahead, threaten me,
it's done.
(Muffled screams)
Spike:
No!
Albin: - David!
Spike: - Leave her alone!
Natalie:
(Muffled scream)
No! Let her go!
Albin: - David!
Spike: - Leave her alone!
David, let's get outta here.
Finish what you started.
Finish what you started!
(Breathing heavily, seething)
(Irate)
Agh! Aggghhhhh!
Team one, talk to me!
Come on.
Ed:
(Coughs) Boss, no harm.
Sam got us out in time,
he got the door closed.
It's good to hear.
There's debris,
but we can get through.
Okay, you got an exit
east wing hall...
One flight up.
Okay, Sam, Jules,
circle around from the outside.
Raf, you and me.
Okay, me and you here.
Slow and careful.
(Keys clack, computer beeps)
They're on the move.
What?
Albin:
They're closing in.
We're done.
It's time to cut our losses,
David.
David: No-no-no-no-no-no.
We're almost there.
We just,
we gotta see this through!
What? No...
(Stammers)
No, David,
we're not almost there,
this is a mess.
No, it's not a mess.
We can't be here, David.
We're out of time.
You know, they're probably
already tracking us.
Listen to me, okay?
We can still do this.
Albin:
No, I said we're done!
You are not calling the shots
here, okay!
Oh yeah?
It's time to call it a day.
David: Hey! Hey!
We still need him!
Albin: - Shut up!
Spike: - You don't wanna do this!
David:
We're not through, Albin!
Albin:
Him first, then her.
Put the gun down!
No! We're doing this
my way!
Put the gun down!
(Gunshot pops)
This doesn't change anything.
I bought you five minutes.
Get them out.
Get them out!
Team one, I've got Spike's
last phone conversation
from the auto-transcripter.
Give it to us, Winnie!
Winnie: Okay, I was only
able to get his half,
so I'm not sure how much sense
this is gonna make.
It starts,
"hey, it still isn't you."
Then, "I can come by
after shift."
Then, "who's David?"
Then, "get you?
Are you in trouble?
I'm gonna tell Sam."
Sam:
Natalie...
Jules: - Who's David?
Sam: - I know him.
He's trouble.
What else did Natalie say?
Winnie:
Spike was getting directions.
He said,
"that's near Witchwood, right?"
Well, it narrows it down
to a neighbourhood.
Okay, it's a place to start.
I'm on my way.
Winnie, you get me some more
by the time I get there.
Sam:
Boss, I'm coming with you.
Sam, can you do this with me?
She's my sister.
Okay, Sam,
you're with the boss.
Jules, command post
in case we get our eyes back.
Raf, it's you and me.
They're armed to the teeth.
So are we.
Kenton: 'Kay, pop this thing.
Let's go.
Why's that door locked?
The locks must've reset.
Unset them.
It's no use, it's manual.
We shoot this,
the unis know we're here.
Kenton:
We need another exit.
Scarlatti, this exit's no good.
They need something different.
I'm looking.
(Computer trills)
(Computer beeps)
Sam: Natalie was
traveling for three years.
She had her freedom,
she was happy, you know?
And the day she's coming home
we get a call from Bogota,
she's in jail.
Apparently she's unaware
that this guy she met,
David, had packed her suitcase
with heroin.
Luckily for her,
his fingerprints
were all over the place.
So my dad pulled
every string he had.
As long as she testified
against him,
the charges would be dropped.
There's no love lost
between this David
and Natalie then.
Sam: I'm guessing he'd be happy
to see her out of the picture.
Hey, Eddie,
we have to stall for time.
We need them
to need Spike alive.
Copy that.
Let's move.
Spike:
Okay, right there.
They can backtrack
the way they came in.
That doesn't work.
That's the best I got.
David:
Find something else.
Everything else is a dead end.
Find another way.
It's okay, looks like
we're going in heavy.
How's this work?
They said the perimeter's
would be thin.
These are hollow point,
more effective.
We're gonna bust right through.
Boss, I think I got something.
Figured it had to be somebody
who knew what to look for.
Vince Albin,
mid-level soldier working for...
Parker:
Karl Morse.
Sam:
So he knew about the dope.
There's gotta be dozen guys
who did.
Jules:
Yeah, but according to customs,
when David Fleming flew back
into the country last month,
he flew back in with Albin.
They have a history?
That doesn't tell us
where they are.
Jules: Well, maybe it does.
'Cause after Morse got busted,
all his assets were seized,
went into foreclosure,
including a bunch of houses.
Any near Witchwood?
Sending you the number
right now.
Ed:
Police! Stay where you are!
End of the line.
Time to put the guns down.
Do it now.
That's it, slow and careful.
Sorry about this.
(Gunshot pops)
Hollings: Agghhh! You shot me!
What're you doing?!
Kenton:
Now, I have a hostage.
Kenton, what the hell
just happened?
What's going on?
You have a hostage?
Kenton:
I shot Hollings.
The cop was getting too close;
I had to improvise.
David:
(Exasperated sigh)
SRU caught up.
Kenton took Hollings hostage.
This was not the plan.
This was quick and clean,
in and out.
No one even knows.
(Cocks gun)
David, this could still work.
Your guy is right;
The team has to negotiate now,
that's the protocol,
and I can do it for you.
Gimme the mic.
Raf, that gate...
Raf:
Out flank 'em?
Go, now.
Hollings:
(Quick, tight breaths)
Give me the mic,
I can get them out.
But they have to do exactly
what I tell 'em to say.
You have a gun.
If I don't get them out,
you can use it.
Hey, can you hear me?
Mm-hm.
That was a smart thing
you did there,
grabbing a hostage;
it changes the game.
Now, I can get you outta there,
but you have to say exactly
what I tell you to say.
Do you understand?
Uh-huh.
Start with,
"I just want to talk."
Kenton:
I just wanna talk.
Okay. You mind telling me
your name?
Trying to make
a personal connection.
Tell him,
"I'll tell you my name,
if you tell me yours."
Kenton:
You tell me yours,
I'll tell you mine.
Ed:
No problem.
Ed Lane,
Strategic Response Unit.
Spike: Ask him how long
he's been on the force.
How long you been
in uniform, Ed?
Come on now,
you're not here to talk
about that, are you?
Spike: Hey, Ed,
let's not rush things.
We got all the time
in the world.
No need to rush things, Ed.
We got all the time
in the world.
Ed:
Hey, I'm not in any rush.
I'm just saying,
you got an injured colleague
here.
I need to know he's okay.
Kenton: He's okay. He's fine.
Right, buddy?
Ed: Okay, good. Now, listen.
My team can hear
what's going on.
They know your friend's gonna
need medical attention ASAP.
Kenton: One paramedic
, send in just one.
And everyone else
keep their distance.
Parker: - Spike...
Ed: - No problem.
Ed: We just wanna
stop the bleeding.
We'll take it from there.
Kenton:
Okay.
'Kay, boss,
you go through here.
I'm going high; Fire escape then down.
Copy that.
Ed: Can you tell me
your name again?
Kenton:
I didn't tell you my name.
Okay.
You mind telling me
what you're doing here?
Kenton: I don't wanna
talk about that.
I want you
to not do anything rash,
or people could get hurt.
This guy's talking
like a negotiator.
Sam: It might be Spike
in his headset, boss.
It's gotta be.
He's dragging it out.
Ed, do not take this guy down.
Repeat, do everything you can
to keep this going.
We do that, that hostage
is gonna bleed out, boss.
Parker: And we do anything
else and they kill Spike.
Okay...
How's your buddy doing there?
Kenton:
He's gonna be just fine
as long as you do everything
I ask you to do, Ed.
(Lock clicks)
Sam?
Almost there.
Now, calmly state your demands.
(Muffled sobs)
Stay back.
Stay back!
Ed:
All right.
Kenton:
We need a way outta here, Ed,
me and my friend.
Well, I think your friend
needs medical assistance.
Raf: In position,
just give me a signal.
What we need is a car.
In position.
Ed:
All right, Raf,
on my mark.
Kenton: Stay back.
Don't come any closer!
Ed: - Now.
Kenton: - My friend, Ed...
Raf:
Freeze!
Ed: Put the gun down!
Turn around!
Ed: On your knees!
To your knees!
We need an EMS
to the rear loading bay
immediately.
(Device beeps)
Cops.
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
Natalie:
(Muffled screams)
Spike:
No! No!
Police Strategic Response Unit.
Let her go!
David:
Back off!
Parker:
I can't do that, sir.
Now, you put the gun down
and step away from the girl.
Do it now, please.
David:
We are walking out of here.
You're not going anywhere.
How're you doing, Spike?
Spike: Could use a set
of handcuff keys.
Copy that.
(Keys jingle)
Parker: Sir, I need you
to put that gun down,
and step away from the girl.
You're not going anywhere.
Please, I need you
to listen to me.
Spike:
No! Don't listen to him!
(Chair clatters)
(Riled up) Listen to me!
Maybe you get past us.
Maybe by some miracle
you get outta the country.
You know what?
Doesn't matter.
Spike, that's enough.
I don't care
what third-world jungle
you hide out in,
I will find you.
Whatever I have to do,
I will do.
Device is set, ready for entry.
I will never forget you.
Not after what you did
my friend's sister,
and not after what you did
to my team.
Back off!
Spike:
Why?
Why, you wanna shoot me?
Go ahead.
Go ahead!
Shoot me!
Parker:
Sam!
(Blast pops, glass shatters)
Spike: You're okay.
Natalie, it's okay.
Sam: You're done, dirtbag!
On the ground!
Natalie:
(Crying)
Spike: Okay, it's okay now.
You're safe now.
Natalie:
(Frantic breaths)
You're okay.
(Sobbing)
♪
♪ is this a mystic's
deep dark spell ♪
♪ or a joke to make us
come undone and yell ♪
♪ another blackness
tries again ♪
♪ to bend our will
behind our backs ♪
♪ and hold us down ♪
♪ till we say when...
Will this be over? ♪
♪ when... ♪
♪ will we be free in the end? ♪
Raf:
(Laughs)
My man.
Jules: "Whatever third-world
jungle you may hide out in?"
"I'll find you.
I will never forget you?"
- You good?
- I'm good.
How's Nat?
I think she'll be fine.
That was a lot for her today.
You sure she should be alone?
Sam:
As soon as we're done here,
I'm gonna go home,
make her a nice dinner.
Guys, I just wanna say...
I'm sorry.
I made some choices today,
I pulled you guys into trouble.
Yeah, but you didn't choose
that trouble.
I didn't know what else to do,
so I turned to you.
Jules: Someone needed
you and you reached out.
Where's the part
where you made the wrong choice?
This is gonna sound crazy,
but I think of Lou...
And my dad,
and today I nearly lose
you guys.
And I start thinking...
Anybody who gets close to me-
Parker:
Spike.
Without you around...
(Chuckles warmly)
Buddy, we'd fall apart.
You hear me?
Been a long day.
What do you say
we debrief tomorrow,
go to the goose, grab a beer,
call our loved ones?
What do you think, boss?
Call my loved ones.
♪ Clear water, clear ♪
♪ so deep that
we can all come clean ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com