(Gunshot pops, glass shatters)
(Breathing heavily)
Go, go, go.
(Gunshots blast,
glass shatters)
(Boots thud heavily)
Jules: Whitter's safe
in the stairwell.
I lost him.
(Thunder rumbles)
(Rain pours)
(Guns click)
(Lighter lid clinks open)
(Lighter snaps shut)
(Gun cocks)
Donna: Who else was
gonna give me away?
My dad's gone,
my sister's overseas...
Hank loved the idea.
Ed: Absolutely.
I mean, we're family, right?
Who's Hank again?
(Feigned titter)
(Sighs)
What's going on?
I don't know.
Ed:
Tell me.
So, you know I was a beat cop
for eight years.
Ed: Yeah.
Donna: Vice for 10.
Right.
Donna:
SRU for two now.
I met Hank
and I started wondering,
is this all I am?
Ed: Donna, you're one
of the best cops
I've ever served with.
So, come on.
Donna:
How many co get married?
Ed: I don't know, most of them.
All of 'em.
Can't do it alone.
'Kay.
How many stay married?
Why is that?
Is it the hours?
The people they're choosing
to marry?
Maybe the job just
changes you.
I know I was a totally
different person
before I became a cop.
Where're you going with this?
After my honeymoon, I'm...
I'm gonna take my package.
Early retirement.
(Takes a deep breath)
Winnie: Team one, we have a
second report of shots fired.
Parker:
On our way, Winnie.
Spike: No visible
activity outside the house.
Boss, we have eyes
on the vehicle.
Parker:
Copy. Approach with caution.
We still haven't confirmed
the nature of this call.
Gunshot confirmed.
Victim is female,
D.O.A.
(SUV engine rumbles)
Sam:
The house is clear,
Spike and Raf are patrolling
the block.
Copy that.
Another sighting,
Winona Drive,
white male, armed,
fits the description.
Raf: I'm one over from Oakwood,
what's the cross-street?
Jules:
Ah, closest would be Davenport.
Copy.
Stop! Police!
(Violinist plays
classical melody)
(Low hum of chatter)
She'll be here.
Hank:
I'm not nervous,
I'm just... happy.
(Laughs)
Ungh!
(Man lands hard)
(Violinist plays,
guests chatter)
Hank:
I'm happy.
Oh, here we go.
You can still change your mind.
Donna:
Oh, I asked him, remember?
Ed: I mean about
leaving the force.
Donna: Oh my God, shut
up and give me away.
(Car horn blares)
(Violinist plays,
cameras click, guests murmur)
Raf: He's running through
the elementary school!
Ed:
Here we go.
You look great.
Donna:
Thank you.
- Hi.
Raf:
We're in the schoolyard.
Minister:
Friends, what a happy day.
What a time for joy,
when people come together
and make the most important
change imaginable...
Raf:
Stop!
Headed to Davenport.
(Fence rattles)
Minister: Let these rings
be a reminder of your vows
and your love for each other.
May it renew itself
for every day
you have together.
(Fence rattles, raf grunts)
Minister: And now, by the
power invested in me,
I pronounce you
husband and wife.
Well, go on,
this is the good part.
Donna and guests:
(Laugh)
(Applause)
Stop!
(Car tires screech,
glass shatters, body thuds)
Minister: Friends, it is
my honour and privilege
to present to you all,
Mr. Hank Gerald
and Mrs. Donna Gerald.
Male:
Somebody, please help
please!
Please, somebody help me!
Somebody!
Please, someone help me!
Gun! Stop!
Get down!
(Two gunshots blast,
glass shatters, guests scream)
You all right?
Yeah, I'm good. Go.
Ed:
You okay?
It's not me.
Where is it?
Hank: I'm okay.
Donna: Are you all right?
Pete?
(Gasping for breath, groans)
Donna:
Okay... look at me.
Man:
Donna, let me help.
It's Tom, team three, right?
Yeah.
I'm gonna go after the shooter.
Tom:
I'll back you up.
Ed: No, go after them
they're part of it.
Ed, you need a sidearm.
Ed!
Someone with a cell phone
call 911.
Gimme your neck tie.
It's all right. All right.
Look at me. Look at me.
Raf: Subject's wallet.
Stainton: Thanks.
Mike Garvis.
Well, we got victim,
shooter, weapon.
We gotta call you guys
more often.
What about motive?
Ha! Don't tell me
you got that too.
You're gonna put me
outta business, Parker.
Jules: - Boss.
Parker: - Yeah.
Just got off the phone with Ed;
he's at a shots fired call.
Parker:
He's at Donna's wedding?
That's where the shots
were fired.
Okay, let's move, let's go.
(Two gunshots blast)
Two at the wedding...
Assailant:
(Pants heavily)
And two on the path.
Reverend.
Sergeant Parker with the SRU.
There was a guest here,
a police officer,
he ran after the shooter.
Yes, yes.
There were two.
The first went that way,
but he told another officer
to got that way over there.
Sam: Okay, Raf, take east.
I'll head west.
Ed: (Into cell phone)
Call Greg Parker.
(Parker's cell rings)
Excuse me.
Eddie?
Eddie, Sam's on foot,
he's looking for you.
What's your twenty?
Ed: Tell him to go through
the park to the marina,
dock four.
Parker: I copy, Eddie
, but are you armed?
What're you carrying?
Ed: Doesn't matter what I have,
he's only got a revolver.
(Gunshot pops)
Five.
Donna:
Right to the top now.
Spike, super tight,
I'm not letting go.
Jules, ems?
Jules:
Yeah, they're here.
Hank:
It's okay, it's okay.
Donna, I want to...
Not now, Hank, I'm sorry.
Hey, Donna Sabine, SRU.
Victim is male,
mid-30's,
gunshot wound
to the upper thigh,
possible femoral artery.
Officer:
What'd you see?
Three guys...
Over here, one guy over here.
The gunshot came
from that side.
(Gunshot pops, glass shatters)
Ed!
And that's six.
Stay back!
(Gun clicks)
They count the shots.
How's your day off going?
Guess I'm back on the job.
♪
Flashpoint Season 4, Episode 12
A New Life
Original Air Date: November 1, 2011
♪
==sync, correction by dcdah==
for www.addic7ed.com
♪
I was almost on him
when he drew on me.
He's maybe five feet away
from a group of women,
one of them has a baby,
and this guy starts shooting.
So I got to the women
and covered them,
but he was gone
by the time they were secure.
Look, I know it
doesn't feel like it,
but that was a good call, Tom.
How the hell was Lane so sure
is what I wanna know.
Ed:
New York City, 1965.
Sam:
1965?
Ed:
Crowd of about 400 people,
some guy yells "get your hand
out of my pocket!"
When everybody looks at him,
Malcolm X takes a shotgun blast
to the chest.
It's a smart tactic.
It almost worked here.
History channel -
you should look into that.
Planning on it.
Just waiting 'til I'm 70, sir.
Ed:
(Chuckles)
All right, we still have
one active shooter here.
Your guy talking? No.
But he's got a record...
B & E and assault.
Liam Garvis.
Garvis?
Garvis.
The call we had earlier,
that kid's name was Garvis too.
Could be related.
Ed: Who was the victim
on that shooting?
We don't know yet.
Sam:
I'll find out.
Maybe there's a connection
with Donna's friend.
We gotta ID the shooter here.
You wear that to the wedding?
The tux was a rental.
(Chuckles)
Jules: Is there anyone you know
who might be threatening Pete?
No, I...
Um, he's in IT
like me.
Who would threaten him?
Does he owe any money?
Is he a gambler?
Gamble?
(Laughs ruefully)
No. You guys sound really close.
Yeah, we, uh...
Grew up in
the same neighborhood,
went to the same school.
First computer I ever got,
he helped me set it up.
Just a couple of techies.
(Exhales)
Look...
I-I don't know anything
about any of this.
You're not supposed to.
This must all seem
kinda normal for you, right?
Because of...
What you do?
What Donna does?
Normal? No.
No, this is...
It's never normal.
It's just, it's the job.
Okay.
According to our guests,
our yelling guy's six feet.
No, he was 5'2".
He was wearing boots.
No, he was wearing shoes.
At least they can agree
it was a "he."
I got three guests
that swear it was a woman.
Maybe we got some help.
(Murmuring over police radio)
Donna:
Hi.
(Sighs)
How's Pete?
He's stable.
They're putting him
in the ambulance.
It's leaving now.
I wanna go to the hospital
with him.
I should come with you.
No. Don't you have to stay
and uh...
Do your job?
Hank, you see
how crazy this is?
This is my job,
That's why I want out.
I've never seen you
like that before,
doing what you do.
You were amazing.
Ed:
Donna.
There's something
I need to show you.
I'm going with Hank.
I got my phone, you call me.
If you need to stay, stay.
I'll be waiting for you.
Okay?
Yeah.
I love you, and I'm sorry.
(Exhales, emotional)
- I'll see you soon.
- Okay.
- Okay...
- You got a lead?
Yes, I do.
Let's go.
Ed: We found the car
two blocks over.
We got an eyewitness
who saw the shooters
getting out of it.
Car was clean, no registration.
They left these.
Is that the police news letter?
Yeah, that's us in Mexico.
Of course, it's about me.
Why'd they shoot Pete?
Spike.
That's our runner.
Raf's matching
for facial recognition.
But then we saw this...
Man:
Please, someone help me!
Ed:
Gun! Stop!
Get down!
Spike:
He was bumped.
Ed, I don't think they meant
to shoot Pete.
Donna, I think they meant
to shoot you.
(Sighs)
All those years as a cop,
Eddie,
it could be anybody.
Sean Garvis.
He's the brother
of Mike and Liam -
our other two kids.
Sam: Homicide ID'd the woman
from this morning: Ruth Comax.
Ed: Ruth Comax.
That ring any bells?
No. Well, apparently
her ex is a cop.
They split up just a month ago.
He's living in a motel,
Ruth got the house.
Wait, is this Joe Comax,
over in fraud?
I think so.
Ed:
He used to be in vice.
You ever do anytime with him
back in the day?
Donna: I don't know Comax!
I don't know the guy!
Okay, okay.
Parker: Well maybe that Garvis
kid didn't mean to get the wife.
Maybe he saw the car,
assumed Joe was driving it
and ran up shooting.
Sam:
Not much of a hitman.
Ah, none of them are hitmen.
They were all small-time
up until today.
The biggest charge they got
is getting busted holding dope
for this local drug gang,
the uh... the Logans.
(Exhales, knowing)
What is it?
They're not a gang,
they're a family.
The Logan family.
Vice, undercover,
we did a huge op...
Over a year.
There was me, my partner,
there were some other cops.
But we were deep under;
I have no idea who they were.
Parker: I remember that.
You busted them wide open,
you sent the head of the family,
Calum Logan,
away for life, right?
Crown had enough evidence,
we didn't testify.
They're a real special kind
of mean, the Logans.
So our identities
were kept a secret.
Okay, let's move.
Looks like the secret's out.
Okay, so we have at least
one active shooter,
possibly gunning
for former members
of Donna's undercover team.
Parker: It could be some
young up and comer,
trying to impress his new boss
and doesn't give a crap
about collateral damage.
Okay, Spike,
I need the names
of those undercover cops.
Anybody gets in your way,
you call to the chief
immediately.
Parker: Let's find 'em
, bring 'em to SRU HQ.
They'll be safer there.
Raf, you and I'll go talk
to the Logan family personally.
You think they'll talk to us?
Parker:
I don't need them to talk.
I just need them to listen.
Donna: I need to make one
of those calls myself.
Parker: No way, Donna.
You're going to SRU too.
You're laying low.
I'm a gun team leader, Greg.
Ed: Okay, Donna, we know
this is your old case...
The man who ran
the undercover squad,
Bill Kedrick,
my partner for three years.
He was closer to the Logans
than anybody.
If they know his name
or where he is,
- he's next.
- Fine.
We put an all call out,
if he's on shift,
he'll hear it.
Yeah, but he took
a leave of absence.
He's in the wind.
He's not near a radio.
I know where he is.
I'm going to him.
Ed: Okay, okay. You know what?
You and I'll go, all right?
Grab a vest, we'll go.
She's on the edge, Eddie.
I know, I know.
I'm gonna keep her
from falling off.
Okay.
Parker:
Okay, team,
there were five UC officers
on the Logan case:
Sabine, Duceppe, Laputto,
Whitter and Kedrick.
What's your status, guys?
We're putting Greg Duceppe
in a car right now.
That three leaves more
on the list.
Jules: Just leaving Phil
Laputo's apartment.
Unis are escorting to SRU
as we speak.
Parker:
All right, that's good.
That leaves us two former
undercover cops to bring in.
So far, no word on any other
attempted hits.
That's a good thing.
Jerry Whitter is next up.
I want the three of you
to go find him.
He retired last year.
What about the name Kedrick?
Ed and Donna have got
that one covered.
Well, then you better fix it,
I guess.
(Phone keys beep)
Yeah, it's me.
No, some complications.
But nothing we can't fix.
And Kedrick?
I'll handle him myself.
Still no answer?
No.
That doesn't mean anything.
He could be out,
or sleeping it off,
I don't know.
Yeah.
And no family we can contact?
Donna:
No, he never settled down.
He said with our life,
it wouldn't be fair.
We were his family.
Ed: You know, when
I was in guns and gangs,
half the busts were due to him.
I know.
He taught me a lot.
Yeah, three years undercover
together.
You must've been close.
Donna: Yeah, we were deep.
We were...
Just the two of us.
He called me last night
to wish me congratulations.
Hey, Don, it's me.
Uh...
Just saw the news and I just...
I'm probably the last guy
you wanna hear from,
but I just honestly
wanted to say...
Congratulations.
And um...
That's it, I guess.
Bye.
Donna: Picked up the message
just before the wedding.
You didn't invite him?
Parker: Raf and I are
at the Logan's bar.
Keep your sidearm ready.
What, you think
they'd draw on us?
I don't know
what they're gonna do.
Ida Logan?
(Sighs heavily)
I am through talking with cops.
My husband made no
deathbed confessions.
Stomach cancer takes
the talk out of you,
in the end.
When did your husband pass,
ma'am?
I'm losing track.
You folks keep finding reasons
not to release the body.
I don't know, two weeks?
Mrs. Logan,
I'm very sorry for your loss.
But what's happening right now,
what your family is doing?
It'll destroy you
and your family completely.
I'm sorry, what...
my family's doing?
What we're doing is grieving.
If this was
your husband's idea,
please,
take the opportunity
and call it off.
I am asking you, please,
to leave us alone now.
We have nothing to do
with your trouble.
Show some respect!
Raf:
Uh, Mrs. Logan,
one of the Garvis brothers
died today.
He worked for your family.
Let me tell his mother
what happened.
We already have one
of his brothers in custody
and we can bring
the other one in safely
if you'll just...
If you'll just stop this.
Having people you trust
sit with you,
act like family,
and then betray you
and leave you like this?
I would say
to those boys' mothers,
"I am sorry,
my heart breaks for you."
But this is worse.
Much... worse.
Thanks for your time.
Sam:
Boss, you there?
Go ahead, Sam.
We're still looking
for Whitter.
No answer at his place,
no cell phone listed.
Spike:
Might have something.
Neighbour says
the Whitters play racquetball
every Friday.
Club's at Bay and Charles.
Same club, every week.
Sam:
Jules, you anywhere near there?
I'm on my way.
Parker: Okay, let me know
as soon as you find him.
That guy who just left?
You get a look at his ring?
Raf:
Nah.
Police association.
You get it at retirement.
What's a retired cop doing
hanging around the Logans?
That's what I'd like to know.
22, right?
Yeah.
(Knocks twice)
Bill?
(Knocks)
Bill, it's Donna.
(Door crashes open)
Donna:
Bill!
Bill? Are you in here?
Bill.
It's all right.
(Panting heavily)
Donna, what...
Arne't you supposed to be
getting married?
Whitter's game should be over;
I'm heading in.
We're on our way.
Woman:
Nice game.
Whitter:
Well, I was winning.
(Woman) - I know.
(Whitter) - I was winning.
Jerry Whitter, Metro PD?
Uh, used to be, yeah.
Everything all right?
It will be.
I need you guys
to come to my truck.
Okay.
Did you notice anybody
following you today,
or anything
out of the ordinary?
No.
A nice quiet day.
(Gunshot blasts)
Shots fired.
Gun it, let's go!
(Siren wails)
(Frightened murmurs)
(Gunshot pops, glass shatters,
woman shrieks)
You okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
(Breathing heavily)
Donna:
You drink this.
Then we need to talk.
Just tell me what I did, Don.
Just drink it.
(Grunts) Mm...
Could use a little something
to spice it...
No.
We need to talk.
Aw, come on, is this a uh...
Intervention?
No offense, buddy,
aren't you supposed to know
the guy getting intervented.
So do I know you?
No, sir.
This isn't an intervention.
Something happened today, Bill.
Yeah, I know.
Donna: - You know?
Bill: - Yes. It's your big day.
Congrats.
Good for you.
Donna, we don't have
a lot of time here.
Kedrick:
Hey, don't let me keep you.
Donna: Bill, Joe Comax, was
he one of the UC's you used
in the Logan case?
'Cause his wife
was shot dead today.
But we think that
they were aiming for him.
Joe? Why?
Donna: They shot at me today,
Bill, at my wedding.
Kedrick:
Wait, wh-who's this "they"?
Donna:
The Logans.
They know who the UC's are
and they're coming after
everybody.
So, would you please
come with us today?
(Forced exhale)
Jules:
Sam?
Sam:
We're two blocks away.
All right,
top of the parking garage.
Southeast stairwell.
You're gonna come up
behind him,
we're on the other side.
Sam:
Copy that.
(Five gunshots pop,
glass shatters, tire hisses)
Jules:
I'm gonna cover you.
I want you to go the stairwell,
Carol's gonna stay here
with me.
I'm gonna try and pin this guy
until my team gets here.
Sir, for your safety,
I need you outta here.
Kedrick:
Look, you gotta protect them.
I got their names,
I kept them here somewhere.
Bill, we have the list;
We got it from vice.
We're covering them.
Sorry, Donna.
Donna:
It's not on you, Bill.
Look, if I was half the partner
I should've been -
I used to be...
I could've at least been there
for you today.
You guys go, okay?
I'm gonna head down to vice
and see what I can do.
Okay, Bill,
for your own safety,
we need you to come with us.
Bill:
No. I'm fine, all right?
Please, please come.
Donna, I don't need
a babysitter.
Yes... you do.
Parker: Eddie, Jules has taken fire.
She needs backup.
Fast is good.
Donna, we gotta move now.
Donna:
I'm not going without him.
Ed: Winnie's called a squad
car, we gotta go now.
Will you wait for them?
Swear.
Swear you'll stay right here.
Lock the door.
Hey, Don...
Thanks for coming back, huh?
Not everyone would've.
Donna:
Just lock the door.
Don't say anything.
Ed:
What're you talking about?
You should've seen him
back in the day.
He's why I left undercover.
'Cause that's
what happens to you.
That's Bill Kedrick up there.
I need you to get him
to the SRU immediately.
Anybody comes at you,
anything seems off?
You call for backup.
Uniform: - Got it.
Ed: - Let's go.
Sam?
Sam:
We're seconds away, Jules.
Jules: Copy.
Sending Whitter your way.
Okay.
Whitter's wife:
Be careful.
Love you.
Go, go, go.
(Pants heavily)
(Gunshots pop)
Jules: Whitter's
safe in the stairwell.
I lost him.
(Gunshot pops)
Mr. Kedrick?
Check the perimeter.
(Car keys jingle,
siren wails in the distance)
Hey, Bill.
You son of a bitch!
All this time a friend, huh?
A brother?
Greene:
Where you going, Bill?
You know by now
they're putting two and two
together...
What you told me.
I never would've
told you anything!
Is that what you're gonna say
when they got you downtown?
Why all your old friends
are being hunted down?
'Cause you saw my pawnshop ring
and thought I was a cop.
Bill:
I never gave you their names!
Not their full names.
But you gave me plenty:
First names, dates and details.
Enough to lead to the death
of several people.
The guy doesn't even know
we're both cops.
Which guy is this?
Calum Logan.
No, no... the other cop.
The UC who was with you.
Who? This is the guy
that plays basketball.
Jerry!
Did I tell you Jerry
plays racquetball?
Doesn't matter.
- Calum Logan.
- To Calum Logan.
When the bust goes down.
Yeah. You get to see
the look in his...
On his face.
(Moans weakly)
Where you gonna go now, Bill?
I mean, you're in it
and we both know you got no one.
If the force thought of you
as family,
you wouldn't be where you are.
So let us help you.
Us?
Get in.
There's something
I need you to do.
I trusted you.
And my husband trusted you.
There's something
you have to do for us.
(Breathes shakily)
No, I don't care
what happens to me.
I'm not doing that.
Ida:
Unless you do what you're told,
your friend will die.
Ed:
Sam.
Got here as quick as we could.
You all right?
Yeah, all good.
SIU took my hand piece,
said we'll debrief
after the call.
Ed:
Okay. Okay.
Jules:
So the subject's down.
All the other UC's
accounted for.
I think we're good, right?
What's going on?
Parker: We saw this
guy at the Logan's,
thought he might be a cop.
Turns out his name
is Peter Greene.
He got out of federal prison
last year.
He's done everything.
Sort of a freelance consultant
to the criminal underworld.
Well, since he got out,
vice is trying
to keep tabs on him.
Let me see.
Donna, that's Bill Kedrick's
apartment building.
Gotta be a good reason
for that.
Kedrick would never deal
with the Logans.
Parker: This photo was
taken last week, Donna,
and they have others too.
Donna: Well, if vice saw
him at Bill's place,
why didn't they
pick him up there?
Parker:
They didn't know.
Donna, you said yourself,
he moves around.
He hasn't been on the job
in a while.
He's off the radar.
And ask yourself this:
Who else would know
the identities
of those undercover cops?
The man I know
would never do it. Never!
Donna, you said yourself,
you don't even know this guy
anymore.
Parker: Vice just wants
to sit down with him,
get it all straightened out.
You know, the gunman
got the jump on me
because he went for Carol.
We thought
he was after whitter,
but he was actually after
Whitter's wife.
Ed:
And the shooting today,
the victim is the wife
of an undercover cop.
Parker: That picture of
you that they had...
In Mexico -
me and Hank.
Sam: They weren't ever
trying to get the cops.
No, they're after the wives
and your husband.
Hank's at the hospital.
I mean, even if it is true,
hitting that wedding,
that's risky.
(Cell phone rings)
Yeah.
You're kidding me?
Where the hell is he?
Yeah, okay.
Thanks, thanks.
Hank's not at the hospital.
He just left with
a plainclothes police escort.
It's him.
It's Kedrick.
He ducked the escort.
It's him.
Hank: We should call
Donna, let her know.
I told you,
first thing we need to do
is to get you to a safe place.
But what does this
have to do with me?
Kedrick: Look, you may have
been the target, all right?
Donna would want you
to be safe.
She ever tell you about me?
Yeah, she did.
Yeah? What'd she say?
She said you were
the best partner she ever had,
and her best friend.
Right. So...
Trust me on this, all right?
Jules: Guys, I got a lock on
the GPS on Hank's phone.
Ed:
Copy that.
Let's see if we can figure out
where they're going.
Spike: Ed, that
turn-off they just took,
there's an empty warehouse.
Let's bring in the E.M.T.
Donna:
Bill took the Logan's down.
I don't care
what happened after,
he was the best guy
undercover ever had.
If he has Hank,
then he's doing it because
he's trying to keep him safe.
Donna, I saw his file.
He didn't take
a leave of absence,
he was let go.
"Conduct unbecoming."
The drinking,
the suspected drug abuse,
insubordination...
Donna: He was undercover
too long, Greg.
He needed help.
And when he started to stumble,
everybody that he trusted
and worked with
didn't wanna see the price
that he paid,
so they just turned
their backs on him.
Like being "weak"
was contagious.
(Knock at the door)
Hey.
Kedrick:
I got nothing to say to you.
Donna:
I'm sorry, Bill.
Kedrick:
I don't want to hear it.
I sat in that hearing
for half an hour, alone.
My team, my brothers,
they all turned
their backs on me.
But you, Donna?
I had a call.
Kedrick: You know, I
kept saying to myself,
she's gonna be here
because I trained her up right?
She's going to be here.
I planned to be there.
I had a call.
I'm an SRU team leader, Bill,
I got more than one back
to watch.
You remember
what I said to you,
first day we were
on the job together?
I said, "whatever happens
in this job,
whatever this job makes you do
or turns you into,
you're gonna be okay
"because no matter what,
I have your back."
That is supposed to be
a two-way street.
I have your back!
Kedrick:
Donna, don't lie to me.
Okay.
(Chuckles uncomfortably)
Remember what the other thing
you said to me that day was?
To be a good undercover,
you don't lie.
Because the lies are harder
to remember then the truth.
I don't lie to you, Bill.
I am here for you.
It's too late.
Bill...
Get out.
(Alcohol sloshes)
Go!
We let him down.
Donna, you didn't turn
your back on him.
Donna:
No?
Did you see him
at my wedding today?
Even I couldn't do it anymore.
Hank:
What're we doing here?
It's, uh, safer
than the cop shop.
What about Donna?
Hey, there's nobody around,
what do you need that for?
(Tearing up)
This isn't who I am.
Look, I have no choice.
No!
I'm sorry.
(Gunshot pops, Hank cries out)
(Grunts and moans)
(Gunshot pops)
Kedrick:
I'm so sorry, Don.
(SUV's rumble forward,
siren wails)
Ed: Go, go, go!
Parker: I'm with them, Eddie.
Donna:
Hank! Hank, can you hear me?
Donna: Oh no. Hank? Hank?
Ed: Donna, don't worry.
Ed: - EMS is on the way.
Donna: - I can't find his pulse.
Ed: EMS is on the way.
Don't move him.
(Pounding footsteps)
Ed: Don't move him, don't move him.
EMS is on the way, it's okay.
I can't get a pulse.
Ed: Come on, come on. Let's go!
Donna:
Hank?!
Ed: He's got two gunshot
wounds to the back.
Donna:
I can't stop the flow.
Paramedic: You need to step back.
We have to get him stable.
Don't touch me.
He's my husband, don't.
Ed: Donna, let 'em do their job.
You gotta let 'em do their job.
Paramedic:
Bp is way down.
Donna:
(Sobs) Oh no, no.
No, no, no!
(Anguished cries)
Ed:
Okay...
Okay, okay.
You got him, guys?
Donna. Donna. Donna!
Sam:
Drop your weapon!
Drop it!
Parker:
Bill?
You're as deep as you can get.
Can we stop running now?
(Panting)
Parker: We're in no rush, buddy.
We can talk this through.
Donna: Bill!
Parker: Donna...
Donna, you're in the line
of fire.
Donna:
What'd you do?
Look me in the face, bill.
Look me in the face!
Parker:
Okay, let's start
by both of you
dropping your guns.
Kedrick: I didn't mean for
this to happen, Don, I swear.
Donna: Don't say anything
to me, Bill.
We gotta listen
to what he has to say;
that's what we do here.
Donna:
No, not him. No more.
Parker:
Bill, you were a good cop.
(Whimpers) Yeah, I wa...
I was a good cop.
Parker:
You did your job,
got your man, and then...
Where were you, Don?
Don't talk to me!
Look at me, Bill.
I hear you.
You got left behind.
When I was alone,
where were you?
Where were you?!
I was there always!
Always.
You pushed me away.
How many nights did I take
your drunk ass home?!
Where were you
when it mattered?
I was alone in that bar.
The guy comes in and...
He told me he was a cop,
and he talked to me
like I still mattered.
Donna: All the people that
trusted and believed in you, Bill,
and you gave it up
to some guy in a bar?!
Parker:
Donna, you're not helping.
Please...
We all do it, right?
(Whimpers uncontrollably)
When we trust each other,
we tell our secrets...
When we're alone!
Parker:
Yeah.
Yeah, you didn't mean
to give those names up,
did ya?
I know.
I know that you didn't know
who he worked for, right?
Ed: Donna, he is
gonna face justice,
but we have to do this right.
You shot my husband...
In the back, Bill.
In the back.
Do you remember doing that?!
Kedrick: I did that for you!
I did it to save you!
Donna:
What're you talking about?!
After you left,
they put a gun in my hand.
They told me I was the only one
who could get
your husband alone;
that he had to die.
That's what Logan wanted.
Logan's already dead.
Wasn't him.
It was Ida, it was his wife.
She wanted the hit.
Not at the cops,
but at their families.
They told me if I didn't do it,
if I went to the cops,
that they would kill you.
I couldn't let that happen,
Donna.
I'm sorry.
(Cries pitifully)
I'm so sorry.
No!
(Fires weapon)
No.
His gun's down,
he's not a threat.
You're a police officer.
Get back, guys.
I don't care what I am.
Ed: Give her some room.
Donna, you're a police officer.
I wanna kill him.
Donna, I don't believe that.
Come on now.
Donna: You're not supposed
to contradict me, Ed.
Don't contradict me.
I wanna kill him.
- Donna...
- I wanna kill him.
Donna, come on now.
I hear you're angry,
but shooting him's
not gonna solve anything.
It's not gonna make you
feel better.
Donna:
I don't wanna think, Ed.
Shut up!
Ed:
Can I tell you what I think?
I think that man right there,
that you once loved
and admired,
I think that no matter
how far he's fallen,
no matter what
he's been through,
he is still the man
that made you who you are today.
Now, you shoot him, Donna,
it's over.
You will lose everything.
You will never have
the life you want.
Donna:
But I...
You know the life I wanted
and he took it away.
And what do I have now?
Ed:
That's up to you.
It always is, come on.
It's okay.
Kedrick:
I did it for you, Donna.
Donna: I hate you! (Sobs)
I hate you.
(Anguished sobs)
Ed: Come on, it's okay.
(Murmuring comforting words)
Donna:
(Anguished sobs)
Donna, it's Hank.
He's asking for you.
Donna:
What?
Oh.
♪
How's Hank doing?
He's gonna pull through.
Good.
So much for the honeymoon.
Sam: You really think
she'll leave team three?
We'll see how she feels
after four weeks
of doing nothing all day.
I mean, she can't give up
that easy.
No.
So, hypothetically,
you ever think of a honeymoon?
Love a honeymoon,
hypothetically.
All right, just promise me
it's not daiquiris
on the beach.
Extreme hiking, remote trails,
no outhouses.
Nice! I like it.
Oh, you mean with you?
Flashpoint Season 4, Episode 12
A New Life
Original Air Date: November 1, 2011
==sync, correction by dcdah==
for www.addic7ed.com