Okay, loser buys the coffee.
You're on.
All right.
One.
Two.
You remember how I
take my coffee, right?
Two.
Agh!
Nice shot!
You okay?
Yeah, I just...
I just couldn't get
my breath there.
That's 'cause you
shot in that wind.
Okay, so coffee.
Yeah,
double-double, you bet.
You are
valuable to me out here,
and you wouldn't wanna know
what happens
if you talk to the police
about this conversation.
I know Lainie Summers.
If you ever wanna
see her again...
Oh, Elliot!
This is a message
for Lainie Summers.
Lainie...
By the time you see this...
Um, I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry?
But I wanted to thank you
for being so patient with me
and such a good friend...
But I can't handle this.
I'm sure you
wouldn't want to see her get hurt.
All I can tell you
is there's no other way.
I know you're the only one
who can understand
why I have to do this.
I'm so sorry, Lainie.
Hi, how are you?
Good.
Are we good for today?
Yes, yes, I have the results...
Not a sound.
You see the gun?
You'll be shot
if you try anything.
Are we clear?
I'll give you instructions
as we go.
Walk!
So, Sam said that, uh,
you went to your dad's place
this morning,
had a little round of "golf"?
Yeah.
Yeah, he said you made
a pretty sweet shot.
The wind was at, what, forty
with a three o'clock crosswind?
You make a shot like that,
usually we can't shut you up.
Greg, there's no
story here, all right?
It was a damn golf ball.
Come on, Eddie.
Come on, what's goin' on?
911, what is your emergency?
There's a man trying to
break in across the street.
23 Dittmar.
He's going in.
Oh my God, he's got a gun!
Team,
911 on a possible home invasion.
23 Dittmar.
Confirmed - one armed subject.
Winnie, we're on it.
All the way to the end.
No, it turned out
to be some students
just playing a prank.
Yeah, I gave them a warning.
Help!
Code white! I need backup!
Team one, we
got another hot call.
Attempted abduction, U of T.
I can re-up team two.
Yeah, hold off on that, Winnie.
Sam, Spike,
what's your position?
We're almost at the house.
We're just arriving, boss.
All right, you stay on it.
Winnie, we'll take
the university call.
Keep team two on standby.
Copy.
He jumped in a car.
He went that way!
- What kind of car?
- I don' know.
White, a regular car.
You see a license plate?
Can you describe him?
Um, a white guy in a suit.
White car, no plates.
That's not a lot to go on.
He's long gone.
Let's check the house.
Ma'am, any shots fired?
Um, when he came out
of the house,
he went to the garage,
and then it wouldn't open
so he screwed, um, a...
what do you call it? -
A silencer on the gun,
and then he started
shooting at the lock.
Who lives here?
A single guy, Evan...
No, Elliot.
We hardly know him.
He's super-quiet
and he keeps to himself.
Sam, there's a
car running in here!
Wait here.
Winnie, call an ambulance
and find out who lives here!
Copy.
Elliot, are you in there?!
Elliot, can you hear me?
- Elliot?!
- All clear!
Bullet damaged the lock.
Ma'am, do these
garages have inside doors?
No.
Let's grab the halligans.
Okay, EMS is on its way.
Homeowner's name
is Elliot Thaine.
He's a self-employed accountant.
This is Jules Callaghan,
I'm with the police!
We're here to help!
You're gonna be okay!
We're gonna get this door open!
Guys, this place is like
a blank slate.
No colour, no books,
nothing on the walls,
no photos.
Hang on.
Think I got something.
The man who broke in,
did you ever seen him before?
No, he looked legit.
I mean, he was wearing a suit,
but I've never seen
a visitor there before.
Yeah.
Hold on.
You the one that was attacked?
Lainie Summers
sergeant Parker, officer Lane.
The man had a gun?
- Yeah.
- I got close,
but he got into a crowd
of students.
He's gone.
Either of you
get a look at him?
Dark hair, maybe
six foot, dark clothes.
Any idea where
he was taking you?
No, I got-I got lucky.
I saw the guard.
She decked
him, you know, I jumped in...
Some of the kids helped too.
I just... I don't know.
He didn't like the odds.
He just took off.
Okay, Winnie, we
need UNI's on campus.
Sweep George street,
the quad...
Copy.
Wanna give me a hand with that?
Miss Summers...
Doctor Summers.
Lainie's fine.
Lainie, any idea why someone
would try to abduct you
in broad daylight?
No, I have no idea.
It's okay,
Elliot, we got ya.
No...
How long has he been exposed?
Minimum ten minutes.
He needs oxygen,
non-re-breather mask.
All right, Elliot,
you're gonna be okay?
We need to get him to
the hospital, run tests.
That's a serious amount
of carbon monoxide.
Winnie, call 52,
get a detective
to the hospital.
We need to question him
when he pulls through.
Copy.
Boss, your attempted
abduction, her name's Lainie Summers?
Yes, Spike,
we're with her now.
Elliot Thaine left a
suicide message on his computer
and it was for her.
This message
is for Lainie Summers.
He's apologizing.
He's visibly stressed.
He's upset, saying goodbye.
There's just no other way,
and I hope you can understand.
I'm sorry, Lainie.
Lainie,
you know an Elliot Thaine?
Elliot?
Yeah, of course.
Team one, we have
a hijacked ambulance,
Lansdowne and Dupont.
Lansdowne and Dupont?
You're kidding me.
That's just around the corner!
Two gunmen.
Is one of them in a suit?
Left the attendants
on the side of the road
and took off with the patient.
It's gotta be him.
Elliot Thaine.
- Sam, find that ambulance.
- Copy.
How do you know Elliot?
I'm a neuroscientist.
Elliot is a research subject
of mine.
He's... He's a friend.
Why were you studying him?
Elliot, is...
He's one of a kind.
He has a rare kind
of hypermnesia.
He has exceptional memory?
More than
exceptional, it's perfect.
Limitless.
Like I said, he's...
He's one of a kind.
Elliot, are you in there?!
It's okay, Elliot.
We got ya!
Elliot, can you hear me?!
We need to get him to
the hospital, run tests.
That's a serious amount
of carbon monoxide.
Elliot!
Elliot, what were you thinking?
== sync, corrected by Martzy ==
www.Addic7ed.Com
Okay, team, the ambulance
is heading South on Dansdowne.
I've got transit and taxis
in on the APB,
but the ambulance is running
lights and sirens.
Copy.
Are we clear?
Good.
You see,
nothing's gonna happen to her
as long as
you don't disappoint me.
All right, we're good.
Just make sure you stand...
We don't have her.
There were complications.
Yeah, well, isn't that a shame.
I don't think it's gonna make
much of a difference.
Guys, Lakeshore and Jamison,
the ambulance is stopped
at the intersection.
All right, Winnie,
lock off the traffic.
He tried to kill himself?
Yeah, I'm sorry. We
know that's hard to hear,
but maybe you can help us
understand why.
And why someone
would wanna take him.
One of the first tests
of his memory, I...
I gave him these pages.
Ma-na-ba-fa...
Meaningless random
syllables, four pages of them.
I read them to him
and he recited them back.
That was three years ago.
Last week I asked him
if he still remembered
the syllables.
And he did?
Yup. Also the weather that day,
what he'd had for breakfast,
that we drank ginger tea
and I was a wearing
a peach-coloured shirt.
That's him.
That's quite a gift.
Not the way he sees it.
Our brains are conditioned
to forget selectively.
We forget physical pain,
trauma.
It's how we cope.
We all take that for granted,
but...
Elliot doesn't have
that luxury.
What do you mean?
He lives with constant flashes
of intrusive memory.
They fill every second
of his day.
They can come at any time.
He hears a car honk;
It doesn't just remind him
of one car,
it reminds him of every car
he's ever seen.
They all pop into his head
and they're all honking.
That's why his home
is nearly empty...
the blank walls...
so he avoids
too much stimulation?
He stays away from smells,
sounds, bright colours...
People.
He won't even open his blinds
at home.
Medication,
meditation, hypnotherapy.
He can't control
what he remembers
or what he sees.
So these memories are triggered
by random, ordinary things?
Yup.
He had a hard childhood.
Yeah, he faced a lot of loss,
and everything
he's lived through,
it's with him from the moment
he opens his eyes
until when he goes
back to sleep.
All he wants is a little peace.
Is that why he's suicidal?
I knew that Elliot
was struggling with depression,
I just... I didn't realize
how serious it was
until a couple days ago.
Tequila? Seriously?
Yeah, I read
that if you have enough
you get a little numb,
you don't feel so much.
Play your cards right,
you might even black out.
Ell, you're 30-years-old
and you've never tried Tequila?
Why? Have you?
Oh jeez.
Yeah?
There was a party.
I was about 18-years-old.
My parents were out of town.
It involved me climbing up
onto the baby grand
and singing show tunes.
Very loud.
It was great until
the piano cover cracked
and I got grounded
for six months.
I wish I could have seen that.
No, you don't.
When I heard
how much he was hurting...
I didn't know what to do,
you know?
I'm...
I'm not a therapist,
I'm a researcher.
So this was last night,
and what happened?
Well, at first,
I thought it was working,
everything sort of slowed down.
I didn't "see" so much,
and then the whole room starts
spinning and tipping
and I got sick,
and the taste
and the smell and...
And now that's locked in.
It's another thing locked in.
It's so stupid, Lainie!
I'm sick,
I'm in pain, I need treatment,
and there isn't any
and there never will be...
And there's nowhere safe
for me,
not even at home.
I'm a friend...
And I should've been there
for him.
Lainie, don't blame yourself.
He may be suicidal,
but something else tipped him
over the edge today.
We're approaching
the ambulance.
Copy that.
Why would they just stop?
This is the police
strategic response unit!
Throw your weapons out
of the vehicle
and step out with your hands
where we can see them!
Let's move in.
This is the police!
Come out right now!
On
three, two, one.
No one's in there, Ed.
Elliot's not in the ambulance?
No, they left it as
a distraction to stall us.
Elliot's long gone.
Okay, let's break this down.
Who breaks into a house,
carjacks an ambulance
in broad daylight...
go to all this trouble
just to get their hands on a...
On a human camera?
Elliot drew the rosetta stone?
He saw it at the British
museum when he was eight.
He drew it from memory
when I met him.
That's ancient Egyptian,
demotic script, ancient Greek.
It's a flawless replica.
So Elliot remembers
words, numbers, patterns...
Everything.
Even in languages
he doesn't understand.
So you could send him somewhere
and he could absorb
information undetected,
somewhere you couldn't
bring a camera.
You said he was reclusive.
Who else would know
he could do this?
Oh, we did an interview
on "enquiring minds,"
the TV news magazine.
They featured this drawing.
I mean, it could be anyone.
Hey, you look good, Elliot,
but today your name
is Gregory Cook, okay?
Now, like I said,
they're gonna show us
the security room, okay?
I need you to study
the floorplans
and make sure that
they match the camera angles.
Also, we're gonna be nice and easy.
We're gonna go in,
we're gonna go
for the target, work fast,
and get out.
Yeah.
Meet us at the doors
in 15 minutes.
Stay out of sight, ok?
Until then, yeah.
Eyes open.
I can't. I don't think I can...
Hey, hey!
You can, Elliot.
You can, okay?
Come on, okay?
Looks like they were too busy
to disengage the cameras.
It means we have a
rear and an inside view.
Yup.
Hang on, Elliot,
won't be long.
Barnaby Howe,
senior projects manager.
We spoke on the phone.
Yeah, we were just
talking to each other
about how grateful we are
for your co-operation.
Absolutely.
Keep us on our toes.
Government compliance officers.
We've got another
security spot-check.
Any metal objects
on the tray, please.
Oh.
This scanner's
state-of-the-art,
picks up even
the smallest metal mass.
Arms out.
Hold still, please.
Clear. Proceed.
Mm-hmm.
Please hold still, sir.
Clear. Proceed.
Howard, you'll be our escort.
Security compliance check.
Attention all staff.
We have government security
compliance officers
with us today.
Please give them
your full co-operation.
Thank you.
I won't cramp your style.
Catch you on the way out.
Appreciate it.
Uh, gentlemen, I
just wanted to say
we've had some grave concerns
in regards to...
Hello! We got a face.
Winnie, Spike's sending you
a picture of Elliot's abductor.
Anything you can find.
We've also got an image
on the bumper cam, Winnie.
They switched into a grey van,
marker 6-8-9 4-T-M.
Okay, I'll run the photo
and put an APB out on the van.
What kind of information
is worth the risk
these guys are taking?
Information
worth a lot of money.
Whatta you got, boss?
Okay, team,
Elliot's got an extraordinary
phographic memory.
We're thinking where would
you need a guy like that?
You can get micro-cameras
the size of a freckle.
Why would you use a human,
an unwilling one?
A human gets past
metal detectors.
So somewhere with
tight security,
no photos.
Maybe government, military?
Team one, the
licence plates on that van
are officially bogus.
It's a dead end,
but we do have a match
on our hijacker.
Go, Winnie.
Jay Penak. He's
on the federal watchlist.
He's a frequent flier,
especially to Eastern Europe
and China.
He's well-connected
and he's known to have contacts
with arms dealers.
Of course, weapons.
Don't say anything.
Come on, come on.
Okay, we got three private
companies that do research
A.G.S. Loeb, Brebtech,
and Morton & Floyd.
Okay, I'll get
unmarked cars to all three,
eyes peeled for the van.
Okay, the blind spot,
the blind spot,
which way?
Uh...
We gotta pass two cameras.
Third door on the right...
Just show me, just show me!
Let's go!
Grey van's been sighted
near Tomken and Brittania.
And that's right near...?
A.G.S. Loeb.
- Let's move!
- Let's do it.
Come on in and I'll
review our security protocol.
Okay.
Everything's by the book.
You know there was that
near-breach last year.
Yes, we know.
We tightened everything up.
It's impossible for information
to leave the premises,
physically or virtually.
There are no hard copies
of the research,
no ports in the computers,
and there's no wireless signal
within the facility walls.
So, we're unhackable.
We know.
This shouldn't take long.
They have a contract
with the department of defense
to build a smart gun system.
Details are classified,
but they use
self-guided bullets.
Yeah, the military's been
testing prototypes for a while.
They get this right,
it's the perfect firearm.
Meaning what exactly?
Meaning it will hit
every target every time.
Meaning anybody
who gets his hands on it
will think he's an unstoppable
killing machine.
So if tech like
this hits the street...
You think gang
wars are bad now?
Wait until they have
the firepower of an army.
Greg, it's not gonna matter
how hard we train.
If we start going up against
guys with this kind of force...
I know,
Eddie, let's move!
Mr Howe, this is Ed Lane, SRU.
Sir, we believe there
are unauthorized personnel
on your premises
looking to access
classified information.
That's not possible.
Sir, could you check your logs,
tell me if there are
any unfamiliar personnel
entering the facility
within the last half hour.
We have two security
compliance inspectors,
but they were fully accredited.
Are they still in there?
I'll find out.
One-one-five, come in.
One-one-five, priority!
How's it going?
Almost done.
This is everything, right?
All the notes, test results,
updates?
Everything, I swear to God.
So where do you keep
the prototype?
I said where?
In the lockup.
Show me.
Ed, Sam, Jules, we're going in.
Keep your eyes open
for the van.
Copy.
What's goin' on?
My escort's not responding.
They may have his gun!
Okay.
Ammo?
Which way?
Here.
Is there a
phone in that room?
Yeah, hard-wired.
Call it, please.
I want you to show
me how this works.
Tell me how this works.
Uh...
Tell me.
You get a lock on your target
with the laser sight.
It charts a path
for the bullet,
the bullet auto-corrects
in flight.
No answer.
What if my
target's behind cover?
You take your reading
from the obstruction,
manually adjust the distance
one yard or two.
You adjust your position,
the gun measures
the change of angle
based on the original
laser reading.
You fire,
the bullet corrects its path,
you hit the target
behind the obstruction.
I gotta tell ya,
that's something else.
Are you done, Elliot?
Elliot!
I'm done.
This is your brain child, huh?
No one knows this stuff
like you?
That's right.
That's good.
Shot fired! Go, go, go!
Let's go.
Now!
Or Lainie's next!
Trevor was our lead researcher.
This is how Jay Penak
deals with competition?
Where are your weapons kept?
He's got the XC-2 prototype.
Silver lining.
Elliot's safe.
As long as he's got
those schematics,
they won't let anything
happen to him.
Yeah, but now they'll do
whatever it takes
to get him to the finish line.
Spike, let's get eyes.
We gotta get 'em
before they leave the building.
Your security, which way?
Follow me.
No one saw them
enter the secure room
or access the research?
No cameras in that room.
Security reasons.
Did they get access
to the facility's floorplans
or the CCTV system?
The security room
was their first stop.
Guys, Elliot saw the floorplan.
They got an advantage.
They're gonna know
every square inch of this place.
Well, at least they can't
get the schematics
out of the building.
Actually, they can.
Long story.
They're gonna avoid the
cameras in the main hallways.
Spike, what about
service corridors?
Yeah, I was just
thinking the same thing.
Boss, you go straight ahead,
you turn left.
Attention all employees.
This is
the Strategic Response Unit.
Please leave all open areas
immediately.
Damn it! Let's go!
Remain behind locked doors
until we give you
the all-clear.
Okay, this facility's
got four exits.
You got two exits
on the South side.
So Elliot and Jay,
they're headed here or here.
Ed, service corridor C.
We don't know if he's going
to the east or the west exit.
I'll back you up.
Leah, west exit with the boss.
I'll take the east.
But the police are...
Just keep movin'!
Which way?
Come on!
I can't do this anymore.
East exit. Which way?
I'm sorry, I can't see it.
You start seein' it or
Lainie Summers is gonna die,
do you hear me?
East exit!
Elliot...
Elliot, what are you doing?
Think braniac! Come on!
For God sake,
we're out of time!
Focus!
Elliot,
you need to listen to me.
You need to listen to me
right now.
What are you doing?
It's that way.
Good. Okay, go! Go, go!
What can you tell
me about this smart gun?
Well, the bullet
has an onboard chip
and the gun has a laser sight.
The gun tells the bullet
where to go.
How?
By radio signal.
Vehicle's approaching
the delivery door,
black Alpha two.
We'll stand by to intercept.
There. East exit, Ed!
Which way, Spike?
Boss, Leah, you guys go
straight past the loading bay,
then you go left.
Ed's nearly there!
Let's flank him.
He won't know what hit him.
Copy. Ed, we're
right behind you.
On my go.
He's here.
Please don't hurt anybody else.
You have me.
You have everything you need!
Don't, please! Please!
Put the weapon down!
No.
Ed, status.
Come on.
Spike, can you
get eyes in there?
Ed's hit.
Boss, I don't have a visual!
Eddie.
Come on, buddy, talk to me.
Okay, Jay,
I'm sergeant Parker
with the police.
I just want to know
if my guy's all right.
Step back!
Eddie.
I'm okay.
Hey, stay
calm and cuff him.
Sam, Jules, move in on the van.
Moving in on the van!
Police! Drop it!
Don't even think about it!
Drop it now!
On the ground now!
Drop your weapon now!
Hands where I can see them!
On the ground!
Drop it! Drop it!
Hey, Jay,
you got what you came for.
Now all I'm asking you to do
is walk away from that officer.
No, he's comin' with us!
Anything or anybody
gets in the way
and I'm gonna kill him!
Come on, let's get him up!
Stand him up.
You're gonna have to call off
your reinforcements
and give us clear passage,
do you hear me?!
Stay with us, stay with us.
We'll find a way.
You hear me?!
Okay, team, stand down. Leah.
Sam, Jules,
team one stand down.
Boss, say again?
Stand down,
you heard him.
Yes, sir.
All right,
you've got clear passage!
Let's go! Get the door!
All right, let's go.
Go.
Let's go.
What's the plan, boss?
The threat to Ed is real.
We co-operate for now.
We're not taking that chance.
All right!
Come on, get in there!
Let's go!
Sam, let's get
a GPS on that van!
I'm on it!
You got it!
Let's go.
They're four blocks away.
Let's move!
The second
they see us interfere,
we've got a serious risk to Ed.
We keep our distance,
we plan on the fly.
Picked up some collateral,
but no one's gonna interfere.
It'll work.
Oh my God.
Breathe, Elliot, breathe.
My God, he's
dead, he's dead.
Just breathe. My
God, he killed him.
Elliot, Elliot, just breathe-
No talking!
I'm just trying
to calm him down.
You heard me.
He's dead.
What're you gonna do?
You gonna shoot us?
Let me just talk to him.
I'm gonna calm him down.
You need him calm,
so let me talk.
Elliot, listen to me.
I didn't mean for this
to happen.
All I wanted to do,
all I wanted was...
you just wanted to forget.
I understand.
Elliot, I know about
your condition
and know how difficult
this is for you.
Now, son,
I don't have what you have,
but tell me
if this sounds familiar.
Sometimes I'll be doing
something ordinary
and for no reason at all
I see something
and I remember a girl
that I saw die
and the images flood my mind
and I can't control it.
It just happens, Elliot.
I could be lookin'
at a coffee pot
or a golf ball...
And one thing just flips over
into the next thing
and everything takes you
some place you don't wanna be.
And the more you try
not to think about it
the worse it gets.
Yeah, yeah.
Everything you've done,
everything you should
have done...
Everybody that you lost, right?
Yeah.
Yeah? We're en route.
So what happened here
with these guys?
Uh, two days ago,
guy comes to my door.
He said he knew a lot about me,
and he said he wants me
to do a simple job for him
for a crazy amount of money.
He didn't tell me
what the job was.
No, thank you.
Are you sure?
I mean, come on, Elliot,
think about the freedom.
You take a long holiday
and visit that
Rosetta Stone again.
No, thank you.
All right, fine.
Then I'll double my offer
and that'll give you a chance
to buy back
the old family cottage.
You see, Elliot, I know you.
I've done my research.
You've very valuable
to me, Elliot.
I know Lainie Summers.
I'm sure you wouldn't want
to see her get hurt.
And I know you're not gonna
want to know what happens
if you tell the police
about this conversation.
And so he says he's
glad that I see things his way.
He said he had to make
preparations
and he would be back
at 11 A.M. today to get me.
By which time you'd be dead.
Ed, I couldn't let anything
happen to her.
I wouldn't let them touch her.
She's the only one
I trust with everything...
the truth, okay?
I would do anything
to keep her safe.
You know what I'm remembering?
I remember a girl
in a peach-coloured shirt
and the taste of ginger tea.
What, you mean she's, she's...
Shh...
No, it's not a problem.
We're gonna cover it with cash.
She's all right,
and I'm pretty sure
she'd want to see you
in one piece,
so help me get out
of this now, okay?
Just focus.
They're heading
northwest, city limits.
If I were Jay
and money's no object?
I'd take a flight out
under the radar,
take Elliot with me,
download somewhere safe.
Any chance they're
heading toward an airport?
They just took a right.
If they keep going straight
they're gonna end up
in Buttonville.
That's a commuter airport.
Private flights.
They can puddle-jump anywhere
from there.
I'll make the call.
What's wrong?
He's having a seizure!
You have to give him
his medication!
Don't move and don't talk!
Help me with the cuffs.
Give me your tie.
Not a word.
I just talked to Buttonville.
There's a private plane
permitted to the airfield.
It's scheduled to leave
in ten minutes.
- Scarlatti.
- Spike, it's Ed.
Ed, talk to me.
Where are we going?
Pretty sure you're
headed to Buttonville
for a flight out.
All right, we took
out the babysitter.
I got his gun.
Jay still has
the trump card here.
What do we know?
The weapon they took
is a prototype
of an earlier work-in-progress.
We have got to disable
that gun.
I've got the specs.
That's right, you do.
Can you disable it remotely?
I don't know.
I mean, it's all in my head,
but I don't understand
most of it.
Okay, Spike,
talk to Elliot,
see if we can narrow this down.
Go.
The bullet and the
gun talk to each other
on a radio frequency.
We can't stop him firing,
but if we override the signal
we can take the "smart"
out of the bullet.
Okay, Elliot, any reference
to radio frequency,
radio guidance?
Uh...
Are you sure?
I'm
so sorry, Lainie.
What's going on, Elliot?
I'm, I'm trying.
I'm sorry, I'm trying.
It's okay, it's okay,
you can do this.
We need the specific
channel that the gun uses
to communicate with the bullet.
"Rp-4280/
results of phase three tests
to radio guidance system."
Good work, good work. Spike?
We're looking for a
number, a megahertz range,
somewhere between 100 and 150.
I can't see it.
Maybe not
MegaHertz, maybe MHz.
Uh...
Elliot, just breathe,
slow it right down.
That's it, that's it, that's it.
You got it.
There you go.
Here.
MHz. 122.8.
The bullet receives its signal
at 122.8 MHz.
Nice. Spike?
122.8, 122.8, 122.8.
Nice! Nice!
Better than nice.
We should be able to jam it
using a walkie
at that frequency,
use the airport's antenna
to boost the signal.
The antenna signal's
way more powerful than the gun.
It should override it
and make the bullet
unsteerable.
Leah, we need to get within
40 metres of that weapon.
Spike, can you be
at that airport
before we are?
We're gaining ground.
Okay, I'm gonna try
and stall 'em.
Get there as soon as you can.
Elliot, good work.
122.8.
Okay, Eddie's their safe passage
onto that plane.
After that...
He's disposable.
What do we
do with the cop?
Well, he's gonna
know we flew out.
He doesn't have to know where.
Well, that's not gonna happen.
Okay.
We're gonna get
him on this plane
and dump him en route.
Let's go.
Don't do it!
You're not gonna shoot him.
You think I'd ever let that gun
get out on the street?
You think I'd ever,
ever let that happen?
By shooting an innocent person?
One life for thousands?
That's a no-brainer.
Or we could end this
right here.
Look around you.
Keep your gun on the cop.
Jay, I suggest
you put your guns down,
you and your friend!
You know how
this works, right?
Those shields are redundant!
This bullet will find you.
I pull this trigger
and you're dead!
Not if we get
this right he's not.
So, you see,
you have no choice.
Math's not on your side.
You're gonna let us go
or one of you is gonna die!
That's guaranteed!
Spike...
Almost there.
Just hookin' up the walkie.
We're leaving.
Spike.
Keep him talking.
Okay, if we
put these guns down,
no one gets hurt!
We good, Spike?
We're good, I think.
What do you
mean "you think"?
No, we're good.
Okay, Sam, go!
Copy.
All right, that's it!
Put your weapon down!
What don't you understand?
If I shoot, you die!
Put it down!
Put it down now!
You see, Jay?
The math is not on your side.
Last chance!
Don't do this!
Okay, it's over, it's over.
Hands behind your back.
Stand up.
I'm so sorry!
Lainie.
I thought I knew
what it was like for you.
I thought I understood.
I almost lost you, Elliot.
You should have
seen this guy.
He couldn't leave his house
a week ago.
He was able to cut through
all that chaos
and find the one tiny piece
of life-saving information
we needed.
122.8 megahertz.
Yeah, I cleared my mind.
I didn't have a choice.
That's amazing, Elliot.
That's a beginning.
You see that, right?
Yeah.
I was outside myself
for a little bit.
I wasn't stuck in here.
I was...
Part of something
bigger than me.
Thank you.
You're welcome, Elliot.
Good luck to you.
Okay.
Let me see that.
You know that's evidence,
right?
I do.
Keep it safe.
I can't imagine living with
what he lives with.
Well, a lot of people
can't imagine living with
what you live with.
Buddy, I need help.
There are things
I can't get out of my head.
I think I might know someone.
Okay?
Yeah, come on.
With my research,
I've been so busy.
I think you're
gonna like her, Eddie.
I check in with her myself
sometimes.
It's just a conversation,
you know?
Just talking, no judging.
You're good at talking, right?
Yeah.
♪ ...where we're walkin'
tonight ♪
♪ just sit back ♪
♪ and watch it come to life ♪
♪ just sit back
and watch it come to life ♪
== sync, corrected by Martzy ==
www.Addic7ed.Com