Winnie?
Winnie!
Where were you?
Just making some copies.
We need the briefing room.
- Team three's prepping a warrant.
- Tell them to brief somewhere else.
- You let him get the drop on you.
- I let him... I was covering you!
Hey-hey, cool it!
Winnie, those files come in?
- I'm working on it.
- Winnie.
- I know!
- No talking to witness officers until you've...
I heard you the first time.
- Sam!
- You heard the man,
- Don't talk to witness officers.
- Sam,
- You gotta listen to me.
- Where you going Sam?
I'm gonna shower and go home.
- We're not done here.
- Well, maybe I am.
We got a debrief.
- I got nothing to say.
- It's not an option.
Get in there. Now.
- You okay?
- This is a subject officer.
- Yeah, I heard you the first time.
- I'm good.
Eddie, give the man your statement.
The rest of you, let's go!
Thank you.
Winnie, no one in there until this is done.
- Ok.
- Winnie, the files.
- Yeah.
- Come on!
The key's gonna be
bringing down the stands.
A few sticks of dynamite.
You're gonna need more than dynamite.
Whatever, just get it for next week.
My guys can't do it next week.
Then get new guys.
I can't get new guys.
No one wants this job.
Okay, I get it, I hear you.
A building like this, a heritage
building, so beige, so square,
and so much better when my big ass
tower is going right out of the middle.
Word of advice?
- Might wanna watch what you say.
-Why?
This place is like a temple to these guys.
Morning.
Tell me again the last time your
guys made the finals? Refresh me.
That's not the point.
Wasn't it half century?
42 years.
Yeah, might be time to move on.
So,
you're telling me these
stands are load bearing.
Help me get him outta here! Come on!
Hot call! Shots fired, Godwin Coliseum.
We got it, buddy, thanks.
How you doing?
- I've been better.
- You were in there?
Yeah, I'm the, uh, demolitions supervisor.
You get a visual on the shooter?
No, but we weren't looking
around. We got outta there fast
You get sense of what
direction the shots came from?
No, place is huge. There's a lot
of concrete, echoes. Like i said...
You were getting shot at,
you weren't thinking detail.
- I know.
- No, I'm sorry.
- Those the, uh, blueprints to the arena?
- Yeah.
You mind?
I'll see you in there.
- This is a friggin' nightmare.
- I understand sir.
How long is it gonna
take to nail this guy?
- If you can tell us...
- I need to get my men in there.
Sir, we're asking you again,
are you sure you can't recall any
detail of where the shots came from?
I didn't see anyone all right?
Why don't you get in there
and put my tax dollars to work?
- May I?
- Absolutely.
- What the hell you doing?
- What you can't tell us,
your wound will.
- Dammit!
- small bore,
downwards strafe The shot
came from somewhere high.
Which way were you facing?
- What?
- Relative to the front door,
- Which way were you facing?
- That way.
Okay, so west.
So the shots came from
around here somewhere.
- Yup.
- Thank you, sir.
Best wishes for a eedy recovery.
I've got uniforms on every door.
Nobody's been in or out.
The guy's likely in there.
Could be more than one guy.
So everybody else is out of the building?
Security company says so.
There's one guard unaccounted
for, but he's on end of shift.
Probably gone home,
they're trying to confirm.
All right, good. Let's keep it contained.
- Jules?
- Copy that.
I'm gonna find you a place
to command post inside.
copy.
Eddie?
April 2nd, 1957.
You know who played here?
The Memphis Flash.
Boss, focus.
The king.
Hold-hold-hold hold-hold-hold.
Infrared sensor.
Everyone's good?
- Good.
- No problem.
Same impact point, each shot.
It's rigged to go when
someone walks across it.
- It's out of ammo.
- Clever.
Yeah, takes a bit of know-how.
That matches the angle
of the bullet wound.
That rifle's somewhere in the northeast.
I'm guesng somewhere in the blues.
Okay, you and Leah check
it out. Low and slow.
So, no shooter.
But we got a booby trap.
Means we may have more.
Sarge, there's a secure
room, east entrance.
Some kind of VIP lounge.
Copy that. We'll command post there.
Stove Club Lounge. Players and brass only.
I always dreamed of getting in there.
Pretty open.
Yeah.
The gun's right there.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Cover me.
Jules, I got a serial number.
Great, I'll run it through the registry.
Everything you dreamed it was, wordy?
Still smell the cigars.
All right, we gotta
lot of ground to cover.
Boss, what're you thinking profile-wise?
Lots of people not happy
to see this place go.
So what, you shoot
somebody over a building?
It's not just a building.
Besides Elvis '57, you
got Winston Churchill,
the Beatles three times,
70 years of pro-hockey,
people met here, people married here.
Right, big emotional investment.
A lot of motives.
So, who's pushed far enough
do something about it?
All right, i gotta get
inside of that rink.
If he's set more traps
that's where they're gonna be.
Where the heart beats. Go careful, eddie.
Okay, wordy, grab the ball cam.
Sam, Leah, how's your vantage?
About 80 percent.
We're almost blind on the north side.
Sarge, got a hit on the rifle.
Belongs to a Max
Dykstra, downtown address.
Okay, let's send some uni's over there.
I got a guy ther on the way now.
I'm gonna try and get some
more background on this guy.
You got anything on
him besides the address?
No record, but he's a
retired hockey player.
One year pro, 1978.
That's good news, Jules.
Eddie, we may have a line on the object.
Copy that. Wordy.
Let's see if he left us anymore surprises.
This place is massive.
And lots of shadows.
Okay, clear.
Let's move in, a foot at a time.
We're looking for laser,
trip mechanisms, wires.
Eddie, talk to me!
I'm good. Wordy?
Uh-huh, no harm.
It's live fire!
We've got an active shooter.
He's here.
Transcripted by chamallow35
for www.Addic7ed.com
Those were targeted shots?
He's here.
He's watchng.
Sam, Leah, what do you got?
Ricochet mark on the south end.
Could be above us, could be below us.
Didn't see any muzzle flash.
He's in our blind spot.
Okay, could be the catwalk,
could be the gondola,
could be the grey seats,
it could be the greens.
'kay, we don't see anythin on the cam.
We gotta regroup and contain,
take this piece by piece.
Sarge, the owner of the rifle...
- Yeah, Jules, what?
- He was at home.
Then who's firing on my team?
It's his hunting rifle. He
says someone must've stolen it.
Claims not to know that it was missing.
And you believe him?
Ex-hockey player, hockey coach,
his rifle goes missing.
You know what they call
that in the police business?
- Hinky?
- hinky.
Interrogate him.
Uniforms are bringing him in.
Your unit is trespassing.
Leave the building immediately.
I repeat, you are trespassing.
Leave right now.
Okay, the wires run
into the press gondola...
It's gotta be the announcer
booth, northeast corner.
Okay. Eddie, we're going up there.
Ed, you can get at it from the
south, but you gotta be careful, okay?
It's a long corridor and it's exposed.
Copy that. We're on our way.
Sam?
We can cover you, he
still might be in there.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Clear.
Ed, you at the door yet?
Door's closed.
Sam, keep this hallway covered.
Clear.
Ready?
This guy wants to talk, let's talk.
This is Sergeant Greg
Parker with the poli...
Hold on.
He's cut the wires. Boss, i
don't think he wants to talk.
All right, who the hell is this guy?
Thoughts?
Young voice. Sounds under 30.
He mentioned the word "unit",
maybe there's a military connection?
or he knows we're the
strategic response unit.
All right, it's a pretty
sophisticated device for a civilian.
Okay, Jules let's look into
any recently returned vets.
It's a pretty wide net.
Cross reference guys
with criminal records.
Boss, you calling me?
What? No?
- Yeah.
- Why are you still here?
I'm glad you called,  is ed...
Get your unit outta here.
That was him. Where'd
you leave your phone.
- On the table, command post.
- You sure?
Yes, I'm sure!
There's only one way in there.
Get uniforms on the door.
Let's go, let's go, let's move it.
Officer.
Anyone walked through that
door in the past five minutes?
No, sir.
What, this guy walks through walls.
Let's take it up.
Go!
- Ready?
- yeah.
Sam.
Boss, give me your hand.
he may  have left us a he print.
He touched the wall.
Right there.
Straight ahead.
- Dammit rabbit hole.
- Spike.
No rabbit hole on the floor blades.
All right, he's got the upper hand.
He knows this place inside out.
All right, we're gonna need more intel.
Or he's gonna spend the afternoon
using this place as a shooting gallery.
When I was a kind, the
*** used to tell us about
hidden rooms, and passages.
Mostly retired guys, took the job
so they could see the game for free.
If anyone'd know, it'd be them.
Jules.
I'll find someone.
We should follow his
trail before it cools.
It's a confined space, we
don't know where it goes.
Yeah but it's either that or we sit around
waiting for grandpa to show us to our seats.
I'll go with him.
All right, no unnecessary risks.
Strict noise discipline.
Spike, I got a door on the left, anything?
You're still off the gridge.
Deny defeats and rise...
Deny defeats and rise on victory wings.
That's the dressing room.
I've got goosebumps, I'm
not even a hockey fan!
Fall back! Go! Go! Go!
- Hurry, hurry!
- Sam, Leah, status.
- Sam, talk to me.
- Status, status!
Go, go, go.
Move, move, move!
Get the water. let's get the water now.
Let's go.
- Bring it!
- Come on, come on, come on.
I gotta get this off.
What the hell is it?
Phosphorus.
Who get their hands on phosphorus?
A lot of stuff you can get in the
black market, but white phosphorus?
Afghanistan, leftovers from
the war with the Russians.
Well, this guy is military.
It didn't break the
skin, you're gonna be ok.
- And if it had?
- You would ***
- it would have damaged the organs.
- Son of a bitch.
Winnie crossed reference recent
vets with criminal records
I have 37 names.
We need a shorter short list.
They let guys with
records enter the military?
No, they get their records
after they come home.
Domestic disturbance,
assaults, DUI.
Possession of controlled subtances.
It's about recklessness and agression
on the lack of impulse control.
I'm trying to feel something
again. I don't feel something.
Ok.
Jules, one fo those 37 vets
might be taken this personnally.
I'm looking for a connection.
Sergeant Parker?
Yeah?
- You sent for...
- Charlie Howard.
I used to be an usher here 77 to 98.
Hey Charlie. Sergeant Parker,
sir. Thank you for coming.
Sergeant Parker, let me
get something straight.
Somebody's trying to stop this demolition
and you want me to help  you stop him?
Yeah, we hear you Charlie, but it's
his methods that we're not happy about.
His methods Charlie, live fire,
chemical assault against my team.
Ok. I got you.
And he's a step ahead of us, because
he knows every inch of this place.
You mean he's been squatting here?
It's a fair assumption.
Wow.
- Maybe he found the bunker.
- The bunker?
Daniel Gotwin's secret apartment.
I only saw it once. I mean
the man liked his privacy.
Can you show us where it is?
Hell, no. Hey, not on the map.
Like I said, I only saw
it once, and that was
wow, Toron versus Pittsburgh '87.
Let me guess, we lost?
- Hey!
- I'm sorry.
All right. Charlie, this
is important here, okay?
You remember where?
I just remember it was
near a concession stand.
There's 24 concession stands.
Why don't you get up there? You know
the old muscle memory might kick in.
No, it's too risky Charlie.
Look, I... I gotta be
on my feet, all right?
Trust me, I'm the one that feel it.
All right, we take him in diamond
formation through the concession stands.
They got great visibility. He'll be safe.
Ok.
Wordy, Lee and Sam, let's go.
Hey, let me try him on the
cellphone. Maybe he'll talk to me.
You okay if I keep Sam?
- Spike?
- Yeah.
All right Charlie, let's get
you dress. Guys, let's go.
Hey Jules, I'm sending
a text on boss' phone.
If this guy's picks up are you gonne
be able to patch him into the headset?
No problem.
Ok.
- Charlie?
- No.
I don't know if it's a sign, but
that's not it.
Braddock?
Aka Badass Junior.
That's right.
What do I get to call you?
What are you doing in my AO?
I'm just keeping the piece.
Braddock, I need you ***.
Copy that. I just need to know
that everything is gonna be okay.
I'm not gonna say it again.
I'm just glad to be back in the game.
I haven't been here
since the '94 playoffs.
Chicago, game 5.
See that game?
I want to fucking kill to see that game.
But I had a tournament in Hamilton.
Get out of here.
You must have been what? Bantam, pee wee?
Atom.
I didn't have a choice.
Team needed me.
So, how did it go on Hamilton?
It's the best we ever played.
- Really?
- Had to make it worth while, right?
Mr. Dykstra? Have a seat.
What the hell is going on?
My rifle get stolen, and I'm the
one getting the criminal treatment?
- Why didn't you report the theft?
- I didn't know there was a theft until you call.
So somebody broke into your garage,
went straight for a conceealed rifle.
- Didn't touch anything else.
- That's right.
Or you gave it to someone.
I didn't give it to anyone.
Then who knows where you
keep your locked rifle?
Why are you assuming that...
Because you're a hockey coach,
and this is the hockey arena.
And I'm not convinced
that this is a coincidence.
I wish I could help you.
Well, you're not leaving until you do.
What position did you play?
- All of them.
- Really?
You know, the coach made us crossed ***.
We had to think each position.
Cover for anyone.
Sounds like my unit.
So, why this place?
Nice place.
This is where anything
that ever matter happens.
All right, let's talk about the
divisional finals on Hamilton,
1994. Who was on that team?
I've 37 names of men who just came
back from military services overseas
who had a rocky landing.
It's gonna take me about ten minutes to get the
names of the guys in the team you've coached.
And about three seconds to narrow
that down to one name in common.
Look, there's a young man in there
and you know him.
And I'm guessing you care about him.
If you don't help me right now...
Darren Kovacs.
Thank you.
Subject's name is Darren Kovacs.
Thanks Jules. Winnie?
Find me family for Darren Kovacs.
Copy that.
See if you can get military records too.
Those could be classified.
Pull strings, whatever it takes Winnie.
Got it.
First time I saw him play was
right here at the coliseum.
It was a novice league
fundraiser. He blew everyone away.
He was 8.
You know when you're here,
you know what you're for.
If you're on the stands,
or if you're on the ice.
You know what you're for.
You feel like you belong, I hear you.
I took him under my wing,
helped him out the ladder,
I mean, he... he was
this close to turn it pro.
What happened?
He comes to me one day, and he...
he tells me he wants to go serve
on another team for a while.
You know you can count
on your team. You know?
Through all the...
the blood, the sweat,
the crowd...
That was a promise.
Broke my heart to see him go.
And not... not just 'cause of the
hockey. We spent so many hours together.
He was such a damn good kid.
He told me he'd come back.
He came back.
Most of him.
You know, when things got bad over there,
I...
I had one thing that I could hold on to.
I knew I'd be back here one day.
Back at the Goldwin Coliseum.
***
Hold it, hold it, hold it.
Server uniforms.
This is it, I'm sure. It's in there.
All right, we've got a 20 on the
***. Le's get uniforms up here.
Send them in the back
through a secure passage.
He sat in my living room there, last week,
it... it was the first time
I saw him since he got back.
I barely recognized him.
When I get back here,
and they're tearing it down...
I lived through all that.
And for what?
The lifestyle condos, and the parking lot?
He sat there.
He was empty.
He... he... it was like
he's mind was somewhere else.
Like he was sleep walking.
What happened to him over there.
Never told me.
Condos and a parking lot, just
what downtown needs more, right?
Pictures from the front.
Looks like his unit.
Sending a picture.
Syotos, Sam?
No. He doesn't know Spike.
Darren, are you there still?
Darren?
You guys must be close, he's not talking.
Hey guys, guys.
I gotta go.
He's on the move.
On three.
One, two, three.
Darren Kovacs!
Get down, get down, get down!
Eddie?
Flashbag.
In pursue.
- I'm on my way.
- Sam, *** concessions.
He's got down the escalators.
Anything?
No joy.
He cut the power.
Sarge, I got Darren's father on the line.
Copy that Jules. Eddie?
I'm not going in blind
so he can shoot us again.
We get the power on,
we're going after him.
Ed?
Ed, he's been shooting to miss.
You don't know that. He's injured two
people today, Sam, and you're of them.
That wasn't personnal. Now it is.
- Sam.
- I got a connection boss.
I know where this guy is coming from.
First solution is to talk, right?
You be objective.
But I saw you over here,
I know how it works.
Ok, Ed.
Ed, dig in, take cover.
Let's do what we do,
let's talk him out. Sam?
Yeah boss.
I'm letting you do this.
Thanks boss.
And he has not been getting
any professional help?
Uh, asking for help is
not one of his thing.
Sounds like your son, huh,
grow up with a lot of
expectations around him.
Yeah, but, it never went to his head.
Darren was always just,
he was always afraid
to disappoint the people
who believed in him. That's
why he worked so hard.
And then when he came back home?
He just... cut himself off.
Started... you know he
wouldn't talk to anybody,
he started the drinking, and
picking fights with strangers.
Did he ever tell you why?
Hang on, I'm nearly there.
Braddock?
Yeah.
Where did you get my name?
It's... it's our MO. We like
to know who we're talking to.
I was in the forces for a
couple years when I was young.
And so was my dad. I mean, thats...
this way you're supposed to do.
You serve your country.
But when Darren told me, that
he wanted to take his turn,
I wasn't happy.
It was a bright future
he was putting on hold.
I knew it.
It killed me to see him do that.
But I always told my
son,you make your choices.
So I couldn't stand in his way.
Where was he deployed?
Kandahar.
Hey,
you found his... his musketeers.
Hey!
It's Howie Carson, his right winger.
And a little higher, Jordan and Pete.
Those guys,
they mean everything to him.
What happened in Kandahar?
Well,
he lost them.
Yeah. And what else do you know?
I know what it was like over there.
You know your war.
You don't know mine.
I know. Everyone's different.
Sam, Darren lost his three closest
friends in a patrol near Kandahar.
AED took them out, he walked
away without a scratch.
Copy that.
You wanna know what my war was Kovacs?
I'm a long distance marksman.
Sniper.
Yeah.
And I served with a
friend too. Close friend.
Ben.
He didn't make it.
When I found him, he'd been hammered
with a .50 cal.
There was nothing of him left.
Sam, what's your game plan here?
He has to know, I understand.
I get that.
He has to hear that he is not alone.
Ok. You don't have to push too hard.
Boss, trust me on this.
This is what I can do.
Kovacs, is that Hungarian?
- Yeah.
- Syotos means anything?
No.
Me and my guys,
we went everywhere together.
All for one.
But that night,
I was thirsty, so I, huh,
slowed down to go to my canteen.
I was 20 paces ahead
when the bomb went off.
Darren, you didn't plant that AED.
If it hadn't been for me,
Howie never would have sign up.
He did it for me.
And now, I have his blood on my hands.
And you don't know what that's like.
Yeah I do.
The shot that took out Ben, that was...
that was me.
I was given the order, I
was cleared to fire, and I...
I took the shot. He was in the
wrong place, in the wrong time.
And I killed my best friend
from 2 kilometers away.
I killed him.
I...
I thought I was gonna go
crazy, but I got through it.
You've got a place in
your mind where you go to,
when you can't take it anymore.
When you think you're gonna die?
And you think that you'd rather
be dead than be where you are.
Yeah.
And for us, me and Howie
this was it.
We knew if we could just
make it back, you know...
We'd close our eyes, and
we'd imagine ourselves
back here in center ice.
Now they're gone.
Howie's gone.
And I can't let me back in there.
And I got nothing here.
I got nothing to see me through.
I thought it was over for me too, Darren.
I know, ok?
I know.
But I found a different place to
go, a different person to be...
that's why I'm here, so let me help you.
What was your first name again Braddock?
It's Sam.
I'm tired Sam.
Then let's get some rest.
Let's do this together.
Ok.
Nicely done Sam. All
right, let's bring him home.
All right Darren, I need you to...
I need you to put down your gun.
Ok, I will.
And I need you to come down at the
bottom of the escalators concessions area.
- No.
- Darren.
Center ice.
And it has to be you.
Too exposed.
Darren I can't.
Center ice.
I'll be there.
Almost there.
Nice work Sam.
All right, let's do this.
I want his covered boss.
Bring me Sam's rifle. Leah, spot me.
Spike, Wordy, you cover Sam.
He's unarmed and in plain view.
Basic precautions Sam.
He trusts me. If he sees
rifles what does that tell him.
Ok, but how do we know we can trust him?
Well, that's your first sign.
Yeah.
So, after Darren lost his
friends, what happened?
Well, they sent him home.
Before his tour was up.
How did he take that?
He wasn't happy.
He applied to get back into combat.
But all the requests was denied.
They said he was no longer eligible.
In position.
You're good to go.
He wouldn't tell me why.
Just that you know, they were
wrong, he was a good soldier...
I'm right behind you Sam. Spike?
But I knew in my gut,
I knew why they wouldn't take him back.
There he is.
Darren it's me.
It's Sam.
You made the right decision.
We're gonna get through this ok?
I'm here.
You see Sam?
I'm a good soldier.
Get down on the ground.
Hands on your head.
Get down on the ground. Now!
Stop man. What are... what are you doing?
Think about this.
You don't need to do this.
Sam, stop.
I mean, think about what you're doing.
I don't have a shot.
Sam, stay right where you are.
I promised we would
get through this, but...
Get him to come to you.
But... this is something we can
work through. You just have to...
you just have to trust and
we can get through this, ok?
I'm a good soldier.
And I needed you to know that.
I know that, buddy, I...
you gotta stay with me,
ok? Please stay with me.
See you on the other side.
Subject down.
Why did you do that?
He wasn't gonna shoot.
I coulda stock it out.
He wasn't gonna shoot!
All right, stay there.
Any weapons?
No, I'm a security guard. I work here.
- What?
-I work here, I'm a security guard.
All right, get up.
When the shooting started, I
just went inside, it was stupid.
It's ok.
As soon as I see him, ***,
and put me in the closet.
Jjust now he came back.
He said he'd shoot me if
I didn't do what he said.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's ok.
I'm so sorry.
That's my son, that's my son.
That's my son in there.
Look, you can't go in.
He wasn't gonna shoot.
He was an immediate threat.
It took him 30 seconds to turn the tables.
We gave him the upper hand
because we trusted him.
No. I trusted him.
You killed him. It didn't
have to be like that.
He was clearly threatening
both Spike and you.
Sam, you did great, you
just... you lost perspective.
You put yourself right
in the line of fire.
I knew him! Do you understand, I knew him.
Oki, what do you think he wanted Sam?
He wanted to save the arena.
His military files.
No, look, he needed a mission,
to... to find the last place left
where things made sense.
Where things were fair.
He wasn't gonna hurt me.
We couldn't take that chance.
You've never taken that chance?
I've seen you do it!
He's got a point.
You've done it, I've done it, but
the question is, why did you do it?
For Darren?
Or for Ben?
Maybe you wanted a second
chance to save your friend.
- Jules.
- Darren applied to return to service.
He wanted to go back.
Why was he denied?
Because they found him
psychologically unfit.
Darren suffered from post-traumatic
stress, and he wanted to go back.
Sam, what was the last thing he said?
Huh, he said, huh,
"I'm a good soldier."
Roll back the tape.
Right there.
Pump the volume.
Now.
What did he say?
"See you on the other side."
He said "see you on the other side."
Syotos.
***
Yeah, but not this time.
He was saying goodbye to you Sam.
That's why he wanted to go back.
He thought he should have died with
his friends the first time around.
"I'm so tired."
That's when he knew that it was over.
Sam.
His connection with you was real man.
But he knew what he wanted.
And there's nothing you could
have done Sam, to change that.
"It has to be you."
- He wanted me to kill him.
- Come on Sam.
It's all right, I get it.
Look,
when I left the field and I joined the SOU
I didn't want to be a point-shoot guy
that could take people from mile away.
I wanted to...
save people, you know?
And the one I should
have been able to reach,
I mean the one guy,
I couldn't.
I wasn't objective, I put my team at risk.
I don't belong here.
It doesn't get any easier.
We don't get to win every time.
You gotta be at peace with who
you are to get through that.
There's a bunch of guys I know,
they're cops, military guys
we meet up and we talk, and we
help each other keep it together.
Greg and I are going for it tonight.
You should come.
Transcripted by
chamallow35 www.addic7ed.com