This is Sam Braddock
from the Police
Strategic Response Unit.
I'm calling you
about Charlie Alanak.
He escaped from his facility
today.
You think he's coming here?
Parker: Okay, team, subject is
violent and unpredictable,
so tread careful.
(Siren wails)
Kevin:
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Charlie!
Woman:
(Shrieks)
(Short, tight breaths)
(Hard whack) Ungh!
(Panting)
(Hard whacks, grunts in pain)
(Grunts of pain)
Agghhhhh!
Ungh!
(Shrill scream)
(Groans then gasps, startled)
(Knock at the door)
Lorraine:
Morning, Charlie.
How are you?
The same?
Shall we ask Dr. Lavery
to adjust your meds?
Charlie, talk.
You have to talk.
It's not...
Pills...
That I need.
It's okay.
What do you need?
Lorraine:
Oh...
I'm sorry, Charlie.
I wish I could.
Spike: It's all in
boxes, up to here.
My mom and I are eating
out of paper plates.
Ed: You guys lived there
for a long time, right?
40 years worth of stuff,
and I got six days to clear it
before the open house.
Craigslist,
where priceless family
heirlooms go to die.
So tell me, your dad's wine,
is that stuff any good or what?
Terrible.
But, you know, every year
like the house would smell
like wine juice and like yeast,
and my dad'd be going
down there in the basement
like every 20 minutes-
Spike.
- Hey. Boss.
- Come on, let's go.
It's late.
A lot to cover.
Okay, let's go.
(Bottle clanks)
Hey, Charlie.
(Dice clack)
Get out of my face, Alanak!
Hey, Nestor!
Stop it!
Nestor: (Infuriated
growl) I'll kill you!
Guards!
Nestor and Charlie:
(Grunting)
Patient:
Get him!
Nestor:
(Guttural grunt)
Charlie: - Nurse!
Lorraine: - Charlie?
Nestor:
Get back!
Guard: Hey! Hey!
Nestor, step back!
Lorraine: - Charlie?
Guard: - Take it easy!
(Sirens wail)
Winnie: Meadowview Institute
, 7673 Keele street.
Subject's got a knife,
one injured.
The name is Nestor Prejean.
I'm forwarding you his records.
Assault.
Assault with a deadly.
Assault with intent.
Attempted murder.
Can't the guards
get it under control?
They're unarmed, like a prison.
Winnie, I need to speak
with the doctor in charge.
Winnie:
I'll get him on the line.
Boss, turn your comm off.
You all right?
- Yeah.
- Did you see Spike when he came in today?
Yeah.
Mom's moving back to Italy,
selling the house.
He's on his own
for the first time in his life.
Did you hear that?
How'd I miss that?
That's my point, Greg.
I mean, usually you don't.
So I ask you again,
you all right?
No. It's just...
It's some stuff at home, Eddie.
Is it Marina?
I love having her
in my life, I do.
But everything
she's been through,
she needs a lotta support
and she deserves it.
She deserves it.
She deserves someone there,
someone to listen.
But sometimes I come home
from work,
and there she is
and I'm burned out.
I'm on empty, I just...
Winnie: Boss, I'm patching through
Meadowview's chief physician...
Turn your comm on.
It's your call.
Dr. Lavery, hey,
it's Sergeant Parker.
What're we looking at here?
Dr. Lavery:
This patient's highly volatile.
He stabbed a fellow patient
and now he's got
a security guard trapped.
Parker: Okay, we've
got Nestor's record.
What can you tell me
about his condition?
He's schizoaffective.
And he's been known
to resist his meds,
which leads to paranoia,
hallucination, anger,
and right now
he's showing all the signs
of a full-scale
psychotic break.
Parker: Okay, doctor, just
keep your staff out of range.
We're almost there.
Raf: He'll see anything
we do as a threat.
He's gonna see our arrival
as a threat.
Ed: Boss, we got a
talk-down option on this?
Not a chance, Eddie,
not with his condition.
Okay, team,
we're skipping the talk,
going straight to tac.
We're gonna surf him.
Raf, Sam, less-lethal.
Spike, prep the sonic shield
as a distraction.
Copy that.
Ed: Gear protection
as soon as we're inside.
(Tires screech, sirens wail)
Thanks, Sam.
Parker:
Doctor Lavery?
Yes, this way, down the stairs.
Sir, we need to clear
this area out now.
We're in lockdown.
Everybody's being moved
to their cells.
Guys, let's move.
Nestor: Cut him!
If you don't, stab him.
Ed: Spike, on my go. You ready?
Spike: Yeah.
Ed: Go!
Police! Right there!
Nestor:
(Shouting and grunting)
SRU! SRU!
Ed: (Grunts forcefully)
Nestor: (Grunts)
Ed: Drop the weapon! Drop it!
(Metallic rasp
as knife slides across floor)
Nestor:
(Struggling grunts)
Sam, you got him?
Spike: You're okay, you're okay.
You're gonna be okay.
(Cuffs clank)
Subject secure.
Parker:
Eddie, we've got a problem.
Security guard:
Right there.
Dr. Lavery: That's one of our
nurses, Lorraine Manley.
Where's the security guard?
Parker:
Who's that?
Dr. Lavery: Charlie Alanak
, the patient Nestor attacked.
He's supposed to be
in the infirmary.
He got out.
Team one, new deal!
Winnie, let's get an apb
on the nurse's car.
It was seen leaving
the parking lot.
I'm gonna need
Charlie Alanak's file -
everything you have on him,
starting from where he's from.
Spike: Boss, I'm gonna
review the incident,
see what I can read.
Parker: That's good, Spike.
Do that.
Dr. Lavery:
Here's session notes,
and there's more
on the computer.
'Kay, team, I'm gonna feed you
on the fly here.
Charlie's a local,
lived in the city
his whole life.
Ed: He's gonna head
towards what he knows.
Raf: There are two main
routes into town from here.
Ed:
Sam, head east.
We're west on the 407.
Let's go.
Sam:
Copy that.
Dr. Lavery: Most of the patients
here have been diagnosed
with mental illnesses,
but Charlie's story
is different.
He suffered a frontal lobe
injury at 19.
His football helmet
came off during a game,
just before he got hit.
The football injury
also caused a minor stroke
triggering a form of aphasia.
Aphasia.
That's a language disorder,
right?
Dr. Lavery: That's right.
It's hard for him to find words,
put them in order.
What about logic and foresight?
Cognitively
he's pretty high functioning.
Frontal lobe damage
can mean a lot of things.
Dr. Lavery: For Charlie,
it's impulse-control,
mood swings,
bouts of violent aggression.
Parker:
And that's why he's here.
A year after his injury
he was involved in a fight,
killed a young man.
Ed: - Murder.
Parker: - No. Manslaughter.
Parker:
He pled diminished capacity,
but I don't see
a police report.
Ed: Okay, Winnie, contact
the arresting officer.
We need more on this.
Winnie: - Copy.
Dr. Lavery: - I can tell you
that Charlie's pattern
of aggression continued
once he got here.
There were regular altercations
with the patients,
and recently these outbursts
have been getting
more frequent,
and more violent.
(Computer beeps)
Spike: Boss, you're gonna
wanna take a look at this.
Be right there, Spike.
What do you have, Spike?
Well, he's definitely
high-functioning.
Watch.
Charlie approaches Nestor,
tries to provoke him...
Dr. Lavery:
And then Nestor stabs him.
That's what the witnesses
have described.
Except that's not
what happened.
Charlie cut himself?
To get to the infirmary.
Grabs a hostage with car keys.
All eyes on Nestor,
he makes his move.
Team one, listen up,
this may be
a premeditated escape.
Charlie may be
working out a plan here,
and we've gotta find him
before something triggers him
and he loses control.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Lorraine:
Where're we going, Charlie?
This...
Used to be all...
F-fields.
Yeah.
Yeah, they started building
two years ago.
(Frustrated exhale) Up here.
Left.
(Phone rings)
Don't. No.
(Phone ringing)
Lorraine:
Charlie,
you know they're gonna
come after you, right?
(Phone ringing)
No.
I've, I've...
I-I've got...
You've got your freedom?
Yeah, I know.
You do now, Charlie,
but what happens next?
Hmm?
I stay that way.
(Gas gauge dings)
Charlie:
Stop at gas station.
I don't have money, Charlie.
I left my purse.
(Phone ringing)
No answer on Manley's phone.
Winnie:
Boss, I've got Officer Carlyle.
He was first on scene
when Charlie was arrested.
Okay, patch him through,
Winnie.
Carlyle:
It's Carlyle here.
You're looking for background
on a Charlie Alanak?
Parker: Hey, officer.
The subject's at large,
but our profile's
a little spotty.
Hoping you can shed some light
on his crime.
Yeah, of course.
A call came in late,
Kempton campus.
Victim was 19, 20,
same age as Alanak.
There was a verbal exchange
and some taunting.
They fought.
Alanak pushed the kid
off the football stands.
He hit his head and he died.
Schoolyard brawl,
two lives changed forever.
Carlyle:
Alanak confessed.
Witnesses corroborated.
Case closed.
You know if he and the victim
had a history?
Carlyle:
No. No indication of that.
By all accounts
he just snapped.
I will tell you what I remember
the most, sergeant.
Parker:
What's that?
That look in his eye.
(Murmuring voices, girl crying)
There's kids crying,
there's a body
lying on the ground,
blood everywhere...
(Murmuring voices, girl crying)
And Alanak?
Dead calm.
Okay. Thanks, officer.
Thanks for your time.
Winnie: Boss, just got
a hit on the plate.
Toll camera picked them up
leaving the 407 at Bayview.
Raf, next exit.
Ed: Sam, we're close.
Come west, we'll flank him.
Copy that.
On my way.
Spike: Ed, I'm mobile,
headed South.
Ed:
Copy that.
Parker: Okay, team
, second time today,
subject is violent
and unpredictable,
so tread careful.
Attendant:
Hey, bud, it's pre-pay!
I don't...
Gotta come inside and pay.
Charlie:
No.
Cash.
Oh, you're looking for
the free gas station.
Sorry, it's about a half mile
down the block.
Sir?
Give him gas, please.
I can pay you back later.
I work just up the road.
Please.
Tell you what,
why don't I call my manager.
Maybe we can figure
something out.
No. Stay!
Wade: I'm just gonna
make a quick call.
Charlie: (Slurred) This is an emergency!
I need gas!
Lorraine: It's okay, Charlie!
No-no-no! Charlie, no!
No, Charlie, no, no!
Back off!
Boss,
I got a live 9-1-1 call.
It's Lorraine Manley.
Get here fast.
They're fighting.
Lorraine, where are you?
Lorraine: - True Value gas.
Ed: - Got it!
True Value gas.
Langstaff and Bayview.
We're a minute away.
Lorraine: Charlie, please let go of him!
Let him go!
Lorraine, you listen to me.
You get distance
and you stay covered, all right?
Lorraine: You have to let go!
Let go of the gun!
Parker:
Lorraine?
(Siren wails)
Lorraine: No! Don't!
(Gunshot pops)
Eddie, shots fired.
Extreme caution!
(Siren wails, tires screech)
Lorraine:
You're gonna be fine.
Everything will be fine.
Just relax.
Raf: - SRU!
Ed: - Where's Charlie?
Lorraine: He's not
here, he's gone.
They were fighting
and the gun went off.
He panicked.
Boss, we missed him.
Lorraine:
Officer...
He took the gun.
(Low hum of chatter)
I never imagined
he'd do something like this.
I tried to talk to him,
he wouldn't listen.
I'm sure it wasn't your fault.
Ed: Winnie, let's get Charlie's
photo and description.
Full media alert,
he's armed and dangerous.
Will do.
Parker: - Team.
Ed: - Go, boss.
Charlie's on
a cocktail of meds:
Lithium, methylphenidate...
It goes on.
Mood stabilizers.
Yeah, and the longer
he goes without 'em...
Ed:
The worse our day's gonna get.
Doctor, I need a list
of Charlie's friends
and family,
anyone who so much as sent him
a get-well card.
- I'll get the visitor log.
- Thank you.
Okay, Eddie,
I can tell you this,
no brothers or sisters.
His father died
when he was young.
Just a mom, Katia Alanak.
Okay, boss, on our way.
- Sam...
- We'll finish up here.
Spike, you're with me.
Let's move.
Dr. Lavery: (Recording) Charlie, I wanna
talk about you understanding your actions.
Talking...
Doesn't help.
I'm still...
Trapped.
I'm still trapped here!
Dr. Lavery:
Yes, Charlie, you are.
You are here,
but you need to...
I printed off the names
of all the visitors.
There's twelve in total.
Pretty standard pattern.
Regular visits
in the first couple months,
classmates, friends,
and then they taper off.
Most of the names on this list
haven't been here
in a couple of years.
Once they realize
conditions like Charlie's
is a lifetime's work...
People move on.
Okay, team, I'm sending you
a list of 12 names.
Let's cross 'em off.
Spike: Boss, any old
teammates on that list?
Coaches? Trainers?
What're you thinking, Spike?
Spike: Well, Charlie used
to play football, right?
Those can be strong bonds.
That's better.
Doctor?
Any of these football buddies?
Yeah. Don Colby
and Kevin Baines.
They were on
his university team.
Parker:
Let's start there.
Don Colby, Kevin Baines.
We'll send unis
to cover the rest.
(Siren wails)
Sam:
Thanks.
No answer at Don Colby's.
I'm heading over there.
Okay, I'll try Kevin Baines.
I'll catch up with you
when I'm done.
(Phone rings)
Kevin: - Hello.
Sam: - Kevin Baines?
Kevin:
Yes.
Sam:
This is Sam Braddock
from the Police
Strategic Response Unit.
I'm calling you
about Charlie Alanak.
He escaped from his facility
today.
You think he's coming here?
Sam: This is just
a precautionary call, sir,
I don't wanna alarm you,
but I have to tell you...
Charlie's considered armed
and dangerous.
Armed?
Sam: So if he tries to make
contact with you in any way,
call the police immediately,
okay?
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
I will.
Thanks for the call.
(Phone beeps off)
Oh gee...
Guess who?
Uh... is it Lady Gaga?
No!
Oh, it's Nicky!
You all right?
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, the moving trucks
don't get here for a bit.
You wanna get outta this mess.
Sure.
That'd be great.
- Okay.
- I'll go get the stuff.
(Banging on door)
Police! Open up, please!
(Door crashes open nearby)
Hey!
Stop! Right there!
Don Colby?
Yeah.
What's this all about?
What're you running for, don?
Oh, let me guess.
It's medical, right,
and you're just filling
out the paperwork?
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah, well, I'm here
because a patient escaped
from Meadowview complex today.
We need to know
if he's contacted you.
Charlie Alanak.
Wait.
Charlie busted out?
You haven't heard from him?
No.
Not for a couple years.
(Truck rumbles)
Doctor, Charlie's crime,
I can't find a sentence.
That's because Meadowview
isn't a prison.
Sentences aren't preset.
When Charlie arrived,
we had reason to believe
he'd only be with us
a couple years.
What happened?
Well, we can't start
the release process
until we're absolutely sure
he doesn't pose a danger.
Based on today,
he's got a ways to go.
Here, let me show you
something.
(Car doors close)
Ed:
Katia Alanak?
Yes?
Hi. Officer Lane.
This is Officer Scarlatti.
We were hoping
you could help us.
Of course.
Have you seen your son today?
I think there's been a mistake.
My son's in a facility.
Your son escaped
from Meadowview, ma'am.
Dr. Lavery; How did
it start, Charlie?
I didn't... start it!
Dr. Lavery: Well, it takes
two to fight, Charlie,
and when you respond
impulsively,
that's where
the trouble starts.
That's what got you here
in the first place, remember?
No.
Dr. Lavery: Yes, Charlie
, and you know it.
You lost control that night
and a young man died.
I made... a choice.
Dr. Lavery:
What're you saying, Charlie?
I had to.
Dr. Lavery:
Had to kill him?
Answer me, Charlie.
Are you saying
you did it on purpose?
No more.
Dr. Lavery:
That was two months ago.
It's a discouraging change
from someone who showed remorse
about a moment of impulse,
to this, unfeeling, combative,
confused about his own
state of mind.
Man on a fast-track
out of here.
A week ago it got worse.
Charlie shut down altogether.
No change in his health?
His meds?
Dr. Lavery:
No, not at all.
You know what I remember most
about when Charlie was healthy?
What's that,
Mrs. Alanak?
The noise.
(Low hum of chatter)
Katia:
The boys and the commotion.
(Chatter and laughter)
Katia: After the accident
, life just got so quiet.
It was easier for him
not to talk.
It was embarrassing.
Charlie's friends stopped
coming by after that?
Kevin didn't.
Even when Charlie
was in trouble,
Kevin was there.
His family found us a lawyer,
and helped pay
for the legal costs.
I don't know what Charlie
would do without him.
What do you mean by that?
Kevin took a job out west.
- He's leaving?
- Mm-hm.
Mrs. Alanak,
when is he leaving?
I wrote it down.
Today.
Ed:
Boss, we got something here.
Yeah, go ahead, Eddie.
Ed: Charlie's closest
friend is Kevin Baines.
Yeah, he's in the logs.
He visits regularly.
Yeah, well, not any more.
He's moving away, today.
So, loss of a best friend;
That's a huge blow.
Especially for someone
in Charlie's position.
Okay, Eddie,
you stay with the mom,
I'm on it.
Kevin:
Suz, let's go.
Suzanne:
Just a second.
Charlie:
(Unintelligible stammer)
Charlie.
Man, look at you.
Are you all right?
Um... um...
(Stammering)
I got... got...
Escaped.
I know, Charlie.
The police are after you.
Mm-mm. Uh...
(Murmurs)
I need...
Look, this isn't a good place
for you to be, buddy. Okay?
They already called here.
Tell you what.
Why don't you go
to my cottage, okay?
Do you have some way
of getting around?
No. Kevin...
You can't abandon me.
Look, I...
I, uh...
Charlie, I don't know
what to say.
I'm sorry, okay?
We fly tonight.
You said...
You sa...
Stick by me!
- And I will, Charlie...
- You promised!
Suzanne:
All shoed up?
Kevin: - Wait, Suz.
Suzanne: - Let's hit the road.
Kevin:
Um...
Suz, I told you
about my old friend.
Charlie Alanak.
Hi.
(Cell phone rings)
- Don't.
- I gotta take this, Charlie.
It's... police.
Kevin: Now, we've got a
thousand things going on.
I'm gonna answer my phone,
okay?
Whoa, whoa, Charlie!
Charlie!
Don't answer!
Suzanne:
(Shrieks)
Don't answer!
Kevin:
Okay, look, Charlie,
just let them go inside, okay?
Charlie: - No.
Kevin: - Charlie,
you're scaring my family.
Okay, you're scaring my boy.
Okay...
Charlie:
Then... we drive!
Kevin:
Okay, we can do that.
Just me and you, the two of us.
To Robbie.
Robbie?
You think that's
a good idea, Charlie?
Kevin: - Okay!
Charlie: - Now!
Okay.
Go inside.
Honey, go inside.
We're going, okay?
We're going.
(Sirens wail)
Winnie: Boss, 911 call
from the Baines house.
Charlie was there.
Officer's on his way
and I got Suzanne Baines
on the line.
Suzanne, hi.
My name is Sergeant Greg Parker.
Suzanne:
He took Kevin.
He has a gun.
A police officer is heading
to you now, ma'am.
You're safe.
His name's Charlie Alanak.
Kevin knows him from school.
Parker:
Okay, okay.
Do you know
where they were going?
Suzanne:
No. Well, yes...
To see someone...
Someone named Robbie.
Parker:
Do you know who that is?
No idea.
Why did he come here?
Parker: I'm trying to
figure that out, ma'am.
But help's on its way, okay?
You just stay inside.
Suzanne:
Okay.
Mrs. Alanak, does Charlie know
somebody named Robbie?
Robbie's not a person.
Ed: Boss, Tom Robbarts field.
Kempton University.
The scene of the crime.
- Let's move.
- Mr. Lane?
- Please.
- Ma'am, we're gonna do everything we can.
I promise you that.
(Sirens wail)
Parker: Okay, team, why does
he go back to ground zero?
Maybe he wants to face
his ghosts.
Some kind of atonement.
Parker:
Charlie's assault,
he snapped, pushed that kid
to his death,
it was an impulse.
Charlie talked about making
a choice that day...
There's something
we're missing here.
Sam: Hey, boss,
I'm here with Raf now.
The police report said
that don witnessed it.
Okay, bring him, Sam.
We need to get inside
this thing.
Need all the help we can get.
Okay, copy that.
Don, we're gonna need
your help on this, okay?
Oh man.
Kevin: Not sure you thought
this through, buddy.
I mean...
What're we doing here, Charlie?
This is not a good plan.
Charlie:
I had to.
You broke out, Charlie.
Okay?
The cops are chasing you.
I had to!
Okay, listen to me,
listen to me.
You're only making this worse
for yourself.
Okay?
It's gotta be easier...
Team one, just got a 911 call
from Kevin Baines' phone.
The line's open,
but I can barely hear anything.
Covert call.
Kevin's in trouble.
You gotta hear me on this,
you're being rash.
Talk... to you.
Okay, okay.
(Sirens wail)
Don, Charlie's assault,
did he intend to hurt that kid?
Look, am I being arrested here
or what?
Answer the question.
No. He barely knew him.
It was...
It was just some kid
who didn't know
when to shut his mouth.
Sam:
He provoked Charlie.
Yeah, that's right.
Take me through it, don.
Through what?
I gave my statement
a thousand times.
You should have no problem
getting up for one more.
It was late.
We, uh...
We'd lost a game that day.
(Mumbled chatter)
Don: We were just
trying to forget about it,
blow off some steam.
Charlie'd come back from rehab
maybe a month before.
Hey!
Hey, Charlie.
Don:
He was totally different.
It was hard to see him
like that.
Tough game.
Yeah, it was a tough loss.
We really missed you out there.
Don:
Kevin was good.
He tried to keep Charlie
in the fold.
But I'll be honest,
I never knew how to act
around him.
But you, um...
You, um...
Guy: (Snickers) You...
You, you, you, you...
You...
(Laughs)
Ignore him, Charlie.
Guy: Yeah, listen to
your quarterback.
Kevin: Hey, why don't you
do us a favour, Columbine,
and shut your mouth.
We're gonna go, Kev.
Call you tonight?
Kevin:
Yeah.
Guy: Nice job, freak dog.
Real smooth.
Uh, wait up.
Guy:
Way to kill a party.
You're such a loser!
Freak.
Guy: Freak! Look at you!
Learn to talk!
Kevin: Hey, just stop.
Look at me! Hey! Let it go!
Guy: Get your freak ass
back to rehab, dogface...
Kevin:
Just let it go.
Next thing I know
we hear shouting.
I ran back
but it was already over.
(Shrill shriek)
Cracked the kid's skull
wide open.
Spike:
There they are.
Ed: Let's use the
stands for cover.
(Siren wails)
So you didn't actually see
Charlie beat that kid.
Like I said,
by the time I ran back...
It was over, right.
So, in fact, the whole thing
could've gone down
some other way.
You wouldn't know.
Don: Charlie confessed.
Kevin agreed!
The cops, the judges,
they all agreed, man.
And you?
Don, two of your friends
are in a world of trouble
right now.
If you know anything
that might help,
now is the time.
Okay, look,
I stand by everything I said,
all right?
But you step into a thing
like that,
you get a feeling, like...
Like a flash.
There was something
in their eyes,
a look.
Something between them.
A secret.
I don't know.
Sam: Don, are you saying
Kevin could've been the one?
Those are your words.
But it's crossed your mind.
I don't know.
It...
It was a feeling.
(Stammers) It was a feeling,
that's all.
(Sirens wail, tires screech)
This lines up, Sam.
I think this is what Charlie
was trying to say.
It was Kevin
who pushed that kid
and he made a choice
to take the fall for Kevin.
Sam: Don, you think Charlie
would've taken the fall for Kevin,
wear that for him
all these years?
I mean, Kevin was your leader,
your best friend.
You looked up to him.
And Charlie?
Charlie just wanted to be
on the team again.
Okay, team, we gotta treat this
as a real possibility.
Charlie might've confessed
to protect his friend...
Until he can't take it anymore.
He tells Kevin to come clean.
That's when Kevin tells him
"sorry, buddy,
I can't help you,
I'm moving on."
Then he busts out
to make one last appeal.
Charlie?
Charlie:
No!
Parker:
I need you to stay calm.
Don't come near!
Charlie, listen to him!
Charlie! Okay...
Okay, okay.
Whoa. Just let me go!
(Gunshot pops)
Charlie: Keep away!
Okay...
(Panting)
Talk... to them!
Or what, Charlie?
I do...
What I have to.
Eddie, he points that gun...
Ed:
I know.
I got the solution.
(Sirens wail)
Charlie?
My name's Greg Parker.
I'm gonna cut to the chase,
buddy,
'cause I know
you deserve the truth
and you're smart enough
to handle it.
But if you point that gun,
my team will have no choice
but to shoot you.
Sam, they move,
I lose my line of fire.
Cross me, north angle.
Sam:
Copy.
Parker:
Spike, I need ears in there.
Ed:
Raf, cover him.
Copy.
You here with me, buddy?
Charlie, I need to see you
put that gun down.
I'm...
Not going back!
Charlie,
they will shoot you, okay?
They will shoot you
where you stand.
Parker:
Kevin, please,
I just need to talk
to Charlie right now.
Will you let me do that?
Kevin:
So talk!
Make him understand!
He threatened my family!
He waved a gun
in front of my son!
Kevin, please.
Kevin: Look, Charlie,
what you want from me,
I can't give you.
(Murmurs, fuming) No!
Kevin:
Look, it's too late.
It's to late, okay?
I wish that weren't the case.
(Sighs, frustrated)
Spike, status.
Spike: Here it comes.
(Device beeps)
Charlie: (Breathing hard) No...
- We...
- My son, my wife,
you're asking me
to throw that away.
- It's time!
- Time to what?
To throw away
three healthy lives
for one broken one?
No! Stop!
You... you...
I... the...
It's time!
You promised!
Kevin: Okay, okay,
okay, just calm down.
Eddie, Charlie doesn't wanna
hear us right now,
but he needs a voice.
You want me to take this?
Yeah, I want you
to talk to Kevin,
leader to leader.
He was their quarterback,
so tap into that.
Copy. Sam?
I have the solution.
Charlie:
(Pants)
Ed:
Charlie Alanak,
my name's Ed Lane.
I need to speak to Kevin.
Is that all right?
He's the one with the gun,
okay?
Just get me outta here!
Ed:
Kevin, we all want that.
We just gotta work
together here, okay?
Kevin: All that I've
done for him and he...
He threatens my family,
drags me here at gunpoint.
I stood by him like a brother!
Ed: I know that, Kevin.
You've been good to Charlie.
Kevin: Everyone wrote
him off, but not me.
Tell him!
Kevin: Our own coach
turned against him.
Told me he was a distraction,
told me to move on.
You know what I told him?
You remember, Charlie?
I told him I'd quit the team
if your name came off
your locker.
- Didn't I? Didn't I?
- Tell him.
Yes.
Tell him.
Ed:
Okay, Kevin, I get it.
You stood up for Charlie.
That's what happened
in the stands that night;
somebody came at him,
you defended him.
You were the team leader,
Kevin,
you had his back,
he was your friend.
Only this time
something went wrong,
and suddenly your whole world
is in the balance,
your career,
your scholarship, all of it.
No, no, no,
you got that wrong, okay?
Charlie saw that,
he knew what was at stake.
He saw your future, his...
And he made a choice
and he took the hit.
Kevin: No, look, if he's
saying that, he's lying.
Mm-mm!
It's your word against mine!
I didn't!
Ed: Kevin, listen to me.
Listen to me.
Charlie never said anything.
All these years, he kept quiet.
Think about what that cost him.
Charlie,
tell him why you did it.
You're my friend.
Ed:
He's your friend.
It's as simple as that;
Kevin, you know Charlie better
than anybody else.
You stood on the field
with him,
you grew up together.
Charlie knows what it is
to be a friend.
He proved it.
For five years, Kevin,
he proved it.
It's your turn.
He deserves to live a life.
He deserves to be able to have
the same hopes and dreams
as the rest of us, Kevin.
To be able to hold his head up
to the world.
Now you gotta give him
that chance.
Please.
I...
Wasn't supposed to be
like this, Charlie.
So many times
I wanted to make it right
and then I...
I look at my wife, my son,
and I... (Sighs)
I'm sorry, Charlie.
I'm so, so sorry.
I know,
but that's not what I need.
I did it.
I pushed that kid.
I killed him.
If there's anything else,
I'll let you know.
Hey.
Oh...
Thank you.
For the words.
You're welcome, Charlie.
♪ Everybody says they're sorry ♪
I love you.
♪ 'Cause nobody knows
the story ♪
♪ the recipe of life ♪
Today's not gonna win him
any points
with the authorities.
No, no.
But he was innocent,
and he showed
a strong moral code
and that counts for a lot.
I'll talk to Lavery.
Maybe a criminal institution
isn't the best place for him.
Change of environment?
It's gonna make
a world of difference.
Be nice to get someone
out of prison for a change.
Hey. Hey,
that was good work.
And, uh, thanks
for letting me know
about Spike.
I'm gonna talk to him.
No, you're not.
You're gonna go home,
you're gonna put your feet up.
Buddy, you got too much
on your plate.
Let me help you out here.
Eddie,
you're worrying about me.
You don't need to worry.
You know why?
You used to say that
when you had a date
with a bottle of scotch.
So go home.
I'll file the report.
I'll take that as a yes.
Go on.
Okay.
Thanks, Eddie.
♪ They say oh-oh ♪
♪ whose side are you on? ♪
Hey, yeah,
this is Mike Scarlatti.
Yeah, I'm calling
about the wine kit.
I got it right here,
so I just gotta...
What're you doing?
Hey, sorry to interrupt.
This is Edward Lane.
I'm Mr. Scarlatti's
wine representative.
I'm sorry to tell you
that we got a better offer,
so, uh, thank you,
and you have a great day.
Done.
Just like that.
We were thinking maybe
you shouldn't sell this stuff,
Spike.
Raf: You don't wanna waste it on
a guy who won't appreciate it.
Ed: Buddy, come on, we can
figure out how to make
a couple bottles of this stuff.
It's gonna be great.
Are you serious?
I'm more of a beer guy, myself.
Christmas presents, Sam.
- Mm-hm.
- Right?
I'll catch up with you guys.
Sam:
All right.
Marina: It can be the
strangest things sometimes.
Like...
I see red roses,
and I see the rose
and I see his face again.
Triggers.
Triggers can be anything.
It could take a long time,
but that is normal.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
♪ I've asked for forgiveness ♪
♪ I try being right ♪
♪ I've lied wide awake ♪
♪ under the weight
of the night ♪
♪ my heartache grows harder ♪
♪ till you decide it's time ♪
Marina:
Parmesan.
There you are.
♪ If anybody says
they're sorry ♪
♪ could you easy up their way ♪
♪ nobody wants their story ♪
♪ tell them they're okay ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com