text jules: no way, our lou?
i know, eh?but put him on the dance floor,
you'd think he...
hey, happy feet!
- lewis: hey, what's up?
- spike: you got the pictures?
- wordy: jamaica!
- ocho rios.
110 degrees in the shade.check out my man here,
he got a bit of a tan.
is this guy fast-forwarding to bridget?
jules: who's bridget?who's bridget?
sam: she's hot.
i haven't seen her since high school.
and then i don't see this guy for three days.
jules: really?you think it's the real deal?
destiny speaks, i don't ask questions.
man 1: sheila's freaking out about
joey talking or not talking.
man 2: kid's one and a half.
tell her to cut him some slack.
man 1: this is sheila we're talking about?
the word "slack" is not in her vocabulary.
man 2: he got any new words?
man 1: yeah, "up, dada.
- man 2: what, no "mama"?
- man 1: no.
man 2: well, there's the problem.
gotta teach him "mama.
" pretty quiet.
yeah, great for writing reports.
i was thinking i'd go down to the range.
i got some new ammo for the remmy...
homework first, then go play.
- how did i know you'd say that?
- parker: 'cause you know me.
boss?
man: in ten minutes, the future headquarters of globalmax energy group will be destroyed by a bomb.
parker: this is sergeant parker, who am i talking to?
man: in ten minutes, the future headquarters...
pre-recording, eddie.
winnie: this is for real?
- parker: we move like it is.
- ed: bomb call!let's go!
can we trace that call, winnie?
winnie: no, it's v.o.i.p., rerouted through an anonymous server.
future headquarters.it's a construction site.
okay, find out where globalmax is building.
get a hold of the foreman, patch him through to my phone.
got it.
winnie: foreman's not picking up, sarge.i'll keep trying.
parker: this is sergeant greg parker with the police...
we've received a bomb threat targeting your construction site.
speak up, i can't hear you.
jimmy, kill it!
yeah, go again.
parker: this is the police, we've received a bomb threat.you need to evacuate.
come on, i don't got time for this, who's this?
parker: sir, this is not a prank.
we've received a bomb threat, you need to evacuate now.
there's a bomb.
there's a bomb!everybody evacuate!get out now!move it!evacuate!
foreman: let's go!
i need everyone off the site now!this the foreman!this is not a test!
there's a bomb!everyone off the site now!it's an emergency!
move!move!move!move!keep moving, let's go!off the site!
- parker: everyone okay?
- wordy: all right.
i'm good, boss.
spike: yeah, me too, boss.
parker: you okay, buddy?
parker: get e.m.t.here right away.
everybody get out okay?
yeah, i think so.i think so.we gotta do a head count here.
winnie: sarge, priority call.
patch it through.
man: a bomb has been placed in the offices of a known environmental criminal
and it will detonate in one hour.
parker: priority one: we profile the subject.
locate the target, intercept it in time.
all right?spike?
spike: lou and i will check for a follow-up bomb.
if we're clear, we'll run diagnostics on the site.
see what we can learn from the bomber's materials.
boss, i had a look at a lot of i.e.d.'s in afghanistan.
parker: that's great, give 'em a hand.
ed: wordy, let's take the witnesses.
- wordy: got it.
- parker: jules, command truck.
let's get to know our friend.
what do you have, spike?
spike: okay, blast radius: 3.2 metr depth: 1.6 metres.
so, explosive force of about 3000 kilojoules.
that narrows it down.
what have we go on globalmax energy group?
jules: well, they patented a method of extracting crude from the tar sands.
effective, but environmentally toxic.
'kay, let's talk to csis, see who they've got on their eco-terror watch list.
- lewis: boss?
- parker: yeah, lou, go ahead.
ion scanner's identified the explosive.it's tnt.
can we trace it?
spike: yep, the residue, it has tracer elements embedded into it.
the lab can trace it right to the manufacturer,
right down to where the shipment was delivered...
okay, you had me at "yep." let's do it.
spike: copy that.
sam: spike, check this out.
we can trace this.
it has solder on it.
this batter set it off.we got a bar code.
sweet, sam.
nice.
eddie, any leads on a suspect?
we're working on it.
foreman: i can't believe they went this far.
these guys are a royal pain in the butt.
they're here every day like clockwork.
foreman: yesterday, things got out of control.
male protestor: globalmax murders the planet!we are not moving!
- you are not getting...
- hold on one minute, i'll get rid of 'em.
male protester: you are not getting through here!
call your boss, call your boss's boss, tell him we're not moving.
tell him he's accountable for murdering the planet!
you go call him, i gotta a job to do!
- get outta here!
- male protestor: no, we're not moving!
we are not moving!
foreman: all right, move it on.let's go, move it in.
you are not getting through here!
- you are not getting...
- foreman: i said move!i meant move!get outta here!
male protestor: this is not over!
i'm gonna be your worst nightmare!we are taking this to the next level!
boss, we had threats uttered yesterday by a member of an activist group
called "the olive branch collective.
" wordy: he wanted to take the protest to the next level.
jules: olive branch...
yep, they are on the csis watch list.
parker: it is not exactly a covert operation, they've got a downtown office address.
okay, here's what we've got.
we've narrowed the list of potential targets to three possibilities.
keffler corp, duchamp energy, and morgan-ellis.
now, they're all toxic bad boys fighting charges under the environmental protection act.
all right, good.we will talk to their heads of security,
we'll coordinate an immediate evac with fire and police.
- parker: all right, let's go.
- jules: let's go.
we'll take sam to help handle the bomb sweeps,
split the targets with the bomb techs from team 2 and team 5.
while you guys shake down the tree-huggers.
parker: environmental activists.
whatever.
man: hey, let's see your warrant.
we don't need a warrant to walk through an open door.
oh, no warrant?yeah, then you can turn around and walk right out that open door.
it's okay, jordan.
i'm john martens, can i help you?
sergeant greg parker, officer jules callaghan.
wanted to ask you a few questions about a bomb that was detonated at a construction site.
globalmax energy group.i just read the news feed.
we understand you were there yesterday.
yeah, we staged a lawful non-violent protest action.
foreman said that you uttered threats to take it to the next level.
i threatened him?
have a look.
martens: you tell him "take it to the next level"
means unleash the most badass internet tition in history.
we don't do bombs.
we start with the carnage, we lose the public.
no more donations, our revenue streams dry up.
violence runs counter to our business model.
business models and revenue streams?
the times, they are a-changin'.
yeah, well, just because he speaks mba doesn't mean they're not into something harder.
hey, what if one of his comrades went rogue?
or maybe john martens is hiding in plain sight.
winnie, let's get a hold of with 41 division,
let's send an undercover unit to surveil john martens and the olive branch.
copy that.
ed: okay, let's split up.report back with evac status.
we're gonna start at the bottom, work our way up with fido, here.
sam and wordy: copy.got it.
spike: boss, we got something.
we've been working on finding our guy's signature.
signature?
spike: yeah, bombers, they tend to be consistent;
they find their favourite materials and their techniques and they stick to them.
so it could be a specific photo-electric sensor from a smoke detector...
- okay...
- or a specific pattn of circuits.
so we ran all the elements through the federal signature database.
find a match?
spike: hey, boss, i know the database doesn't lie,
but lou's never heard of these guys, i've never heard of these guys.
the p.l.c.?people's liberation core.
p.l.c.that goes back.
winnie, you got anything for us?
winnie: uh, full membership number unknown.
string of environmentally related bombings, late '70s.
leaders...vanessa and sheldon kominski, arrested in 1980.
okay, any recent activity?
winnie: nhing reported.
parker: what about our friends, the kominskis?
vanessa and sheldon kominski are now faculty at the university.
- parker: how's that?
- professors emeritus, poli-sci.
professors, huh?
times are a-changin'.
this is the most powerful aspect of hegemony.
state control is redundant.
we've internalized the values...
parker: sheldon and vanessa kominski?
we need a word with you.
speaking of state control, is today "show and tell"?
sheldon: we've always been very open about our past with the p.l.c.
it's probably what gives us credibility with our students.
but the membership's long dispersed and we've had a lot of time to think,
as one does behind bars.
besides, as soon as we were released, i got pregnant with sara.
- jules: is this sara?
- vanessa: yes.
vanessa: how could we run around being outlaws when we had a responsibility to her?
okay, well, then how do you explain this morning's bomb had the p.l.c.signature?
there was only one bomb technician among us, rafer wilcox.
- where do we find him?
- no idea.we hardly see him.
27 minutes until the next bomb goes off.think hard, we need to talk to him.
rafer's always lived off the grid, on principle.
and to tell the truth, ever since we had sara, we kept our distance.
okay, but is there something you can give us...
a former address?an alias?
he used to go by simon richdale.
other times it was ronald mellor.
that's great.thank you very much for your time.
- boss?
- eddie.
ed: we're in the machine room, keffler corp.
we got bomb number two.
flashpoint
Season 03 Episode 01
lewis: 11:43 am, bomb call, robot sending out signal blocking remote detonation.
spike: we're sending in babycakes.
assuming the device is triggered by a timer, boss, we got 25 minutes until detonation.
that's also assuming our guy's any good at setting timers.
and that he plans on sticking to the schedule.
spike, i'm gonna come out there and give you a hand.
forget it.rule number one of diffusion:
don't blow stuff up?
never more than one man down-range.you know that.
sam: let's go, let's keep this moving.we need to evacuate this building immediately.
sorry, ma'am, we need to keep moving.
businesswoman: let me get this, just take a sec.
there's no time, we need you to keep moving.
i didn't get my laptop.i have to go back for it.it'll only take a minute.
i've got eleven years worth of work on it.
sam mam, if anything happens, i'm not gonna be the one to tell your family it was just gonna take a minute.
let's keep ming.
parker: winnie, has the lab come back with anything on the tnt?
winnie: just in.
manufacturer's name is procan chemical.
that's great.
now let's look into purchases made by a ronald mellor or a simon richdale, last six months.
opy that.i' red flag large quantities.
no.negative.notarge quantities.
large quantities is for legitimate industrial clients.
we're looking for small quantities only.
knew that.
ed: building's secure.spike's the only remaining personnel.
spike: and babycakes.don't forget babycakes.
okay, spike, read me the tea leaves.
okay, you see that shadow, top left?that's looking like a digital clock.
so it is s to trigger byimer.
ed: let's set up transport to move this bomb off site.we've got 21 minutes.
spike: exce you see those two shadows, bottom lef those are mercury switches.
motion sensitive.
spike: motion very sensitive.
can't me it.
gonna take human hands not to setit off.
i'm going in.
spike...
okay.
copy that.
sarge, we got another call coming through.
i'm patching th one in live.
voice: the third bomb will detonate 12:30 pm on the campus of halliwell technical college.
the third bomb will detonate 12:30 pm...
all right, that's 40 minutes from now.he's picking up the pace.
dividing to conquer.
parker: jules, you stay here with spike.
lou, let's get to the college.
eddie?
on .
lou, get a head-start on the scans, i'll catch up soon as i can, okay?
lewis: copy that.
spike: you gotta be kidding me.
i got a match.
tnt delivery to a simon richdale.
that's rafer's alias.
at's the address?
788 joliet in parkdale.
ed: boss, that' close.
change of plans.we're gonna drop in on rafer.he might have answers...
or demands, or something we can use.
sam police strategic response unit!
stay where you are!show us your hands!
wordy.
hands in the air!
or you'll shoot me?
rafer wilcox?
ed: put down ringe!
relax, nothing in it.
ed: put it down!
rafer: no.
wordy: clear upstairs.
you had tnt was delivered to this address weeks ago.
rafer: that's right.
ed: for what purpo?
to blow stuf up.
boss, we got a trap door.
you're responsible for the bombs?
rafer: no, globalmax energy group and keffler are responsible for the bombs.
we just put them there.
you sick here, buddy?what's going on?
it ain't catchg.
- hands in the air!
- all right.
ed: put it down!put it down!
winnie, i need an e.m.t.
won'tget heren me.
then y're gonna talk fast.
wordy: sarge, we found his maps.
the third bomb...
is located at the foot of the earth sciences building.
sam: and he knows what he's dng.he's planted the bomb at a suppo column.
it blows, that building comes down.
copy that.we're seconds away.
sam: the good news is, it looks like it's the last of 3 targets.
you said, "we just put them there.
" is thisc.?
no, the kominskis took everything we fought for, spat on it,
and sold it out for an ivory tower tnure.
we just need the schematics for the bombs.
i'm running out of time to make a difference, so i'm calling the shots now.
we're getting the message out.
you and who else?
- i can't hear you.
no, you don't get to lecture me about human lives, jacoot.
we need to defuse the bomb, please.
how do you defuse the bombs, rafer, please?
i'm not the one to blame for collateral damage.
you and who else?
- this is what i'm here for.
- you oka?you and who else?
you and who else, buddy?you and o else, please?
parker: he gave himself a heart attack?
he injected himself with air.
okay, did you get anything out of him, eddie?
ed: yeah, he's not working alone.
wordy: andwas sick.
sam: yeah, his hands were shaking.
assembling a bomb is precision work.he'd need someone with steady hands.
let's tear this place apart.we look for emails, letter anything that can help us id the accomplice.
let's go.
spike: you guys?schematics.
schematics would be great.
parker: all right, team, our subject, may he rest in peace,
has left us juggling an unidentified accomplice and two scheduled detonations.
11 minutes to go on the keffler corp bomb, 29 minutes to go...
on the halliwell college bomb.
ed: this guy wants to save the world, make a big statement,
"oh, i know, let's blow up some college students, that'd be good.
" it's not just that.hliwell college just signed a huge funding deal with the lyrium think tank.
global warming deniers.
parker: the way he saw it, they're brainwashing a new generation of climate killers.
wordy: sarge?halliwell?lyrium?
is there anything you dot know?
it's the burden i bear, wordy.
jules: that and it was a fture article in the star last weekend.
ouch.thank you, cstable callaghan.
now how we doing on tracing that baery?
jules: well, it's a common brand and a partial bar code, so, il keep you posted.
copy that.thanks.
spike, what kind of schematic are we looking for?
anything showing a circuit and 3 batters.i'm flying blind here.
half these wires are dummy, and he's given me 3 det wires to choose from.
i cut the wrong one, or i even touch a crush wire...
copy that.
spike: if wrun out of time, i'm gonna have to walk away, let it blow.
copy?
sam: copy.
parker: hey, inspector, how're you doing?
stainton: sergeant.
our bomb's at the base of that pillar there.it's under the garbage bags.
'kay, i'll get started on e reckie.
- and our evacuation's in progress.
- thank you, inspector.
jules: winnie, any update on that battery?
i've traced theerial number and the expiry date to a bulk club outlet in mississauga.
a lot shipped two weeks ago.
that's gat, bulk club works by membership.
i checked the membership records, there's no rafer wilcox or any of his aliases.
well, it's his accomplice that we're looking for.
- can you upload the bulk club security feed to me, please?
- i'm on it.
spike: lou, we're looking for anyone or anything that looks out of place.
any sign of a pulwire near the device?
lewis: okay, it's hidd by garbage bags, but there's nothing extending out.
i don't see anythg.
how're we doing, wordy?
wordy: not great.our pal rafer was pretty fond of his paper-shredder.
sam: spike, good news.
got the schematics for all 3 bombs, including one with ththree batteries.
samtastic!upload me a photo, would ya?
one minute.
parker: clock's running down, spike.howe you doing?
boss, we got the schematics, let me get a head start.
spike: no-no-no, i'll be there.i'm nearly done here.
lewis: spike, i've seen you do it, okay?i cahandle a pair of cutters.
spike: copy that.
we're gonna lose people here.
'kay, go.
going down range.
okay, i'm on scene, spike.
spike: okay, lou, you id three garbage bags?
anything rigged if they move?
lewis: okay...
no visible booby-tra, no wiring.
spike: okay, that's good.so you get those garbage bags out of the way, okay?
take it real slow.make sure they don't touch the device.
okay.
got60 access to the device.
it's a shaped charge, spike.
it's big, man.
guys...
what is it?lou?
i think i just stepped on a land mine.
come again,lou?
i just stepped on a land mine.
how do you know that?
i heard the click.
i can feel the trigger
spikes through my boot.
okay,lou,important thing
is...just stay calm.
- i'm clm.
- okay?yeah?
yeah,i'm good,boss.
okay,you just make sure...
- i'm not moving.
- all right,good.yojust...
relax.
lou,don't even shift your
weight,okay?no decrease in pressure.
okay,i got you,spike.
i'm gonna get this thing
nailed,and then i'm on way,
i'm gonna get you
out,buddy,okay?i'm gonna get you out.
spike!
you just stay focused,okay
we're all good here.
boss,how much time we
got left on this bomb?
we got,uh...we got...
we got time,lou.
eddie,go to channel four.
what do you think we're looking at?
i don'know.he heard a
click,no visible wires.
if it were magnet r vibration
triggers,it wod've already gone off.
but is there any way of
knowing what he's standing on?
- sam?
- could be a blast mine,bounding,frag...
guys,if he stepped on one of those...
it's over.
all right,i got uniforms
containing the uare.
all communications is now on
channel 4,i'll keep lou on channel 3.
t's important keep him calm.
- and let the rest of the team know,winnie.
- copy that.
sarge,i think i have soing.
battery purchase matching
the bar code,six days ago.
it's not rafer,it's a female.
i got a feeling.
okay,i need more than
a feeling here,jules.
okay,hang on.
11:02 am,ember number 0763827.
vanessa kominski.
- nice.
- wait.
okayit's her card,but it's their
daughter.it's sara kominski.
okay,we're gonna need that
photo.send it out to everyone,jules.
on its way.
hey,winnie,let's send
a team to the ominski's,
see if sara's there and i
want her parents here,too.
on our way.if we find sa,maybe
we find a way out of this for lou.
sam,it's getting a little delicate here.
i'm gonna need both mv y
hands,okay?can you talk me through?
he's hasn't colour-coded his wires.
hs soldered hundreds of them
together.the guy has a death wish.
had a death wish.
okay...
on the right side of the
resister,third battery,
i'm looking at a y-circuit,all
right?three wires.
is one of them marked?
- you're looking north?
- yeah.
okay,east wire of the y,it
looks like it grounds out?
yeah.
it doesn't,that's the one you want.
it's the only one connected to the
active detonator on the third battery.
unless that's what
he wants you to think.
you mean,he leaves a phony
schematic lying around?
he might.he didn't look toourprised to
see us.he may have been expecting company.
spike?
doe't matter,it's done.
all right.bomb needs to
be contained and disposed.
sam,send me a preview
of that college bomb.
lou,buddy,i'm on my way.
no one's talking to me.
who would wanna talk to you?
you guys switched channels.
that's because you're
always driving us nuts.
you with the talking,talking,talking.
i can do it,spike.
no,we're close.
we're not that close,spike.
lou,you take your weight off
that trigger,it's gonna blow.
isn't the job about risk?
that's why we're here,right?
lou...
isn't it about saving lives,spike?
come on.
come on,spike,talk me throh.
talk me through,spike,come on.
let him do it,spike.
you goa kit?
yeah.
okay,lou.
don't touch the detonator,okay?
he's got three yers of countermeasures,
and we are gonna disable
them in revee order.
inspector.
there are people in there.going on?
i got everavailable uniform here.
what about those guys?
you gotta clear that building
there are live bombs here.
yeah,i got it.
upper right corner,you see the battery?
- use that as your orientation point.
- okay.
we're calling that north,you got it?
- okay,iot it.
- you sure?
i got it.
yeah?'use it wouldn't be the first time you
took a le when i told you to take a right.
eddie,how far are u?
we're here.
i got her.
sara kinski.light purple sweater.
we're here,buddy,i can ee you.
okay,let's count 'em up now.
how many you cut?
six.
oh,that's good.you
only got one more,okay?
just the one.
- how're ya holding up?
- cool as ice.
- yeah?
- yeah.
three minutes.
you good to go?
leg's a little shaky.
you need a sec?
- is the perimeter cleared?
- it's sealed.
the building's evacuated.we're
three minutes away.
eddie?
we got her,boss.o,don't move!
get off me,jackboot!
sara,that's not very nice.
mr.kominski.
sara and rafer have any history?
there's no aughter is involved.
she bought the batteries that
triggered these bombs,sir.
- she was rafer's accomplice.
- there's a mistake.
no,sir,there was no mistake.
we hardly see him.
hould he have dragged her into this?
last time we saw him,he dropped
by the office,out of the blue.
about 3 years ago.
he hadn't seen sara since she was a kid.
for ten years they're killing a
river,poisoning an entire community.
because nobody does anything.
one night is all it took.
morning,rafer.
morning,professors.
just fling in your offspring
here on the good ol' days.
sara,don't you have class?
- dad..
- sara.
oh,that son of a bitch!
rafer wox took his own
life a half hour ago.
boss,60 seconds.
get behind the truck.spike!
move 'em back.
building's not clear!
- what?
- we got kids on the roof somewhere,we just found 'em.
buildings not clear.
come on,inspector,do it fast!
right side of the
relay,a y-circuit,3 wires.
- yeah.
- east wire,east of the "y",where it splits.
you got it?
that's east.
- that's your det wire.
- okay.
no wrong turns,right,buddy?
no wrong turns.
done.
inspector,bomb's defused.
the land mine's not.
sara!all right,here it comes.
is it true,you and rafer?
yeah,it is,so lock me up.
you know,you weren't so scared of jail
yourselves,when there was important work to do.
all right,i've had enough of this.
land mine sara,tell me about 'em.
what,land mines?
don't play dumb.
no,i swear,we would never do
land mines.property damage only.
that's why we gave advanced warning.
oh,oh my god,rafer.
uh,we set the bombs
last night,about 3:00 am,
and then he insisted that i go home.
he didn't set those bombs himself,with
his unsteady hands.come on,sara.
land mines are totally safe
to handle until they're armed.
get her out of here.
- lou,you feel that trigger under your foot?
- yeah.
okay,what does it feel like
- at,a spike,or a bunch of spikes?
it's a buncof spikes.
- gotcha
- what are you doing?
these mines are plastic.a metal detector won't
work.i'm gonna use a ground penetrating radar.
spike,gpr is not...
you got something
better in your backpack?
spike,it's a land mine.
he is on the trigger.now,even
if you make your way through...
i'm gonna get him out.
spike,stay where you are!
lou,buddy,what are you doing?
hey,lou,you found us,huh?
you guys gotta nd aetter
hiding place than channel 4.
coming out there,lou.
no,you can have two
men down range,spike.
oh,what's the fifth rule,lou?
fifth rule is break the
rules when you have to.
he's not wrong.
this job's about what?
yeah,saving lives.
following your footsteps,buddy.
oh,got one.
how we doing,buddy?
i good.
hope you're ting
advantage of the downtime.
yeah,i'm just hanging out.
ah,another on
there's ather one.
this guy was busy.
okay,we're car.
what took you so long,man?
traffic.you know how it is.
what're you doing?
i'm gonna see if he
booby-trapped the booby trap.
keep your foot still,okay?
yeah.
yeah,there it is.
okay,here we,let's see
what we're loong at.
move them back!
this is still a contained situation!
spike,what do you see?
whwe got,ike?
spike.
it's a bounding mine.
it's a cr-38.
i think you should just
get outta here,spike.
doesn't change a
thing,man.not single thing.
spike,we gotta strategize here.
nothing to strategize.
- i'm gonna defuse the land mine and lou's gonna walk aw
- defuse it how?
i'm gonna excavate around the
mine,and then i'm gonna render it safe.
- spike...
- shut up.
i'm getting you of here,we're
all going home today.
- **
- yeah,they're russian.
igniter sets off a propelling charge,it
fires the mine a metre in the air,
that ignites the main charge.
what if we get a shield out there?
it's not gonna do any good.
the cr-38
is anti-tank.
can spike defuse it?
sam?
it's a 38.
maybe he can re-pin it.
land mines,man.you don't
mess with land mines.
it'll take two men down instead of one.
if anybody can do it,it's spike.
if i were the sarge,i'd
give him a direct oer.
well,if i was spike i'd pretend
i didn't hear that order.
almost there,buddy.
almost there.
you know what i'm looking for?
it's a little hole.these,these
mines,they come with a safety.
with a little luck,i
can re-pin the hole.
fir rule of tactic never rely on luck.
did you say something?
okay,hello.
there you are.
you got it?
status report,spike.
he glued it.
he glued the hole.
i can't even touch it.
no,no...no,no...no.
come on,we gotta think of something.
we dissolve it with acid?
freeze it with liquinitrogen.
oy works on electronics.that
mine's mechanical.
sam?
you gotta pull spe outta there,boss.
- how many shields we got in the truck?
- won't do any good.
hold your foot still,okay?
i'just gonna re-stabilize.
okay,i know there's a way.
there's always a way.
of course there is.
okay,he sealed down the safety with glue;i
can lock down the spikes with glue,unless...
remember in ocho rios?
uncle rodney,bonie and her
kids took us to that jump-up?
y,that was good.
okay,neodymium magnet.
w-we'll place it underneath,wll
lock down all moving parts.
bridget and her friend...
rum and ginger beer by the beach...
lou,you mind?i'm thinking.
aays feels good in the ocean,man.
you get rocked by the waves...
like you're going full circle,you
know?back to being a baby again.
water's just rockin' you.
water!
we'll do a weight transfer.
oh,it could w we run water into a
container a gallon of water is what,
is eight pounds,right?
spike,you know what you should do?
what?
you should call up bridget.
what're you talking about?
there's a ge on tonight,right?
she loves baseball.you should
call her up,you should take her ou
we transfer the weight.
it's a good shot,it's
the best shot we...
it's a good shot!
- spike.
- i'm not leaving you okay.
okay,water,we'll do it.
but first get the explosives
from the first bomb out of range.
no,no,no,it's defused,you
cut the detonator.
spike,the mine goes off,it triggers the
tnt in there,we bring the building down.
okay?
we just gotta py it safe.
it's a gd thought.
i have my moments.
don't go anywhere.
i'm gonna see you in a bit,okay?
it's not going to work.
- you don't know that.
- actually,i think i do know about that.
radios off.
sam,how do you know that?
that's the trigger.that's his foot.
you're not getting anything in between
there without a decrease in pressure.
no offence,but do you
know that for sure?
i've dealt with mines in the field.
so you know everything that is to know?
- i didn't say that.
- easy.easy,guys.
sam?
- is spike's plan gonna work?
- the chances are not good.
okay,so you don't know.
- i know physics.
- oh,andi don't?
what i know is that
it's a long-shot at best.
'kay,a long shot is still a shot.
greg,we're talking about two lives here.
wordy: let's give spike a chance.
you wanna see two guys get blown
up by giving spike a chance?
okay.
spike?spike,maybe we
should slow this thing down.
no,n boss,there's no time.
spike.spike!
i'moming back to the truck,okay?we're
na need something flat,like...
like a shield.somebody grab a shield.
- we can't let him go back out there.
- he's made up his mind.
he's emotional,he's panicking,he
is not thinking straight.
- and you are?
- i'm just...i'm saying...
he can't make that
decisn,we cannot let him...
- he's given us an option.
- it's not an option.
lou'leg is shaking,his muscles are
gonna spasm,and when that happens...
- sam.
- you gotta make the call.
i'm not gonna be the one to hold
him back from saving a friend.
and i'm not gonna lose 'em both.
so,what are we gonna do?just
wait for lou to get tired?
what's the option here,greg?you tell me.
dad,mom there?
oh yeah?
no.
i just wanna say i love you guys.
no,no...
everything's good.i'm
just,uh...i'm just at work.
just,um...
tell her i called.oust,um...
tell her i was thinking about her,okay?
all right.
why are you all just standing there?
let's go.i said,we need a
shield,we need wate okay?
we're gonna do a weight transfer!
spike?
yeah,bud.lou!
it'sgonna be okay.
lou?