(Suspenseful music)
(Grunting)
What?
What do you have to say?
Hostage:
(Grunts and pants)
I have a wife.
I got two kids.
I want this to be over
as much as you do.
Oh, it will be over
very soon.
SRU: Police! SRU! Right there!
Get down! Drop your weapon!
SRU! On the ground now!
Right there!
Ed: Where's Hamilton?
Where's Hamilton?!
Hey! Ed! Come here!
(Wheels rasp along pavement)
(Board clunks onto platform)
(Button beeps)
(Wheels rasp)
(Camcorder beeps)
Holy crap!
(Doorbell dings)
First Monday of the month, my turn.
Hi.
Double double,
skim milk.
Since when is home delivery
part of the deal?
Well, since I have news.
Police services
just announced the, uh...
Law enforcement professional
of the year.
Julianna Callaghan.
Really?
Congratulations.
The gala's in a month.
Spotlight's all on you.
"In recognition
of exemplary service-
Sam:
Hey, Jules, I'm starving.
You want some eggs?
(Wheels rasp)
But this isn't just any bag.
It's a black courier bag,
with no ID.
Man: Hey!
Girl: And inside...
Bag, now.
Oh my God,
he's got a gun.
Oh my God.
I put my job on the line
for you.
For both of you.
I gave him my word.
Sam: Have you seen
our performance slip?
Has there been one moment-
it only takes
one moment.
The whole team
is still on probation;
everytime we go out on a call,
it's put under a microscope.
The priority of life.
Jules:
Boss, we know.
We put the lives of the public
ahead of our own.
Ahead of each others'.
It's not gonna change.
Parker: You know
what the worst part is?
I knew.
I was hoping I was wrong,
but I knew,
and now my head is on the block
if this ever comes out.
(All cell phones chirp)
Yeah.
I'm on my way.
Gun call.
911 from MacLennan Park.
Team four's already out,
we got upped early.
And we will pick this up
later.
Hey.
I know.
Someone took it,
but I got it back.
I don't-
yeah, fine.
I'll hand it off myself.
All right?
Just get here.
(Sirens wail)
Girl:
This isn't just any bag.
It's a black courier bag
with no id.
Man: Hey!
Girl: And inside.
Man:
Bag, now.
Girl:
Oh my God, he's got a gun.
Oh my God.
And that's it.
Okay, any idea
where in the park?
I'm sending out a map
right now.
Sam:
That's a big park.
Spike:
Three acres of urban wilderness.
I'll see if I can
narrow it down.
We have a name?
Yeah, the cell phone
belongs to Hana Stampf.
Parker:
We make a call?
Jules:
No answer.
Robbery.
Spike: We found a clean
part of the call.
I enhanced the background
and made a loop.
Listen.
(Rustling sound)
Guesses?
Shopping cart?
Parking lot?
Skateboards.
Some guy not quite
making a trick.
Ed:
Home-run, Spike.
Sam: There's a skateboard
park off Leslie.
Spike, Raf,
come in through the back,
off of Woodbine.
Talk to witnesses
and find the girl,
and hope we're not too late.
It's in there?
Yeah.
All of it?
What do you think, I'm stupid?
Ed:
Sam.
Black courier bag.
You called the cops?
Sam:
Police! Drop the bag!
Man: Go!
Sam: Stop! Stay right there!
(Fires two gunshots)
No one moves!
Spike: Was that gunfire?
Raf: Backup on the way.
Ed: Negative.
Stay with the runner.
Spike:
On him!
Sir! I need you to put
the gun on the ground.
I need you to stop
where you are.
Parker:
We can do that.
I just need know
if the girl's okay.
What girl?
The girl you took
that bag from.
She sounded pretty scared
on the phone.
It's what happens when you
get in over your head.
Let's not get any deeper.
Where is she?
No idea.
Spike: Police!
Stay where you are!
Okay, I'm gonna put
my gun away,
lower the temperature
a little bit.
Mind telling me
your name?
Connect, protect,
respect, right?
That's right.
Martin: Yeah, SRU.
You guys got all the answers.
But today
we're playing it my way.
Greg, I'm not reading drugs
on this.
Suit like that,
you get someone else
to do your drops.
He knows the protocol.
Maybe he's a cop?
Sam: With that gun,
I'm thinking military.
Ed:
He knows what he's doing.
He's not pointing
the weapon at us.
Wanna tell us
what your way looks like?
Not yet.
We waiting
for something?
We're waiting
'cause I said so.
Dark haired youth:
(Pants)
Blond youth:
Hey!
Man, gimme my bike!
Raf:
Stop!
Spike: I got the kid,
I got the kid.
Raf:
Police! Stop that bike now!
Spike: That come off him?
Blond youth: Yeah.
Stay right here.
Boss, I don't like him
calling the shots here.
Ideas?
Ed: Let's swap out
, do less lethal.
Parker:
All right, go for it.
I think this guy's
playing us anyway.
I'll give it
one more shot.
You know what, sir?
No one's in a rush here, sir,
but I gotta tell ya...
Standing around
in the middle of a park,
waving a gun?
That sets a bad example.
And I'm guessing that
you're not gonna use it,
so it's time to put it
on the ground.
Not yet.
I'm afraid so, sir.
I'm gonna give the signal,
you're gonna get hit
with rubber bullets.
Man:
Ooh... they sting.
Oh yeah, they do.
Okay.
(Gun clicks)
Ed:
Hands up, behind your head.
Raf: Police!
Stop that bike now!
Aw, man,
you gotta be kidding me?
Southwest end of the park.
Suspect's on wheels, guys.
I could use a hand here.
We're on it.
Spike: I know why our
guy was so interested
in making tracks.
Quick look...
About a quarter
of a million dollars.
Parker:
Robbery,
resisting arrest...
Any other charges
you wanna tell me we can add?
You guys
intercepted the bag?
Yeah, we did.
Then you just killed
my client.
Hey!
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Sync by Alex1969
www.addic7ed.com
♪
(Siren wails)
He could be anywhere.
Back alleys,
subway stop...
Could've stashed his car
right here and taken off.
I don't know.
I lost him, man.
Don't worry about it.
Let's go, let's go.
Parker: It's all right,
the day's not over.
Come on back.
That guy get away?
Who is he?
Don't know, don't care.
You deliver a bag
full of money
to a stranger,
you pull a gun
so he gets away,
and you don't seem interested
in us helping out.
There's still a chance
this whole mess works out
if you guys just walk away.
That's not gonna happen.
Officer?
Hold him.
Spike.
Martin Terran -
everything you can find out
about the guy.
Driver's license,
credit cards,
that's not gonna be problem.
Jules, any luck on
our 9-1-1 caller?
Terran threatened her
with the gun,
took her phone,
and told her to get lost.
She's a little fighter;
she snuck back
with her video camera.
I'm gonna bring it to you.
Parker:
Okay, thanks.
Sam was right.
You were talking
to captain Martin Terran -
or he was.
He left the army
two years ago.
Intelligence branch.
Citations,
awards, medals.
So, why'd he leave?
Spike:
Better paycheck.
He's vice president
of risk operations
for a company called CMI -
Conflict Management
International.
(Tires screech)
I know CMI.
They're real active overseas.
Private security?
No, more like training
and support.
Liaison.
Fixers really.
Well, you know this guy Terran?
Sam: If he's former military
, I can make some calls.
Parker:
That'd be great, Sam.
Jules: Okay, I found a good
three-quarters shot of our guy.
I'm gonna get a screen
grab and send it out.
Raf:
That's a gang tat.
On his neck?
Yeah, Metaca Mafia - M2.
It's a sign of commitment.
Once you're in,
you're in for life.
Parker:
Ed?
Boss, it's time to check in
with guns and gangs.
Spike: Got a lead on
the money, boss.
Sequential bills traced back
to Hingston Financial.
Withdrawn from a corporate
account this morning
connected to an oil
and gas firm
called Bridgefield
International.
Sam: 'Kay, that's the
connection, boss.
Bridgefield hired Terran
six months ago.
They send their employees
to some pretty dangerous places
and Terran specializes in
anti-kidnapping protocols;
what to do to keep
your employees safe.
So, what's he doing
at a skate park?
(Siren wails)
Is this detective
Kevin James Wordsworth,
rising star of guns
and gangs?
Edward Tucker Lane.
More like second from the bottom
of the totem pole.
Gimme a pencil though,
I can push it for you.
Ed: (Laughs) Look, Wordy
, I need a hand here, buddy.
Shoot.
I need some info
on the Metaca Mafia.
Wordy: No problem.
How's that new guy doing?
Ed:
Oh, he's doing okay.
Big shoes to fill,
buddy.
(Half laughs)
I bet.
So here's what we have
on your guys.
Metaca Mafia - M2.
Big in Mexico.
Into pretty much everything
down there.
Slowly moving north.
Listen, what's their game
up here?
Looks like a bit
of a blank slate.
Uh... recruiting.
Making noise...
There's a tag on the file.
Meaning?
Meaning... you're gonna have
to talk to someone
a little further up
the totem pole.
Parker: Hey, wordy,
any chance kidnapping
is on their to-do list?
Spike: Bridgefield - the company
Terran's been working for -
had a rash of kidnappings
down in Mexico
and M2 seems to be behind them.
It's good to hear your voice,
gentlemen.
Uh, there's nothing in the file
on kidnapping.
But like I said,
I'm not the expert.
Okay, thanks, wordy.
I'll be there in five.
I'll line up some intel.
Get him out.
Jules?
Okay...
(Sighs heavily)
So, an oil and gas company
hires you
to train their guys
in case they're kidnapped.
'Cause it happened
down in Mexico.
And now, here you are,
handing out money in a park,
obstructing police.
Feels like the kidnappers
have moved north
and you've decided to do
the ransom drop-off yourself.
Tell me when I'm wrong.
We're not in Mexico anymore,
Martin.
Everybody plays
by the rules here.
Come on...
We're the only ones that
can save your client now.
All right, look.
This is express kidnapping.
In Latin America,
there's a gang called M2.
They grab a worker,
demand a small amount -
10, 15 grand -
the company pays.
Is it common?
Reported cases?
Uh, 1500, 2000 a year.
Unreported?
Five times that, easily.
Dealing with these gangs
is the cost of doing business.
What about the police?
They're usually in on it.
Gangs give 'em a cut.
Does it happen up here?
Yeah, it's a carbon copy
of what we've seen down South -
the same wording,
the same timing,
the disposable phone
they gave me to use.
Though the price tag
is a little higher.
Target's more important?
They took Bridgefield's CEO -
Colin Hamilton.
(Inhales and exhales shakily)
Jules:
So what's next?
Well, hopefully
they call back
and we get a another chance
to deliver the cash.
Maybe not,
because now they know
we're involved.
Or they might use Hamilton
as an example,
so that they're not crossed
in the future, right?
Yeah.
We gotta move,
boss.
Yeah, I hear ya.
All right, team,
listen up.
We've got
a confirmed kidnapping -
Colin Hamilton.
He's very much at risk.
We need a new plan.
Eddie, we need to push this up
the chain at guns and gangs,
figure out where M2
is holding this guy.
I'm downtown now, boss.
Wordy's on it.
(Knocks on glass)
Spike: Boss, two of
the bridgefield employees
who were kidnapped in Mexico,
they live in town.
Who are they?
Spike: Carl Miller
and Esmie Vargas.
Maybe the victims
are gonna have insight
on how they're guarded
and where they're kept.
Spike,
you got addresses?
Yeah, Vargas lives downtow.
Jules, I'm sending you
the address right now.
Jules: I'm on it.
Spike: Carl Miller.
Carl Miller lives
in Scarborough.
Good.
I'll call him from the truck.
Larson: We first caught
sight of these guys
three months ago.
Orders are to come down hard
before they get established.
We think they've grabbed
the CEO
of an oil and gas company
and are holding him
for ransom.
Well, kidnapping's certainly
part of their bag of tricks
down South.
You got any idea
where they might be holding him?
Well, they bought a flower
import warehouse,
which we think they're using
as a front.
Flowers and gangs...
It's a good cover.
We've had surveillance on 'em
for a month,
but nothing
we can move on yet.
Okay, maybe we can help
each other out here.
Or maybe you destroy
a month of work on a hunch.
Look, hehe clock is ticking
on our victim here, okay?
Wordy: I've read the file.
I could go with them,
keep 'em on a leash.
All right.
A short leash, Wordsworth.
This is on you.
You're not a biter,
are ya?
(Chuckles)
Parker: Mr. Miller, once again,
thank you for taking the time.
Yeah, happy to help.
Uh, you're saying that M2
may have moved up here?
Parker: Yeah, that's
what it looks like.
We were hoping you can tell us
what happened in Mexico.
Carl: Ah, well, it all
went down pretty quick.
I was on my way to work,
got jumped by two guys.
No vienence?
Carl: Well, I was held in a
basement for a couple of days.
Blindfold, gag,
that was pretty much it.
Parker:
Tell me, sir,
what do you think
would've happen
if the company hadn't paid?
They would have had no problem
killing me.
That was just business,
you know?
It's just business
I understand.
Woman: She says she wiil only
need another moment.
Okay, grate.
Are all these Esmie?
Yes, every one.
Yeah.
She ran a lot of marathons, huh?
I'm getting tired
just looking at these.
Woman:
Esmie never got tired.
The only one who could
keep up with her
was her brother.
But Esmie always wanted
to do more.
Well, I know the feeling.
It takes a lot of hard work
and dedication
to run a marathon.
Yes.
She is not like that
anymore.
Jules:
That's normal, Daniela.
Something like this
can cause depression.
It takes a little while
to get back in the world.
No. It is not only that.
Ah. Here she is.
Venga aqui, carina.
Esto eso que.
Esmie:
Hola. Hi.
Jules: I'm Jules Callaghan.
Esmie: Esmeralda Vargas.
Jules: Nice to meet you.
Esmie: Nice to meet you.
(Siren wails)
Ed: Okay, boss, I got a
lead from guns and gangs.
There's a warehouse
at the bottom of the DVP.
Parker: Thinking that's where
they're keeping thhostage?
Best place to start.
Okay, listen up.
New target.
Ed: It's at the corner of
munitions and commissioners.
Guns and gangs
are gonna meet us there.
What's going on with Terran?
He's coming with us
until this is over.
Parker: Well, they're certainly
making their presence known.
Martin:
Dogs marking trees.
Spike: Smart enough
to kidnap the guy
you're supposed to be
protecting.
How can I help?
Do you know this guy,
the CEO, Hamilton?
Martin:
Yeah, I trained him personally.
Breathing techniques
to stay calm,
positive visualization -
the works.
Parker: Any chance he's personalizing
himself to the kidnappers?
Martin: Instrumental
kidnappings like this,
where the only goal is money,
that's what we recommend.
You talk to them,
you try to find common ground.
Parker:
That's good.
Makes you seem more human.
Harder to hurt you that way.
If I did my job right,
he's got a chance.
(Long calming inhale)
Esmie:
People who've been kidnapped.
They all say the same thing:
That they never expected it
to happen to them.
And if anyone had
a blessed life,
it was me.
M2?
They took that all away.
They grabbed me
from the street
in the middle
of the morning,
and it was over in a second.
There was a gun to my back,
and a hand over my mouth...
And then nothing.
(Crying)
I couldn't walk
more than a few steps.
I was alone for, for
hours, or days.
I, I don't know.
(Lock clinks)
Esmie:
But there are worse things.
Man:
(Speaks in Spanish)
Hey! Look at me.
(Threatening grunts)
(Laughs)
Esmie:
And then...
My uh...
(Takes a deep breath)
My company refused to pay.
They were tired of being
held hostage by these gangs.
But M2 meant business.
(Screaming)
Man:
(Yelling in Spanish)
They wanted to send
the company proof
that they had me,
and that they were serious.
It took...
It took just a second
for them to get
what they wanted.
I'm so sorry.
You know, uh, diabetics,
our bodies don't handle
injuries very well;
bones get infected,
they begin to die,
especially in our feet,
and the treatment
is very expensive.
Yeah.
You've been
a really big help.
Can I ask you
one more question?
Of course.
Was this one
of your kidnappers?
Yes, he was with them
in Mexico.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
You don't forget
those faces.
He was with M2.
Okay, thank you.
Spike: That pass for a
uniform in guns and gangs?
Wordy: We don't need help
remembering each ether's names.
Spike, let's go.
Eyes.
How're you?
How are things?
Say it like it is,
buddy.
Parkinson's is good,
everything's fine.
Raf Rousseau.
Wordy: Hey.
Hear good things. Wordy.
Oh, I know who you are.
These guys won't
let me forget.
(Laughs)
Wordy, you're looking good,
man.
Yeah, you too, boss.
What do we know?
They got between 10
and 15 guys inside.
They're armed with everything
from sawed-offs to pistols.
This is Ronaldo Ortega.
Big name in Mexico -
they sent him north
to run the farm team.
Do you have anyone inside
we need to worry about?
Wordy: We're wondering about
this guy, Miguel Salazar.
Mexican undercovers
approached him
a couple of months ago.
It was looking promising...
then it fell apart.
Well,
once you're inside...
it's tough to get out.
That's right.
Do you have pictures
from the inside?
Wordy: No, we haven't
gotten inside yet.
Jules: Sarge, I got a
positive id from Esmie
on the guy at the
skate park -
he was with M2 in Mexico.
She said that these guys like
to keep their captives close
and they're not afraid to act
if they don't get
what they want.
Well, the M.O. matches
what I got from Miller.
Warehouse is looking
better and better.
All right, boss,
let's take these guys down.
Copy that.
Spike:
Best bet is a loading bay
where they bring in
all the pretty flowers.
Just saw a delivery;
when the truck goes through,
there's no one standing
guard on the door.
Ed: Okay, next truck
in, we follow.
These guys are looking
for an out-of-the-way place
to keep their victim.
'Kay,
building like this,
probably poured
concrete floor,
so no basement.
But a warehouse's gotta have
a machine room -
air conditioning,
heating.
You gotta keep
those flowers healthy.
Okay, guys,
that's our target.
Guns and gangs
cover our flanks,
keep a tight perimeter.
Spike, I need you back
down here.
Copy that.
We go in hard,
we go in fast.
Okay, do not fire
unless you're fired on.
Ed:
Guys,
we're gonna stack up
at the entrance.
As soon as we get in,
we split up.
Alpha team -
Spike, Jules and myself.
You three will be Bravo team.
Jules,
what's your 20?
Seconds away.
As soon as she gets here,
we're a go.
Parker: All right, let's
stay ahead of the news.
Wordy:
Ed? Ed, Ed, Ed.
This is our shot
at getting these guys.
If we go in there
without a warrant or intel...?
Wordy, we got credible proof
there's a life in danger.
But is his life in danger
in there?
You wanna go knock
and ask him?
What if we don't find
anything?
We keep looking.
And the investigation
falls apart,
these guys walk...
Larson made it clear.
This is my ass
if it goes south.
Wordy, Wordy,
you got a better idea here?
Look,
we're coming with you.
Of course.
You cuff 'em,
but leave the driving
to us.
You sure?
I'm positive.
Wordy,
if this thing goes bad,
it's on me,
all right?
Give you some distance
with Larson.
You're gonna be all right,
trust me.
Thanks.
Okay, guys...
Let's get 'em.
(Vehicle rumbles)
Spike: Once that truck goes through,
we got a really short window.
Ed:
Go, go, go, go.
(Door clanks shut)
(Locks squeal)
SRU: (Whispered commands) Right down, right down!
On the ground now!
Ed:
Down on the ground now!
Okay, guys,
we got a set of stairs.
Raf and Jules,
you take 'em.
Wordy? Give us a minute,
we'll give you the sign.
Ed: You good?
Parker: Yeah.
Let's go.
No money,
no second chances.
Your company,
they don't care enough
to play by the rules.
I guess I'm gonna
have to show them
that we mean business again.
Sam: (Hushed tone) Show me your hands.
Now. On your knees.
Ed:
Right there.
Sam: Drop your
weapon, drop it.
Now!
Ed:
Wordy.
Jules: It's just a
lunch room up there.
It's all clear.
Sam:
Hammer and Anvil?
Ed:
We'll meet you in the back.
(Panicked breaths)
What?
What do you have to say?
Hostage:
(Grunts)
J-just try again.
Try again.
I don't know
what went wrong.
All you have to do is call.
He'll get your money.
So they can have me
arrested?
No.
They don't care enough
about you to pay;
I don't care enough about you
to let you live.
Right there,
right there!
Hands in the air.
Put it down.
Jules: In the air.
On the ground.
Gang member: Okay, okay.
Jules: On your knees.
Jules: On your knees!
Get down!
Ed:
Someone on him!
I have a wife.
I got two kids.
I want this to be over
as much as you do.
Oh, it will be over
very soon.
Parker:
Go, go. Go!
SRU: Police! SRU! Right there!
Get down on the ground!
(Breathing shakily)
Please!
SRU: Drop your weapons! SRU!
On the ground now! Right there!
(Overlapping shouting)
Ed:
Where's Hamilton?
Hey! Ed!
Come here.
Where is he?
Where is he?!
No hablas English,
officer.
Boss?
Parker: It's over, Eddie.
Everyone's cuffed.
He's not here.
Hey, wordy?
What?
Raf: Got something you might
wanna check out here.
No way.
Raf: Yeah, it's a damn
good way to smuggle
and distribute product, man.
You can use that?
(Scoffs)
If even half of these ferns
are filled... uh huh.
Larson's going to love me.
Ed: Well, like I said, rising
star of guns and gangs.
What about Hamilton?
Where else would they keep him,
Wordy?
M2 has dozens
of smaller hang-outs.
Doesn't fit the profile.
There's a guy at the front desk
we need to talk to.
Let's do it.
Yeah.
That's the guy.
Ed: So this is the
potential informer.
Raf:
Should I talk to him?
Yeah,
see what you can get.
All right.
Can you take him
outta here?
You speak English?
I have nothing to say.
That's cool.
I get it.
It's the code,
right?
Talk to the police...
Es malo para usted.
(Mocking)
Malo para usted...
Yeah, it's bad for you.
If you help us,
we can help you.
Your going to help me
when they deport me
back to Mexico, huh?
Come on.
Yeah, you're right.
All right, well...
Can you at least...
(Pda beeps)
Identify a guy?
I don't know him.
Really?
No.
Got the same tat.
Where's Colin?
He wasn't in there.
These guys don't know
where he is?
They're not talking.
What the hell's
your new plan, Parker?
We'd a done this my way,
Hamilton would be at home
with his wife and kids
right now.
And next week another CEO
gets kidnapped.
There's no way we're letting M2
think that's how it works.
Sam:
So we took a closer look
and no one here
is a match
for our guy
at the skate park.
Raf: That's 'cause
he's not one of them.
Tattoo was on the wrong side
of the neck.
It's always on the left
'cause it's closest
to the heart.
There's no way
he gets that wrong
if he's the real deal.
Okay, so if the guy
that we're chasing isn't M2,
then Esmie Vargas
lied to us.
Nah, she was keeping us
off track.
The kidnapping changed
her life.
She can't get even
with the gang,
so maybe she takes a shot
at the company
that put her there.
Martin:
Knowing we'd pay.
Well,
she had to have help
because she didn't pick up
that ransom by herself.
She's got a brother.
Her mom said that
she was close to him.
Spike: I've got the
brother right here.
His name's Joaquin.
He's a match
for our money man.
It's on your PDAs.
Ed:
I got it.
Parker:
Okay, new game, team.
Everything we can
on Joaquin Vargas.
Parker: Jules...
Jules: I'll talk to Esmie.
Martin, come with me.
How is he?
Terrified.
Good.
Maybe that's enough.
What do you mean?
You wanted him to feel
what you felt.
Yeah.
Okay, he does.
But I told you, Ez,
the police are on this now.
The money...
it's just not gonna come.
Joaquin, you haven't
called Terran back?
(Sighs)
You said you would!
That's why I came
to watch over him!
It's just too dangerous.
If I go to a drop-off,
the police will be
everywhere, 'kay?
Right now, they still don't
know who we are.
We should let him go.
What? And walk away?
Are you kidding?
This man has to pay
for what did to me!
There's gotta be
another way.
I can't work, I can't think,
I can't sleep,
I can barely walk!
I need this money.
I can help.
Do you have
$60,000 dollars?
Because you know
that's what it's gonna cost
just the first operation.
Plus airfare, and physio.
I...
Joaquin, Joaquin,
Joaquin...
Do you remember our first day
at St. Michael's?
Mami dropped us off
outside the school.
I held your hand
because she told me to.
She said you were going
to be scared,
but you weren't.
I was.
Yeah, you didn't come back
after lunch.
And you found me hiding
in the field
behind the school.
Do you remember
what you said to me?
When you run away,
you lose.
And to win, you have
to face them head on.
You help me
get my life back, Joaquin.
Help me again.
Call them.
Hey, boss, just got off
the phone with Esmie's mom.
She's not there,
but she went to go-
Parker: Meet her brother?
Jules: Exactly.
Jules:
No location though.
We're looking into Joaquin now.
Good luck, man.
I know her.
Who?
Esmie Vargas.
Call them.
Ed: What do
you know about her?
Miguel: I can't help.
Raf: Yes, you can.
If she makes
the wrong move now
she won't live
through this.
And what happens to me?
Nobody needs to know about this,
Miguel.
Raf: I can see that you
care about her, man.
Now is your chance
to protect her.
I should have before.
(Door lock clicks,
Esmie gasps in fear)
Miguel: I was one
of her kidnappers.
Shhh, shhh, shhh,
shhh, shhh.
She was so scared.
(Scuffing of
approaching footsteps)
Gang member:
(Speaks in Spanish)
(Panting) What?
Gang member: Ayuda me.
Esmie: What? What? No!
Gang member: Ayuda me!
Esmie: No! Nooo!
Gang member:
(Speaks in Spanish)
Esmie:
(Shrieking)
(Cracking sound)
I did not help him,
but I did not stop.
It was not supposed to be
this way.
The first three times -
no problem.
We grabbed them,
the company pays.
Easy money.
But this time...
(Sighs)
No, no, no, no, no...
I tried to help
the only way I could think of.
(Shushes Esmie)
It's me.
I'm sorry.
This will be over soon,
I promise.
You will be free again.
I don't know.
Mira me.
From now on,
I will protect you.
I promise you.
(Speaking Spanish)
This is my sun,
keep it close.
You are not alone.
Be strong.
You will be free.
(Door creaks closed)
It was a wooden carving
like this.
Ed:
(Unclear comment)
It's made of ironwood.
It's very, very strong.
I thought it would help.
Ed:
It still might.
(Phone rings)
That's him.
Parker:
Hold on.
Sam, can you trace it?
I can get it started.
Sam, I'll be there
in two seconds.
Just don't answer yet.
I gotta pick up this call.
They're either gonna cut him or worse.
Okay, just keep him on the line, all right?
You know how to do that?
Yeah.
Terran.
This is your last chance
to get Hamilton back unharmed.
Martin:
Yeah, thank you.
Look, we obviously
wanna cooperate.
Joaquin: You have to
make the police understand.
If I see them... he dies.
I understand.
30 minutes.
Under the clock
at Union Station.
Last chance.
Martin:
Yeah, uh, okay.
Listen, how do I know
my guy's alive?
I need to know that he's alive
and, uh...
And that he's in one piece.
You'll have your proof.
Spike it's somewhere
in the waterfront.
I'm sending everybody a
map right now.
We're looking
at a six-block radius -
our kidnapper's somewhere
in there.
Let's go.
I'll make some calls en route.
Jules?
Engine's running.
Ed: We can't let this guy
get to union station.
There's too many bystanders.
We need to button
this up now.
Parker: These
aren't professionals.
They'll be quick to panic
and overreact.
Boss, Miguel Salizar,
he's one of the guys
who kidnapped her in Mexico.
The guy right there?
What he say?
Raf: Long story.
Ed: Fill you in on the way.
If it's Esmie Vargas,
this changes everything.
Not just about money
anymore.
Hamilton's training,
you know, to reach out,
uh, make a connection -
that's for instrumental
kidnapping,
not emotional.
Parker: If he does that to
Esmie, it could backfire.
It could escalate her.
How volatile is she?
Martin: Well, you've
read the literature.
Her reactions can run the gamut.
Uh, shock, numbness...
Yeah,
impaired decision-making.
Hostile attitude
toward the world.
I'm not talking
about generalities.
I'm talking about Esmie,
specifically.
You didn't talk to her
after she came back?
Martin: Like a
decompression interview?
No.
Not everybody needs it.
Oh, come on,
you don't believe that.
No. No, I don't.
But post-captivity programs
are expensive
and Hamilton was already
furious
at having to shell out
10-grand to these guys.
He didn't wanna do it again.
And he washed his hands.
Against my recommendation.
Well, whatever Esmie
is dealing with...
she's doing it all
on her own.
(Phone beeps)
(Phone rings)
Hamilton: September 15th.
Two o'clock.
Martin:
That's him.
Taken a minute ago.
Please, pay them
and end this.
Spike? Find them.
Gimme the phone.
I'll see what I can do,
boss.
Sam: Joaquin Vargas
works for the city's
marine maintenance department -
ferries, freighters.
Empty ship,
nice remote location.
Only if you're sure
there isn't anybody on it.
Sam: The Great Lakes Navigator
cargo ship out of Michigan,
it's been decommissioned
for a week.
Work doesn't start
'til Monday.
There's a couple of ferries
there that are the same,
so could be any one of them.
September 15th.
Spike: Those are 1200 amp
genies behind him.
There's two of them.
It's a definitely a ship;
you don't need that kind
of power for a ferry.
Well, cargo ship's
the target then.
Spike, find us a location.
Copy that.
Just in case.
(Tense breaths)
Hey.
You're doing the right thing,
letting me go.
It's best for everybody
if this just...
This is all over.
Over?
I know you don't
wanna hurt me.
It's...
It's just a business deal,
I get it.
Soon...
You'll have your money.
Be like this
never happened.
It won't be over soon.
Isn't that what you want?
It's never over.
I'm sorry, I don't...
I don't understand.
No, you're right,
you don't understand.
Ed:
Start at the engine room,
work our way up
through the ship.
Parker: Let's get him out safe.
Direct to threat.
You don't have any idea
what you did to me.
What I did?
What have I ever done to you?
Joaquin:
Esmie.
We gotta go.
The police are here.
No, no! If we leave now,
I have nothing.
We'll find a way.
But if we don't go now...
No, no!
This ends here.
Ez, don't!
Look at me!
Now do you understand?
Do you see?!
I'm sorry,
I don't know who you are.
(Stunned gasp)
(Whispered)
Esmie...
You don't know?
No.
Then I'll make sure
that you never forget.
My name is Esmeralda Vargas.
I worked for you
and you abandoned me.
Ms. Vargas, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Joaquin:
Ez, we gotta go now!
Ez, now!
Esmie: I was the fourth
employee taken...
The employee they mutilated
to make you pay.
I don't remember...
I don't believe you!
Esmie: They took a piece
of me and sent it to you!
Hamilton: I didn't
handle the negotiations;
I didn't know
what was going on.
Look at me.
Look at me!
You knew.
Yes.
In position.
Raf:
Esmie:
...For what?!
Hamilton: I couldn't keep paying them.
Every week...
Ed:
Boss, we gotta go in now.
Jules:
Hey, boss.
Why don't you
let me take this,
so I can build off of what
I've already established.
All right, take it.
Tell me why I shouldn't do
the same thing to you?!
Esmie has a knife
in play.
Esmie: You could afford
a few thousand dollars.
Sam: Jules, buy me
time to get down there.
Hamilton:
When does it stop?
Esmie: What gives you the
right to decide, huh?!
Esmie, don't do this.
No, let go!
Let me go!
This man has no idea!
He has to feel it.
He has to feel it!
Esmie.
(Gasps)
It's Jules.
Jules Callaghan from before.
Remember?
Listen, I want you
to put down your knife
so that we can talk.
No.
20 seconds away.
Boss, I have the shot.
Jules: I can't imagine
what you've been through,
but we can help you
deal with it.
You don't have
to hurt this man.
There's a better way.
Esmie, I want you
to put your knife down.
Esmie, you gotta
listen to her.
This man has to pay
for what he did to me.
Spike: Boss?
Esmie: What he took from me!
In position.
Jules:
This is not the answer.
Esmie, drop your knife!
Esmie: No!
Joaquin: Esmie!
No!
(Shrieking)
(Cries)
Ed: Turn around.
Turn around now.
Jules: It's okay.
It's okay.
No, it's not okay!
It's never gonna be okay.
When I sleep,
I'm back in that room
and when I'm awake,
every step I take
reminds me
of what I lost.
What this man took from me.
I had know idea
what they were gonna do to you.
(Cries)
My life...
my life...
how do I get that back?
All you can do
is use every step
to move forward.
Look at what you've overcome
and how strong you are.
A friend tried
to tell you that once.
Remember this?
Oh my God.
(Sobbing)
Something like this
scars you,
but you can't let it
define you.
Let me help.
(Sobbing)
♪ Walk away ♪
♪ things will not change ♪
♪ hide your heart ♪
♪ fake another day ♪
Esmita!
(Unclear) Mi corazon,
mi mija.
Esmie and Daniela:
(Speaking in Spanish)
Daniela:
Mi corazon, mi vida.
How many people did we have
kidnapped in Mexico?
Eighteen.
Hamilton: I want to
meet every one of them,
and try and make things right.
Martin: Yes, sir.
I'll set it up.
Parker:
Yeah, not for a while.
Right.
I can't be, uh,
in the middle of a park
waving a gun around.
It sets a bad example.
Bad example, yeah.
Parker?
Thanks for your help.
That was a good takedown.
Good talk.
What're we gonna do?
Parker:
That's good work today.
Then again,
what did I expect
from the law enforcement
professional of the year.
What happens now,
boss?
We go home,
come back to work again
tomorrow.
We're not gonna
let you down.
I have faith.
Sync by Alex1969
www.addic7ed.com