Helen.Helen.
Talk to me, Just talk to me.
Mr.Mitchell,i think she's
had Enough for one day.
For god sake,helen, It
doesn't have to be this way.
- You're the one Who made it this way.
- I am?
- None of this had to happen, It was you that...
- e one who lied In there.
I didn't lie.I'm trying to
do What's best for my kids.
- For your kids?
-  Mr.Mitchell, The case is closed.
- Custody is settled.There's nothing more To discuss.
- Get outta my way.
- Lawyer: Haven't you done Enough damage?
- Me?What about her?
Lawyer: It's over,all right?It's over.
I was just gonna say, I wish
we would've both Done better.
Lawyer: You've got some papers To sign.
Morning.Morning.
Nice scar.
Thanks.
Professional Or recreational?
A little of both.
Oh,yeah?
What happened?
There was an apartment
fire In high park.
Old building, So the thing
went up In about five minutes.
People were jumping
From their balconies.
It was a mess.
So i was bringing this kid Down from the third
floor, And that's when The stairs collapsed.
Barely made it out myself.
The kid make it?
- Nope.
- Jules: Sorry.
What was the recreational Part?
I got so pissed off That night, Threw
back a few shots And jumped on my bike.
Harley didn't make it, I did.
You know, There's good plastic surgeons,
If you ever wanna Get rid of that.
Winnie: Team one,suit up.Suit up.
Gun call, Business
district, 2002 bay street.
Nah,it's a good reminder
Not to be an idiot.
Yeah, Got four brothers for that.
Crowd: This is a mistake.Please.
You're not listening to me!
Lawyer: There's nothing
i can do, I swear to god!
I'm gonna give you...
One last chance!
Parker: I got it all, Thanks.
White male,late 30's.
Pulls a gun, Forces another
white male Into the building.
Did you get a location Inside?
Jules: They were seen in the
atrium, But beyond that, No idea.
- Ed: shots fired?
- Parker: not yet.
Uniforms cleared The first two
floors, But they don't have shields,
So,they backed off In
case the guy Went active.
All right, Let's see what spike's got.
Parker: Let's start talking
Before buddy takes it up A level.
Priority is on "who" And "where.
" Bonus points for "why"?
Parker: Okay,guys, We've got 12
floors, A dozen offices Per floor.
Sam?
That's a lot of window,
360 degree exposure.
Can't pick a sniper
perch Without more intel.
All right, Let's narrow it down.
Spike: Okay,i got the
building's Head of security.
His guys on these floors Have reported no
disturbances.He's awaiting instructions.
Ed: Okay,tell him to
lock down The elevators.
First priority is to immobilize
And contain the threat.
Spike: Copy that.
He came up this way.
He starts yelling At the other
guy Who was just coming out.
Then he pulls a gun And makes the other
guy Turn around And go back inside.
Parker: Do you know Either of the men?
Well,i seen the guy He was
pointing the gun at.The lawyer.
He's a lawyer?
I'm pretty sure he hangs out With
the other lawyers From the building.
What was he yelling?
Something about his kids.
Somebody took his kids.
Okay,and you said it seemed
Like they knew each other?
Parker: Do you know where His office is?
Well,it's not on The first floor; I
got my office there.I know everybody.
Above that?I really don't
have a clue,man.I'm sorry.
Any idea what kind Of weapon it
was?A handgun or a shotgun, Rifle...
A handgun.I just saw a flash Of silver?
I'm sorry, I don't know guns.
No-no,that's good, That helps.
Do you know the victim?
I don't know his name, But,yeah.
I think he has an
office In the building.
Any idea which office?
**********
Parker: Eddie.
Hostage may be a lawyer.
Ed: Okay,copy that,boss.
Spike, You got a tenant list?
Lawyers.We got plenty of lawyers.
Law firms from here to
here, And here and here.
Jules: Hey,guys,my witness says
They seemed to know each other.
This is personal.Something
about losing His kids.
So,he's stressed.He's
just suffered a loss.
How stressed Do you have to
be To come after a lawyer?
So,what, The guy grabs the lawyer,
Takes him To his own office?
Or he grabs the guy And takes
him To the most convenient office.
Ed: All right, Until we learn
more, We'll do it the hard way.
We start at the tenth
floor, We work our way down.
Stealth entry.
Locate and evacuate
Any citizens at risk.
Leah: Sru.Come with me.
Clearing two friendly's.
Wordy: Tenth floor: clear.
Ed: Find the subject And the hostage
Without alerting them To our presence.
Clear.
Sam: Ninth floor,
Suites 901 to 910,clear.
Got it.
Donald: Where are my kids?
Donald, You need to calm down.
Don't you patronize
me, You son of a bitch.
I will not lose them.I haven't come this far,
I haven't worked this hard Just to walk away.
Now start talking!
This guy sees this other guy, Like he's
waiting for him, Then he gets out of his car.
- He almost knocks me down.
- Which car?
That one,right there.
Seventh floor: clear.
Where are you,buddy?
Sam: Sixth floor:
Suite 601 to 610,clear.
Got it.
Subject's located.
Two males arguing.
Office of adam westfall, Room 612.
Door facing the atrium, Southwest.
Spike: Adam westfall.I'll track recent
cases And see what might have Triggered this.
Let's keep 'em contained.
Spike: Adam westfall.Specializes
in family law.Small office.
One employee: Amanda martin,paralegal.
Parker: She could be in the office
As well.She could be at risk.
Wordy,get eyes in.We may have a second
citizen In there.A possible hostage.
Maybe somebody injured Or hiding.
Wordy: Copy that.
Man: You know exactly What's going on.
Now that she's got 'em?
She takes 'em back to ireland, Her parents
help her out And i never see them again.
Well,that is not Going to happen!
The subject's telling him Now that she's got the
kids, She's taking them back To ireland to her parents;
He'll never see them again.
Spike: Checked with the uniforms, Amanda
martin's car Is in her space in the garage.
- A couple people Saw her at work today.
- Parker: Chances are she's inside.
She's a wild card.I
don't like wild cards.
Maybe we get lucky And
she's outside the building.
Boss,there's no way We can
go in 'Till we've located her.
Hey,spike, The subject's car is
registered To a donald mitchell.
Spike: Donald mitchell...Cross-ref
with adam westfall And...
Oh,i get to say,bingo?
Parker: Please,don't say bingo.
Spike: Westfall was in court This morning
Representing a helen mitchell In a custody case.
He loses custody, Blames her lawyer.
Okay,see what you can
find out About the case.
Get an address on the
wife And send it to jules.
- Jules?
- On my way.
Snake cam's good to go.Let's
figure out Where to put it.
Spike,we need the schematic
For westfall's office?
Coming at you.
Sam: Two rooms.
Wordy: My guess, She's in the closet.
If she's hiding, Or even in there.
Parker: Well,we got uniforms
Checking the crowd for her.
You know, Nobody's found her yet.
Can we get a cam Into that closet?
Wordy: If i go in through The
outside wall.It's concrete.
- Might take a while.
- Fast is good.
Get eyes into the main office,
Then we'll focus on the closet.
- Copy that.
- Okay,quick and quiet.
Guys,as far as i can tell,
Mitchell's a solid citizen.
No arrests, Not even a speeding ticket.
Parker: What about the custody case?
Spike: Well,according to the clerk In
family law, It was a really nasty one.
- And donald lost the kids.
- Spike: No,he won.
He got full custody.
Say that again?
He got custody?
His wife's stealing the kids.
So this isn't about revenge On a lawyer.
This is about A parental abduction.
flashpoint
Season 03 Episode 04
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com/=-
Proudly Presents
YTET-ÅÝÅÝ·É ±´±´
Spike: 2:14 pm,armed hostage taking,
Motivated by possible Parental abduction.
So mitchell gets full Custody of the kids, Then
goes after The wife's lawyer?I don't get it.
Well,his means are extreme,
But his purpose is rational.
I think it's time to go
verbal.You got his cell number?
Call her.Call helen.
Adam: No,i'm not
leading her Into a trap.
Donald: Do it!Make the call!
Donald: Speed dial?
- Yeah, I knew you two were close.
- She's a client.
Donald: I know what she's like.
- Went straight to voicemail.
- Have her call you.
Yeah.
Parker: Donald mitchell?
My name's sergeant Gregory parker, I'm
with the police Strategic response unit.
Police,right.How are you?
Parker: I'm doing
okay.How are you doin'?
Donald: I'm fine,just fine.
Just taking care Of something,
Since you couldn't Help me out.
It's a little time-sensitive,
So maybe i can Get back to you.
Yeah,it sounds like You're
under A little pressure here.
Donald: Yeah.
My wife stole my kids!
I called the school To tell 'em I'm
gonna pick them up early, They were gone.
They weren't at her place.
They were just gone!
Okay, Well,maybe there's a reason?
She stole my kids!
And this son of a bitch Helped her out.
He tells me where they
are And this is over.
Let me help you, Donald.
Donald: I already called the police And they
blew me off.The guy says, "yeah,you know,whatever.
Why don't you just come
down And fill in some forms?
" Okay,donald,i'm sorry That they didn't
listen to you, But i can assure you...
She's on her way To the border as
we speak, She is taking them away...
Donald, I'm here to help you!
Donald: I need an answer
now, And i am handling this!
Parker: Let's get a photo Of helen mitchell,
Put it out there, See if we can't track her down.
Okay,let's find out Where
his kids go to school.
If his story checks out, We need photos
of them For an immediate amber alert.
Let's put a call out To the border.
Spike: Sending out a photo
Of helen mitchell,now.
Parker: Jules,you get that?
Yeah,he think his wife
Abducted their kids.Copy that.
Like they are gonna let him
Have the kids back after this.
Custody fights, They get pretty primal.
Right now He's all tunnel vision and...
Short-term thinking.
Yeah,well, There's "primal,"
Then there's "just plain crazy.
" I do crazy-ass stuff To save other
people's kids.Makes sense to me.
Parker: What would you do?
- What do you mean?
- Parker: You and sophie plit up?
This wouldn't hpen.
Parker: Just say you and sophie Split
up, She wanted clark, What uld you do?
- Just like i said.
- Wha
Wouldt happen.
Soon as we gt eyes, Let's go in.
Parker: Unless i get him Talking again.
Jules: Have you seen
her Or her kids today?
Nonot today.What's going on?
Well,yor neighbour's Ex-husband
Involved in An armed incident downtown.
- What?
- We're doing everything We can To resolve this peacelly,
But we need Theigger
picture.Can you help us?
How well do you know The mitchells?
Uh,i've kwn them For about six years.
They used to be really Great together, But the
lt few years Have bn pretty streed Between them.
Helen.
Seren Serena: Then last
yr They got divorced.
- You know,sameld.
- Workin' like a dog?
- So,are they ready?
- Soon.
- We said 4:30.
- Yea we did.They'll be ready soon.
We had an understanding.The
movie startsn 20 minutes.
Donald,no.Youan't just walk
right in Like you still livhere.
Donald: Liam!Alice!
Helen: They're not here.
- What?
- You heard me.
- Donald: Where are they?
- They're at the store, They'll be bacin 5 minutes.
You can't keep doi this.You bring them
late, We missed two visits This month.
I can't even say good
night To them on the phone.
- Hey were already leep.
- Oro you say.
- You think i'm lying?
- No,i think i'm entitd To say good night to my kids Three days week!
I get to y good night To my kids
on the phone The days a week!
- Don't yell at me!
- Lm: Daddy!
Go e your daddy.
Hey,buddy.
Oh,come here.
Hey,don, How're you doing?
- Alice: Daddy! - Dond: Allie-allie-allie!Popcorn
onachos,huh?Popcorof nachos?
- Let's go,buddy.
- Liam: bye,mom.
Helen: have fun.
Serena: I mean,the
real problem Was jason.
Who's jason?
Uh,jason wallace, Her boyfriend.
I don't know if i should...
Are you her friend?
Wellnald is threatening
Her lawyer with a gun.
I need the whole sto Right now.
Well,it was hard for
helen Coming to live here.
Away her old life, Er
parents, Her friends.
How was she with donald?
They us to be head Over heels.
I mea donald proposed A month after
they met, That's how sure theywere.
T she was so yong, You know?
And she gavep her studies,
Her country,everything.
Was she isolated?Did he work a lot?
Oh,yeah,donald Was always at work, Talking
about work, Breakingromises for work.
It was hard.
She sd,by the end, It
was like living alone.
And then along comes
jason Who apeciates her.
Ah,here she comes.Helen?
Jules: Helen mitell?
I'm jules callagh With the sru.
- Helen: Whas wrong?
- We're trying to locate Your children.
Locate them?
Theye at school.
The school says That you have them.
I don't have them.
What are you saying?
What's happened to my kids?
Helen: Iold you they're not here!
Jules: We just need to be sure.
Please, You've gotta find the.
Sarge, Found helen mitchell.She says she has no
idea Where he children are.They're not in the house.
All right, Get to the school.Let's
find out Exactly what happened.
Ok.
Donald and adam: Onald: 'M
gonna give you One laschance!
Got our first pair of eyes.
Working on the closet now, Boss.
E Copy that.
Okay,if the paralegal's
the, She's hiding.
Donald: Don't think i
won't ht you.I will...
Wordy,when can we see To that closet?
- Uh,thr,four minutes.
- Ed: Excellent.
Two minutes,good.
Wordy: Yeah,yeah,fast is good.The
thing is A silent rill is kinda slow.
Lorraine: I don'tnderstand.Mrs.Tchell called.You
said a frnd would be Picking up the children.
That's impossible.I never called.
I'm so sorry.Nothing li
Has ev happened before.
Helen: What's wrong with you?
You can't jt hand over
My children to anybody?
I men Don't you have rules?
Do you have surveillance tapes?
Yes,hallways and entrances.
- Great.Ieed to see those Right away.
- Of course.
Second eyes in,bos
All rig, There she is.
Parker: Guess we didn't get lucky.
Not today.
Can we get her out
Without alerng donald?
Boss,there's no cover In the room,
We'd be seen.I don't know howe'd react.
We go in hd.
Okay.
Here's the plan: Sam,window entry.
Le,wordy, Through the door with
me.Wordy,you're on ram.Ah,you're on dd's.
I can do the window,ed.
- What's that?
- Leah: I've got a lot of experience On that.
You know, Burning buildings and all.
Excuse me?
Right,copy that.I'mn dd's.
Good.
Questions?
I'm on my way up.Get into position.
Guess that was a mistake.
When you're the democratically Elected team
leader, You get to make Autocraticecisions.
- That one yours?Man
- No,his.
Don't worry, You'll get your chance.
Jules: There.
Do you recognize him?
Oh my god, It's jason.
Jason wallce, Your boyfriend?
Why would he take your
kids Thout your permission?
I don't know.
Really,helen?
We broke up Couple days ago.He...
He took it pretty bad.
Kinda lost it.He has anger issues.
- Would he be angry enough Thurt your kids?
- I don't know.
He said i'd regret it.
Oh my god...You gotta find them.
We will.Do you have any
recent Pictures of him?
Yes,i do.
Here you go.
These are great.We're gonna get
these Put out an amber alert.
I'm gonna ve a police officer
Pick you And take you,okay?
No,i'm fine.Don't need a ride.
Len,we need to keep In touch with you.
All right,i want you To wait here,okay?
They're gonna be here In a few minutes.
Oy.
We'na find the
Sarge,we got jason wallace
On tape picking u the kids.
Ske: So,jason wallacejarfar We got
a couple of assaults On his record.
He got busted a couple
of times For dealing ot.
And i got an address.
Let's dispatch uniforms To contain.
On my way.
Parker: Pick up sam enroute,jules.
It's one guy,sarge.I
can handle him myself.
He's a potentially vient man Who's
taken His ex-girlfriend's kids.
Sam's on entry, He'll be ne By the
time you get here To pick him up.
Copy tt.
Winnie, I'm sendi you pictures And
descriptions of alice And liam mitchell,
Ty were last seen With jon wallace,
Ou already got His description.
Full amber alert To all agencies.We
gotta find these kids fast.
Wine: Co that.
Adam: Or godsake,donald, Use your head.
Why the hell would i
help len Take your kids?
Because you spent The whole trial
Trying to take them.The two of you.
- I was doing myob.
- What,byabricating?Lying?
- There was no lying!
- I workedyself ragged So she could have Hat she wanted.
All she wanted was a man Ho had a
little space In his life for her.
Donald: Yeah,i knew that!I had just
arraed To delegate half my workload.
I was cominhome early With champagne,
With takout to surprise her, To celebrate.
So she found someone.You
made h pay, Right?
- And here she is... - You'll say Whatever it takes...
- Ith this guy!To make her out to An unfit mother!
- Team,they're escalating.Stand by.
- Donald: And what aut you,huh?
Y made it sound like I hurt the kids.
I never touched them.
- Nobo said you did
- No,you implied.
You,you suggested.
Parker sam,how lg Until a position?
***
Boss,hird party.
She's looking pretty nervs.
She's just fighting For a chance toave
a life, To make a chce of her own.
And there you are invoking "rental
alienation," "malicious mom syndrome.
" Donald: Well,what do you callt?
Spike: Don'tike where This is headed.
Die,woman in the
closet's Abouto make a m
Copy that, Standing by.
agreed To the schedule!
Parker: Update,m.
Sam: Just setting tcharge,boss.
Ed: Hding for you,sam.
- She didn't rlize...
- Forget it,okay?
E only thing that matters now
Are my kids.Where are they?
Stop!Hey,stop!Stopyou!
- Damn it,stay there!
- Tell me where my kids are.
- He didn't do anything.
- Donald: Where are they!
- Helen love those kids.
- I love them,too.
More than you coulever know.
Sam: Five seconds.
Ready for entry On my go.
Donald: Do not make me hurt you.
Amanda: Sp!
Parker: Fast is good.
Ed: Three,two,one...
- Go!Go-go-go-go!Police!Right
ere!Right there! - Sru: Hands in e air!
Hands in the air!Police!
Leah: Get your hands down,now!
Donal
No-no-no-no-no-no.
Let's take a walk.
Wordy: You good?
I'll get you down To the paramed.
Liste Would you just listen?
You gotta stop her!You gotta do somethi.
Sir,the man you had At gunpoint...
He's hidingy wife And kids.
If they get out Of the
couny,I'll never see them Again.
Now why do u think He's involved?
Bause the bastard Everything that
he could To take them from me.
He's a lawyer,That is his job.
It's more than that.
It is y more than that.
It's something i heard
him Say at the pre-trial.
Please,donald.
N't take liam and alice Away om me.
They're all i've got.
No,you've got someone else.
Why is it alwas about him?
Because i loved you,Helen.
We could've All stayed
together,But you made your choice.
Fine.I'll leave m,today.
Anything,please.
Just stop this,okay?
I can't trust you anymore.
You're willing to Break uwith jason,
Maybe we can still work Something out?
Anything.
I'll do anything.
I'even get back together With donald.
Amanda: Really?
I'd rather be bied
alive,But to keep my kids...
Anything.
Don't worry.
Whatever takes,We won't leyou Lose them.
Hatever it takes,All right?
Thk you.
I was just about to say
Maybe we can wo this out,
Then i heard hesay that.
What'd i even do t Her ate me so much?
I didt even think about it 'Til later...
"whatever it takes," She
wouldn't lose the kids.
And that's what he did,Anything it took.
He helped her take them.
He knows wherehey're going Right now.
Okay,donald,We talked your wife
And there's no indication That
she's got the children With her.
Then who picked them up From school?
-Jason wallac
-Jason?
Took them on his own?
We don't have The answer to that.
Oh my god.
You gotta get 'em back!
You gotta get 'em back.
Boss,we have situation.
Uforms report jasowallace
Wasn't at home.
Neighbours saw him leave.
What abouthe kids?
Uncod,But,uh,we found juice boxes.
Could be his.
Spotty leopard Jungle nectar?
Well,they werehere.
Where are they now?
We just did A credit card check.
He checked into the royal
york About tn minutes ago.
Oy,good work.Keep me posted.
Did you promise Hen mitchell
That she woul Get her ildren back
No matter what it takes?
I tell my clients What they need
to hear To build their confidence.
But i never make Misleading promes.
And you dn't have Any backup plan?
Like facilitating an abduction
Along with her boyfriend?
And break the law,Risky career?
There's plenty of times I'd like to;
I got kids of my own.
How about you,amanda?You got kids?
Yeah.
You're not sure?
yes,I have tree children.
Police! Sru!
Police,don't move!
Sam: Hands in the air! Has in the air!
Stop
Where are they?
Where are helen's kids?
Ion't know!I swear,i don't know!
You're lying.
I'm tling you,I ven't
seen thoskids In weeks.
Son,the school Has video surveillance.
You were caught on tape 2
hours ago with the children.
I wanna speak to a lawyer.
No,you wanna speak to us.
Okay,this is kidnapping
And you have a record.
If we don't find those kids,Things
won't look too good F you.
I've got nothing to say.
Sarge We've got jason wallace.
No kids at t hotel And
this guy is not talking.
Eep trying.
Rry about that.
So two girls,boy.
They live with you?
They live With their father?
Boss,i just got off the phone
With the uniform We sent to the
kids' school Ttake helen home?
Yeah,spike.
Spike She was gone when he got
there,And she's not at her house Either.
So,hen isn't at the school,She
isn't at home,This is interesting.
Where would she go next?
She's got an older sister,Colleen.
I got her addres Sier,colleen.
Leah?
I wu to go to the house,Ee
what the sister knows.
Copy at.
Amanda?
Nything we should know here?
So,why're you being so
loyal To an ex-girlfriend?
What do you mean?
Well,she id that you
guys Broke up two days ago
No,that's not true.
Apparently,Shwas willing
to lee you If imeant
she could Hang on to the kids.
Where'd you get that?
According to donald.
Eah,he wishes.
Yeah,well,when helen
saw The surveilnce tapes,
He freaked And she made y out
to be A dangerous angry guy
Who would take it out On those kids.
She said Whatshe had to say.
Why would she lie?
Because she loves those kids.
She needed time.
How long you been working
Stody cases,amanda?
A long time.18 years.
Must feel good when you win.
What feels good Is
working out a settlement.
Letting both parents See the kids.
Mr.Westfall always Tries to do that.
But hat didn't happen This time.
Donald was so...
Bitter and angry,He just
wouldn't list To reason.
How even-keeled was hen?
She adored those kids.
Every mother loves her
kids,But thewere everything.
She gave up everything For them.
She ised them Practically alone.
Every minute of hs Was theirs.
It just wasn't fair.
It hurts to lose Doesn't it?
I have a question To ask you.
As you know,
Things will go A lot better
for you If you tell the truth.
She deserves better Than to be
a housekeeper For some guy who...
Comes home late Every
night,Expecting dinner The table.
He wouldn't even talk to her.
Okay,let's stick to the poi,Jason,We're
not here Because you had affair.
She loves to go dancing,She deserves ...
Just be able to kick back
And enjoy something for once.
Okay,we get it,You love her.
But do you ally want
to go To jail for this?
Because at's what Will happen
If we do not find Hose children.
I droppedhem off With her sister.
Helen didn't want the kids At
hehouse Icase donald came there.
Sarge,confirming That the children
We dropped off At the sister's.
Thanks,jules.
You knew things Weren't
gonna go her way,
So you helped her Ith plan b.
Amanda...
I helped her forge A
letter of parentaconsent.
You need one to cross The border.
I used signatures From donald.
She deserved th.
She deserved them.
I didn't say she didn't.
Colleen lester?
I'm leah kerns,sru.
I'm loong for your sister Helen.
Is something wrong?
Her children are missing.
But that's impossible.
They were with me.She juspicked 'em up.
Y musta just missed her.
Leah Helen and the kids
justeft,They can't be far.
I see her And she's got the ks.
She's travelling north To spadina.
Alpha 2 julia leema 271.
I'm in pursuit.
Okay,we're on our way.
-Keep a disnce,Not provo her.
-let's move.
Don talk me with you.
I want to make sure Ty're all right.
It's a little la in the
game For that,donald.
Oh,boss,come on,You're
not gonna take him?
Strsful situation For the kids.
It might be gooto have
The other parent ere.
Come on,if it was
youroy,What would you want?
You taing about my boy Or your boy?
Follow us.
Boss,the car helen's driving
Is registered to jason wallace.
Copy.
You didn't tell us That
y lent helen you car.
You didn't ask.
Is there anything else
You didn't tell us?
If you find helen Don't hurt her,pase.
Why woulwe hurt her?
There's a gun in e car.
Awsome
Mom,are you gonna Answer the phone?
It's just a wrong number.
Can we play the beetle game,Mommy?
Okay,i'm the only beet In the world
Tt can flip from its back
To its feet in one move
-The click beetle!
Yay!
Okay,i'm t one with The
big antlers like a moose.
Thetag beetle.
mommyi spilled.
Hold on...
It'okay.
I'm the one hat eats poop.
Dung beetle!
Yay!
Still following.
Looks like she's heading Out of town.
We're right behind you.
Mom,the phone keps ringing.
She's still not picking up.
All right,We gta make a move.
What're you thinking?
There kids on board,We
gotta take it easy.
We can't use road
spikes,We can't ram em.
We gotta do A rolling roadblock.
Eddie,she's got a wea In the car
She's driving under stress,She's latile.
We start crowding her...
She's not talking,Boss.
It's time to make a mo.
Spike!Spike!
The make of car,Any chance she's got
One of those onard Emergency
communications Systems?
Checking,checng.
Do i get to say bingo?
Only ift's a "yes.
" Bingo.
Awesome.
Let's makehis happen.
What about the one th
can fly,Awl and swim?
Mommy,Where are we going?
Remember how you said You'd
really,really love To see iland?
yay!
Yeah,so,we're gonna drive
A littleit and then...
We're gonna get o A brplane.
Helen mitchell?
Hi,my name's gregory parker.
I w trying to reach you On your cell.
Can you hear me All ght?
Hi,liam.Hi,alice.
You guysoing okay?
We're fine.
They're fine.
It's kindfunny,huh?
A voice coming out of the car.
It's actually A security feature In case
people need help,And i'm a policeman.
We're going to irela!
You are?
It's soeautiful there,It's
so beautiful there.
Helen,do you think You can
pull ov So we can talk a little?
No.
Leave ualone.
Helen.
Helen,i'm justthinking Of
everybody's safety here.
-You think you can slow it down?
-Mom,i'm scared.
All right,eddie,Let's go
fr The rolling roadblock.
Jules,ve in front; Leah,get
bide her; I'll take the rear.
Copy that.
Uniforms are now diverting Traffic.
Mommy?
It's okay.
Liam: But there's police cars.
Everything's gonna be All right.
Helen,it's greg again.
I just want you to know What we're doin
So you guys aren't worri,All right?
Everything's okay.
These cars are just gonna
Help you slow do safely.
Nobody's in trouble,All right?
Jules,I'm closing on 15 feet.
Start decelerating.
It's okay.
L's tighten it up.
Decelerate.
hi,helen.
Stay away from us.
I'm greg.Hi.
Hi,liam.
Hi,alice.
How are you gs?
I'm the man who was talking
To youmom in the car earlier.
Boss,you need a shield.
Mommy,what are doing?
Why do you have a gun?
How're you guys doing?
I'm scar mommy.
Boss,wa for the shield.
She thinks the system's Against her,ed.
She nes to see some trust,And
i know you got My back.
Greg.
I'm good,eddie.I'm good.
That gun comes up...
Have to take the shot.
Helen.
Look at me,helen.
Look at me.
I'm gonna put this down,Okay?
So we can talk.
Boss,you don't wanna do that.
Tnk you do the same for me?Please?
No.
What does she think She's gonna do?
She's not thinking,Hat's the problem.
How do you reach a person
Who's ge primal mother-bear?
Through her cu.
It's okay.
You can...
Just...Just try to
keep it down,How's that?
Hey,guys.
I konw your mom
loves you more than anything
You know how i know that?
Because of everythg She's done today.
She's a sma lady.
I'll bet you she's taut you
To never talk to strangers.
You're not a
stranger,You're a policeman.
Yeah,that's right,I am.
Just let us go.Let us through.
I could do that,iuess.
I'm not really sure Where
things go Aer that though,So...
You probablywon't get
Through the border.
Even with those documents
That amanda me for you.
The airport then.
Your mom's ld you A lot about ireland,h?
I've been theronce.
You know what they y About ireland?
It's true,It's really,really green.
And your mom wants To
ta you there Because
she wants u guys To be
able to stay together.
Right?
They need me!
I ow.
But let's y you guys
Got on that plane today.
You'll never be able To come back.
Younow that,right?
Mom,wh about daddy?
It's not right.
He lied to them.
He toldhem i was
malicious,Unfit,Irresponsible!
You' sure it wasn't just
His lawyer doing his jo
I meanhe way he talks About you?
I'not convinced He believed it himself.
Helen: but then why...
'cause he loves you.
And when he lost you,He
got angry And he...
Felt heless.
And no o wants To feel that way,No one
wan to have their kids Tan away from them.
People go to extremes For
somethi they love,Right,helen?
Yeah.
Eddie,Let's get the dad out.
Let 'em see him...
I hear you.
It's okay,kids.
It's all right,Nones gonna hurt you.
No ones gonna hurt your mom.
T's gonna be okay.
I promise,It's all gonna be okay.
Liam and alice: Daddy!Daddy!
No,wait!
Helen,listen to me.
You haven't hurt anyon You haven't
threatened anyone,And that's good.
It means you will be With your
kids again Sooner rather than later.
But if you raise that gun
Right now,Everything changes.
So,please,Please just put the gun down.
Don't you dare.
Don't ma me go there.
Donald?
What hpened?
What've you done?
I thought i was long The kids...
Losing you.
What have we done?
Thank y,helen.
Parker: It's okay.
Ay,that's great.Thank you.
They'll be able to stay
With r sister,colleen.
When kids are involved,It's
hard to see straight.
It affects your judgme.
Yeah.
Yeah,i hope like hell
They get a second chance.
I'm talking about you Here,greg.
What're you saying?
You were thinking about
Your kid out there?
My oices were appropriate.
Your choices Were dangers.
You know what,eddie?
All the calls Have an element of risk.
You want me To watch your back?
Boss.this is me watch you back
I'm just saying.
-=
http://bbs.sfileydy.com/=- Proudly Presents
http://bbs.sfileydy.com/=- YTET-ÅÝÅÝ·É ±´±´
flashpoint
Season 03 Episode 04