Julianna Callaghan,
I vow to be true always,
to give you all of myself -
no secrets...
Until death parts us,
and even after...
'Cause I've been yours
since the first day I saw you
and made a fool of myself.
'Cause I knew right away,
I knew that it was you
or no one...
Even though
you didn't know it yet,
and I had to be patient.
I was right.
Just saying.
Samuel Braddock,
I vow to always be yours.
I tried to...
think of words,
but there's so many...
there's so many words.
So, I vow, to you, this...
Yeah!
So um... since you guys
are all here,
we would have told you earlier,
but we didn't want
to jinx anything.
We're three months along;
we're having a baby.
- Congratulations. Good for you.
- Thank you.
- Right on!
- Come here, you!
911, what is your emergency?
I'm wearing a peach dress,
so if you wear a peach rose,
it means... gratitude.
Oh, right, 'cause
he should be grateful
that you asked him to prom.
What colour's your boutonnier?
Uh, whatever colour
means "no curfew
'cause it's prom."
- Seriously?
- Yeah,
my parents have late-night
plans of their own.
They're going
to some hotel downtown.
Plus they trust me.
It's weird.
Plus you're not gonna
tell them.
Scary.
Just like your dad.
You sure you wanna date
a walking polygraph?
Yeah, I'm sure.
All right. You
guys need a ride?
Nah.
We're gonna be okay, man.
All right. See you later.
Later.
So you've met
my infamous brothers.
Good to meet you.
You talked the boss
outta the brown suit.
Well, Wordy, somebody had to.
Hey, I heard that.
I mean, really,
it's a fabulous dress.
I like it.
- Really?
- Yes, Donna.
Such a gentleman,
and always a kind word;
That's why I love you.
Debrief went long;
some people have to work hard.
How's team three?
I'm kicking 'em into shape.
I told you she couldn't
stay away from the job.
How are you, Wordy?
I'm good.
Girls are good.
I miss the days though.
Days miss you right back.
You going to the reception
tonight?
Absolutely.
You know what? Team one's got
a shift to get through first
because some of us
work even harder.
Not a word.
Not a word!
You're doing
great, hon, stay with me, okay?
I'm gonna need you
to breathe out for me...
Nice.
Four minutes
between contractions,
which is awesome.
I'm sending all this
to the paramedics
as soon as they get there...
Which will be in two minutes,
okay?
You got a name picked out
for the little man yet?
So slow...
I think one of the servers
needs rebooting.
Can you do it?
I'm wrapping up
the miracle of life over here.
Yes.
You got a bag
packed for the hospital?
Now don't worry.
I'm gonna stay right here
with you...
Aw...
I know.
Man, getting
married and going to work,
that is dedication.
Well, it's the only day
Sam's dad could be here.
You know, reception's
at the party boat tonight.
I wish I could've been there.
Me too.
Spike, you were there.
No, I mean I wish
you could've been there
too, too.
"Too, too?"
"Too, too," as in too, also.
Gotcha.
SRU.
Hey, Winnie,
this is Nina from 911.
Hey, Nina.
What's going on?
We've got something
in our server room
that doesn't look like it
should be there.
911's got a problem.
Nina, I've got team one here.
It's some kind
of a device in a box,
in our server room.
It's got exposed wires
and a blinking light.
Was it left in plain sight?
No. No, it was concealed
in one of our server cabinets.
We only found it
when we went to do a reboot.
Get any non-essential
staff out of there,
we're on our way.
Winnie, call Stainton,
get him to see if there's
a spike in terrorist chatter.
You got it.
Spike?
Just... you know.
I'm always careful.
Hitting 911?
The nerve centre for
the city's emergency services.
We can't shut the place down
without leaving the city
stranded.
Babycakes is ready to roll.
Ma'am, they are
on their way right now,
so I'm gonna need you
to calm down for me, okay?
We're down to three
operators and three dispatch.
The evac'd staff is out front.
'Kay, Leah, let's check
out the rest of the building.
I'm gonna talk to staff,
start profiling.
We're gonna
need CCTV footage.
- Already pulled it.
- Great.
You're husband is pinned by the
steering wheel,is that correct?
Howie? Howie, give
Ethan his blankie back, please.
Howie? I need you to listen,
okay?
That belongs to Ethan, honey.
Fine!
Thank you, Howie, good choice.
Let's go! Back at school!
Here we come!
I see the box.
Sending out electronic
counter-measures
against remote detonation.
Ha! See, Ethan?
I told you we'd find it.
Run!
There you are!
911, what is your emergency?
Simcoe and Wellington?
How many are injured?
How many do you see?
What's going on?
911, what is your emergency?
It's a federal building,
Health and Welfare.
Team, we're looking
at another bomb
that just went off downtown.
Mass casualties
in a busy building...
No way this was accidental.
We are looking at terror.
Flashpoint 05x12
Keep The Peace
Original Air Date December 6, 2012
==sync, correction by dcdah==
www.addic7ed.com
It is difficult
to get a clear picture,
but it appears that
the explosion took place...
Spike, talk to me.
I'm working it, but
this is gonna take time.
Guys, go.
I got this.
No, Spike, listen...
Ed, go!
Okay, copy!
Guys, Simcoe and Wellington.
Sam, you're with me.
Let's move!
We're gonna need
all emergency personnel
on standby.
Crowd control,
casualty transport.
Okay, thank you.
Nina, all of you have
to get outside
with the rest of your staff.
We can split some of
the load with Durham Region,
but then they'll be overloaded.
We need to stay
and keep answering calls.
Negative. This bomb could
still go off.
The bomb could still go off,
but people definitely need
our help.
It's not just our lives
on the line.
Okay.
Winnie, I'm not liking the way
this day is going.
I need all SRU teams reupped
right now.
You got it.
The X-ray is up.
I see batteries, I see wires,
I see a timer...
And I got anti-handling
measures.
This is gonna
complicate things.
Please, ma'am,
stay where you...
Everything's fine, dad.
Just making sure you guys
got all checked in okay.
We're gonna see you
at the hotel
after work, all right?
Bye, dad.
You'd do anything to just...
Wrap 'em up
and keep 'em safe.
Your parents were in Haiti
during the earthquake, right?
All you can do is do your best.
Yup.
No, Sophie, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Look, I'm sure Clark's
okay, too.
He's probably
just somewhere noisy,
where he can't hear his phone,
all right?
I need you to call me
as soon as you hear from him,
okay?
I love you.
She heard about the bomb?
Yeah.
Guess your wife knows
where you are.
"Wife."
Feels funny, huh?
It feels good.
No chemical
detection, no nerve agents,
no blood agents, no radiation.
I'm going in manual.
24 minutes.
Okay.
Can you sever the power source?
Yeah, I think so,
but it's underneath.
I can't reach it
without triggering
the anti-handling device
embedded in the C4.
I'm gonna have to disable it
by hand.
It's a Mercury tilt switch.
That drop slides over
by a hair,
and touches those two wires,
and I lose my 24 minutes.
22 minutes.
How do you disable
a Mercury tilt switch?
Acetone.
And where are we gonna
get that?
Anybody have
any nail Polish remover?
Seriously!
Anybody?!
Thanks!
Ed, that was Stainton.
There's been no chatter-spike
on the terrorist channels.
Okay. Thanks, Winnie.
So if it is
a coordinated strike,
it's a group
that's not on our radar.
Or it's a lone wolf
with no group to chatter with.
All right, assuming
it's the same individual,
what's his next step?
He hit the heart of the city's
defense system
and a symbol of government.
It sounds more political
than personal.
He wants to show he can make
a whole city vulnerable.
Well, if it is
statement oriented,
he'll come out
from behind the curtain,
and share his world view.
Spike, what's going on?
Submerging the
Mercury in acetone.
Two minutes,
I'm moving the rest
of these people outta here,
unless you tell me different.
Copy that.
Adding dry ice
to lower the temperature.
Minus 36 degrees...
Two more degrees
and the Mercury freezes over.
Come on... come on...
Come on!
Minus 38.8 degrees.
Going for the power source.
I see it.
Cutting the power supply.
Done!
We're clear!
Call centre's
back in business.
We're okay;
the bomb's disabled,
your colleagues can come back.
Okay, Jules, Leah, help
EMS identify the wounded,
30 seconds per patient.
Sam, same thing inside -
find survivors.
Go!
Guys, remember, four
Green is for minor injuries;
yellow is for urgent;
red is for immediate.
Black's for dead.
Or beyond saving -
it's a judgment call here.
Sir! Sir!
Can you hear me?
Check his pulse.
Sir, I need you
to close your eyes, please.
Okay, he's in shock.
Raise his legs.
- Let's put this under.
- All right, gently.
We
got a red here!
Tag and move!
Let's go!
Let's move!
911, what is your emergency?
Where are you located, sir?
Okay, is anyone with you
right now?
- No, stay on the line with me.
- Breathe...
What are you
thinking, Spike?
I'm thinking one bomb,
that's probably your day.
Two bombs...
I think your day
might not be over.
Let's figure out who made this.
Copy that.
911, what is your emergency?
Ma'am, can you hear me?
Are you able to walk?
We've got a yellow!
All right,
paramedics are coming.
You're gonna be just fine,
okay?
- Let's go.
- Just keep on breathing.
All right, hold her neck.
Ma'am, can you hear me?
Ethan...
Okay... hi, honey.
My name is Jules.
I'm gonna help you, okay?
I'm so sorry...
I'm so sorry, honey.
Jules!
She says there's a daycare
in there.
There's more kids!
Ed! Inside!
There's a daycare!
Copy! Sam, check
the floorplans;
we gotta get there.
I'm on it!
Ma'am, somebody's gonna
be right with you, all right?
Is this the daycare?
I can hear a woman, kids.
Somebody might be hurt,
I can't be sure.
Hello!
This is the police!
We're gonna help you!
Can you hear us?
Guys, the daycare's front
door's fifteen feet in.
They can't hear us
with all this debris.
Controlled demolition
to open the way?
Sam, we can't do it.
It's too unstable.
We gotta go in.
Sasha, please, honey, stay calm all right?
You gonna fit
through that hole?
We're gonna
get outta here, okay?
I'm gonna try.
Ed, there's no
way, it's too risky!
Just... just leave Howie!
Look, he can't move right now.
He's... he's sleeping.
Okay,
there's a kid...
There's a kid pinned down
in there.
I'm small enough;
I can fit through that hole.
Jules, the structure's
been compromised here.
We can't let you go in,
it might collapse.
I can do this!
Jules, stop. We'll
find another way.
Sam, you've
gotta let me do this!
Jules, you're not
thinking straight!
There are children in there
and we are running out of time!
Now, Sam, right now,
are you my teammate
or my husband?!
I can do this.
Let's go. Let's go.
Hello!
I'm coming in!
What's happening here?
Oh my God...
Another bomb's gone off!
Sir, could you
repeat that, please?
I'm sorry, ma'am, I'm
having trouble hearing you,
did you say City Hall?
Sergeant,
we have a man
claiming responsibility.
He wants to talk
to the "decisionmaker."
This is sergeant Greg Parker
with the police Strategic
Response Unit.
Your rank doesn't impress me.
Are you the one
running the show?
Sir, very busy down here.
I'm gonna have to hang up
if I'm not convinced you are
what you say you are.
I'm gonna give you ten seconds.
Nine, eight...
The building
you're in is still standing.
Nice work, puppet.
I'm listening.
Three bombs...
You think it ends there,
but it doesn't.
Whoa...
This is just the beginning.
Sir, there are more bombs?
How many more?
Lots more.
Shouldn't be long
'til the next one.
How long, sir?
About half an hour,
and one after that,
and after that...
Look, who is this?
Who is this?!
You're talking to the one
running the show.
A second
detonation in the downtown core
has given weight
to the speculation
that these incidents
are terror-related.
But we repeat,
this is only speculation
at this point.
All non-critical casualties
are being transported...
But what's available?
Every truck you can spare,
every ambulance, every crew,
we need them on the road
to Toronto immediately.
I understand.
All right, team,
they've just upgraded this thing
to a category one emergency.
Fire and EMS from Durham
are on their way.
We're reaching out to Halton,
Peel and York.
It's all hands on deck.
Have you contacted
the military?
Yeah, we've got
units from CFB Borden.
They're gonna control
the streets
and set up a mass casualty
triage at the stadium,
all the hospitals
are gonna be over capacity.
Ed, I've got
your wife on the line.
Winnie, tell her I'll
call her as soon as I can.
Tell her what's going on here.
Spike, what're we looking at?
I can't trace it.
It's a disposable cell.
The voice has been
digitally altered.
I can't unscramble it
but it's a fair guess
it's a "he."
That narrows it down.
Anything in the background?
No. I've filtered it,
I've boosted it,
but all I'm getting is him.
Your rank
doesn't impress me.
Are you the one
running the show?
He hates authority.
He's setting his own terms.
The building
you're in is still standing.
Nice work, puppet!
"Puppet."
He's the master...
And he's pulling all
the strings.
Hello!
Can you hear me?!
Hey!
Hey! Over here!
What's your name?!
- - Della!
Della, my name's Jules.
My team's here.
We're gonna come get you, okay?
There's a hurt
little boy in here!
Please hurry!
Careful, Jules.
Jules!
Jules, what's going on?!
I'm okay.
Rebar dug into my leg.
Dean. Son.
Dad.
You didn't answer.
I just...
We didn't know.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Ed?
Ed's fine,
we're all fine.
How about you?
You're still at school, right?
It's study day, remember?
I'm downtown with Mira,
we're shopping for prom.
Where are you?
I'm on Gerrard.
Is Clark with you?
He was.
He split off, dad.
He went to get a permit.
A permit for what?
For the prom -
that outdoor party.
Do you know where?
No.
Did you try his cell?
Yeah, no answer.
Dad, what's going on?
Everybody's freaking out,
they're saying it's terrorism.
Dean, we're figuring
it out, buddy, all right?
I want you and Mira
to go to the station.
Wait for me there.
Okay.
Don't go into the subways
and avoid public buildings,
you hear me?
Avoid public buildings.
Just keep your eyes open,
all right?
Dean?
Dean. Deano!
Hey, we just lost a whole
cell phone zone downtown.
Lines are overloaded.
That's just gonna
accelerate everybody.
That's just
what our guy wants...
Fear for fear's sake.
What if we make a
public announcement on TV,
acknowledge
what's happening here.
It'll make our
guy even happier.
More attention,
more validation,
more mass panic.
But if we don't
warn people to be vigilant,
we could be putting them
at risk.
Fear's about
not having answers.
Winnie,
get me the mayor's office.
We need to go public, now.
Someone needs to talk
to the city.
Copy.
I see it! The
daycare's up ahead.
We're gonna be okay.
We're gonna get outta here
and we're gonna be okay.
There's someone here!
Oh, thank God!
Oh my God!
You have to help him!
Please! Please!
He's stuck there!
Please!
Della. Della!
Della, stop it!
Look at me.
You've held it together
for these kids
this long, okay?
You just need to keep on
doing that.
Just keep breathing.
You got it.
Let's go.
Okay...
Come on, come on.
Hi, honey.
Can you talk to me?
Buddy?
Buddy!
Hi! Hi. Are you okay?
I'm gonna get you outta here.
All right, Della,
I want you to gather the kids,
get them ready.
When I get our friend out,
we're gonna go.
Wanna see how strong I am?
Yeah?
It's gonna
be okay, all right?
We're gonna go home soon.
I'm scared.
Ungh!
That's my Jack!
Let's see how strong I am.
- Do you feel that?
- Mm-hmm.
Good. Can you move your legs?
- Yeah...
- Yeah?
Let's get you to your mom.
How 'bout that?
He's okay.
Let's go.
I miss my mom.
Let's go! We're gonna
get you outta here, okay?
Yes, sir, I understand.
I will do my best.
The mayor got caught
in the blast at city hall.
He's being treated.
The deputy mayor
wants a uniform
to talk to the city.
Boss, no one better.
Let's get you set up.
We go now to this
critical incident's officer in charge,
Sergeant Gregory Parker
from the police service's
Strategic Response Unit.
Sergeant?
You're probably aware
that the city's facing
an emergency situation;
two explosions
right in the heart of our city.
I want you to know
that we've got a lot
of good folks on the case,
responders from the city
and from surrounding regions
are all working together
to keep you safe,
and to keep everything
under control.
Now, you're gonna hear
a lot of speculation
and maybe some rumours,
'cause that's just what happens
in a situation like this,
and some of it may be alarming.
But I wanna tell you
that the best way to stay safe
is to stay calm and to look out
after each other.
Highways, roads, cell phones,
911...
Please use these as sparingly
as you can
because if these systems
are overloaded
they will shut down.
Today is the kind of day
that we'll all look back at,
years from now,
and remember exactly
where we were
and what we did.
We have a chance
to make choices here
that we will be proud of.
Today's the day that we did
not let fear break us down,
and turn us against each other.
This was the day
that we took care of each other.
The day that we said no
to terror,
together.
I want us all to think about
how we want to remember
this day.
It's up to us.
I want to thank you
for your attention,
and for your courage.
Thank you, sergeant Parker.
We return now to our live...
What'd you think, Spike?
Cheesy?
Not cheesy, boss.
You gotta stay off this leg.
How's the pain?
Pain's pain.
Well, what do mean
the boys are downtown?
Parker they went shopping
together, then Clark split off.
That's all I know.
Well, did he say
where he was going?
To get a permit for a party.
Greg, that's at a
municipal building.
I, I... I haven't been able
to get a hold of him.
Eddie, I'm sure he's fine.
It's probably cell towers.
Well...
Well, what am I gonna do?
What do I...
What am I gonna say to Sophie?
Look, Ed,
just wait till we have
more information,
before she gets worried
for nothing.
Ed! Okay, I'll figure it out.
I gotta go.
Yeah?
I got a casualty report.
What do we got?
Forty-one green,
eleven yellow,
seventeen red,
and too many dead.
Whoever did this...
Is gonna get his ass
nailed to the wall.
Okay. Thanks, Leah.
Hey. We're done tagging.
They want us over
at the next bomb site,
- priority one.
- Okay.
What?
It's Clark.
He's at a municipal building
and I haven't heard from him.
- City Hall?
- Donna, I don't know.
Ed, I'm headed there.
I'll call you as soon
as I can, okay?
Come on,
what're the odds, right?
Okay.
I'll call you when I get there.
Okay, thank you. Thank you.
All right?
How's the leg, Jules?
Did you talk to your folks?
I can't get a hold of 'em.
I'm sure they're fine, though.
Yeah.
How are you?
We're good.
So you still haven't heard
from him at all?
I haven't.
It's not like him,
not this long.
Well, you know, Soph,
like I said, he's probably...
Probably just got
his headphones on, so...
Ed, I'm worried.
Why hasn't he called?
I mean,
what if something happened?
Soph, we're gonna
get him home okay.
He's gonna be fine.
Guys, check your inboxes.
Soph, I gotta go.
I love you.
Okay.
52 Division just
forwarded an email
from the guy claiming
to be the bomber.
It comes with a tube link.
Claims to be his manifesto.
He sent a tube link
to the police?
No, to the media outlets,
and they sent it to us.
I like to think of
myself as a thought-provoker,
a provocateur.
But to provoke thought,
first I need to get
your full attention.
We live in media-saturated,
technology-fractured,
short-attention-span times;
it's not easy to secure
an audience.
I hope
what I set in motion today
has succeeded on that front.
This thing goes
on for 47 minutes.
Can you track the
computer he posted that from?
No; He's transcoded the video...
I can't get
to the original file,
and it looks like he put it up
using a dummy account.
It's totally anonymous.
How do you know
it was a dummy account?
Because he called it
dummy, underscore, account.
Did the email itself
come from the same computer?
Well, he's been so
careful to cover his tracks,
I can't see-
Hold on a second.
I think he slipped up.
This publicity thing,
he sent it from a smart phone.
I can back-track that.
I can get you a number.
Phone number is 555-0193.
I might be able
to get a location too.
No. He's turned off
the GPS, but we can still get a name.
Winnie?
The smart phone is registered
to an Anson P. Holt.
I'm sending his address
to you now.
Ed! Let's move,
let's go!
Boss?
Yeah, Jules,
you stay off that leg.
I need your help profiling.
Let's figure out
who our "thought provoker" is,
maybe we can figure out
where his bombs are.
Copy.
Ed, I'm on my way!
Boss, these bombs are
a half hour apart.
If he's sticks
to his promise...
I know;
eleven minutes
till the next one blows.
- Clear!
Greg, he's not here.
Boss, I think he
sees this as taking a stand
for personal freedom;
the liberty of the individual
against control...
any kind of control.
He wants to show we can
all fight back
by claiming our own
personal autonomy.
Cut the puppet strings.
I get it, Jules,
but it's just general
theoretical justification.
Yeah, but look,
he actually lists the forces
he's fighting against.
Each one gets a graphic.
What if each one is a target
he's planning on hitting?
The Government
Federal Building.
Just like a security blanket,
the safety is all an illusion,
and the child
that depends on it
will soon be forced to grow up.
"Communications"...
That's what he calls the city's
"security blanket."
Well, that's 911 -
the people who keep us safe.
Petty politics?
City Hall.
It's all lining up.
How many forces is
this guy fighting against?
Seven, eight, nine...
We got ten targets.
Okay, we're onto this bastard.
Good work, Jules.
But that doesn't
tell us where the bombs are.
"Justice" can mean
any courthouse.
"Media" could mean
any television station.
Anson Holt is a psychologist.
Go head, Winnie.
He's a Professor
at Brookfield University.
Lots of publications,
major research grants,
lecture tours...
And one of the highest
student ratings of the faculty.
Oh! Correction.
He was "let go"
from the university
five years ago.
Why?
No reason anyone was
willing to put on the record.
All right, get me the head
of the psychology department,
and I'll get it out of them.
Day like today, boss,
I'm gonna do my best, but...
Winnie, just find them.
Sorry, boss, will do.
Where the hell are you?
Dad...
Clark, what's going on?
Talk to me!
Talk to me.
Can't move.
Clark?
Clark, you're at City Hall?
Are you in City Hall?
Yes...
Rush!
Okay, okay, stay with me.
Can't...
It's okay,
just stay with me.
I'm here.
Call Donna, tell her
Clark's at City Hall.
Track his phone.
I'm coming to get you,
stay with me.
Boss, you copy that?
Yeah, I did, Spike.
Boss, there was a false back
on his office bookshelf.
What was he hiding?
Some pretty disturbing books.
"Embracing sadism."
"The courage to dominate."
He's got a private
DVD collection,
plain covers.
Hey, guys, I think
I found another target.
He's hit communications,
big government,
petty politics.
But his biggest grudge to date
is education.
Listen to this.
Substitute "institution
of higher learning"
for "institution of conforming
and crushing."
I will crush you back.
Crush you where it began
in that lab.
I will be watching you.
His old workplace,
where his grudge began.
We need to find that lab.
Clark, let me ask you,
do you feel any pain?
Yeah, my side...
It hurts.
Legs...
Legs are killing.
Pain's good, buddy. It
means your spine's okay.
Now, Clark,
I know this hard,
but I need you
to just slow your breathing
right down for me.
Let's get that heart rate down,
okay?
It'll help you think straight,
you're not gonna lose
so much blood.
I taught you sniper breathing,
right, Clark?
Clark?
Clark!
I know it's hard for you
to speak, but...
Clark, I know you can hear me.
You are such a strong kid
and I am so proud of you.
Now, I need you to stay strong.
I'm on my way.
I love you, buddy.
I love you.
Sarge, I tracked
down the Dean of Psychology,
Monica Butler.
That's fantastic, Winnie!
Professor Butler?
My name is
Sergeant Greg Parker.
I'm with the police
Strategic Response Unit.
I need you to answer
a few questions.
Uh, yes, of course.
Where's the
lab Anson Holt worked
before he was fired?
Uh, that was the old
Casey Jeffers Building,
but that's not in use any more.
Why?
Okay, just hold on the line.
Winnie? I want a citywide search
for Anson Holt.
Anyone who's not at a bombsite
is looking for this bastard.
And which team is closest
to the Casey Jeffers Building
right now?
Donna. Team three.
Great. Donna, you hear me?
- Yeah, boss.
-  Clark!
Donna, I need
you to get to that lab.
There could be
another bomb there.
I'm at City Hall
looking for Clark.
Anybody hear me?
Donna, you're the closest
team to that site, all right?
I'll be right behind you.
I know protocol,
boss, but this is Ed's kid.
Donna, I'm almost there.
You gotta go.
Get to the lab -
priority of life.
Clark!
Eddie, I'm right here!
Donna, I got it.
Clark?
Donna, thank you
for everything.
Jimmy, we gotta go.
Team three, let's move!
Donna, stay safe.
Always, Eddie.
Everyone, you
are the heart and soul.
All of you, thank you.
Soph, we know where he is.
But listen to me...
Sophie, he's hurt.
He's in one of the buildings.
Oh, Ed...
Look, I know you're
scared and I'm scared too,
but he's tough.
Soph, he's tou...
Hold on, hold on, Soph.
I got EMS.
Hold on, please.
Steve.
Ed, we tracked his cell signal
to the second level
of the parking garage,
but we haven't found him yet.
Hold on! Ed! Ed!
I got the car.
I'm sorry, Ed, but uh...
It's crushed under concrete.
It's not looking good.
Okay, I'm right there.
Soph?
Now, I'm gonna get him out.
Now you gotta believe that,
'kay?
I'm gonna bring him home,
okay, baby?
Guys...
I think I've got a positive ID
on Anson Holt.
He's here at the lab.
All right, Donna,
there are bombs ticking down
all across this city;
no time for kid gloves.
Copy. Go.
Anson Holt, put your hands
where I can see them!
- SRU! On the ground!
- Police! Get down now!
Get down on the ground
right now!
Get on the ground!
Turn him.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You make one move I
don't tell you to make,
you get shot,
do you understand?
Do you understand?!
Good!
Donna, what's going on?
He's strapped to an
M112 demolition charge,
and he's watching
the whole city carnage
on his computer screens.
Donna, I'm right behind you.
Professor Butler,
why did Anson Holt get fired?
Ethical issues were
brought to our attention.
Listen to me, Professor,
in under two minutes,
I'm gonna try to talk this man
out of blowing up
more innocent civilians.
Please just tell me
what happened in that lab.
He was fired
because of a series
of psychologically abusive
experiments
that he performed there
on student volunteers.
He was a sadist?
Yes.
One woman downrange,
the rest of you go.
Somebody's gotta cover him.
If he makes a play
when you're working...
Okay, okay. Jimmy, stay.
The rest of you go.
You're gonna raise your arms,
very slowly,
away from your body,
into the air.
Do it.
You're gonna talk to me, Holt.
You tell me where
the rest of the bombs are!
Winnie!
Are you okay?
Yeah, we're fine.
Okay.
Steve! Steve!
- Ed!
- Where is he?
The phone signal's here, man.
It's gotta be him.
Clark!
Spike, I got no timer.
I got C4 and wires.
This doesn't look like
your 911 bomb.
Donna, if there's no timer
on the bomb,
then you can wait
till I get there.
No! I can handle it.
How many wires do you see?
Uh...
Eighteen.
Arms up!
Okay, the bomb's exposed,
that's good.
Now, just find the detonator.
I don't see any detonator.
No, there's
gotta be a detonator.
I don't see
it, I'm looking.
Is this the fastest way?
It's the only way.
Every on ramp and highway
is jammed right now.
We're going as fast as we can.
Donna, how's our subject
Quiet, co-operative -
could be the gun on his head.
Boss, this make
any sense to you?
If he was gonna blow
himself up,
why didn't he already do it?
This is your very last chance.
Tell me where the detonator is
right now!
Right now!
What're you looking at?
Team three, I'm here.
What do you see, Donna?
I got a blinking
camera in the ceiling.
Get outta there, now!
Move!
Aggghhhhhhhhhhhh!
Boss!
I'm okay.
Holt wasn't the bomber.
He was the bait, Eddie.
She's gone, Eddie.
She was right in front of him.
Sonofabitch.
Sonofabitch!
==sync, correction by dcdah==
www.addic7ed.com