Ed Lane.
It's Ed Lane I want.
Okay, okay.
Let me start working on that.
Working on that?
Well, yeah, he's out of range.
I got to track him down.
He's standing next to you.
???
-Eight-- is that enough?
-Yep.
You still have Santorini
blue on your hand.
Got to use
the thinner.
Yeah, maybe if you left me some.
I'll bring you
some more tonight.
Flowers, bottle
of thinner.
-Instant romance.
-Hey, by the way,
it's not Santorini blue;
it's Sanrini sky.
Guys done with
the restock?
Yeah.
We're meeting
in the briefing room.
Okay.
Jules, how, uh...
how are the renovations coming?
Oh.
Really good: one room left.
A renovation ahead of schedule.
Wow, you getting any help?
-No.
-Come on.
Your own two hands...
that's amazing.
-That's got to feel good.
-Yeah, it doe
Hi, it's Luka.
Leave a message.
???
??
I'll leave a key for you.
Take anything you want.
I just have one favor to ask.
Look at you.
Got three hours
till vacation.
Someone's already
the dock
with his fishing rod
and his nice, cold beer.
What?
I'm right here for you, buddy.
You know why?
No "I" in "team."
That's good. You can take
the next crank call,
kick some swatter ass
before you go.
Go for Ed.
Go for your beleaguered wife.
Hey, I thought you said
you were gonna pack your own clothes.
They were wet.
You know that big thing
beside the, uh...
washing machine?
-It's called a...
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Are you gonna pick me up
at noon or what?
Yeah, as soon
as Clark's done music camp.
Hey, where are the fishing rods?
So, they're in the car.
I packed them myself.
Ah, he packs the fun stuff.
You gonna be done shift on time?
Yeah, as long ase don't
get swatted again.
What's that?
We're getting a bunch of 911s
from fake caller IDs.
I just busted in on an old lady
having a cup of tea.
Well, how about this?
You're late, and I'll swat you.
Nice.
Long as you promise to wear
that old lady dress that I like so much.
Goodbye.
Okay, I know
it's been a long day.
It's been a long
ten-day shift.
A few more hours.
Let's just keep it
together, okay?
Now, three swatter calls
in a day.
-A little hinky.
-Hinky?
Boss, it's starting
to feel personal.
I hear you.
Kira's trying
to do some digging around,
see if she can find a
connection, but in theeantime,
what do we do
if we get another call?
Any suggestions?
If a real call comes in,
we split up.
We don't want to be jammed up
in the wrong end
of the city
chasing our tails, right?
That's good: splinter unit.
Splinter unit
for anything unconfirmed.
Wordy, you're in charge of that.
The two of you ride along
if it smells like another prank;
the rest of us...
let's stay here on standby.
Hit the gym, do target practice.
Do something. Let's get it out.
All right.
I have no choice.
This is what war is.
Your father gave me no choice.
That... that's my bus.
I'm sorry for you.
I'm sorry for everything.
It's terrible to be at war.
Don't blame me.
Blame your father.
So, what
do you guys say?
Parking lot hoop
Game of 21?
When's the last time
you ever got 21?
Afraid of losing
to a family man, huh?
Hey, Clark,
how you doing, buddy?
Look...
Look, slow down, slow down.
Just... no, just start
from the beginning.
Clark?
Boss, I just got
off the phone with Clark.
-What happened?
-Some guy came up to him on the street,
started talking crap about me,
about how this is war.
Don't blame him; blame me.
Hey, sit down.
Sit down.
-Is Clark okay?
-He's okay.
I'm sure
it's nothing.
But why don't you go anyway.
You sure? I was gonna ask...
Yeah, we're covered.
It's slow.
You're going
on vacation.
You are going
on vacation, right?
I'm going on vacation, yeah.
So, go see
your son.
Get out of town
before the traffic hits.
All right, be safe.
I'll see you.
Alright,
have fun.
Think he knows?
Who?
Sarge.
Yes, I think
he knows.
Ow... why?
You have blue paint
on your ear.
Well, we might as well
just tell him now.
Get it over with.
I'll do it. I don't care.
Yeah, and then what?
One of us gets transferred
to another team?
These guys are my family.
Not just yours.
Doesn't mean I want
to give you up.
Jules...
What?
Team 1, hot call
at Nathan Phillips Square.
Repeat: hot call.
That's City Hall, boss.
I hear it... Kira?
Reports of shots fired.
Multiple witnesses.
-Not a prank?
-No, sir.
I've got Inspector Stainton
on the line.
Let's see what's going on.
Inspector?
Sergeant, we got
one serious situation here.
Tell me.
One injured: City Hall security guard's
been shot in the leg,
and we're pinned in here
real bad.
How many shots fired?
Thre four... they're coming
every two minutes.
Honest to God, we don't know
where they're coming from.
You clear all the civilians,
four-block radius?
We're doing the best we can.
It's summertime in the city.
Greg.
Okay, we'll be right there.
Containment is the priority.
I'll call you back in three.
Kira, call Team 4.
All hands on deck. Eddie?
Trucks are loaded.
Okay, boys,
let's keep the peace.
Flashpoint S02 ep04
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@夏风
Sync:FRS@山石 小荸荠
???
Let's get
some shields.
Heads down.
They're pinned behind the car.
How is the victim doing,
Inspector?
He's holding on.
Sam, Louis, Wordy.
Let's give him some cover.
Get him inside
so the EMT can get to him.
It's been a nightmare;
we got no idea
where these shots
are coming from.
And how are we doing
on containment?
We've evacuated all civilians
into the underground lots,
but you got people coming in and out
of all these buildings.
Shooter's active.
Like clockwork,
every two minutes.
-Lou?
-I'm on it.
Acoustic locator's
gonna nail his position
as soon as he shoots again.
Beyond the security guard,
there's no other injuries.
Thank God
this guy's not a pro.
Wordy, you get a look
at the wound.
Yeah. The exit wound's lower
than the entry.
Means he's shooting
from up top.
Okay, it's a target-rich environment
that's almost uncontainable.
I got no one to talk down.
Any word from counterterrorism?
No, I'm telling you,
no chatter, no warning, no nothing.
This guy's come
from of where.
Okay, Spike,
you stay in the Command Truck.
You run all the maps
and the intelligence,
all information flows
through you.
Copy.
Okay, I'm looking
at 300-meter radius on the 3-D.
Buildings are dense.
Lots of places he can be,
lots of angles.
We got to try to narrow it down.
Find out where the shots
are coming from.
Locaters are online,
so we got ears.
Let's see
if we can get any clues.
Louis, Wordy.
We'll do witnesses.
All right,
you press them for details.
I need to know where
that shot came from.
-Copy.
-The way the ??
did he spin,
did he crumple?
Any visible shimmers, muzzle flashes,
reflection, movement.
Sam, Jules, let's break it dow
Came from the south.
We got a lot of options here.
Where would you go?
Clock tower, classic,
lots of shadows, good concealment.
Building under construction,
lots of visual distraction...
Whoa, whoa.
Buddy must be lucky
or he knows what
a sniper locator looks like.
He's located himself.
Ricochet directly through the target
to the point of origin.
-The hotel.
-Could be the roof.
Any of those top floors.
A lot of tinted windows.
Let's start with the roof.
tive shooter,
we go to him.
Okay. I'm gonna brief the Chief.
I'll be in the truck.
All right, use the overhang
for cover.
How many seconds
from his lt shot?
60 seconds.
Sam, grab a shield. Let's go. Go! Go!
I'm going to cover you.
If you don't think
you can make it,
wait till he fires again.
Copy that
Spike, count us down.
Ten, nine,
eight, seven, six,
five, four, three,
two, one.
Two minutes, right?
Copy. Over two minutes now.
All right, he's breaking
his pattern.
Maybe we're
getting warm.
Or he's moved.
Where would you go next,
it was you?
Clock tower's a no-biner.
Right there.
All those vents, visual distractions,
clean view of the square, boss.
Okay, see it.
-Inspector?
-Yeah?
Clock tower--
lock up the whole
southeast quadrant.
Copy that.
-No one in or out. SRU only.
-Done.
We got a chopper coming in
to sweep the rooftops.
You want a long-range, precision weapon
against a big noisy target?
-I'll call it off.
-Thanks.
-Sam, Jules?
-Almost there.
Somebody opened
those doors.
We're thinking he's moved,
but if he hasn't,
you're looking at booby traps,
ambush, suicide,
suicide by cop.
Maximum caution.
Our friend hit a seven-inch
target from 400 meters.
Roof's clear.
He's not up here.
But he was.
It's a .762. Carbon Striations.
He's got an HK G3.
That's nasty.
Shields are safe,
but that'll crack body armor.
This hotel has 43 floors.
Stainton's got uniforms sweeping
the interiors.
The rooftops are up to us.
Clock tower's next.
Copy that.
Wordy, Louis, any luck
with the witnesses?
thing we don't
already know.
All right, move on.
Next highest building,
City Hall,
both rooftops.
Copy that.
On our way.
Spike, get forensics up
to the hotel roof.
Right now we're doing
everything we can.
Yes, sir.
Every step of the way.
Yeah. Bye.
Hey, way to start
your vacation.
Team 3,
I need access.
We kept the elevator
open for you.
What a scene, huh?
I don't get it.
I really don't.
What kind of a person would
do something like that?
-Thank you.
-Good Luck
Tactically?
-We can't do anything until...
-Until he starts shooting again.
Okay, so help me out.
Who is this guy?
Criminal sharpshooter.
I mean, usually, it's military
or law enforcement...
Yeah, but this guy doesn't seem
to be hitting his mark.
He's trying hard
not to, right?
A dozen shots, only one injury,
what are the odds, right?
Hit the locator pretty good.
Okay, let's assume
he knows what he's doing.
Typical profile?
Tyrannical sadist.
Antisocial,
wants to play God,
wants control, wants to see
innocent people suffer.
-Except...
-Except there's only one injury,
not much
of a sadist.
Maybe it's targeted.
Maybe it's revenge.
Maybe it's...
maybe it's personal.
That's what Wordy said in
the briefing room, right?
"Feels like it's personal."
Three swatter calls, one shift.
That's a first.
This guy's trying to wear us out.
It's urban warfare strategy.
You hit the army when they're
tired returning from battle.
All right, I'm going
to check with Kira,
see if she tcked down
those swatter calls.
Sam, Jules.
Uniforms are sweeping the hotel.
We're heading to the clock tower.
Kira forwarded the sound files
from 911 calls this morning.
They come from different
phone numbers?
Yeah, but it sounds
like spoofing to me.
-Spoofing?
-Seems it's perfectly legal
to impersonate
another caller ID
if it's "for entertainment
purposes only."
Oh, my God, he's going
to shoot me!
They guarantee privacy.
They don't release
clients' names.
It's my friend. He says
he's going to shoot himself.
For a little extra they'll mess with
the pitch of your voice.
Help, please, put the gun down!
You hear that?
Three voices, one accent.
Eastern European?
Ed.
Personal.
First York.
No way.
No choice. "It's not me,
it's your father. This is war."
How did Clark describe the guy
at the bus stop today?
Yeah, European accent. Young guy.
Noay.
-Call your family.
-All right.
Team, listen up,
We think we know
who this guy is.
???
thing staying at school.
Just sit tight, buddy.
Sit tight till Mom gets there.
Okay, I love you, too.
Kira, get my wife and kid to the
station and lock down the SRU.
Okay, mid-20s, dark hair,
ordinary-looking. Spoke with an accent.
I know.
You shot his father.
He was close enough
to feel the bullet fly.
He took me to court
for wrongful death.
-And he lost.
-Yeah.
Okay.
Kira, Spike,
I need you to pull u
a wrongful death lawsuit.
Last name: Tomasic.
Copy that.
I'm also sending out
a photograph of the subject.
News footage of First York.
Boss, I've got
his employment records.
Next of kin?
Goran Tomasic.
That's his father.
He's deceased.
y emergency contacts?
Luka Boblic.
Here, I got a cell number.
Okay, let's get that guy here
immediately.
Let's send a squad car.
Guys, what are
we doing here?
We've ID'd the subject.
We're looking for him.
He's camouflaged,
or he's hiding.
And what's the next step?
We get in his head;
we anticipate his next move.
Until en...
wait till he shoots again.
Terrific.
Uniforms have locked down
the entrances to the south buildings.
Wordy, Lou, how you guys doing
on the City Hall towers?
Rooftops are clear.
Going to the
mechanical room.
Where are you?
Just looking for my tennis
racketYou almost ready?
Listen, there's a squad car
going to come by.
It's going to pick you up.
A squad car?
Why?
Sophie, it's just
a precaution, okay?
I'm sorry.
I'll explain as soon as I can.
YeahYeah, okay.
-I love you.
-I love you, too.
We got to find this guy now.
Yeah, Spike found
a photo.
The guy's name is Petar Tomasic.
Quit his job two weeks ago,
and no one's answering the phone
at his apartment.
Guys, subject is confirmed.
Petar Tomasic. 26 year-old,
Caucasian, dark hair.
Sam, Jules, where are you?
We're heading up
the clock tower.
Sweeping floor
by floor.
Nothing here, Ed.
Copy. Sam, Wordy, Louis,
what's your 20?
Clearing the mechanical room.
Heading to the East Tower.
All right, keep talking to us.
Eddie, Luka Boblic is here.
He was on scene.
You might want to listen in.
Luka, this is Ed Lane.
I know who you are.
You know why you're here?
Petar left a message on my phone.
I heard on the radio what was happening.
I came down as fast as I could.
No one would let me through.
Petar left a message?
He said, uh, good-bye.
I knew something was coming.
Where is he?
That's just it; we don't know.
So, let's start with the basics, okay?
Does Petar have access to a gun?
I-I don't know.
Last week he told me he was thinking
about getting a rifle from some guy,
black market. I don't know who.
When I heard that, I said,
"Petar, you do this, I swear,
I'll turn you in myself."
He told me to forget it.
He was just kidding.
I believed him. I believed him.
This isn't your fault, Luka.
Okay, he made his own choice here today.
But you can still help him.
He was...
so angry at everything, everyone.
He think you ruined his life.
Did he say what kind of rifle it was?
I don't know.
Does he know how to shoot it?
Does your friend know
how to shoot a rifle?
Snipers were how we protected ourselves.
Petar ot eight men dead before he was 16.
Croatia, it was a civil war, sir.
Petar Tomasic was one of the
best snipers in our country.
We were like brothers; we were little
kids together; we grew up together.
So, what happened?
Petar got recruited by the local militia.
He fought alongside his
father against the Serbs.
Everyone called him
"Mali Sniperist"--"Baby Sniper."
He protected our village.
Subject is a skilled sniper,
familiar with urban warfare.
If he was missing his mark,
he was missing it on purpose.
Guys, this is a revenge situation.
Good news: We've narrowed it down.
He's looking for me.
I killed his father at First York Plaza.
Two years, I was at school, he was hiding
in the hills, fighting our enemies.
Until they found out who he was.
They didn't come after him.
They came after his family.
They tortured his mother
and they killed her and...
And he nearly went crazy.
But his father saved him.
They escaped through two countries on foot.
So, the woman that, um,
that was shot at First York?
His stepmother.
Boss?
Yeah, Kira.
You were right.
Spoofing network confirmed all three 911s
were routed through them
from the same client.
But they don't want to release
the client's name without a subpoena.
Want me to play bad cop on them?
No, thanks, Ki.
I think we may have
what we need right here.
Copy that.
Luka, if we can talk to him,
we may be able to stop him
from harming anybody else.
I know his cell number.
Thank you.
Petar Tomasic?
Petar, it's Greg Parker with the
Police Strategic Response Unit.
Thank you very much for picking up.
Petar?
Petar, I think it's important
that we start talking.
Why?
Maybe I can help you if I can
understand what you're looking for.
- I know what I'm looking for.
- Oh, yeah?
Ed Lane. It's Ed Lane I want.
Okay, okay, let me start working on that.
Working on that?
Well, yeah, he's out of range.
I got to track him down.
He's standing next to you.
I guess you can see everything, huh, Petar?
Like you. You can hear everything.
You can see everything.
Almost.
???
We, we waited till he shot
again, didn't we, Sergeant?
That kid was 24 years of age.
Fresh out of police academy.
You tell me how we could've
prevented that! You tell me!
You want to call the Chief on this?
You call him, you explain it!
No, no, I want to settle this thing.
Confirm Team 4 is containing
east buildings.
Can't tell where the sound came from.
Could be any building in this range.
He's using these curved walls.
Refracting the sound,
he's covering his tracks.
He's in the vicinity.
He's accelerating to get a respoe
and he's targeting law enforcement.
He can see me and he's
trying to draw me out.
Boss, if you get him back
on the phone, keep him on it;
I can try acking his position.
Copy that.
- Knew my dad was a cop, right
- thought he was a farmer.
Yeah, well, before that he was a cop.
Remember the Tower Sniper?
Yeah, 40 years ago,
guy in a clock tower?
- He killed 16 people that day.
- Cops couldn't get to him.
They didn't have the tools or the training.
When it was all over with, they decided
they were gonna do something about it.
You're kidding. Your dad was
part of the first SWAT teams?
No, he was one of the cops
that couldn't do anything.
He bought a farm in the prairies and
raised me and my brothers away from it all.
So, I guess he wasn't exactly
thrilled that you became a cop.
We got to get this guy.
You know what? He's not answering.
- Luka, you mind calling him on your own phone?
- No.
Boss, boss, the subject's already volatile.
You sure we want to bring
in a third party now?
Yeah, we're out of time.
And you think the kid can talk to him?
No, but he can keep him on the line long
enough for Spike to get a lock on where he is.
- Okay.
- Luka...
Luka, if you get him talking,
think past his plan to the bigger picture.
- You said you were like brothers, right?
- Right.
Team, we're bringing in a TPI.
Put it on speaker. Spike, I'm coming in.
Petar.
English.
What good is this going to do?
you know what they did.
You know what I have to do.
He promised me it'd be
different here, but it's not.
Come on. Come on.
I got used to not being afraid.
You don't need to be afraid.
They told me no one will be hurt.
That's what they said
before he shot my father.
Tell them I want Ed Lane to come out.
Or more people will die!
Petar!
Phone's dead.
Doesn't matter. I got it.
- Where?
- Right there.
He's on the roof.
That was locked down.
How'd he get in?
Jules, Wordy, meet me at the
southeast corner, Bay and Queen.
Copy.
On our way.
Let's stop this guy before
he shoots somebody else.
Eddie, you're the target.
You're not going anywhere.
You're staying covered
right here, okay.
You can act as spotter
from the ground.
- Boss...
- That's an order.
Team, report in.
Leaving City Hall.
There's an employee entrance.
Let's do this fast
before he shoots again.
We kept the freight elevator
open for you guys.
Stairwell's been blocked off.
No one's been up or down?
Not since we locked it up.
One SRU officer, that's it.
One SRU officer?
- Alone?
- Yeah.From Team 3.
Thanks.
Hey, Ed, Team 3 on the scene?
Negative. Team 4. Why?
Copper said an SRU went up to the roof. Solo.
He said he was Team 3.
Jules...
Yeah, I know.
Spike, put out an APB.
Subject may be wearing an SRU uniform
or a mockup identifying himself as Team 3.
We got reports that SRU entered building
southwest corner, Bay and Queen.
We're accounted for.
Team 4's accounted for.
Is there anything else
you can tell us, Luka?
Anything at all?
He's not a bad person. He's not.
He got a job. tried to fit in,
but when his father was killed
right in front of him...
I wanted to help him. The lawsuit--
it was useless, expensive.
It just made it worse.
He got more angry, more bitter.
It was... It was terrible to watch.
Ed, we're at the roof.
We're ready to move in.
Northwest corner by the air vent.
Looks like a rifle barrel.
Copy.
Guys, they're going in.
Boss?
Yeah, I'm on my way.
- Lou, Wordy?
- Almost tre.
Thanks.
He's not moving.
- Low and slow.
- Copy.
He shot himself. Any signs of trauma?
- It's hard to tell.
- I think we got him.
Police, drop your weapon!
Hands in the air  or we will shoot!
Show me your hands! Show me your hands!
Show me your hands!
It's a decoy!
Where is he?
It's a decoy. Fall back.
Fall back now! Take cover!
Officer down! Officer down!
Medic, come now. Jules has been hit!
Officer down. We need EMS.
Bay and Queen. SRU officer down.
Stay with me, Jules.
Stay with me.
Stay with me.Stay with me.
We're under fire! Get up here now!
Somebody get an angle on this guy!
Shots are coming from City Hall.
Boss, this is about me.
I come out, draw his fire,
you get her out of the way.
Negative. Negative.
We do it as a team.
Copy, Greg. Get her out of there.
Spike, you and me,
West Tower, City Hall.
Low and tight.
- Louis, you cover.
- Yup.
Roof's a grate.
We'll get eyes on the mechanical room.
Keep her sealed off.
Stay tight. Stay tight.
You're gonna be okay.
- We're getting you out.
- Keep her stiff.
We're getting you out, Jules.
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Easy! Easy!
Hang on.We got you.
Come on. Come on.
She's clear!
We've got him. Upper left.
Go.
Hey, got to let her go.
Team 4 Sierra's countering
from the East Tower.
Sam, let's find a Sierra shot.
I got it.
???
Boss, I found a vantage point.
I can see thmechanical roof.
Petar.
??? r the first five minutes of every day,
I forget that he's gone.
Then I remember, and I see him die.
Okay.
He's got Ed.
He's got a gun to his head.
We're on ouray, Spike.
I don't have a clear shot.
Ed's in my line of fire.
Come on. Come on! Come on!
You know what it's like to do what you
got to do to save your family, okay?
I'm just... I just...
My family's dead.
- Okay, take a breath.
- You killed my father.
- Petar. Petar.
- ???
Let's just slow it down
here, buddy, okay?
I need you to...
Tomorrow morning, for
the first five minutes...
...your son will forget that you're gone.
I need you to listen to me now,
buddy, all right?
Sam, we need a solution.
I can't get a clear shot.
He's behind the pillar.
Ed, you got to move forward.
I need you to listen to me.
I'm sorry, but I need you
to listen to me.
Please don't shoot.
Subject's down.
Not a good day for either of us.
Yes, sir.
Just give him a minute, will you?
- Where is she?
- Saint Simon's. We're on our way.
- I want to go with you.
- Sam.
??? Get there when you can, okay?
We'll be there.
We're not going anywhere.
It's a good job.
Braddock?
What? Please? Please?
He was my friend.
- He's cleared.
- He wasy friend.
Next of kin.
What should I have said to him?
What should I have said?
What? Hey.
You did the best you could do.
Know that.You hear me?
You know that.
That's all you can do.
Go on.
Hey, Jules.
Hey, sweetheart, how you doing?
I got here as fast as I could, Jules.
I'm so sorry.
I should have protected you.
Jules.
Okay, time to go, buddy.
No way.
There's nothing for you to do here.
If there was, I wouldn't
let you leave. Go on.
She's on my team...
Eddie, you're two hours away,
anything happens, anything changes.
You need to be with your family.
Do you hear me?
Those aren't just words.
Go on.
???
Hey, kiddo.
How's she doing?
She's stabilized.
She's in good hands. She'll be okay.
And how are you doing?
I'm exhausted.
Yeah. Want to talk about it?
- en we get there, okay?
- Okay. I'll drive.
Hey, kiddo.
Hey.
Can I sit in the front, Dad?
All right.
Jump in. Jump in.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net