(Lively chatter
throughout casino)
We gotta move now,
we gotta move fast, okay?
Let's go.
It's gonna be all right.
- Who are you?
- We're just leaving.
Man: - No you're not.
- Who is he?
Man 2:
Maybe he's a cop.
Spike:
Guys, Ed's been made.
Parker: Just keep it verbal, Eddie.
Low-key, just...
Please, let her go.
I said come with me, right now!
Robyn:
Okay, biggest cake ever,
and yes, you can make
the loot bags.
Can it be a sleep-over
too?
Robyn: Of course,
you only turn ten once,
we gotta do this right.
Mom says yes!
Man:
Good morning.
I didn't hear you leave
this morning.
Ah, blame the yen.
Asian markets got us
called in early.
I'm almost at the office.
How's your resume coming?
Tim:
Good.
Done.
Cover letter's standing by.
So what time you home tonight,
should we wait for dinner?
Robyn: Uh, I got clients
coming in after the bell,
and I don't wanna make promises
that I can't keep.
(Doorbell dings)
- Ah. Okay, no problem.
Amy: - I'll get it!
I'll keep it warm.
Gotta go.
Someone's at the door.
Okay, bye.
I love you.
Love you.
(Gasps)
- Give me your phone.
- What?
You wanna die today?
Give me your phone!
Assailant:
Drive! Move! Now!
(Tires screech)
Assailant:
I don't need to tell you.
Robyn: No mistakes, no alarms,
and I don't know you.
And I'm watching.
You've got 10 minutes.
Teller: Can I help
the next person, please?
Hi, how are you?
Good.
Mrs. Engles, right?
- Yes.
- How are you?
Uh, great.
I need to, um...
Cash out all my accounts,
um, cash advances
on the credit cards...
Whatever's available, please.
Oh, and um, I need to access
my safety deposit box.
My... my key.
Okay.
I just need to see your ID.
Uh, my id?
Teller: It's a
formality, I'm sorry.
So the full remaining amounts
in these accounts, in cash?
Yes, please.
Oh. I'm afraid that
your checking account
has been overdrawn,
but there's $2000 left
on your credit limit,
and $800 in your savings
account.
What about the, um...
Registered education fund?
Your daughter's education fund?
Full 30,000?
Yeah. We, uh...
We broke down,
we're sending her
to private school.
It's a great curriculum,
but it's not cheap.
My daughter's begging
to go to St. Adpolphus,
just because the uniforms
look like...
Harry Potter.
Teller:
Mrs. Engles?
Robyn:
Yes.
Is everything okay?
It's fine.
So, you intend to close
your accounts today
and withdraw the full value
of your assets in cash?
Robyn: - Please.
Teller: - Okay.
Can you just wait here
a moment, please?
Robyn:
Yeah, I just...
I don't have a lot of time.
I'll...
I'll be right back.
Winnie: Uh huh. Yeah. Hold on.
Boss!
Parker:
Yeah.
Okay, so she didn't actually
see a weapon?
Ms. Forbes,
I'm gonna put you through
to sergeant Greg Parker.
911 has a branch manager
at Hudson Trust.
They flagged a client
they believe's under duress.
It's not a gun call, but...
Ms. Forbes, hi.
I'm Greg Parker
with the police strategic
response unit.
Hester: We're not sure
what we're looking at,
but we have a client making
a large cash withdrawal
inconsistent with her
transaction patterns.
Okay.
Hester:
She's not armed herself,
but she's visibly stressed,
sweating,
hands are unsteady,
she's near tears,
and she keeps looking
towards reception.
My associate believes
there's a man there
who has her under duress.
What makes her believe that?
Sergeant,
she's a regular customer.
There's clearly
something wrong.
Parker: Okay, we're
gonna play this safe.
You stay on the line,
get your teller
to stall for time,
but show full co-operation,
all right?
But make sure that
both party's are unaware
that they've been flagged.
Do you understand?
Hester:
Thank you, sergeant.
Okay, we're on our way.
Hot call, Winnie.
Winnie:
Copy that.
(Sirens wail)
I'm sorry, there shouldn't be
any problem at all.
I just have to ask you
a couple of questions,
it's routine.
(Sirens wailing)
Raf: So she's taking her own
money out of her own account.
Yeah.
We had five robberies
like this last year.
Robbery by proxy.
Guy targets a wealthy client,
forces 'em to go into the bank
and bring out the money.
That way he doesn't have
to put on a ski-mask
and go in there yelling,
"this is a stick-up."
And if it's a false alarm?
I don't know,
we could go do some shopping?
(Sirens wailing)
Teller:
And the service fees,
were those reasonable
in your op...
Sorry, look, I just...
I don't have a lot of time,
I have an appointment.
Teller:
Sure.
Franca's keeping her talking.
What should we do next?
Get your client out of view
of the reception area
and let her know, discreetly,
that help is on the way.
And then inform security,
but make sure the client
is unaware.
(Security's phone rings)
Franca: I've printed
off your statement,
if you'd like to take a look.
(Sirens wail)
Ed: We need to get the
other customers outta range
without attracting attention.
Winnie, patch me in
to the manager too.
Here you go.
Okay, Hester,
here's what we need you to do.
Franca:
And for the denominations,
were you thinking large bills?
Large bills are fine.
Hester:
Customer surveys.
And I need to access my um...
Security box, yes.
You can follow me.
Jules: All right, Hester sent
us a profile on the victim.
Robyn Engles,
married, mother, homeowner,
currency trader.
Good regular income...
Low bank accounts though.
Okay, the floor plans are in.
Hester,
can you situate the victim
and the suspect for us?
Hester: Mrs. Engles is stepping
into the safety deposit booth.
Yes, it's concealed.
(Keys jingle)
Franca: Mrs.
Engles, the police are on their way.
What?
Everything's under control.
Oh my God!
(Franca's phone chimes)
Ah, yes, she's here.
Um, it's the police for you.
Hello?
Jules: Mrs. Engles, this is
officer Jules Callaghan.
Yeah, I'm sorry,
I don't understand
why this is a matter
for the police.
Okay, we're a minute away.
Robyn:
No, just don't, please.
I mean, it's really,
it's not necessary, please.
Jules: Okay, well, if that's the
case then we're all gonna go home
and everything's gonna be
just fine.
Franca: Mrs. Engles, did someone
force you to come in here today
and take out this cash?
You're a minute away?
Jules:
That's right.
Robyn: Yes, the man
in the baseball cap,
in a gray jacket,
he's sitting by reception.
He told me he has a gun.
Mrs. Engles, I want you to stay
right where you are.
Do not move.
This is gonna happen very fast
and you need to be
out of range.
Ed: All right, we're gonna
hit the front doors
with flashbangs.
We'll disarm him while getting
any remaining civilians
out of range.
You good with that?
All good.
(Flashbang pops)
SRU: Police! Down on the ground!
Down on the ground!
Get down! Get down!
(Cacophony of shouting)
Jules: Come on, let's go!
Let's go! Come on!
Man in ball cap:
What're you doing?!
Ed:
Subject secure.
Where's your weapon?
What weapon?
Franca: Mrs. Engles!
She just took off!
She went off
with that other man.
What man?
Franca: The man who was
standing right there,
I thought I saw a gun.
They both ran off into the street.
Guys, let's move.
They couldn't have gotten far.
Let's go.
Let's go, go, go!
We had her safe.
She just sabotaged
her own rescue.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
ed: Police!
Raf: Outta the way!
Ed: Police! Stop right there!
Right there!
Woman:
Ungh!
Ed:
Police!
Police! Stop right there!
Sam:
Why's she following him?
Assailant: Drive! Drive!
Eh, eh, back, back, back!
- Where're the keys?
- Front.
SRU: Police! SRU! Stay where you are!
Right there! SRU!
Assailant:
Go, go, go, go, go!
(Gunshots pop repeatedly)
Hold fire!
Halt fire!
Hostage at risk!
Sam:
We're losing 'em!
Ed:
Too many civilians.
He's already opened fire, Sam.
I'll take out the tires,
immobilize the vehicle.
Ed: You do that, he'll escalate.
He's not on a spree, Ed,
he's trying to...
Sam, this is my call.
My call here.
Winnie, APB on a grey van,
traveling west on Dundas,
plate 689 4-tango-Mike,
let's move, let's move.
She followed him
into the alley,
she's facilitating this.
He's not your regular
street thug...
Well dressed, labels...
Definitely into image.
Well, this was never
your random robbery.
He's talking to her...
And he keeps his distance.
He's not using
a physical force.
Parker:
He's completely confident
that she's gonna
follow through.
You get this capture to Spike?
Jules:
He's running it through records.
Spike:
I got him.
Dan Lefebvre.
Ties to organized crime here,
Montreal, Boston...
No convictions?
Spike: Guys he works for
, witnesses tend to go away.
Something's missing.
Why would he pick out
Robyn Engles?
And why is she helping him?
She had a chance to escape,
but she protects him.
Did you notice anything else
about her state of mind?
She may have been
co-operating,
but that was real fear.
Okay. Well, maybe there's
something more important
right now than her own safety.
Family.
Yeah.
Winnie, call the house,
call the kids' school.
I already got the numbers,
I'm on it.
I'll see if I can
track her cell.
Sam: So we just stand around till
some cruiser spots the vehicle
halfway outside the city?
Ed: Where we can apprehend
him without risk.
Sam:
We had him.
Before the vehicle
even left the alley,
I could've shot the tires.
I had a shot too, Ed.
Look, you shoot the tires,
the van swerves,
he's got his finger
on the gun...
We might as well
shoot her ourselves!
She was out of range,
the gunman's arm
was outside the van.
Ed:
Sam, I hear you.
Let's just move on here,
all right?
It's over.
Guys, Robyn's cell phone's
a dead end.
Winnie: Nobody's picking
up at the Engles house,
but the squad car says
the car's still in the laneway,
shears are drawn,
but their daughter Amy did not
show up for school today.
All right, we gotta get there.
Thank you.
Jules: House is on Don
Bridge, Hogg's Hollow.
Parker: Let's get the
husband and daughter safe.
They may lead us to Robyn.
Sam:
We're there.
(Engines roar to life,
sirens wail)
What's going on with Sam?
He's challenging Ed,
he's second guessing orders.
He's debriefing
in the street, Jules.
Are you asking me
as your teammate right now?
If I was asking you
as my teammate,
I would keep the headsets on.
Hey,
I let this thing go on
between you
means I keep a close eye;
that's the deal.
Well, I think that
it's been hard for him, boss.
He ran tac for five months
while Ed was recovering.
And he did a good job.
Maybe he feels like
he's got more to offer
than he gets to give.
I think it's more than that,
Jules.
Sam gets his own team,
it doesn't just help
his career.
I know, we both know.
But then he wouldn't be
working with the best, boss.
(Sighs) All right.
Let's see what we can dig up
on the Engles.
(Headsets beep on)
(Sirens wail)
(Phone rings)
Yeah.
Dan:
Put the daughter on.
Say something.
Hello?
Robyn:
Amy, are you okay?
Daddy's tied up and...
Dan: - That's enough.
Amy: - Mommy?!
Done.
Please,
just let me hear her again.
Please, just let me talk
to my baby again.
Mommy?
What's going on?
Nothing,
we're just behind schedule.
Gunman: You need me
to add some pressure?
(Muffled)
No. No.
No.
That's my show of good faith.
Now how 'bout yours?
Robyn:
I gave you everything.
You have everything.
If I had anything else,
it would be yours.
Dan: This is $33,000 and
some family souvenirs.
That's not enough.
Don't hurt them, okay?
We can work this out.
How? How?!
We don't have time!
My employer's
not the kind of guy
who "works this out"!
I've seen what happens
to people who let him down.
I have nothing else!
Then make some calls!
Move some clients'
money around,
get something transferred.
Even if I did,
the bank's already flagged me,
I can't turn that into cash.
(Sobbing) Okay, okay...
Okay, maybe there's one way.
It's our only option left,
I think I can do it.
Make it happen.
(Sirens wail)
Jules:
Okay, thank you.
All right, the brokerage firm
that Robyn works for
says she's a great employee.
High achiever,
hard-worker.
Yeah, I'm looking
at their bank records.
They've just re-mortgaged
their house,
and she's been supporting
the family
single-handed for months.
Jules: Now her husband,
Tim, on the other hand,
lost his job about a year ago.
"Performance issues,"
"problems at home."
Ah, you lose your job
it's gonna be a strain
on a marriage,
especially when your partner's
a winner.
Jules: And a lot of men
are not good with that.
Resentment issues,
insecurities, secrets.
Spike: Organized crime
says Dan Lefebvre's
into collections and loans.
So he's a loan shark.
Parker: Robyn's
husband is unemployed;
Maybe he's got a little secret
and maybe it involves
borrowing money
from this Dan Lefebvre.
So Dan takes Tim
and his daughter collateral
and then sends the wife
to go drain the accounts?
Parker: Today might be the first
time she even knew he had a problem.
Something doesn't seem right.
Raf: Yeah.
Why is a loan shark robbing banks?
Maybe because
he's under pressure himself.
(Sirens wail)
(Engines roar)
Amy:
I want to talk to my mom!
Gunman: You're gonna have
to keep your voice down
or I'm gonna duct tape you
like I did your dad.
Is that what you want?
Sit down.
- Sit down!
- Let me go!
(Key beeps)
The husband's immobilized...
He's vulnerable.
Girl's in range
of his weapon too.
We have to isolate him.
I got a plan.
Amy:
(Whimpers)
Tim: (Muffled pleas) No!
No-no-no-no!
Stop!
(Fire alarm beeps)
Amy: - Fire!
Tim: - Please. Please.
Tim: - Undo her legs!
Amy: - Please! Help!
Amy and Tim: (Desperate pleas for help) Please!
Help! Undo her legs!
(Fire alarm beeps)
SRU: Police! SRU!
Get down on the ground!
Right there! Right there!
Right there!
Gunman:
(Grunts)
Sam:
Don't move.
Subject's secure.
Good job.
Jules:
Okay, you're okay.
Where's Robyn?
Do you have her?
Parker: We're gonna
find her right now.
Is there anyone who can
look after your daughter
while we talk?
It's gonna be okay.
Come here.
(Sniffles)
Yes, my parents,
their number's on the fridge.
I'll make the call.
Tim:
Sweetie, look at me, okay?
Omi and Opa are gonna come
and get you right now, okay?
So that I can talk
to the police.
(Cries)
Ed: Buddy, you're looking
at home invasion,
extortion,
unlawful confinement,
unlawful firearm...
Raf:
On top of previous offenses.
Sam: So unless you help us
find Robyn Engles right now,
you're looking
at a lifelong sentence.
Gunman:
I give anything up,
I might as well slit
my own throat.
Yeah? Well maybe
that's not such a bad idea.
She cleared out
the bank accounts?
(Breathes shakily)
Everything?
And the safety deposit box too.
Tim:
Why?
Now we're not here
to judge you.
If you've developed
some kind of dependency,
whether it's substance abuse
or gambling,
we know you've been struggling
with unemployment.
I am not the one
with the gambling dependancy.
It's Robyn?
Yeah, (Sniffles)
She's the reason
we are $300,000 in debt.
(Takes a calming breath)
She's been playing the tables
for years.
That's how I lost my job.
'Cause I never knew what time
I'd be getting to work
in the morning,
or when I'd have to leave.
'Cause sometimes, Robyn,
she would stay at the tables
all through the night
and, and...
She'd forget to pick up
our daughter at school.
Team one, you copy that?
Ed: Copy that. Thanks, boss.
Good news, we're done.
We got what we need, let's go.
Wait, you found 'em?
Ed: You had your chance
to get in the game,
it's a little late now.
Sam: I hope he doesn't find out
you were in police custody
when we got our break.
Gunman: Wait, you don't
know everything.
We know enough.
Gunman:
Did you know that, uh...
That Dan's got a thing for her?
Definitely something going on...
For months now.
I don't think the husband
even knows.
The money Dan loaned her?
He skimmed
from his bosses profits.
A hell of a risk.
He thought he could pay it back
before he noticed,
until yesterday
when he finally caught on.
Who caught on?
Was it Dan?
Gunman:
No, his boss.
Right, before Dan caught on.
No, before Harvey caught on.
Ed:
Oh, Harvey.
Harvey Micks.
Gunman:
Wait.
You guys said you already knew.
You'd think this guy
would recognize a bluff.
Gunman:
Look, please.
You can't say it was me
that told you.
We don't even know your name.
If Dan doesn't have the money
by noon today,
he's dead!
People disappear!
Robyn: You're sure
Micks isn't there?
He'll be here at noon.
You've got an hour.
(Inhales shakily) Okay.
(Van doors close)
Who's this Harvey Micks?
He's the top of the totem pole.
Organized crime had him
on three murders last year,
but nothing sticks.
Spike:
Three murders this year.
Four murders last year.
Harvey Micks
has got expensive lawyers
and lots of employees willing
to take the fall for him.
You don't wanna get invited
to this guy's company picnic.
Ed: So Harvey Micks finds out
that Dan's stealing his money
to prop up a losing player.
Sam: He calls in the money
, full amount, no mercy.
That's how he does business.
And Robyn owes what, $300,000?
Tim: Yeah, that's after paying
Dan back twice that amount.
Jules:
She only has $30.
How's she gonna turn that
into $300?
You gamble it.
Ed:
He's running out of options.
Now, vic said
she's a good player.
Tim: Well, maybe she's
gone back to the casino.
Micks' place,
where she's in debt?
Tim: Yeah. It's the highest
stakes table in town.
It's where she's gone,
I'm sure of it.
Okay, let's move.
We'll keep talking.
Ed:
Okay, let's get to the casino,
tell Robyn her family's okay
and get her outta there safe.
(Low hum of chatter)
(Cards flutter)
(Roulette wheel whirs nearby,
poker chips clink)
Tim:
She's good.
I mean look at her job, right?
Stock-trader.
Same buzz.
They get paid to gamble.
Still a big leap from there
to Harvey Micks.
Tim: Yeah, it was a
broker from work.
Introduced her.
After the markets closed,
she used to go
to these private casinos,
open around the clock.
(Sighs heavily)
All it took was one bad game.
Parker:
You try to help her stop?
Yeah.
Two months ago,
I woke up and she was gone.
Again.
(Casino chips clatter)
Tim: You are coming
home with me right now.
Let's go.
Robyn: I... yeah, do you
know how much I just lost?
I can't leave.
What're you gonna play with?
We have nothing.
Dan'll give me more.
He knows I'll win it back.
I don't care
about winning it back.
I want you home,
it's four in the morning.
- Let's go, come on.
- I can't!
You want me to tell Amy that?
Huh?
When she wakes up
in the morning...
Yeah, don't do that to me!
You don't do that to us.
You look at me.
Because this is it.
This is your last chance.
I love you.
But if you do not walk
out of here with me
right now,
we will not be there
when you get home.
Do you hear me?
Everything all right, Robyn?
Tim:
Robyn...
Dan: Maybe you should
give her some space, Tim.
15 years of marriage
doesn't end this way, Robyn.
Robyn.
Tim:
Get your hand off my wife!
Robyn...
(Crying)
Please...
Robyn:
(Crying)
I'm sorry.
(Crying) I'm so sorry.
Tim:
She did it.
She stopped.
She's so strong.
She had not been near a table
in two months.
We were paying Dan back
on a regular schedule
and I was working like crazy
to find a job...
And then someone knocks
on your door this morning.
Tim:
Yeah.
Now she's playing again.
You try anything,
I call your house
and my guy starts
applying pressure.
You won't have to;
I just did a hundred thou.
Yeah, well, you better
make it three by noon
or he makes an example
of both of us,
and we end up in a dumpster.
You're distracting me.
Get moving.
Yeah.
(Sirens wail)
There's the van.
Spike:
This place is big.
Nightclub closed down
last year,
but judging
by the electricity bills,
it's still seeing
some serious action.
The casino's operated
out of a room inside.
Sam, what's the John street
exit look like?
Okay...
Metal doors, no handle,
and there's a security camera.
No stealth entry.
It's a problem.
Spike: There's another
entrance in the alleyway.
Ed, you see that one?
Ed: Kitty corner
to the parking lot, yeah.
Parker:
Must be the player's entrance.
With illegal gambling,
we're looking at guns,
exit strategies.
Spike, anyway we can
get a look inside?
Spike: I'm picking up a signal
from a wireless network.
Chances are that's carrying
their CCTV.
If I can decrypt the password,
their cameras
become our cameras.
And you can just do that, huh?
Spike: That's a well-kept secret:
Anyone with wireless can do it,
you just gotta
crack the password.
Jules: Confined space,
potential hostage,
and Dan's facing an ultimatum
from Harvey Micks.
Yeah, that's a of pressure.
He sees us,
he could get violent.
So how do we isolate the threat
without going inside?
We separate 'em.
I'll go in undercover.
Let Robyn know
her family's safe,
and then there's nothing
keeping her there.
What do you think?
Can't just pull up a chair
and have a chat.
Jules, I can if I've got cards
in my hand.
Dan: So listen,
everything's on track.
That means you have it all.
Dan:
Yeah, the full amount.
I'm um... I'm uptown now,
so how about I meet you
down at the club at two.
Micks: Did you just say
two o'clock, Dan?
I know didn't hear you
say that,
because if you did...
Dan:
Okay, noon like we said,
noon's good.
I'll, uh...
I'll see you then.
(Half laughs, ends phone call)
Place like this,
they're looking for trouble.
They frisk me, they find a gun,
it's all over.
So no weapon, no wire.
That's it.
Spike:
Guys, I see gamblers.
I'm in.
Parker: Did you just guess
at the wireless password?
No, but I guessed
that Harvey's IT guys
are one step behind
the highly illegal
password-cracking software
to which I subscribe.
Spike, sometimes you scare me.
Spike:
I scare myself sometimes.
Patching the cameras through
right now...
There's no audio.
Sam: Okay, button mic, one-way.
We hear what Ed hears.
I'll hotwire the van;
Block the John street exit.
We secure the alley,
stealth the service entrance.
Robyn: (Laughs) Oh my God.
Now way!
What's that, $120?
Bet faster.
They only deal one hand
at a time.
So bet more.
Do you wanna take my seat?
Parker: Now, you're sure
he didn't see your face
in the alley?
We can do this.
All right,
let's get you dressed.
How you doing?
Ed's entering the nightclub,
security's escorting him.
(Footsteps clomp on stairs)
(Wand feedback squeals
and beeps)
Spike: Weapons check
, single round sidearms.
(Low hum of chatter
throughout club)
Time to play.
(Casino chips clink)
Hey, buddy,
which one's the hot table?
Thanks.
Spike:
One guard by the money...
Tod's left...
And another guard
walking the floor.
That's one guard
in the nightclub,
four guards in the casino.
Sam:
Spike, I'm on John street.
Copy, Sam.
I'm looping the John street
CCTV right now.
And stand by...
And...
(Computer key beeps)
Freeze frame.
Go, go,
before someone notices
the time code.
John street exit secure.
I'm outta camera range.
Spike:
Copy.
(Lively chatter)
Boss, your guard's coming back
through the players entrance
right now.
How you doing, sir?
Don't even think about
touching that alarm.
Alley secure.
Raf?
Raf:
One guard.
We got a cam too.
Spike: Camera five, got it.
Looping the feed.
(Keys clack, computer beeps)
Go!
(Footsteps clomp)
Sam:
Excuse me.
Hands in the air,
no moving, no noise.
Sam:
Alpha in.
Spike:
Smooth, guys.
All right, Ed's making his way
to the cashier.
Looking good.
(Lively chatter)
(Chips clink onto betting)
Cashier: Welcome
back, Mr. Yorski.
Your house account toy?
Uh, what do I got in there?
$55,000.
Ed: Um... thirty.
Thirty to start.
Excellent, thank you.
Green light on Ed's entry.
All clear so far.
(Chip clinks on betting pile)
Dealer:
Welcome to the table, sir.
Ed: - Hey..
Adele: : - Lines are 500 to 1000.
Hey, how're you doing??
Let's do it.
Contact.
Raf:
No noise.
We're secure.
We have uniforms
at all entrances.
Casino is contained.
Parker:
That's good work.
Spike, keep the uniforms
out of range
until it's time.
Spike:
Copy.
Jules:
It's up to Ed now.
Ed: Well, somebody's gotta
put my kids through school.
Might as well be you.
Up another 10.
Dealer:
10 to stay.
You're not gonna regret
investing in their future.
Spike: Hold on, Harvey
Micks is in the house.
He's making an entrance.
He's got a bodyguard
shadowing him.
Parker: I thought the
casino was sealed.
Spike: He came in from the back
, outside of camera range.
Must be an office somewhere.
Looks like he's been
in the building the whole time.
Jules:
Dan's backed against a corner.
Robyn hasn't had enough
time yet.
Dan:
It's noon.
(Stammers nervously)
No, no, Robyn, Micks is here.
All in.
(Chips clink)
Dealer:
Bets to you, sir.
Hey, hey, hey.
- Problem?
- You showed him your card.
What're you talking 'bout?
When she checked her down card,
she let him see it.
I did not.
Dan:
Buddy, back off.
Wait, is this some kind
of scam here?
I saw her!
Spike: Team one, stand by.
Ed's making the play.
Player:
Look, I didn't see anything!
I don't even know her.
She's cheating.
Dan:
No, she's not cheating.
Play, bet or fold.
Re-deal.
Robyn: No, just...
You can't do that.
Do you know
what I was sitting on?
Shouldn't have shown him
your card.
Robyn:
I didn't show him my cards.
I'm gonna have to ask you two
to sit out the next hand.
Dan: - Come on!
Dealer: - Cool off.
You're free to rejoin the game
after the next hand.
Fine.
- Sit down.
- I just need space, okay?
Just, I need some space.
Dan: 30 seconds,
you're back in this chair.
Okay.
(Casino chips clatter,
patrons chatter)
- Mr. Micks.
- Dan.
I didn't see you come in.
I didn't.
You know you're pretty
entertaining
on the closed circuit tv.
I've been watching you
lie your ass off to me
while that one over there
tries to save it.
How's she doing anyway?
That new guy just fouled
the hand.
Otherwise, I'm almost there.
Almost, Dan?
That's not good enough.
Now's the time
if you wanna leave here
breathing.
Spike:
That's the signal.
He's going for extraction.
Okay, ready entry.
Priority is on Dan.
He's armed,
he's got the least to lose.
Dan:
Harvey, come on, I...
Who was that guy?
(Stammers) I'm on it.
(Exhales shakily, emotional)
Ed:
Robyn, my name's Ed Lane.
I'm a police officer
with the
Strategic Response Unit.
Robyn: Police?
Ed: It's okay, it's over.
I'm here to help you.
Your family's safe,
they're not gonna be harmed.
We've got Tim downstairs, okay?
Tim is here?
And Amy?
Amy's fine, too,
just come with me, all right.
It's okay, it's okay.
Amy's fine.
I need you come with me
before Dan causes anymore
trouble,
all right?
The guy at my table?
Okay, thanks.
The bald guy at my table?
It's Roman Yorski.
No, Dan,
that's not Roman Yorksi.
I know Roman Yorski.
So who is it?
Ed: We gotta move now and
we gotta move fast, okay?
Robyn: - Okay.
Ed: - Let's go.
Ed:
Okay, come on.
It's gonna be all right.
Robyn:
(Whimpers)
- Who are you?
- Roman Yorski.
Look, we're just leaving.
No you're not.
Who are you?
It's a simple question.
Look, my friend here's
gotta go.
Spike:
Guys, Ed's been made.
Just keep it verbal, Eddie,
low-key.
Just... low-key,
Dan: Ten minutes ago
you were complete strangers
and now you're visiting
in the ladies'.
Who is he?
Maybe he's a cop?
Take them out back,
both of them.
No, no, no, no,
it's under control.
I'm taking care of it, 'kay?
You both need to follow me.
- Please, right now.
- Let her go.
I said come with me,
right now!
Weapon's out!
Go, go, go!
Sam and Jules:
Police! Police! SRU!
Hands in the air!
Hands where I can see them!
Jules: On the ground!
On the ground now!
(Cacophony of shouting)
Dan:
Back off!
Danny, you're a dead man.
SRU and patrons:
(Cacophony of shouting)
Ed:
Dan...
Dan's got Robyn.
They're heading
for the rear exit.
Parker: Quickly as
possible, clear the room.
Spike:
Boss, Dan's run out the back.
Ed's in pursuit.
Dan:
Let's go!
(Door clunks)
Dan:
Dammit!
Robyn:
(Cries)
Ed:
Dan, the building's surrounded.
Dan:
Stay back!
Okay.
I'm not gonna come any closer.
But there's no way
outta here, Dan.
Shut the door behind you.
You let anyone in here,
she dies, got it?
I got it.
All right?
Door's shut, it's all good.
(Door shuts)
Nobody else is getting in here,
okay.
Now just calm down,
we're not in any rush.
Ed's negotiating.
Ed knows we're here.
He'll bring Dan toward us.
Fall back, take cover.
Jules:
Okay, let's go.
Sam: - I'll take point.
Parker: - Let's get 'em out.
Just relax.
Take a breath, buddy.
Robyn:
(Breathes shakily)
Dan:
You brought him in here?
- You did this to me?
- What?
Dan:
We were this close,
but you had to bring
the police.
Robyn:
Why would I do that, Dan?
You had a guy with a gun
to my little girl's head.
My husband!
Dan: Micks had my
back up against a wall,
I did what I had to do.
No, you did not have
to steal from the man
in the first place.
- I did it for you.
- Why?
Why?
You coulda just said no to me.
Stopped me.
I wish you had.
I was hooked.
That feeling that...
No matter what crap
you're dealt,
you can win if you can play it.
Until you can't
and you drag your whole family
into hell with you.
I couldn't say no either,
Robyn.
You think I would have
put it on the line
for anyone else?
I mean, all this time, you...
I thought maybe
we had something.
Didn't we?
You had money, Dan.
I needed you.
But I love my husband.
Ed:
Dan...
Than good luck to you.
Dan... Dan!
Good luck to you.
Ed: - Dan!
Dan: - You're nice future...
Put the gun down!
Dan: She's my shield.
She's gonna get me outta here.
Ed:
Dan!
Dan: I'm gonna back
out the way we came in.
Ed:
Okay.
Down on the ground.
Down!
Stay back!
Clear out.
I want everybody out.
We're leaving.
You're gonna give me car keys
and if anyone tries to stop us
I will shoot her,
you understand?
Parker: No one's going
to interfere, Dan.
Dan: Then put your weapons
down and back off.
Team one, stand down.
Parker:
We're not aiming at you, Dan.
You can put that gun away.
He's not gonna shoot me.
Dan:
I swear I will.
Just try me.
No one's gonna do anything.
We're just going to clear
the way, okay?
No, you can take him.
He won't shoot me.
I know he won't.
Shut up, Robyn!
All in.
Robyn...
Robyn:
Please, Dan, it's over.
Do not raise your weapon, Dan.
Dan!
Ed:
Dan, just put the gun down.
Dan, just give me the gun.
Let Robyn go home
to her family.
It's all right, buddy.
(Stifled sob)
Gimme the gun.
Let Robyn go home
to her family.
(Whimpering)
It's over.
That's it.
Come on, Dan.
Just give me the gun, Dan.
Let Robyn go home
to her family.
It's okay.
Micks is in cuffs,
we're good here.
(Breathes shakily) I'm sorry.
Parker:
Subject's secured.
Sam, good work.
(Handcuffs rasp)
♪
♪ underneath the clothes
we're wearing ♪
♪ scars we all carry ♪
♪ some that don't fade ♪
♪ and they read just like
a road map ♪
♪ time cuts a deep track ♪
♪ through skin and vein ♪
♪ do you know everyone falls ♪
♪ sometimes don't they all ♪
♪ you know Bridges get burned ♪
♪ sometimes as we cross ♪
♪ don't we all... ♪
♪ fall... ♪
♪
What's going on?
(Inhales and sighs)
So, Sam...
Yeah.
I mean, you two pulled it
together on that call.
- He's good.
- I know he is.
He's hitting the glass ceiling.
He wants to lead a team.
Yeah. Something like that.
Something you're not saying?
What I'm saying is,
is that you, my friend,
are not going anywhere.
You know, I don't know,
maybe we could...
Let him spread his wings
a little bit.
Let him take a few calls,
give him incentive.
Or we give him your job.
Put him in the command truck,
requisition a dress.
You know I outrank you, right?
That's funny.
Both:
(Hearty laughter)
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com