I vow to be true, always.
I vow to always be yours.
Yeah!
Previously on "flashpoint":
Team, we're
looking at another bomb
that just went off downtown.
We're looking at terror.
Steve!
- Ed!
- Where is he?
Phone signal's here,
man, it's gotta be him.
Clark! Clark!
Donna, if there's no timer
on the bomb,
then you can wait
till I get there!
No, I can handle it.
How many wires do you see?
Uh...
Eighteen.
Donna, how's our subject?
Quiet, co-operative -
could be the gun on his head.
Boss, this make
any sense to you?
If he was gonna blow
himself up,
why didn't he already do it?
This is your very last chance.
Tell me where the detonator is
right now!
Right now!
What're you looking at?
What do you see, Donna?
I got a blinking camera
in the ceiling.
Get outta there now!
Donna, what's happening?
Eddie...
Move!
Boss!
I'm okay.
Holt wasn't the bomber,
he was the bait, Eddie.
She's gone, Eddie.
She was right in front of him.
Sonofabitch!
Clark! Clark!
Steve, get in here!
Get the oxygen mask in there!
Clark!
Let's clear the door!
Let's clear it!
Pull up! Get in there!
Clark, I'm here.
You're gonna be okay, buddy,
I'm right here.
Okay, you're gonna be okay.
Clark?
Okay, let's get a board!
I need a board!
Okay, let's get that board!
Let's get that board down here!
Okay, I'm right with you.
Okay, okay.
Okay. All right.
What...
What happened?
You're okay, you're okay.
We're gonna take care of you,
all right?
They got him!
Guys, I got him.
We're good.
We're good here.
That's great. You
stay with him, Eddie.
You gotta stay back.
My people need to see
if the structure
of the building's compromised
first.
All right.
Okay?
Oh God...
Hey! I need your cruiser,
there's another bomb.
Hey, I told
you to stay outside!
There's nothing you can do
to help here.
Look, my people
are still in there.
I'm sorry. It
was over in a second.
Supporting wall is compromised.
It's not safe.
I'll show you another way in.
All right, boys, let's go!
Got it. Yeah.
Okay, easy.
We got you.
We got you, okay.
- Easy, easy.
- Easy, guys.
Hey. He's gonna be okay.
He's getting an IV started,
and, you know, he's okay,
he's conscious.
Tell me everything,
don't leave anything out.
Soph, he's got a broken
leg, a broken wrist.
I think he's got
some broken ribs.
I'm telling you
everything I know.
Is he okay?
Where are you taking him?
I'll meet you there!
No, no.
Soph, stay at home with Izzie.
Just stay safe.
It's not over, okay?
I'm gonna take him
to the hospital,
we're gonna get him x-rayed,
we're gonna check him out.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Just tell him
I love him, okay?
- Ed, we're ready to move.
- Okay, Soph, I gotta go.
Eddie,
please, be careful.
I will, okay? I love you.
Bye.
We have to get
out of here right now,
it's not safe!
Everyone out, now!
We have to set a new perimeter.
We got a problem -
a big problem.
I got really high readings
in there.
Team one, new deal.
Okay.
Let's get you fixed up.
You ready to ride?
- I'm gonna be okay?
- You're gonna be fine.
You gotta go, dad.
I'm not going anywhere.
No, dad, please!
You gotta get this guy.
Ed, coming or going?
No, hang on, hang on.
Buddy, I'm not going...
Dad, no, okay?
You gotta do this!
I'm gonna be fine. Please?
Are you sure?
Yes.
Okay. Okay,
I'll see you at home.
I love you.
Your mom and I love you.
I love you too.
Team one, I'm coming to you.
What's happening?
We're not allowed
to cross the perimeter.
Boss, what's going on?
Team, just hang tight.
Boss!
No, don't! Don't!
Stay back!
Why? What's going on?
Exposed to radiation.
It was a dirty bomb.
All right, guys,
you know the drill.
I've gotta go offline,
get scrubbed,
get blood tests.
I need you to stay on task.
Do you copy?
Copy that, boss.
Now, someone dropped
a trail of breadcrumbs
leading us right here,
leading us to the wrong man.
He watched as this man died.
Someone hated Anson Holt
personally.
Holt was a sadist;
Sadists have victims.
And he was arrested
for abusive experiments...
- Officer!
- I'm not done yet!
They were performed right here.
The manifesto said
it began here;
we're looking for
one of his students.
What just happened?
- He just signed off.
-  Why?
His headset's contaminated.
He's gotta get himself
cleaned up.
We can't just drop contact.
You're right.
Okay, guys, let's do this!
Sam, coordinate
with the military.
We need more boots
on the ground now!
Flashpoint 05x13
Keep the Peace Part 2
Original Air Date December 13, 2013
==sync, correction by dcdah==
www.addic7ed.com
Okay, outer layers off.
Equipment, cell phones,
gloves...
Anything that's exposed
stays here.
The material released
by the device is Caesium 137.
You're gonna be taking one gram
of Prussian Blue.
It binds to the Caesium,
moves it faster through
your digestive system.
I'm gonna be sick.
Okay, okay.
Here.
What's your name, son?
Jason. Do you know how
dirty bombs work, Jason?
They spray radioactive
material,
contaminate the area.
They spread fear;
That's the bomber's point.
The good news is,
fear is easy to treat.
A dose of facts
usually gets you results.
How long were you in there?
Not too long.
Okay, demron blankets.
You wrap them tight
around your body.
But we were already exposed.
It's all right,
it protects others
from exposure to us.
It's just a precaution.
So this was hidden
at the prof's house.
It looks like Holt kept
the video archives
of his experiment.
Subjects...
Eight students.
Okay, it's a start.
Get these names to Winnie.
Firewalled.
The video server
he was using in there,
I can't trace it,
I can't trace the IP.
I have no idea where
he was watching this from.
Yeah?
Go ahead, Winnie.
Colonel, wind's
10k South, southeast.
That means from here
to the lake,
we've gotta keep everyone
inside their houses.
Windows shut, vents sealed.
Duct tape, plastic,
whatever's available.
We're upwind on the north side.
You can stage here.
Anything comes in contact
with the ash or the debris,
seal it in a plastic bag,
shower off immediately!
Guys, we can cross
"big banking" off the list;
team two just defused a bomb
at the Hudson Trust head office.
Okay, okay, good news.
Team one, the
bomber's just called 911
and boss is offline.
Copy that, Winnie.
Jules, you take this.
Okay, Winnie,
patch me through.
This is Jules Callaghan
with the Police Strategic
Response Unit.
Where's my other puppet?
He's in the field right now.
You got what you wanted;
The manifesto's out there.
You're gonna be famous.
You want to tell us
what your name is?
Why would I
make it that easy?
That's right, the last
time you made it that easy,
we walked right into it.
You sent the manifesto
from a smartphone
spoofed to Anson Holt's name.
Very good.
Then pointed us
straight here to the lab.
And Holt walked
right into it, too.
And then you
strapped a bomb on him,
made him watch the news,
made him watch what you'd done.
While I watched him sit
there too scared to even breathe!
You've proven your point.
I think the five remaining bombs
are redundant.
How'd you
know there were five?
Where are they?
You think people know fear yet?
This is nothing.
This isn't fear,
this is an inconvenience.
People still have illusions
someone's looking out for them.
Police, paramedics,
government, doctors...
Authority figures.
You think you can trust them?
It's all lies, it's smoke,
and when people
understand that,
when they realize
no one's looking out for you...
Then they'll know fear.
Then they'll grow up.
Five down, five to go.
Confirming a
total of ten bombs,
but still no closer
to who this guy is.
Maybe a little closer.
Those eight participants
in Holt's study,
how many of them
know how to set up a firewall?
We're looking for the one
with the most security measures.
But four of the subject's
students
have moved to other cities.
Four of them are still local,
three of them have open IP's,
no security.
Leaving one
Marcus Faber.
Winnie, we need an address!
Marcus Faber,
266 Robinson Street.
Twenty-five years old,
parents deceased.
He dropped out
of Brookfield University,
but before that he actually
attended schools for the gifted
as a child.
He skipped grades twice.
Well, any trouble with the law?
Six months in jail for assault,
charges for vagrancy,
that's it.
Does he work?
Uh... no tax records
filed, so nothing on the books.
Here, he took a job
three months ago
as a telephone technician.
That lines up with
the bomb's wiring!
And he would've had the access
to plant them.
This has gotta be our guy.
Thank you.
Sergeant Parker!
This came from SRU.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you, Winnie!
Thank you, son.
Let's go, guys, hard and fast.
Let's move!
Let's move now!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Police! Police!
Get down!
Clear!
Okay, team,
let's tear this place apart!
We've gotta get ahead
of him here...
Equipment, plans, anything!
Right here! We've
got a map on the wall!
Has he marked the targets?
- Negative!
- Keep looking!
What's this?
Spike, bomb components!
Yep.
Caesium 137.
Same stuff Hazmat found.
Trace amounts...
It's not dangerous
at this level.
H8, K6, G11.
Some kind of code?
Is that some kind of datasheet?
This is old school.
These are the targets.
Map coordinates.
The 911 call centre.
H8, Brookfield University.
We got the Federal Building,
City Hall.
K6, Hudson Trust,
that was team two's package.
Okay, team, I'm here, I
heard the last part of that.
We've got the five
remaining targets,
and the subject
is Marcus Faber.
G11, police station
on College Street!
EMS headquarters, and
there's a TV station.
Okay, what about a timeline?
He's on a half-hour schedule.
The lab was the last one to go,
which one's next?
There's no indication.
All right, team, I'm scrubbed.
I'm not waiting
for my blood test.
You've got too much
ground to cover.
Greg, you wait until
the blood work gets back,
you hear me?
We got this.
Okay.
All right, Jules,
let's get inside
this guy's head, then.
We've got video
on Holt's experiment.
Marcus was one of his students.
I'm gonna stream it to you.
It's gonna take a minute though
'cause there's a lot to upload.
Copy that.
And another student,
Tony James, lives close by.
I'm gonna go talk to him,
get his take on Marcus.
Okay now, the rest of us,
we're gonna split into
rapid intervention teams:
One SRU, one EMS,
one firefighter.
Each team takes a target,
we find the bomb, we defuse it.
Spike's gonna talk us through
the tech.
- Let's go.
- Wait a minute!
We're short one bomb.
What do you mean, Spike?
Ten targets.
He's written down
nine locations.
We're missing one.
Where's the last bomb?
Guys, we need you
outta here now!
Copy that.
Radiation level?
Uh, clean so far.
Okay, the floorplans have
the server on the second floor.
Are we good?
Yeah, it's all good.
Let's get it done.
Team one, status?
Bravo team at the emergency
medical services building.
Charlie team
at Adelaide Systems.
Delta team, we're
at the TV station.
- Team...
- Boss?
I know this is hard.
We're split up,
we don't know
what we're walking into.
But today's like any day;
We walk through doors together,
we're in each other's ears,
and we've got
each other covered.
And even though
I'm not there with you,
my hand is on your backs,
and don't forget that.
It works both ways, Greg.
Negative for radiation.
We're good.
Okay. Clear out, guys,
only one man downrange.
Spike, I got a picture,
it's coming to you.
Okay, silver lining,
our bomber's
a creature of habit.
It's the same device
he used at the call centre.
Okay, guys, radiation levels?
Negative for bravo.
Negative for Charlie.
Okay, guys, I'm the only one
that needs to be here.
Okay, timers!
Mine's a little over
thirty-five minutes.
Ed, what do you got?
I got fourteen minutes.
Twenty-three and change.
He's picking up the pace.
Guys, it looks like
I got the short straw.
Five minutes
and thirty seconds.
Okay, guys, I need you
to get outta here now,
make sure
this building's clear!
Five minutes...
What the hell am I doing here?
Okay, Spike,
just focus on Sam, okay?
Spike, we're gonna
follow along.
Just focus on Sam.
Yeah.
Spike, what happened to Lou...
was a sacrifice he chose.
It's the reason
you're still with us.
But that's not going
to happen today,
you know that, right?
Yeah, I know that, boss.
Okay.
Okay, Spike, what do we do?
All right, Sam, guys,
take out your meters,
and I want you to check
the resistance, okay?
Then I need you to take out
your tac knives.
Marcus was a
couple of years younger.
He was gifted,
and, I don't know, different.
How?
Awkward, vulnerable.
You met him through
Anson Holt's study?
We were all honoured
to be chosen.
I mean, there were fistfights
just to get into
this guy's seminars.
What'd you do when you realized
that the study was a bit more
than you bargained for?
He told us, "what
happens in the lab,
stays in the lab,"
and we did what he said.
I mean, this is Anson Holt.
He made us tell him
what we loved,
what was precious,
what gave us hope,
what we...
Eyes up!
What our secrets were,
what we believed in.
He took it in.
Each of us had to sit
in the "hot seat"...
Eyes up! Keep your
eyes on the monitor!
Camera in our face,
with all the other
students watching,
while he tore us apart.
And then Holt started
giving us medication.
We never knew
if it was real or placebo.
He made us watch these DVDs.
- Eyes up!
- Torture...
Keep your eyes focused!
Snuff films.
It was...
Look up!
It was sickening.
Tony, I need
you to stay focused.
Tony, stay focused!
Tony!
I can't!
Keep your eyes on the monitors!
He's just a little kid!
- He's what?!
- He's a little boy!
He is what?!
A victim! He's a victim!
That's right, Tony.
He's a victim.
He made us watch
them again, and again,
'til you keep seeing them
all day, and all night,
and I couldn't stand it!
They found my
son in his residence.
He'd taken a bottle
of sleeping pills.
I brought him home,
I finally got him to talk.
I talked to a lawyer,
I called other parents.
I tried to get a lawsuit going.
I didn't see any records
of charges being laid.
The university came back
with a huge settlement offer
on condition of silence.
I just wanted
it all to be over.
Thank you, Tony.
My name is Marcus Faber,
I'm nineteen years old.
Well, I'm eighteen.
Nineteen in May.
Tell me, Marcus...
what do you love?
Who do you think
can protect you?
This is fear, Marcus.
It owns you now.
You're just another victim,
and you know what happens
to victims, don't you?
Victims get what
they've got coming!
- Sergeant Parker?
- Yeah.
We've got the results
of your blood work.
You're gonna wanna follow up,
but you're a lucky man.
You're good to go.
Oh, thank you!
Okay, team, how we doing?
Okay, careful now,
carefully put the dry ice in
with the acetone.
Sam, how're you doing?
I'm still trying
to expose the switch.
I'm going as fast as I can.
You go as
careful as you can.
Right.
Fast and careful.
- And safe.
- I know, Spike!
I'm cooling it down now.
I'm under ninety seconds.
Sam, you're running
out of time.
You need to get outta there,
buddy.
Building's not clear.
Okay, Sam, you're not gonna
have enough time to do this.
You need to get outta there
right now.
Team, you just
stay focused on your task.
Hey, boss, I
talked to Tony James.
These kids were young, bright,
eager to please,
trusted authority.
He used that authority
to break 'em down.
Jules, Jules, wait.
Winnie sent me the files.
They all took
the settlement money.
Four of 'em left town,
two of 'em are in drug rehab,
and one's in jail.
You either lash out
or you self-destruct.
Jules, just
stop, all right?
Just go to channel one.
It's Sam.
Sam, what's going on?
I've got time.
Sam, no, you do not!
Sam, do you need
to get outta there?
It's working, I've got this.
Sam!
It's working;
Temperature's going down.
It's minus thirty-five degrees.
Sam, you drop your tools
right now,
and you get yourself outta there
right now!
Come on...
Sam, listen to him!
Minus thirty-eight degrees!
Sam, you listen to him!
It's almost there!
Sam, we will not
lose each other today!
Sam?
Sam, get out!
Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Sam, get out of there now!
Get out, Sam!
Sam!
Sam, talk to me.
Sam, talk to me!
Okay, team...
team, I need you to hear me
right now.
I need you to keep safe.
Spike? Spike!
You listen to me, all right?
We still need you, we all do,
and whatever happened,
you need to keep going.
You hear me?
You keep going!
You all do!
Okay.
What the boss said, guys.
Trust me,
you don't wanna do this
the hard way.
Sam Braddock, you do not
do that to me again.
Okay, Sam, get yourself
cleaned up, all right?
That's the last bomb
he's gonna blow up today!
Okay, guys, let's do this!
Okay, Spike,
temperature's dropping.
Thirty-eight,
thirty-eight five,
thirty-nine.
Okay, Ed, that
should be frozen solid.
Spike, "should be?"
No, it is, it is.
It's frozen solid.
Just lift the circuit board,
cut the blue wire.
Okay...
Boss, the bomb is defused.
I'm on my way.
Spike, I just froze
the tilt switch.
Copy that, Leah.
Same thing I told Ed.
Lift the circuit board,
cut the blue wire.
Clear!
Nice, Leah!
I'm on my way
to the stadium.
Okay, Jules,
let's just cut to the chase,
all right?
We gotta find that last bomb.
Let's nail who this guy is.
Yeah, I'm getting
mixed messages.
I'm with you.
The manifesto's all about
fighting back
against forces of control,
like he's on some twisted
mission to help people...
Free them from government,
or whatever.
Yeah, but if you're gonna
help people,
you don't kill their children.
This is about Marcus
being in control.
He doesn't wanna feel
like a victim anymore,
so he shows Holt,
beats him at his own game.
Shows the world
he's in control,
he's the boss.
This is about Marcus
being in control.
All right, I'm Marcus.
I'm gonna reduce my world
to black and white.
The strong and the weak.
Jules, I think I know
where the last bomb is.
I think it's right here.
The bomb's right there
in the stadium?
How can you be sure?
I'm not, but wouldn't it explain
why Marcus didn't have
the location of the last bomb?
Yes, and he wouldn't
have known it himself
until about an hour ago,
when they mentioned the triage
on the news.
Jules, a lot of these people
can't be moved easily.
It's gonna take a lot more time
than we might have.
Best chance is finding
that bomb,
and defusing it.
Okay, boss, if this
is a last-minute target,
he still could be there.
You watch yourself!
Okay, just send me a photo.
Now, listen, I don't
think talk is an option, okay?
He's not gonna wanna be
psychologized,
especially by a guy in uniform.
You are everything
that he hates.
Yeah, copy that.
Hey, I want you to meet me
over there.
Okay, boss, we'll get a
kit sent to you right away.
Meantime, your tac knife
is your best friend.
See if you can get an ohm meter
from a stadium tech.
This is the bomber,
his name is Marcus Faber.
Keep your weapons ready.
We're looking for packages,
wires, suitcases.
Check stairwells,
garbage cans, vents.
It could be anything, anywhere.
All right?
Communications
on channel three.
Good luck.
Greg, if you're Marcus,
you want maximum damage
from a single bomb, right?
Yeah, right.
He knows that bomb will not
take that stadium down,
and this is his grand finale.
Yeah. It's gonna be dirty.
Greg, he's gonna put that bomb
up somewhere high,
somewhere where everyone
in that stadium
will be exposed.
And the city outside, Eddie.
I'll keep you posted.
It's taking way too long.
Boss, Jules and
I are on the scene.
Evac's a mess here.
I've found the bomb,
top level, catwalk.
You were right, Eddie.
- I'm on my way up.
- Negative, negative.
Ed,
this one's definitely dirty.
I you need to clear
everyone away
and get everyone out of range.
Boss, are you sure?
Spike, CS 137.
I'm sending you a photo.
Boss, my bomb is defused,
I can be there in minutes.
Up high, maximum damage.
Caesium 137,
right next to the C4.
I've got access to a timer -
three minutes, forty seconds.
Officer, let's move
these people back!
Clear room for vehicles.
Copy that.
We need to get the
most critical out now!
Can you locate
the power supply?
Not that I can see.
Okay, it's gonna be underneath
just like all the other ones.
What about the detonator,
is that exposed?
Not that I can see, Spike.
That's 'cause he's got
it in the middle of the C4.
Okay, boss,
the first thing we gotta do,
we gotta make sure...
The anti-handling devices...
We gotta find those first,
okay?
So I want you to check
for leads.
Do you see any leads
going into the circuit?
Yeah, stand by.
Yes! Okay, perfect.
Get the ohm meter
and I want you to check
that circuit.
Winnie, we need every
available vehicle down here now!
Get the door!
Ohm meter's holding steady
at nine.
It means there's no
resistance in the circuit.
Yeah, is that a good thing?
That's a great thing, boss.
It means there's
no anti-handling devices.
There's a clear path
to the detonator
and the power supply.
He must've ran out of time
on this bomb or something.
Step by step,
what do I do next?
- Boss?
- Boss!
I'm taking fire.
He's here, it's him!
- Sam!
- Right behind you!
Okay, Spike, what do I do?
What do I do?
Get away from the bomb!
Boss, are you there?
Boss, you there?
Yeah,
just took it in the vest.
Spike, what do I do next?
Just lift the cover, boss!
Just lift the cover
and get underneath
to the power source.
Okay, Spike.
Oh! Agh!
Marcus?
Marcus, listen to me.
I know I'm not gonna try
to talk you down,
and I'm not gonna try
to talk you down
because I know you don't care.
Oh, you tried to hurt
those around me.
You killed kids,
you killed people I love,
and I know you don't feel
any fear anymore
because your message
is already out there.
That feels good, doesn't it?
Your will, your messages...
Will live on.
Mission accomplished.
Sever the wire!
Cut the wire
between the power supply
and the detonator.
Sorry...
Sorry it didn't work out
because I just stopped
your bomb...
And my team stopped
your other bombs.
Your message isn't going
anywhere.
Your message is going nowhere.
You're done!
You stay with me!
Subject neutralized.
Okay, okay, I got ya, I got ya.
We have an officer down!
We need EMS
to the upper level now!
I repeat, officer down!
- You're gonna be okay.
- Where's the medic?!
We need a medic up here now!
You're gonna be okay, buddy.
You stay with me, I got you.
I got you.
Stay with us,
dad, we're here!
Stay with us.
You did it, buddy,
you defused the bomb.
Are you trying to put Spike
out of a job? Huh?
I got you...
They're on their way.
We're gonna get you
out of this.
Hey, you remember
a couple years ago
when I had to shoot
Goran Tomasic,
and you said to me, buddy,
"you might wanna do the math
on all the 'I'm fine's."
I've never said thank you.
You're more than fine, buddy.
You're more than fine...
Stay with me.
No, you don't.
No, you don't!
Stay here!
We're not done!
No you don't!
Greg, don't leave me.
You're not going anywhere!
Greg, stay here!
Stay here! You're staying here!
Medic!
♪ And I will watch you
disappear ♪
♪ from my fortress over here ♪
♪ and I will never understand ♪
♪ every heart's a foreign land ♪
♪ and I'm so afraid to ♪
♪ so afraid to ♪
♪ love you ♪
♪ and I will turn my eyes away ♪
♪ from the harsh light
of your day ♪
♪ and I have slept through
pouring rain ♪
♪ it was all that kept me sane ♪
♪ and I'm so afraid to ♪
♪ love you ♪
Hey! What have I told you guys
about holding hands at the station.
We're off the clock boss.
Where's everybody?
They're just behind.
Ed... good speech.
Thank you.
He was a tough man.
Sadie! Look who's here.
Aunt Winnie and Uncle Spike.
She didn't fall asleep
in the car?
She didn't want
to miss any of the action.
She's all like "Where
am I going?
What kept you guys?
Greg, you forget the way
to the barn already?
Nice speech Ed.
Thank you.
Found out a lot about
this guy tonight.
Thank you buddy.  You said
some nice things tonight.
You're welcome.
Look, I hated to drag you outta
your retirement party early,
but I just thought that uh...
you know, it might be nice,
just us...
Last time as Team One.
Yep.
Here, let me take her.
Come on, Sadie! Yes!
There we go!
Oh, she's adorable!
Let's go for a walk!
Guys, to uh...
absent friends.
Mm-hmm.
To Donna and Lou.
Donna and Lou.
To the new team leader
of Team Three!
Thank you.  And to the new
head instructor at the academy,
Bravely teaching
the next generation.
- Congratulations.
- Yup.
And to sergeant Ed Lane,
for taking team one forward.
Sarge.
Cheers!
I miss it.
I miss it like hell.
I know you do.
But you're here Ed.
You're all here.
Yeah.
And I've got my hand
on your backs,
just like you've always had
your hands on mine.
Come on.
Team One.
==sync, correction by dcdah==
www.addic7ed.com