Hostage:
Agggghhhhh!
(Coughing)
(Gasping for breath)
(Lighter flicks open)
Ed:
Right there!
Third floor clear.
Copy, Sam.
That's it, building's clear.
Sam: They knew we were coming.
They probably escaped.
Ed:
How? The perimeter's secured.
The roof.
No.
(Traffic rumbles)
(Match flares)
(Phone keypad beeps)
(Phone rings)
(Phone beeps on)
I'm tired, Ruby.
You can't sleep all day, ba.
Come to the store.
I'll call you later.
(Phone beeps off)
(Sighs heavily)
(Phone clicks onto cradle)
(Flames roar, siren wails)
(Streetcar rumbles past)
(Gun magazines click)
Dean:
That was a great weekend.
Parker:
Yes, it was.
You'll come back soon, right?
Yeah... you know.
What is it?
(Sighs)
Well...
Look, mom...
Mom told me not to expect
too much from you.
You checked out once
and I guess she's just...
She's just worried
you might do it again.
I understand.
I mean, the truth is,
is that I've given her
a lot of reasons to worry.
Well, that was then though,
right?
I mean, you don't drink
anymore.
You're like a super cop
or something.
Totally different guy.
Oh, I'm still the same guy.
Buddy, I'm still the same guy.
I'm just uh...
I'm just a little wiser
that's all.
You have something to say?
No. No, it's cool.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Look, I'm sorry I couldn't
drive you to the airport.
Ah no, it's cool.
I'm not a kid anymore.
I get it.
Yeah, you are.
(Door chime jingles)
You thought
we wouldn't find out?
Where's your father?
Ruby:
He's not here.
Leave us alone.
(Struggling grunts)
Do you know how stupid you are?
(Cell keypad beeps)
Eh.
(Computer beeps)
(Pained cries)
Jimmy:
(Shouting in mandarin)
(Ruby pants, boxes clatter)
(Panting)
(Box tumbles, hangers scrape)
(Rattling door, bangs on door)
(Switch clunks, power fizzles)
(Footsteps scuffle)
(Mouse clicks)
(Ceramic shatters)
(Tight, frantic breaths)
(Soft metallic clanking)
(Switchblade snaps open)
(Sirens wail)
Winnie: "Shang-Hai imports"
is at Huron and Dundas.
I've dialed back
that 911 caller,
he says he saw two men
in the store,
one had a gun.
His first name's Terrence.
He's not giving me a last name.
I'm putting him through
to you now.
Terrence,
my name is
Sergeant Greg Parker.
I'm with the police
Strategic Response Unit.
Terrence:
You need to hurry.
We're on our way.
Where are you?
I'm across the street
from the shop.
Ed: We're minutes
away, Terrence.
How many assailants are there?
Terrence: Uh, two, and
one of them's got a gun.
I have to go,
they might see me.
Okay, you go to a safer place,
but stay on the line
with me, please.
I need more information.
Just hurry, please.
Gunman:
Hey!
Agh!
(Gun clatters)
Phu!
Ruby:
Don't move!
(Two gunshots pop)
Terrence?
You still with me?
They shot her.
You heard gunfire?
How many shots?
Terrence: Two, I think.
I have to go.
Terrence, don't go.
Terrence, stay on the line
with me, please.
He hung up.
Parker: Winnie, he knows her.
See if you can track him down.
And get EMS on scene,
there may be wounded.
Ed:
Guys, let's set up a perimeter.
Raf, Jules, with me at front.
Sam: Spike and I will
stage in the alley,
wait for your go.
Ed:
Copy.
(Sirens wail)
Sam?
Sam:
Door's open.
Okay, let's move.
(Gate clanks open)
(Door opens,
door chimes jingle)
Ed, Jules and Raf:
Police! SRU! SRU! Police!
Jules.
Police!
Come out with your hands up.
(Beads clatter)
Jules and Ed:
Clear!
(Door clunks open)
Sam:
All clear.
Okay, Spike, Raf,
check the perimeter.
Boss, there's no sign
of the victim
or the subjects.
Copy that.
According to
the corporate records,
this shop is owned
by a Zhen Mai, 50,
and a Ruby Mai, 22.
Parker: 911 caller said
Ruby's our victim.
Jules: Their home
address is 423 Belleview.
That's only
a couple blocks away.
Parker: Winnie, let's send
a cruiser to that address.
Winnie:
On its way.
The hard drive is missing.
Parker:
Jules.
Surveillance camera.
It's definitely
not a deterrent.
Shop owner didn't want
anyone knowing
they were being photographed.
Jules: Well, the images
were being recorded
right into this computer.
Parker: Well, maybe our guys
realized they were being monitored
during the robbery?
(Register dings)
Not a robbery.
Well, then what were
they after?
Jules:
Boss, I've got something.
(Kettle whistles)
(Water sloshes,
loud bang nearby)
Ruby?
Get out.
Zhen: But we have
business to discuss.
Zhen:
Aggghhhh!
Sam:
Makeshift tripwire.
Let me see.
That's a pretty creative
defense strategy.
Why wouldn't they just
run out the back door?
Winnie: Squad car's taking
fire at the family home -
423 Belleview.
On our way.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Officer McCabe:
Heading north on Belleview.
Grey Sedan, no plates.
McCabe: We're clear?
Ed: You okay?
McCabe:
Yeah. They shot out the tires,
took off with a hostage.
Ed:
How'd it go down?
Two Asian guys -
gang members, we think -
came out of the house
with an older guy,
started firing.
How'd you know
he was a hostage?
They were using him
as a shield.
Chinese, 50's.
Uh, nobody's left
in that house,
we checked.
It's clear.
Okay, thank you.
Boss, the father,
Zhen Mai, was taken hostage.
There's no sign of Ruby.
We're looking at
a double kidnapping here.
Parker:
Copy that, Eddie.
Detective Lee?
Hey. Sergeant Parker?
Yeah.
Thanks for coming down.
My pleasure.
Call me Vivian.
Greg.
Double kidnapping,
officers taking fire...
Hell of a Monday morning.
Yeah, no kidding, right?
Hoping you can give us
a leg up.
Well, this area of Chinatown
is under the control
of the Golden Dragons.
This sound like
their kind of action?
Vivian:
Honestly, no.
They're more into
protection rackets,
heroin trafficking, gambling.
It's unusual for them
to resort to brazen violence.
They don't like
to draw attention.
Well, if they're trying
shake this shop down
and the owners refused
to cooperate...
It's possible,
but why go to the trouble
of kidnapping them?
Why not just damage the shop
or beat someone up?
Sends a simpler message,
comply or else.
Jules: Boss, I think
I can answer that.
Parker: Okay, we'll be
right there, Jules.
Follow me.
(Keys clack, computer beeps)
Parker:
Jules Callaghan.
Detective Vivian Lee,
Asian crime squad.
Thanks for helping us out.
Vivien:
Sure.
All right, the hard drive
on the shop computer was taken,
but I found a jump drive
in the back of the cash drawer
with these images on it.
Parker:
Some tough customers.
Can I see that one?
Jules:
Mm-hm.
Vivian: That's the
Dragons' boss, Wei Caa.
And next to him, Jimmy Ying.
He's Chua's right-hand man.
No. You see here?
Can you zoom in?
Those cigarette burns
are the mark of the Dragons.
Looks like the Dragons
are collecting payoffs.
There's images on here
from at least
four different stores.
Parker: Well, this is
some sort of resistance.
The shop owners
are collecting evidence
against the extortion racket.
Not unless someone's
willing to testify
and explain what's happening.
Jules: Motive for a
kidnapping, or worse.
Parker: Any idea where the Dragons
might've taken their hostages.
Vivian: I can have my
people try and narrow it down
to a list of known
Dragon locations.
But we might have
another way in,
drug squad has wires
on the cell phones
of two active Dragon soldiers.
We can piggyback on those.
Let's do it.
Those merchants are at risk too.
I'm gonna see if I can identify
any of the shops
in these images.
Winnie: - Boss?
Parker: - Yeah, Winnie?
The 911 call was made
by a Terrence Lau.
He owns the Po Chi Lau
herbal medicine shop,
1612 Nassau street.
Jules: Boss, that description
matches one of the shops on video.
Herbs, mushrooms, teas.
Parker: Gentlemen, I need you to
check out that medicine shop.
Our 911 caller might be
part of this resistance.
Ed:
Will do.
I'll let you know
as soon as I have something.
Parker:
Thanks, Vivian.
Winnie:
And, boss, one more thing.
Yeah, Winnie, go ahead.
Winnie:
Your son's here.
Dean's at hq?
I put him on a bus headed home.
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's fine.
He didn't even want me
to tell you he's here.
But he said
he'd talk to you later.
Winnie, I...
Winnie: It's okay, boss.
I'll take care of him.
(Sighs)
Okay, thank you, Winnie.
Terrence Lau?
Sir?
Terrence:
Yes?
Sir, I'm officer Lane,
this is officer Rousseau.
Strategic response unit.
You called 911, right?
Is Ruby okay?
We think she's been abducted,
along with her father.
Ed: Sir, you did the right
thing calling 911,
but we still need
your help here.
Now, do you have any idea
where the Dragons
may have taken Ruby
and her dad?
I don't, honestly.
May I?
Mr. Lau, we know that
you're a victim here too,
and we know that you've been
working against the Dragons.
Raf: Can you give us
names and descriptions
of any of the gang members?
I do that and they find out,
my family is next.
Sounds to me like a good reason
for you to step up.
What happened to you,
little man?
Oh. My son, Eugene.
He's been fighting
with other boys again
in the neighborhood.
Raf: You see anything, Eugene?
Anything at all?
No.
Raf:
Really? Sure about that?
I told you no, okay?
Raf:
Okay.
If you care about Ruby,
you need to tell us
what you know here.
Okay. Raf.
Man: Look, I told you
, I know these people.
Just tell me what happened.
Parker:
Officer? It's all right.
Come here, son.
Jules:
You have some id?
Dixon green.
Now what the hell happened?
Is Ruby okay?
How do you know Ruby?
I'm her sensei.
I work at a martial arts studio
on Bloor.
Ruby's my student.
You always check
on your students
at their workplace?
Ruby's more than a student,
okay?
I care about her.
We believe Ruby's
been kidnapped,
as well as her father.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no...
Why wouldn't she listen?
Okay, look,
I know who did this.
It's a gang.
They're called
the Golden Dragons.
They've been squeezing Ruby
and her dad for years.
Is that why
she takes martial arts?
To protect herself?
Ruby? No.
She wants to fight back.
She's been gathering evidence
with all the other shop owners
against the Dragons.
Someone must've ratted her out.
Do you know
who she's working with?
I don't know.
She knew I was against
the whole thing.
Made me swear not to tell
the bit that I did know.
I don't even think
her dad knows.
What about her mother?
Her mother died last year
in a fire
in that warehouse right here.
Ruby's pretty torn up about it,
and her dad...
He's still not over it.
Okay.
Just stay close, will you?
We may need to ask you
some more questions.
Officer?
Just keep an eye on him.
Ruby's running the resistance,
but they take her father too.
Might not have known
she was acting alone.
(Into headset)
Go ahead, Vivien.
Vivien: Hey.
So, my team has just recorded a call
between a Golden Dragon soldier
name of Phu Wan
and an unknown female.
I'm sending you the audio file.
Vivian, I'm loading
the audio file now.
Female:
I got your message.
Male: You did the
right thing calling.
No reason for all of this.
Everything's okay, right?
Female: I don't
know, you tell me.
Male:
Everything's okay.
Stop the tape.
You thinking what I'm thinking?
Maybe it's Ruby.
Parker:
Let's get Dixon in here.
Vivien, thing is,
no one actually saw Ruby
get abducted.
Maybe she got away.
Maybe she's the shooter,
not the other way around.
But why wouldn't she go
to the police?
She may not trust us.
The Dragons had an officer
on the payroll in the past.
There's more you need to hear.
Dixon, you recognize
any of these voices?
(Key clacks, computer beeps)
Female: You really
think I'm that stupid?
Give me one reason
why I should believe you.
That's Ruby.
Male: We need to know who
you've been talking to.
You tell us,
everybody goes home, okay?
Ruby:
Augusta street cafe.
15 minutes, on the patio.
Male:
Come alone.
You talk to the police,
you know what happens.
- Ruby's okay?
- Yeah, she is for now,
but we're running out of time.
We need your help.
You mind coming with us?
Jules, let's go.
Vivian...
Vivian:
I'll meet you there.
(Car horn honks)
Parker: She gets away
from two armed gangsters
and now she's trying
to negotiate
her own father's release.
The kid's got brass.
Jules: That brass is gonna
get her into trouble.
Ed: There's no chance the
Dragons will honor that deal.
Jules:
No, they need Ruby alive
so that she can give
the names of her resistance.
Parker: Intimidate anybody
who might wanna testify.
Might try to abduct her again.
Ed: We gotta be in
position to protect her
without letting the Dragons know
we're there.
Okay, guys,
looks like we'll need
some civvies here.
(Door clunks shut)
Where we at, guys?
Spike:
Almost there with the parabolic.
Thank you.
Copy that, Spike.
Sam?
Sam: A lot of civilians,
including Ruby.
I'm going less lethal.
Ed:
Good call.
Raf? Jules?
In position.
Jules:
Six o'clock, Ed.
You clean up well.
You too.
Spike, you hear me?
In full stereophonic sound.
Parker: All right, no one
gets made, you understand?
Dragons think Ruby's
working with us,
they could have
her father killed.
Spike: Got it.
Sam: Copy.
Vivian: My team's just narrowed
down the possible locations to five.
Parker:
That's good work.
We'll give 'em
as much time as we can.
Ed:
Two, please.
Parker:
Dark blazer, spiky hair.
Vivian: That's Lak
Tang, senior guy.
Reports directly to Chua.
You hear that, Eddie?
He's headed toward a table.
We got eyes.
Tang: Just give me a minute
and then we'll order.
Sidewalk next to the patio,
on a motorcycle.
Vivian:
Yes. A soldier.
Confirmed.
Parker:
Okay, I think that's her.
Where's my father?
Don't worry.
If you do your part,
we'll do ours.
Ruby:
I wanna see him, first.
Tang:
Don't be stupid.
All I have to do
is make one quick call
and that's it.
He dies.
You write down the names
of your friends
and we check it out.
If you're telling the truth,
we'll let him go.
Brave girl.
Your father doesn't deserve
your loyalty.
What're you talking about?
Last chance
to change your mind.
Ed:
Okay, he's making a call.
Put the phone down.
Now.
Do it now.
(Cocks gun)
Gun.
Ruby's got a gun.
You're making a big mistake.
Soldier's on the move.
Ed:
We gotta move now.
Let's take him.
Right there.
Get down! Drop the gun!
Drop the gun now!
Jules: Weapon on the ground.
Weapon on the ground.
Turn around, turn around.
Parker:
We got a bogey.
Possible gang member
across the street.
Vivien, can you confirm that?
I can't be sure.
Parker:
He's making a phone call.
Boss...
Parker: Hold your fire, Sam.
We need to make sure.
Confirmed.
(Gunshot pops)
Raf: On the ground. Now!
I need you to come with me.
You don't understand.
As soon as they find out
police are involved,
they'll kill my father.
That's why we need
to find him fast.
Lots of witnesses, Ed.
Don't want word getting back
to the Dragons
that the police are involved.
Ed:
Copy that, Spike.
Let's get him off the street,
get some answers.
You talked to them?
You promised me...
Dixon:
I was worried about you, okay?
You can't take them on
by yourself, Ruby.
Parker:
It's okay.
Ruby, my name is
Sergeant Greg Parker.
I'm with the strategic
response unit.
What you did was very brave,
but you put yourself
and your dad
in a lot of danger.
Jules: Ruby, somebody
told the Dragons
that you were coordinating
a resistance;
Somebody who knew
what you were doing.
Parker: You need to tell us
who you talked to, Ruby.
If we can find the leak,
maybe they could lead us
to your father.
I'll tell you,
but it won't do any good.
If someone told the Dragons
about me,
they're not gonna believe
you can protect them.
Ed:
Raf, give me a second.
Buddy, you tell me
where Zhen Mai is,
and I'm gonna help you out.
(Scoffs)
You're 25-years-old,
you are gonna do 10 years
in prison.
You're okay with that?
Fair enough.
Raf?
Raf:
Let's go.
Vivian:
Hey. Anything?
Ed:
Ice in his veins.
The gangs recruit these kids
when they're really young.
I mean, how're they doing it?
Is it drugs? Status? What?
They target a newcomer,
pay a couple of other kids
to bully him,
then a gang member
miraculously shows up,
scares the bullies.
Kid's so grateful,
next thing you know...
That easy.
(Vivian's cell rings)
- Excuse me.
- Yeah.
Gotta take this.
Hey.
Boss.
Go ahead, Eddie.
Ed: I think I have an
angle on our leak.
Parker:
Someone we know?
Yeah, that 911 call,
Terrence Lau.
Parker:
Yeah?
Well, when we were
at his the shop,
his son Eugene was
all bad attitude and bruises.
Parker: Okay, Eddie
, let's look into it.
Copy that.
Raf, let's gear up.
Raf:
Copy.
Now, we need to move fast,
before anything happens
to your dad.
You gotta tell us
what's going on here,
and I mean everything.
The Dragons,
they've been extorting us
for money for years.
Last year, Chua asked
for even more money.
Well, I like
the color assortment there.
(Door chimes jingle)
Zhen:
If you want it, take it.
My boys tell me
you refuse to comply
with the new arrangements.
Zhen:
We're already running at a loss.
What do you think happens
without us?
Hmm?
We protect you.
Zhen:
I can't afford any more.
Jimmy:
(Charging yell)
(Glass shatters)
Stop! Stop!
Okay! Okay!
Zhen:
Okay!
(Chuckles)
You are smart man.
You think of your family.
Xie xie.
(Door chimes jingle)
(Grunts forcefully,
decoration snaps)
(Door chimes jingle)
My father was so angry.
He wanted to fight back.
But my mother begged him
not to do anything.
She wanted to sell the store
so we could move away
to start over.
Whatever my father did next
made Chua very angry,
because a week later...
(Sirens wail)
♪
After my mother died,
my father just gave up.
He hardly eats or sleeps.
Never comes to the store.
Police investigate the fire?
Ruby:
They said it was arson,
but they couldn't link it
to the Dragons.
The Golden Dragons
destroyed my family.
(Door creaks open)
I told you, I can't help you.
Ed:
With all due respect,
we're here to talk
to your son, sir.
Come here for a sec.
Terrence:
Eugene, do as you are told.
Ed:
What's that?
Your son's been recruited.
Ed: You talked to the Dragons
about Ruby, didn't you?
Eugene, you need to tell us
where they are right now.
Do you understand me?
You're already
in a lot of trouble,
don't make this any worse.
They said they were
just gonna scare them.
Ed: Boss, the kids says
they're at the Yonge building
on Spadina.
That's a big place, Spike,
plenty of places to hide.
Any ideas?
Spike: Well, we have
the most recent plans,
but they might not be accurate.
Filed with the city years ago.
These old Chinatown building
are often renovated
without plans and permits.
That's good to know.
Ed: Building's fully
attached on both sides.
We got a secured loading door
on black wall.
We're gonna need the Halligan.
Ruby: Why are you looking
at pictures of the roof?
Spike: 'Cause often they can
tell us what's underneath.
Okay, you see those
two plumbing vents?
They're at the back wall,
so that means that
the sweat shop offices
and bathrooms on red wall.
Spike: East wall.
Ed: Copy that, Spike.
Parker: Let's get uniforms
setting up a perimeter.
Ed:
Copy.
Drug squad just intercepted
a call between two Dragons
from within the building.
They know that Ruby's working
with the police.
Parker:
Time's up, let's move.
Raf and Jules:
Police! Police! SRU!
Raf: On the table now! Down!
Parker:
Everyone stay where they are!
Vivien:
Jimmy's on the line now.
Go ahead.
Jimmy's talking to Chua.
He's asking for instructions.
(Sewing machines whirr)
I'm gonna check upstairs.
(Speaking in mandarin)
Raf:
Police!
Vivien: Wei Chua!
Put the gun down now! Now!
Parker:
Put your hands up now!
Chua:
(Chuckles)
I thought this was
a civilized country.
Parker: Wei Chua, you're
looking at kidnapping,
extortion and arson.
You order the death
of Zhen Mai,
you'll add murder to the list.
And why would I do
such a thing?
(Speaks in mandarin)
Parker: - What did he say?
Vivian: - It's time.
Parker:
Wei Chua, you're under arrest.
Put your hands on the table.
Do it now!
Zhen:
Agh! Aggghhhh!
(Coughs and gasps)
(Lighter flicks)
What are you waiting for?
Just do it.
Jimmy:
The decision is yours.
Chua says he's gonna tell
your daughter the truth.
Said he wants her to know.
Third floor clear.
Copy, Sam.
That's it.
Building's clear.
Sam: They knew we were coming.
They probably escaped.
How?
The perimeter's secured.
The roof.
(Door squeaks open)
Ed:
Right there! Stop!
Spike: - Go, I got this.
Ed: - You sure?
Spike:
Go.
I'm officer Mike Scarlatti,
SRU.
You're Zhen Mai, right?
Zhen, you wanna tell me
what's happening right now?
Sam, they're coming down
the fire escape.
Sam:
Copy.
SRU! Stop right there!
Lower your weapons
on the stairs, now!
Now!
Spike:
I'm here to help you, Zhen.
Officers have arrested
the Dragons.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Stay back!
Spike:
Okay.
Leave me be.
Boss, found the hostage.
He's alive,
but he's doused in gasoline.
He's threatening
to set himself on fire.
Parker: Yeah, copy that, Eddie.
Why, what's going on?
Zhen:
Leave me be.
Minimal cognitive response,
tunnel vision.
Sam:
He's not bluffing.
Tac options?
Ed:
Rushing him is not a safe play.
We need a fire extinguisher
up here now.
Go for it.
(Breathes shakily)
Okay, fast as possible, Sam.
Jules and Raf,
let's go over everything we know
so far.
Let's dig into
his psychology here.
Let's identify any triggers.
We need to know
why this is happening,
why it's happening now.
- Copy.
- On it.
Ruby?
We found your father,
my people are with him.
But I need to ask you
a few questions.
Why, did something happen
to him?
He's threatening
to take his own life.
What?
I don't understand.
Yeah, we don't either.
We need to figure this out
so we can stop him
from harming himself.
Ruby: (Screaming)
What'd you do to him?!
Parker: Ruby, I need you
to stay calm, all right?
Spike:
Zhen? Ruby is safe.
She's out front
and she's waiting for you.
Ruby...
She's so brave.
When she finds out
what I've done...
Parker: Well he's done something
that he can't come to terms with.
In Chinese culture,
suicide can be an honorable way
to alleviate shame.
Parker:
Ruby?
Can you think of any reason
why your father would be
in this state?
He's still mourning
the death of my mother,
but...
That can't be why.
All right, Ruby's mother died
in a warehouse fire
about a year ago, right?
The fire was determined
to be arson.
Investigators didn't
have enough evidence
to lay charges.
Ruby said that the Dragons
set the fire as retribution.
Retribution for what?
She didn't know.
She said her father
provoked them.
So he feels responsible.
Is that enough to ma h him
suicidal?
I just lost my father, Zhen.
We didn't always see
eye-to-eye,
but I'd give anything
to have him back in my life.
Your daughter loves you.
Let her help you.
She can't help me.
Ed: He's unstable here, boss.
He's on the edge.
Parker:
Copy that, Eddie.
Maybe it's time
to bring Ruby in.
Jules:
Are you sure, boss?
Zhen's shame is focused on
what Ruby thinks of him.
Parker:
Not a lot of options, Jules.
Maybe the emotional connection
could de-escalate
the situation.
(Ruby weeps quietly)
Ruby?
Are you up to talking
to your dad?
Can you do that?
Yes.
Come on.
Ed:
Zhen, it's okay.
It's okay, my name's Ed.
I just need you
to listen to me for a sec.
Stay back!
Ed: Zhen, what you're
thinking about doing here,
it doesn't always kill you.
It can leave you badly burned,
and in terrible pain.
Now you don't want that.
That's what I deserve.
To burn like my poor Lin.
Parker: Your father's
in pretty bad shape.
So the last thing we want
is for him to think
that he's upsetting you.
- Okay.
- So just connect to him,
just let him do the talking.
Just put that in your ear,
all right?
Just remember that
you won't be alone.
Okay.
Zhen received a full payout
from the insurance company
after the fire.
Ruby said that
he used that money
to pay off the Dragons.
So just when he needed
the money...
He gets it.
Boss.
I hear ya, Jules.
But there's no hard evidence.
Jules: According to
the incident report,
the wife ran inside
and tried to put out the blaze.
No insurance policy
on the wife.
He didn't intend
to hurt anyone.
And this is hitting him
now because?
Jules: Chua and Jimmy
threatened to tell Ruby
knowing it will make Zhen
suicidal.
They figure his suicide
will be devastating to Ruby
and that she'll have
nothing left to fight for.
They clean up their mess,
sending a message
to the rest of Chinatown,
all without risking
a murder charge.
And if it's not true,
it's a hell of an accusation.
Jules:
Well, she has to know
'cause she's our only shot
at talking him down.
Parker: Ruby, I have some
news about your father.
Ed:
Zhen, whatever you've done,
it's not worth this.
Zhen:
Stay back!
Ed:
All right.
Spike: Zhen, you do this now,
you hurt Ruby even more.
Parker:
Look, Ruby,
there's no easy way
to say this.
There's a possibility
that it was your father
who set fire to the warehouse.
What're you talking about?
He might've done it
for the insurance money
to pay the Dragons.
If he did set that fire,
I'm sure he never intended
to hurt anyone.
Certainly not your mother.
No way.
He would never do tat.
I'm saying we don't know
for sure.
But it might explain why
he's in this state of mind.
You're the best chance we have
to getting through to him,
but if he did start that fire
and you can't forgive him,
then you can't help him.
(Door squeaks open)
Ruby: Ba??
Ba.
Why are you doing this?
I'm so sorry, Ruby.
It's true, isn't it?
You set the fire
that killed ma?
I did.
(Sobs)
I know it hurts.
I know it hurts,
but your father just tried
to protect your mother and you
to the best of his ability.
Why, ba?!
We could've just moved,
like ma wanted.
I didn't know what else to do.
We could have fought back.
I didn't want
to see you get hurt.
(Cries)
Parker: This isn't your
father's fault, Ruby.
No, he can't shoulder
the blame.
Not now.
Not like this.
Zhen:
At least now you know.
Ruby:
Ba, wait!
Parker:
That's it.
Just think about
what he went through.
You wanted to protect us.
Ma didn't want you
to fight back.
I was too weak.
I killed her.
Parker:
Now you need to forgive him.
He needs to hear that, Ruby.
Ba...
Remember when
we first moved here?
I was so little.
I was so scared, I missed home.
You know what ma told me?
She said you were a tiger.
She said you'd always
protect me.
But I'm not.
You're the strong one.
Ruby:
Because of you, ba.
Always because of you.
Ruby:
(Cries softly)
I miss ma.
I miss her so much.
But I still need you.
We still need each other.
Please, ba.
I forgive you.
Please, ba...
Ruby:
It's okay.
♪
♪ if you go ♪
♪ I will fall ♪
♪ into... ♪
♪ the deep ♪
♪ you knew
while I have discovered ♪
♪ everything I need to live ♪
♪ forget the smoke
and mirrors ♪
♪ you can't go back ♪
♪ if you leave ♪
♪ I will drown ♪
♪ take your keys ♪
♪ burn this town ♪
♪ there's no way now ♪
♪ you knew... ♪
Hey.
You keep the peace today?
Yeah, actually.
It was a good day.
Yeah. I, uh...
I didn't get on the bus.
I can see that.
What's going on?
Well, I, uh...
I just wanted to ask you
a question.
I thought...
If it was all right with you,
I could come live with you
for a while.
You and your mom
not getting along
or something?
No. No, it's not that.
I wanna be here,
you know, with you.
Does she know about this?
Yeah. I just...
I just told her I wanted
to bring it up with you first.
I... I thought
you'd be happy.
I am.
I'm very happy.
Listen.
This last year,
getting to know
each other again,
it's been awesome.
I'm proud that you get
to see what I do
and that you've changed
your mind about me.
It's what I've always
hoped for.
But...
You and I just haven't spent
a whole lot of time together.
I just don't want you
to be disappointed.
I won't be.
So?
Is it okay then?
(Half laughs)
Yeah.
Yeah, it's okay.
It's absolutely okay.
♪ You can go back ♪
♪ you can go back ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com