Where you going?
I'm gonna go see some friends.
- No!
- Those guys are not your friends.
- You're just business to them.
- Just let go.
No.I am not gonna let them
suck the life out of you.
Come on,jimmy!
Jimmy!
Help me save him!
He's my brother!Come on,jimmy!
It's too late.
Uh,excuse me.
I heard you threw donnie
outta here last night.
Is that true?
Is it true?
This is my place.I get to
decide who comes in,who doesn't.
What do you got against
our friend donnie?
I mean what's wrong with a guy who wants to
sit at a bar and have a quiet conversation?
I don't like him doing
business in my place.
He's welcome to do it someplace else.
You're messing with our business.
And when you mess with our
business,we mess with yours.
Bar owner: what're you doing?
No,don't! Please!
Oh,you sons of bitches!
Language!
This is a family establishment.
Come on,guys!
Let's talk this over!
Please.
He's the local dealer.
Stop!
You have to get down here.
The gatto nero.College street.
Stop!
You don't need to do that,guys!
Bastards!
Don't touch that! Don't touch that.
No.It belonged to my wife.
What do you think,vince?
- Nice!
- Crystal.You know,i bought some like this for my mom once.
Cost a couple stacks.
- What's this cost?
- It's not about what it costs.
Please.
Back off!
Your call.
Oh,my god!
He has a gun.Please hurry!
You all right?
Yeah,yeah.
Watch it!
Wh-what're you doing?Let it go.
I'm not letting it go.
Oh,shelley,one more thing... Um,you
want to go to eddie's tonight?
Barbeque,kids.
- What time?
- I don't know.Like 6:00?
Team one,hot call.
12 clouster street.Shots fired.
Better make it 8:00.
eight o'clock.Love ya,gotta go.
Team one,seconds away.
Copy.
Copy,copy.Command truck's on its way.
First responder?Talk to me fast,officer.
We've got two males,baseball bats and
a handgun,start tearing the place apart.
A patron jumps in,the gun
discharges,everybody runs.
Whose gun?
The guys wrecking the bar.
- You get a description?
- Yup.
Mid-20s,long coats.
One's 6'4" with dreadlocks,injury
on the right arm.
The other's a small
build,jeans,black t-shirt.
No word on the good samaritan.
The good samaritan?
- That's what the owner called him.
- Thanks,officer.
Sam,you get those descriptions?
Yeah.Well,we're right behind them.
- We move fast...
- We can bring 'em in.
Okay,we work a grid.
Wordy,you are alpha with me.We
will work north and south.
Sam,leah,bravo,east
and west.Let's move it.
Jules,let's see what we can find out.
Do you know why these men
would be targeting your place?
They're drug dealers.
I threw out one of
their friends last night.
You stood up to them.
This is what it got me.
You know the men who did this?
Leon is the little one.Vince is
the big one.That's all i know.
And who's the man who attacked them?
He didn't attack them.
He chased them out.
I didn't get a look at him.
Did he take his handgun?
Two against one.I'm just wondering
how he managed to chase them out?
Yeah,he had the gun.
It's sick.
What are you talking about?
I grew up here.
I didn't know that.
Used to be kids in the streets all hours,hide
and seek,people outside on their patios.
You sitting on the back of a
pickup,strummin' your first guitar.
I just hate to see what's happened.
I hear you,wordy,but you
gotta talk to city hall.
There were a lot more cops
on the street back then.
Team one,turns out our
good samaritan is armed.
Got i.D.?
Not yet,but he may be going
after the same target as you.
So what?We've got some citizen
trying to be a vigilante?
Looks that way.
- Vigilante?
- What would you call him?
Some guys try to intimidate a local businessman,and this
guy steps up,fights back... I'd call him a good citizen.
A good citizen in
pursuit with a firearm.
It's okay,it's okay.
How you doing,leon?
I'm good. How about you?
Proud of yourself?You get a
rush out of what you did? Huh?
Takes a big man to bust up someone's place,someone's
treasures; pieces of a life that they actually worked for.
Takes a real big man.
What do you want?You just
tell me what you want.
So you got no idea what he looks like
- tall,short,heavyset,blond,brunette... Stop me here.
No? Nothing's coming to you?
Everything happened really fast.
You got a pretty good
look at the other two guys.
Alphonse,look,i realize
he did you a favour.
But he chased two men out of here with a loaded weapon,and
we'd like to help him before he gets in too deep.
I never saw him before.
- You sure about that?
- Absolutely.
What about you,ma'am?Do
you remember anything?
I just... I was in the back here.
I didn't see the guy at all.
Ed,uniforms called in a man in dreads in a
long coat running south on parliament street.
Dreadlocks,three o'clock!
In pursuit on foot,corner
of montrose and college.
Ed,right there!Stay there!Right now!
Do not move! Do not move!
Give me your hands!Let me see
your hands! Let me see your hands!
You got any weapons?!Get up!
It's dislocated.
- What's your name?
- What's your name?!
What's up,eddie?
Boss,we got one of the dealers.
The name he gave is vince packer.
Okay,spike,see if you can get
anything on a vince packer.
On it,boss.
Parker: look for any connections
to someone named leon.
Our friend vince denies vandalizing "the
gatto nero" or knowing anyone named leon.
Apparently he dislocated his shoulder playing hockey this
morning,in a neighbourhood that lost its rink five years ago.
Ed,your guy vince?
He gets busted a lot
for such a good athlete.
Possession,assault... And look at this
- last time he went down,he went down with fellow athlete leon weeks.
Where can we find mr.Weeks?
If he's headed home,he's
right in the neighborhood.
211 watson.That's clouster and watson.
Two blocks from us.We're on it.
Shots fired!Alley west of clouster!
On it.
Sam,this guy's really a mess.
Winnie,we need an ambulance.
Bad news,boss.The vigilante
has kicked it up a notch.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly
Presents
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET- °îµÂÖí Åùö¨±´±´
Flash
Point Season 3Episode 08
Winnie,where's that ambulance?
Sending emt's to your gps location now.
Talk to me,sam.
The subject from the bar has been shot.
Bullet wounds in both legs.
It's nasty,but it's
not life-threatening.
Looks like he was carrying some cocaine.
This is circumstantial!
You're leon weeks,right?
I want a lawyer.I know my rights.
We're not here about the drugs.
Oh,yeah.Right.I know how this works.
You're gonna plant some drugs,then
you're gonna try and pin it on me.
Leon,we just wanna know who shot you.
That's all.
Cooper.Robert cooper.
Thanks,leon,we've got the
spelling.Spike,you copy that?
Get right back to ya.
Robert cooper.
- What?You know him?
- Not well.
My dad and i used to hang out at his
dad's hardware store all the time.
Robert cooper's taking
this pretty personally,leon.
Was there something here you want to
tell me,like why he'd want to shoot you?
The guy's a wacko.
He's out of control.You
gotta stop him,okay?
Maybe cooper's not fond of
people in your line of work.
I said this is circumstantial.
Guys,listen to this.
"a west end neighbourhood sentinel association won a court
battle which would have the imperial arms apartments torn down.
President and local
businessman,robert cooper,
said 'the association has dealt a body blow to the
drug dealers trying to take over our neighbourhood.
'" From community activist to vigilante.
I'm sending you a
picture of him right now.
Alphonse... You know it's illegal
to lie to the police,right?
Robert cooper was your good samaritan.
Now how do you not recognize the
president of your neighborhood sentinel?
I didn't want to get him in trouble.
- He just shot a man.
- Oh my god.
Yeah,might not have happened if
you had given us a straight answer.
Alphonse,we need to bring him in
here before he hurts anybody else.
You got an address,a phone
number?Anything you got.
I don't know where he's
living.You'll have to ask his wife.
So what's her name?
Patty cooper.
Let's get her down here,jules.
Leon,we need to talk to
you about your crew,buddy.
I don't know... What crew?
Cooper's declared war.You
think he's gonna stop with you?
Leon: he wanted me to give up names and addresses for the guys i work with
- the top guys.
Did you tell him?
I don't know the top
guys.I only talk to torres.
- Torres?
- John torres.He's the middle guy.
That's all i know.That's all i told him.
All right,let's see what we
can find out about this torres.
You think he's gonna go after
every dealer in the area?
That could take a while
in this neighbourhood.
Sorry,leah,what about
this neighbourhood?
When i was a firefighter i took a lot of
drug-related calls,especially in this neighbourhood.
But bobby doesn't own a gun.
It appears he took it from one of the
men that he assaulted this morning.
We believe robert's been hunting
down a local gang of drug dealers.
Did you know that he was planning
on doing something like that?
No. No. God,no.
I would have called
the police immediately.
Well,we need to know what made him do this.Can
you tell us about his state of mind lately?
He's angry... About what happened to the
neighbourhood,about what happened to his brother.
His brother?
Jimmy.He's... He's younger.
They never really had an easy time.
Their mom died a long time ago,so it
was just bobby and jimmy and their dad -
they were close
- and then me.
For a few years,we
ran the store together.
We were happy.
We were good.
What happened?
Their dad died... And
jimmy started using.
Jimmy became an addict?
Not overnight.It was a long slide down.
We lost the jimmy that we loved.
We tried to help him.We
did the best we could.
Jimmy.
Hey,how're you guys
doing?What can i get ya?
I just got a call from
gordie.Where the hell were you?
Aw,jeez.Man,3:30.
you told me you wanted
to work in the dealership.
- I put my neck on the line,i get the job for you...
- Okay,enough.
I get the message loud and clear.
I let you down... Again.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go meet some friends.
Cooper: hey,i know who you mean,and
those guys are not your friends.
Now you're gonna tell
me who my friends are?
Get the hell off me.
You're not their friend,jimmy,okay?
You're just business to them.
You son of a bitch,just let go.
No,no.Hey,listen to me,all right?
I am not gonna let them
suck the life out of you.
Let me go.Just let... Go!
If you walk out of that
door,i am done with you.
I didn't mean that.
- I'm gonna go.
- I know.
- Bobby!
- No.
Jimmy!
He's not gonna give up looking for him.
When was the last time you two spoke?
When he ran after jimmy
about two days ago.
Do you mind me asking why he left?
Losing the store,losing
jimmy... I mean he's a good guy.
He's lost.It's just eating him up.
Just uh... Hold on a second.
Okay,team,new deal.
Robert cooper's got a
little brother,jimmy.
Jimmy got hooked with the local dealers...
And now robert's trying to track them down.
So,it's personal.
Yeah,it's starting to look that way.
Boss,i did a credit
card search on cooper.
Good work,spike.Whatchya got?
I got an address.
He just moved into a
by-the-week rooming house.
112 mcarthur.
Team one,seconds away.
I'm gonna apologize to wordy.
He's got a real
connection to this place.
I didn't need to push.
Word of advice for the
rookie from the last one?
When i joined the team i made a lot of
mistakes,i did my share of apologizing.
But the one thing i never had to
apologize for was speaking my mind.
You see something you
think affects the call,
like your general impression of a neighbourhood
based on professional experience,you say it.
What's up?
You tell me.
Uh,i don't know,you
know,busy... Workin'.
I'm coming out of my house this morning and two
high-ranking security agents want to take me out for coffee.
Oh... That.
Yeah,that.
And they wanna talk to me about you.
It's not what you think.
- No?
- No.
Okay.
We'll pick this up later,all right?
Second floor,end of the hall.
Wordy,you're alpha with me.
Sam,leah
- bravo.
Let's do it.
Police,freeze! Police! Police!
Clear.
Boss,cooper's not here.
Thanks,eddie.
All right.
The neighbourhood sentinel seemed like they were getting
somewhere,so why would robert do something like this?
Things started turning bad when
the family business burnt down.
The hardware store?When was that?
A few weeks ago.Bobby was sure it
was the drug dealers out to get him.
What?Because the sentinel had
closed down one of their buildings?
Yeah,retaliation.
The family store meant a lot to him.
But,you know,he didn't
talk about his feelings.
But he was taking it pretty hard.
Well,he hated feeling helpless.
He became obsessed with
fixing things,like his dad.
It was all about fixing things.
But this wasn't something that he could fix
and he wouldn't talk about it,not even patty.
After a few weeks,he just... He lost it.
So he left his wife,moved in here.
Pictures of his family;
that's a good sign.
Used to go to that
store every halloween.
Old man cooper really went all out.
It's a shame that place is gone.
All right.
Boss,i found cooper's brother.
That's good.How soon
can we get him here?
He's not going anywhere.
- Why not?
- He's in the morgue.
Jimmy cooper o.D.'D early this morning.
Who found jimmy cooper's body?
Dispatch said it was
an anonymous 911 call.
Someone saw him having a seizure
right in the middle of the street.
At least someone cared
enough to call it in.
Think cooper knows his brother died?
If he does,it could
have been the trigger.
I'm gonna talk to the
paramedics involved.
I guess i go tell patty.
Spike,i've got some
friends at "guns and gangs.
" see if you can get
some intel on john torres.
The middle man.Copy.
All right,we find
torres,maybe we'll find cooper.
So,michaelangelo,international
man of mystery.
- He told you?
- Yeah.
He's not happy.
He doesn't like to see
the family break up.
Tell me about it.
- But he's proud of you.
- Really?
Federal agency seeks you
out?That's a big deal.
Yeah?
Y- eah.- Yeah.
Thanks,jules.
So,is this the guy from last night?
Yeah,that was him.
Came running over when he
saw us working on his brother.
He totally freaked out.
So was the brother still
alive when cooper got to him?
He was circling the drain,but
cooper wouldn't give up on him.
Clear! Charge to 360.
and clear!
Come on,jimmy. Come
on,jimmy,stay with me.
Stay with me,buddy,come on.
Come on.
I'm sorry,he's gone.
No,no he's not.Keep trying!
-I'm sorry.
-No!
Come on,jimmy.
I'm sorry,sir,you have to let him go.
No!
Come on,jimmy.
Jimmy!Jimmy,please!
No!No,he's not some junkie!
He's my brother!
it's too late,sir.
I'm sorry.
No!
Jimmy...
Thanks,guys.
Seeing your kid brother
die right in front of you...
So he's upset about his brother's death,and
blames it on the people who sold him drugs.
And now he's out for blood.
Guys,that middle man leon
mentioned,john torres,
his name comes up in connection
with the steele brothers.
The steele brothers.
I've heard that name before.
Yeah,real up and comers.
They allegedly run the
coke trade this end of town.
Why allegedly?
Drug squad's been building a file.
The steele brothers,they
come from money.
Mom and dad disowned
them,but not before grady
used daddy's money to buy
into the trade big time.
Looks like his kid brother
dru got into the business,too.
They got money,they move around.
Yeah,and the cops have
never been able to touch 'em.
I guess they keep a pretty low profile.
They're most likely
cooper's number one target.
So we'd better find
them before cooper does.
We got an address on
the steele brothers?
No last known.Like i
said,they move around.
But what i do have is a lead
on their middle man,john torres.
I'm sending you photos.
Torres does business out of a
blue panel van with spoke rims.
Perfect mobile office.
Normally trolls the area
between bloor and gerrard.
Spike,let's access city traffic
cameras,help us narrow down the search.
On it.
Okay,guys,let's work the grid.
Let's go.
-Problem?
-No problem.
Anyone have eyes?
Negative.
Still looking.
Wordy,you got something
to say,spit it out.
We protect drug dealers now?
We keep the peace.
If that includes stopping some guy from
shooting up a bunch of drug dealers,
then,yeah,that's what we do.
Great,so,when we catch up to him and he
doesn't share our feelings about civic order...
We make him listen.
And if he doesn't listen,and it's
down to him or the drug dealer?
Wordy?
Yeah,leah.
When bullets start flying,they
don't just hit drug dealers.
Wordy,we protect everybody,all right?
We protect the families,and,yeah,we
protect the dealers.
And we protect cooper.
I mean who do you think's gonna be
more familiar with the use of firearms?
All right,we got three vans matching
the description in your vicinity.
Someone reported music blaring from a blue
panel van parked behind wayne's tavern.
Uni in the area confirmed
the van had spoke rims.
I'm betting that's our guy.
Team one,move in!
The cab's empty.
Check the back.
I can't see in.
The door's locked.
Mr. Torres,this is the police!
Please exit your vehicle!
Can't hear anything
over that music,eddie!
Wordy,let's go!Let's go!
Stack it up.
Police!
Looks like cooper beat us here.
He's been shot in the stomach.
Winnie,we need an emt here immediately.
Copy that.
Never thought i'd be...
So happy to see the cops.
Did cooper do this to you?
How long ago?
Don't know!
Half hour,maybe.
Let me guess: he was looking
for the steele brothers.
Did you tell him where they're at?
No choice!
What's the address?!
Mr. Torres,i know you don't
want to give up your bosses,
but unless you tell us where they
are,robert cooper gonna kill 'em.
The steele brothers can handle cooper.
He got the drop on you,didn't he?
The emt's are here,
but they won't treat you 'til
we give them the all clear.
24 aynes road.
Aynes.Thank you.
We got an address.
Let's go!
Let the emt's through!
Patty,it's me.
Oh,bobby,thank god!
Are you okay?
Winnie,put a trace on
patty cooper's cell phone.
I'm on it.
Listen,i heard about jimmy.
I am so sorry!
Please,bobby,just come home!
Patty,listen to me...
Bobby,you're scaring me!
Please come home!
There's something i've gotta do.
It's,it's nearly over.
Bobby,you're scaring me!Okay?
Just come home!
And no matter what happens i need...
No matter what happens,i need
you to know that i love you.
Where are you?!
I'll come get you!
Bobby?
Oh,bobby!
He's gone.
Sorry,jules,i didn't get it.
Sarge,cooper contacted his wife.
You get a lock on his location?
No,it was too quick.
But he said that he needed to do
something and that he loves her.
Either way,he knows
it's not gonna end well.
What the hell's going on here?
The cops are all over
torres,and not just regular cops.
Swat.
Torres is not gonna talk.
I don't wanna go to jail,man.
No one is going to jail.
We need to clear the supply
and lay low for a while.
Just... Just 'til the dust settles.
Hey,listen!
The cops are always
gonna be after us,dru.
The trick is not to panic.
When you panic,you make mistakes.
I don't know,man.
Okay,this is why... Come on,grady
- you freak out over everything.
That's not true.
If you don't have the
stomach for this... I do.
I swear.
Really? Yeah.
I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you.
Now put this back where it belongs.
Hey,i got us tickets
to the game tonight.
I don't think you're gonna make it.
That's a lot of money you've got there.
Who the hell are you?
You want it?
It's yours.
Just let him go.
You must make a good living.
$50,000
- all yours.
Just let him go and walk out that door.
Is that's all your brother's
life is worth to you,hmm?
$50 grand?
I can give you whatever you want.
Whatever i want,huh?
Name it.
I want my brother back.
You killed him.
You killed jimmy.
I don't even know anyone named jimmy.
He was one of your best customers!
We don't know our customers.
You don't know your... He
died early this morning!
Overdose!
Okay,man,i'm sorry.
That's rough.
I tried to help him,but i couldn't.
Does that seem right to you?
Cooper's armed.
We have every reason to believe
the steele brothers are armed.
But we go in aggressive,we
could trigger a firefight.
Can't go in without intel.
-Wordy,leah -
eyes. -Got it.
Sam... I'll find a perch.
Transmitting.
Boss,we're good.
All right,he's got 'em.
Look at him.
His arm's shaking,he's breathing hard.
He's working up the
courage to kill them.
We're running out of time.
Sam,do you have the solution?
Negative.
Jules,cooper's got himself barricaded
inside the house with
the steele brothers.
Let's bring patty down here,maybe she
can help us get through to her husband.
Copy that.Come with me.
Did they find bobby?
Yeah,i'm gonna take you to him.Come on.
Please,don't.
Okay there,easy,easy,easy.
Open that bag of coke
and pour it on the table.
Okay,no problem.
How much do you want?
The whole bag.
Okay. All right.
They're breaking out the drugs.
I didn't think cooper was a user.
As far as we know,he isn't.
You know my brother was so high once he
went right through a plate glass window.
There was blood everywhere,but,jimmy,he
didn't even know he was hurt.
That's what this stuff did to him.
Do you want me to cut it for you?
It's not for me.It's for him.
I don't touch that crap!
Okay,we just sell!We don't use.
Hey,if it's good enough for my
brother,it's good enough for yours!
Get down!
Okay,okay!All right,all right!
You want him to do a line?
That's cool,man.
No,not a line.
All of it.
That'll kill him.
Okay.
No!
let him go,man!Let him go,man!
Let him go!
Robert cooper!
This is sergeant gregory parker with
the police strategic response unit.
I need you to put down your weapon and exit
through the front door of the house immediately!
come on!Do it!
Robert cooper!
There's cops all around us,man!
You're done!
Now let him go and give yourself up!
Shut up!
Mr. Cooper,i need you to stay
away from the front windows
We'll be breaking the glass
and sending a phone in.
I need you to pick it up
and talk to me,all right?
Just a little privacy.
Just you and me.
I think they want you to answer it.
I said shut up!
Answer the damn phone!
Well,he's not picking
up,but at least we got ears.
Come on,cooper.
If you were gonna shoot
us,you'd have done it by now.
Grady... We didn't... We
didn't kill your brother,man.
Yes,you did!
He did it to himself.
He's escalating him.
We didn't force him to take drugs!
That was all on him!
He's trying to distract
him,throw him off his game.
You say you love your brother,why
didn't you stop him from using?
Shut up.
Maybe an intervention.
You better shut your mouth!
Immediate action,white door.
Go in now,now!
Everyone fall back!
Fall back!Fall back!
Status,status!
No harm.
I'm good.
Coming to you.
I'm done listening.We're going in.
Immediate action.
I think he's trying to force our hand,
to get us to storm in and end this.
Okay,that makes sense.
That makes sense.
He's never shot to kill before.
He wants us to do it for him.
No one's dying today.
Sam,what do you got?
two entrances,living room.
Two bedrooms upstairs.
You got a basement?
Yeah.
Okay,where do the stairs lead?
Back entrance goes
straight into the basement.
Basement stairs go right up to
the kitchen into the living room.
Right to the target.
Looks like it.
All right.
Let's stack it up.Watch the windows.
Got it.
Wordy,you're on point.
Alpha team,move in.
don't speak!Do not speak!
Robert cooper!
Shoot him!
We're not here to hurt anyone!
No,shoot him!
He's gonna kill my brother!
Nobody's gonna get shot today,robert.
Oh,so now you show up?
All these years,begging for your
help while these guys take over.
I hear you,buddy.
I hear you.
I just need you to put that gun down.
They destroyed everything
that my father ever built!
We know what you lost,robert!
They killed my brother.
I'm gonna put my weapon
down so we n talk,okay?
Robert,my name is kevin wordsworth.
My friends call me wordy.
I loved your dad's store.
What?
Yeah.
Yeah,he had a rack of those
old dime-store westerns,
but nobody ever bought 'em.
He let me just hang out and read 'em.
He never kicked me out for not buying.
That's the kind of man he was.
What,you think that i don't
know that he was a good man?
He worked his hands to the bone!
And then these...
Low-lifes,they come along and...
Wordy,we've got cooper's
wife,patty,here with us.
She's gonna help us out.
Your wife is here,robert.
She's real worried about you.
No,no,no,no,i have to do this,all right?
I have to do this for my brother jimmy.
Listen,i loved jimmy,too,but i know
that he wouldn't want bobby to do this.
She's telling me that jimmy wouldn't
want you to throw your life away.
There is no life!
There is no life.
They took away anything
that ever mattered to me!
What about patty?
She's right here and she loves you.
She's better off without me.
No!
That's not true.
We were gonna start a family.
Patty's all about your future.
You were gonna have kids.
Robert... You want to
honour your brother's memory?
Start living again.
No one is better off without you.
It's not right.
It's not right!
They should pay for what they did!
I know.
Okay,that's why i became
a cop and not a cowboy.
I'll make sure... I'll make sure
they get what's coming to them.
But not like this.
Bob,put the down.
Come on,man.
We gotta do this the right way,coop.
Put the gun down.
Come on,please.
Let's do this together,huh?
You and me.
Come on.
Good.
All the way down.All the
way down on the ground.
Drop it,drop it.
Now,get down on your knees.
That's it. That's it.
Hands behind your head.
Good job.
Thank you!Thank you.
*you act like you wonder *
*if i know * *right from wrong *
*believe me *
*i understand *
i've been thinking.
You know,it's not like by
the middle of next month
they'll have found all
the international bad guys
and i'll have missed my chance.
A guy could stay pretty busy keeping
the peace in his own backyard.
*i am who i am *
*and i am haunted *by the things *
*that you're saying*
you did good in there. Thanks.
One good thing came out of all this.
Cooper kept them so busy...
They never had time to
get rid of the goods.
Looks like they're going
away for a long time.
So tonight at 8:00,or what?
Can i get a rain check on the barbecue?
I,uh,have some phone
calls i have to make.
No problem. Yeah?
I told 'em,michaelangelo scarlatti,
code name "spike," is
a disgrace to the force.
I mean he cracks under pressure.
He can't shoot his
way out of a paper bag.
He can't be trusted with sensitive
information on a surprise party,
let alone national security.
He can't type if his
life depended on it.
No,wait,that's what i wanted to say.
Boss,they were headhunting me.
Okay,no,it's not like i was-
i mean you get to see the
world,international intrigue.
Young guy like you,right?
Just when you make the
choice,spike,i will support it,okay?
Boss,need you outside.
I'm comin'.
Teni mi informato.
Keep you posted,boss.
*i'll try to defend our lives *
*i will try to defend*
*our lives *
*and you'll understand *
*that i won't let you down *
*hey, hey, hey, hey... *
wanna help me out?
*i am haunted by the things *
*that you're saying to me *
*and i try to defend *
* *
*i will try to defend our lives*
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly
Presents
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET- °îµÂÖí Åùö¨±´±´