Guys, I got a signal.
Lower lever, north quadrant.
Ed: 'Kay, listen up.
This guy knows the terrain.
We go in hard and fast.
Boss, get him on the phone,
keep him occupied.
Copy that.
Man: What're you thinking, Parker?
I had it under control.
Parker: It looked ragged.
I made a call.
Why don't you come on in
and we'll debrief.
Ed:
In position.
Man:
Well, you know what?
I'll bring my sidearm,
you bring your inkblots,
we'll see who makes
a better case.
Ed, Raf and Sam:
Police! Freeze! SRU!
Boss, signal relay.
He's not here.
Greg, come in.
Greg.
Boss, make some noise.
He's got Greg.
Raf: I know this hasn't
been an easy day for you, Tim.
Tim: No it hasn't
, and it's her fault!
Raf: Okay, but I don't think
you wanna harm your wife.
I don't think that's how
you want this to go.
Tim: Don't you tell
me what to do!
Raf:
She's afraid, Tim.
This can't be easy for her.
You're scaring her.
I don't wanna scare her.
Raf:
'Course not.
'Course not, Tim.
So how 'bout you let her go,
and you and I, we can sit down
and talk this through, okay?
Just the two of us.
I'm worthless.
I don't wanna scare her.
I'm with you on that, Tim.
We're gonna work through this.
Aw, come on!
See the suicide cues, Raf?
Calmness.
Introspection.
Doesn't always
mean cooperation,
sometimes it means
he's given up.
Come on, buddy.
The first day on the job.
The bridge jumper, remember?
Yeah.
Parker:
What else did you see?
Raf:
He was tidying himself.
Parker:
And you kept pushing him.
Again.
(Sighs) Again.
Hey! Who is in the monitor room?
Decklan: We're just
having a cigarette, Gil.
Who's covering?
Would you relax?
We're just giving these
lighting dudes some pointers.
You should be on your route.
Decklan:
Seriously, dude.
Your job's not to patrol around
looking for other
security guards.
You do know that, right?
Yeah, I know my job.
I'm not the one who takes
unscheduled breaks everyday.
Listen, it's 15 minutes.
Either you want to join us?
Or do you can back right off
and let us finish our smokes?
(Laughs)
(Panting)
Raf:
I appreciate that, Tim.
Now, I'm gonna holster my gun.
And maybe we can talk about
what's going on here, okay?
I've said my piece.
Raf: I'd just like
to hear some more,
if that's okay?
Just talk to me.
Just tell me
what happened here today.
(Gunshot pops twice,
Raf groans, agitated)
Parker:
And... you're dead.
Spike:
Really dead.
Raf:
You said he just had the 9-mil!
Parker:
Yeah, I got it wrong.
Raf: - Are you serious?!
Parker: - That'll happen.
(Incredulous laughter)
Parker: - Let's go again.
Raf: - Come on!
Ed:
Zero for nine, Raf.
You gotta step it up, buddy.
Raf: Ed, I was getting
through to you?
I was getting through to him.
Really?
I see a shot cop.
Raf:
Okay, so what's next?
Someone gonna bust through
the window with an uzi?
Parker: Hey!
Every one of these scenarios
come from case files.
Every outcomes has happened.
This is real life.
Now the moment
you start thinking
that you've got
all the angles covered,
you have failed, my friend.
Do you hear me?
Yes, sir.
Parker: We've been at
this for three hours,
you must be tired.
No, no, I'm fine.
Parker: Good,
'cause we're going again.
(Keypad lock beeps)
(Door clunks shut)
(Keypad beeps and trills)
(Door keypad beeps)
Get back!
Don't make...
Don't make noise.
Just get back!
What was that about?
Oh come on, Eddie.
He needed to hear it.
Remember how long it took me
to get that drill?
Yeah.
Remember I had to
get into your face too?
Spike:
Hey, chin up.
That's why we do the exercises.
You passed it?
Spike:
We all passed it.
You're really used to getting
A's on the report card,
aren't you?
Don't sweat it, Raf.
Takes time.
(Call bell rings)
Armed robbery
at Fletcher stadium.
Subject has a knife,
possible hostage situation.
911 caller is Decklan Pownell,
he works security
at the stadium.
(Sirens wail)
Parker:
Mr. pownell?
Decklan: Yeah.
You guys gotta get up there,
the guy's crazy,
he's got Roger.
Roger a colleague of yours?
Yeah, he walked in on him
in the money room;
the guy pulled a knife.
We tried to intervene, but...
Parker:
Who's "we", sir?
Me and Gil.
Another guard.
We tried to calm him down,
but he flipped out.
Okay, it's all right.
Where are they now?
A luxury suite.
He dragged Roger in there.
Ed: Okay, Decklan, how many
people in the building?
Small lighting crew.
Six security staff.
Okay, have 'em drop
what they're doing,
and exit immediately.
- Do you understand me?
- Yes.
Parker: One subject, one
hostage, one knife.
Let's fill in some blanks.
Ed:
Okay, guys, here we go.
Sam, Raf, take the suite.
Spike, CCTV.
Jules, money room.
Jules:
Copy.
Ed: Boos, I'm gonna try
to get a Sierra shot.
Parker:
Good. Go.
I need to get through
to that suite.
Yeah, yeah, follow me,
there's a phone
in the security room.
Just...
Just think, Danny, just think.
(Phone rings, Danny gasps)
Are you gonna get that?
Shut up!
Shut up while I think!
(Phone rings in the distance)
Sam, he's not answering.
Give him a nudge.
(Sam knocks at the door)
Sir, this is Sam Braddock
from the Police Strategic
Response Unit.
We need to talk to you,
please answer the phone.
(Phone smashes)
He's not so keen to talk, boss.
Parker:
Copy that.
Spike, let me know
when you got eyes in.
Spike:
Yeah, 220 of them,
but none where we want 'em.
There's no camera in there?
Uh, they're executive suites.
You know, these guys
like their privacy.
Eddie?
What do you see?
Ed: Not good, boss
, glare and shadow.
Hang on.
Boss, we got a bogey.
We got a security guard
on the balcony.
Your guys are still out there?
Decklan: It's gotta be Gil, I mean,
everyone else is accounted for.
He must've took cover
on the balcony.
Sir, it's him.
Gil calling.
Parker: Gil.
This is sergeant Greg Parker,
I'm with the Police Strategic
Response Unit.
Gil:
Hello, Greg Parker.
Parker:
Are you safe?
Gil:
Yeah, I'm hidden.
Hey, buddy,
can you get out of there?
No, they're between me
and the door.
Parker: Okay, Gil, can you tell
me if the hostage is hurt?
Gil: No, no, no, he looks fine.
He's just scared.
Subject is Caucasian,
5' 10", dark hair.
I heard him call himself
"Danny."
He's got a 7-inch blade,
I think it's a bowie knife.
Gil, that's very helpful.
Thank you.
Spike, see what you can do
with that.
Got it, boss.
Parker: Okay, Gil, I
need you to stay low
stay quiet, all right?
We're gonna get you
outta there.
Hey, sarge, I think I should
talk to this guy.
No, I don't want you
to do that.
Danny: It wasn't supposed
to go like this.
Gil: No, no, no, I hear remorse.
I think I can get through him.
Parker:
Gil, that is a negative.
One wrong word
and he could escalate.
You gotta trust me
on this here, buddy.
All right.
Parker:
Thank you.
Okay, team, listen up.
Good news
is we've got eyes inside
and, ah, things seem calm
for the moment.
So talk to me,
who're we dealing with here?
It's gotta be a smash and grab,
right?
Parker: So he gets
interrupted, panics.
Eddie?
Fits the bill.
He's volatile,
he's got no demands...
Yeah. I hear a "but".
I don't know, I mean,
the place isn't exactly
a liquor store, right?
Jules: - Boss?
Parker: - Yeah, Jules?
Money room's three floors up
behind an unmarked door.
Cameras, keycard entry,
regenerating password,
and that's all before
you even reach the safe.
Raf:
So much for smash and grab.
Parker: So he's
high-tech on the way in,
hunting knife on the way out?
Boss, got a partial off CCTV
and matched it
to the description.
Our subject is Danny Lucic.
Drugs, assault.
Mostly small-time.
His one star turn
was an attempted robbery
at a credit union,
and he took a teller hostage
at knife-point.
How'd that end?
Spike: Teller got a
punctured radial artery
and Danny got three years
hard time.
It wasn't supposed
to go like this.
Gil:
Sergeant, we got a situation.
(Heaving grunt)
Ed: Whoa, gun in play.
Gun in play.
Gil, talk to me.
Gil: No, no, no-no-no-no.
Danny: I said stay put!
Roger:
(Pained cries)
Freeze! Right there!
Ed:
No visual.
Gil, talk to me, please.
Danny:
Back off!
Okay, calm down, mister.
Just relax.
Parker: - Gil!
Danny: - Back off.
Back off or he dies!
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
My name is Gil Collins
and I'm here to help you.
Danny: If you take one
more step forward
I will cut his throat out!
Eddie, what do you see?
Our civilian's gone cowboy.
He's charged in there
with a big piece.
All I got's his back.
We breach now, we are right
in the line of fire.
You guys carry guns?
I've never touched a gun
in my life.
Okay... ah...
Just calm down.
Look, I'm gonna
put the gun away.
Okay?
I'm putting it down.
Now listen to me.
That man that you're holding
is named Roger.
He's a friend of mine,
this'd be a lot easier
if you'd just lower
the blade a little.
He's humanizing the hostage.
Roger:
Listen to him, mister
you keep your mouth shut!
And you back off!
I'm not coming closer, I swear.
Okay?
You have my word.
I just... I wanna talk.
Okay?
Can we just talk?
Okay.
Thank you.
Subject's de-escalating.
It wasn't supposed
to go like this.
I understand.
Your name's Danny, right?
How'd you know that?
I was just outside,
I overheard.
Danny: It wasn't supposed
to go like this.
It was supposed to be fast.
No one around!
Okay, but you haven't
done anything
that can't be made right.
All right?
So let's not change that.
Let's just work this out, okay?
I gotta get outta here.
Gil:
All right.
And I wanna help you with that.
I'm just gonna talk
to some people
on the other end of this phone.
Police?!
Gil:
Yes, police, okay?
But they're gonna make sure
that we all get outta here
unharmed.
Look, it's what they do.
It's their job, okay?
Just... let me talk to 'em.
I'm not gonna move,
I'm just gonna talk.
(Roger coughs weakly)
Sergeant?
Yeah, Gil,
you're doing great, Gil.
Is Roger hurt?
Gil:
Affirmative
abdominal penetration.
Okay, team,
we got a wounded hostage.
Eddie?
Entry options?
We got a gun, we got a knife,
we got a cornered subject,
we are half-blind.
Alpha, you have got
to get eyes in there now.
Pole cam.
From the suite above.
Sam, do it now.
Quick and quiet.
Parker:
Gil.
We're working out
a solution here, buddy.
You just keep Danny calm.
Will do.
Parker: Let him know
I'd like to talk to him,
but don't pressure him.
Right?
Let him set the pace.
Okay, I got it.
Parker: And don't
promise him anything.
I said I got it.
You do your job, I'll do mine.
Winnie, EMS here?
Winnie:
Standing by.
Jules: Boss, I found a
keycard at the scene.
The log shows a direct route
from the outside
into the money room.
It's gotta be how Danny got in.
Who's it registered to?
Spike:
No, it's a blank.
After-market.
If you know the system,
you can make a skeleton key.
If you know the system.
Jules: That's where
this is leading too.
Sophisticated, pre-planned.
I mean, either Danny's
seriously upped his game...
Or he's got help.
Okay, Jules, known associates,
family history.
On it.
Parker: Spike, check the
stadium employee list for priors.
See who pops.
Copy. But, boss?
The break-in's all over
the security tape.
You looking for an accomplice,
you might wanna start
with who was working
the monitors.
This your post, Decklan?
Yeah. Why?
You on shift this morning?
Okay, look,
I took a cigarette break.
It was ten minutes,
I swear to God.
You left the monitors
unattended?
Yeah, but...
Look, you gotta believe me.
I don't know anything
about this.
I mean, Roger's a friend
of mine,
why would I do this to him?
I shoulda listened to Gil.
Gil?
He caught us smoking
this morning.
Started nagged us
about doing our job.
This happened today?
Happens all the time.
We just blew him off.
I mean, that's Gil.
He takes everything
so seriously.
Officer.
I screwed up.
We're gonna get your friend
outta there, Decklan.
It's okay.
Hey, Spike?
Our guy Gil,
he knew the monitors
were unmanned.
Well, funny you should say.
He just came up.
Criminal record?
Spike:
Other side of the ledger.
He was a cop.
Gil Collins.
Looks like he's been off
the force a couple of years.
Explains the piece.
Jules:
And the language.
Yeah, but from cop to this?
Spike: I've heard of
quitting the force
for the private sector, but...
Parker: Okay, Jules, let's
pull up his police file,
see who we're dealing with
here.
Copy.
Gil: Sergeant?
Danny has some demands
he'd like to pass on.
Okay.
I want a bullet proof vest!
And I want a car.
No, motorcycle!
I want something fast!
Parker:
Okay, I got it, I got it.
Gil, negotiation's good;
That's a step forward.
And you have 20 minutes!
And I want a clear path
outta here, no cops.
I see anyone and I'm gonna
finish this guy off,
I swear to God!
You just keep him talking.
Tell him we'll do our best.
Just keep him engaged.
Roger:
(Wheezed breaths)
They're working
on your demands, okay?
I'm...
Hey, hey...
I'm just gonna go
stand here okay.
It's all I'm doing.
Sam, I'm losing visual!
Two minutes.
Danny:
They have 20 minutes!
Hey, Gil, how's Roger doing?
Roger:
(Dry coughs)
Gil:
Faster's better, sergeant.
Parker:
I copy that.
Hey, you never told me
you were police, Gil.
Hey, I got a little bit
on my plate here, Parker.
Jules: All right, boss, Gil
Collins was a cop on the rise.
Breezed through the academy.
Couple commendations of merit,
but after a few years
on the force,
things took a turn.
Run-ins with superiors,
insubordination.
Got busted down.
Terminated about two years ago.
On what grounds?
Jules: Not specified.
"Unfit for duty."
I got something else for you,
boss.
I checked Gil's pass code
against the log...
About three minutes before
Danny entered the building,
Gil walked the exact same
route to the money room.
Clearing a path.
Jules:
Sure looks that way.
Hey, Spike,
where was Danny arrested
for that credit union job?
Dundas and Dovercourt.
14 division.
Gil's beat.
Parker:
Okay, team, listen up.
Things are getting fluid here.
I'm thinking Gil
is our inside man.
Okay, boss,
make that make sense.
Parker: Okay, let's say he
set this whole thing up,
it's a two-person job,
he needs a bagman.
So where does he turn?
His cop past.
Parker:
And Danny's got the perfect MO,
so Gil makes contact,
he keeps it anonymous,
and he tells him
he's got a big score for him.
Sets him up with a keycard
and a map...
Parker:
And no one's at the monitors,
he cues Danny
and they're on our way.
Perfect inside job.
So the question is,
what is he doing now?
Covering his tracks?
Eliminate his accomplice?
Jules:
Or he got cold feet,
wants to put the brakes on.
Sam! I need eyes!
Seconds away...
We have a visual.
Visual's up.
Routing it to you
right now, boss.
I know him.
Ed:
Who?
Parker:
Gil. The cop.
Winnie, Gil Collins?
He ever try out for SRU?
Gil Collins...
He did, twice, we have a file.
Jules, get down to the station,
pull that file.
I everything we have
on that guy.
Psych evals, fit-for duty
tests, all of it.
On my way.
Danny, I got a proposal.
You let Roger,
I take his place.
Why the hell I do that?
What're you doing, Gil?
Gil: Look at him,
he's hurt really bad,
you don't want him to die.
How many times I gotta tell you
to stay back?!
Parker: Gil, I need you
stop engaging him.
Back down.
Gil: I got this, boss. Trust me.
Look, he dies,
this goes really bad for you.
Danny: - Hey, I'm warning you!
Gil: - Let him go,
he gets patched up,
you take me, it's all good.
Gil, you're scaring him.
Alpha team, less lethal.
Ed: Copy that. Rubber bullets.
Raf, seconds away.
Parker: Gil, please
, listen to me.
You are losing him.
He will attack.
I'll not let that happen.
Danny:
I will cut him,
and I will cut you!
I will cut his throat!
Ed:
Gotta move, boss,
we gotta move now.
Alpha team, go!
Now, now!
You take knife.
I'll take gun on three,
one, two, three!
(Raf bashes against door)
Sam and Raf:
Police! Everyone down!
Drop your weapon!
Everyone down!
Gil:
No! No!
Roger:
(Pained cry)
(Moans)
Ah!
(Pained grunt)
Hostage has been shot.
Our security guard
fired a round.
You breached.
You startled him,
I had no choice.
Sam: - Drop your weapon!
Gil: - I had no choice!
Sam: I said drop your weapon!
Drop your weapon now!
(Grunts of exertion)
Raf:
Whoa! Whoa!
Danny:
(Impact grunts)
Ed:
Subject on the move!
Hey, stay where you are!
Gil, stop right there.
(Pants and grunts)
Gil, gimme your hand.
Come on, don't risk it.
Here.
Don't do this, Gil.
Gil!
Gil, stop!
Danny: - Ungh!
Raf: - Don't move.
All clear, get EMS in here!
I lost him.
Spike?
Spike:
He's in the blind spots.
No, wait...
West, maybe.
Ed:
Gotta get a lock on his cell phone.
On it.
Decklan,
what was in the safe today?
Uh, some register floats.
Maybe a thousand bucks.
And on a big day?
Game night? Probably 150,000
goes through there.
Ed:
What are you thinking, boss?
I'm thinking this wasn't
about money.
I'm thinking this was about
being a cop again.
He set this whole thing up
so he could stop it?
Step in and save the day.
Parker: Prove that he's
SRU material after all.
Parker:
An officer needs assistance,
you're the first on scene.
You see the officer being
beaten by a male subject,
but there's a 30 foot
chain link fence between you.
The officer is losing
consciousness,
what do you do?
Neutralize the subject.
Lethal?
Officer down, no choice.
Parker:
So, no hesitation?
Gil: Okay, so you wanna
see some reluctance,
is that it?
Parker: Try not to think about
what I'd like to see, Gil.
Just answer honestly.
Gil: Officer's in danger
, you gotta take the shot.
Parker:
Okay.
That's protocol.
You're saying it's not?
Parker:
No, I'm not saying that.
Gil: I could call out,
see if the subject responds.
Parker:
And if he does?
Gil: Then I don't take shot.
Obviously.
Parker: Are you
changing your answer then?
(Pants)
You're trying to corner me.
Parker:
No, that's not my intention.
Gil:
Then I neutralize the subject.
That's it!
No hesitation.
(Cocks gun)
Ed:
Danny, who set this up?
I know you didn't plan this,
so who did?
He talks you let us know.
Go.
How's he doing?
Not so good.
Spike:
Guys, I got a signal!
Lower level, north quadrant.
He's not moving.
Ed: - What's down there?
Spike: - Storage room.
Could be digging in.
Let's go.
Okay, listen up.
This guy's knows the terrain.
We go in hard and fast.
Boss, get him on the phone,
keep him occupied.
Copy that.
(Phone rings)
What were you thinking, Parker?
I had it under control.
It looked ragged, Gil,
I made a call.
I had him!
You screwed it up!
Parker: Listen, Gil,
why don't you come on in
and we'll debrief.
Gil:
Oh, now you wanna debrief?
Okay, how 'bout this...
You know what?
There was a time when a cop
just had to be a cop.
Now he's gotta be a shrink too.
Parker: Is that what
this is about, Gil?
Maybe there's room for both.
Ed:
In position.
Gil: Well, you know what?
Let's meet up,
I'll bring my sidearm,
you bring your ink blots,
we'll see who
makes a better case.
Ed, Sam and Raf:
Police! SRU!
Boss, signal relay.
He's not here.
Still with me, Gil?
Yeah, can't talk right now,
Parker.
I got places to be.
Ed: He's playing us, boss.
New plan.
We'll drift-net.
Vertical line, one per floor.
Let's move.
Jules: Okay, Gil Collins
first tried out
for the SRU four years ago.
Tactical scores
were off the charts,
psych eval came up short.
Tried again the following year,
same results.
After that, he just spiraled.
Fights with his partners.
Problems at home.
Divorced.
Parker:
You talk to his ex?
Jules:
She's on her way here now.
There's something else, boss.
He filed a grievance
against you.
I don't remember that.
Jules:
Well, it was dismissed.
It didn't get high enough
up the chain
for you to be notified.
Here's the thing is,
I don't think that today
is about proving to the world
that he's a good cop.
It's about proving it to you.
(Sighs and pants)
Just like you, Parker.
Code red
and you're still holstered.
Decklan:
Gil. Dude...
Gil:
Shut it, Decklan.
Over here on the floor.
Hands behind your head.
Move!
Decklan:
Okay.
Stay there, or he dies.
Turn around.
(Magazine clanks)
You're smaller than I remember.
Turn around.
Do you remember me?
Yeah I do, Gil.
Wanna talk about that?
No!
You don't get to talk.
You only get to talk
if I tell you to talk,
do you understand?
Yeah.
Wrists. Him.
Tie up his wrists!
Ed: Boss, what's the
status on our backup?
Spike, is Parker with you?
Negative.
Greg, make some noise.
Tell him headed South.
I can't do that, Gil.
Gil:
South across the bowl.
Tell them.
Ed:
Greg, talk to me.
I'm here, Eddie.
Subject is headed South,
repeat, he's headed toward
the South end of the bowl.
Ed: Okay, team one,
you heard the man.
Stop the sweep.
I need everybody to regroup
on level one.
Parker:
Back-up's on the way, Ed,
so move with caution
and stay frosty.
He's got Greg.
Guys, switch channels.
Spike?
I'm here, I heard it.
Ed: Get Parker's
headset offline now.
Gil:
Isn't that interesting?
You told them to head South,
but they're not complying.
Is it "frosty", Parker?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
The distress code.
Is it "stay frosty"?
Yeah.
(Half laughs)
Thought it was a little
hot dog for you.
Ed: Raf and I will go to
the last point of contact.
Sam, underground parking.
Spike, you watch those exits.
Every door, every window -
he does not get outta here
with Parker,
do you understood me?
Copy, Ed.
Let's go.
And of course, here they come.
Listen, Gil, buddy,
whatever you're up to-
shut it, Decklan!
Gil?
If we got stuff to work out,
let's just focus here, okay?
If you had let me work it out
in the other room,
none of this would be
happening.
What is happening, Gil?
Plan b.
Let me ask you something.
How's your hand-to-hand?
Think you can, ah...
Disarm me?
No I don't.
See, that's too bad.
'Cause we're gonna go
for a little walk,
and I was really hoping
that you would try.
Turn around.
Hands down.
Behind your back.
Let's go for that walk.
Hi.
Thanks for coming.
I'm Jules Callaghan,
I talked to you on the phone.
Why don't you have a seat?
You said this is about Gil.
Is he in trouble?
We're trying
to figure that out.
Are you still
in touch with him?
He sees our son.
But it's not easy between us.
Can you tell me why?
For a while we tried
staying in each other's lives,
for Jacob,
but Gil has so much anger.
He blames me for the divorce.
It...
It just got toxic.
When was the last time
you saw him?
This morning.
Jakey, let's go.
Hi.
Gil...
I'm sorry,
I know it's not Friday,
but today's an exception.
Can I just...
Can I just get 30 seconds?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Look, I don't wanna
say too much,
I don't wanna spoil it,
but I...
I got something going at work.
That's good, Gil.
I'm happy for you.
Thanks.
I know what you're thinking.
And that it's been hard,
and that's on me,
that's my fault.
But I just want you to know
I've never been more proud
of anything in my life
than I am of you.
You and jakey.
And I know it's up to me
to make you proud of me.
Again.
For us.
For us?
(Front door opens)
Gil: - There he is!
Jake: - Hi dad!
Gil: Hey, buddy! Guess what?
Special day.
I am walking you to school.
Great!
Gil. Please.
You just love this, don't you?
Holding all the cards.
There is nothing about this
that I love.
Ah, you know what, pal?
I just remembered
I got something I gotta do.
So can I get a rain check?
Something to look forward to?
Thanks, buddy.
Have a good day, pal.
Come here, you.
Please.
Tell me what's going on,
Officer Callaghan.
Does the name Greg Parker
mean anything to you?
Yeah.
Gil talked about him
all the time.
Gil:
After you flunked me,
I got my hands
on my evaluation.
Go left.
You remember what you said?
No.
Six years of my life,
thousands of hours
on the range,
in the gym,
in the psych manuals...
You don't remember
what you said?
Sorry, Gil,
I do a lot of evaluations.
Gil: "Good tactical.
Unfit to negotiate."
Gil, you have to understand,
we get a hundred applicants
a year,
that's a lot of great
candidates turned away.
Five words, Parker.
You used five words
to ruin my life.
Move.
Move!
Ed:
You all right?
Agh!
Which way did they go?
Up.
(Monitor beeps)
- There.
- Sam, Spike!
Two rifles, stadium floor, now!
Ed: - Stay here!
Decklan: - Got it.
(Hand cuffs rasp and clank)
Down we go, boss.
(Sighs)
Gotta tell you, Gil,
I'm not crazy about heights.
Overcome it.
Ed:
Guys.
(Buckles clank)
Parker: You wanna tell me
what you're thinking here, Gil?
It's tactical, Parker.
You wouldn't appreciate it.
(Panicked breaths)
Don't do it, Gil.
Please, you don't wanna
do this.
(Ropes rasp, buckles clank)
Guys, full hay setup up here.
Gil:
Oh... sprint shoot.
My best drill.
200 yard dash,
setup up their rifle,
dead-center a target
at a half-mile.
Let's set up right here.
Go, go, go!
Let's go, let's go.
Sorry, Parker.
Problem is they shoot me?
They kill you too.
(Rifles click)
He's gonna push him!
(Rifle cocks)
Raf:
Hold fire! Hold fire!
(Gil grunts, Parker gasps)
We shoot him,
he lets go of the rope.
Parker:
(Panicked breaths)
What do you want from me, Gil?
Thought it was obvious.
I want a lesson.
You got an agitated subject
bent on revenge.
So show me how it's done,
Parker.
Talk me down!
I'm not seeing tac on this.
Spike: He's got vantage.
Distance. Full control.
Anything we do, he drops boss.
He's got every angle covered.
Jules, give me something,
why's he doing this?
Jules:
Well, Gil shows signs
of narcissistic personality
disorder,
it's a preoccupation
with prestige and power.
Attention.
It's built on shame,
fear of inadequacy.
And when things go bad,
when things feed that fear,
troubled relationships,
failure at work,
people with NPD they usually
resort to "splitting".
Spike: - Splitting?
Raf: - All-or-nothing thinking.
White hats and black hats.
Jules: Yeah, it's how he
preserves his self-esteem;
by ascribing his own failures
to the actions of others.
A good guy under attack
by monsters.
Can you get through to him?
The psychology's
really tricky on this.
He's vulnerable, raw.
It's a minefield.
Jules, we're running out
of options here.
I'm gonna call, Ed.
I'm gonna call.
Gil:
So. Assessment time.
What do you make
of the subject, Parker?
Parker: Hey, look...
(Gil's phone rings)
Sorry, that'll be, ah...
That'll be your boys.
Excuse me while I get that.
(Phone smashes)
They can't help you now.
It's just you and me.
I wanna have a conversation
with you, Gil,
but this...
Wha! Ah!
Assess the subject.
All right.
You know what I see?
I see a good man
who's in a lot of pain.
The sweet talk.
No, no, no, no...
I see a guy who doesn't always
have the easiest time
fitting in.
Because what comes naturally
for most folks,
the day-today living stuff,
just doesn't come
so easy to you.
You're wrong.
I'll bet when you joined
the academy,
all that changed?
Right?
Suddenly you felt like
your life made sense
for the first time.
Am I right, Gil?
Am I right?
We gotta get up there.
Try him face to face.
Does he look like
he wants company, Spike?
Spike: So what're we gonna do?
Watch?!
Hope for the best?
Shockround.
The electrical charge
will keep his grip firm.
Involuntary muscle contracture.
It'll gives us time
to make a play.
Come down from above,
and get a rope around boss.
And then neutralize
the subject.
There's a thousand ways
that can go wrong.
It'll have to happen in,
what, five seconds?
Raf: If that.
Sam: Plus he's armoured.
It's gotta take a perfect shot.
Raf:
It's all we got.
Let's do it.
Sam, you take the shot.
On my cue.
Raf?
Raf: - I'll harness up.
Ed: - Spike?
Spike:
Okay, I'm on the mic.
Ed: I'll stay on Sierra.
I will finish it if I have to.
Parker:
And I know, I know.
I know how it goes, buddy.
You put on a uniform,
and all the labels
get rewritten.
"Headstrong"
becomes "dedicated".
And "reckless"
becomes "fearless".
And all the stuff
that you fought inside,
all the demons...
Now they're your assets.
Right?
They're your assets.
They're the things
that keep you alive.
that make you good.
How do you know that?
One... one cop to another,
brother, that's how.
(Pants)
Gil:
No.
Nice try, Parker, you know.
I see that you're trying
to connect.
But I'm not some meth-head
with a knife.
You can't fool me!
No, that's not what
I'm trying to do.
Yes it is!
It's Greg Parker to a tee.
So smug his feet
don't touch the ground
until some nutcase
picks up a gun.
Spike:
Ears are up.
Gil:
...But you know what?
You're leaving out
the most important thing.
Please, please tell me
what that is.
You took it from me!
All of it!
I aced every drill,
but I wasn't good enough
for you
because some role-playing
exercise
didn't go the way
you wanted it to!
You've been gunning for me
since day one, Parker.
Just like today.
Determined to see me fail!
So I push back.
I told Miranda.
You know what I said to her?
I said, "he's testing me.
He's testing my resolve."
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna work harder.
I'm gonna try again.
I'm gonna show him all.
(Buckles clank)
(Rifle clanks)
Gil: But you know what
I didn't count on?
Everyone taking your side.
My sergeant, my own partner,
everyone.
You poisoned 'em against me.
Parker: It was my
face on that setback.
I get that, Gil.
I get that.
You don't get the last word
this time.
(Gil grunts, Parker yelps)
I've got a teenage son.
And he did the bravest thing
I'd ever seen,
he let his deadbeat dad
back into his life.
It's all I wanted for years,
it's all I thought about.
And guess what?
Now that it's happened,
I wake up at night and I think,
I say to myself,
I should push him away now.
Push him away now
so I don't do it by accident
down the road.
Gil: Stop talking.
You're just gonna say anything
to try and get outta this.
Parker: You think I'm
gunning for you?
Let me tell you something,
I've got a whole team
down there
who depend on me.
You know how I've repaid
their trust?
I've kept secrets from them,
I've lied to them,
I've broken protocol.
That's right.
Lives and careers
and relationships...
They could all
go down the tube,
and that would all be on me.
And you know...
And you know why I do that?
Because I don't know
any other way!
It's the best I can figure out!
No, no, no...
You're trying to trick me.
You're trying to build empathy.
Parker: I'm not negotiating
with you, Gil!
I'm saying my piece!
You think you know me.
You think I'm one kind
of thing,
well I'm not!
I'm something else.
I'm not after you.
I don't even know you.
I've got enough going on
in my life
you're not part of it, buddy.
You misread this,
you understand?
You're wrong!
On my word.
Parker: But if you let
go of this rope,
you'll become the thing
that you hate.
You'll become the thing
that you think I am.
You get that?
So what's it gonna be?
Who are you?
'Cause I'm done talking.
On three.
One...
Two...
Hold! Hold!
(Pants)
Miranda was right.
Parker: - Gil...
Gil: - Parker, you're right.
Parker:
No!
Gil, please don't.
Just stay here with me.
No, I see it now.
It's okay.
Parker: No, you made
a good choice, Gil.
You just focus on that, buddy.
You just focus that.
Introspection...
Parker: No, no, there's
a way through this.
You gotta build
from this moment.
You gotta move forward
from here.
You work though it from here.
You're a good man!
(Parker's voice echoes)
Here... good man...
You're a good man...
...A good man...
(Somber music plays)
Spike?
Talk to Winnie?
- Yep.
- What's in your hand?
It's the audio drive.
Gotta get rid of it.
Ed, what boss said up there
has no bearing on the case.
It's not our call.
He was torn wide open.
He was fighting for his life.
There's no reason why
everybody's hear that.
It could cost him his job, Ed.
I hear ya.
Parker:
Spike.
Give it to me, Spike.
Boss, no one needs to know
we used the parabolic.
It doesn't affect
the investigation in any way.
It all goes in.
Every word.
No more secrets.
How you holding up?
I killed him Eddie.
Greg, he was unwell.
Killed himself.
He was splitting.
He set out to slay the monster
and I convinced him he was it.
Greg, he was trying
to kill you.
He was trying to kill you.
You did what you had to do
here, buddy.
You did what you had to do.
I got angry.
I got angry and I lost control.
Parker: Why do you
want to be an SRU?
That one's easy.
Heh.
Um...
You know how
when you're out on patrol
you meet a lot of people
but you, you look...
Raf: Um, just got
word from the hospital.
The hostage, Roger,
he's gonna be okay.
Uh, I've been thinking
about this morning.
The exercise.
I think I know the solution.
Go on.
There is no solution.
The failure, it's...
It's built in, you know.
And it ain't even about
beating the drill,
it's not that, it's about...
It's about learning to live
with the choices you've made.
My man.
Boss, I want you to know
that I am honored
to be learning this job
from the best.
Gil:
So, uh... I don't know,
you take all the things that
I love about being a beat cop
and all the things
that I'm good at,
and you multiply that by 10
and that's...
It's SRU for me.
So, I mean,
I don't wanna be greedy,
but you know it feels
this right to be a cop.
(Papers flitter)
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com