we got a possible i.e.d.:
batteries, wires, pipe.
five...
confirming no visible
identification.
four...
blocking remote detonators.
three...
gonna try chemical detection
for any nerve agents.
two...
this isn't good.
one...
fire in the hole.
(4 hour earlier)
i'm dyin' already.
want me write you a note,
get you outta class?
could you?
would you, officer lane?
boss, what's the word?
we gotta guy
comin' in for the ac.
hallelujah! okay!
tomorrow.
oh, come on. nice.
okay, we're gonna hit
the briefing room
and then we're gonna patrol
in air conditioned comfort.
have i told you recently
how much i really do
love you?
hello, boys.
jules.
how do manage
to stay so fresh?
i think cool thoughts.
kira, we're gonna hit
the streets.
team two's gonna hit rexdale.
sergeant rangford.
that's, uh, mr. rangford
to you, sir.
hey, don't call me "sir,"
i work for a living.
how're you doing,
daniel?
i'm doing fine.
it's good to see you, greg.
good to see you, too.
you look good.
what're you doing haunting
the barn?
a day like today
you should be out
hitting the golf course.
what are you kiddin' me?
you been out there?
you don't call,
you don't write...
eddie!
how you doin'?
fine. fine.
so?
how's sophie and clark?
they're good.
they're all good. yeah.
sru.
spike! you still wear
the rookie badge?
nunh-unh.
this is sam braddock.
he's new
but he's trying.
good to meet you.
i'm danny.
hot call, team one.
gear up!
what do we got?
suspicious package.
train station,
south terminal.
babycakes, i'm comin'!
let's go.
hey, danny!
keep the peace, boys.
who called it in?
a security guard.
he says the suitcase
has been there almost an hour.
copy that.
we gotta keep
that perimeter wide,
we gotta keep it locked down.
hey, who was the guy
at the station?
danny rangford.
most decent, honest cop
i ever met in my life.
the guy's a legend,
retired about a year ago.
he's the guy
that brought me into sru.
yeah?
yeah. him and barney fletcher.
the two of them.
they fought to have us trained
in psychology and negotiation.
if it wasn't for them,
we'd be straight-up swat.
so he was commander.
never made it passed sergeant.
avoided promotion.
why?
keeps you in the action.
i thought maybe
it was the booze.
you didn't smell it
off him?
you new?
three weeks.
uh, look,
do you know
if anyone's using
the briefing room
in the next little while?
mm, i don't think so.
team three's going off shift,
team one's out.
good. i just wanna get
a few things in order.
is it okay
if i use the room?
go ahead.
i'm just gonna have
a walkabout first.
that okay?
mm-hmm.
strategic response unit.
okay.
morning, sergeant.
inspector stainton.
what's the word?
we're not liking this.
there's been a spike
in terrorist chat
last two weeks.
station sees over 200,000
commuters a day.
i'd say it has "hot spot"
written all over it.
sam, north containment.
lewis west;
copy.
wordy, east;
spike, do your thing;
jules, second the boss.
stay connected.
we're gonna need
everyone's brain on this one.
let's get to know our friend.
kira, can i trouble you a sec?
mm-hm.
there's a file
i've been meaning to look at.
a file?
yeah,
it's number 5512,
you'll find it
under team four, 1989.
okay.
what's this in regard to?
ah... just getting
a presentation together.
you know. old boys
on a lecture circuit.
uh, it's probably not
on the computer.
uh, look,
if it's any trouble
i can always go down
to the archives myself.
oh no, no, no.
it's no trouble.
i just need to clear it
with commander holleran.
uh... what do you need
to do that for?
oh, i just can't release files
without permission.
it's policy.
uh, well, it's not like
it's a breach of uh...
anyone's privacy.
i mean, it was a case of my own.
i was there.
sorry, but officially
you're a civilian now, so...
no.
you don't need
to do that.
look.
the old days,
one of us at the desk...
we'd have looked
the other way.
hm? huh?
well, i'm sure
commander holleran...
you're not hearing me.
i didn't come this far...
stay quiet, mm?
but i can just-
no. just stay quiet
and look down.
hm?
i need that file.
do you understand?
yep.
let's go, darlin'.
10:36 am, suspicious suitcase.
constable scarlatti initiating
electronic counter-measures.
i'll wait here,
you go in and get the file.
fast is good.
wait.
i'll take that.
sorry.
okay,
i know the subject,
anticipate the weapon,
target the solution.
what kind of person
plants a bomb
in a public place?
organized personality,
not impulsive,
not mentally incompetent...
emotionally detached,
above-average
intelligence...
access to volatile material,
and familiar with its use.
yeah, and who wants to strike
the city's transportation hub.
or just doesn't like tourists.
okay, everyone,
eyes and ears open.
we may be dealing
with an individual
who likes to hang around
and watch the carnage.
it wasn't supposed to go
this way, you know?
wasn't supposed to go
this way.
you could've just given it
to me.
all i needed to do was
go in the briefing room,
get a little work done,
undisturbed.
i'll make sure
you're not interrupted.
uh huh.
well, maybe you're not trained
for this at your desk,
but where i came from
we're trained
to profile people
and here's
what i get from you:
you're ambitious,
you're serious about your job,
you don't wanna be passive,
be perceived as the victim.
so here's what you'll do:
i walk into
that briefing room,
you'll sound the alarm
first chance you get.
i try walking out of here,
same problem.
man with a gun,
making unorthodox demands.
you see my dilemma?
smile.
hey, kira.
any word
on the air conditioning?
tomorrow.
sergeant rangford?
troy!
you hear?
i made sergeant.
team three.
huh.
so you haunting
the old barn?
yeah.
sit down.
sit, sit.
okay, confirming no visible
identification.
babycakes is sending out
a signal
blocking remote detonators.
i'm gonna start
with the infrared.
good news so far.
nothing unusual
in the heat patterns.
gonna try chemical detection
for any nerve agents,
blood agents...
sergeant?
inspector, anything good?
some of the people
that reported the case
said they smelled hay
nearby.
so? hay...
moist hay.
one woman said she smelled
freshly cut grass.
stainton,
so what're you sayin'?
that someone stuffed the case
with hay?
boss? hay and grass
aren't the only things
that smell like hay
and grass.
those people that smelled hay
and grass,
track them down.
they gotta be put under
medical observation
immediately!
no physical exertion,
or it'll accelerate
the spread.
spike,
what do think it is?
phosgene.
it could be phosgene.
by the time you smell it,
it's already
at its lethal level.
so, daniel,
you and michelle
finally gonna take
that round-the-the world trip
she kept asking for?
well... ah, maybe.
little hot in that?
mmm.
yeah.
you know what?
no, i-i'm good, i'm good.
anything i can help you with
there, daniel?
i'm fine, troy.
i'm really fine.
i just wanna be left alone,
okay?
i don't think
that's a good idea.
stand down.
stay back.
hey! sergeant?
keep it cool, guys.
everything's okay.
okay, troy,
you're gonna keep your boys
at a distance.
sure.
sure, daniel.
you know how this works,
boys.
kira?
kira,
did you try to transmit?
what's up, jules?
i don't know.
this is not the way
it was supposed to happen,
you know?
never is, right?
no.
look at me.
i'm the subject.
you don't have to be, daniel.
we can work this out.
sorry, troy.
wait, she's sending
something through.
sarge.
team one hot call...
kira?
kira, you copy?
immediate priority immediate
immediate at sru
jules, you're in charge.
lean on stainton
if you need to.
eddie,
we got a priority call;
i need you, sam and wordy
to come with me.
lewis, you cover spike.
jules, let's get extra uniforms
and detectives.
copy that.
i'm on it.
ed, the priority call?
it's at the station.
why don't you tell me
what's...
don't...
negotiate me.
okay?
now...
i'm gonna go in here,
i'm gonna shut the door.
i'm barricading myself in.
you understand what that means,
don't you, troy?
i do.
and you're gonna leave me
to my own devices.
otherwise, the situation
is gonna get dangerous.
you know that, right?
right.
i want you to consider me
a threat level red.
you got that?
i got it, boss.
i'm gonna stop talking now.
threat level red.
can you say that for me?
that's good.
you're doing a good job,
troy.
-==זזאדנאצפ°חדחי·מן׳==-
±¾׳צה»½צ¹©ס§ן°½»בק£¬סן½ףדףתילעµףדם¾
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
flashpoint µת2¼¾µת3¼¯
-=זזאדנ׳צה»׳י=-
ך±¼הצב£÷¶¯׳ק»¹ךחהחד´ג‎µה±¿כיךף
it's daniel rangford.
he's armed
and he's barricaded himself
in the briefing room.
boss.
talk.
he's got a beretta.
40 cal.
panels hold up to that?
yeah, yeah,
they're polycarb.
so what's he doin'
in there?
he disabled
a security camera.
he hasn't talked since
he shut himself in there.
classified himself
a threat level red,
negotiated me
like i was a rookie.
are you surprised?
can your team
cover the entrances?
yeah. we're all we got, though.
most of my guys
already clocked out.
yeah, we're down three.
the rest of us are dealing
with the bomb threat.
you want me to call my guys
back in?
yes.
no.
eddie...
boss.
we keep this in the family.
we can handle it.
okay, eddie.
nobody gets in
through the front.
garage access only.
i'm assuming
he's closed the blinds,
but we still need eyes in.
so grab
some rangefinders,
go outside,
double-check.
copy that.
wordy? he's gonna be
looking for the snake,
so let's use
the fiber cam.
got it.
auto-transcriptor, boss?
we don't need it.
jules has it anyway.
it can just be for us,
or...
or what, greg?
when this is over, okay?
all right.
let's use team three's.
you set it up.
but call his wife first.
her name is michelle.
let's figure out
what's been going on at home
lately, okay?
on it.
'kay.
i want you to talk to him.
okay?
none of us
can stay objective.
but you know him best.
yeah.
all right, good.
kira, walk with me.
so what do we know
about phosgene?
it's not hard to make
and it's nasty.
it could take 24 hours
to show symptoms.
so your victims don't even know
they've been exposed...
until their lungs
stop working.
okay, well stainton's
on top of the med reports.
i'll tell him
to alert his units
for a potential
chemical evac order.
maybe we need to block
incoming trains as well.
anything else?
get him to broaden
the perimeter,
especially downwind.
got it.
okay, babycakes,
let's take a look inside.
danny?
what's this i'm hearing about
you being in there with a gun?
huh?
tellin' troy
it's threat level red?
danny, come on.
last time we talked
threat level red was code
for "there's a wife
in the station."
it's just me out here,
danny.
it's eddie.
kira, what happened?
he seemed fine when we left.
i mean, how did he seem to you?
calm, at first.
well, sweating a lot.
yeah, well,
we all are, right?
but steady eye contact,
relaxed posture,
chatty...
then, when i wouldn't
get the file for him,
he came off the rails,
like that wasn't the plan.
what do you think
the plan was?
???
getting the file,
preparing a presentation
in the briefing room.
he wanted privacy.
think he wanted to leave
the station with that file?
no, i don't think so.
and he didn't want
holleran alerted, right?
that's right.
remember anything
about the file?
name on it was gehring.
1989.
'89.
so there's no computer backup.
anything about that case?
just that it was his.
sorry.
no, no, you did everything
right, kira.
thank you.
you can go home.
you're free to do that.
hey, i'm not going anywhere.
i'm a cop too.
okay.
put on a vest and radio.
call harvey silver.
his name
and number's on file.
he was on daniel's team;
they retired same year.
tell him we need him here
sooner than asap.
eddie,
how's our friend?
he's not talking.
i got eyes in.
fiber optic neutralized.
troy,
you got eyes outside?
he's moving.
looks like he's closing
the shutters.
wanna try the ball cam?
he's gonna be looking for that.
let's get thermals.
okay,
i got it right here.
danny?
you sticky
my fiber optic camera?
nice job.
what'd you use, duct tape?
forgot how much you liked it
low tech.
remember that corner store
barricade, danny?
day like today -
hotter than hell.
you remember that?
you had me talk to those kids
for an hour and a half, danny.
then you came in,
turned up the heat,
20 minutes later,
they came running out.
and that was low tech
all the way.
thought you were on
a bomb call, ed.
we're on it.
just came back here
to see what was going on.
i'm not here to negotiate you,
danny.
i just wanna help you
figure it out.
all you've done for me
over the years?
come on.
back to your bomb call.
spike's on it.
danny, you know the bomb guys!
you know what's good for you,
you stay out of here.
i'm not going anywhere.
i'm gonna stay right here,
long as it takes.
danny, what're you saying to me?
how long?
oh, uh...
about 14 more ounces.
11:27 am barricaded subject
daniel rangford.
boss, how do you want me
to characterize the subject?
barricaded.
leave it at that.
you talk to his wife?
yes. i called her,
i told her husband
was at the station
and she got really upset;
she hung up on me.
sru!
boss, come and see this.
...now!
eddie?
he's shooting at nothing.
he's shooting at a chair.
i got thermals.
on the ground!
danny!
danny, our weapons
are not raised!
we are not here
to hurt you.
down! down!
danny, talk to me!
danny,
it's greg parker.
what's going on, buddy?
what're you shooting at?
what's going on?
i don't know.
he's shooting at somebody
who's not there.
is it an hallucination?
yeah, maybe a flashback
or something.
where's daniel?
i wanna see him!
ma'am, i'm sorry!
???
what the hell is going on,
guys?
no one through the front.
ma'am, you cannot go in there.
sam.
sam, it's okay.
michelle...
i wanna see him.
where is he?
let's just walk over here
for a second.
we can talk about it
over here.
where is he?
i wanna see him.
you bastard! you bastard!
calm down.
you did this to him!
all of you! you bastard!
just calm down.
it's okay, it's okay.
just go with kira
and we'll find you a place
to sit down, okay?
and i promise
i will come to you
as soon as i can, okay?
michelle, let's sit down.
it's gonna be okay.
boss,
take a look.
all right, that's enough.
i'm gonna open it up.
he said he was gonna fire.
you wanna spend the rest
of your life
thinking about what
we should've done, wordy? huh?
okay.
wordy, cover.
sam, we're opening up.
'kay,? go.
i told you not to come in!
let's slow this down,
danny.
close the damn door!
i'm not gonna be able
to do that, dan.
one step closer?
we're done.
okay.
let the subject set the pace,
huh?
don't rush a negotiation.
'cause i'm not finished here
and i'm gonna
get this thing right.
okay, eddie?
okay.
back off.
boss.
i'll go talk to michelle.
i think he's slowing up,
so let's just keep him
on his timetable, okay?
okay.
arriving now.
harvey, i'm sam,
team one.
where is he?
i wanna see him.
that's not gonna happen.
i gotta talk to him.
he'll listen to me.
harvey,
this isn't a good idea.
this is, this is garbage.
i can't just stand here.
harvey, there's not a guy here
who feels different,
but we just need to streamline
the inputs a little, okay?
ed lane is with him now.
eddie's with him?
yeah.
okay.
okay?
good.
we need your help.
we need you to remember
everything you can
about the gehring incident,
1989.
this is not good.
we got a possible i.e.d.
batteries, wire, pipe...
is that shrapnel?
could be. it's not nails
or ball bearings -
some kind of small objects
though.
this thing could be on a timer,
it could be motion-sensitive,
so we're not taking it
anywhere.
we detonate it here,
in the square?
negative.
detonating will only release
more gas.
we do a render-safe
with a water cannon.
okay.
we gotta disrupt the mechanism.
and turn the phosgene
into hydrochloric acid.
i promise you'll see him
as soon as we know it's safe.
safe?
michelle, we need to understand
what he's doing,
where he's coming from.
can you help us?
yeah.
'course i'll help.
thank you, 'cause i'm...
'cause you're the one
who knows him best.
you think?
i know the guy i married.
i remember him.
this guy?
i mean, i was counting the days
'til he retired.
'til he came back to us -
to me and liam.
wake up to the world,
have a bbq,
put up his feet,
enjoy.
something.
didn't work out that way,
huh?
no.
'cause when he took off
the uniform...
it turns out there was
nothing left underneath.
almost there.
all right, we just gotta get
past the part of him
that sticks to a plan.
so... maybe we bypass
the logic brain,
force him to run
out of there.
thinking about tear gas?
the animal instinct
in the midbrain
thinks it's drowning,
running for air.
well,
i don't recommend it.
why's that, danny?
you'd have to evacuate
the whole building for 3 days,
just to breathe in here...
and 3 weeks
with a sanitation crew.
we're not worried
about making messes, danny.
think it through, boys.
you wanna cripple the sru?
all on the gamble
that i didn't think of, uh,
packing a gas mask
in this bag?
does he let you
touch him?
no he doesn't.
and i don't mean
just ibed.
i try to hold his hand,
he pulls away.
the last time he touched me,
i woke up with his hands
around my neck
and he was screaming
at me.
he's been hanging off a cliff
all these years.
he won't talk to me.
not about work,
he never has.
and he won't talk to you
'cause he knows...
you'll shake your heads,
"oh, so sad
to see the great guy fall.
what happened to him?
we thought
he could hack it?"
then you'll turn
your backs,
so that you can keep
on pretending
that he's the exception.
michelle, it's gonna be okay.
it's okay.
danny,
we are not playing chess
here now.
you're thinking about
a permanent solution
to a temporary problem.
i appreciate your faith, ed,
but...
all right,
then you gotta appreciate...
don't interrupt
the subject!
don't "handbook" me,
danny.
danny, faith is what you need
when there is no proof.
we don't need faith to know
that you deserve to live.
(heavy breaths
oh yeah?
that's something
you can prove?
yeah.
yeah, i think i can.
let's talk about all the people
whose lives were made longer
because of you.
don't start.
the gehring incident...
it was a home invasion,
regent park,
but this little place
was neat as a pin.
you know who's keeping house?
a little 18-year-old girl.
parents are both deadbeats,
one's in jail,
one's awol...
she's holding it
all together,
looking after
her little brother and sister.
what happened
with the home invasion?
by the time we got on-scene,
bad guys had gone:
the girl, she'd taken a whack
at one of the guys
with a baseball bat,
scared 'em away.
so, team went back out
on patrol
and danny and i stayed behind
to write it up.
that was it?
the little guy,
10-years-old,
he wanted to show us
his baseball card collection.
i said "no, we gotta go,"
and danny said "no, let's stay."
he just bought a fresh pack
for his own son,
went out to the truck
to get them.
we sat crossed legged
on the floor...
middle of the afternoon,
summer day...
trading baseball cards
with the little guy.
it was good.
you remember this pretty clear
for such a long time ago.
yeah, well, you would.
two hours later
it wasn't our file anymore,
it was homicide's.
that little girl
down by the dock.
you remember her?
she was turning blue,
she could hardly breathe.
you did mouth-to-mouth on her
in the ambulance,
all the way to the hospital.
buddy,
you saved her life.
you stayed with her
the whole time
and then they called
from the hospital...
to say "congratulations,
she's gonna live."
danny, you got
the silver shield
for that, buddy.
proudest friggin' 9 seconds
of my career.
'cause then they give you
the punchline...
which is something
we don't tell the rookies...
about how the girl
was brain damaged
from lack of oxygen.
oh yeah,
she' gonna live...
like a vegetable,
shriveling up,
until her family decides
to pull the plug
to put her out
of her misery.
which i gotta say,
seems to be a good idea
right about now.
danny... danny.
i know you're self-esteeming me
like crazy here,
but you know what?
that's the last thing
i need right now.
that's the last thing.
excuse me.
okay, danny.
all right,
let's take a break.
he's almost at the bottom
of that bottle.
the more we talk
the faster he drinks.
let's just...
take a little pressure off,
okay?
boss,
i'm not gonna leave him.
all right,
you stay.
you stay,
but let him do his thing.
i need to find out
what's going on in that file.
okay.
we got the homicide file yet?
squad car's flying it over.
give you a deadline?
yeah, what's left
of his bottle of scotch.
harvey,
what do you remember?
two victims...
older sister, younger boy.
perps got away.
tragic as hell,
but it's nothing we don't see.
yeah, but why did this one
get to him?
what was different
about it?
did you ever talk
to him about it?
i don't know.
you know how it goes?
i might have asked him
how he was doing?
and what'd he say?
"i'm fine."
inspector, we're getting ready
to cannon the package here.
no one comes close.
perimeter is locked up.
thanks.
danny, you thirsty at all
in there?
huh?
danny?
a little water, buddy.
just gonna roll it in there,
okay?
no surprises.
nice and easy.
incoming from homicide.
gehring, jeremy,
august 8th 1989.
august 8th?
that's today.
find out why.
we got witness tape.
all right, dig out a vcr.
let's get some answers.
oh, you gotta be
kidding me.
it's beta.
aw, he's almost finished
that bottle.
i'm gonna open it up.
are you sure?
yeah,
we need more access.
sam, i need you.
troy, grab your guys.
we're gonna open this up.
what's happening?
michelle, i need you
to stay out of range.
i won't hide in there
anymore.
he's my husband.
you know what?
you're right.
you're right,
i want you to come with me,
i want you to hide
behind the shields,
and i want you
to stay close.
all right, we ready?
we ready? sam?
danny, listen to me now.
danny, danny,
don't do it.
don't do it!
danny, put the gun down!
danny,
michelle's here.
daniel.
michelle?
what're you doing?
you can't be here?
get outta here!
you shouldn't be here!
i'm not going anywhere,
daniel.
get her out of here!
i'm not going anywhere!
don't make me do this
in front of her!
danny,
just listen to me now.
get her out,
get her out of here!
danny, put that gun down.
we're not leaving you,
danny!
we're not leaving you.
come on!
in five...
four...
three...
two...
one.
fire in the hole.
hold fire.
daniel! please!
michelle,
he's not gonna hurt me.
are you, danny?
i'm crossing the line.
you think i won't do it?
cardinal rule.
gun's pointed at an officer.
hmm?!
sometimes you gotta
break the rules, danny.
remember?
remember who taught me that?
i'll do it.
i have the solution.
wordy, dammit, go.
hey.
hey, hey, hey,
hey-hey.
no-no-no,
it's okay.
you know what you gotta do?
you gotta keep safe.
you ever seen this before?
do you have any idea?
no.
you gotta hide.
it starts here.
i didn't want jeremy
to find it.
he told me to stay
under the bed.
so i didn't see them.
but do you think
they might'v been the same...
the same men
that had come before?
don't know why they came back
'cause he said we'd be okay.
who said you'd be okay,
petra?
the policeman
with the baseball cards.
he said...
he said we'd be okay.
then he went away.
but he didn't know
that they'd come back, petra.
but maybe he did.
because...
because he told jeremy.
what do you mean
"he told jeremy"?
he said,
"you know what you gotta do?
you gotta be brave
and show your sisters."
and so jeremy wanted
to be brave
so he could save me
and my sister.
but it didn't work.
it didn't work.
boss, we got something.
home invaders came back,
boy stepped up
to protect his sisters,
daniel and his team
were done,
daniel didn't do anything
wrong,
it was something
he told the boy.
yeah. "you know
what you gotta do?
you gotta hide."
no, that's not what he said.
he said,
"you know what you gotta do?
you gotta show your sisters
you're brave."
what was the boy's name?
jeremy.
okay, thanks.
you hide, like...
daniel?
michelle, you gotta go.
you can't see this.
daniel, i'm not leaving you!
daniel, let's talk
about jeremy.
jeremy?
the file you wanted.
guessing it was about jeremy,
right?
'cause today's the day.
isn't it?
august 8th?
it's funny, those days
that stick in our minds.
i'm guessing that jeremy
was a pretty brave kid, but...
i don't know that
for sure,
could you help me out
with that one?
daniel?
danny, you can't do this.
you can't do this without...
without telling us why!
i know...
about a kid...
sitting on the floor.
i went back.
he didn't look any different
from the last time i saw him.
his eyes are open,
he's looking at me,
baseball cards
spread around him.
but he's real quiet.
he's real still,
and i'm thinking,
"why is he so still?
why doesn't he say 'hi'?"
and then i see it...
an eight-inch screwdriver
buried into his throat.
and i put it there.
you didn't put it there,
danny.
criminals put it there.
if i hadn't been called there,
i wouldn't have said that
to him.
"you gotta be brave
for your sisters."
if it wasn't me,
he, he would've lived.
you don't know that,
buddy.
danny.
i spent my whole career
screwing up.
being too late,
being too... early,
not saying the right words.
i spent my whole career...
looking at the worst 20 minutes
of other people's lives
and i can't take it anymore.
danny, how about remembering
the good stuff?
the good stuff,
all the lives you saved,
all the people whose lives
were made better,
their lives were made longer
because you were there
for those 20 minutes.
i can't remember.
you see?
i can't remember!
all i see are the ghosts.
all i got are the ghosts,
the ghosts,
and i can't take it any more.
daniel!
eddie...
please.
please help me.
pull the plug.
okay, wordy.
no!
okay?
danny, this...
this isn't about jeremy.
these guys think
it's all about him,
but it's more than that.
isn't it?
jeremy's just...
who you always think about.
i get it.
you know what, buddy?
every time...
every time i look out
that damn scope,
i see a kid runnin' across,
i see a spray of blood...
and you know what else,
danny?
you know what else i see?
all the calls
we didn't get to in time.
the mothers that
we couldn't talk down;
the kid who thought
it'd be fun to...
pull a gun on a cop.
you're not the only one
who sees ghosts, danny.
i gotta tell ya,
i don't know where
to put 'em anymore either.
eddie, please, no.
you taught me
everything i know.
you made me who i am,
danny.
you can't...
you can't tell me...
that this is how it ends.
you can't.
give me the gun.
no...
you'll be okay.
stand down.
it was harmless.
he just wanted
to keep us busy.
inspector stainton,
those witnesses
are free to go.
hay and grass.
i'm gonna take you to a place,
a place i've been myself.
and we're gonna get
through this.
we're gonna get
* and if i don't make it home
tonight *
* don't leave it
up to me again *
* to feel fine *
* and if i don't make it home
all right *
* give me the day or so *
* to rest my mind *
* but isn't that the way *
* you tell me everything's
all right *
* i stay up all night *
* and, baby, when you tell me
that it's me this time *
* i don't close my eyes *
* i sacrifice
a little peace of mind *
* is love like this always? *
thought we were gonna keep
this one in the the family?
well, families and secrets,
you know?
i don't think that's
such a good thing.
* there's nothing left
that i won't do *
* to make it feel brand new *
* so, oh,
i'll leave it up to you *
* so, baby, when you tell me
everything's all right *
* but i stay up all night *
* and baby when you tell me
that it's me this time *
* i don't close my eyes *
* i sacrifice
a little peace of mind *
* ooh, love like this *
* ooh, love... *
i'm sorry
* and baby when you tell me
that it's me this time *
* well i don't close my eyes *
* i sacrifice
a little peace of mind *
* yeah, yeah, yeah *
Resynced - as good as possible - for your enjoyment! by Ashaכl