Oh my God!
No!
Nooooo!
Oh my God, my baby!
My baby!
Ed!
Oh my God!
What happened up there, Ed?
Eddie!
What happened up there?
Just about.
You want me to pick up anything
on the way home?
Sure.
Red or white?
Something "full-bodied
and juicy."
Honey, I still have my Freud
textbooks from med school,
don't make me use 'em.
Right now?
Shooting took place
on the Center Island Ferry
just over an hour ago.
SRU were on scene
and the Special
Investigations Unit confirms
there has been
a civilian fatality.
I don't know.
Well, no, I couldn't tell you
even if he was.
That-that's not gonna work.
You make a great dinner
every night.
You can't bribe me that way.
I will.
I love you too.
Ed! Hey!
Did we... I didn't forget
a session, did I?
No, no. I just wanted
to drop off the books
and the journal and stuff
you lent me.
Are you done with them?
Actually, I'm done
with the sessions
and the therapy.
I just wanted to let you know.
Okay. Can you come in
for a sec?
Yeah. Can you shut the door?
Sure.
Look, I know you're busy, so...
No, it's fine.
I just need to go through
a few things
to wrap up our work.
- Do you have a sec?
- Yeah.
Okay, and you started coming
here, when was that?
Two months - two months,
one week, five days.
That's right.
You wanted to talk about some
specific issues around a case,
"May Dalton."
Shame, we never got around
to talking about that.
Oh, that's okay.
Look, you have been great.
You've given me a lot of stuff
to think about,
and I just wanted
to say thanks.
I appreciate that.
I'm wondering, though,
why you feel like
you're done with therapy?
Uh...
No offense,
it's just not for me.
So I'm not that great, huh?
I didn't say that.
You kinda just did.
But - can I ask,
we didn't have a session booked
till next week...
Why didn't you just drop
the stuff off then?
No, I just, I... I hate
when people borrow stuff
and don't return 'em, so...
This wouldn't have anything
to do with today, would it?
Center Island Ferry?
I can't talk about that.
You can talk about
anything here, Ed...
You know that -
if you want to.
Whatever happened today,
it's got nothing to do
with that,
it's not why I'm done.
Okay.
Look, you've already paid
for this week's session.
And I like you, Ed,
but I'm still gonna
charge you for it.
You're here anyway,
why don't you just tell me
about your day.
You sure there's, uh,
no place you have to be?
I'm right where I need to be.
Okay.
The day started normal.
Up early, out early.
Just the way I like it.
Don't you look nice...
How's the family?
Sophie, Isabelle...
Good.
How about Clark?
Cutie...
Just you had mentioned
you guys were having
some issues communicating.
No, he's good. We're all good.
We're all good.
- Work was-
- "Good?"
It was.
All right!
All right, now, I love today.
Do you know why I love today?
Whatever it is,
I'm guessing it means
why we won't love today.
That's right!
Today is drill day...
Races, weights,
punishing physical activity.
What's not to love?
Wow.
And they haven't found a way
to accidentally shoot you yet?
Well, there's a reason why
we're the best team in the city.
Trust me, they love it.
Anyway, it didn't matter.
Hot call, Team One.
911 call, firearms involved.
Saved by the Winnie!
Multiple callers
report single white male...
White male, 30's,
downtown area,
had a duffel bag and firearm.
You hear yourself, right?
You talk to me like
I'm your sergeant,
or the Special
Investigations Unit.
I don't need
an official report.
Just try telling me like uh...
I'm a friend, or another cop.
But you're not a cop.
I mean, I'm sorry,
but you're not.
No. I'm not.
But I know a bit about the job.
Really.
Well, how?
Just try... telling me
the story
however it feels best.
We were unsure
where the subject was
in the downtown area.
Spike, traffic cams?
Sending you
what we've got so far.
Looks like he's heading south
on Bathurst,
past Lakeshore.
Looks bigger than
a sidearm to me.
Could be a sawed-off
shotgun.
He's carrying it out in public?
And whatever's in that bag.
Guys, what do we got
down there...
Parks, construction yards,
what?
Harbourfront.
Okay, team, Harbourfront.
No lights, no sirens;
Let's not spook our subject.
Spike, look for him on
Harbourfront CCTV footage.
Guy's carrying a
weapon in plain view.
We might be looking
at heightened emotion,
and desire to provoke
confrontation.
Guys...
He's getting on
the Center Island Ferry.
His weapon's concealed.
We can't let that boat
get out on open water.
No, the footage is
from four minutes ago.
The boat's already left.
He starts shooting,
it's fish in a barrel.
We'll have no way to stop him.
We get a marine cruiser,
we can board from the port side
emergency ladder.
Then you lose the
element of surprise.
We could call the boat back
to the terminal,
and rush it when it docks?
There's too many
people, it's uncontrolled.
We don't know
what's in that bag;
if he's got a bomb,
weapons, what.
Isn't there another
old marine terminal,
down below Lakeshore?
They still got a dock,
totally abandoned.
We'd have complete control.
Good thinking, Leah.
All right, Eddie,
you get eyes in on the boat,
I'll co-ordinate
with the port authority.
We'll announce
an emergency evacuation.
No, no. Don't make
it sound like an emergency.
Just have the captain announce
that they have to make
a last minute stop
and they'll be
on their way soon.
That must be hard...
Rushing to a scene,
not knowing
what you're about to face.
I'd find that hard.
Scary, even.
Well, you hope for the best,
plan for the worst.
We are  docking
temporarily to address a minor repair.
Thank you for your patience.
Good visual on the ferry.
No joy on the subject.
Eddie, we're holding
off on the gangplank...
No one on or off
until we know what
we're dealing with.
We are docking temporarily
to address a minor repair.
Thank you for your patience.
He must be inside.
Okay, hold on. We got
a middle-aged man here,
he's carrying a duffel bag.
Check his right arm
- he's hiding something.
He's talking.
To who?
I don't know. He's got no phone.
He's alone.
He's got no headset.
He's acting erratic.
He's reaching for the bag!
What's he got in there, Eddie?
It's a baby.
Flashpoint 05x11
Fit for Duty
Original Air Date November 29, 2012
==sync, correction by dcdah==
www.addic7ed.com
A baby, say again?
Affirmative. Subject
has a baby in his bag.
What's he doing?
Okay, we lost him.
He's gone inside, boss.
I'm coming down
for an action plan.
Officer Braddock remained
in position
to cover the boat
while the rest of the team
and myself
formed an action plan.
Save the infant,
evacuate the passengers,
remove the subject as a threat.
What was that like?
"Like?"
That's my job.
We get two or three EDP calls
a week...
That's "Emotionally
Disturbed Person."
I know what an EDP is;
That's my job.
I'm just wondering
what it's like to be there,
knowing that a life's
in danger.
Knowing that...
it's up to you.
You mean
"how did it feel?"
Would I ask something
like that?
You just did.
That's true.
It felt good.
Because I knew that we were
the best chance that baby
and those people had
of getting out alive.
Because of my team.
They're fast, they are smart,
and they're brave.
They'd give their lives
for each other,
the public, for me.
And your sergeant?
And Greg he's a... he's
at a whole other level.
I mean,
nobody knows people better...
How they think,
what they'll do.
He wrote the book, huh?
He is the book.
Boss, I got
an Amber alert here,
came out about an hour ago.
"Katherine Thompson,"
5-month-old infant.
Okay, Winnie,
let's put a call out to the...
The mother?
I'm patching her through.
Nice work, Winnie.
Mrs. Thompson?
I've got sergeant Greg Parker
on the line.
Oh my God, where's my baby!
Do you have my baby?!
Mrs. Thompson,
my name is Greg.
Now, I can't imagine
what you're feeling right now,
but I need you to help me
with something, please.
Now, you get why
he did that, right?
Terrified woman,
out of control.
Instead of asking
about the baby...
The source of her fear...
He asks for a favour,
giving her some control back.
Did I pass?
Hmm...
We needed to figure out
a connection
between the subject
and the baby.
She's with a man, in
his thirties, brown hair...
It was just her and me all day.
She doesn't sleep so well,
so anytime she dozes,
I put her in her room, alone.
I opened the window.
I just did it for the air.
Best thing for a little one.
But who would have access
to that window?
I'm on the fifth floor,
it leads into a fire escape.
Someone could have come up,
it could...
I don't know, I don't know...
It could be anyone,
I don't know!
Ask if she knows anybody
who plays piano.
Anybody you know play piano,
Maria?
Harold.
Who's that?
My neighbour.
Harold Beamer, I think.
He plays piano all day
and night.
Sometimes he wakes up Katie,
but he always stops
when I ask him to.
He's nice, he's nice...
Even if he's a bit...
well, crazy.
Can you even say "crazy"
these days?
Sam, meet us down below.
We'll cover onboard.
Copy that. On my way.
Right this way,
thank you very much.
- Right this way.
- Right over her, folks.
Right this way, please.
Thank you.
Sorry, folks.
Port Authority.
We have to vacate this boat.
Technical issues.
Sorry about that.
Right this way.
Eyes on subject -
seated bow, port side.
He lives alone.
H-he barely comes out.
Today, there was a couple guys
in moving uniforms.
They were banging on his door.
There was a woman with them.
She was crying.
I asked them to keep it down,
for Katie,
but he never came out,
so they left.
He could have gone out
of his apartment,
and up the fire escape.
Is it him? Oh
my-why would he do this?!
Mrs. Thompson, I'm
gonna have a police officer
come and get you,
bring you down here, all right?
You hang tight.
Winnie, "Harold Beamer"...
Psych hospitals,
criminal record,
anything you got.
Eddie, what was with
the piano thing?
It was just a hunch.
It looked like he was
playing scales
on the gun barrel.
"Scales?" Really?
How'd you know that?
Oh! Clark plays,
doesn't he?
Turns out the hunch was good.
Harold Beamer,
admitted to the psych ward
at St. Patrick's Hospital,
2002.
Right this way, folks!
There'll be another boat soon.
He's a former pianist
with the Toronto Philharmonic.
Diagnosed bipolar/
schizoaffective disorder.
He's prone to delusions
and mania.
Come on, hon, the
man's being very patient.
It's fine, it's fine.
Right this way, come on.
- Oh look!
- Ma'am...
No! No! You need
to be quiet, okay?!
Subject is armed.
'Kay, sir,
sir, look at me.
You don't need to use
that gun, okay?
Oh, look what you've done!
Oh no, oh...
Sam, port side. Jules,
take the door, stay low.
What if he
comes out blasting?
Whoever has the
shot takes the shot.
Our options were
extremely limited.
I made sure each of us
was ready
to neutralize the subject...
To "neutralize"?
To kill.
Okay. Go on.
Say it.
Sorry?
"How could you kill
a sick and desperate man?"
That's what you're thinking.
Actually, I wasn't.
I was thinking about you,
I wasn't thinking about
your EDP.
"Harold Beamer."
We knew his name by then.
That's interesting.
What?
Well, when you
started, he was "the EDP"
or "the subject."
Now, he's...
Harold Beamer.
That's the job. "Connect,
respect, protect."
That includes EDP's
like Harold Beamer.
We wanna get through to them
so we don't have
to neutralize them.
There's that word again.
It's not my word.
It's official
police terminology.
It makes people feel better...
The brass, media, everybody.
Trust me, you shoot a girl
in a public place...
"A girl?"
What?
You said "girl."
A girl, a guy, "subject."
Harold Beamer.
People want you to use
the magic words
to protect them...
There's no brass here, Ed.
No media. Just me.
And I may not be a cop,
but my dad was a 20-year vet
on the force,
so you don't need
to protect me.
Okay.
The situation was a mess,
and it was about
to get a lot worse.
Harold
oh... oh no.
Please, okay, no noise.
Please just keep it down.
Come on, let's go. Quick!
Oh, she's upset.
It's okay, Suzy.
Baby's name is Katie.
I don't know who Suzy is.
Next of kin is listed
as Jordana Hauser,
she's been notified.
Shhhh... she's very sensitive,
she's sensitive.
She doesn't...
She doesn't like the noise,
and she...
she needs to hear the music.
I just need to...
I need...
I need to turn it around.
I need to turn it around!
Spike, just keep him
focused on you.
Okay, talk to me,
how do we turn it around?
You can't.
Only I can if I'm...
Harold, Harold...
We don't have to rush
this thing, okay?
We can just talk it through.
How do you know my name?
Of course you know my name.
You know my birthday,
my blood type,
my shoe size...
Everything!
You don't know
what I know though.
Suzy... oh!
You don't know...
you're a liar!
You're a liar!
I don't have the shot!
Harold, stop right there!
It's okay...
Oh! Suzy...
It's okay, Suzy.
It's okay.
Daddy's...
Daddy's here.
Thank you, Harold.
Thank you for that.
Harold...
Don't worry,
daddy's got you.
- Harold! Harold!
- Daddy's here, Suzy.
Harold, you don't need
to do that.
Ed?
Can you keep going?
The baby, was she okay?
You want a happy ending.
Everybody does.
But when things don't work out,
you know who they blame?
I could see the baby,
right there,
but there was nothing
that I could do about it.
We couldn't shoot
- he'd drop her.
We couldn't rush him...
We had to wait
and see what he'd do.
Ed, status?
If he jumps, I'm
going in after him.
We need that police boat
here now.
- No!
- Harold!
Stay back!
Just leave us alone!
You have to let me through!
Please! Please! Harold?!
Calm down, ma'am.
Harold?! Calm down. Who are you?
- I'm Jordana Hauser.
- Harold Beamer's next of kin?
Yeah. Where is he? Okay.
- What did he do?
- Calm, calm...
The officer wouldn't
tell me what he did.
Calm down, all right?
Now, we're dealing with a very
dangerous situation here.
Harold's up there,
he's in an extreme manic state.
He took a baby,
he calls her Suzy.
Suzy's his daughter.
She's our daughter.
But she's right there.
Stay back!
Okay, Harold, just wait.
Nooooo!
Harold, don't do it.
Harold, no!
What's happening, ed?
He's climbing.
He's still got the baby.
Sam, get up to the next deck.
Harold, Harold,
take it easy, okay?
We're not trying to hurt you.
There's nowhere
left to go, Harold.
Just take it easy.
It's okay.
No. You don't understand.
You don't understand...
Harold!
Harold.
Ed, stop.
No, I can do this.
I know, I
know, just breathe.
Look at me.
Any numbness?
Dizziness?
I'm not having a heart attack.
I don't think it's your heart.
I think we should go back.
Start again.
Okay, fine. Fine.
The subject had stopped,
he was unresponsive to our...
No. Not there.
Back - to the start
of your day.
Why? Because we go
through this every time.
For the past two months,
one week, and five days,
you come in, crack some jokes,
you tell me I'm not a cop,
and the moment we get
to something real,
like your marriage,
your son, May Dalton,
You race
through the session,
and then you leave.
I don't need to
talk about all that.
- Ed, you're having a panic attack.
- I've got a job to do.
Not if you walk
out of here you don't.
- Excuse me?
- I'm not your sarge, Ed,
but I am a psychologist
with specific obligations,
like reporting that a patient
who works with the public,
who,
in my professional opinion,
is not fit for duty.
"Not fit for duty?"
Let me tell you something.
I have faced every board,
every panel, and every trial,
and I have been cleared!
I'm not talking about that, Ed.
Where were you
when I had to shoot May Dalton?
I mean, who are you
to judge me?
Nobody was there,
but everybody wants
to judge me.
Who's judging you, Ed?
You said yourself,
you were "protecting" us.
Because you don't know
what it's like!
Then tell me.
Tell me.
- You wanna know?
- Yes.
Okay.
I woke up this morning,
in my basement, alone...
Like I've done every day
for the last two months
because it's just easier
that way.
Clark! Clark!
Come on, you don't have
to do that right now.
Come on, it's okay.
He has a recital tomorrow.
A recital?
Why am I the last to know
about this?
So, no, I wouldn't say
we're really "connecting"
right now.
Okay. And work?
All right...
All right, all right,
all right!
I mean, is that what
you wanna hear...
That I'm sleeping alone?
That my kid won't talk to me?
And deep breathing
before facing your team?
It's not like
I let anyone see that.
Why don't you?
'Cause I'm their team leader.
Okay, I'm their team leader.
When we're on a call,
when it all goes to hell,
they look to me...
To be calm, to be in control,
to keep them all safe.
That's my job.
Nobody wants to know
about the rest of it.
They don't need to see that.
Thank you.
For what?
For being honest.
So... you were on
the ferry.
The baby was safe?
No, the baby wasn't safe...
That was the problem,
and it was still the priority.
Mr. Beamer?
Officer Callaghan
took lead on negotiation.
Harold?
We know women are
less threatening
to subjects like Harold.
I'm Jules.
I'm hoping that
we can sort this out.
Can you tell me
where you're trying to go?
We're on the Center Island
Ferry, aren't we?
You're a musician?
I see that you're doing scales.
Don't patronize me.
What kind?
I'm sorry?
What kind of
scales was I playing?
I don't know.
They're exercises.
They're the uh...
Hanon exercises.
Yeah.
Can you tell us about
your music, Harold?
When we started dating,
he was already "eccentric."
I'd been second flute
long enough
to know the genius type.
He played Chopin by ear
at age 11...
And... the Philharmonic
at age 21.
When did he stop
just being "eccentric"?
Um...
It was after Suzy was born.
He lived for her.
He would sleep
next to her crib,
in case she woke up,
and he would play music to her
on this little...
Um, it was a little toy piano
that we had.
She was just six months old,
but he was sure that
she was smiling, you know;
that she could hear the music.
I didn't notice the change,
at first.
That he stopped going
to rehearsals,
and then he stopped
playing concerts.
You know, he would only
play for Suzy.
The ridiculous orchestra,
the people listening...
They couldn't really hear.
I mean, not really.
My Jordana could hear,
but... not anymore.
Suzy, she could hear!
I would play for her,
and it was beautiful.
When he's lucid, he
knows that he needs help.
And then he starts
to take his meds
and he says
he can't hear the music,
so then he stops taking
his meds
and then this happens and...
You know, we couldn't
stay together...
I paid for an apartment though,
you know,
and a piano.
And I knew if I played
and I practiced,
and I played,
and then she would hear.
My Suzy would hear.
And then one day, a miracle...
She's right next door.
And I played, and she listened.
It was good.
I called him a week
ago, and he was raving.
Something about "Suzy,"
and "the music," and...
He hadn't eaten in days.
He needed help,
so I called the movers
to take his piano
to the hospital,
so that he could play.
But then when we got there
this morning,
he wouldn't even come out
to see us.
And then the neighbour came out
and told you that
her baby was sleeping.
Oh God, no, is that the baby?
Did I do this?
No, this is no one's fault.
You know,
if you could just see him,
if you just knew him
the way that he really is...
This is not who he is.
He was just staring at me.
Not Jules.
Not the baby.
Me.
Why do you think
he was staring at you?
It didn't matter.
He believed what he believed.
He posed a threat to himself
and to others.
We had no choice.
Liar!
Put it down, Harold!
I would never hurt her!
And the subject
was neutralized.
Is that what
you wanted to hear?
Am I "fit for duty" now?
I'm sorry, I just...
I don't understand
how this man
went from telling you
about the music,
and his daughter,
to pointing a gun.
He was mentally ill.
He was in a manic phase.
But what happened in the time
between him staring at you
and the shot being taken?
What happened to Jules?
Or the baby?
What're you leaving out, Ed?
I told you.
The man was shot.
He was killed.
Yes.
But you didn't shoot him,
did you, Ed?
I told you my dad was a cop.
So I know that,
after a shooting
in the line of duty,
an officer must turn everything
over to the SIU as evidence...
His notebook, his gear...
His uniform.
So, tell me,
what really happened
on the ferry?
Ed?
Ed.
I wanna help you,
but you have to be honest
with me.
Tell me what happened.
He just wouldn't stop
staring at me.
Harold, we're right
here if you wanna talk.
How did you know?
The Hanon exercises -
how... how did you know?
Ed, his voice is
lowered; He's personalizing.
He might be transitioning
to a lucid phase.
I got the shot.
Sam's covering, ed.
If Harold's reaching out to you,
you reach back.
My son plays, Harold.
The piano?
And the cello.
Oh...
The soul of the orchestra.
Hi, princess.
Do you know that one?
I do. That's...
Clair... Clair uh...
Clair de Lune.
Debussy.
That's right, that's right.
And all of a sudden, he seemed...
happy,
and for a second, so did I.
Why do you think that is?
It made me
think of Clark.
But that's not the point.
We had to move fast
and get into reality testing.
Find areas you agree on:
"The sun is out,
you are a man..."
We're on a ferry.
I'm a police officer.
And that's a baby at your feet,
right, Harold?
Yeah, yeah... it's...
It's my Suzy.
Okay.
Harold, can I ask you
how you know that's Suzy?
I know, I don't...
Wait. Wait, stop!
No problem, Harold.
You okay?
Between me and you,
there seems to be a lot of
people with guns around here.
Probably not the best place
for a baby, right?
Now, I know that you don't
wanna hurt anybody here,
especially not that baby.
Look at this.
I did this, didn't I?
It's okay, that's
why we're here
to help you out of it.
I thought it was working.
But... then he stared at me
again,
and this time...
It was different.
Different how?
He didn't seem curious...
or interested in me.
This time...
he looked like he finally
understood something.
It won't ever stop.
I'll go away
and I'll take the pills,
and I'll... I'll think
that I'm better, you know?
I'll just end up back here
all over again.
Okay, he's bottoming out.
Ed, Sam, watch for a shift
to suicide.
Jules, if his attention
is on himself,
you get the baby.
Harold, let me ask you,
you were going over
to the island, right?
What's going on there?
Talk to me.
Harold I came to get
my piano, they were...
They were banging on the door
and Suzy was upset.
I mean, she doesn't know,
she's just a baby.
All the noise,
I just wanted it to be quiet,
so I could hear.
The music?
Yeah.
When I...
When I hear the music,
it tells me that there's love
inside me and everyone,
and that we're all safe.
And then I take my pills,
and I listen to the doctor,
and there's no music.
It's just me.
And all the things
that I've done
and the people
that I've hurt...
My Jordana, my-my...
My Suzy...
Harold, I know you love
your daughter,
but what happened
is in the past.
But I need you to do
the right thing now.
No, it is not.
It's...
It's in here.
It's in here
and I can't make it stop.
I can't!
I'm so sorry...
I think we should go now, Suzy.
Harold...
Are you sure of that's-
that's Suzy, Harold?
- Yes!
- Okay.
Yes, it is.
You don't think I know
my own daughter?
I didn't say that.
You're a liar!
Careful,
Eddie, he's splitting;
he's making you the enemy.
- Harold!
- Liar!
Harold, I'm here to help you!
- No!
- Look at me! Talk to me!
No!
I wouldn't hurt her!
Drop it!
- I would never hurt her!
- Put the gun down!
- Put it down!
- I would never hurt her!
Ed? Ed, where are you?
I'm right there...
in the moment...
The moment I kill someone.
Okay. Describe it for me.
I use a four count
breathing method
to keep my heart rate
at 40 to 50 beats per minute.
I maintain light pressure
on the trigger of my weapon.
I aim for the center mass,
in order to make the kill.
But it isn't
that simple, is it?
I read somewhere
that in World War II,
only 10 or 20 percent
of soldiers
actually fired at the enemy.
The rest aimed above,
to the side...
Anywhere but at the man.
Because... it isn't easy,
is it,
to go against
the fundamental instinct
not to kill
a fellow human being.
I mean, that's why we train
to break that instinct.
So that in the moment,
we don't think.
It's like a switch
on or off, black or white.
"Connect, respect, protect."
Or kill.
It is my job now.
This is what I must do.
No!
I would never...
The imminent
threat is clear.
The target is clear.
I have the shot...
And I can't do it.
Then it all went wrong.
I didn't take the shot.
I think you're right.
I don't think
I can do this job anymore.
How do I go back now?
I mean, what do I tell them?
What do I tell my family?
Well, first, we need to finish.
You didn't hear me?
I am finished.
No, Ed, on the ferry.
Finish what happened there.
You don't think
I know my own daughter?
You're a liar!
- Harold!
- Liar!
Harold, I'm here to help you!
Look at me!
Talk to me!
No!
What happened?!
What'd you do?!
What happened up there, Ed?
Eddie!
What happened up there?
Ed!
Somebody tell me something, please!
What happened?!
What'd you do?
Oh no! Tell me what happened,
please, somebody!
No, please!
Subject's neutralized.
Ed, what're you doing?
Gotta fix him up;
His family's down there.
Hey.
They can't see him like this.
Ed,
it's a crime scene.
You can't do anything
to his body, okay?
I couldn't stop... looking.
At what?
At the hole...
Where his heart used to be...
When he was still alive.
Step aside.
Who took the shot?
I did.
Braddock, you're sequestered,
you have to relinquish
your firearm.
You know the drill,
I'll take you to SIU.
The baby...
She's okay. She's
on the dock with her mom.
Says she wants to talk to you,
say thank you.
Jordana and the daughter?
What happened, Eddie?
Parker, what're you doing?
I've gotta go.
Ed, you're a witness officer;
the team stays
until Braddock and I go.
I didn't take the shot.
Hold up, buddy,
I'll come with you.
I got it, no.
I just drove.
I got in the truck,
the books were in the truck,
and I just had to get here.
I don't know why.
I just had to get here.
I blew the call.
Another person's dead.
What am I gonna do?
Okay.
You blew the call...
Not sure that's what I heard.
Can we do a little bit
of reality testing,
see what we agree on,
the two of us?
- Yeah.
- All right.
The baby was saved.
Yeah.
The passengers were saved.
Right.
You profiled your
subject, in order to negotiate.
When all other options
were exhausted,
your teammate was ready.
Whoever has the shot
takes the shot.
So it all went
how it was meant to,
based on what you tell me,
and based on how
you trained them.
No, not them -
not them at all. Me.
It's black or white;
you take the shot or you don't.
- You kill or you don't.
- Yes!
And if you kill, you're judged,
you're blamed.
Yes.
And if you don't
kill, you judge, you blame...
Yourself.
Is this really about whether
or not you took the shot?
Why are you here?
To hear me tell you
you're a monster?
Or to tell you why
you can't talk to your son?
- What do you want, Ed?
- I don't know!
- Yes you do.
Yes you do, and
you have to tell me.
You have to say it.
What's wrong with me?
I see these people -
everyone I ever...
May Dalton?
I'm up on a roof, I see
her through my scope...
Every day, every night.
Did your father ever talk
about that?
No.
I mean, maybe that's what
the drinking was about,
the nights away...
Until my sixteenth birthday
when he didn't come back.
I try to look for him
every once in a while,
but, you know, so far...
You know, maybe one day
he'll come back
and tell me what it
was like for him.
But so far,
he hasn't had the courage.
Not like you.
I couldn't do my job.
That's not "courage."
I'm not talking about
your job, Ed.
I'm talking about you.
Why did you come here?
Harold said he was going
to the island to be safe.
Maybe that's what
I was looking for.
No. Harold was going
to the island to escape.
You came here
for something else.
Let me show you.
Come with me.
It hurts to do your job.
It hurts to take a life.
It hurts to be the one
who stands on a rooftop...
or a boat...
and kills.
Even when it's right, it hurts.
So you can quit your job,
stop talking to your son,
or run away from it all
like my father, or Harold,
but none of that
is gonna help you face
the one thing you're actually
running away from.
So the question is, Ed,
can you allow yourself
to feel the pain?
How?
How do I face that?
She was eighteen...
she was eighteen.
She had her whole...
she had her whole life
ahead of her.
I took it.
I took it!
I took it...
She was...
eighteen years old.
She had her whole life
ahead of her
and I took it.
How can I face that?
How can my kid
look me in the eye?
You know what I see
when I look in your eye?
I see a cop,
a father,
a hero,
a man.
I'd be worried about you
if you didn't feel like this.
if you didn't come
to see me today.
But I'm not.
You're gonna be okay.
Just remember, Ed,
the job is black and white,
but how you feel isn't.
That's... that's okay?
Yeah... that's okay.
I've stood on so many
of these rooftops.
You want your son
to look you in the eye,
you need to tell him how it is.
I got a few people
I gotta talk to.
Yeah, there's a few people
I think I need to talk to.
Sorry, I can do this later.
No. It's okay.
Don't stop.
It's beautiful.
==sync, correction by dcdah==
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ know you"re not alone ♪
Across the country,
it"s a love we all share.
♪ ...I"m going to make
this place your home ♪
Now Canada"s favourite
coffee is coming home.
Where the tassimo brewer"s
bar code technology
brews Tim hortons coffee
the way it was meant to be.
Now that"s something
to celebrate.
Before we got
the capital one aspire card
we never had enough Miles
to get away together.
Aloha.
Isn"t it beautifu,
honey?
Mmm.
Let me show you around.
Wait till you
see the clubhouse.
Fore!