Come on... Where
are you, Rebecca?
Rebecca...
Rebecca!
Oh my God!
Are you okay?
Stuart...
Spike, can you get it
so we see what he's seeing?
Rebecca... Moments away, boss.
You thought you'd be my hero?
You thought you'd just rescue me?
It wasn't supposed
to go like this.
This isn't some game,
Stuart.
These are dangerous men, they
have Eric out there right now
looking for the leak.
Do you understand?
They're looking for you!
Okay. Okay. I'm-I'm
gonna tell the cops
where you are right now.
Just don't, please...
If you call the cops, I'm dead!
Do you understand?
I'm dead!
Okay, I got one for you.
Hypothetically speaking...
and I'm just speaking
hypothetically here...
if someone you know
is about to do something bad,
is it your responsibility
to stop them?
How bad?
You want a ten-point scale?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Um, if one is not picking up
after your dog,
and ten is... Murdering
Santa Claus...
Right in front of the elves -
santacide.
I'm glad that we're
getting so scientific about this.
Of course.
Anyways,
on that scale,
well, this is about a seven.
Seven... that sounds criminal.
It is.
Okay. Why didn't you say?
Yeah, if someone's about to commit
a seven, then you call the cops.
That's what I thought.
What are you doing?
Are you having
an Internet fight?
No. I'm just
making conversation.
Okay, well I gotta go.
But Stuart,
I just wanted to let you know
that I got an "a"
on my final.
Are you kidding me? That's...
Rebecca, that's great.
So thanks for that.
No, that is all you.
No, it isn't.
You helped me a ton.
So I just...
I wanted to let you know
how grateful I am.
It's no problem.
You're a great friend.
Likewise.
Ugh! Okay. Blah!
Mushy mush.
I gotta go.
Bye.
Likewise?
Good job, Stuart.
No, it was a disaster.
It's not spicy enough.
See, that's why you never
cook without an assistant.
- You offering?
- No, you can't fool me.
Oh, you...
Okay.
What?
You ever gonna tell her? Who?
Why are you communicating
in looks?
Spike, you're incapable
of walking past Winnie's desk
without trying
to make her laugh.
Oh, wow, Leah,
that's so far off.
You should tell her
how you feel.
It's sort of embarrassing
how far off that is.
Point is, Spike, there's no
upside in keeping it secret.
Well, I'm not keeping
anything secret.
You're right about that.
Hey, Spike, can you
come take a look at this?
Excuse me, Leah,
I've got work to do.
Mm-hm.
Yeah.
- What's up?
- I don't know,
this just popped up
on my screen.
Well, did you
open an email or a link?
No, no. I didn't do anything.
It just came out of nowhere.
According to that timestamp,
the image is live.
A prank?
Doubt it.
You gotta penetrate through
some pretty thick security
to get to
our internal network.
An attack?
We better get boss.
See if anybody else is getting this.
Okay.
Man, check this out.
What do you got, Spike?
A roadside cafe.
It's a rogue signal.
Whoever's feeding us
is following this guy around
like a live TV director.
Where is that?
Those power lines.
- That's Highway 7.
Halton Truck Stop.
Just talked to IT.
Nobody else is reporting the signal.
So this is for us?
Guys, right there.
We got a hot call,
Halton Truck Stop.
Let's move!
Winnie, a chopper
up, APB on both vehicles,
and see if cruisers
are in the area.
You got it.
Boss, video gives us
a partial plate on the car
but nothing to ID the rig.
Copy, Spike.
Share what you got
with the unis.
Winnie, get me someone
from auto theft.
You got it.
Just talked to the security company
at the truck stop. Nobody saw a thing.
Now how is that, Jules?
Weren't we watching
through their cameras?
Well, it seems so, but they record
on a loop. Nobody was monitoring.
Someone was.
Well, our tipster must've
hacked into the system,
tapped into the signal
and routed it to us.
That's great; Hacked their
system, hacked our system...
This guy doesn't have
a phone?
Maybe it's a rival gang.
They wanna remain anonymous.
Boss, I've got Detective Wendy
Travis from the Auto Theft Squad.
Put her through.
Sergeant,
thanks for contacting me.
I understand you have
a semi-truck theft?
Yeah, that's right.
Halton Truck Stop.
Let me
guess, driver abducted?
Sounds like
you know this crew.
Well, I know their work.
My unit's been tracking them
for months.
Okay,
please talk to us.
They're a slick operation
high-value targets only, late-model rigs,
expensive cargo.
Well, if it's about property,
why the abduction?
Well, they're buying time.
They grab the driver,
strip out the rig's GPS,
throw both in the back
of a support vehicle
and then continue along
the truck's route.
So the dispatcher
doesn't suspect a thing.
He has no reason to.
Looks like everything's
rolling normal.
The thieves then take
the stolen rig
to an unknown location,
they unload the cargo
and chop the truck.
That's the last
we ever see of it.
Then, hours later,
the driver shows up
at the side of the road.
Harmed?
Well, sometimes.
Last driver took a tire iron to the head.
Three days in a coma.
Okay, team,
these guys are gonna get violent if
we push them, so let's be cautious.
Listen, sergeant,
this outfit's stolen four million dollars
in trucks and cargo in the last year,
and my unit hasn't even
had a sniff.
How did SRU
get on top of this?
Tell you the truth,
Detective,
we're not entirely sure.
Suspect vehicle heading
southbound on Highway 427.
Team one, the car's been
spotted heading southbound on the 427.
Two cruisers in pursuit.
Okay, tell them we're on our way.
Tell them to hang back.
Sam, Jules,
you're with us on the car.
Spike, Leah,
you are on the rig.
Copy.
Car just took exit
on the County road 50,
and chopper's got a visual
on the semi.
Headed westbound
on service road 33,
just crossed Bellmont.
Here. Some farmland,
undeveloped forest.
Good visibility, no exits.
Let's set our net.
Team, we've spotted the car.
Go, Eddie.
Can we box him in?
If the whole team was here,
but not with those cruisers.
If we shoot the tires,
he could ride the rims
for miles.
There's a hostage in there,
we gotta end this.
Sam, pit manoeuvre;
Hang back,
I'll take point.
Let's go.
Got it.
Bring it back.
A bit more.
Bit more.
Good.
Officer Scarlatti?
Detective Travis.
We put a hail out
on all the frequencies,
so whoever's driving that truck
isn't listening.
Let's hope
he's a visual person.
Right.
Ed, in position.
All right, hang on.
And... showtime!
Out of the vehicle now!
Down on the ground now!
Do it now!
On the ground!
Hands behind your back!
Do it now!
All right, buddy. You're okay.
Feet first.
I got ya. Here, I got ya.
- You're okay.
- Here you go.
Where's my rig?
It's all right, sir,
we'll get your truck back.
I don't care about the truck! It's the
cargo; It's full of Anhydrous Ammonia.
Pull the roadblock!
Tear it down!
- What?
- Now! Now!
Talk to me, Spike.
Boss, Anhydrous Ammonia
is a pressurized liquid gas.
It's very toxic
and extremely volatile.
If that rig gets into a wreck,
it's gonna blow everything
sky-high.
Guys, go!
Come on!
Get the cars out!
Go!
Move! Move!
Go! Go! Go!
Come on!
Oh, come on.
Come on.
What're you doing?
Don't lose him.
Boss, that truck
was not gonna stop.
Truck's continuing along 33.
We can intercept
at Dixie Road.
And then what?
We got an awfully determined
subject here.
We can stop it with a fifty cal,
steel core round.
Hit the intake manifold,
engine stops dead.
Ed, that's ten square inches,
traveling 80 Miles an hour,
hidden under a hood.
Boss,
we can't wait this out here.
That truck gets into
a populated area,
it's gonna go from bad
to worse.
Okay, set it up, Eddie.
Detective Travis,
we need to lock down
that highway,
evac the whole area.
I'm on it, sergeant.
Jules, why ammonia?
Bombs?
Oklahoma, Oslo, Delhi -
all ammonia-based bombs.
But it's also used in
methamphetamine drug-making.
And this crew,
so far they've stolen
electronic equipment,
medical supplies, machinery.
Stuff with street value.
Yeah, I don't think these guys are
terrorists. I think they're opportunists.
Spike, what about our tipster?
Well, all I can say
at this point
is that he's good,
boss.
To infiltrate
our internal servers,
not to mention remotely hijack
our CCTV system,
that's big league.
Does that mean
our comm is compromised?
I don't know.
I can tell you he's been
in our system for awhile.
How do you know that?
Well, he had to tunnel
through the firewall,
and set up some kind of
encrypted backdoor controls.
It takes time.
That goes for the
cameras he hijacked too.
He would've had to crack them
in advance.
So this guy's been
planning this day for a while.
- Hey.
Give me one sec, Recci,
I'm right...
In the middle of something.
Okay.
We'll cover below.
All right, be careful.
Ed, the intake manifold
runs along the top of the block,
about three feet back
from the grill.
Okay, Spike,
we got it.
We're in position.
For a clean shot,
you'd wanna hit it
three inches off center.
Left or right?
Hard to say without
knowing of the engine's stock.
You're just gonna
have to find it.
But the main thing is,
you aim low,
you're into radiator,
and that thing can rumble on
for miles.
If you miss high,
you could deflect off the hood,
hit the driver...
And we got a runaway bomb.
Sync and correction by GeirDM
www.addic7ed.com.
Here it comes.
Should I call back?
No. Sorry.
Hang on one sec...
This is almost over.
300 meters...
Contact, left of center.
No effect.
Come on, Eddie.
Two hundred fifty...
Two hundred.
Jules
got it! Target hit.
Let's move.
Show us your hands!
Hands where we can see them,
right now!
SRU! Get out of the vehicle!
SRU! Get
out of the truck!
- On your knees!
- Get down right now!
Who is this guy?
What is this?
Where is he?
Where is who?
One sec, Becca.
Rebecca?!
I gotta go, Stu.
I'll call you back.
No. No, no, no.
Becca, hold...
what's going on?
Anybody call?
Did anybody come by?
No... no.
What's going on?
Come back to me,
Rebecca.
Are you sure?
No, no, no. No. No!
Okay, look, we
gotta go out for a bit.
Eric, just calm down! Talk to me.
What's the matter?
Everything
! Everything's the matter!
No! What's he doing there?
Come on.
No, hold on.
What kind of trouble
are you in?
Okay. Right now,
let's go.
No! Get off!
I'm not going with you.
Wait.
- Your ride's here.
- Let's go to the kitchen.
Where are we going? No
one's going to the kitchen!
We're going to the warehouse.
Think, think.
- I'm not talking to you.
- Relax.
I'm not ask you,
all right?
I'm telling you!
Relax, okay? I'm going!
Don't tell me to relax!
Damn it!
Go!
Ok. Sit tight.
Sit tight. Sit tight.
Come on, come on..
Yes, that's right.
Check it, check it, check it!
I'm not asking you! I'm not
asking you, all right?
I'm telling you!
Team one,
check your computers.
We got another video
coming through.
I'm sending it to you now.
Look at it, look at it,
look at it, look at it.
Relax, okay? I'm going!
Don't tell me to relax!
Go!
Good. Come on.
Are you kidding me?
Spike, can you tell
where that is?
No. It's a personal webcam.
There should be an ip address,
but it's buried.
No, no.
Come on.
- We're going!
- Go!
Boss,
I don't like it.
He's playing games
with us here.
I don't like it either, Eddie.
Let's go!
Winnie, send cruisers
to 589 Claremont.
We got an armed abduction
in progress.
We're on our way.
You got it.
Okay, team, talk to me.
Boss, I spoke to the
landlord at 589 Claremont.
The apartment is rented
to a Rebecca Vaughan
and an Eric Moore.
Hey, boss,
I think I got something,
the guy at the house,
he was also at the truck stop.
He's gotta be
part of that crew.
That's a good bet, Ed.
Eric Moore.
Busted two years ago
for selling stolen
auto parts.
Three months probation.
So Eric was in on
this deal, it went bad,
and now he's in trouble.
That's good; That's starting
to feel like something.
Yeah, but it still doesn't
explain who's sending us messages.
Guys, we got it!
Door's ajar;
We're late to the party.
Quick and cautious, guys!
Let's move! You ready?
Spike, let's go!
Hit it!
Right there! Police!
SRU!
Police! SRU!
- Clear!
Upstairs clear!
Spike, I want you on top of the tipster.
Somehow he's at the center of this,
and if we find him,
we might find
our abducted couple.
Copy that, boss.
Detective Travis.
Officer. Sergeant.
Good to meet you.
Any luck with those men
we apprehended?
Zero.
Whoever they're working for,
they're either fiercely loyal
or just terrified.
Boss, I got a pay stub.
Eric Moore is a mechanic
at Apex Freight.
They on your radar?
A mid-sized
transport company.
Above board
as far as I know.
But they'd have
equipment and storage.
They can easily process
hot trucks.
Sure.
Where are they located?
North. Castlefield area.
That's where the rig
was headed.
Let's pay 'em a visit.
Let's go.
Thanks, Detective.
In your office,
boss.
Okay.
Mr. Burnett,
I can explain.
I need you to be quiet, Eric.
Have a seat.
Where's the girl?
In the back.
Get her.
Mr. Burnett,
please just let me...
Well, the cops
aren't at the door.
Let's call that good news.
Tell me something, Eric.
You were supposed to drive the truck.
What happened?
The guy came out sooner than we expected.
You know, we got caught out of position,
so we switched.
Who made that call?
I did.
So you can see how this
is a bit of a thing for me, Eric.
Mr. Burnett, I promise...
you changed plan last minute;
The SWAT team arrives;
You're the only one
who got away.
Eric; No, look, I swear to you,
everything was running smooth.
Those cops came outta nowhere.
They just showed up!
Ah...
It's Rebecca, right?
What's going on?
Rebecca,
I'm Eric's boss.
I'm not sure if you know
what that means.
I thought you were
a mechanic?
That's true.
But he has other
responsibilities too.
Oh God, Eric, I thought you
left that all behind...
Becca, not now, not now...
How could you lie to me
like that?!
No, Becca, just forget about it
for a second, okay?
We'll just deal
with it later.
Are you done?
Yeah.
Now, it's important to me
that you understand exactly
how serious this is.
Mr. Burnett, hang on...
Today, Eric
was in charge of a job
and it didn't go very well.
No, please, Mr. Burnett...
Please, please...
And that's gonna hurt me, see,
because my clients are
a very unforgiving group.
Just please
can you just let us go?
Mr. Burnett,
I swear to you, okay?
I'm not the leak!
So what's gonna happen now
is Eric's gonna tell me exactly
how exposed I am.
If I hear one false word...
Listen, okay?
There's a security attendant at the truck
stop lot! I paid him to turn a blind eye,
and he seemed solid,
but he must've caved.
Okay, that's the only
explanation.
Okay, look, none of this will
go back to the buyers.
I swear to God.
None of it will go back to you.
I'll clean this up.
I promise you, okay?
I-I...
I'll bring you the leak.
Just let me do that.
Please, let me do that.
You have half an hour.
Thank you.
No, no. She stays.
Wait.
You even think of going
to the cops...
I'll kill her.
Eric...
Okay, Apex
Freight, established in 1971,
but ownership changed last year.
The new guy
is Terry Burnett.
He took over last year,
you say?
Yeah, just
before the truck thefts started.
A legit business
gives him cover.
Facilities and payroll,
and a means to launder profits
hiding in plain sight.
Ed, building's located
at the South end
of an industrial park.
The intel's spotty.
These places go up as shells
and get filled in
over time.
Okay, team, lay up short.
Sam and I'll recon on foot.
Jules, Spike,
how you making out?
Rebecca Vaughan.
Steadily employed,
taxes paid.
She's currently enrolled
in night classes
at a community college.
Boss, I've isolated the malware
that's hijacked our vehicles
security cameras.
The code's author
goes by the name "rot 2".
Weird part is,
there's no mention of him
on the hacker boards.
Is that unusual?
Well, an exploit like
this, it's pretty elite stuff...
seizing control of the cameras,
overriding activiation lights.
We're talking the ability
to peer into people's homes
undetected.
So you're saying there's
an appetite for this technology.
I'm saying, in the hacker
world, this guy could be a rock star.
But there's no mention of him
or his code,
and nobody's ever
heard of him.
Okay, it's not about fame,
it's not about profit.
It's about today.
Can you find him, Spike?
I might be able
to put eyes on him.
How, Spike?
Because I'm gonna turn
his own script against him.
Okay. Keep us posted.
Did you say
his handle is rot 2?
Yeah, why?
Well, she's taking
design class,
the folder's right here
on her laptop.
Lessons online
with a tutor.
Oh, that's nice.
Tutor.
Backwards.
Rot 2... rot 2.
Tutor backwards.
Rot 2.
You're brilliant.
That's brilliant.
Let's take a look
at one of those lessons.
So the guy calls,
saying that he might've
forgotten something
at the restaurant,
but he's being all cagey
about what it is.
Doesn't actually tell
you what you're looking for.
Exactly.
So I go back to the table
and what do I find?
I don't know,
I'm guessing not an umbrella.
Teeth.
- No...
- Yup.
No!
Dentures.
Under the table.
Wh-what do you mean,
from his pocket?
No, like from his mouth.
It had like the glue on them
and everything.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait...
Teeth are a big part
of your face, Rebecca.
Yes they are, Stuart.
Yeah, you see what
I have to deal with?
Guy's just a kid.
That's why I have to do well
in these classes, Stuart.
It's just-it's time
I put the waitress life
behind me,
once and for all.
On that note...
I'm gonna get a tea,
and then you and I are
gonna go back to work.
Be back.
Hey,
why do you do that?
What? Do what?
You always point
the camera away
when you get up.
I don't want my students
peering into my life.
Well, surely I'm not
just another student.
Um... Okay, wow. All right.
I thought we had
something special.
You are special.
Mmm.
I'll be back.
Boss,
I think we've got our hacker.
His name's Stuart.
He's got a relationship
with Rebecca.
What kind of relationship?
Well, he's her
tutor, but it runs deeper.
He's in love with her.
Doesn't take a profiler
to see it.
So the hacker loves
the girl,
but the girl's
got a boyfriend.
The boyfriend's a crook,
- so the hacker tries to get him busted.
- And the whole thing goes sideways.
I'm gonna track
down the tutoring company.
They got cover,
vantage, exits...
And there's civilian
workers everywhere.
Come on, come on...
Gotcha!
Boss, I'd like
to introduce you
to our hacker rot-2,
first name Stuart.
Jules is getting
more information.
Spike, can we talk to him?
No, I had to modify the
code to get though his defenses.
We can hear him,
but he can't hear us.
Come on...
Where are you, Rebecca?
Rebecca...
Rebecca!
Oh my God...
Are you okay?!
Stuart!
Spike, can you get it
so we see what he's seeing?
Rebecca!
Moments away, boss.
Stuart, how did you find me?
It wasn't
supposed to go like this.
I knew that Eric
was lying to you
about where he got
his money from,
about what he does.
What're you talking
about?
I told-I told the cops.
I told them about Eric's job.
You what?
Because I see how he treats you.
I've seen it
so many times.
I couldn't watch it anymore.
What do you mean
you've seen how he treats me?
I mean,
you've told me about it.
That's not what you said.
Stuart, how do you know
all this?
Have you been spying on me?
I just...
I just wanted to help.
Becca, listen.
Please listen to me.
I've never met anybody
like you before.
We haven't met,
Stuart!
I know, I know,
I know.
I know that!
I mean, when I...
When I talk to you,
I've never felt so close
to anybody
in my whole life.
You thought
you'd be my hero?
You thought you'd
just rescue me?
Oh God...
This isn't some game,
Stuart.
These are dangerous men.
They've got Eric out there right
now, looking for the leak.
Do you understand?
They're looking for you.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
I'm gonna fix it.
I'm-I'm gonna tell the cops
where you are right now.
Just don't!
Please, if you call the cops,
I'm dead!
Do you understand?
I'm gonna make this right.
Rebecca; Don't, okay?
Stay outta this!
Stay outta my life.
Stuart, God,
the last thing I need right now
is more help from you!
I'm sorry, please.
Okay, Eddie,
we got a confirmation;
Rebecca's inside.
She's under threat
of violence.
We gotta move.
Sam I'm not seeing a clean approach.
They'll spot us coming.
What do you know
about the trojan war?
Not much.
Me neither.
Let's do it.
Detective Travis, we
need more manpower here.
Copy that.
Hey, you see that?
He's got a slight limp.
Yeah, thought I saw some
stiffness in his hand too,
same side,
on the left.
One-sided paralysis.
Seems like a stroke.
Okay, Spike, Stuart
tried to play hero today
and it backfired.
You gotta get to this kid
before he tries to put himself
further into the line of fire.
Copy that.
Hey, what's up!
Aghhh!
You thought
you could rat us out?
What're you talking about?
You have no idea
what kinda trouble you're in.
You stay there, okay?
And shut up!
Eric.
I'm the one you're after.
Who is this?
I'm the one that told the cops
about you.
If you let Rebecca go,
I can make this
all go away.
How do you know about Rebecca?
I know everything, Eric.
Let her go.
Deal with me.
All right.
All right,
just tell me where you are.
Sir, I'm gonna need
the truck
and the jacket.
Stuart's address
. Apartment tower downtown.
Okay.
Wait. Look... Look,
this is what you want.
This is it,
right here.
That's everything I collected
on your operation;
That's photos, videos,
transcripts.
Everything.
I wiped my hard drive.
That's it.
No one's ever gonna know.
You here alone?
Yes.
So you can let Rebecca go,
please.
Rebecca?
Just who in the hell
are you?!
I'm-I'm Stuart.
My name is Stuart.
How did you know
about today, Stuart?
I studied you.
I watched you plan
some of the jobs.
I watched you
plan this job.
Oh, you followed us.
I didn't follow you,
I watched you on the computers.
What?
Why?
Eric, come on, man, let's
just get him to the boss.
I gave you everything
you need.
On no! Wait!
Start talking!
Run for your lives!
Go, now! Now!
Police! Stop now!
Right there!
Hands in the air!
On the ground!
On the ground now!
Stay there!
Don't move!
Get down on
the ground now!
Leah, with me!
Let's move!
Take the stairs.
Bottom of the South stairs
clear and contained.
You stuck your nose
into something, Stuart,
and you don't just get
to walk away now!
Becca...
What is this?
What is it?
It's gotten to the point
where I,
I ask how his day was,
and he gets defensive
with me.
It's like by just expecting him
to say words,
I'm pointing out
some kind of defect.
No, that can't work.
You're the only one that's putting
any effort into the relationship.
It's not like that.
It sure seems like that.
It's not.
I mean, he gets me, you kn??
He knows me.
He knows what I need to work on,
what I need to improve on.
He tells you
what you need to improve on?
He's right.
I mean,
he makes mistakes too.
Stuart
yeah, he stole cars.
Stuart, that was in the past.
He's changed.
Do you believe that, Becca?
Or do you just...
Wanna believe that?
Oh wow.
Stuart, it's starting
to come together for me.
Once you get me
out of the picture
and she runs into your arms...
Is that the basic idea?
Well, you know,
full points for taking
your shot there, Stuart.
I just-I just got
one question.
What kind of twisted fantasyland
do you live in, man?
Aghhh!
You know, all that talk...
What, you think that means
that she's into you?
That it means you're safe?
Agh!
It means you're nothing.
You're not an option,
Stuart.
You're a girlfriend to her.
A buddy... A gimpy,
lonely little buddy...
Eric, let's go, man.
Tell me one thing...
How often did you
spy on her?
That's not what it was for.
You're telling me
you never snuck a look?
No.
No?
Maybe when she was undressed to
take a shower or changing for work?
I swear.
Late some night,
you're feeling lonely, right,
so you turn on the computer
just for a second, right?
There's no harm, right?
You just wanna see her.
Yeah,
maybe watch her sleep,
watch her breathe.
Oh yeah.
Did you tell her that,
Stuart?
Did you share that with
your special friend?
That you are a sick,
lying pervert
did you do that?
I lost my job
because of you!
I lost my girlfriend.
I lost everything
I've worked for!
Everything!
You pathetic! Little! Puke!
Okay.
Stay away!
Come on, come on.
- Eric!
- Get off!
Get off!
Come on! Come on!
- Let's go!
- Get off!
Do you want some more?!
SRU! Get down
! Get down on the ground!
Down on the ground!
Get down on the
ground right now!
Hands on your back!
Don't you move!
Subject located!
Second floor!
Drop your weapon!
Drop the blade!
Weapons down!
Okay.
Drop the gun!
Do it now!
Stuart?! Where'd you go?
Stuart?!
Stuart! Wait!
Stuart!
No! Just don't! Don't!
Don't come near me!
Okay, man, I'm
gonna stay right here!
Stuart, you were trying
to help someone
you care about today.
You were trying to put
some bad characters behind bars.
Those are noble goals.
I saw you
on the road today.
You're the one
who looked in the camera.
That's right.
How do you know
what I did today?
I spied on you.
I tapped into your webcam.
I used your program
against you,
and I went into
your private video files.
Then you know that Rebecca's
in trouble because of me,
because of my stupidity,
and my lies...
Isn't she?
Isn't she?!
No! No!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Stuart! Stuart!
Don't come any closer now!
Put the gun on the floor!
Do it now!
Terry Burnett.
Back off, now!
My name's Greg Parker.
Oh, you've got
yourself in a bit of a fix,
haven't you,
Mr. Greg Parker?
How's that, sir?
Well, I'm not gonna give
up and you're not gonna shoot me.
I don't wanna shoot you.
No, you are not gonna shoot me.
You can't shoot me.
That's how this works.
Okay. You wanna
talk me through that, sir?
It's real simple.
You put a bullet in me,
I can still squeeze off
a shot.
It'll be my last gesture
on earth.
Hell, it could just be
a muscle spasm.
Could be my finger hitting
the trigger on the way down.
Either way,
it does make a difference
to this girl...
And her blood'll be
on your hands, Parker!
So I'll tell you what.
Tell your guys to back down,
clear me a path,
and let me outta here.
I can't do that just yet, sir.
Look, I am not interested
in standing around, Parker!
Just stay there!
I'm not going anywhere!
Listen to me...
You took a chance today.
You looked out
beyond your life
and you imagined
something better,
and you went for it.
You know what?
Maybe it was foolish,
maybe you overreached.
Yeah, you think?
But the point is it happens.
My God, Stuart,
it happens all the time.
When the heart's involved,
we botch things up.
It's how we're wired.
But the thing is
it can all be made better...
all of it.
You know why?
Because you acted out of love.
And when you do that,
those mistakes you make,
they can be corrected...
all of it...
Now, you made some
questionable choices today
that you are gonna feel
bad about for a while,
but there is one choice
you coulda made
that you would have
regretted forever.
You know what that is?
It's doing nothing.
Doing nothing is easy,
Stuart.
To hide away,
to put up walls.
The hardest part
is reaching out,
and you did that.
You took that chance.
Today is a beginning;
It's not an end.
All right, we're ready to
move this thing along, Mr. Burnett,
but you need to know something
first.
You need to know
that there are targets...
clusters of nerves,
lobes in the brain,
that'll put a person down
instantly.
We call these kill points.
You hit one
and there are no last gestures,
no muscle spasms.
You just switch off
like a light.
Now they're small,
these kill points...
about the size of a dime...
but to these three officers
aiming at you right now,
who spend fourteen hours a week
in a gun range
training for
just this situation,
they look like beach balls.
We're about to move to
the next stage of this thing,
Mr. Burnett,
so you tell me...
How do you want this to go?
Put the gun on the
floor right now, Mr. Burnett,
and step away from the girl.
Do it now!
Yes, sir!
Thank you, sir!
That's a good choice.
- On your knees!
- Get down right now!
- Get down! Get down!
Yes, yes, yes!
It's okay, it's okay.
Kill points?
Just came to me in the moment,
Eddie.
Spike, subject is secure.
Hostage is safe.
Rebecca is safe.
Stuart, Rebecca is safe.
My sergeant just told me.
She's unharmed.
Okay...
It still doesn't excuse
what I did...
It doesn't mean
she's gonna forgive me.
Maybe not.
I'm no good out there.
No. That's
where you're wrong.
Yeah?
How do you know?
Because I watched you
with Rebecca
and I saw how you
talk to her,
and I saw your honesty,
your generosity,
and I saw an open heart.
And I saw you listen...
And you know what,
Stuart?
That's it;
That is the ball game.
If you can do that,
everything else,
it will come.
You really believe that?
Oh, I know it.
You and I,
we're not so different.
Yeah, right.
Look at you.
It's mostly gear.
Trust me.
You think you can
come over on my side?
I'd feel a lot better
about that.
You used my own
malware against me, huh?
It's a beautiful
piece of code.
It's hugely illegal
on so many levels,
but it's really...
It's quite spectacular, buddy.
Can you come back
on my side?
Come on.
Right here.
I've got you, bud.
There you go.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
♪ maybe we'll come back
some day ♪
♪ you see how we've grown ♪
♪ carve our names
on everything ♪
Rebecca...
I am so sorry.
Who did that to you?
It doesn't matter now.
Did Eric do that,
Stuart?
Yeah.
I was worried about losing
your friendship.
You think maybe we
could just start over again?
I don't know.
Can we be straight
with each other?
Yeah.
You see the fingers
on this hand?
From a stroke.
I've known for ages.
Are you kidding me?
How?
Because I called
your supervisor
after our first session
to tell him
how great you are
and he told me.
I... Okay.
Well, in terms of big,
scary revelations,
that's kinda
my best card.
So...
Hey, Winnie.
Hey, what's up?
Are you all right?
Uh, what? Yeah.
No. Uh...
It's just, it's been brought
to my attention that...
Wait, rewind.
Would you like to go out
to dinner with me sometime?
Spike,
you're asking me out?!
I am.
Well, I don't know
what to say.
Tongue-tied;
That's gotta be a good sign.
Yeah, no... I just...
Um, I'm flattered,
but I don't date cops.
Ever?
I'm sorry.
It's just my rule.
Okay.
Just so I know,
is this one of those rules
where you use it
just to let guys down easy?
No!
No?
Like one of those rules
where the perfect guy
comes along
and the rule would go
out the window?
No, no, no.
It's one of those rules
that...
It just reminds me that
I need balance in my life.
I mean, the perfect guy
just came along.
Okay.
♪ I've got something ♪
♪ you've got something ♪
♪ we've got something ♪