Where is Michelle Dalton?!
Michelle!!!
Team One, James is headed
to the banquet kitchen.
- Come on, let's go.
- Excuse me.
Where is she?!
Wh-what's he doing?
Ed?
Seconds away.
Michelle?!!
James?
Mom...
_
We carry machine guns;
nine millimeters, cornershots.
And we are trained
to fire those guns...
And then we are trained
not to fire them.
Now, this job isn't
about firing guns,
this job is about getting
into the subject's head.
It's about listening
to what they have to say.
I'm gonna holster my gun...
You gotta connect...
Respect and protect.
Keep the peace.
That's right.
Okay.
You guys,
who here has thought about
being a cop?
Good. Good, good.
My son, Clark,
he's got other plans;
I can respect that.
Anybody else?
Now, in my case,
my dad was a cop,
my brother's a cop,
and I started out
walking the beat.
And it was actually
this guy's dad
who convinced me
to join this new unit--
the SRU.
Wasn't easy--
not for any of us.
Hundreds apply, few make it in.
First you take a psych test,
multiple choice--
what kind of cop are you?
What kind of human being? -
1600 questions.
And you get through that,
then it's fitness tests
and drills.
We specialize
in marksmanship...
Bombs, tech, psychology,
negotiations.
Every day, you push yourself
to your limit...
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Physically, mentally...
So that you can handle the job
when the job gets tough.
Because the job does get tough.
But you work hard,
you do your best.
You do what you think is right
and you'll find peace
in whatever you choose to do.
Aghhh!
Watch the corner.
We're almost there.
We are getting way too good
at this.
Seriously.
Oh my God.
Okay.
So I'll tell you
what I'm thinking.
After work,
I'll buy a bottle of bubbly,
bring it back here,
and we'll crack it open
and celebrate
your show tonight.
Just the two of us.
Well, maybe not the first time.
Second maybe?
I could suck.
- Shut up!
- You shut up.
You are May Dalton.
You're smart, talented.
Wise beyond your years,
and you are the bravest person
that I have ever known.
And who do you think
I got all that from?
I gotta go. Bye.
Hey.
Hey, goddess.
Shouldn't you be working?
I've got eleven posters left,
and I do not plan on
letting them go to waste.
Tobias, you're already late,
and your boss is gonna--
It's whatever.
You're worth it.
You know, it's killing me
that you can't be there tonight.
So sing for me now.
What?
- Please?
- I can't just--
Just sing it
like you're up there
and I'm the only one
watching you.
Okay, just hang on a second.
♪ My heart has wings, love ♪
♪ wings to carry me home ♪
♪ my heart it sings, love ♪
♪ your name is its song ♪
♪ though valleys-- ♪
Hang on.
Call waiting.
It's him.
Not taking it.
Uh, that's good.
That's good, that's good.
You know what? I'm gonna um...
I'm gonna come see you.
I need my good luck kiss.
Hi, this is
may, leave a message.
Hey... it's me.
Um... I just I wanted to call
and give you
this cell phone number.
I had to get a new cell phone
because the phone company's...
All right, I just...
I just want you to know
that I'm thinking about you
and...
and happy birthday.
And uh...
I would really like
to hear your voice, okay?
Dammit!
The couple moving in's
been more than patient.
I told you, I can pay.
You were supposed to be out
a week ago--
Look, the new job,
it's as good as mine--
No way.
Two weeks-- first paycheck,
it's all yours. Come on--
I've heard it before.
Okay, look, take my watch.
It's worth $300 bucks,
all right?
I don't want
your damn watch--
$300 bucks, all right?
You can have the ring as well.
It's white gold, all right?
I sure as hell don't need it
anymore. Take it.
James...
Come on.
All right, look...
Here. Take this.
It's real crystal.
It's real.
You gotta be able
to get something for this.
Come on, take it.
Take it!
You're gone by tonight.
Don't make me call the cops.
You will show me some respect!
- How was class, Ed?
- It was good.
Your kid's school, right?
Yeah. Boss's kid
goes there too.
Dean seemed pretty into it.
Oh, yeah?
Well, more than Clark did.
That's because your boy's
had seventeen years
living with a cop.
Mine's just getting started.
Yeah, we'll see.
What's not to love
about being a cop?
The hours, the glamour,
the girls...
The girls?
King Street, Saturday night?
I'm just saying, I saw you.
Hey, I was just making sure
the ladies got home safe.
Both ladies.
Raf.
Yeah, boss.
So, uh, coming up
on a year next week.
Yeah, I know.
So how is it goin'?
You tell me.
I think you're doing great.
But it's a two-way relationship,
you and the job.
You know what I'm saying?
I think so.
After a year,
you get a taste of how
the job's doing for you.
I hear you, boss.
It's all good.
Good. Okay.
So two girls, huh?
Actually, it was three,
but who's countin'?
Yo! Tobias!
The new graphics look good.
Just finished programming.
Sweet! How's May?
Big night.
She's gonna be awesome!
Won't be long
till she's playing here.
You know it!
Can I help you?
Hey, we're not open yet!
I'm here for him.
Hey!
We need to talk.
- What're you doing here?
- I need some information.
I'm not gonna talk to you.
Yes, you are gonna talk to me.
Winnie, go for the 911...
David?
David,
this is Sergeant Greg Parker,
I'm with the Strategic
Response Unit.
Can you identify the gunman?
No idea.
He came in,
went straight for my friend.
Okay. Does he know him?
I don't know.
He's shouting at him--
Tell me where she is!
You gotta get here.
Oof!
Oh my God!
What's going on?
I don't want to hurt you!
Tell me where she is!
Come on, David, talk to me.
What's happening?
Tell me now!
Ungh!
Aghhhh!
Eddie...
Get up! Get up!
Get up now!
Start walking!
David! David!
I'm here.
Don't engage him, please!
I just need you to tell me
what he is doing?
He's taking him outside.
He's getting away.
All right, we're almost there.
You hang tight.
I heard another shot!
David, stay inside!
Sam, take the
entrance on Richardson.
Copy that.
He's getting away,
I think he's got Tobias
in the car.
What kind of car is it?
Grey Sedan.
I can't make out the plate.
Ends in a one.
Sixty-one.
Sam, you get that?
Affirmative.
We got him.
Only one person in the car.
This is
the Strategic Response Unit!
This is the police!
Pull over immediately!
I repeat,
pull your vehicle over!
We got an image from the
CCTV, it's gone to your phones.
No sign of Tobias.
If Tobias took a
blow to the head,
he could have passed out
in the car.
You heard three shots, right?
Yeah.
So one when you land,
and the second hit here...
And then one outside.
I'll call in forensics,
see if they can account
for the third.
We didn't see any impact
or ricochet marks outside.
You think he's been shot?
What's going on?
Excuse me, who are you?
May Dalton. The cop outside
told me to come in
and talk to you.
His girlfriend.
Where's Tobias?
Listen, May, your
boyfriend was taken by somebody.
- What?
- Somebody came in here, took him outside.
He was armed.
Okay, May, sit down--
No, I don't need to sit down,
I need to know what's going on.
We're trying to figure
that out, all right? Spike.
Do you know this man?
Oh God...
May, do you know this man?
That's my father!
Still in pursuit.
This guy's not slowing down.
Pull over!
I repeat,
pull your vehicle over!
You see that?
Let's see if we can
force him off Gerrard.
Get up close.
Winnie, set up a roadblock
on Jarvis.
Sam!
Pull back! Pull back!
Oof!
Winnie, we need EMS, right now!
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Winnie, give us an APB,
Gerrard heading east
from Ontario.
Where's EMS?
Tobias, keep still,
we're gonna take care of you.
- You gotta tell May...
- Easy, easy, easy...
He's gonna find her, okay?
He's gonna find
both of them--
What do you mean?
Both of who?
He said he wanted to know
where May was,
but I wouldn't tell him,
and then he said
he'd ask her mom,
so I told him...
Told him what, Tobias?
Royal York Hotel,
where she works.
He's going there now.
He's got a gun!
I'm calling the hotel.
Everything we can
on any James Mitchell
- matching his description.
- Copy.
- I need to see Tobias.
- Tobias is gonna be okay,
but we gotta get
to your mom and dad
and make sure
they're gonna be okay, too.
You can't let him near my mom.
I hear you.
What's your name?
It's Ed.
Ed Lane.
Ed, you can't let this happen.
You don't know my father.
Can you help us know him, May?
May, can you ride with us?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
Tobias is with EMS.
We're on our way to the hotel,
squad cars en route.
Jules, any luck
reaching the mother?
She works the banquets,
they don't know
if she's showed up to work yet.
They're looking for her.
So you and your
mom left last year?
Is that right?
It should've been sooner.
What happened?
It wasn't just one thing,
it was everything.
Then it just got worse.
Were you afraid of your dad?
Yeah.
He thought I didn't know
who he was.
I knew who he was.
Your problem is
you just don't think.
James, I told
you about it last week.
You told me...
You said it was okay.
The sheets were only on sale
for the weekend--
I said it was okay?
You did.
Are you telling me
what I remember now?
- No. Please...
- Are you?!
No!
Because now I have a
car payment that bounces.
- I'm sorry.
- I have a car payment that bounces
because you need new sheets!
You know what?
From now on,
you sign your cheques
over to me, Michelle.
I give you what you need.
You don't need to do that.
Why not?
You planning on making
a move, Michelle?
- Don't...
- Don't you lie to me!
Dad?
Hey, May-be.
Uh, you finish
your Egyptian project?
Yeah...
Yeah, almost.
Hey um...
Do me a favour?
Help your mom clean up
the plates she broke.
You know how she gets.
Thank you, sweetie.
He took away all her money
so she couldn't leave,
made her think she was crazy,
and that he was the normal one.
May, moving out,
the restraining order.
Your mom changing her name,
those are all things
that both of you did right,
and that past is behind you.
But it's not!
I mean, look where I am.
I'm in a car with two cops.
I mean, no offense, guys,
but you really haven't done
the best job
of keeping him away.
He called me today
'cause it's my birthday.
How'd he get
my cell phone number?
He even tracked down
where Tobias works.
Now he knows where my mom works.
I mean, what are we supposed
to do?
Tobias has done everything
so that we can feel safe.
But I guess that's just
not gonna happen.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Uh, Heather,
I wonder if you can help me,
I'm looking for someone.
Of course.
Is this person a guest with us today?
No. An employee.
Oh, okay.
You'd need to speak
to the resident manager.
- Shall I call him?
- Sure.
You know, actually,
I just came in to say hi.
It's the manager
I'm looking for...
I have a job interview.
A friend set it up.
I have his name here
somewhere...
Floyd Mather.
Mr. Mather.
Right.
Take those stairs
up to the mezzanine,
then all the way around
and look for the signs.
Thank you so much.
Good luck!
Boss, James served two
30-day sentences last year--
Assault and violating
a restraining order.
Domestic offenses
go back four years,
and he's been out of work
for over a year.
There's gonna be money issues.
I talked to Tobias.
Michelle and May
have moved three times
in the last year
and James keeps finding them,
and every time he escalates.
Dominating personality,
multiple stressors,
his life is out of control.
He picks today to lash back
at the one person he can blame.
And we know how these things
often go.
Yeah, that's what
I'm afraid of.
Murder-suicide.
I'm looking for the manager.
Can I help you?
Yes.
Where's Michelle Dalton?
May, we're gonna do
everything we can
to keep your mom safe.
This is what we do, May.
Nobody needs to get hurt today.
Tell me your name again.
Greg Parker.
Greg.
Greg and Ed.
I wanna be able to hold you
to what you just
told to me, okay?
Okay, May.
Okay.
Let's go!
Where is Michelle Dalton?!
Michelle!
Where is she?
James...
Is that him?
Yeah.
That's definitely him.
Spike, we got a positive ID
on James.
Concierge says he's looking
for the HR manager.
Thank you, Heather.
Heather, where can I find
the manager?
Uh, mezzanine.
Up those stairs.
Thank you.
Spike, transponders on.
Let's move.
Up the stairs, left and left.
May's gonna help us profile.
No problem.
May? Spike.
Have a seat.
Thanks.
Okay?
This wasn't necessary,
Michelle?
You know that none of this
had to happen,
don't you?
All you had to do
was talk to me.
You know what day it is today.
Four, seven, Bravo, Kilo
underscore Tango, X-ray.
Thank you.
Those dots, is that your team?
Yep, and if my mom
was in trouble?
They're the ones I'd wanna see
coming through the window.
That's-that's inside.
How did you...?
It's magic.
Or hotel security
just gave you their access code
and wi-fi password.
She sees right though me.
Sir, the man who attacked you,
where did he go?
Michelle Dalton,
he went after her.
She was just in
the banquet kitchen.
- Banquet kitchen?
- The other side of the hotel,
through that door,
two flights down.
Okay, go back to your office.
We'll get you help
as soon as we can.
Team one, James is headed
to the banquet kitchen.
Copy that.
Boss, you're close.
Down the stairs to your right.
Okay.
Here we go.
He's going to shoot her.
No, this is Team One
we're talking about May.
I need to hear.
Can we hear?
No. You know,
it can get a little bit intense--
Spike, I'm not a kid, okay?
You said so yourself,
she'll be fine.
Now am I here to help
or am I not?
Boss, okay if I patch May
into the conversation?
Okay, Spike,
but use your judgment.
Copy that.
Okay, I'm gonna put it
on speaker.
You're gonna hear
the team's mics
and whatever we can pick up
from the kitchen
intercom system.
I've been more than
reasonable with you.
This is what happens
when you push a reasonable man
for too long!
No problem, James.
It's no problem.
Put the gun away
and you and I can have
a reasonable talk, okay?
All right.
Let's start with this...
Where is my daughter?
Where is she?!
Let's get the other
civilians out of the kitchen
and get him talking.
This man needs
to feel in control.
He's not a fan of
cops telling him what to do.
He doesn't like anyone
telling him what to do.
He has to be in charge.
Boss, you copy that?
Yeah, Spike, I heard.
Let's clear the room.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Sir, I need you
to leave right now.
I need you to leave now.
- Come on, let's go.
- Excuse me...
Subject's standing twenty
feet from the banquet doors,
facing away.
How could you do this to me?!
James, I don't know
what you're talking about!
Don't lie to me!
I'm not!
Don't stand there
and lie to my face!
Don't try to turn this around!
You know damn well
this is your fault!
Please put the gun down.
I don't know
what you want me to say.
I want you to tell me
the truth!
James?
My name is Greg Parker.
I'd like to talk to you
if that's all right?
This is no one else's business.
I appreciate that,
but what I'd like to do--
Who the hell are you?
My name is Greg, like I said,
I'm a professional negotiator.
What I'd like to do here
is maybe help facilitate
a dialogue.
A conversation is
what I am trying to do here!
I don't need
a professional negotiator
to have a conversation
with my own ex-wife,
for godsake!
All right?
What I need is
a little privacy.
Okay, that's great.
Let's do that.
I mean, you're in charge here.
Why don't you just tell
the other people in the room
that it's time for them to go.
I just wanna talk to my wife!
I hear you, James.
Ed, what's your status?
Seconds away.
It'd be easier
to have that conversation...
In position.
You're calling the shots here.
They'll do whatever you say.
Just ask them to leave.
In position.
You want privacy?
That's reasonable.
You want them to go?
That's fair.
Just tell them.
Okay, okay.
Get out of here!
Everyone get out!
Except for you.
Get out now!
Get out!
Thank you, James,
that's a good choice.
I said, get outta here, now!
I'm not going anywhere.
You've got something to say,
you can say it now.
No.
What's wrong?
Hold it!
You hold it right there!
That's Keith;
that's my mother's boyfriend.
You're him, aren't you?
- James.
- He is, isn't he?
You're the workplace boyfriend.
Oh boy...
Congratulations.
How is it?
W-w-what're you
talking about?
My ex-wife.
How is it?
It's my fault.
Last time I talked to him,
I was just trying to help.
You mentioned your mother
was seeing someone?
I just said we have to stop
dwelling on the past,
on grudges,
and we have to move on...
and then I mentioned Keith.
Oh my God!
May! You didn't make
this happen.
Hey, James, why don't we just
stay on track--
I am talking here!
Don't you take another step!
Look, if it's me
you got a problem with--
You back off!
James, you wanna have
a conversation with Michelle,
let's just do that!
Let me give you
a friendly warning...
You watch your back.
I'm serious, James,
this is between you and me--
Watch your
bank account, watch your wallet,
watch your goddamn dog!
Because this woman,
she will take everything
from you!
You make 'em stop that!
You shut it off!
Yup.
Get 'em to turn it off
right now!
James?
Let's you and I just go
and talk. Just...
No problem.
Just the two of us.
I know the best way...
way out of here, okay?
Okay.
I want nice and slow.
Let's go.
New deal.
Subject's preparing to exit.
Raf, Jules, go around,
isolate Michelle,
and cut him off.
- Copy that.
- Copy.
Wait. W-w-what's he doing?
Ed?!
Get down!
- Clear the room!
- No shot! Get down!
James Mitchell! Right there!
James Mitchell!
They're in the elevator.
We lost 'em!
They're gone!
Mom!
Units have taken care
of the evac,
getting the fire under control.
Spike, the subject
and his hostage
have taken
the service elevator.
I know, and I'm on it.
The elevator they took
is the only one
with rooftop access.
- You got control?
- I do.
We get him to the roof,
it's contained,
we keep him away
from civilians.
Okay, good. Nice.
Is there a security camera
in there too?
That's just where I was going.
And we also gotta have a phone
that we can hear through.
What if he gets out
at the lobby
and makes a run for it?
I've got full override
and they go where I say.
Guys, I'm gonna send down
another elevator.
It doesn't go to the roof
but I can get you through
a window.
Spike, get the uniforms
to the stairs
with Remmy's for me and Sam.
Copy that.
'Kay, there's vents for cover.
You take the low one;
I'll get a higher vantage
from the 18th floor.
Let's move.
There's still a
chance we can talk him down.
Jules if he wanted to kill Michelle,
he already would've done it.
There's something else
he wants.
Come on, come on, come on...
Okay, let's break it down.
This is a guy
who's lost everything.
I think what he's fighting for
is a situation
where he's back
in control again.
Even if it's the last thing
he controls.
This might not be a dead end.
He's got May.
It's me he wants.
He doesn't believe
I don't like him.
He wants me, not her.
She's the one thing standing
between him and giving up.
She is the light
at the end of his tunnel.
The talk's gotta be about her.
What the hell...?
What the hell?
Come on!
No, no, no, no.
Someone else must've
called the elevator.
I realize
that, bright-eyes!
It still should've stopped
at the lobby
on the way up!
James, just calm down.
We're gonna get there
one way or another.
Stay calm, okay?
The most... precious thing
in the world to me...
and you took her from me!
Why would you do that?
He thinks cops
are messing with him.
If we want his attention,
he's more likely to listen
to the daughter.
Use May as a TPI?
Third Party Intermediary;
a civilian involved
in negotiations.
It gives him a reason
to look to the future.
She's just a teenager.
Why would you do that to me?!
James...
Why?!
- Aggghhhhh!
- You're not getting away with it anymore!
James, please!
Spike, turn the speaker off.
What're you doing?
Why are you turning it off?
I'm sorry.
Guys, this could be
emotionally traumatic.
Do we wanna put her
through that?
I'll do it!
He'll listen to me.
Usually, we try not--
I'm eighteen, okay?
I can make this choice.
Please, let me help my mom,
or this will never be over.
Boss, she is old enough
to know what she's doing.
Raf's right;
May's not a kid.
She's pretty together.
Let me talk to him.
Go ahead.
Greg, I won't even talk
to him if you don't want me to,
but if he sees me up there,
watching...
He cares a lot more
about my respect
than he does yours.
Subject's on the roof.
Come on!
Come!
Come on! Come on!
May, we can't control
what your father might do.
You got me and Sam on Sierra.
There's no way
we'll let James harm her.
It's worth a try.
He's heading into an endgame...
If he feels that he can
revive his relationship
with his daughter...
Even if it's from jail,
it's something to hope for.
It'll feel more within reach
if he can see her.
All right, May.
But you have to follow
our instructions
and stick to the script.
Promise.
Spike, bring her to the roof.
Copy that.
Let's go, bella.
Aggghhhh!
Sam, you got eyes?
In position. I see 'im.
You know it's over, right?
Everything changes today.
What changes?
This game you play,
this power game,
where your attorney
sucks my account dry,
where you sabotage
my reputation,
where you play hide and seek
all over the damn city,
and your favorite part--
where you write down the rules
about when I can see
my own daughter.
- I'm not to blame!
- Did you say something?
We're almost there, guys.
My little girl is eighteen,
for Christ sake!
I just wanna hear her voice.
I call her
and none of my messages
get through.
So, I'm sorry,
but I gotta wonder why.
You have her cell phone number?
You made me do it!
I had to track you down
and ask you,
where the hell is May?!
Come on.
All right, listen to me.
I want you to talk about hope,
I want you to talk
about the future.
Look at me.
I need you to stay positive,
all right?
That's all you need to do.
We're gonna be
right there with you,
okay?
Okay.
Okay. Let's do it.
If she's not returning
your calls,
she's choosing not to.
- You have to accept that.
- No! You're a liar!
Daddy?!
May!
I'm right here, okay?
I'm right here.
Look what you've done!
The cops, again!
You bitch!
I need you to get him to focus
on the two of you.
All right. Okay.
Please, dad,
just let her go, okay?
It'll just be you and me
and we can talk
as much as you want.
I have survived,
I have pulled through,
and every time
I think I'm close,
you do it again!
Dad, I wanna hear
what you're feeling, okay?
Why don't you tell me!
When will it be enough?!
When?!
Tell me!
Ed?
Weapon's not in play.
What do you want?!
You want me to give up?!
What're you doing?!
You have to stop it!
May, when we shoot,
we shoot to kill.
It's a last resort.
Can't you just shoot him
in the leg,
or do something?
It's too risky.
He could fire by reflex.
Don't give up on words.
Do you want me to die,
Michelle?
Would that make you happy?
Would that work for you?
Sierra two, stand by.
On my go.
Copy.
Don't you dare!
May!
Boss?
May's got a weapon.
She's got a weapon.
Don't you dare!
May, drop your weapon!
Hold fire!
Leave her alone!
This ends now!
Okay, she's crossed the line.
I've got...
I've got May.
I have James!
May, drop your weapon now!
May, baby, no!
- May, don't do it!
- Drop your weapon!
Drop your weapon!
Drop your weapon now!
May! Back away!
Back away right now!
May, you put that weapon down
or we will have to shoot you!
Boss?
Drop it, May!
Boss, she's active.
Greg, she's gonna kill him.
Drop it!
Scorpio.
I just wanted to see her...
Noooo!
Oh my God...
My baby!
You son of a bitch!
You killed her!
- Who killed her?!
- You killed her!
You did it!
You don't call me a killer,
you son of a bitch!
You did this!
So it was a complex situation.
It was a complex situation.
In the audio log,
in the last two minutes
before scorpio command,
there were numerous voices,
raised voices,
shouted instructions.
The impression it gives is...
loss of control.
We had complete control.
What you heard
was communication
between members of my team.
The raised voices were
our instructions
to May Dalton, we were...
trying to avoid
the use of lethal force.
There were... two gunshots
before scorpio call.
Yes.
You allowed her to fire
before scorpio call.
She raised her weapon,
her grip was unsteady--
You allowed her to fire twice.
Isn't that a breach
of protocol?
You heard the audio.
We were trying
to get her to stop.
Noted.
Your sergeant, Greg Parker,
states...
She was in the "tunnel."
She steadied her right hand
with her left,
and prepared to fire
a third time.
She crossed the line,
I took the shot.
After your sergeant's
scorpio command?
At the same time.
And are you convinced that
all options were exhausted
before the use of lethal force?
What did I just say?
Well, thank you for your time.
You know the process.
She was right
beside me in the truck,
how could I not have known?
Spike, what,
are we supposed to frisk
all our witnesses?
Okay, May said she and her mom
never felt safe, right?
That the cops couldn't
protect them?
That he could track
them down anywhere.
I remember that.
"Tobias has done everything
so that we can feel safe."
Come on, from that,
we're supposed to know
that Tobias procured her
an illegal gun,
which she kept with her
at all times, just in case?
She should never
have been on that roof;
that was my fault.
Boss, don't go there.
We all signed off on it.
It was a judgment call.
She insisted--
you all heard that, right?
She said, "let me go up there,
let me talk to him."
That's irrelevant; She
was emotionally involved.
That wasn't her choice to make.
We made that choice.
She knew when she said it
that she had a loaded weapon.
I'm just saying.
All right, bean bag rounds.
Raf and Spike,
if we sent you from here
and here, and we timed it--
Sam, we don't take that risk,
not when the subject
has a weapon
inches from the victim!
I know, but what I'm saying
is we missed an opportunity
when he was distracted
by May coming towards--
I was the one who let her run.
I had her, hand on shoulder.
She was safe.
And next thing I know
she's running into
the line of fire.
All right, stop!
Just stop.
We did nothing wrong.
We followed protocol.
An eighteen-year-old girl's dead
and there's nothing right
about that.
She was a brave girl.
She deserved to live,
and it is a tragedy
that she's gone.
But she knew
what she was doing;
she was armed.
She was an active shooter,
and we have a code,
we have rules,
so that when
we are under pressure
we function as a team
and we know what to do.
This one time,
we could've made an exception.
We could've taken the risk.
We could've shot to wound.
Raf, that's a slippery slope.
Okay, you know what? How 'bout
I just do us all a favor
and say what we're
all thinking.
We could've just held fire
and...
let her kill him.
No, we couldn't.
Because that's not
how it works.
We are not judges, we are cops.
We're cops and we all-
all of us--
have to be on the same page.
Okay, let's all sit down.
I get it, all right?
I get that's the job--
No, no, no!
We don't get to wing it.
We don't get to choose
which rules we're gonna follow;
that's what the bad guys do.
What we do...
we serve the law.
Now, are you good with that?
Ed, I respect that this is
what you've gotta believe
to get through this,
after what you had to do.
Oh man...
I'm just saying,
if that's the job...
Look, I am very serious
about serving the law,
and this last year has been
the proudest of my life,
but...
I just don't think this
is the best place for me
to keep the peace.
Raf, it's been a long day.
Raf, we've all had days
where we've questioned the job--
I know, I get that, boss.
It's just, for me, this...
This can't happen again.
It won't happen again.
Why don't you sleep on it?
Give us a chance
to talk you out of it.
I appreciate that, guys.
It's um...
It's just not a place
that I can go.
♪ My heart has wings, love ♪
♪ wings that carry me home ♪
♪ My heart, it sings, love ♪
♪ your name is its song ♪
♪ Should we be parted ♪
♪ by winter winds
blowing cold ♪
♪ I'll give my hand, love ♪
Hey, dad.
How was your day?
Did you keep the peace?
♪ The waters be wide, love ♪
♪ though they be mighty
and fast ♪
♪ I will ford over ♪
♪ held in your arms at last ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com