Close your eyes - They're closed.
Are you sure?
- Yeah. - Positive?
Okay, open them now.
Look at it! It's great!.
Hey, what do you think Montelli?
Daddy, look at the lake.
- Come on, Mark, let's go to the lake.
Come on, Mark. Let's go!
Oh, look, a motorboat.
It's so nice. I love it!
Hey, kids!
That's dangerous.
I don't want to see you near the edge.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
What?
Yes, sir!
Oh, look at it!
It's ours, it's ours.
Be it ever so ...
- Stop! - What? - One, two, three ...
Be it ever so humble ...
there's no place like home.
What's this? The Andrew's sisters?
Hi, Daddy. - Yes.
- Where's Sonny?
He's right behind us.
He should be here in a minute.
I thought I told you to stay together.
- Home, sweet home.
Daddy's such a creep.
Be respectful.
Hey Dad.
New car is fantastic.
You should have see it at
the red light. A guy was
stepping on the accelerator.
So, I put pedal to the metal ...
You should've seen it. It was fantastic!
I left the guy miles ...
- Where the hell were you?
I told you to back up your mother.
She knows the way.
- Don't be smart, boy.
You’re not too big for a whipping.
I know. You proved that to me.
- Okay.
You're pushing it.
You're right on the edge.
- I just stopped at the corner for cigarettes.
- Stop your whining.
You're gonna be a man by
smoking cigarettes, now, you're
growing a little fuzz over here?
Learn, how to take some orders.
Do you hear me?
I didn't hear you.
Yes, sir.
I'm so excited.
Tricia, look at that fireplace.
Look at that staircase!
Hey ... these windows are stuck.
They're nailed.
Wow! this is a mansion.
Oh, what's going on? What's
this? Peggy Fleming?
- The first and last time you skate in here.
I wonder what idiot nailed all
these windows shut.
- Ah, goddamn it. They nailed every window
upstairs the same way. - Oh, no.
I have a good mind to call that
asshole Real Estate guy.
It's here! It's here!
Hello.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm going to introduce you to your new room.
If you don't watch, I'm gonna fall on you.
No nails here. Over.
Isn't it great?
Ah, it's all right.
I love it.
You're getting heavy.
Hey, you used to hug me all the time.
- That was when you were lighter.
- It's 'cause now you're old and snotty.
Well, there is another reason.
- What?
You're not my type.
You like them tall?
Big boobs, right?
- That's none of your business.
How about you? What's your type?
I like them ... sensitive, dark,
and about this high.
- You're ridiculous. - No!
Come on.
Let's get to know the house.
Can you feel it?
Yeah.
I was wondering, if there was a girl
here before, like me.
And she was in love with a boy.
Yeah.
But she was unhappy.
Unhappy?
The boy didn't love her.
Why?
Because she was ugly, like you.
- Oh, stupid.
Just ... put that down over there.
Anywhere?
They're my husband's guns.
You better put them in the closet.
Hey, lady.
Looks like you got another room in here.
The realtor didn't tell us about that.
Want me to check it out for you?
- Would you please? - Sure.
Great.
Oh, here's a light over here.
This is a really good one.
- All right. Thank you.
You gotta problem in here, lady.
Must be a busted sewer line or something.
Oh, my.
Lady, it stinks in here.
Hey, are you all right?
Come on out of there.
Oh, my goodness. Oh. Are you all right?
- Yeah.
Oh, what happened?
What is that on your shirt?
- Shit.. Excuse me, ma'am.
There's a lot of flies, a lot of mud.
a lot of everything in there.
If I was you, I'd stay out of there.
- Oh, I'm sorry I had you go in there.
Listen, take this towel ...
and go upstairs and wash up.
There's soap and stuff upstairs.
- Okay, thank you. - Watch out for your head.
Mom? Did I scare you?
Somebody ...
touched me.
What?
Somebody ... touched me.
- Who touched you?
Somebody.
Here.
Now.
You mean you actually felt somebody's hand?
It felt like ...
like ...
like fingers on my arm.
Mom, it must be your imagination.
You put the fork here, stupid.
Shut up. - Don't tell me shut up.
- Come on children, that’s enough.
Sit down, everybody.
Anthony did you wash your hands?
What do you think?
I think we're a very lucky family.
Let's eat. Come on. It's getting cold.
Pass me the string beans.
- Pass me the spaghetti.
Haven't we forgotten something?
Heavenly Father ...
bless our new home.
And watch over us as we become
a part of this community.
We thank thee for this food.
Bless it for the nourishment of our bodies and ...
Goddamn! - Don't even look at me,
I didn't put that mirror up there
- No Daddy! - Why does
he always blame me ...
Stop it!
Can't we just eat our first meal
in this house without fighting?
All everybody's been doing
ever since we got here, is fighting!
All right I had enough of it with you!
I don't want to hear any more of it!
Look ...
It's not even broken.
All right, let's continue.
Bless this food for the nourishment ...
of our body in the name of the Father,
the Son, Holy spirit. Amen.
Good night, Trish.
Good night, Sonny.
There better be a good ...
Okay.
Come on back to bed, honey.
I see you there.
There's a 12-gauge shotgun waiting
for anybody trespassing.
Anthony ...
somebody is ...
is here.
Don't move.
What happened?
Brushes.
The brushes?
Anthony.
You can't do that to the kids, no!
But Daddy, it was the brushes! We didn't do it!
Mark, you think that's funny?!
He can't even write!- What about her?!
- Don't you touch her!
- Get out of my way! You leave her alone!
I'll kill you.
I'll kill you, you!
Where's your sister? You had
something to do with this?
No! - You stop it!
You think that’s funny?!
That's funny?!
You're a big man!
Don't you hit them.
Daddy, no! No! Daddy don't! Mommy!
Oh, my god.
What's happening to us?
Why didn't you pull the trigger?
Why didn't you shoot ... that ... pig?
We believe in one God,
the Father, the Almighty,
Maker of Heaven and Earth ...
of all things seen and unseen.
We believe in one Lord, Jesus Christ,
the only Son of God,
eternally begotten of the Father,
God from God, Light from Light,
True God from True God,
begotten, not made, one in Being with the Father.
He ascended into Heaven
and is seated at the right hand of the Father.
I'm Dolores Montelli, and I have four children.
Well, that's splendid. Welcome Mrs. Montelli.
- Thank you. Thank you. - Welcome.
And Mr. Montelli?
My husband is a ...
a good man Father, but he's
not a big church go-er.
- Thank you.
I was wondering if  ...
If you would come to our house and bless it.
- Yes certainly. Certainly, I'd be delighted. - Thank you.
Mr. Montelli, I presume.
I'm Father Adamsky.
Your wife asked me to stop by.
Dolores?
May I come in?
Oh, Father.
Oh, you came. - Mrs. Montelli.
- Oh, I'm so glad.
Have you met my husband?
- Yes, yes. We just met. - Oh, good.
Father please come into our living room.
Children. Children take your coats off.
Children this is the man you saw
in church this afternoon.
This is Father Adamsky.
Father, these are our two
youngest children. This is ...
Mark. - Mark, it's good to meet you.
- And this is Jan. Honey?
Jan, pleasure to meet you.
- Honey? Just put your things
down here, Father.
Honey?
Would you please ... go get
Tricia ... and Sonny?
Give us a minute.
Oh, excuse me.
What the hell is the matter with you?
I don't go to church ... and you bring it here?
Yes.
He's going to bless our house.
Sonny?
Hey, what?
Anthony ...
please.
Anthony please go inside.
Please be nice to him, for me.
Please.
Tricia?
There's somebody some place
around here, but we can't find him.
- Oh, you can't find him.- What's that?
This is ...
a surplice.
Oh, I bet you know what this is for.
I've seen it, but I don't know the name.
- It's a stole.
Want a smoke, priest?
- Uh, no. Thank you.
You mind, if I do?
Not at all.
Jan?
Yes, sir.
See if  ...
the priest wants a drink of something.
A glass of water would be very nice.
- I'll get it. I'll get it!
No, I'll get it! - I'll get it!
You're dead! - You're dead!
You're scaring me. I can't breathe!
It's like a movie. - You're scaring me.
Don't worry, it's okay.
Here, you can take the glass.
I love you.
Father ...
This is my first born.
Sonny.
He hasn't been feeling well, lately.
Good to meet you, Sonny.
What do you kids think this
house is, a playground?!
- We didn't do it!
Don't you lie to me!
Please! Don't hit the child.
Mister, this isn't your business.
Do you hear that?!
I raise my children, the way I see fit!
Now you do what you got to do and go.
Anthony!
You think that's funny, huh?
But dad, we didn't do it.
Father, please forgive my husband.
Please, Father.
- I think there'll be a better
time for this Mrs. Montelli.
Yes of course, Father. Of course.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
No, it's not your fault.
Perhaps one day your husband
and I can meet as friends.
- Of course, Father. Of course.
We are going to get into the car ...
and we're going to go to the church.
And you are going to apologize
to the priest in front of your children.
Or else ...
Or else?
Or else what?
Or else I'm gonna walk out of this house tonight ...
and I'm not ...
going to come back.
- Jesus Christ, Dolores.
Hey, snotty.
You coming to church?
Hurry up. Come on, hurry up.
Where's Sonny?
- Oh, he's upstairs. He said,
he isn’t feeling well.
Is that you?!
Who's there?!
Patricia?
Jan?
Who's there?
I've got a gun out here.
Come on out!
Oh, my god.
No!
I thought you were asleep.
I was.
When did you get back from church?
Oh, hours ago.
What happened downstairs?
All the windows were open.
I don't know.
Something.
I don't remember.
You look terrible.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I feel all right.
You should see a doctor.
You've got dark rings around your eyes.
What happened at church?
Oh, it was unbelievable.
Daddy made his apologies.
But then he took us out for a ...
steak dinner.
Yeah.
He tried to get mommy drunk,
but she wouldn't go for it.
You know ...
There's something strange.
I think mommy doesn't want
to make love to daddy anymore.
I think ... he tries to force her.
I heard her crying.
Why're you looking at me like that?
Because you're beautiful.
I'm beautiful?
Hey, come on, stop teasing me, huh?
- No, I mean it.
Sit on the bed.
Come on, strike a pose for me on the bed.
We're gonna play a game.
Where you're the beautiful model.
And I'm the famous photographer.
Pose for me.
You know, Trish ...
I think that you are probably ...
the most beautiful girl in the world.
Oh, probably?
You're not sure?
I'm sure.
Take off your nightgown.
What?
Just for a second.
Okay, just for a second.
There.
I think.
Now I can say.
You are the most beautiful girl in the world.
Put your hair up.
Oh, now I put my hair up?
You have a beautiful neck.
Enough.
No.
I have a secret I want to tell you.
What?
They're mine.
My panties.
I took them from the laundry.
But ... but why?
It's a big sin.
Don't be afraid.
I ...
went all the way ...
with ...
my friend.
You must ...
resist this temptation.
One day perhaps you'll ...
meet someone.
Marry. Raise a family.
Even if you love him very much,
you must resist.
- We don't love each other.
You don't love each other?
Then this is ...
This is only a sexual matter?
He does it ...
just ...
to hurt.
Well ...
to hurt who?
Hurt you?
To hurt God.
My child you shouldn't say that.
Now tell me everything from the beginning.
No!
I try, and pray at home ...
He's here. Stay away from him.
The words won't come.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
That's all right.
You're here now and ... and ...
and you'll bless the house and
everything will be all right.
Won't it?
Of course.
Sprinkle me with hyssop O Lord ...
and I shall be clean.
Wash me.
And I shall be whiter ...
than snow.
Hear us Holy Lord,
almighty Father. Make us ...
Upstairs too, Father.
Be merciful to me, my God ...
for great is thy goodness.
Glory be to the Father, the Son,
the Holy Spirit. Amen.
You're not coming with me?
My son is upstairs and ...
Well, he hasn't been  ...
happy to see us lately.
Well, I don't want to disturb him.
Oh, you must go Father.
Oh, please.
Please.
- It's all right.
Hear us Holy Lord,
Almighty Father,
Eternal God.
And then send us thy Holy Angel from Heaven.
To guard, cherish, protect, visit and defend ...
all who dwell in this house.
Hello, Sonny.
Sprinkle me with hyssop O Lord
and make me clean.
Why are you hiding?
I'm not.
I just don't want to talk to anyone.
This is my room. I want to be alone.
Your ... your mother ask me to come.
So?
Bless my mother's room.
Would you like to be alone?
Yes.
Is there anything I can do for you?
You want me to leave?
Sorry.
- It's all right.
Maybe we can talk sometime.
It's nice territory.
Oh, my bedroom, Father.
Oh, my bed too.
No!
Here's the sprinkler.
- From which the blood emerged.
That is correct.
Well, what do you want of me?
Well, I may need approval for an exorcism.
An exorcism?
- After what happened in the house ..
- Wait a minute.
Do you believe in ghost, Frank?
I saw a ghost once.
Or at least ...
what appeared to be a ghost.
Although I thought I saw a ghost.....
There may have been another explanation.
Likewise, in the matter at hand.
We must start with you.
Make sure, you're seeing
what you think you are.
The worst thing in this whole area ...
and you know this, Father ...
is to rush into anything.
- Frankly, I don't think we have time.
- Father ...
I will be in touch with you.
We will take our time.
For we wrestle ...
not against the flesh or the blood.
Hi.
Patricia.
Well, come on in.
How are you?
I'm fine.
You're fine?
I think we should discuss your ...
behaviour at confession.
I'm sorry about that, Father.
I apologise.
I'll try again next week.
Good.
How's your mother?
Oh, she's okay.
Oh, by the way we're having a birthday party
for my brother Sonny...
This afternoon.
Can you come?
Please.
- Well, I ...
have to work on ...
my sermon for Sunday.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
For asking me though.
Maybe I could stop by on Monday or Tuesday.
You'll feel better.
When you confess.
Just a minute.
Hello?
I'm terribly sorry.
Father, I have to talk to you about Sonny.
- 327 Clay.
I'll be there right away.
Oh, that's too bad.
Mr. Conner had a stroke.
Hi.
Did you ...
see a young girl in the hallway?
Yeah. She's in a big hurry too.
She almost knocked me down.
I don't have time to deal ...
- Camping anyone?
One of my parishioners is dying.
Sorry to hear that.
Here, let me help you.
- I'll be right back. - Okay?
I'll be here.
Happy birthday to you ...
happy birthday to you ...
Happy birthday, dear Sonny ...
Happy birthday to you ...
You live in a zoo.
You smell like a monkey ...
and you look like one too.
Oh, god.
Look at this.
- Make a wish and then
blow out the candle.
Make a wish?
It's magic!
- It's magic. Did you do that?
Huh, monkey-face?
You trying to make a fool of your big brother?
Or it was you?
It was you?
Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
I love you.
- I love you, too.
I love you, mom.
- Oh, Sonny.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
It's very nice.
Look at them. They're pathetic animals.
They'd be better off, if you killed them.
Don't you think so?
Yes. You think so.
Hi. - Hi everybody. - Oh, hi Danielle. - Hello.
Hi, Sonny.
Happy birthday, Sonny. - Thank you. Hi.
- Happy birthday. - Thank you very much.
How're you doing?
Happy birthday.
Anthony, let me get you and Jody together.
- Hurry up, honey.
They're waiting for you down there.
- Wait, wait, wait. Oh, I missed it.
Everybody hungry?
- Yeah.
... it's great, I love it. It's wonderful ...
So? I'm ready.
I ran out of film. I have
to go get some more film.
Sonny, I'm here.
So what?
I thought you ... were calling me.
I changed my mind.
What's the matter with you?
Are you feeling guilty?
I'm not.
- Stop it!
You act like you hate me sometimes.
I'm confused.
Please, talk to me.
- Go away, damn bitch!
Don't you ever talk to me again!
I'm sorry. The number you ...
Please, Father answer me.
Answer me!
Oh, Father I know you're there.
I don't want to answer it.
Oh, good idea.
Hello?
Now ... let's hit the trail
Come on. Let's go.
Let's go.
I was just going to get some ice cubes.
What have you done with your brother?
Me?
What have you done?
Nothing! Mom!
Do you understand what you've done?
No.
No!
You must do it.
You must do it now.
Answer me. What is that?!
Answer me!
Don't you understand? Don't you see anything?
- What?! Spit it out, what's on your mind!
I don't ...
- You don't want to do it anymore?!
- Just, lets ...
Just, see it.
- Every time I touch you, you get sick.
What makes you sick? Come on, answer!
It's a shame!
What's a shame?!
Everything.
- Are you nuts?
Our family is shameful. Don't you understand?
- What's it got to do with our family!?
I just don't want to wake up anymore!
Let's go away.
Mommy!
Mommy.
No!
Mommy!
Mark.
Mark, hide.
Hide.
No! No!
What are you doing?
No! No.
Please.
I wouldn't tell anyone.
Oh, no!
Frank, wake up. You're having a dream.
You're having a dream.
Frank, what're you doing?
Frank?
Frank! Wait a minute. You're still asleep.
Frank, hold on a minute!
Would you at least tell me where
we're going? - Amityville.
Why?
Something horrible has happened.
Frank, you had a dream.
It might have had a powerful
effect on you, but it was just
a dream. - I pray to god you're right.
Did you see that?
Hi. I'm their priest.
He's with me.
Hold it, gentlemen.
Okay, let them in. He was their priest.
- Okay, Father.
Who are they?
Two parents and their kids.
I'm a priest.
It's okay.
Okay. You guys can take off.
You're too late.
Oh, Father. Please.
Don't touch those things.
It's a crime scene.
Everything's going to be all right.
Take it easy, kid.
I don't remember.
I don't. I don't remember.
Let's get him out of here.
And calm him down.
Okay Chief.
Lieutenant. He hasn't said a word.
He's still in shock.
What about the doctor?
- He's on his way.
May I go in now?
Lieutenant Turner,
take the Father in to see the boy.
Did you kill them, Sonny?
Sonny ...
Who is inside you?
In the name of the Father and the
Son and the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
It was Patricia on the phone that night.
She was trying to reach me.
I'm responsible.
You loved them, didn't you?
Do you hear me? Sonny.
Help me to help you.
The Lord is my Shepherd.
I shall not want.
He maketh me to lie down in green pastures.
He leadeth me beside the still waters.
He restoreth my soul.
He leadeth me...
No! No!
No!
Did he hurt you Father?
No.
Anyway, it's not his fault.
What do you mean, Father?
He can't help it.
He's dominated by ...
another force.
What force?
The boy is possessed.
I saw one once in Puerto Rico.
He was shouting ...
kicking ...
Show yourself.
Unclean spirit.
Kiss the crucifix.
And beg the Almighty for forgiveness.
I must take him to church.
That is impossible.
In church, I could succeed.
Please, understand.
Help me.
Are you asking me to let him go?!
It's the only way.
No, Father. You got three minutes
to talk to the boy.
That's all.
Officer.
I told you, you'd have to leave.
You want to destroy this boy's life?
I do what I want.
You must leave this boy's body,
which your foul presence occupies.
Why should I leave?
I like it here.
I will cast you out.
Oh ...
How?
With an exorcism.
You can't do that.
You're not authorized.
How do you know?
We know everything.
Is it your intention
not to show yourself again?
I could.
When?
When I please.
Father, what are you doing here?
Are you all right?
Can I give you a lift?
Yes.
Yes. Thank you.
I know some strange stories about that house.
I've been working here for 25 years.
- Here, let me help you.
Thank you.
At first I thought it would be very boring.
But these records are more
interesting than any novel.
A woman expelled from Salem for
witchcraft violated the Indians law against
building on an ancient burial ground.
Since then. It's been desecrated by people,
who have no right to live there.
Hello?
Who is this?
Father Adamsky?
Father?
I'm worried.
I'm worried about Sonny.
Afraid of him.
I don't know why, but ...
I think he wants to kill us.
Your honour its my attention to
prove to the trial that ...
Sonny Montelli is a victim of
demonic possession and therefore ...
- Of what Mr. Booth?
Demonic possession, your Honour.
Possession by demons?
And therefore innocent.
The charges placed against him.
- Your honour. This is highly irregular.
- Will Council, please approach the bench?
Your honour, there is no precedent ...
Mr. Booth ...
I admire your originality.
If I accept your plea,
regardless of verdict ...
Every courtroom in this country would be
in inundated with pleas of possession.
Nobody will be guilty of anything.
"The devil made them do it."
No, no, no, no, Mr. Booth.
I cannot accept your plea.
You have three days to submit another.
Father Adamsky?
The Chancellor would like to
have a word with you.
Monsignor, it's good to see you.
I've more to tell you about the Montelli case.
Wont you come in?
- Sorry. I'm in a hurry. But I want talk to you.
Who gave you permission to let the people
in the court of law believe that the church
was preparing to perform an exorcism?
You told me.
- I told you I was going to talk to the Bishop.
But you anticipated his decision
and put the church in a bad light.
Now, the Bishop is very worried about you.
He would like you to take a leave of absence.
- A leave of absence now?
- You are not listening to me!
I'm listening to my own conscience!
The facts, the sprinkler, the diabolical
influence in that house! You didn't listen.
Now I understand why all the
prisoners are complaining about him.
He's coming back.
I ask one thing.
Your authority to perform an exorcism
on Sonny Montelli.
- The Bishop does not think you are qualified.
Nor above all, have the correct steadiness
of character. - Too much prudence
could be cowards, Monsignor.
You are not only forgetting obedience.
You're forgetting humility as well!
Let me talk to the Bishop!
- The Bishop wants to talk to you!
But we'll tell you when!
Now you are to go home and remained there ...
Do not do anything on your own
initiative, and wait for our call.
God be with you, Father. Let's go, please.
How's the boy?
They're gonna try electroshock therapy again tomorrow.
- That's just torturing him.
- I'm sorry, Father. He's probably insane.
That's why I suggested we plea
insanity in the first place.
Let him in.
He won't eat anything.
He's dying.
Are you crazy?
They're taking the best care of him here.
I should call the doctor.
You understand, the only way we can
save him is by taking him out of here.
Look, let me get the doctor!
- That's pointless and you know it!
Now you're ...
a good man.
Don't ask me this, Father.
I could lose my job, I could go to jail.
- You want to let him die?
Father ...
this is the key to the door ...
of this ward.
When you got there, unlock the door.
Turn left.
You'll find the fire escape.
Take it.
Take it, Father.
The butt, right here.
Go on, Father, hit me,
before I change my mind.
Forgive me.
No.
Sonny.
Sonny?
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
- Yeah, that crazy priest pulled him out of here.
We know he's gone.
We got an APB out on him.
Yeah. Turner's fine, okay. Bye, bye.
Sonny?
Dear God.
Let your powerful strength ...
force the serpent ...
to release ...
your servant.
So it no longer possesses him ..
whom you deign to make
in your own image.
Sonny ...
if you can hear me ...
pray, my son.
Pray!
Fight the evil inside you.
"He who commands you"
"Is he who ordered you to be thrown
down from the highest heaven ...
into the depths
of hell."
"He who commands you ...
is he, who dominated the sea
and the winds and the storms."
"Fear ...
him who was crucified as a man.
and who rose from death."
Most unchased spirit, in the name of our
Almighty Lord, I command you to tell me who you are.
Tell me your name.
Your name.
Your name!
You know my name.
You know my name very well.
Father ...
Now, you must confess, mustn't you?
Look at me.
When I was making my confession,
you thought about making love to me.
Didn't you?
No.
Look at me!
Confess!
Dirty priest.
You wanted it.
You wanted it!
"Creator of Heaven and Earth you are the
true king. Your kingdom is without end."
"Humbly, I supplicate your majesty and
your glory that you deign to free ...
this your servant from unclean spirits!"
Prince of lies! ...
return to the depths of darkness!
I like you, Adamsky.
I understand you.
You want to dominate, like your Bishops.
And more.
I can give it to you, Adamsky.
Sonny ...
If you can hear me ...
resist the unclean spirit.
Will it ...
to leave your body.
You've decided to do this on your own.
Without the support of the church.
You are disobeying the church.
Now you are alone, Adamsky.
Flee ...
evil spirit.
Depart ...
from this servant of God.
- No!
Flee ...
evil spirit.
I command you.
In the name of God.
In the name of God!
Let it be me, my God.
Not him.
Let it be me!
My God, let it be me!
Take him away from here.
What about you?
Take him away, now!
Sonny ...
you come with me.
Come on.
It's all right, Sonny.
It's all right. Come on.
They'll understand it wasn't your fault.
We'll make them understand.
Blessed Lord, Lord of my life!
Do not forsake me!