AUTOMATIK
Mary, l need you to push.
Come on, Mary. Don앖 do this to yourself.
Just push. Come on.
l won앖 have this child!
Please, God. Please help her.
l have no god.
She압 arresting!
We need to get the baby out now.
- Prep for emergency C-section. Scalpel.
- Ma아m, step back.
- Prepare for incision.
- Please, you have to save her.
- How we doing on the mother?
- No improvement.
Please, God. Please help her.
She is only 1 8.
Okay, got the head.
Stand by on paddles.
l absolve you from your sins.
Clear.
- ln the name of the Father...
- Again.
...and of the Son...
Clear.
...and of the Holy Spirit.
By the grace of God.
Amen.
Come on.
Come on, let압 go!
l앐 late.
My God. l can앖 believe he went.
What압 in style?
Hey.
Sorry.
l앐 gonna miss you, honey.
l love you, Mom.
l앐 a phone call away.
Later, guys.
Seriously, l앐 going shopping.
Okay, Mom.
Excuse me.
- Hey, wait up.
- Lots of time.
Bless you.
Thanks.
What압 up? Jessica.
Grace.
- Nice to meet you, roomie.
- Heh, heh. You too.
Fuck me.
Um, what압 in the bottle?
Um... A little water,
a little vodka. Mostly vodka.
Want a swig?
Um...
No, thanks. Heh.
Suit yourself.
Yes.
Hello?
Grandma?
GRANDMA
Did you find your Bible?
I had to pack it for you.
l was going to, l just...
l...forgot.
Grace, you need to keep God
in your life.
That place is full of sin and sex.
lt압 not like that.
lf you came here, you would see.
I know exactly what it압 like.
Are you trying to hurt me?
Is that why you left?
No, it압 just l had
to move out eventually.
That압 exactly how it started
with your mother.
You are becoming more like her
every single day, do you know that?
l았e made up my mind.
Sorry.
What was that?
lt압 just my roommate. l should go.
No. We pray first.
Grace?
I pray, Lord,
Lord, that you enlighten my mind,
purify my heart and sanctify my soul.
Amen.
Don앖 forget to pray.
So, all that praying and shit,
what are you, like, super religious?
l suppose so.
Well, to each their own.
Where you going?
Wherever this takes me.
Hey, wait.
So was that your mom
on the phone earlier?
No, l live with my grandma.
Why was she being
such a tight-ass?
l don앖 know.
What? Mark.
- Jessica.
- What압 up, dude?
- My God. How you doing?
- Ha, ha. Long time.
- l didn앖 know you go to MSU.
- Yeah, of course.
This is my roommate, Michael.
Hey, Jessica.
This is my new roommate, Grace.
Hey.
Grace?
What압 up, Grace?
Hi, Grace. Michael.
- lt압 nice to meet you.
- Heh. You too.
lsn앖 this campus amazing?
Heh, yeah.
So, what are you
and your friend up to later?
L don앖 know.
Sigma Phi Delta,
theyre having this angels
and demons party. lt압 gonna be sweet.
Personally, l think you앇 make
a pretty sexy demon.
l았e been wondering if you could purr--
Shut up. Get out.
- Yeah. Where is it?
- You gotta come with us.
Yo, check this out.
Get in here.
Come on, let압 do it.
All you guys, all right.
- You gonna go?
- Yeah.
Nice to meet you, get in here.
We need one more person.
One more.
Umm...
- You. Come on in here.
- Me?
- Come on, come on.
- No, it압 okay.
- Youre gonna do awesome.
- What?
Youre gonna do awesome. Here you go.
Okay.
- l앐 on the wrong side.
- You ready?
l앐 ready. You ready?
l don앖 know.
What do l do?
Just tug as hard as you possibly can.
- Tug. Ready?
- Okay. No!
Come on, guys!
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on!
Come on. You can do better than that.
Come on.
Come on, guys. This is not--
Oof! Whoa!
That did not work.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
l앐 Brad, by the way.
Hi, l앐 Grace.
Nice to meet you.
Beer pong? Did l hear beer pong?
Wanna play?
Beer pong?
New girl, come on.
No. l앐 fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
lt압 not really her thing.
l앏l be your teammate.
Okay. All right. All right, well,
really nice to meet you, Grace.
Hope to see you around.
- Are you sure you don앖 wanna come?
- No, it압 fine.
Okay, all right.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Here압 your towel, bro.
- Who wants vodka?
Child.
Come on, man.
Bless me with your infinite graces
so that l may remain pure
and protect my soul
against daily struggles.
Defend me from the forces of evil,
and l am yours, forever and ever.
Amen.
What?
Grace. Grace.
Holy shit, wake up, dude.
What is wrong with you?
Sorry.
Jesus. Freaked me out.
What were you dreaming about?
Goddamn. Vodka.
What time is it?
Um... Ten-thirty.
No, no, no.
Why didn앖 my alarm go off?
l don앖 know.
- How앇 you get that?
- What?
L... l don앖 know.
l-- l앐 late for class. l gotta go.
Moods.
Who is that?
Well, so nice of you to fit us
into your busy schedule.
- l앐 sorry.
- Have a seat.
Who is that?
That압 Grace.
Take your time.
Now, we were talking about love.
- Hi.
lt seems to me that an awful lot of you
really believe in it.
Well, l hate to break it to you,
especially the ladies,
but love is merely a byproduct
of evolution.
And over the course of this term,
we앏l be learning about how
all of our behaviors when it comes
to sex, whether it be cheating
or jealousy, monogamy,
are all motivated by simple biology.
And we앏l get into that
over the course of this term.
Go long! Go long!
Yeah.
Yes.
My God. You did it.
That is awesome.
- Good job.
- Thanks.
We just won the game.
Nice shot. Dickhead.
Is that what you wanna play?
What? What? No.
My God. You are so disgusting.
How is that disgusting?
Next you앏l tell me you don앖 watch porn.
Yeah, of course l watch porn,
and, yeah, l masturbate,
but you hitting yourself in the face
with your own spunk,
l don앖 need to hear that.
lt압 not disgusting. Youre disgusting.
l앐 wounded.
Thank you.
lf l don앖 masturbate
once a week, l get anxious.
Once a week? Try twice a day.
Um, l앐 okay. Here.
That does not surprise me.
- What about you, Grace?
- What?
How often do you... You know?
Um...
lt압 gonna come out eventually.
l don앖 really do that.
Maybe she just doesn앖
wanna talk about it, guys. Drop it.
Like, ever?
You--
Yo, are you a virgin?
Dude, come on. Don앖 say that shit.
No, l앐 just-- l앐 just asking.
lt압 a legitimate question.
- Come on, youre just being rude.
- Yeah, come on.
- No, Grace.
- Don앖 listen to him. He압 an idiot.
No, it압 fine. l just have to
go to class. l앏l see you guys.
Grace.
l앐 sorry.
Yeah.
Stop it.
Grace. You made it.
Brad.
Nice to see you. How are you?
- Hey.
- So glad you made it.
- ls everything okay?
- Yeah.
No, l앐 fine.
You look great, by the way.
And l았e had a lot of these.
You need to catch up.
So l앐 taking this. Can l take this?
Thank you so much.
Okay. Ahem.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
- Cheers.
- Heh. Cheers.
Heh. You okay?
Yeah, it just--
lt kind of tastes like hay.
What? l thought all you small-town kids
drink your faces off, got shitfaced, no?
Hey, Brad.
Yeah, what압 up?
l am freezing my balls off out here,:
Yeah, it압 pretty cold.
Do you want to head inside?
Sure.
Yeah? Follow me, let압 go inside.
Okay.
Nice outfit.
Thanks.
L hope it압 okay
l borrowed some of your stuff.
Yeah, sure. Anytime.
Okay.
Ahem.
Okay, so it압 pretty insane in there,
so just follow me and it앏l all be good.
Okay.
Ready?
Yeah.
Let압 do it. Whoo!
Yeah!
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Nice.
Excuse me, coming through.
Coming through.
Excuse me.
- You into this kind of music?
- Yeah.
Yeah?
Here, l don앖 want you getting lost.
- Okay.
- Excuse me. Coming through.
Got a train going on, or something.
Nice.
l don앖 know. Whatever.
- Excuse me, bro. Cheers. Cheers.
- Cheers.
- Watch your step.
- Okay.
- Watch your head here too.
Joel, where are you?
Where are you? There you are.
Come get liquor in your system.
Okay.
That guy just threw up.
Me, you.
The little lady.
Whoa, whoa. lf you didn앖 like beer,
youre not gonna like that. Powerful shit.
- lt압 like gasoline.
- No, l can try it. Seriously.
Hey, thattagirl.
- Okay. All right.
- Bottoms up.
Cheers, cheers.
l spilled it on my chest.
You okay?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
All right!
Were good.
More.
Round two, bitches!
Round two.
My aim is so pro.
Round two. Ding, ding.
- Round two.
- Okay.
Cheers.
L love the poison.
Don앖 worry, were gonna turn you
into one of us in no time.
One of us, one of us, one of us.
Yes! l just have to go to
the bathroom, but can you wait here?
Sure. Yes, yes, yes, we can.
No. No--
- Yes.
- Thanks. Heh.
- Hey, Grace.
- Hi.
l just want to say
that l앐 really glad you came,
and l앐 just happy to have you here.
Thanks, me too.
All right, cool.
Three-thirty. Pardon me.
Pardon me.
Do you know where the bathroom is?
- Over there.
- Thanks.
Heh.
Wha--?
Brad?
Excuse me.
Hey. Come dance.
Crazy bitch.
Grace.
You see how easy that was?
What?
How l can just take him like that?
Why would you do that?
You steal my clothes,
you wear my makeup.
- l앐 sorry.
- And for what?
Youre still a child.
Nobody wants you.
Leave me alone.
Do you even know what it feels like
to be touched, little girl?
Just like your mother.
How do you know about my mom?
Another worthless...
l앐 not like my mother.
- ...ugly...
- Stop talking!
- ...child!
- Stop it!
No.
My God.
Grace!
Been looking everywhere for you.
What압 up?
- What압 up?
- l...
l didn앖 mean to do it.
Okay, do what? Youre freaking me out.
- What are you talking about? What?
- Jessica fell off the roof.
ls this some kind of a joke?
l don앖 understand.
- What?
- There압--
There압 no one there, Grace.
But l just saw her there.
Okay, all right.
But--
That압 fucked up for you to do.
Jesus.
Which one did l put my weed in?
- There she is.
- Jessica.
Hey, guys.
Whoa, are you okay?
Whoa, Grace, whoa!
How are you feeling?
Any pain?
What happened?
Were still trying to figure that out.
You lost consciousness.
Jessica. ls she okay?
Who?
The-- The girl that fell.
She--
Did you take anything?
Other than alcohol?
No.
You on any medication?
- Has this ever happened to you before?
- No.
What about family? Follow me.
What do you mean?
Any history of mental illness?
My mother was on antipsychotics.
What압 her condition like now?
She died.
How?
Giving birth to me.
And your father?
l-- l never knew him.
l앐 sorry.
Well, aside from a nasty bump
on the head, you appear to be fine.
But l should tell you
mental lllness is often hereditary.
Early diagnosis and treatment
are critical.
So l recommend you see
a psychiatrist as soon as you can.
You understand me?
Yes.
Good.
Wait, is there a phone l can use?
lf youre looking for your ride, we already
called your emergency contact.
Coming up,
we have a nasty stretch
of weather coming your way.
Break out the umbrellas
as it is going to be wet.
Did you have sex?
No.
Don앖 lie to me.
l앐 not lying.
And look at me when you answer.
Okay.
But you drank?
Yes.
Yes, of course.
l앐 sorry.
l think l need to see a doctor.
Grace. Why?
Because l앐 worried
l might be sick like Mom was.
Now압 not the time for making excuses.
l앐 not. The doctor told me--
l don앖 care what the doctor told you.
Your mother suffered
from sickness of the soul.
That is not something a doctor can fix.
Pull your skirt down.
There압 a jacket in the back,
and l want you to put it on.
l don앖 want them seeing you
in that clown suit.
Who?
Get in here.
Coffee압 ready.
Come on in, Grace.
Don앖 be rude, say hello.
Hello, Father John.
Have a seat.
You look more like your mother
every time l see you.
l guess so.
l want you to meet the newest member
of our congregation.
He comes to us
from St. James Seminary.
lt압 good to finally meet you, Grace.
You as well, Father.
Well, l앐 still a deacon.
But l plan on taking my vow
to priesthood very soon.
With Father John압 approval,
of course.
There you go, Father.
Yes.
Well, until he압 ready,
Luke will be assisting me
with those who need guidance.
Now that youre back, l expect you앏l be
spending more time with the church.
Um...
Actually, l앐 just gonna be here
for a few days,
and then l앐 gonna go back.
What?
Youre not going back.
Wh--? Wh--?
l pulled you out of school.
Why would you do that?
lt압 done, Grace.
But--
Not another word.
Home is where you need to be right now.
Don앖 you speak of it.
Understand? Not a word.
Hello?
Grandma?
Keep quiet.
Listen to yourself.
- Grace!
- Grandma.
You know to keep away from there.
Grandma, there압 somebody in there.
Ridiculous. Nobody압 been
in your mother압 room for years.
What?
Go back to your room.
No, but, Grandma,
l heard somebody in there.
Grace, now!
Grace.
You stay away from that room,
do you understand me?
Yes.
Come on, come on.
Pick up.
Is that Grace?
Give me that.
- Let me talk to her.
- Hang up.
Hello?
Grandma?
What?
Who are you?
Make him suffer.
Grace, you better be
getting ready in there.
- Grace, do you hear me?
- Yes.
- Do l look all right?
- Yeah.
Don앖 embarrass me today.
l won앖.
But really l앐 just excited
to wear the fancy robes.
Did Alicia tell you
were starting up a youth group?
L see.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Paul. Paul.
l have your favorite
Chocolate chip cookies.
No, no.
Margaret, Margaret.
Look at you.
You look beautiful.
Would you--?
Would you care for a sweet?
lt압 a little too early for cookies, dear.
Lt압 never too early for sweetness.
Um...
Where should l put these?
Grandma?
ls everything okay?
Give me those.
Let temptation into your heart
and the devil will destroy it!
We all feel it, every day.
Satan압 grasp, calling us,
asking us to betray God
for earthly pleasures.
The Bible teaches us to reject this call.
To ignore this temptation.
But who among us is without sin?
lt압 easy to convince yourself
that youre walking the righteous path.
That you have remained untainted.
Sin is like an open wound.
Left alone, it festers.
Spreads, grows before your very eyes.
That is why we must confront
our mistakes,
correct them.
Grace.
Stop it.
Restore the purity of our souls.
lt is the only way into heaven.
Let us pray.
The body of Christ.
What압 wrong with her?
Grace?
Grace.
You are in church. How dare you?
She압 so sorry.
Out. Out. Out.
l don앖 know
what has gotten into you.
ls this because l took you
out of school?
ls this some sick game youre playing
to hurt your grandmother?
No.
Well, then, what is the problem?
l았e-- l았e been hearing things.
There압 voices inside my head,
and l just...
l keep having these nightmares.
But they feel so real
and l앐 just a little scared
to fall asleep.
l need to know what happened
to my mother.
Don앖 start, Grace.
Everyone said she went crazy.
Drop it. l said drop it.
What if the same thing
is happening to me? l need help.
Your mother disobeyed me,
ran off and got pregnant.
You do not need help.
You need God.
Mama.
How did you get in there?
The-- The door was open.
No, it wasn앖.
l told you to stay away
from her room.
l앐-- l앐 sorry.
- What was that?
- What?
- That noise?
- Nothing.
- What do you have?
What압 behind your back?
Nothing.
You show it to me.
Leave me alone.
l앐 not gonna ask again.
Grace! Grace!
You show me what압 in there!
No!
Show me what압 in there.
Grace! You keep this up,
youre gonna be just like your mother.
- Leave me alone!
- Open this door!
Grace!
You stubborn, disobedient child!
You open this goddamn door right now!
You are a bastard child!
Did you know that? A bastard!
You should have never been born!
Your only father you ever had was God!
You are just as simple
as your goddamn mother!
l hate you! l hate you!
l hate you!
Morning, sunshine.
Brad?
What are you doing here?
Well, l came to see if you were all right.
l came to visit you.
l missed you.
l thought l앇 be back soon, but...
Well, l guess l couldn앖 wait, then.
You look great in the morning,
by the way. Heh, heh.
You think l look...?
l think you look beautiful.
This can앖 be real.
You can앖 be real.
lf l wasn앖 real,
would l be able to do this?
Would l be able to do this?
What are you doing?
Trust me.
My God.
Brad.
Brad, Brad, slow down,
slow down, slow down.
Brad. Stop!
Doesn앖 that feel good?
Grace?
My God.
l앐 sorry.
You need to learn
that what you did is wrong.
No! No! Grandma! Grandma, please!
Filthy! Filthy! Filthy!
- Turn over.
- Please stop!
Filth! Filthy! Filthy!
Filthy! Filthy! Filthy!
Grace?
Look at me, Grace.
lf you can앖 control yourself,
how are you going to stop men
from controlling you?
Your mother fought with me to leave
this church, look what happened.
She let some filthy stranger
Stranger?
open her up to sin
What?
and that is what
is gonna happen to you.
Here압 your stranger.
Grace. Grace, get back here!
You must understand,
the needs of the flesh are very real.
The trials of life,
you are gonna experience.
But in this room, we can talk about it
in, you know, a casual...
Grace. Hey.
l앐 so glad you came.
Come on, please join the circle.
Everybody, this is Grace.
Hey.
Hi, Grace.
Now, were talking a lot
about the pressures outside,
but what about inside?
The desires of the flesh.
Now, l know it압--
lt압 a tough conversation,
but sexual desires are real.
And remember,
it압 not temptation that압 the sin.
lt압 how you deal with the temptation.
Does anybody want to share?
Grace?
Anything you want to share?
- No.
- Okay, no pressure.
l want you to know
that whenever you feel like sharing,
this is a--
Really?
l heard that you were pretty busy
at school.
l thought that you앇 have lots to share.
- All right.
- What?
l only thought
maybe she could help us avoid
making the same mistakes
that she did.
Okay, Sally--
Or,
the same mistakes
as her mother.
- Aah!
- All right, that압 enough.
Get off me! Get off!
Youre crazy!
Youre just like your mother!
Grace, what are you doing?
Aah!
Father John?
- No.
- Grace.
What was that? Are you crazy?
l am crazy.
l앐 sorry.
l didn앖 mean it like that. l just...
You can앖 haul off and hit people, okay?
Stop. Calm down.
Youre gonna be fine.
l앐 here for you.
Do you really mean that?
Of course l do.
l think you have the wrong idea.
l-- l don앖 know why l did that.
Grace, calm down.
l앐 sorry.
Listen--
Grace.
Grace? Grace.
Grace, please, get in the car.
Grace, get in the car.
- Get away from me!
- Grace, get in the car.
Where are you going? Stop!
- Grace, l need to talk to you.
- Leave me alone!
Grace!
Made me filthy.
lt압 not real.
He made me filthy.
It won앖 come off.
Get out of my head.
lt won앖 come off.
He needs to be punished.
- He needs to be punished.
- What do you want?
What do you want from me? What?
What did he do to you?
Look what he did to me.
Just tell me.
Just tell me what happened, please.
You앏l see.
Youre hurting me.
Stop crying.
God forgive us. God forgive her.
Grace?
- Mama?
- Please.
- Help me, please.
- God forgive her.
God forgive her. God forgive her.
God forgive her.
- Please, help me.
- God forgive her.
- No. Mama?
God forgive her. God forgive her.
God forgive her.
- Let go!
- God forgive her.
Let me go.
Hello, Grandma.
Grace. Thank God.
l았e been looking everywhere for you.
Why are you wearing that?
Sweet girl.
L앐 sorry.
Don앖 cry.
Hello?
ls anybody there?
Grace.
Are you okay?
Can l come in, please?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, come. Come in.
ls Father John here?
l, l think he stepped out.
Hey, does your grandma know
youre here?
She was calling earlier.
l already talked to her.
Grace, look, what압 going on?
She told me not to come home,
says she doesn앖 want me anymore.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Stop, youre fine.
l shouldn앖 have come here. l앐 sorry.
Come on. Come sit down.
Look, let압 talk.
l know that you았e been under a lot
of pressure recently.
l았e just felt so
out of place, like l don앖 belong.
l think we can all feel like that
from time to time.
ln fact, l았e felt a little bit of that myself.
Well, l guess were not that different.
You know what it feels like to be alone.
Don앖 you?
Yeah.
l do.
Well, it압 very late.
Why don앖 we get you home?
lf l ask you something,
would you be honest with me?
Do you think l앐 beautiful?
Grace, l...
Of course, youre beautiful, but--
Would you love me if you could?
God can앖 always fill that void.
l cannot give you
what youre looking for.
Don앖 you want me?
Just once before taking the vow?
Please.
lt압 okay.
Please stop.
Nobody has to know.
Please.
You don앖 understand.
No, no.
Just take me.
No, l can앖.
l want you to.
Stop, l can앖.
You will.
Stop, stop.
lt압 all right.
God will forgive you.
Stop.
Devil! Leave her.
She압 coming to.
Bind her.
Grace?
Grace, wake up.
l recommend you keep your distance.
She압 awake.
Luke?
Grace.
Do not look at him.
You will answer to me only.
Who are you?
l앐 Bishop Michael,
and l앐 here to help you.
What?
Why am l tied down?
Show me the mark.
Luke? What--?
What are you doing? Stop it.
Please.
Why are you doing this?
Grace,
if this is in fact Grace
that l앐 speaking to,
the symbol you possess is a mark
of a dark servant, a demon.
What does that mean?
lt means you are losing possession
of your soul.
What?
What압 gonna happen to me?
Grace, the ritual youre about
to experience is very dangerous.
You must understand that l will do
everything in my power to save you.
What are you gonna do?
No, please, no.
l speak now directly to the evil
hiding in this body.
Reveal yourself.
But l am Grace.
Evil cannot hide in the house of God.
Please, please just let me go.
l feel better. l feel so much better.
- Please, please stop!
- That압 enough. Youre hurting her.
lt압 not Grace that l앐 hurting.
Please.
Brothers, we should begin the ritual,
as we았e discussed.
l didn앖 do anything wrong.
Please.
Youre hurting me.
See the cross of the Lord.
Be gone your hostile powers which have
assaulted this servant of God
and clouded her with terror.
l cast you out, unclean spirit,
along with every satanic power
of the enemy
every apparition from hell
and all your legion,
in the name of Jesus Christ.
The Lord be with you
and with your spirits.
For he himself commands you.
He who cast you from the heights
of heaven to the depths of hell.
No one commands me.
Tremble in fear, Satan.
Enemy of the faith.
Foe of the human race.
Begetter of death.
Depart, persecutor of the innocent.
Depart. For you are guilty
before almighty God.
Lord, hear our prayer.
Our cries come before you.
ln the name of the spotless lamb,
l adjure you, ancient serpents,
the judge of the living and the dead,
and your creator,
he who has the power
to resign you to darkness
that you depart posthaste.
Your soul is marked, priest.
You broke your vow.
Stop.
Silence, silence!
God has forsaken you.
Eternal suffering awaits you.
What have you done?
Hold her down!
Go, go.
Christ the Lord brings your plans
to nothing!
Fear him!
Crucified as man,
yet triumphed over the powers of hell.
You cannot run from your sins, priest.
You raped her mother,
abandoned her...
...and left a child for me to take.
Too long have you gone unpunished.
l am your retribution.
Do with me what you will.
l go to the hands of God.
Let압 see if he catches you!
Devil!
l command you to leave her.
You can free her,
but only through death!
l will not murder for you.
Very well.
Wait, stop.
Take me instead.
You give yourself willingly?
Only if you let her live.
Her soul for a priest압?
A worthy trade.
Luke?
Are you okay?
No, go away.
Wait.
l앐 sor-- sorry.
Please, please.
You have to go.
Go!
Father, were ready for you.
Hallelujah
ln the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
Let us pray.
Visit DanteG2  -  http://subscene.com/u/867995