Mary, I need you to push.
Come on, Mary. Don't do this
to yourself. Just push. Come on.
I won't have this child!
- Please, God. Please help her.
- I have no god.
She's arresting!
We need to get the baby out now.
- Prep for emergency C-section. Scalpel.
- Ma'am, step back.
- Prepare for incision.
- Please, you have to save her.
- How we doing on the mother?
- No improvement.
Please, God. Please help her.
She is only 18.
Okay, got the head.
Stand by on paddles.
I absolve you from your sins.
Clear.
- In the name of the Father...
- Again.
...and of the Son...
Clear.
...and of the Holy Spirit.
By the grace of God.
Amen.
Come on.
Come on, let's go!
I'm late.
My God. I can't believe he went.
What's in style?
Hey.
- Sorry.
- I'm gonna miss you, honey.
I love you, Mom.
I'm a phone call away.
Later, guys.
Seriously, I'm going shopping.
Okay, Mom.
Excuse me.
- Hey, wait up.
- Lots of time.
Bless you.
Thanks.
- What's up? Jessica.
- Grace.
- Nice to meet you, roomie.
- You too.
Fuck me.
What's in the bottle?
A little water, a little vodka.
Mostly vodka.
Want a swig?
No, thanks.
Suit yourself.
Yes.
Hello?
Grandma?
Did you find your Bible?
I had to pack it for you.
I was going to, I just...
I... forgot.
Grace, you need to
keep God in your life.
- That place is full of sin and sex.
- It's not like that.
- If you came here, you would see.
- I know exactly what it's like.
Are you trying to hurt me?
Is that why you left?
No, it's just I had to
move out eventually.
That's exactly how it
started with your mother.
You are becoming more like her
every single day, do you know that?
I've made up my mind.
Sorry.
- What was that?
- It's just my roommate. I should go.
No. We pray first.
Grace?
- I pray, Lord,
- Lord, that you enlighten my mind,
purify my heart and sanctify my soul.
- Amen.
Don't forget to pray.
So, all that praying and shit,
what are you, like, super religious?
I suppose so.
Well, to each their own.
Where you going?
Wherever this takes me.
Hey, wait.
So was that your mom
on the phone earlier?
No, I live with my grandma.
Why was she being such a tight-ass?
I don't know.
What? Mark.
- Jessica.
- What's up, dude?
- My God. How you doing?
- Long time.
- I didn't know you go to MSU.
- Yeah, of course.
- This is my roommate, Michael.
- Hey, Jessica.
This is my new roommate, Grace.
Hey. Grace?
- What's up, Grace?
- Hi, Grace. Michael.
- It's nice to meet you.
- You too.
- Isn't this campus amazing?
- Yeah.
So, what are you and
your friend up to later?
- I don't know.
- Sigma Phi Delta,
they're having this angels and
demons party. It's gonna be sweet.
Personally, I think you'd
make a pretty sexy demon.
- I've been wondering if you could purr...
- Shut up. Get out.
- Yeah. Where is it?
- You gotta come with us.
- Yo, check this out.
- Get in here.
Come on, let's do it.
All you guys, all right.
- You gonna go?
- Yeah.
- Nice to meet you, get in here.
- We need one more person.
One more.
- You. Come on in here.
- Me?
- Come on, come on.
- No, it's okay.
- You're gonna do awesome.
- What?
- You're gonna do awesome. Here you go.
- Okay.
- I'm on the wrong side.
- You ready?
- I'm ready. You ready?
- I don't know.
- What do I do?
- Just tug as hard as you possibly can.
- Tug. Ready?
- Okay. No!
Come on, guys!
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on!
Come on. You can do better than that.
Come on.
Come on, guys. This is not...
Oof! Whoa!
That did not work.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- I'm Brad, by the way.
- Hi, I'm Grace.
Nice to meet you.
Beer pong? Did I hear
beer pong? Wanna play?
- Beer pong?
- New girl, come on.
No. I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
It's not really her thing.
I'll be your teammate.
Okay. All right. All right, well,
really nice to meet you, Grace.
Hope to see you around.
- Are you sure you don't wanna come?
- No, it's fine.
Okay, all right.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Here's your towel, bro.
- Who wants vodka?
Child.
Come on, man.
Bless me with your infinite graces
so that I may remain pure
and protect my soul
against daily struggles.
Defend me from the forces of evil,
and I am yours, forever and ever.
Amen.
What?
Grace. Grace.
Holy shit, wake up, dude.
What is wrong with you?
Sorry.
Jesus. Freaked me out.
What were you dreaming about?
Goddamn. Vodka.
What time is it?
Ten-thirty.
No, no, no.
- Why didn't my alarm go off?
- I don't know.
- How'd you get that?
- What?
I... I don't know.
I... I'm late for class. I gotta go.
Moods.
Who is that?
Well, so nice of you to fit
us into your busy schedule.
- I'm sorry.
- Have a seat.
- Who is that?
- That's Grace.
Take your time.
Now, we were talking about love.
- Hi.
It seems to me that an awful
lot of you really believe in it.
Well, I hate to break it to you,
especially the ladies,
but love is merely a
byproduct of evolution.
And over the course of this term,
we'll be learning about how
all of our behaviors when it comes
to sex, whether it be cheating
or jealousy, monogamy, are all
motivated by simple biology.
And we'll get into that over
the course of this term.
Go long! Go long!
Yeah.
Yes.
My God. You did it. That is awesome.
- Good job.
- Thanks.
We just won the game.
Nice shot. Dickhead.
- Is that what you wanna play?
- What? What? No.
My God. You are so disgusting.
How is that disgusting? Next you'll
tell me you don't watch porn.
Yeah, of course I watch porn,
and, yeah, I masturbate,
but you hitting yourself in
the face with your own spunk,
I don't need to hear that.
It's not disgusting.
You're disgusting.
I'm wounded.
Thank you.
If I don't masturbate
once a week, I get anxious.
- Once a week? Try twice a day.
- I'm okay. Here.
That does not surprise me.
- What about you, Grace?
- What?
How often do you... You know?
It's gonna come out eventually.
I don't really do that.
Maybe she just doesn't wanna
talk about it, guys. Drop it.
Like, ever?
You...
Yo, are you a virgin?
Dude, come on. Don't say that shit.
No, I'm just... I'm just asking.
It's a legitimate question.
- Come on, you're just being rude.
- Yeah, come on.
- No, Grace.
- Don't listen to him. He's an idiot.
No, it's fine. I just have to
go to class. I'll see you guys.
Grace. I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Stop it.
Grace. You made it.
- Brad.
- Nice to see you. How are you?
- Hey.
- So glad you made it.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah.
- No, I'm fine.
- You look great, by the way.
And I've had a lot of these.
You need to catch up.
So I'm taking this. Can I take this?
Thank you so much.
Okay. Ahem.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
- Cheers.
You okay?
Yeah, it just...
It kind of tastes like hay.
What? I thought all you small-town kids
drink your faces off, got shitfaced, no?
- Hey, Brad.
- Yeah, what's up?
I am freezing my balls off out here.
Yeah, it's pretty cold.
Do you want to head inside?
- Sure.
- Yeah? Follow me, let's go inside.
- Okay.
- Nice outfit.
Thanks.
I hope it's okay I borrowed
some of your stuff.
Yeah, sure. Anytime.
Okay.
Okay, so it's pretty insane in there,
so just follow me and it'll all be good.
- Okay.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
- Let's do it. Whoo!
Yeah!
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Nice.
Excuse me, coming through.
Coming through.
Excuse me.
- You into this kind of music?
- Yeah.
Yeah? Here, I don't
want you getting lost.
- Okay.
- Excuse me. Coming through.
Got a train going on, or something.
Nice.
I don't know. Whatever.
- Excuse me, bro. Cheers. Cheers.
- Cheers.
- Watch your step.
- Okay.
- Watch your head here too.
Joel, where are you?
Where are you? There you are.
Come get liquor in your system.
Okay.
That guy just threw up.
Me, you.
The little lady.
Whoa, whoa. If you didn't like beer,
you're not gonna like that. Powerful shit.
- It's like gasoline.
- No, I can try it. Seriously.
Hey, thattagirl.
- Okay. All right.
- Bottoms up.
Cheers, cheers.
- I spilled it on my chest.
- You okay?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
All right! We're good.
More. More.
Round two, bitches!
Round two.
My aim is so pro.
Round two. Ding, ding.
- Round two.
- Okay.
- Cheers.
I love the poison.
Don't worry, we're gonna turn
you into one of us in no time.
One of us, one of us, one of us.
Yes! I just have to go to the
bathroom, but can you wait here?
- Sure. Yes, yes, yes, we can.
- No. No...
- Yes.
- Thanks.
- Hey, Grace.
- Hi.
I just want to say that
I'm really glad you came,
and I'm just happy to have you here.
- Thanks, me too.
- All right, cool.
Three-thirty.
Pardon me.
Do you know where the bathroom is?
- Over there.
- Thanks.
Wha...?
Brad?
Excuse me.
Hey. Come dance.
Crazy bitch.
Grace.
- You see how easy that was?
- What?
How I can just take him like that?
Why would you do that?
You steal my clothes,
you wear my makeup.
- I'm sorry.
- And for what?
You're still a child.
Nobody wants you.
Leave me alone.
Do you even know what it feels
like to be touched, little girl?
- Just like your mother.
- How do you know about my mom?
- Another worthless...
- I'm not like my mother.
- ...ugly...
- Stop talking!
- ...child!
- Stop it!
No.
My God.
Grace! Been looking
everywhere for you.
What's up?
- What's up?
- I...
- I didn't mean to do it.
- Okay, do what? You're freaking me out.
- What are you talking about? What?
- Jessica fell off the roof.
Is this some kind of a joke?
I don't understand.
- What?
- There's...
There's no one there, Grace.
But I just saw her there.
Okay, all right.
- But...
- That's fucked up for you to do.
Jesus.
Which one did I put my weed in?
- There she is.
- Jessica.
Hey, guys.
Whoa, are you okay?
Whoa, Grace, whoa!
How are you feeling?
Any pain?
- What happened?
- We're still trying to figure that out.
You lost consciousness.
Jessica. Is she okay?
- Who?
- The... The girl that fell.
She...
Did you take anything?
Other than alcohol?
No.
- You on any medication?
- No.
- Has this ever happened to you before?
What about family? Follow me.
What do you mean?
Any history of mental illness?
My mother was on antipsychotics.
What's her condition like now?
She died.
How?
- Giving birth to me.
- And your father?
I... I never knew him.
I'm sorry.
Well, aside from a nasty bump on
the head, you appear to be fine.
But I should tell you mental
illness is often hereditary.
Early diagnosis and
treatment are critical.
So I recommend you see a
psychiatrist as soon as you can.
You understand me?
- Yes.
- Good.
Wait, is there a phone I can use?
If you're looking for your ride, we
already called your emergency contact.
Coming up,
we have a nasty stretch of
weather coming your way.
Break out the umbrellas
as it is going to be wet.
Did you have sex?
No.
Don't lie to me.
- I'm not lying.
- And look at me when you answer.
I'm not lying.
Okay.
But you drank?
- Yes.
- Yes, of course.
I'm sorry.
I think I need to see a doctor.
Grace. Why?
Because I'm worried I might
be sick like Mom was.
Now's not the time
for making excuses.
- I'm not. The doctor told me...
- I don't care what the doctor told you.
Your mother suffered from
sickness of the soul.
That is not something
a doctor can fix.
Pull your skirt down.
There's a jacket in the back,
and I want you to put it on.
I don't want them seeing
you in that clown suit.
Who?
Get in here.
Coffee's ready.
Come on in, Grace.
Don't be rude, say hello.
Hello, Father John.
Have a seat.
You look more like your
mother every time I see you.
I guess so.
I want you to meet the newest
member of our congregation.
He comes to us from
St. James Seminary.
- It's good to finally meet you, Grace.
- You as well, Father.
Well, I'm still a deacon.
But I plan on taking my vow
to priesthood very soon.
With Father John's
approval, of course.
There you go, Father.
Yes.
Well, until he's ready,
Luke will be assisting me
with those who need guidance.
Now that you're back, I expect you'll
be spending more time with the church.
Actually, I'm just gonna be
here for a few days, Father,
and then I'm gonna go back.
What?
You're not going back.
Wh...? Wh...?
I pulled you out of school.
- Why would you do that?
- It's done, Grace.
- But...
- Not another word.
Home is where you
need to be right now.
Don't you speak of it.
Understand? Not a word.
Hello?
Grandma?
Keep quiet.
Listen to yourself.
- Grace!
- Grandma.
You know to keep away from there.
Grandma, there's somebody in there.
Ridiculous. Nobody's been in
your mother's room for years.
- What?
- Go back to your room.
No, but, Grandma,
I heard somebody in there.
Grace, now!
Grace.
You stay away from that room,
do you understand me?
Yes.
Come on, come on.
Pick up.
Is that Grace?
Give me that.
- Let me talk to her.
- Hang up.
Hello?
Grandma?
What?
Who are you?
Make him suffer.
Grace, you better be
getting ready in there.
- Grace, do you hear me?
- Yes.
- Do I look all right?
- Yeah.
- Don't embarrass me today.
- I won't.
But really I'm just excited
to wear the fancy robes.
Did Alicia tell you we're
starting up a youth group?
I see.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Paul. Paul.
I have your favorite
- chocolate chip cookies.
- No, no.
Margaret, Margaret. Look at you.
You look beautiful.
Would you...?
Would you care for a sweet?
It's a little too early
for cookies, dear.
It's never too early for sweetness.
Where should I put these?
Grandma?
Is everything okay?
Give me those.
Let temptation into your heart
and the devil will destroy it!
We all feel it, every day.
Satan's grasp, calling us,
asking us to betray God
for earthly pleasures.
The Bible teaches
us to reject this call.
To ignore this temptation.
But who among us is without sin?
It's easy to convince yourself that
you're walking the righteous path.
That you have remained untainted.
Sin is like an open wound.
Left alone, it festers.
Spreads, grows before your very eyes.
That is why we must
confront our mistakes,
correct them.
Grace.
Stop it.
Restore the purity of our souls.
It is the only way into heaven.
Let us pray.
- The body of Christ.
What's wrong with her?
- Grace?
- Grace.
You are in church. How dare you?
She's so sorry.
Out. Out. Out.
I don't know what
has gotten into you.
Is this because I took
you out of school?
Is this some sick game you're
playing to hurt your grandmother?
- No.
- Well, then, what is the problem?
I've... I've been hearing things.
There's voices inside
my head, and I just...
I keep having these nightmares.
But they feel so real
and I'm just a little
scared to fall asleep.
I need to know what
happened to my mother.
Don't start, Grace.
- Everyone said she went crazy.
- Drop it. I said drop it.
What if the same thing is
happening to me? I need help.
Your mother disobeyed me,
ran off and got pregnant.
You do not need help.
You need God.
Mama.
How did you get in there?
The... The door was open.
No, it wasn't.
I told you to stay
away from her room.
I'm... I'm sorry.
- What was that?
- What?
- That noise?
- Nothing.
- What do you have?
- What's behind your back?
- Nothing.
You show it to me.
- Leave me alone.
- I'm not gonna ask again.
Grace! Grace!
You show me what's in there!
- No!
- Show me what's in there.
Grace! You keep this up,
you're gonna be just
like your mother.
- Leave me alone!
- Open this door!
Grace! You stubborn,
disobedient child!
You open this goddamn door right now!
You are a bastard child!
Did you know that? A bastard!
You should have never been born!
Your only father you
ever had was God!
You are just as simple
as your goddamn mother!
I hate you! I hate you!
I hate you!
Morning, sunshine.
Brad?
What are you doing here?
Well, I came to see
if you were all right.
I came to visit you.
I missed you.
I thought I'd be back soon, but...
Well, I guess I couldn't wait, then.
You look great in the morning,
by the way.
You think I look...?
I think you look beautiful.
This can't be real.
You can't be real.
If I wasn't real,
would I be able to do this?
Would I be able to do this?
What are you doing?
Trust me.
My God.
Brad.
Brad, Brad, slow down,
slow down, slow down.
Brad. Stop!
Doesn't that feel good?
Grace?
My God.
I'm sorry.
You need to learn that
what you did is wrong.
No! No! Grandma! Grandma, please!
Filthy! Filthy! Filthy!
- Turn over.
- Please stop!
Filth! Filthy! Filthy!
Filthy! Filthy! Filthy!
Grace? Look at me, Grace.
If you can't control yourself,
how are you going to stop
men from controlling you?
Your mother fought with me to leave
this church, look what happened to her.
- She let some filthy stranger.
- Stranger?
- open her up to sin
- What?
...and that is what is
gonna happen to you.
Here's your stranger.
Grace. Grace, get back here!
You must understand, the needs
of the flesh are very real.
The trials of life,
you are gonna experience.
But in this room, we can talk about
it in, you know, a casual...
Grace. Hey.
I'm so glad you came.
Come on, please join the circle.
Everybody, this is Grace.
- Hey.
- Hi, Grace.
Now, we're talking a lot
about the pressures outside,
but what about inside?
The desires of the flesh.
Now, I know it's...
It's a tough conversation,
but sexual desires are real.
And remember, it's not
temptation that's the sin.
It's how you deal
with the temptation.
Does anybody want to share?
Grace?
Anything you want to share?
- No.
- Okay, no pressure.
I want you to know that whenever
you do feel like sharing,
- this is a...
- Really?
I heard that you were
pretty busy at school.
I thought that you'd
have lots to share.
- All right.
- What?
I only thought maybe
she could help us avoid
making the same
mistakes that she did.
- Okay, Sally...
- Or,
the same mistakes as her mother.
All right, that's enough.
Get off me! Get off!
You're crazy!
You're just like your mother!
Grace, what are you doing?
Father John?
- No.
- Grace.
What was that? Are you crazy?
I am crazy.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean
it like that. I just...
You can't haul off
and hit people, okay?
Stop. Calm down.
You're gonna be fine.
I'm here for you.
- Do you really mean that?
- Of course I do.
I think you have the wrong idea.
I... I don't know why I did that.
- Grace, calm down.
- I'm sorry.
- Listen...
Grace.
Grace? Grace. Grace,
please, get in the car.
Grace, get in the car.
- Get away from me!
- Grace, get in the car.
Where are you going? Stop!
- Grace, I need to talk to you.
- Leave me alone!
Grace!
Made me filthy.
- It's not real.
- He made me filthy.
He made me filthy.
It won't come off.
- Get out of my head.
- It won't come off.
He needs to be punished.
- He needs to be punished.
- What do you want?
What do you want from me?
What? What did he do to you?
Look what he did to me.
Just tell me. Just tell
me what happened, please.
You'll see.
- You're hurting me.
- Stop crying.
God forgive us. God forgive her.
Grace?
- Mama?
- Please.
- Help me, please.
- God forgive her.
God forgive her. God forgive her.
God forgive her.
- Please, help me.
- God forgive her.
- No. Mama?
God forgive her. God forgive her.
God forgive her.
- Let go!
- God forgive her.
Let me go.
Hello, Grandma.
Grace. Thank God.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Why are you wearing that?
Sweet girl.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
Hello?
Is anybody there?
Grace. Are you okay?
Can I come in, please?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, come. Come in.
Is Father John here?
I, I think he stepped out.
Hey, does your grandma
know you're here?
She was calling earlier.
I already talked to her.
Grace, look, what's going on?
She told me not to come home,
says she doesn't want me anymore.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Stop, you're fine.
I shouldn't have
come here. I'm sorry.
Come on. Come sit down.
Look, let's talk.
I know that you've been under
a lot of pressure recently.
I've just felt so out of place,
like I don't belong.
I think we can all feel like
that from time to time.
In fact, I've felt a
little bit of that myself.
Well, I guess we're
not that different.
You know what it
feels like to be alone.
Don't you?
Yeah.
I do.
Well, it's very late.
Why don't we get you home?
If I ask you something,
would you be honest with me?
Do you think I'm beautiful?
Grace, I...
Of course, you're beautiful, but...
Would you love me if you could?
God can't always fill that void.
I cannot give you what
you're looking for.
Don't you want me?
Just once before taking the vow?
Please.
- It's okay.
- Please stop.
- Nobody has to know.
- Please.
You don't understand.
No, no.
- Just take me.
- No, I can't.
- I want you to.
- Stop, I can't.
You will.
- Stop, stop.
- It's all right.
God will forgive you.
- Stop.
- Devil! Leave her.
She's coming to.
Bind her.
Grace?
Grace, wake up.
I recommend you keep your distance.
She's awake.
- Luke?
- Grace.
Do not look at him.
You will answer to me only.
Who are you?
I'm Bishop Michael,
and I'm here to help you.
What?
Why am I tied down?
Show me the mark.
Luke? What...?
What are you doing? Stop it.
Please.
Why are you doing this?
Grace,
if this is in fact Grace
that I'm speaking to,
the symbol you possess is a mark
of a dark servant, a demon.
What does that mean?
It means you are losing
possession of your soul.
What?
What's gonna happen to me?
Grace, the ritual you're about
to experience is very dangerous.
You must understand that I will do
everything in my power to save you.
What are you gonna do?
No, please, no.
I speak now directly to
the evil hiding in this body.
- Reveal yourself.
- But I am Grace.
Evil cannot hide in the house of God.
Please, please just let me go.
I feel better. I feel so much better.
- Please, please stop!
- That's enough. You're hurting her.
It's not Grace that I'm hurting.
Please.
Brothers, we should begin
the ritual, as we've discussed.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Please.
You're hurting me.
See the cross of the Lord.
Be gone your hostile powers which
have assaulted this servant of God
and clouded her with terror.
I cast you out, unclean spirit,
along with every satanic
power of the enemy
every apparition from
hell and all your legion,
in the name of Jesus Christ.
The Lord be with you
and with your spirits.
For he himself commands you.
He who cast you from the heights
of heaven to the depths of hell.
No one commands me.
Tremble in fear, Satan.
Enemy of the faith.
Foe of the human race.
Begetter of death.
Depart, persecutor of the innocent.
Depart. For you are guilty
before almighty God.
Lord, hear our prayer.
Our cries come before you.
In the name of the spotless lamb,
I adjure you, ancient serpents,
the judge of the living and
the dead, and your creator,
he who has the power to
resign you to darkness
that you depart posthaste.
Your soul is marked, priest.
- You broke your vow.
- Stop.
- Silence, silence!
- God has forsaken you.
Eternal suffering awaits you.
What have you done?
Hold her down!
Go, go.
Christ the Lord brings
your plans to nothing!
Fear him!
Crucified as man, yet triumphed
over the powers of hell.
You cannot run from
your sins, priest.
You raped her mother,
abandoned her...
and left a child for me to take.
Too long have you gone unpunished.
I am your retribution.
Do with me what you will.
I go to the hands of God.
Let's see if he catches you!
Devil! I command you to leave her.
You can free her,
but only through death!
I will not murder for you.
Very well.
Wait, stop.
Take me instead.
You give yourself willingly?
Only if you let her live.
Her soul for a priest's?
A worthy trade.
Luke?
Are you okay?
No, go away.
Wait.
I'm sor... sorry.
Please, please.
You have to go.
Go!
Father, we're ready for you.
Hallelujah
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
Let us pray.