DEADLY RUN
Brussels, late summer...
No, Madeleine...
This time I'm warm.
I think I know which one she is...
I'm sure of it.
- You listening?
- Hurry, my bath's running.
She's the one with the sad look.
Upper left.
Marie had that look. She was a
cheerful child, but often seemed sad.
- The opposite of me.
- In all respects.
- Did I guess right?
- Wrong.
Wait...
She's the third from the right...
with the barrette.
She has your nose.
Your nose exactly...
Madeleine, answer me!
- I can't.
- Why not?
You know you only get one guess.
- No second chance?
- Sure. Next year.
OK, Madeleine.
While I've got you...
"Abundance of bread"... in 8 letters.
- Opulence?
- It fits. You're a genius!
When you put your mind to it.
- How is she?
- That's going too far!
Bitch!
And I almost jumped
out a window for her!
It was November... bitter cold...
Madeleine stopped me.
Whereas that idiot Taruchi...
I saw his hammer just in time...
He saw nothing.
Really dumb.
I fired through my pocket.
So now I've missed
two perfect chances to die...
Some day...
I'll die of sorrow in bed...
like all fathers.
Opulence...
Marie was born in 1953,
the year Stalin died.
I'd married Madeleine in 1952...
The year of the "H" bomb.
The "H" atoll. 6 letters: Bikini.
They left me in 1954...
the year of the cold war.
I got the photo in 1961.
Nothing happened that year.
Except the photo...
At first, I picked the girl
with the barrette...
"You're wrong," Madeleine said.
Then I decided, she was
the little imp smiling at the camera.
"Wrong again," said Madeleine.
Now I love them all...
They're all my little Marie.
I dread disappointing them.
Because I will...
the day I open the door,
and enter the photo...
and Marie comes to me...
Be patient, Marie.
Wait for me...
Where were you?
Doing crosswords?
No, sewing, Mrs. Schmidt-Boulanger...
A loose button.
"The Eye!" My best agent.
The underworld
nicknamed him "The Eye."
Mr. and Mrs. Hugo.
- The name mean anything to you?
- I should hope so.
The celebrated boot makers.
- Established in Brussels since...?
- Since forever!
Mr. and Mrs. Hugo have a son...
- Paul.
- Let's be brief.
It seems Paul has a girlfriend.
A French girl.
Mr. and Mrs. Hugo would like
some information about her.
- You follow me?
- What?
She phoned the house
several times...
Or we wouldn't have known
the young lady existed.
How do you know she's young?
Hugo Jr. is 23.
We'll have no trouble
finding out who she is.
The Hugo’s want a quick report.
- Can you do that?
- Sure.
Can we meet tomorrow,
same time?
- I'll see you out.
- No need.
- I insist...
- We're really grateful.
The cashier is down the hall
to the left.
See you tomorrow.
To the left! The cashier's office...
I hope you got the picture.
Absolutely, madam.
College boy meets hooker,
parents panic, fat fees for you!
- Simple, no?
- Keep it that way.
- Where will you begin?
- By sewing on my button.
That's a woman's job.
I dare you!
The Taruchi case was simple
until you complicated it.
Taruchi was a small-time
blackmailer... a petty crook.
A crook with a hammer
in his hand isn't petty!
That hammer was found
in Taruchi's pocket...
so don't try to snow me.
You wanted it in my skull?
You disappoint me!
I expected a little gratitude.
I got you off the blacklist.
Now I'm giving you a new case...
restoring your dignity!
- I'm generous!
- Very.
I warn you... One more foul-up...
and you'll sweep floors
till you retire.
When I'm 65, Marie will be 39.
Too late for celebrations.
Have I really put on weight?
Around the ass...
and even so... not much.
But you'll always have
pretty hands.
You'll always have a pretty face...
a pretty fur coat...
and a pretty blue car.
What's my car got to do with it?
Just talking.
Hugo And Co. Founded 1802...
Like the great French writer,
in 4 letters.
The illustrious shoemakers...
Outlets on 5th Avenue,
Via Venetto.
Exclusive suppliers to the
national jumping team.
Mr. Paul will sell everything.
Absolutely everything,
to the last shoehorn.
In order to take wenches sailing
on expensive waters.
The Adriatic sea, for instance.
It's an extremely fashionable sea.
His open collar and his cashmere
sweater are to his credit.
Rather handsome and easy going.
If he gets off the highway
in Morteau, I’ll kill him.
70... 80...
90...
100...
A tidy sum.
We'll walk in parks
as we used to, Marie.
Botanical gardens...
I'll teach you the
Latin names of roses.
Shit!
Who has the right
to separate a man and his daughter?
- You like talking to yourself?
- Not really.
I'm waiting for my dad.
Looking for your son?
My little girl.
My dad's an engineer.
When I'm big,
I want to own a dodgem.
Who decides of the kids’ fate?
Who says: You’ll compose a symphony?
You’ll be a typist?
And you a fighter pilot?
You a son of a bitch?
What about you?
What will you be later?
I’ll be a private detective.
Want to take a picture?
OK.
At last!
Who gave you that?
- That man.
- Give it right back to him!
Well, bye-bye!
- Lucie!
- Sorry!
Lucie Brentano...
born Sept. 22, 1962.
Student... no distinguishing traits.
Address:
33 rue Champollion, Paris...
September 22...
Virgo...
The sign of gentleness.
"Dear Schmidt-Boulanger...
"The lady is named
Lucie Brentano.
"She likes peace and quiet.
"Smokes 'Senior Service'...
"and screws singing 'La Paloma. "'
Capricorn... symbol of winter...
Lucie Brentano, student...
Blue eyes... Straight nose...
Distinguishing trait:
Killed a man last night.
- Have a good trip?
- Excellent.
- Put it in the safe.
- Certainly.
Hello, Voragine.
So you're out of the closet.
To kill whom this time?
Know the brunette
at the front desk?
Eve Granger... model.
You see her occasionally.
Not much baggage, no men.
How's Schmidt-Boulanger?
- Spreading out?
- It's prosperity.
Can you get me
on a flight to Nice this evening?
The 6:45 would suit me.
Flight 417 to Nice.
Of course, miss.
"Paul Hugo's fish bait,
Mrs. Schmidt-Boulanger..."
No, If I tell her that,
she'll call the cops.
So I'll say...
Paul and Lucie
went to Reno to marry.
That's no good either.
Paul left alone...
By plane, alone... Montreal...
Air Canada... First class.
His tramp ditched him.
Not if he just took
all his cash out of the bank.
Very well. So get moving.
Get me a ticket to Montreal with
an open return. It's for "The Eye."
- What?
- Money, money.
Get 400 francs ready.
- 800...
- 450! And get a receipt!
Hooker or no,
why'd he dump her?
- Jealous.
- A rival?
Let's just say, another man.
A father.
As I understand it,
the girl's mother was a nothing.
She was raised by her father,
a superior type of man.
She's always bragging about him.
Paul must have felt
unable to compete.
- So he fled.
- How'd you learn all this?
Use a mike?
No my dear, I haven't always
been called "The Eye."
They used to call me "The Ear."
Your dumb daughter is here.
Try to recognize her. Good luck.
She has lilac eyes...
she killed a man,
she looks like a kid...
- and she eats pears.
- Beg pardon?
"To blind," in 6 letters.
- Dazzle?
- Too easy.
Departure of Flight 417 for Nice.
Boarding now...
Capricorns, luck is still with you.
If you plan to travel,
now would be a good time.
Michel! Michel, darling!
I thought you didn’t wait for me!
- I was scared!
- Scared?
More sorry than scared.
I thought you'd forgotten me.
80 people expect you
in Monte Carlo, Dorothee.
Dorothee! It's crazy!
Dorothee who?
Beg pardon?
"To blind," in 6 letters.
It's not "dazzle."
"Betray."
You're all golden. Sunbathing?
I've been sailing.
I wonder what Felix
will give his future daughter-in-law.
- I'm the aunt from Vittel.
- I'm the Paris cousin.
Cousin on the girl’s side,
of course.
The last of the Orthiz?
- Himself.
Dorothee, in the name of the family...
and of all the Meyerganzes...
allow me to present you with this.
They're only emeralds.
Sanseveria... Asplenium Nidus...
Asparagus plumosis...
- ... and one mink coat!
- Mink!
Emeralds!
You're nice to be with, Michel.
Now that you're warm,
are you hungry?
- I want to screw.
- Can't think of everything.
Dorothee Orthiz, just about to indulge
in an imperial engagement night.
But Lucie Brentano gets her
kicks in the shoe business.
Problem. Splash.
No more problem.
We're clearing away.
Would you like something?
No, thank you.
- No problem, right?
- We all have problems.
More or less.
Dorothee! Michel! Where are you?
- Have you seen the kids?
- I was looking for them.
If you ask me they must have...
how to put it? Eloped!
They’re young enough for that.
- Is Miss Granger back?
- Miss Granger?
I mean, Miss Orthiz.
Yes, she is back.
Would you care to call her?
No, she may be sleeping.
Thanks.
I’m sure it’s her.
Her name is Doris Fleming.
She stole a boyfriend
from me once.
They went to Morocco
and he never was heard of again.
Come in!
She could have put on a robe,
don't you think?
We are flying at an altitude
of 25,000 feet.
And on our right,
we can see The Black Forest.
She's killed 2 men...
eats pears, reads Shakespeare:
Active, voracious, cultivated.
Don't get excited, boss.
It's long-distance
and you're paying for it, so listen.
- Where are you? Montreal?
- Marrakesh.
- What!
- I don't set the itinerary.
Paul Hugo is the kind of guy
who flirts incessantly.
First Montreal, now Morocco.
- And tomorrow?
- Home!
Bring that clown back
before his parents call in the cops.
My darling little daughter.
I put a cross so you’ll know
where your Daddy lives.
I do think a lot about you.
Are you writing to Marie?
Yes. The little one can barely
take our separations,
but then, her mother has
to see her sometimes.
You should send them a picture
of you in your djellaba.
It really suits you.
- Yes, yes, thank you.
Have you read the horoscope?
It’s excellent.
As you can see,
I’m taking up your bad habits.
Capricorns:
avoid useless agitation;
things are coming to meet you.
You’ll meet new people
and become really popular.
Love, love, love...
P.S. Beware!
The forces of evil
crawl like spiders towards you.
See you tonight, my friend.
Stop following me!
I'm not!
We always seem to go
the same way.
Hey, Ariane!
We have a date tonight.
Don't forget.
Bet 200 francs you'll sleep
with one of those idiots.
Not likely.
When you get horny,
come sleep with me.
My name is Cora. I'm in 317.
I’d like to change rooms. I’m just
next door to a couple of newlyweds
who wail like wild animals,
and I can’t sleep a wink.
Don’t you have anything
around the number 300?
Number 308 is free
and 320 soon will be too.
- What about 316?
- We never offer it.
It’s an emergency room,
with a mere shower.
I love them. I love showers.
My father is an anthropologist.
He even went up the Nile...
God knows how far.
Another time he went
to the North Cape.
He sent me a postcard
from the Lofoten Islands.
I wonder where he is now.
What are you talking about?
- About my father.
- Who cares about him?
- You mustn't be home much.
- Unfortunately.
My wife always wanted me
to take a sedentary job...
Teacher, or some such.
But when the Nile obsesses you...
We had some painful scenes.
Just before a voyage
to the North Cape...
Madeleine threatened to jump
out of a window..
- "Go ahead, do it," I said.
- My God!
Blackmail.
Excuse me now...
it's time to take the waters.
See you tonight.
What a farce!
You were amoral.
Now you're boring, Jerry.
- I'm not answerable to anyone.
- Of course not.
I'm simply warning you:
Cora's a bitch.
Lays girls, but hates 'em.
When she's through with you...
she'll dump you.
You talk about her
as if she were a guy.
- Talking of me?
- Yes.
- Was it amusing?
- Rather.
What'd he say? That I'm a nympho?
Paranoid? Manic-something?
A bitch!
Funny: Roman whores took milk baths.
Today's use Clorox.
No wonder the streams are polluted.
Don't touch that! Makes me nervous.
Stop biting your nails. It's tacky.
Here's your ticket to Brussels,
Miss Chevallier.
A single with dining car.
- Your taxi will be here at 8:00 p.m.
- Thank you.
Please get my bill ready.
So? This is the big night!
You’re going to pick up
Marie at the station?
Yes. At 11:57 PM.
- Here.
You’ll give this to her.
It’s nothing, really. I did it to
pass the time. I hope she’ll like it.
Thank you.
It’s... It’s pretty.
Do you know what?
Somebody stole my necklace!
Stole, stole!
You probably lost them at the
Roman Baths. Or in the shower.
You’re always flaunting
those rocks of yours.
Stop it! Can’t you see
I’m really upset?
Don’t get upset. We’re going.
Really, this is...
You’ve got a heart,
well done.
Things could have
been different, Jerry.
I mean: a little better.
Too late, unfortunately:
I’m going back to Brussels.
- I’m going back to Brussels.
- Excuse me, my cab is waiting.
Let him wait,
your luggage is in my car.
What?
Can’t he mind his own business?
What a sod!
You were right after all:
she’s a monster.
She dumped me just like that.
Hello, madam,
did you have a nice trip?
- Excellent.
- Keeping your room for the week?
Probably.
Could you give me the envelope
I put in the safe?
I'll come with you.
Hello "The Eye!" Still on her tail?
She just arrived.
- I heard you were in Montreal.
- In Marrakesh.
I was in Marrakesh.
- Is it nice there?
- Ask Flatfoot.
You've had many calls.
One person came by twice.
I've thought about it.
I don't want my room.
Very well, madam.
She's really got you running.
No time to put your bag down.
I'll put it down one day, Voragine.
That day, I'll push
the classroom door...
Let me go! Let me go,
or I'll break your arm!
- Keep the change.
- Change? You must be mistaken.
You've given me 100.
Scumbag. It's 1,000.
Pardon me.
It must be my mistake.
That's all right. Keep it anyway.
This happens all the time,
but it doesn't really matter.
It's deplorable.
It's quite deplorable,
but it doesn't really matter.
What's the book?
I heard you turning pages.
Hamlet.
It's hard to make actors say:
"To be or not to be."
Or... "Murder...
"though it have no tongue...
"will speak with most
miraculous organ."
Do you know the
recording of "La Paloma"
by Hans Albert, in the 30s?
- No.
- That’s too bad.
What time is it?
I can hear pages,
but not the hands on a watch.
11:50 p.m.
The Rome train
leaves in 15 minutes.
I'm going to Rome, too.
Capricorns. If you intend to travel,
jump on the opportunity.
Now is the time.
Train suits you better than plane.
Have a nice trip.
What if I said I was brunette,
had black eyes...
and smoked "Marlboros?"
Fine, but I wouldn't believe you.
You're blond, blue eyed...
and smoke "Players."
"Senior Service."
And you won't take off your coat.
Been thinking about my coat?
Constantly.
My antenna tells me everything.
That's why I don't need
a white cane.
I can foretell storms, hurricanes...
earthquakes...
In my youth...
it saved my mother's life.
We were on holiday in Sicily. Suddenly,
I smelled a snake under the stones...
A foul smell.
You're "The Eye?" You phoned?
I'm Mrs. Comolli. Come on up.
His name is Forbes. He's Swiss.
Very wealthy, very shrewd,
speaks 8 languages and loves art.
Has one of the finest homes
on the coast.
Here's the address and phone.
- What does one say?
- Thank you.
No, I meant what does
one say to your boss?
She telexes daily.
She's sick of chasing you!
Everybody’s running after
someone else, little lady.
One day she'll show you the door!
When I’m shown the door, you’ll only
have to push it, Madame Comolli.
There will be a blackboard,
and little girls.
Marie will say: "Here I am!"
and all the little girls will applaud.
Hamlet.
A tragedy in five acts.
The castle of Ellsinore.
A terrace, battlements...
I've been waiting for you.
Good news:
Schlosser's paintings are coming.
One is specially fine.
I'm sure you'll love it, too.
The Traveller.
When you touch it...
it's as smooth, as exquisite,
as a Latour.
You're exquisite, too, Charlotte.
You're exquisite, Charlotte.
Charlotte who?
Look where you're going!
I don't believe it.
Come on.
Come on, move it.
Bastard smokes in bed!
Why do you let him?
Why does he have the right?
Because he's blind?
Or because he's rich?
We spent our vacations...
in Denmark...
I smelled a snake under the stones...
A foul smell...
I can stink, too.
Bump into furniture. Play dumb.
Looking for something?
My granddaughter's ball...
a sort of round red ball.
A red ball.
It must've come over the wall.
Wait, Marie.
I'm coming.
Goddamn blind man!
But, Mrs. Schmidt-Boulanger...
- Hugo's flying out tonight.
- Where to?
If I knew, I'd tell you.
Anyway, Mrs. Comolli will give me
some expense money.
Screw Paul Hugo and Mrs. Comolli.
- Oh shit!
Those fingerprints did it:
she was born Dec. 20, 1962...
Did some time in jail.
2 years ago.
The French police
have nothing on her since.
Catherine Leiris.
- There's no warrant out?
- You expected Bonnie Parker?
No, no...
Won’t you ask me,
any news of your blind man.
Because I’ve got some.
Alright. Wait,
I’ll translate them for you.
Art and business will soon
be happily married.
"The marriage is announced
of Miss Charlotte Vincent...
"whose current exhibit
is a big hit...
"and Mr. Ralph Forbes...
"the well-known Swiss architect."
What's come over you?
Nothing.
- Happy birthday, my love.
- Happy birthday!
Congratulations!
The exhibit is marvellous.
Congratulate Mr. Forbes.
It was his idea.
Sorry, I'm out of cigarettes.
Happy birthday, Marie.
Go on...
Go on, she's all alone.
Go on.
Happy birthday, Catherine.
You must be mistaken.
Just pulling names out of my hat.
Like: Catherine Leiris...
Lucie Brentano...
Lucie Orthiz...
Did you bring this trash?
I'm out for myself. Aren't you?
No comment?
"Murder, though it have no tongue...
"will speak with most
miraculous organ..."
You talking to me?
Just pulling words out of my hat.
I could also whip out my .38...
and splatter the walls with ketchup.
Louis, there's a maniac here.
- What?
- There's a maniac!
Is. 38 a big calibre?
That's what he's got.
- I’ve got to talk to you.
- Now? - Yes. Come.
Excuse me.
The last time someone told me
"Happy birthday," I was 11.
That year, I wanted
a majorette costume.
But it was much too expensive.
Daddy kept saying,
"Everything will be better,
once we have a little money."
It's just that there was
never any money.
Nothing ever got better.
Wait.
Charlotte,
did you see something?
No, nothing. It's strange.
It's like what I wanted to tell you.
It's a man wearing a uniform
with big buttons...
and a shiny cap.
His wife probably left him
a long time ago.
Maybe she's dead.
The girls at school knew
the shiny cap.
The teachers, too.
Everybody made fun of them...
because her dad's job
was opening taxi doors.
Even he knew
he was incompetent.
He got fired. He became a washroom
attendant in a grand hotel.
Mr Pee Pee.
When he comes home at night,
he still reeks of ammonia.
The 22nd of December
is his daughter’s birthday.
She’s eleven.
An old neighbour gave her
some pears.
That’s all they have for dinner.
It’s very cold.
They went into a department store
in order to get warm.
There was music playing: "La Paloma".
It was beautiful.
The father said: Wait a second,
I’ll go and fetch something for you.
He tried to steal a sweater
but he got caught.
I waited for him all night at home.
The next day, two fucking inspectors
came and told me he was dead.
9221319?
"Hello Mr. Forbes...
"I'm sorry, I can't let you
marry Charlotte."
No...
"9221319? Hello, Forbes?
"Catherine Leiris stole a car.
"A Swiss can't marry a thief.
"She's also slightly lesbian..."
"9221319? Hello, Binky?
"She's killed lots of guys.
"She'll kill you, too.
"You don't stand a chance...
so give her back to me."
"9221319...
"Catherine, I love you."
Can you help me across?
Talking to yourself?
- I was phoning you.
- Oh yes, what about?
About Marie... I mean Charlotte.
You can't marry her.
I'm against the marriage.
I beg your pardon, but...
I'm her father, if you must know.
She surely spoke of me.
She always does.
The man in the shiny cap:
"Mr. Pee Pee."
- A ridiculous figure.
- Ridiculous, that's it.
She spoke of you... her time
in jail... the car she stole...
As if she wanted to put me off.
She could have said anything...
I don't scare easily.
The blind have priority, Mr. Forbes.
You don't stand in line for movies...
you get seats on buses...
But you can't run red lights...
or steal people's kids.
You won't get my daughter.
What have you ever done for her?
I lugged Meyerganz...
through the sewers of Monte Carlo...
and hid Jerry's bags in the ferns.
What did you do?
You just spouted a lot of crap...
Your intuitions... Hamlet...
The snake under the stones
and the cigars in bed...
I'm not denying you my daughter
because you're a cripple...
but because... you're a phoney.
We can cross now.
What's going on?
Capricorn: "Now is the winter
of our discontent..."
All the planets are hostile.
Change surroundings.
Hello, miss.
Your passport, please.
Thank you.
Oh no, shit!
Don't fool with hitchhikers.
Thanks... You're real nice.
I'm going to Biarritz.
That's great. So am I.
You might ask me my name.
What's your name?
Betty.
You could say, "It's a nice name."
And offer me a smoke.
Help yourself.
Last night a truck driver
tried to ball me.
That idiot is at the hospital.
For a long time.
You don't look that strong.
No, but I've got what it takes.
You're driving too fast.
Why so fast?
If it's to show off to that dog...
you'll have an accident,
like Forbes...
We can stop here if you want.
Now what?
Get out.
I've got what it takes, too.
Throw out the penknife.
For some reason,
I don't feel like killing you.
I loved a man, he's dead,
and I'm tired.
No more Biarritz?
- If you promise to be good.
- I promise. I swear.
Do you want me to tell you
about the brothel in Miramas?
What fun I had there!
It was near Marseille.
I was something like,
eight or nine.
There was a room filled with toys.
Lots of things: there were dolls,
plush Mickey Mouse’s,
and... what was there again?
There was... what’s the name?
A circuit with miniature cars.
I used to love it!
I spent all my afternoons
in that room.
Before she locked me in, Mom forced
me to take my clothes off,
and then I could play.
And one day...
I noticed the holes in the wall.
There were guys
next door watching me.
I was part of the show...
There are holes in the
walls here, too.
Someone's watching us.
Hey, go easy on the brandy.
I swear someone's watching us.
Let me tell you something.
People who make holes in walls
only exist if you think they do.
Still there, old man?
I'm here, Marie.
Forbes died accidentally.
It said so in the papers.
Accidentally.
Hey! That's my car!
There's not room
for both of us in this deal.
Looks like my gun, too.
There are things in the trunk...
I care about them.
Always hang on to things
you care about.
There are also some cookies
on the back seat.
Give him his cookies.
Thanks.
Have a good trip!
I'm always losing you, Marie.
It won't do.
I hope you don't get
into any trouble.
Wait for me, my sweet,
I'm coming.
Xerox!
Seal it!
Here. There was another
of those yellow letters.
- Won’t you open it?
- What for? I know what’s inside.
Cut-off point: today, 10 AM.
- I've been looking for you all over.
- I haven't!
I thought I'd see you sooner.
What kept you?
Where's lover-boy?
Pension Hortensias.
I've had enough of that place.
I'm going home to Paris.
14 rue de la Butte aux Cailles.
Will you buy me a drink?
- Take the lady's order.
- A Fernet...
No...
a Pernod... No! A shandy.
Why not mix all three?
Get her a black coffee.
Am I bothering you?
You were sketching?
Looked like schoolgirls...
What a stupid thing to say.
Schoolgirls?
Are you zonked, or what?
So lover-boy threw you out?
Tell me all about it.
There's nothing to say.
Nothing, really.
I banged on the door all night.
I even used my head... See?
He wouldn't open.
He told me to get lost. And worse.
He said: "You're old, you stink..."
He even called me ugly.
It's true... you're extremely ugly.
Let's talk about the girls.
How are they?
Where are they staying?
You mean Princess Eugenie.
In a suite.
And she throws away hundreds
and thousands at the casino.
If it goes on like this,
your model won’t get a cent.
Maybe it will bring back his civility.
Oh, no! You’re not going to joke
about my appearance again?
Maybe it would be less atrocious
with bangs.
Give it a try. Down to there...
There it is.
- Lost something, Super sleuth?
- You bet.
You took my car,
my gun and some photos.
The car's been recovered.
I want the rest.
You can forget the gun.
50,000 will buy back the photos.
You're a bastard.
What can you do
with my mementos?
Invest them.
The Hugo case...
The Meyerganz case...
The Pallenberg case, today...
Right now she's at the bank.
Once she shows up here with the
money... the blackmailer will disappear.
The little girls...
- The photos of those schoolgirls?
- Censored.
Destroyed!
Shame on you, dirty old man.
- My shoes?
- They're tacky as hell.
Taruchi wore them, too.
Who's Taruchi?
An extremely tacky guy.
A jerk like you...
who thought he was smart.
- Good day, sir.
- Hold it, smart-ass.
Your turn to answer.
Who gave you my address?
Which one? Pension Hortensias?
Or the one
on Rue de la Butte aux Cailles?
Hey, that’s below the belt.
- Yes..
Let me guess...
- Not Madame Ugly?
- Right...
A sugarless coffee, a few
quickly dried tears, then the swoon.
Love at first sight.
He said "love at first sight"
Like that?
It’s not a question of money anymore,
it’s a love story, my poor Germaine.
You wouldn’t even recognize him.
He wears incredible shoes,
light ties... silk shirts.
- What's she like?
- He spoke vaguely of her.
White yacht...
Parasols... delicacies...
What about me?
Did he tell you about me?
- Four lettered words!
- The bastard.
After all the things I did for him!
I even walked the street for him,
yes sir, in Barcelona.
On the Ramblas, in 1958.
I don’t look the part, do I?
Do I look like a detective?
In the Barrio Chino,
they called me "Castagnet"...
That’s why I felt funny when you
advised me to wear bangs.
Well, of course I didn’t know,
when I said "bangs"...
She’s not that hot, after all.
Don’t you think I would
be prettier as a brunette?
- Do you know what I’m going to do?
- Don’t be reckless, kid!
Since the bastard is
indulging in a passion,
I’m going to offer him
a crime of passion.
- Come, come, be reasonable!
- Like hell.
Don’t be reckless, I said.
Take a shower, while you're at it.
I'm coming.
This bag's heavy!
- No mistakes, I hope?
- No, all in 50's and 100's.
- Why are you here?
- To please you, my liege.
"My liege."
The detective was right.
You got your pimp shoes on.
- Where you headed?
- What did he tell you?
Looking for the sun?
With that cow, under her parasol?
Listen, Germaine...
Don't do anything silly.
Germaine can't listen.
She's deaf.
Dead!
Goodbye, Castagnet.
So, tell me: how was it?
- Crazy. Totally sexual.
- Good for you.
But what with all that,
we’re going without a penny.
I don’t get it: you’re saying you’ve
got bank accounts everywhere.
You’re talking about Dreyfuss,
the Pommier Bank, the Credit Lyonnais.
Where I’ve got an account,
they’ve got my picture.
Hey, let’s go where you
don’t have an account.
Marie! I’m getting angry,
Come back home!
Come back home now!
They threw a paving stone!
Two girls, with masks on.
Masks? What kind of masks?
- Pinocchio!
Don’t you ever do things
like that again, Marie.
You’ll end up breaking my heart.
From that day on,
the day Catherine lost Betty...
the detective realized dark forces
would always pursue the girl.
Slowly, inexorably...
like a glacier on the move.
She could only
elude them by moving on...
anywhere... ceaselessly.
A deadly whirl...
but that's how it had to be.
Up north...
they crashed a police roadblock.
For the detective,
it was a new
and exhilarating experience.
We’re now putting
Herve Claude on the air
so he can give us all
the latest information
about the accomplice
of Betty Shapira,
who was killed yesterday
during the deadly hold-up
of the Credit
Commercial bank in Melun.
Over to you, Claude.
We just learned from a reliable
source that the said accomplice
is supposed to be already wanted
for several other murders,
including Paul Hugo’s,
whose body was just discovered
by the police in a pond,
in the Brussels area.
According to commissioner Cervin,
there could be a connection
between this case
and the strange disappearance
of Michel Meyerganz,
in Monte-Carlo last year.
The double murder in the
Black Forest is also remembered
Cora Pallenberg and Jerry Beaufil
were killed the same night,
September the 26th of last year.
The police incline to think
that the perpetrator
of all those murders is
the same person
Catherine Leiris,
born on December the 22nd, 1962,
convicted of robbery in 1979
and incarcerated in the
Fleury-Merogis prison from 1979 to...
So they drove for a long time,
going north by northeast,
to a city that Catherine
might have known,
but the existence of which had never
even been dreamed by the detective.
But it really was called Charleville.
The next month, Catherine
checked in the Hotel du Canal,
where she lived cloistered,
but for a short walk in the evenings.
How to find again the unfathomable
grace of Lucie Brentano,
the radiance of Dorothee Orthiz,
the beauty of Ariane Chevalier.
In this sad and idle passer-by?
Enough to make one believe that this
girl seemed interested in nothing...
including herself. It's incredible.
One day, the detective thought that
spiders were crawling up the walls,
that the junkies jumped
in the gutters again.
False alarm.
It was the 22nd of December.
Since nobody else thought about it,
Catherine was celebrating
her own birthday.
Her dress was too loose fitting,
its flounces ludicrous,
its pattern extravagant.
My God!
Already one year since Rome!
mused the detective, who thought
the whole thing was delicious.
Just think, two days ago
I was still in Vegas.
At the "Flamingo."
It's better than here, you know.
I know.
No kidding, sweetheart.
You know Vegas?
My father had an office there.
A whole floor to himself,
on the Strip.
Buy me a Pimm's?
- It's my birthday today.
- Julien!
A Pimm's for the lady.
2.50 francs, plus the olives,
makes 3 francs.
I didn't order olives.
She should go before she
makes a fool of herself,
don't you think?
Run away, quick.
- Who?
- The young girl at the bar.
Anyway, there are
only young girls here.
He died the evening
of my birthday.
Over 1,000 people
came to the funeral.
- Whose funeral?
- My father's.
I'm sure nobody went
to Betty's funeral.
It was probably very sad.
What did those assholes
do with the mask?
Who put this here?
That odd man at the back.
He left right after.
He left you a note.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY MARIE
At this critical point
in their relationship...
the ogre decided to
talk to the little girl.
He asked,
"What are you going to do now?"
I'm going home.
But what does that mean,
"home?"
Her home.
Catherine Nieris,
born on Dec. 22, 1962...
in Bobigny... Seine St. Denis.
How can she go back to the
cockroaches... the rotting walls...
back to the slums?
Server wanted -
Interesting salary - Tips
No. Never seen her.
I'll leave the photos,
you get back to me.
Hello, reception.
- Let's go.
- That money's not mine.
I'm not doing it for
myself, either.
I'll scream, I'll shout for help!
I've shouted for help for 20 years.
No one ever answered.
Come in.
Ignore the mess.
I can't offer you much.
A Coke? Beer?
Brandy?
Make yourself at home.
Perhaps you'd like a shower?
A shower?
That's a dumb thing to suggest!
We'll see...
She goes into the bathroom...
I go to the window.
I live alone.
My wife left me.
Left with my daughter.
I never saw them again.
At first, it was very painful...
Now it's better.
Don't fool with that.
It's loaded.
Don't... It's loaded...
What time you through? No!
What are your hours, miss?
When do you get off?
When does your shift end?
Pardon?
What would you like?
Turkey in supreme
sauce, please.
We don’t have any left.
- Oh?
When do you get off?
2:00 a. m.
Mind meeting me for a drink?
No..
That looks better.
You're right.
More appetizing than ours.
Very well presented.
I forgot... Don't wait in front.
The staff leaves by the stage door.
- At the rear.
- How will I know it?
The trash cans are yellow,
I'll be in blue.
Say!
- Beg your pardon?
You’re drinking my beer, sir.
- Excuse me, I...
It’s no big deal.
You may finish it.
- What time is it?
- 1:55.
My girlfriend smoked those.
- Does the smell of tobacco bother you?
- No. My own smell is bothering me.
The smell of French fries:
it permeates everything.
Where do you want us to go?
Maybe you’ve got an idea?
To a club? Your place? Mine?
- I live in a hotel.
- So do I.
Let’s make it your place.
My name's Catherine...
Catherine Leiris.
When you asked what time I got off,
I thought I knew you.
- I've never been in the "Miami".
- I didn't mean there.
People think they know me:
I'm so ordinary looking.
I look like everybody.
When I grow a beard...
I'm like any bearded guy.
Ignore the mess.
Sit down.
What would you like?
I have a nice little white wine.
A Coke?
A drop of brandy? No, a Coke...
Brandy.
Won't you take off your jacket?
- I'll take it off.
- I didn't mean...
Then let's change the subject.
Just talk.
About you?
OK...
Let's go.
I wasn't always a waitress.
I've been waited on.
My father was
an international thief.
Police everywhere
chased him for years.
On my birthday...
he collapsed,
his pockets full of diamonds.
He said: "Happy birthday,"
and died.
You loved him?
Yes.
That's all crap.
My father was a famous doctor...
a blind pianist...
A brilliant architect...
My father was, what else was he?
But I really loved him.
I'm terribly sorry...
maybe you wanted cookies?
No thanks, I'm fine.
If you feel like resting...
go right ahead.
Unless you'd like a shower?
- The French fries?
- Not at all... I...
It's a good idea.
I'm in a luxury hotel...
but there's no shower.
There's a clean washcloth.
And a mitten for rub-downs.
Careful... The hot and cold knobs
have been reversed.
Red is cold, blue's hot.
Never fails!
- You married?
- Yes...
I mean, no... I was.
My wife left me...
a long time ago.
She left with my daughter...
Marie...
Back in 1958.
Marie died in 1962.
It must have been painful.
Yes.
- You got over it?
- No.
I lost the only photo I had of her.
It was taken in 1962...
Just before the vacation,
a school picture...
She had her arms crossed,
like a sad clown?
Not at all.
Marie was very cheerful.
Look what I found...
Don't fool with it.
It's loaded.
Calm down.
Calm down, troubled soul...
Stop, Marie, please...
I know where I saw you...
You're the photographer.
Yes...
In the park, in Brussels.
By the carousel...
The Hugo case...
I didn’t hear any news.
I phoned.
Mrs. Schmidt-Boulanger told me
you didn’t work for her anymore.
- L'oeil...
- Yes, Madeleine?
What happened?
I lost the photo of Marie.
I'm telling you this for us.
If you've lost the photo...
maybe we should stop
phoning each other?
Maybe you're right.
- What'll you do now?
- Nothing.
Wait.
He waited less than 3 years.
He knew it was his last night on earth
when he finally saw the door...
Marie!
Catherine!
Careful... It's him.
He opened the door...
and went into the photo...
Here he comes.
Subtitles from the cut version
Completely re-timed and expanded.
Expanded scenes translated by
Goupil66
Re-timed by McDuck
May 2009
Edited by
=tosem=