Sazu489...
Sir?
Sir, can you hear me?
He's alive!
Get your ass back here.
Take some cover.
Don't have time
to take a nap.
The prisoner escaped
before we covered.
I think he took a rifle.
He went over there...
Rifle.
Any signs?
-Negative.
Starting sequence complete.
Clea 19, on line.
Hello, commander Karza.
Now, Clea, activate
system link.
System is link. -You got
guys on line? -Check.
Check. -Clea, patch
me in the base.
Transmitting.
Alpha base, this is Commander
Karza. Do you copy?
Copy, Commander.
This is Alpha base.
Prometheus is down.
I repeat, Prometheus is down.
We have three survivors
and need immediately instructions.
Without pick in up
the ship's biken.
Ship biken is not functional.
We need your coordinates.
I.T.A. in 10 hours.
All alive need to activate
your personal biken.
Copy that. -What is the
status of your cargo?
Cargo has survived
and left crash side.
Commander, mission
parameter is remaining.
Organism must be delivered.
And Karzo, it imperative
that you bring him alive.
Is that understood?
Commander, do you copy?
Yeah, roger that.
Karzo out.
End transmission.
-Thanks for the help.
What else is new?
-Enough.
This mission has been
joke from the start.
You think that is joke that
we lost our ship and our crew?
Your prisoner brought my
men down single handed.
And you couldn't do it
damn thing to stop it.
I don't see anything funny
about that. Do you soldier?
No, sir.
-Good.
Now, Clea, speak with
the Lieutenant.
Hello, Centauri 7.
Oh, you are hurt.
Yeah, give me diagnostic.
Serious some stenches trauma
to your left shoulder.
No broken bones.
Heart beat is elevated.
Otherwise you should be
in excellent condition.
Clea, skip
trace improvement.
Activating tracking system.
Redirecting cells to repairing
nerve and tissue damage.
Increasing endorphins
to counter pain.
Better.
The subject is 250 meters
southeast from your position
and moving away
as steady range.
Are you sure
he's moving away?
Yes, Commander.
-We on the move and set out.
We need supplies.
How much left?
-We'll take Logan's pack.
Clea, any idea
where we are?
Planet is on charged.
Computer shows you on
unknown set of coordinates.
Gravity to that
planet is the rest.
Give us the status.
Atmosphere is tin.
Likely surrenders have
been unconscious.
My advice, keeping
your helmets on it
to until I finished
activating your bodies.
Surface's temperature
is 116 degrees. -Nice.
Going cells are
in 72 percent,
which can last just
about 100 hours.
Anything else?
Calculating the
position of the sun.
I estimated 34
hours of day light
with 5 hours of night.
Sound like a paradise.
Maybe I'll move here.
I can't wait on that.
I'm sure you could, sir.
According to Clea, it will be
mess to get this thing.
Let's move out.
Clea, give me a torch.
What you'll gonna do?
Weld it act together?
He's on the move
again. Let's go.
On your feet.
This is brutal.
I don't understand
how those thing
can move so fast
on this heat. -Simple.
If he wants to live,
pure survival instinct.
What's the rush?
He gets no food, no water.
We can track every
move he makes.
Let him die first.
There no be a
needs to recovery.
You heard them.
They want it alive.
Why? -Is not your place to
question orders, Lieutenant.
It is when accosting me
the lifes of my men.
This should be a simple
transport mission.
Are you done crying, soldier?
Get lost.
May it up and move out.
Both of you.
Closing in on subject.
Sublimate press air increasing.
There!
Where is it?
Up on the ridge.
8 o'clock.
Look like we can get up
on a north side.
Grab his rifle.
I will cover you.
Go!
I see it.
-Shut him.
It won't alive.
I'm in command now.
Take it down.
Target lock.
-Take the shoot.
Down.
Hold the position.
It's secure.
I got it.
I said hold position.
I coming up.
It's nothing here
but his cloak.
Fall back!
Clea?
I thought you are dead.
-You are not that lucky.
Where is my rifle?
Ask Tursai.
Night is falling.
Let's the place
to set up camp.
Hard to take the ground.
Only to access points.
I still can catch him.
If you need the rest,
you stay here and I'll...
Why do you think
that I want to hear
your opinion soldier?
I don't.
He was to green. He would
never set in any unit.
He wasn't the one
who rush us into the ambush.
The situation that determine
outcome, Lieutenant.
Components
and the skill do.
Unfortunately, your team
wasn't good enough for those trick.
Now, make
yourself useful
and set up parameter
around those rocks over there.
You have your orders.
43 degrees and dropping.
Private channel's open it.
What's the Commander's
condition?
He's suffering from a
plasma wound to his side.
Extreme nerve
damage has been
sustained on his
left long izenteret.
What meds you got him on?
500 CC sustrofin
and 250 CC for crioksen.
Don't surprise he stayed on
his feet as long as he did.
Reduce his medication.
We have a long way
to travel tomorrow
and I am not to
carry him.
I'm not sure if
Commander Karzo
would agree with
your assessment.
Keep the information on fly.
He doesn't need to know.
It is not in my programming
to lie, Lieutenant.
You want be lying,
you just not share information.
Can you do that?
-Of, course.
Thanks.
Odd.
-What's that?
You have been from all the soldier
that I have been a signed to
you are the only one
that's he ever thank me.
Do you mind it?
-No.
I quite preferred.
Isn't get tirelessness been
endless it worried about.
We have in
common then.
You must work compliant
with the military directed, Centauri.
So, I been told.
According to your record
some of yours
previous inseportinations
border it dangerously
close to treason. -And?
It's a question, why you
chosen to be a soldier?
It is does, doesn't it?
Atmosphere conditioning will
be completed in 10 seconds.
I advise you to keep yours
eyes more on objective
instead of me, Lieutenant.
Atmospheric adaptation
is complete.
It is now safe to
remove your helmets.
Why is the prisoner
not effected on tin air?
He doesn't
wear the life suit.
They can adapt to
almost any conditions.
All this was in the file.
Permission to
speak freely, sir?
Permission?
It never stop you before.
Go ahead.
What's the special really?
Why is that thing
so important?
Does it matter?
-Yes, it does.
Why? -I lost my ship
and my crew.
I would like to know why.
-You are a soldier.
We both are.
We follow orders
without questions.
Tell me what you know
otherwise I go alone.
Disobey orders is
a treason, soldier.
Punishment by death.
All right. This thing is
the last of his kind.
We destroyed
his home world
and now somehow figure
we return the favor.
So, we'll catch it that thing
and get it back to the base.
We made a world
to go home too.
Now you know
what's I do.
Is that you make
feel better, soldier?
Sit down and discuss when some
wild thing is around on us.
You delivery to kept
us in the dark.
You did need to know.
-I see.
This mission
was a hero maker.
Everything we know
was at risk.
Are you deaf
as you stupid?
What level was
this mission?
This discussion is over.
What level was
this mission, sir?
41. Nobel class.
-Highest level.
And you was so
with your ego
you didn't badger to tell us
how danger the creature was.
Your men were
incompetent.
Don't blame me
for your mistakes.
You jeopardized this mission.
You got my verscio.
I'm your superior officer
and you speak
to me as such.
Why?
You don't deserve it.
Let's see what
fight you got in.
You are no worth it.
Clea? What's the
present position?
I had no visual.
Clea?
Come on.
Come on, baby.
Don't live me alone now.
Starting sequence complete.
Clea 19 on line.
Hello, Centauri 7.
Clea.
I thought I lost you there.
-You cant to get rid of
me so easily, Centauri.
I suffered some damage but
seems to be function in properly.
I'm quite adorable,
you know.
That's why keep
you out, babe.
I thought that was my
charming personality.
Clea. What's the
prison location?
78 and increasing.
Look likes just
you and me now.
I'm sorry about
Commander Karza
but if I must
say I'm pleased
that it was you
who survived.
Well, that makes two of us.
Keep trace prisoner.
200 microcliks on
your current location.
Continuing in south
eastern direction.
On the move again.
I hope you'll rot, sir.
It's been moving on a
steady pace for hours.
Hopefully the damn
things collapse it.
Without the water source it could
be coming to dehydration.
Exactly.
Still...
I'm going in.
Report me any movement.
-Of course.
Be careful, Centauri.
I get it.
Clea, my grid?
What is it, Centauri?
It's the tracking device.
Tear out from it's
own throat.
Very clever.
He can't go far.
He cannot brag.
Do you hear me?
I bringing you in.
Dead or alive.
Centauri?
Are you all right?
Centauri 7?
Please answer.
Clea?
Which the time would be?
How long I have been out?
Clea?
The head.
I had to kick the head.
Pull on that.
Hello?
Unknown user,
please identify.
Repeat, identify.
Identify.
Horn Jericho.
Un authorized user.
Terminating access.
Private channel,
open it. -Clea?
Where are you?
-I'm not sure.
I'm in the possession
un authorized user.
Can you give me a signal
of his location? -Of course.
Got it.
He tried to access me
but I terminated
the communication.
It's spoke to you?
-Yes.
And it's understood you.
This damn thing is more
smart then I thought.
Keep that signal going.
Still on the private channel.
I'm on my way.
Clea?
She won't be helping
you anymore.
We can't get out from
this planet without her.
How I do use her?
-You can't.
And if you have her
you still be stuck on this
flooring rock as well.
You get no way to go.
Maybe I not
plan on go anywhere.
If you want a die
kill yourself now and
save me the trouble.
What if I want to
take you with me?
You do then done already.
You are not dumb
as you look.
What's it you want?
I know you
can still hear me.
You are playing games?
Well, here is mine.
I know why they
want you brought in.
And I don't care.
I'm gonna hunt you down
and I wanna kill you.
That's my game.
Give up, Sedonian.
You will never catch me.
You been out smart
enough to run.
Go home.
Why you still got a
home to go back to.
I know something new
I hate about your race.
You packed not enough water.
Because that's more
human thing.
Always be prepare it.
I'm actually surprise you
last as long you have.
Seem how incompetent you are.
Now I know why they put
that helmet mask on you.
You talk too much.
They you want to know
if I can speak your language.
You are right.
It's a good for
somebody like you
to speak the language
of the stars.
Something we pick it
up from the Draks.
Draks are noble race.
You don't know
anything about that.
Nobel?
They are disease on a
galaxy, filthy creatures.
That's funny.
They say the same
thing about you.
Lying bugs.
I tell you this
no one miss you guys
when you gone.
Your the race is in extinct,
human, not mine.
Not so long.
Is that so?
-Yap.
I taken yours to hell.
I hold your fenecy, human.
Been that you
last of your kind
how do you hope to
accomplish this remarkable fit?
Don't you know why?
-I don't care.
That's why.
You want this war
on your advent
and lost your home world.
Those the consequence.
-We didn't enter this war.
You attacked us.
You were harboring Draks fugitives.
-You mean refugees.
Big difference.
They need our help.
You choose the wrong side.
No.
It's cost us everything
but we chose the right side.
Now, it's gonna cost
you everything.
We all die.
That's your solution.
How can you
been so naive?
Another pack will
ride on our place.
An endless cycle.
The only way to brake it
is to take control from
those with power
to rule them instead.
You thought about this?
-No.
It's the way it is.
Maybe you are right.
Human.
You have two options.
You can come with
me and survive
or you can join to the rest
of your race in oblivion.
It's your decision.
I'd choose option
number three.
What is what?
Clea?
Clea? Are you there?
Centauri 7?
-Yeah, it's me.
Has the human
then recaptured? -No.
Then have you
do retrieve me?
Radio sit it
on the skeleton.
Why he live it behind?
Odd, that creature
is kind it dangerously so.
Like he figured something else.
But what is he doing?
I missing something.
I wonder...
-Wonder what?
Clea?
Centauri, I may know
what the human is doing.
Great, tell me.
It would be better
if I didn't. -Why is that?
If you know it might
influence your actions.
I don't...
What?
Do you trust me, Centauri?
-With my life.
And here I do
need you to do.
We may have
another problem.
What now?
-I think my forward
Commander Karza did more
damage to my entire circle
then I first thought.
What you mean?
-My battery isn't holding
the power cells
charge very well.
I'm not going to be able
to conserve enough power
to activate your biken when the
rescue mission will arrive.
Shut down the other system
restraining power.
I have but two main resources
left from my system’s memory
and your medical unit I'm
afraid you have to shutting down
to until you'll
need me, Centauri.
That's not happened.
Cut my meds.
I don't think that
is a good idea.
Cut them.
Meds unit is shutting down.
Your pain receptor
the spank in
and your heart break
is increasing. -I'm good.
Meds should give
us enough power
provided when will ship
arrived for designated time.
With little luck
I'll get on him.
I picking a communications
from orbit. -Our pick up?
No, this is art
military channel
and unknown craft
is approaching.
They could come
down here? -Yes.
But my system can
track it.
Try raise them.
No respond.
They got it to
the radio silence.
It can't be good.
Maybe some randeu
wous with the human.
Maybe is not the last one.
Or they could be Draks.
Great.
Hey!
What?
Money?
Sadonians?
They are paying you.
You are bounty hunter.
That is such an ugly word.
Soldier of fortune
more like it.
They want you been alive, ha?
Just as I thought.
Slyeck.
What would the Slyeck
be doing here?
Bounty hunter.
Alpha base must he send
him like a back up.
It is.
Alpha base or
the Slyeck? -Both.
What you going to do?
He's got my weapons
and my prisoner.
I gonna go get them back.
True your kind will
world wound?
Maybe.
True or lie?
True.
Deserve it they do.
Scare them good you do, a?
You like Sadonians?
-No one like Sadonians.
The way where we
planet make slaves.
There way or no way.
If I kill you
they all die.
No more Sadonians.
-Wait. Remember?
I'm money.
You kill me, no money.
Maybe I'll take you
to the ship first.
Talk with elders.
Good idea.
Smart.
No! Fuck that money.
I'll be hero.
No more Sadonians.
-No, wait.
You have your
business here, Slyeck?
That human is my prisoner.
He's mine.
I don't think so.
Now what?
We wait.
On what?
Extraction.
Ship should be here soon.
What did they
call you, human?
What is your name?
Jericho.
Lieutenant Orn Jericho.
Lieutenant?
We are the same right.
I'm Centauri 7.
I didn't ask.
Not wise to upset me
consider on your
position, human.
No wonder your
kind didn't make it.
No common sense.
-Was that a reason?
I thought was you
genocide war to did it.
War is war.
You lost.
As long I'm still alive
the war ain't over.
You never did answer
to my question.
How were you going to
destroy my planet?
Are. -What?
You said were.
Past tense.
It's are.
All right. How are you going
to destroy my planet?
We sent as ship
towards your planet
feel the capacity
with the filmpejlo.
When's the impact
your world is
blowing to dust.
How long range will detective
harbor before reaches...
Is clocked.
You will never see it coming.
Another trick we pick
it up from the Draks.
So, that's why they
want you alive.
They want to get the ship
coordinates out of you. -They'll try.
But you'll die first.
That's right.
Well, no then is no
reason to keep you alive.
I can kill you right now.
-You could.
But?
-Come on.
Everybody wants
to be a hero.
It's a one glimmer hope
that you might be
a savior world.
I told you, I don't care.
They can go to
the twelve hells.
I don't believe you.
Centauri, I have
incoming transmission.
Patch it through.
Commander Karzo,
this is battle ship Aurora.
Do you copy?
-Copy that Aurora.
Karzo is dead.
This is Lieutenant Centauri 7
as acting commander.
Copy that, Lieutenant.
We'll arrived in the
last known signal point
from Prometheus
before you went down.
We waiting on bipen location.
Clea, activate personal biken.
Signal ineshiated.
-Aurora, you have it?
Affirmative. It's weak
but we should be able to find.
ITA in 15 minutes.
-Roger that.
Centauri 7 out.
When we get back to Sedonia
they gonna torture you.
They will get the
information they want.
You won't last.
The plan we won't be there
by the time we arrived. -That soon?
And all this?
The wild chase to give ship
the time you need it?
Get the long
before we'll do.
Why plans full of people
they are innocent?
They are not
responsible for the war
or your planet
destruction?
The high counsel is.
-You all fall of blindly.
It's no excuse.
-It's the law.
What's the God
that you creed?
Your Gods would telling me
the way to entire world?
No, we split out on different
stars and surrounding races.
By slaving
and destroying now.
They don't accept our
way of life then yes.
You make me sick.
This from the race that couldn't
defend them self get it other.
Let lonely and
beating the army.
Only an ignorant species will
make war against own kind.
Shut up!
You command mass murder
on a galactic scale
and you think
it's holly crusade.
This is a lie!
Unless some
come as a long
and takes away
control from you.
Your words, not mine.
That will never happened.
I wonder why.
You are right.
I do care
about my world.
I have wife
and child there.
I would like to
see them again.
Our women don't fight.
They care about
the children.
Our soldiers
are up there.
As one warrior to another
I respectfully ask that you take
this war to those responsible.
You'll just be killing
the women and children.
Is that what you want a
legacy of your kind to be?
Vega sector, gamma quadrant.
Is that...
-Where the ship is.
Call your people. I'll give
them the coordinates.
You better hurry.
You don't have much time.
Clea? Patch me to
the Alpha base.
Transmitting.
Alpha base, this is Lieutenant
Centauri 7. Do you copy?
Copy Lieutenant.
What is your status?
The prisoner is in custody
and willing to give
coordinates of the bomb ship.
Lieutenant, we are ready to
get the information.
Please, sent to us
immediately.
What's the
coordinates? -No.
I want to be the
one who tells them.
The coordinates are 22...
-Non authorized user.
Clea, authorized the human.
Stage your name.
-Orn Jericho.
Orn Jericho’s now authorized.
The coordinates are 22- 9,
7-13, 0-40, 2-6-0.
Vega sector, gamma quadrant.
It's an M-class
star frigate.
We have confirmation
the ship does identify.
Sending Bell ship to
intercept. -We found it.
Well done, Lieutenant.
We no longer
need the prisoner.
You may terminated
him at will.
Roger that.
Centauri 7 out.
They want me that
terminated you.
I saved your world.
Your family.
Not really.
I don't have any
wife and children.
That's good and you won't have
anything to worried about
when your planet
blowing on bits.
You didn't think
that I give you
the real coordinates,
did you?
We have confirmation
on the craft.
It's a decoy,
you idiot.
No men. There is nothing
but salvage on that ship.
You can't stop this.
It's already over.
Superior race, ha?
I'm giving you
some advice, alien.
Never let your weapon forward
in the hand of your enemy.
I'm gonna let you in
our little secret.
We never lunch
the bomb ship.
We couldn't.
We've no idea
where the Sadonia was.
But now that I'm authorized
the access you date a base
she's gonna tell me
everything I need to know.
You think, I forced the crash
your ship by accident?
You want it the bomb ship?
I let you right to it.
Now, you gonna learn
what's feels like
to be a last of your kind.
You want to know the
different between you and me?
I did have a wife and
son back on the Earth.
Centauri 7,
this is the Aurora.
We just clear
out the gate
and enter into the atmosphere.
The craft it's on it's
way down. Stand by.
Centauri 7, this is
Commander Chane
in the Aurora.
We are on the ground.
What is your status?
Centauri 7, you picking
up my transmission?
Centauri 7,
do you copy?
The only one
who made it, ha?
You look like hell.
Must a be the rough one.
Get you to the
informative right away.
Clea, upload the
coordinates to the Sedonia
into the ship computer.
Clea.
Clea, I command you
to respond.
San of a bitch.
Alpha base. This is
on the craft Jewelry size.
Commander Chane is
no longer responsive.
Starting sequence
complete. Clea 19.
Hello, Centauri 7.
-Hello, Clea.
It's good to have you back.
I take you by
my new casing
that you follow
my instructions.
Centauri, I have incoming
transmission for Alpha base.
Patch it through.
Lieutenant,
this is Alpha base.
What's going on
now down there?
If I were you
I'd be more concerning
what's going on up there.
Centauri 7, you
are on the orders.
What is the status
of the human?
Find another one to
do your dirty work.
Centauri 7 out.
End of transmission.
Whatever you
planning to do, Centauri
I suggest you to
do it quickly.
It won't be long before
the human traced
the source of that
signal at the Sedonia.
He already has.
Is not that right.
He didn't kill you. Why?
Same reason you
didn't kill me.
Yeah, what's that?
I'll tell you
when I see you.
Centauri, how we may suppose
to get out from here?
Another our ship has to pass
be around here somewhere.
You realized we would be
breaking 26 high council's laws
by taking this
course of action.
Is that a problem?
-Not at all.
Let's get to twelve
hells off this rock.
facebook.com/sazu489