Sir?
Sir, can you hear me?
He's alive!
Get your ass back
here. Get some cover.
We don't have time
to take a nap.
The prisoner escaped
before we recovered.
We think he took a rifle.
He headed off in that...
Rifle.
Lost target! Any signs?
-Negative.
Start-up sequence complete.
Clea 19, series Gamma, on-line.
Hello, commander Karza.
Now, Clea, activate system link.
System is linked.
-You guys got her on-line?
-Check.
-Clea, patch me into base.
Transmitting.
Alpha base, this is Commander Karza
(notched helmet comb). Do you copy?
Copy, Commander.
This is Alpha base.
Prometheus is down. I repeat,
Prometheus is down. Inrepairable.
We have three survivors and
in need of immediate extraction.
We're not picking up
your ship's beacon.
Ships beacon is non-functional.
We're diverting close ships to
your last known coordinates
E.T.A. in 100 hours.
Upon their arrival you'll need to
activate your personal beacon.
Copy that.
-What is the status of your cargo?
Cargo has survived
and fled crash site.
Commander, mission
parameters remaining.
The organism must be
contained and delivered.
And Karza, it's imperative
that you bring him in alive.
Is that understood?
Commander, do you copy?
Yeah, roger that.
Karza out.
End transmission.
-Thanks for the help.
What else is new?
-Enough.
This mission has been
a joke from the start.
You think that it's a joke that
we lost our ship and our crew?
Your prisoner brought my
men down single handed.
And you couldn't do a
damn thing to stop it.
I don't see anything funny
about that. Do you soldier?
No, sir.
-Good.
Now, Clea, see to
the Lieutenant.
Hello, Lt Centauri 7 (smooth helmet comb).
Oh, you are hurt.
Yeah, give me a diagnostic.
There is substantial trauma
to your left shoulder.
A plasma wound. No broken
bones. Heart beat is elevated.
Otherwise you appear to be
in excellent condition.
Clea, skiptrace prisoner.
Activating tracking system.
-Patch me up Clea.
Redirecting cells to repairing
nerve and tissue damage.
Increasing endorphins to counter pain.
Administering strophine to wounded area.
Better.
Sensors show the subject is 250 micro-
clicks south-east from your position
and moving away
at a steady rate.
Are you sure
it's moving away?
Yes, Commander.
-Get on the move, let's head out.
We'll need supplies.
Not much left.
-We'll take Logan's pack.
Clea, any idea
where we are?
Planet is uncharted.
Log shows you dropped out of warp
at an unknown set of coordinates.
Gravity at the nearest
planet did the rest.
Give us the stats.
Atmosphere is thin.
Likely to render
you unconscious.
I advise, keeping
your helmets on
until I finished
acclimating your bodies.
Surface's temperature is 116 degrees F (47C).
-Nice.
Power cells are
at 72 percent,
which can last
just about 100 hours.
Anything else?
Calculating the
position of the sun.
I estimate the days here
are 33 hours of daylight
with 5 hours of night.
Sound like paradise.
Maybe I'll move here.
I can arrange that.
I'm sure you could, sir.
According to Clea, we've got less
than three days to get this thing.
Let's move out.
Croyer (no helmet comb),
give me a torch.
What're you gonna do?
Weld it back together?
He's on the move
again. Let's go.
On your feet.
This is brutal.
I don't understand
how this thing
can move so fast in this heat.
-Simple.
It wants to live,
pure survival instinct.
What's the rush? It's
got no food, no water.
We can track every
move it makes.
Let it die of thirst.
Then there won't be a
need to recover it.
You heard them.
They want it alive.
Why?
-It's not your place to question orders, Lieutenant.
It is when it's costing
me the lives of my men.
This was a simple
transport mission.
Are you done crying, soldier?
fuck off.
May it up and move out.
Both of you.
Closing in on subject.
78 clicks and increasing.
There!
-See it!
Where is it?
Up on the ridge.
8 o'clock.
Look like we can get
up on the north side.
Croyer, Grab Karza's
rifle. I'll cover you.
Go!
I see it.
-Shoot it.
They want it alive.
I'm in command now.
Take it down.
Target locked.
-Take the shot.
Down.
Hold the position.
It's secure.
I got it.
I said hold position.
I coming up.
There's nothing here
but his cloak.
Fall back!
Croyer?
I thought you were dead.
-You are not that lucky.
Where is my rifle?
Ask the prisoner.
Night's falling.
That's a good place
to set up camp.
Hard to take the ground.
Only two access points.
I can still catch him.
If you need to rest,
stay here and I'll...
You seem to think
I want to hear
your opinion soldier?
I don't.
Kid was too green. Never should have
been in any unit. Blew our chance.
He wasn't the one who
rushed us into an ambush.
The situation doesn't determine
the outcome, Lieutenant.
Confidence and skill do.
Unfortunately, your team was
in short abundance of those traits.
Now, make
yourself useful
and set a parameter around
those rocks over there.
You have your orders.
34 degrees F (0C) and dropping.
Private channel opened.
What's the Commander's
condition?
He's suffering from a
plasma wound to his side.
Extreme nerve
damage has been
sustained and his
left lung is teared.
What meds you got him on?
500 cc Strophine and
250 cc of Cryoxin.
I'm surprised he stayed on
his feet as long as he did.
Reduce his medication.
We have a long way
to travel tomorrow
and I am not
gonna carry him.
I'm not sure if
Commander Karza
would agree with
your assessment.
Keep the information off line.
He doesn't need to know.
It is not in my programming
to lie, Lieutenant.
You won't be lying, you just
won't be volunteering any information.
Can you do that?
-Of, course.
Thanks.
Odd.
-What's that?
Of all the soldiers that
I've been assigned to,
you are the only one
that has ever thanked me.
Do you mind it?
-No.
I quite prefer it.
It can get tiresome being
endlessly ordered about.
We have that in
common then.
Your words conflict with
the military directive, Centauri.
So, I've been told.
According to your record
some of your previous
insubordinations
border dangerously close to treason.
-And?
It bodes a question, for why you
have chosen to be a soldier?
Yes it does, doesn't it?
Atmospheric conditioning will
be complete in T minus 10 seconds.
I advise you to keep your
eyes on our objective
instead of me, Lieutenant.
Atmospheric adaptation
is complete.
It is now safe to
remove your helmets.
Why isn't the prisoner
affected by the thin air?
He doesn't have
a life suit.
They can adapt to
almost any conditions.
All this was in the file.
Permission to
speak freely, sir?
Permission? It has
never stopped you before.
Go ahead.
What's this mission really about?
Why is this thing
so important?
Does it matter?
-Yes, it does.
Why?
-I lost my ship and my crew.
I would like to know why.
-You're a soldier.
We both are.
We follow orders.
Without questions.
Tell me what you know
otherwise, I go alone.
Disobeying orders is
treason, soldier.
Punishable by death.
All right. This thing is
the last of it's kind.
We destroyed
it's home world,
and somehow it's figured
a way to return the favour.
So, we'll catch the damn thing
and get it back to base,
or we may not have a
world to go home too.
Now you know
as much as I do.
Does that you make
feel better, soldier?
Or let's sit down and discuss some more
when this thing is gaining ground on us.
You deliberately
kept us in the dark.
You didn't need to know.
-I see.
This mission
was a hero maker.
Everything we know
was at risk.
Are you deaf as
well as stupid?
What level was
this mission?
This discussion is over.
What level was
this mission, sir?
Prio one. Nova class.
-Highest level.
And you was so caught up in your ego
you didn't bother to tell us
how dangerous this creature was.
Your men were incompetent.
Don't blame me
for your mistakes.
You jeopardized this mission.
You got my men killed.
I'm your superior officer
and you will speak
to me as such.
Why?
You don't deserve it.
Come on. Let's see how much
fight you got in you.
You're not worth it.
Clea? What's the
prisoners position?
I have no visual.
Clea?
Come on.
Come on, baby.
Don't leave me out here alone now.
Start-up sequence complete.
Clea 19 series gamma on-line.
Hello, Centauri 7.
Clea.
I thought I lost you there.
-You can't get rid of me
that easily, Centauri.
I've suffered some damage but
seem to be functioning properly.
I'm an early model,
and quite durable.
That's why I keep
you around, babe.
I thought it was my
charming personality.
Clea. What's the prisoner's
current location?
78 clicks and increasing.
Look likes it's just
you and me again.
I'm sorry about
Commander Karza
but if I must
say I'm pleased
that it was you
who survived.
Well, that makes two of us.
Skiptrace prisoner.
200 micro-clicks on
your current location.
Continuing in south-
eastern direction.
On the move again.
I hope you rot in the
bellies of twelve gods, sir.
Prisoner has stopped moving.
It's been moving at a
steady pace for hours.
Hopefully the damn
thing's collapsed.
Without the water source it could
be succumbing to dehydration.
Exactly.
Still...
I'm going in.
Report me any movement.
-Of course.
Be careful, Centauri.
Can you give me a tracer signal?
Got it.
Clear my grid.
What is it, Centauri?
It's the tracking device.
Torn out of it's
own throat.
Very clever.
It can't have gone far.
You can't hide forever!
Do you hear me?
I bringing you in.
Dead or alive.
Centauri?
Are you all right?
Centauri 7?
Please answer.
Clea?
It's been toying with me?
How long have I been out?
Clea?
The head.
I had to kick the head.
Hold on to that.
Hello?
Unknown user,
please identify.
Repeat, identify.
Identify.
Orin Jericho.
Unauthorized user.
Terminating access.
Private channel, opened.
-Clea?
Where are you?
-I'm not sure.
I'm in the possession
of an unauthorized user.
Can you give me a signal of the location?
-Of course.
Got it.
He tried to access me,
but I terminated
the communication.
It spoke to you?
-Yes.
And it understood you.
The damn thing is
smarter than I thought.
Keep that signal going.
Still on the private channel.
I'm on my way.
Clea?
She won't be helping
you any more.
We can't get off
this planet without her.
How do I use her?
-You can't.
And if you harm her,
you'll be stuck on this
floating rock as well.
You've got nowhere to go.
Maybe I don't
plan on going anywhere.
If you wanna die
kill yourself now and
save me the trouble.
What if I want to
take you with me?
Nah. You'd have done that already.
You aren't as dumb
as you look.
What's it that you want?
I know you
can still hear me.
You like playing games?
Well, here's mine.
I know why they
want you brought in.
And I don't care.
I'm gonna hunt you down
and I'm gonna you.
That's my game.
Give up, Cydonian.
You will never catch me.
You've been out-smarted
and out-runned.
Go home.
While you've still got
a home to go back to.
I know something new
I hate about your race.
You don't pack enough water.
Guess it's more
of a human thing.
Always be prepared.
I'm actually surprised you Cydonians
have lasted as long as you have.
Seeing how incompetent you all are.
Now I know why they put
that inhibitor mask on you.
You talk too much.
They didn't want anyone to know
I can speak your language.
They were right.
It's offensive for a
creature like you to
speak the language
of the stars.
Something we picked up from the Drax
-Insects teaching the Apes. It's repugnant.
Drax are noble race.
You wouldn't know
anything about that.
Noble?
They're disease of the galaxy, filthy creatures.
That's funny.
They say the same
thing about you.
Lying bugs.
I tell you this
no one's gonna miss you
guys when you're gone.
Your the race that's extinct,
human, not mine.
Not for long.
Is that so?
-Yap.
I taking you all to hell.
All right, I'll entertain your fantasy, human.
Being that you're the
last of your kind
how do you hope to accomplish
this remarkable feat?
Don't you wanna know why?
-I don't care.
Hah. That's why.
You entered this war
on your own, earthman,
and lost your home world.
Those are the consequences.
-We didn't enter this war.
You attacked us.
You were harbouring Draxian fugitives.
-You mean refugees.
Big difference.
They needed our help.
You chose the wrong side.
No.
It's cost us everything
but we chose the right side.
Now, it's gonna cost
you everything.
We all die.
That's your solution.
How can you be so naive?
Another faction will
rise up in our place.
An endless cycle.
The only way to break it
is to take control from
those in power,
to rule in their stead.
You've thought about this?
-No.
It's just the way it is.
Maybe you are right.
Human.
You have two options.
You can come with
me and survive
or you can join the rest
of your race in oblivion.
It's your decision.
I choose option
number three.
Which is what?
Clea?
Clea? You there?
Centauri 7?
-Yeah, it's me.
Has the human been recaptured?
-No.
Then how did you
retrieve me?
Found you sitting
on the skeleton.
Why he leave you behind?
Odd, that creature is
cunning, dangerously so.
Like he figured something out.
What the twelve hells is he doing?
I'm missing something.
I wonder...
-Wonder what?
Clea?
Centauri, I may know
what the human is doing.
Great, tell me.
It would be better if I didn't.
-Why is that?
If you know it might
influence your actions.
I don't... What?
Do you trust me, Centauri?
-With my life.
Then here's what I
need you to do.
We may have
another problem.
What now?
-I think my former Commander Karza
did more damage to my internal circuits
than I first thought.
What do you mean?
-My battery isn't holding
the power cells charge
very well.
I'm not going to be able
to conserve enough power
to activate your beacon when the
rescue ship arrives.
Shut down the other
systems, draining power.
I have, but two main sources
left for my system's memory
and your medical unit. I'm
afraid you'll have to shut me down
until you need me, Centauri.
That's not happening.
Cut my meds.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Cut them.
Meds unit shutting down.
Your pain receptors
are spiking
and your heart rate is increasing.
-I'm good.
That should give
us enough power
provided the ship
arrives at the designated time.
With our luck, I
wouldn't count on it.
I picking ир communications from orbit.
-Our pick up?
No, these aren't military channels.
An unknown craft is approaching.
Coming down here?
-Yes.
However my system can'ф
track it.
Try to reach them.
No response.
They've gone into
radio silence.
That can't be good.
Maybe some rendezvous
for the human.
Maybe he's not the last one.
Or they could be Draxians.
Great.
Hey!
What?
Money?
Cydonians?
-Ha.
They're paying you.
You are bounty hunter.
That is such an ugly word.
Soldier of fortune
more like it.
Shame they want you be alive, ha!
Just as I thought.
Slyak.
What would a Slyak
be doing here?
Bounty hunter.
Alpha base must have
sent him as back up.
Idiots.
Alpha base or the Slyaks?
-Both.
What you going to do?
He's got my weapons
and my prisoner.
I'm gonna go get them back.
True your kind
build world bomb?
Maybe.
True or lie?
True.
Deserve it they do.
Scare them good you do, ha?
You don't like Cydonians?
-No one like Cydonians.
Invade every planet,
make slaves.
Their way or no way.
If I kill you,
they all die.
No more Cydonians.
-Wait. Remember?
I'm money.
You kill me, no money.
Maybe I take you
to ship first.
Talk with elders.
Good idea.
Smart.
No! This bigger than
money. I be hero.
No more Cydonians.
-No, wait.
You have no business
here, Slyak!
That human is my prisoner.
He's mine.
I don't think so.
Now what?
We wait.
For what?
Extraction.
Ship should be here soon.
What do they
call you, human?
What is your name?
Jericho.
Lieutenant Orin Jericho.
Lieutenant?
We are the same rank.
I'm Centauri 7.
Didn't ask.
Not wise to upset me
considering your
position, human.
No wonder your
kind didn't make it.
No common sense.
-Oh is that the reason?
I thought it was your
genocidal war that did it.
War is war.
You lost.
As long I'm still alive,
the war ain't over.
You never did answer
my question.
How were you going to
destroy my planet?
Are.
-What?
You said were.
Past tense.
It's are.
All right. How are you
going to destroy my planet?
We sent a ship
towards your planet.
Filled to capacity
with nuclear payload.
Once it impacts,
your world is
blown to dust.
Our long range scanners will detect
it far before reaches our atmos...
It's cloacked.
You'll never see it coming.
Another trick we picked
up from the Drax.
So, that's why they
want you alive.
They want to get the ships coordinates out of you.
-They'll try.
But you'll die first.
That's right.
Well, then there's no
reason to keep you alive.
I could kill you right now.
-You could.
But?
-Come on.
Everybody wants
to be a hero.
There's that one glimmer of hope
that you might be able
to save your world.
I told you, I don't care.
They can go to
the twelve hells.
I don't believe you.
Centauri, I have an
incoming transmission.
Patch it through.
Commander Karza,
this is battle ship Aurora.
Do you copy?
-Copy that Aurora.
Commander Karza is dead.
This is Lieutenant Centauri 7
as acting commander.
Copy that, Lieutenant.
We have arrived at the
last known signal point
from Prometheus
before you went down.
Awaiting beacon location.
Clea, activate personal beacon.
Signal initiated.
-Aurora, do you have it?
Affirmative. It's weak but we
should be able to home in on it.
We are now enroute. ETA in 15 minutes.
-Roger that.
Centauri 7 out.
When we get back to Cydonia,
they're gonna torture you.
They'll get the
information they want.
You won't last.
The planet won't even be there
by the time we arrive. -That soon?
And all this?
Just a wild chase to give the
ship the time it needed?
It'll get there long
before we do.
My planet's full of people
that are innocent.
They are not responsible
for the war
or your planet's
destruction.
Our High Council is.
-You all follow blindly.
It's no excuse.
-It's the law.
What's the Gods
have decreed.
Your Gods are telling you
to wipe out entire worlds?
No, we spread our knowledge to
the stars. To surrounding races.
By enslaving and
destroying them?
They don't accept our
way of life, then yes.
You make me sick.
This from a race that couldn't even
defend themselves against each other.
Let alone an invading army.
Only an ignorant species would
war against it's own kind.
Shut up!
You command mass murder
on a galactic scale
and you think
it's holy crusade.
It is our way!
Unless someone
comes along
and takes control
away from them.
Your words, not mine.
That will never happen.
I wonder why.
You are right.
I do care
about my world.
I have wife and
child there.
I would like to
see them again.
Our women don't fight.
They nurture
the children.
Our soldiers
are up there.
As one warrior to another
I respectfully ask that you take
this war to those responsible.
You'll just be killing
women and children.
Is that what you want the
legacy of your kind to be?
Vega sector, gamma quadrant.
Is that...
-It's where the ship is.
Call your people. I'll give
them the coordinates.
You better hurry. You
don't have much time.
Clea? Patch me
through to Alpha base.
Transmitting.
Alpha base, this is Lieutenant
Centauri 7. Do you copy?
Copy Lieutenant.
What is your status?
Prisoner is in custody and
willing to give the
coordinates of the bomb ship.
Lieutenant, we are ready for
the prisoners information.
Please, relay
it immediately.
What's the coordinates?
-No.
I want to be the
one who tells them.
The coordinates are 22...
-Unauthorized user.
Clea, authorize the human.
State your name.
-Orin Jericho.
Orin Jericho is now authorized.
The coordinates are
229, 713, 040 bearing 2-6-0.
Vega sector, gamma quadrant.
It's an M-class
star freighter.
We have confirmation.
Craft has been identified.
Sending battle ships to intercept.
-We found it.
Well done, Lieutenant.
We no longer have
need of the prisoner.
You may terminate
at will.
Roger that.
Centauri 7 out.
They want me to
terminate you.
I saved your world.
Your family.
Not really.
I don't have any
wife and children.
That's good. Then you won't
have anything to worry about
when your planet is
blown to bits.
You didn't think
I'd give you
the real coordinates,
did you?
But we have confirmation
on the craft.
It's a decoy,
you idiot.
Unmanned. There is nothing
but salvage on that ship.
You can't stop this.
It's already over.
Superior race, huh?
Let me give you
some advice, alien.
Never let your weapon fall
into the hand of your enemy.
I'm gonna let you know
a little secret.
We never launched
the bomb ship.
We couldn't.
We had no idea
where Cydonia was.
But now that I'm authorized
to access you database,
she's gonna tell me
everything I need to know.
You think I forced us to crash
down here by accident?
You wanted the bomb ship?
I led you right to it.
Now, you're gonna learn
what it feels like
to be the last of your kind.
You want to know the
difference between you and me?
I did have a wife and
son back on the Earth.
Centauri 7, this
is the Aurora.
We have just cleared
the way
and entered the atmosphere.
Shuttle craft it's on it's
way down. Stand by.
Centauri 7, this is
Commander Chane
of the Aurora
landing party.
We're on the ground.
What is your status?
Centauri 7, are you picking
up my transmission?
Centauri 7,
do you copy?
The only one
that made it, ha?
You look like hell.
Must have been a rough one.
We'll get you to the
infirmary right away.
Clea, upload the
coordinates to Cydonia
to the ship's nav computer.
Clea.
Clea, I command
you to respond.
Son of a bitch.
Alpha base. This is
Omicron series 5.
Commander Chane is
no longer responsive.
Start-up sequence complete.
Clea 19 series gamma on-line.
Hello, Centauri 7.
-Hello, Clea.
It's good to have you back.
I take it by
my new casing
that you followed
my instructions.
Well played. It
was you he was after.
Centauri, I have an incoming
transmission from Alpha base.
Patch it through.
Lieutenant, this
is Alpha base.
What the twelve hells
is going on down there?
If I were you,
I'd be more concerned about
what's going on up there.
Centauri 7, you
are under orders.
What is the status
of the human?
Find another grunt to
do your dirty work.
Centauri 7 out.
End of transmission.
Whatever you're planning
to do, Centauri,
I suggest you to
do it quickly.
It won't be long before
the human traces
the source of that
signal back to Cydonia.
He already has.
Isn't that right, earthman?
You didn't shoot. Why?
Same reason you
didn't kill me.
Yeah, what's that?
I'll tell you
when I see you.
And just how are we supposed
to get out of here?
Bounty hunter ship has to
be around here somewhere.
You realize we'll be breaking
26 High Council's laws
by taking this
course of action.
Is that a problem?
-Not at all.
Let's get the twelve
hells off this rock.
Major rewrite by Punar, 2014. (ty Punar!)
Corrections by pkz, 2015.
Unknown original author (Bad english, not making sense).
Major rewrite by Punar, 2014. (ty Punar!)
More corrections on top of Punar's rewrite by pkz 2015.
Hope you enjoy!