I was a bit tense.
Will they let us do it again?
We'll do it as often as we like.
Adrien, finish in the visitor's room
in 5 minutes.
I love you.
In spite of the aggro
that's brought you?
That'll all soon be over.
Amélie drew this for you.
This how she see's us.
When you get out...
So, was it good?
The next time we'll make it a 3...
or a 4.
What's the big idea?.
You wanna leave here
in a coffin?
So what?
Makes more for you.
You know where
the goddamn cash is.
Is it safe?
I can put some buddies
on the job.
They'll guard it
'til we get out.
I wouldn't trust
any buddies of yours.
Yeah!
And any reason why I
should trust YOU?
That's a nice drawing.
Is it your daughter's?
I didn't think
we were on speaking terms.
It was good like that.
You know...
...there's not much nice
in the world.
You gotta hang on to it.
Come on you two,
out!
Time for a walk
Why I would go out today?
Nice weather.
You know the risk
I'd be taking.
You didn't have to assault that girl.
I did NOT do it.
Yeah...I was forgetting.
And I s'pose your stickups
were done by your twin brother.
Or you wanted to pay for
your sick mother's operation.
Can I go now?
OK you scum...
move it!
Everyone here?
Let's go!
[Speaking Russian]
Isn't your rock-spider pal coming?
Scared, is he?
He's saying...
I don't give a fuck
what apes say.
Translate that!
I'm innocent.
I know I'll be cleared eventually.
I've got to survive
in this rat-hole.
I'm called a rock-spider.
They want me dead.
I continue praying my ordeal
will come to an end.
You sure?
You get out.
Without making touble.
If you don't wanna cop shit...
...then scram.
Don't you move.
What do you want?
As you don't go out,
we've come to
pay you a visit.
[Russian]
You hear...repeat it.
"Spasiba."
Go on...repeat it.
Spasiba.
That means thank you.
You'll repeat it.
Understood?
We'll see if the little girls
get you excited now.
That's enough.
Qu'est-ce tu veux?.
We better go down
before there's serious shit.
That's enough...stop!
Shut up...get out!
You shouldn't've
got involved.
6 months more.
Because you defended him.
That's not what
the report says.
The employment agency's
got nothing for me.
I can't afford the nanny.
I can't afford
the speech therapist.
And we've got all
that money.
Do you realise that
this guy Franck Adrien,
went into hiding near our place
after his stick-up.
In Nièvre.
He's been put with me
to protect me.
I'm there to protect you.
That's true.
Why don't you tell me
where you've hidden it?
I'd just take what we need.
Trust me for once.
The reason I'm here's
because I was trusting.
I don't get to sleep.
Every other day,
they forget my medication.
The lawyer's going to see
what he can do.
You believe I'm going
to get out of this?
Of course.
Her mother said to the judge
that she'd invented everything.
He's going to question her
and she's going to crack.
You're getting out...
it's going to happen.
You'll give me a child.
You didn't need to
bring her in here.
This is no place for her.
She wanted to come.
What'd she say?
She wanted to see her father.
While I'm in here
I'm not her father.
I don't want her to see me
as a convict.
I'm sorry, Franck.
We miss you so.
I miss both of you, too.
Amélie, you'll fall over.
Careful!
What a cutie!
What's your name?
She can't reply.
She has speaking problems.
She's going to
learn to speak.
It'll take time.
She may be right
to take her time.
Say goodbye.
'Bye, Amélie.
You make a move
and you're a vegetable.
You wanna kill me, Novick?
Don't you wanna get your dough?
Exactly...the Russki won't miss you.
I wanna know
where the cash's stashed.
So my buddies
can take care of it.
Look, they're not far away.
You've got nothing to say?
Go fuck yourself.
Cough up!
You know Marco's hideout
I'm listening.
It is under the false floor.
G'day, Franck.
How long've I been here?
4 days.
And Novick?
In solitary.
He only got a week.
So he get's out in 3 days...
gotta get outta here quick.
You're worried
about your cash?
Whadda you talking about?
The reason you're in here.
Novick want's to pinch it.
Do you want any help?
How?
I'm getting out!
The girl's retracted her story.
She made it all up
from A to Z.
There won't even
be a new trial.
I want to give you
my phone number.
Call when you get out.
This is not
a good idea.
Why?
I won't forget
what you did.
Let me help you.
I don't owe you anything.
Yes, that's quite right.
You're right.
OK.
Cheers.
Call me.
There's something
you could do.
it's...
call my wife.
Tell her I'm well and that
Novick's watching her.
And then also,
she should see my father,
he'll help her.
Could you do that for me?
Sure,
you can trust me.
Nothing's changed.
We even tidied your cell.
Novick's out?
He said you wanted
to take his share.
He wanted to kill you.
He's been transferred to Fresnes.
Happy?
Cigarettes?
I been waiting 3 days.
Adrien.
Visitors room.
You can feel the evil in here.
The colour-scheme
doesn't help.
Nobody made you come.
Manuel Carrega,
constabulary captain.
Has something
happened to Anna?
Anna?
I've got questions regarding
Jean-Louis Maurel.
Maurel?.
He shared your cell.
You know he was accused of raping
a little girl?
Everyone knew about it.
He's been found innocent.
What did he tell you
about his life?
I wasn't interested.
He told me he was from Nevers,
I've lived there and we talked a bit about it.
He mention any places,
people?
What are you on about?
I'm not on about him...
but I am about his next victims.
Wadsn't he the victim?
Legally, yes.
Do I trust
what he's capable of?
Didn't the girl
retract her story?
Maurel's wife
managed to get to her.
You haven't charged her?
I'm looking for proof.
I need your testimony.
What have you seen
or heard while you
were with him?
He seemed quite normal.
He's a manipulator.
He's cunning.
He's fooled more than one person.
He hasn't fooled me.
20 years ago I came to France
for a woman.
She'd left a guy
who beat her up.
I warned that her ex
was dangerous.
For nothing.
He set fire to
where we lived.
She's dead.
I've survived.
I've escaped death
to help save others.
If anything else
comes back to you.
And if you'd just come
from the asylum?
Believe me...
I'm not the mad one.
The answering machine contains
too many messages.
Please try again later.
Goodbye.
Come on.
I'm taking you to the meeting.
He had to come
Were are you going?
Not far.
He'll pay double.
Cinderella following Big Sister, out.
Waiting for Prince Charming.
We'll follow and join up.
OK
Is it far?
It's here.
You want to stay?
It's him who says what
he wants.
She's perfect.
You can leave us.
Will I move?
We don't know if it's him.
What's she doing?
She's confirming.
Let me do it.
You start undressing first.
Your turn.
I'm thirsty.
Could I get a glass
of water?
It's Costa, go!
We've got him, boys!
Don't move!
Go, go!
Turn over, you fuck!
I wanna see your hands!
Move it!
All OK?
He's in the bag.
The Corsican was right.
You were perfect.
Come on,
get a move on.
You stay there.
Nico,
a bit of privacy.
[Russian]
I'm not translating.
Vous êtes 3!
Franck.
I can fix everything.
Nico!
Let me out!
They're going to kill me!
Nico, open the door!
I'll kill you, you fucker!
Nico!
Shit.
Ça va, chef?.
2 more.
The Costas'll spend Christmas
in the clink.
Hang on...
René's more cunning.
We'll need to be more cunning
to catch him..
Exactly.
Has The Holy Ghost
finished with your cover?
He wants Claire downstairs.
And whadda YOU want?
Couldn't ask for more.
The prisoner
who got out
dressed as a guard.
Franck Adrien, in
for the bank
stickup.
I know.
So?
He had 2 months to go.
He's not ready.
He's going to make
the usual mistakes
getting back the hidden loot.
Anyone can catch him.
I'm staying on the Costas.
The boss wants the best.
The troop that's just had
3 major convictions...
you and your team.
If it's so simple,
you'll be back with the Costas
in no time.
Thank you, monsieur.
That's OK.
Would you know
where to find the eggs?
They're at the end, through there.
Would it be too much to ask
to come with me?
I always get lost
with all these aisles.
Yes, follow me.
- Melissa!
I'm waiting for you.
Sorry, gotta go.
Doesn't matter,
I'll find them myself.
The man thwarted the security checks.
Franck Adrien, convicted
for the holdup of the Savings Bank
didn't have more than 8 months of prison left.
He may be armed and
is considered dangerous.
Got it...
au revoir, monsieur.
D'you think
he'll understand?
Nothing to worry about.
The police have good info, now.
Christine,
we knew he'd get out
one day.
i've got everything worked out.
He doesn't know what's waiting for him.
Trust me.
Nobody's going to take our
happiness away.
She's sleeping?
She looks so adorable
like that.
Thanks for giving her to me.
He's got very few connections.
He avoids his relations.
His wife?
Yeah.
Anna Martens.
She used to visit him.
She's unemployed,
takes care of the kid.
The address she gave
is phony.
And his accomplices?
Guests of the state.
Jérôme Novick
was at Mérancourt.
It wasn't a great  love affair.
He attacked Adrien
with a screwdriver.
Nice boy.
I'm going to question him.
How much did they get?
2 million.
2 million!
We've only got back pocket money.
He's going to want
to get the money back.
Watch the places he knows.
Houses, bars.
His picture's
everywhere.
I've asked for
his visiting room videos.
Ça, c'est quoi?.
Those who could've seen him
in their area.
100 calls.
Dobbing-in's a national sport.
Has the media spoken to Anna?
No.
We got an address for Anna
in the suburbs.
Who's he?
Anna?.
Hey, watch where you're going!
What's going on?
Turn them out!
Nobody leaves.
Are you staying here?
No, I'm covering you.
Police, step aside.
Out of the way!
That's it.
Police, open up!
No one!
Come here.
Look.
We just missed him.
Marco!
Coming!
He's not far away.
We need reinforcements,
He's in the area.
With luick, we'll be back
in an hour.
Avec de la chance, dans une heure, on est rentrés.
Don't move!
Don't you move.
Let me past.
Of course!
Anything else?
I can't go back to prison
now.
Don't move!
I've learnt something
very important.
You can't shoot,
I'm not threatening you
You can see
I'm unarmed
Adrien is on the street.
Warn everyone!
There he is!
Stop him!
You OK?
Close the next station!
If the train stops
he'll get off.
Is he crazy?
Divide up the zone
and set up road blocks.
I know,
good...thanks.
He's probably already far away.
Here...
...yours?
He's crazy.
Something's driving him.
Something really strong.
"Anna, wherever you are,
I'll find you."
She's cleared off
with the cash.
Two for the price of one?
Yeah, that'll make
The Holy Ghost happy.
Yes?
Why did you do it?
Franck, I knew
you'd call.
How are you?
Tell me,
why did you do it?
Why did you kill her?
It was all her fault.
Thank God...
I know how to read people.
Your wife was unreliable.
She would have
given you problems.
I chose to save you
from all that.
What've you done
with Amélie?
What've you done with
my little daughter?
Where is she, Maurel?
Have you killed her?
She's a lovely little thing.
I love her very much.
I shan't do her
any harm at all.
Unless you try
to find me.
What is it?
He wants us to grab Adrien
on his return.
He's in Corsica.
I'd love to go down
to Corsica.
Anna's scrap of paper?
Amélie's drawings.
Naïve style endowed with a certain potential.
Letters for her guy
that she hadn't sent.
Love letters.
"I understand your gesture.
It's a proof of love."
The stickup.
Why hadn't she posted
this deathless prose?
To be read in prison?
Not on.
They aren't the words
of a woman stabbing
someone in the back.
And Novick?
A heap of new insults.
It's a put-up job between
Adrien and his chick.
We know the addresses
he's given,
except for this one.
Le Pré-sur-Lamure?
What's that?
Their hide-out
after the bank job.
Martin, go round!
What's this?
What's this bullshit?
[Russian]
No thanks.
Are your reinforcements coming?
They're coming.
The policeman's refrain.
Are we gonna find the loot?
If it's not already gone.
What's that?
Why've you come?
It's nothing to do with your daughter.
What would you know?
Best you go home.
We should be Corsican.
There's something here!
Capitain, come here.
Stay there.
Look.
Robert, no!
Pull him back!
Nobody touch anything.
It was his daughter?
Yeah. Julie.
Disappeared. He'd been hoping
she was just a runaway.
The guy who did that
is a monster.
Is it one of Adrien's victims?
No way that it fits Adrien's profile.
He has a wife
and a disabled child.
That doesn't fit with a killer
There are always exceptions.
There are some connections.
He was living in the area when
Julie disappeared.
We found his DNA
on the map and the jacket.
That's not all.
What else?
There are 2 other maps
of areas way up in the mountains.
Maybe we'll find
other bodies.
We're not going to get
carried away
If it's a serial killer,
they'll want to bring in the Feds.
They'd want the file.
We have to get him now.
Listen, Claire.
They don't teach this
at police school,
but next time, this guy
doesn't get to get away.
Understood?
Quite understood.
Have a good day.
I don't want to hurt  you.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
You're going to help me
find Maurel.
Where are your guns?
I don't have any.
Don't take me for an idiot,
where are they?
They're there.
In the cupboard.
Go.
He always lived
in the area.
I met him 5 years ago.
I questioned him about
a girl from Dijon.
Sylvie Desmée.
He'd been seen
talking to her.
I smelled a rat.
Maurel raised
too many questions.
He lied about details.
I sensed that he was
playing with me.
He was a bad one.
The girl was never found...
no body, no proof.
There were the other
disappearances.
The resemblance is striking.
It's been admitted
that it was a serial killer.
But a cop investigates facts,
not potential suspects.
You've gone ahead anyway?
Quietly. Got nowhere for a long time.
He was invisible.
No record, town hall official, liked by all.
He was never far away
when the disappearances occurred.
Finally,
2 bodies were found
a month apart.
I brought Maurel in,
but his DNA didn't match.
For the second time,
he trapped us.
His sperm sample was at the station,
Next day it'd disappeared.
I was suspected.
At the same time,
he brought a complaint against me
for harassment.
I was dismissed.
I'm not allowed
to live near him.
You're no longer
in the constabulary?
No, I lied to you.
I investigate privately.
Bugger! I was hoping
you'd be able to help me.
The little girl's 5.
She doesn't look like these girls...
Could he harm her?
She's not his normal victim type.
If he wanted to have a good time,
he wouldn't hesitate.
I've got the phone number.
An old constabulary captain's
maybe got some contacts?
Want a snort?
[Russian] - Thanks!
It's good stuff.
The paper?
You know him?
The constabulary have
found 2 more bodies.
Sylvie Desmée and Karine
Garcia, reported missing.
This is a serial killer for sure!
Thanks , I'm on it.
A truck driver dropped Adrien
at Luzon, in Nièvre.
You coming?
Yeah, coming.
I've come to see Bourgoin.
You got a serial killer for 'im?
Bourgoin,
Luzon Constabulary office.
I need information
on a suspect's number.
It's me.
You got something?
The line's been dead
for 48 hours.
He used it 12 times.
The last time was to
Pré-sur-Lamure.
One of my hideouts.
What else?
Several calls
to the Alpes-Maritimes region.
Where in Alpes-Maritimes?
There's an area of 40 k's
around a  village.
Chasseignes.
That's maybe where he's living.
He takes a medication,
Xyrex.
He was jumpy
when he didn't get it.
Is there a pharmacy
in Chasseignes?
There are the cops everywhere.
You reported me?
No I didn't.
Where's your gun?
A gun's against regu...
Stuff your regulations.
I wouldn't need
to depend on you.
Carrega?.
How come you're here?
I was looking for Bourgoin.
He's directing the search.
The search?
The fugitive's been reported
in the area.
He may have killed
3 young girls.
What do you mean?
Including Sylvie Desmée.
You remember her.
I'm going to give you a hand.
Carrega... you forgotten
you don't work here any more?
Take the lane.
We're taking the lane
with the tall hedges.
Your guns,
over the hedge.
Hurry up!
Go on!
On the ground!
Stay down or...
Or you'll strangle me
like the others?
What are you talking about?
Sylvie Desmée, Karine Garcia,
they ring a bell?
What are you talking about?
Your DNA on the maps
in your old hideout.
HQ to Bravo 2.
Put me on to Capitain Linée.
Bugger!
He's fucked you
like he's fucked me.
Stop!
All units!
Stop him!
Get in!
Bugger, there he is!
Stop!
You OK?
They believe
it's you...
I know.
Who do YOU think it is?
Maurel, as I've always known.
Chasseignes's 600 km.
There's one pharmacy.
There's the address.
Bugger!
They've been warned.
Hang on!
Stop!
Jump out!
Don't worry,
he's gotta be stopped!
Think about your daughter,
jump!
The injured man is in intensive care
at Auxerre hospital.
Condition serious.
They used to think he was crazy.
Now they're upset.
Not my problem.
Got Adrien?
No. On and on it goes.
Tell me,
how did he make Carrega
smash through a road-block?
Believe me,
he's very persuasive.
For you, eh?
All looks very nice and expensive.
This isn't a parade!
You had him!
It's just a matter of time.
There's no time left!
The constabulary's furious.
We've allowed a killer
to escape.
I'm responsible.
I'm in charge.
A bit of criminal analysis
'd do you good.
Commander...
Why did you spare him?
I'm not sure he's the one
who killed them.
I beg your pardon?
He could have shot me.
It doesn't add up.
You put in a report
based on woman's intuition.
I'm going to try and get Adrien...
...and not miss him.
Cut off between D981
and D18 in the Beuch forest.
Received, Delta 3.
Block off the intersection
of Rue de l'étang
and D981...
On D18...
No sign of suspect.
Suspect has escaped area.
Christine,
I've never been so happy.
Me too.
It's hard for me to stop
thinking about that guy.
His face is plastered everywhere.
The police'll get him.
Look.
France's Most Wanted.
Come on.
I'm going to buy you a dress.
Here's a beautiful dress!
You like it?
You'll try it on?
You'll be a real princess.
My goodmess, you're so beautiful!
Jean-Louis!
Isn't she beautiful with this?
Jean-Louis?.
No, Jean-Louis.
I told you, Christine.
I gave you the little girl.
It's too risky.
The little girl is too.
You saw how she was
looking at the newspapers?
You got nothing new,
whatta you stuffing 'round with?
I'm matching Adrien's movements
with his supposed crimes.
Supposed?
You think that we're
pinning these murders on him?
He thinks so.
He said: "He's fucked me."
Who was he talking about?
I know it's someone
we should be looking for.
Can you help me?
I should be out on the job.
Please!
Alright..No!
Don't wanna know about it!
You're a pain in the neck.
Go back to Paris. Shit!
Excuse me.
Can you help me?
We're looking for
a doctor....
Our daughter's sick.
She has a stomach ache.
There's Dr Berlot.
He's further on, in Verneuil.
You need to kep to the right and...
Coukld you show us perhaps?
I have to get back.
We'll take you home
afterwards.
You'd be a great help.
Hullo.
My wife's worried
it could be serious.
Alright then.
Get in the front.
It's easier.
Let me take that.
I'll mind it.
Thanks.
We all belt up
in my car.
This is very nice of you.
How old are you?
That's it then.
At 16,
girls are still very nice.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
It's there on the right.
No, we'd rather
keep going to the right.
That doesn't bother you?
I was talking about,
whether you had a boyfriend?
Yes.
What's that got
to do with anything?
It doesn't concern you.
I want to get out.
What are you doing?
Leave me alone!
Help!
What are you up to?
I love you.
Will they let us do it again?
An envelope for you.
From Paris.
Thanks
I was waiting for it.
It's him.
What about it?
He's been to see Adrien
in prison.
Are you saying that...
They'd already met.
Hadn't you realised that?
They've taken ages
to send this stuff.
Carrega used an alias
to see Adrien.
Olivier Desmée.
One of Adrien's victims was
Sylvie Desmée.
Carrega was obsessed with
the case.
He claimed to know
the identity of the killer.
Adrien?
So, some miserable wretch...
Named what?
He was quetioned.
What was his name again...?
Yeah... Maurel!
That's it,
Jean-Louis Maurel.
Here we are!
Had some work done here...
And there
Careful.
Attention.
Ideal for a family.
Rent's not high.
The owner's keen.
All this'll be removed.
An address?
You aren't on the job.
If Lucciani finds out...
Give me the address.
Maurel rented a house
in the Alpes-Maritimes
2 weeks after he got out.
He pays through a Swiss bank
in Lausanne
Are you going to give me
the address?
You're not planning on
going there?
I'm very late.
Jean-Jacques, I know.
I'll get the ball rolling.
Let's go!
Everybody hungry?
I told him.
That's him for sure.
He strangled those girls?
A woman has a daughter
who disappeared yesterday.
Girl aged 16.
That's her.
See you soon.
Next time at our place.
Return match.
Take care.
Jean-Louis Maurel?
That's me.
Claire Linné,
I'm looking for Franck Adrien.
That's someone
I'd rather forget.
May I come in?
Certainly.
This is my wife,
Christine.
My little sweetie-pie.
It's Daddy.
I think I've told you everything.
He hasn't been
in touch with you?
If he had, I would've
called the police.
I was the victim
of a judicial mistake.
I wouldn't want to
help a criminal.
Is it true what
was reported?
The enquiry's underway,
madame.
Look carefully.
Is this the man that was at
the supermarket.
I don't think so.
What is it
I'm fed up, Alex.
Claire...
Claire inquired about
Jean-Louis Maurel.
Woman's intuition?
Maurel lives 20km from here.
What?
She's gone there.
Call her.
She's not contactable.
Should we go there?
I wish I could've
been more help.
Don't hesitate to call.
Will do.
So happy
to see you here.
I've missed you.
How did you find
our little nest?
It's cosy.
Thanks to you, Franck.
I'll never be able to
thank you enough.
You're my guardian angel.
He's got Amélie.
Trust me...he'll give her
back to us.
You know, Franck,
nobody understands
what I'm looking for.
Nobody.
Filthy scum!
It's all over, now.
We're all back together.
The whole family.
Not in front of her.
Drop your gun!
I said
drop your gun!
He's here...I've got him.
He wanted to kill us!
Don't move!
Jean-Louis!
Get him!
he's got Amélie!
The cop?
I'll fix that.
Stop here.
You go on,
I'll take a look.
Would you like to walk on ahead, Amélie?
Don't go near the edge.
Stay close to Daddy.
You OK, Franck?
Maurel.
Maurel!
Don't move.
Drop your gun!
I've got the fugitive.
He's down there.
Maurel!
Help's coming.
Franck.
it's all over,
Amélie's safe.
Cri de douleur
There's extenuating circumstances.
Trust me.
I can't trust anyone.
It'll be the last time.
Who fired? You bastard!
It came from over there!
Drop it you bastard!
Drop your gun!
Don't move!
Raise your hands.
In the air!
Don't move!
take it easy.
Look along here.
That's it, thanks.
I'm here.
You OK?
Yes, thanks.
We've got Maurel.
Adrien's body must have gone further.
We'll find it.
You know, Claire...
No better.
Maurel's wife's
spilled the beans.
He was doing all the killing
and raping.  Not Adrien.
She's admitted 8 murders,
but there's others.
Without Adrien,
there would have been more.
Go and tell him.
And say what?
I lack your woman's
intuition.
Thank you, Claire.
I tried to aim
for once
Three months later
She's solitary,
but she's hanging in there.
She's working better
with the speech therapist.
She's happy
when you come to see her.
You told me to tell you
about any mail.
She got a letter.
I have a photocopy.
From Morocco?
Just this, no words?
No, since she got the letter,
she's seemed happier.
Do you know who it's from?
Papa.
...
Subtitles:
FatPlank / RLB