David!
Dad!
I'm here. Come quickly.
Where are you?
Come here.
- I'm here, I'm here!
- Where are you, Dad? Dad!
- What happened?
- Damn, the shoulder!
I'm sorry.
Your damn dog woke me up.
He was barking like mad.
- Can you stand up?
- Yeah.
- I don't know what's got into them.
- Who? What are you talking about?
Do not move ...
Wait, wait ...
Oh, shit!
How long have you had that?
What?
That? That's nothing.
It's just my eczema.
It's been itching for a few days
but it's nothing serious.
What makes you say it's eczema?
Is that the tone you used
to persuade Claire to move into town?
Come on!
Oh, shit!
What is this?
Chemical burns!
How could I have got them?
That's what the tests will tell us.
How is my grandfather?
I think he knows
we're sleeping together.
He's well enough to tell me off
about taking you with me.
You should have that cleaned.
Don't you want to tell them
before we leave?
I don't want them to think
that's why I'm going.
Isn't it?
What's your father doing
in your mother's car?
Yes.
Yes, but no!
Tell him I don't care
if his mother is in hospital.
I want her at the factory
on Monday morning at eight.
Yes.
Marie ...
Is Claire the only one
who knows about the fertiliser?
Do not worry, go!
I like your father too much
to reveal to him what you're like.
- Do you understand what you did?
- I will find a solution!
You no longer have a choice!
- Dad!
- Do you think that it does not concern you?
Well, go there!
Why has he brought her back here again?
Do not worry. She can not do anything,
as long as we stay in our land!
She'd better not.
You can't miss a beast like this one.
No, Look at this!
It must weigh at least 250kg.
And this one's for me.
What are we doing?
Shall we take a look at the fence?
No, we'll go to the cabin first.
Then we'll go and look at the lake.
I'm warning you, David.
I'm a proper hunter.
- Surely you're not going to use that?
No, thank you!
- Look at it. It's a beauty.
Nathan, fancy a hunting session
before shutting yourself away in town?
She's waiting for you if you want to go there.
Oh, shit!
It's okay, take off your phone!
Yeah?
No.
No, it's all sorted.
What's in that file?
What happened this morning, puts everything into question.
I do not wanna let you go hunting.
Do you think that it is in your power?
This forest belongs to us.
If you go, you'll ruin my restriction policy.
If word's got out, that is.
What are you doing?
I'm coming with you.
Why don't you stay at the factory
rather than pissing on my patch?
Until further notice.
you'll be living off that factory.
- Hey!
- Hey, let's calm down!
Nicolas rights.
We need all the help we can get to catch that beast.
And our child?
I just need six more months.
You've been needing six more months for four years.
Don't start!
Whenever we do anything together.
you two have to argue.
I do not know ...
What with the work at the lab...
We can always have one later on.
Does your father realise
what he's asking you to do?
Does he have any idea
what it's costing us?
What do you want me to say?
Eric?
Your offer is still valid?
Yes!
What are you gonna do?
If you won't talk to your father.
I will.
I forbid you to do that.
Why do you think I got transferred?
I'm sick of your family
and the fertilisers and chemicals
you build your empire on.
I've kept quiet all these years.
letting him manipulate you.
Not this time.
Nathan ...
Nathan!
Make your mind up.
Are you coming or not?
Leave him alone, David!
I'm glad you're coming with us, Nathan.
OK ...
Now we need to find the others.
- Are you OK?
Not really ...
Damn ...
Well, Move!
Why are you bothering with that?
You can never get it started.
When it was in working order.
I could.
When did we last come here?
Before your mother died.
Nice one, little brother.
You never miss a trick, do you?
Get out of the way.
Asshole!
Damn!
Damn it ...
Damn! shit!
Damn it!
For fuck's sake!
- Want a hand, Dad?
- No, I'm fine. Leave it.
Here. The rifles seem fine.
Thank you, Dad.
Dad, we won't get far with that calibre.
It's not the calibre
that makes the hunter.
We'll leave our mobiles here.
We don't want any more hassle
from the factory.
You can keep yours on you...
But turn it off!
Here, put this on.
It will stop you getting shot.
I thought you wore camouflage to go hunting.
Not with wild boar.
You sniff them out.
Here, you'll be needing this too.
Push back the catch
to finish loading it.
It's not easy when you're left-handed
Dad, have a word with David.
He wants to shoot it on his own.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Just keep an eye out for tracks.
- Did she say what was in the file?
- What??
Claire. Did she tell you
why she wasn't coming?
Just the usual.
Market pressures,
a competitor stirring up trouble.
You're giving your daughter
six months to come up with a formula.
- It's a family thing.
- It's your heritage that's at stake.
I couldn't let her go.
It's nothing personal.
It's just...
She's pregnant!
We were choosing names this morning.
Well?
It's not as if you can't
have them later on.
Like I said, now is not the time.
Don't talk nonsense.
Business has never been better.
Is that it? Aren't things going
as well as you claim?
What?
Does your father know?
What have you told him
about the family business you run?
How can you justify Claire staying...?
Listen to me, you fool ...
Some things are beyond you.
If you say anything to my father...
Fuck off! I'll stop at nothing
to keep her with me.
Is that right?
Yeah?
Do you think she will forgive you?
Do not you understand?
What's your opinion - nothing against our!
Try your luck with my father
and you'll see.
Go on, then.
OK.
We're going hunting and you're going
to keep your fucking mouth shut
Is that the one?
Maybe!
It's nearby.
Get ready to fire.
Go.
Get down.
Hush ...
Be quiet, sit quietly ....
Do not question!
He listens to you!
Only you can omit it!
I've been tracking it all this time
so I should shoot.
You can not even approach him.
You two, surround him, one on each side.
Good!
Pull it back. Easier said than done!
How does this thing work?
Damn!
Nathan!
Drive it, damn you!
Hell, they got me.
Shoot, Nathan! For fuck's sake, shoot!
Damn ...
I knew we needed a higher calibre.
Why didn't you load your gun?
Why did you come
if you weren't going to shoot?
It's been hit.
There's blood pouring out everywhere.
OK.
Quiet, quiet!
Be careful.
We're going to have to smoke it out.
Quiet!
Nico, help me.
Come on!
Oh, hell!
Damn, this can not be ....
I don't believe it.
Maybe it's already dead.
The smell would have been different.
- Oh, NO! No, no, no!
- What happened to him?
Dad, wait. Be careful.
Do not come too close!
This bastard lair has two entrances.
- Dad ...
- Eric, okay?
Aa, go away!
Dad, tell me.
- A higher calibre, eh?
- Everything will be alright, everything will be fine.
- At least I will have beaten your record!
- It's not the one we're after.
- How do you know?
This one has all its teeth.
Look at this.
It's been attacked, too.
It's covered in bites.
Here and here!
Well, what? what happened?
- Nathan, come, look, Nathan!
- What is it?
Such as?
Tell me they're not the same burns.
It must have rubbed itself
against the tree until it bled.
It says a lot.
They rub up against trees to get rid
of any parasites from the wallow.
The wallow?
Eric, do your burns itch
before or after you shower?
After!
David ... give me your knife.
What are you doing?
If it's the water,
we're about to find out.
Oh ... you bastard.
Oh!
Unbelievable!
Where's the lake
you mentioned earlier, Eric?
Tell me, Nathan ...
I have the same marks as the boar.
Does that mean I'm rotten inside too?
- That depends.
- On what?
Have you had any stomach pains recently?
Wait. Can it be cured? Well?
It's getting dark and it's raining.
We should turn back.
Use your torch if you're still scared of the dark.
How many water towers like yours
are there in this forest?
Enough to supply all the taps
in the region.
Give me your phone, Nathan!
I'll call Marie
so she can inform the health board.
I think she already knows.
A health report that ended up
on your ex-wife's desk?
Is that why Claire has to stay
another six months?
We had no choice!
We?
He needed a chemist
to modify the fertiliser.
You've involved Claire in this?
I had to make the fertiliser
more competitive.
Competitive?
Jesus, Nicolas, you've made
your bloody fertiliser so toxic.
it's got into the ground water.
What are you complaining about? You enjoyed it!
Would you rather have lost everything?
The farm, the factory, the land? ...
- What you left me was shit, Dad.
Nicolas, listen to me!
Your factory, your formulas -
it was all shit.
If I hadn't got my ass into gear,
we'd have nothing at all.
Is that how you convinced
your daughter to help you?
I've already told you,
she puts her family first.
You bastard.
Enough!
Dad! Dad!
Dad, come and look at this. Quickly.
Call Marie!
Tell her that's the end of your schemes!
Oh God, no ...
This is unbelievable.
That one was pregnant
when she ate this shit.
Oh, my God!
She must have been breast-feeding
for a while.
Her tits are still swollen.
She still has traces of our products
in her mouth.
Oh, my God!
It's okay, Eric?
All right, thank you!
What is this?
- It's what chased the stags from the forest.
- What?
The rest of the pack.
Damn.
Prepare to shoot.
Switch that fucking thing off.
Dad!
- Dad!
- Shoot!
Damn!
Kill him, kill him!
- Do not be!
Nicolas!
Everything will be fine.
Dad!
Do not go there! Stay on the spot!
- Let me go!
- No!
- Go!
- Leave me alone, I say the same!
- Too late!
- Let me go!
Go to the trees!
Nicolas!
Faster, faster!
Hurry, they're coming.
Give me your hand!
I'm sorry, David.
I panicked!
David, I did not want.
Drool Stop, stop!
David, no.
Did you think you'd just run away, you bastard?
You're going to pay for this.
I'm going to kill you.
- Stop messing about.
- Don't you dare pull a gun on me
I'll kill you, you dirty bastard!
David, stop!
Hell, David, stop!
David, that's enough!
Stop it!
Damn it, stop!
Please, David, stop!
Stop it!
David, stop!
Stop it, David, stop!
No!
No, no!
David, David!
David ...
Oh, shit!
My brother?
He's dead.
- The fall broke his neck.
- I'm sorry, Nathan.
That should stop the haemorrhaging.
That's your mobile.
It's still in my jacket pocket.
I'm sure it's Claire.
She called earlier.
Damn!
She mustn't come here.
What are you doing?
Do Claire and Marie know this forest?
Yes, Claire came here with us when she was a girl.
Why?
What are you doing?
Nathan!
I'm making sure they don't get eaten too.
Nathan! Nathan!
They are coming!
Hello, this is Nathan Fabre.
I'm not available at the moment.
Please leave a message.
Nothing.
Come down!
We have to go to the cabin!
Follow me!
Rather, let him come after me!
They're giving up.
Come on! Hurry up!
I'll hand you your mobile.
Call Claire first, then the cops.
Call her!
- Give me your lighter!
- Why?
Give me a cigarette lighter!
Call her now.
Pass me a gun.
Give me a gun!
Give it to me.
Call her now.
Wait, wait!
Where are you?
- Hello?
- Clare, Clare?
- What the hell's going on?
We've been trying to call you for hours.
Did you think...
...we'd just wait
patiently for you to call?
It's Daddy!
- We're coming to join you.
- No! Turn back!
Why not?
Immediately, turn back!
Immediately!
Say, for God's sake, what happened?
- Nicolas, this is Marie!
- Listen, Marie!
Animals gone mad!
They are attacking us!
- David and dad are dead.
- What?
- It's the fertiliser.
- It got into the ground water.
That's why the animals are like this.
Nicolas, hurry up!
- Watch the traps.
- Don't tell anyone and get the hell out of here.
- Is Nathan with you? Is he OK?
- Just do as I say.
- Get out of here and tell no one.
- Dad!
Nicolas!
Hurry. Get back.
They haven't bitten through it.
What are you doing?
I'm giving them some bait.
Not now, Nathan. Wait till we've gone!
Shit, I can't do it.
We're going to die.
I can't fucking do it.
For fuck's sake!
Shit!
Knock stronger!
Nathan, We Die!
Get out!
Come on, come on!
Leave it!
Are you relying on your ex-wife
to sort this mess out for you?
I don't think I'll be needing her
to sort you out.
After what you've seen,
after what happened with my brother.
you didn't think I'd let you leave this forest.
No, I didn't.
OK.
After what I've seen, did you think
I was going to hand you a loaded gun?
And what are you gonna do?
Report me to the police?
Do you think my daughter will forgive you?
We'll see.
No.
Claire, no, wait!
- Nathan!
- Claire!
Claire!
Nathan, damn it, what happens?
No time!
Get in the car!
What is happening?
Where is Nicolas?
Where is he?
Where is my husband?
He's dead!
Mom?
Claire ...
- Neeee!
No, do not open!
Do not open!
Claire!
Nathan! ... Nathan!
Claire ...
Claire!
Nathan! ...
Nathan ...
O, damn!
Wait, wait, do not move.
Wait, I'll get you out of here.
Damn it! Shit!
Wait a minute ...
Aa, Nathan!
Nathan!
Nathan, hurry up! Nathan!
Look out!
AAA! Nathan!
Nathan?
Nathan ...
Nathan!
No, no! I'll lose too much blood.
- Call the emergency services.
- You're already losing blood.
Call the emergency services.
Everything will be fine ...
Everything will be fine ... everything will be fine ...
Damn ...
Everything will be fine ...
Hello, you called emergency medical center
Please give your name,
number and address
and the reason for your call.
The ambulance service will respond to you now.
Do not hang up, we'll connect you to a specialist
Please give your name,
number and address
and the reason for your call.
You are through
to the emergency services.
Your call will be answered shortly.
Do not hang up, we'll connect you to a specialist
Hello. How can I help?
Leave your phone ...