In New York City's war on crime,
the worst criminal offenders are pursued
by the detectives of the Major Case Squad.
These are their stories.
She is not to know about this.
How much do you usually get?
Think of a number you're comfortable with.
Now double it.
Just now, up in her office.
This is what she thinks of me.
Oh, God. She has no boundaries.
It's not gonna work.
I mean us, Julie. I'm sorry.
We make a good team, Kenneth.
You're fooling yourself. Nan will
make our life a living hell.
I'm sorry, Julie.
I really am.
Kenneth.
(DOOR CLOSES)
He loves me, Mother. Is
that so hard to believe?
Your judgment is off.
Right.
I disagree with you, so I must be wrong.
It's my life. Do you hear me?
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Everyone hears you, Julie.
But as long as you live under my roof,
and work for me, you...
You can't control me!
Is this a bad time?
Julie was just leaving.
She only wants what's best for you.
Dad, how can you take her side?
I'm not.
The last week, when the talk about
selling the hotel came up...
What?
She didn't...
She said she would discuss it with you.
She can't do this!
You can't let her upset you like this.
Come on, you've got everything going for you.
You're young, you're talented,
you're gorgeous.
Guys would kill for the chance to date you.
You know that, don't you?
KENNETH: No. No second thoughts.
I just...
Of course I trust you.
I will.
Mr. Turner! Mr. Turner! The room below,
they call about the water, but...
Slow down, Carlos. Slow down.
There is a leak into the suite below yours.
I called Mrs. Turner many times, no answer.
I didn't want to disturb her.
TURNER: Nan? Nan!
Mr. Turner!
(EXCLAIMING IN SPANISH)
Nan!
(VOICES CHATTERING ON POLICE RADIO)
There's no obvious signs of a struggle.
The wine glass didn't even spill.
Other than the corpse in the tub,
the entire suite is fit for a princess.
Just like the ads say.
She drink and drown?
The body fights drowning.
The throat closes to keep the
water out. The victim suffocates.
Which means she should've surfaced.
Which she hasn't.
Lungs are filled with water
and her throat didn't close.
Forehead has blisters, pinpricks.
Botox shots.
Just a guess,
going by that nice smooth
look in all her photos.
Botox works by paralyzing
the nerves around the
facial muscles, doesn't it?
Does it look like I'd know?
Xanax, Ambien, heart pills.
A real piñata bowl.
The bed was slept in.
You Major Case? I'm Cooper.
That's my boss in the tub.
I'm the house dick here.
Used to be at the 2-4.
I'm the one who called you.
On a drowning?
The husband doesn't want
any insurance questions later.
For example?
She was suicidal?
She makes other people suicidal.
That include her husband?
Ask him.
He's in the study, about a
half a mile down that hallway.
Nan did not do this to herself.
She never would have given her
enemies the satisfaction.
She must've slipped or...
Or something.
The manager said you got home around 3:00.
Yes. Poker night at the Explorers.
Every week for 20 years.
So your wife was here by herself?
Yes.
What about your daughter?
Julie was with her fiancé, Kenneth Rayfield.
She's at his loft now. She's...
She's far too upset to do any good here.
Your wife have enemies?
When Nan's father died,
she took over the old dame.
It's been a battle.
With whom? Unions? The suppliers?
The competition.
She was determined to keep
the hotel in the family.
This belonged to Admiral Peary?
He took it to the pole.
Nan's father acquired it.
And you use it as a, you know, letter opener?
Your competitors, have they
made a play for the hotel?
There is talk that the Grimwalds
are about to make an offer
but you'll have to try Julie on that.
Can't we try you?
When the family trust was set up,
the hotel passed directly
to Nan and then to Julie.
I'm not part of that loop.
One last thing. Did your
wife get Botox injections?
A gentleman does not ask a
lady to reveal her secrets.
I saw Mom just before 8:00.
She was in a good mood.
EAMES: And then you went to your fiancé’s?
I'd just gotten back from the gym.
We ordered Chinese, watched a DVD.
A quiet night.
- It wasn't that quiet.
- Kenneth.
Your father told us that your mother
was gonna keep the hotel in the family.
That's right.
What are your plans?
I grew up in the Townson Hotel.
It's my home. I'm not selling it.
Maybe a competitor thought
they could change your mind.
The Grimwalds, for example.
If the offer was
generous enough?
What did the Algonquin sell
for last year, $30 million?
Forty. And it's hardly in the
same league as the Townson.
I'm an equity analyst at Mason Stone.
Oh.
JULIE: Helen Grimwald's always
had her eye on the Townson.
But she underestimates me,
like everyone else.
KENNETH: So Nan...
It wasn't an accident,
is that what you're inferring?
You mean implying. The listener infers.
And detectives speculate, since we
don't know the cause of death yet.
We'll be in touch.
We're so sorry for your loss,
especially now you're getting married.
We haven't set a date yet.
We just met three months ago
at a benefit and we...
Wow, three months. A whirlwind romance.
Well, we... We both just knew.
Well, you're lucky to have each other.
He knew when he got a look
at her mother's hotel.
The ME's got the tox screen results.
This holds 100 units of botulin.
It's good for four treatments.
Nan Turner had over 3,000
units in her system.
Would this fill a whole syringe?
Sure. It's freeze-dried.
Just add saline solution and find a vein.
What about these pinpricks on her forehead?
Oh, those would be from a regular
treatment, probably the day she died.
The lethal dose went into her jugular.
Now, she had sleeping pills, wine.
She was probably injected in her sleep.
Yeah, the botulin caused
a descending paralysis.
First she can't open her eyes,
then she can't speak, can't swallow.
And can't close her throat.
But she can still breathe.
GOREN: So the killer
dragged her to her bathtub,
pushed her under and her lungs
filled with water.
Death by Botox.
Live slow, die old, leave
a good-looking corpse.
Thanks to your friendly local dermatologist.
Oh, I checked with her doctors.
They never gave her Botox.
Well, there's always the hotel beauty salon.
I'm not licensed to dispense Botox.
Yeah, we've found that a lot of people
do things that they're not licensed to do.
Especially if their landlord insists.
My salon never treated her.
Not only does he remove
hairs, but he splits them.
Your cosmeticians,
technically, they're independent
contractors, right?
Yes.
If you had to pick one?
Jason. He's got a following.
House calls, parties.
Julie, I want you to think.
Imagine the worst thing
that Kenneth could do,
and then ask yourself,
would you still love him?
What's done is done.
What matters is, would you still love him?
Would you?
Then do whatever needs to be done.
NINA: He's incredible.
Isn't Jason the perfect
little miracle-worker?
He has quite a following.
Are these to-dos always so crowded?
No. Half of us were here last Wednesday.
(GASPING)
My dear, I would kill to have your skin.
Laser abrasion, am I right?
No.
If you just saw Jason, why would
you need another treatment?
Because Wednesday he showed up empty-handed.
- Oxygen facial?
- No.
So what happened?
He left his whole supply in a cab.
I know. You had a lymphatic drain facial.
Sorry, just soap and water.
Now serving number 10.
I'll be done in a jiff.
Aren't we eager?
I couldn't take the risk you'd
run out like last Wednesday.
(SIGHING)
What a nightmare!
I'm surprised it didn't
make the evening news.
There's still a chance.
Jason here ran out of Botox
the night Nan Turner died.
What is going on here?
A murder investigation.
The Baronet, isn't that a Grimwald hotel?
Yeah, what isn't?
I gave a party in one of their suites.
The Vam Dam, another Grimwald hotel.
Boy, you are just in too cozy
with the Grimwalds for your own good.
He left those vials in a cab.
How often do you need to hear it?
Helen Grimwald was your regular customer.
I mean, you saw her the Monday
before you saw Nan Turner.
GOREN: (STAMMERING) Come on.
It's written right there in ink.
Did she know that Nan was your client?
He's not gonna answer that.
He's gonna want to say something.
He's already on the hook for nine counts
of dispensing a controlled substance.
It's just Botox, for God's sake.
Just Botox?
You mean anyone could do it?
Even me?
This stuff was derived
from something developed
for germ warfare in the '50s.
A jury might not think it's so harmless.
Especially when they find out Nan died
after having 30 vials of it
jammed into her neck.
I, look... I...
I lugged those vials around all day in this.
First in the fridge at the
Townson's beauty salon.
Then I had some sessions at the
Baronet. I stored them in their spa.
After that, the Plaza.
Well, you get the idea.
The idea being that the vials
could've been stolen
at any point.
Yes. Not that I'm pointing fingers,
but Helen Grimwald knew that
Nan was a client of mine.
She was always asking me
about Nan's health.
It was morbid.
She thought as soon as Nan kicked,
she could grab up the hotel?
Yeah, I tried to tell her
Julie Turner would never sell.
Julie lived to renovate.
But Helen said that she had a little
bird who told her to be patient.
A little bird.
JASON: Yes.
Apparently the same one who saved her a
lot of money when she bought the Baronet.
Okay, thank you.
3 years ago, when the Grimwalds
bought the Baronet,
they got a bridge loan
through Mason Stone.
Kenneth Rayfield's firm.
Yeah, that's Helen Grimwald's little bird.
Once the old lady's out of the way,
he'd sweet-talk the daughter
into selling the hotel.
And he gets a commission from the
Grimwalds and a $40 million dowry.
Except that he killed Nan
before marrying the daughter
and locking in the profits.
Nan was in bad health.
He could've let nature take its course.
Something forced his hand.
Kenneth?
Julie adores him.
You trust her judgment?
Three months, they're already engaged?
Julie's had some bad luck in the past.
She's been divorced?
No, she was engaged about three years ago.
Came to her senses just in time.
Was this guy also in the real estate field?
Junker? He played the field,
he didn't have one.
How'd you find out?
We found out because Nan
did her due diligence.
You didn't tell Julie?
With Julie, if you push one way,
she tends to go the other way.
We felt it better to let her...
Come to her senses? You know...
There's a check stub missing.
it's been ripped out.
And the checks before and after were written
the day of your wife's murder.
It's check 768.
Do you know anything about it?
The trust account was strictly Nan's domain.
PRESCOTT: It's been over a week.
That check should have cleared by now.
The day the check was written, were there
any other transfers into the account?
Mrs. Turner transferred $100,000.
Did I say something amusing?
Not yet. Could you look up a check?
A three-year-old check?
The name of the payee?
Well, we only have the first name.
Junker, with a J.
Just be happy his name isn't Messerschmitt.
There.
Junker Dalton.
$30,000 for traveling expenses.
As in, "Hit the road, Junker."
Nan's MO.
She pays Julie's fiancée to go away.
Ken didn't go.
Why take the consolation prize
when you can stay in the game
and marry $40 million?
So Kenneth killed Nan
and Julie's covering for him.
My father told me all about your suspicions.
You're desperate.
You don't care whose life you destroy.
We care who destroyed your mother's.
When Ken came over that day she
died, it was around lunchtime?
People saw him in the lobby.
Yes, he was here to have lunch with me.
Oh, good, because the people who saw him
weren't sure what day it was.
Oh, is that how it's going to be?
We're going to play tricks?
Well, like you said, we're desperate.
Anyway, so the two of you met in
the loft. That was around 8:00?
- He just came back from the gym,
he took a shower?
- JULIE: Yes.
- Yes?
- No.
- No? What?
- He showered at the gym.
EAMES: Take your time.
And then you ordered in
Chinese from Maple Duck?
Yes. Did we tell you?
We got it off his credit card bill.
You see, we did a little snooping.
The restaurant told us this...
(SNICKERING)
Look at this...
That the order was made just after 10:00.
Well, as Ken alluded crudely,
we were preoccupied.
GOREN: Oh, yeah, well...
Oh, that's right.
You took a tumble between 8:00 and 10:00.
The restaurant also told us the
order was picked up in person.
Well, they're confused.
Ken was with me the whole evening.
Then we're confused,
because his gym said he scanned
himself in just after 9:00.
Oh, someone must have stolen
his membership card.
Next you're gonna tell me
someone stole his cell phone
and called you at quarter to ten.
No, I used his cell phone.
I misplaced mine in his loft, so I called it,
so it would ring, so I could find it.
You're turning every little innocent
thing into evidence of nothing.
While you waited for Ken at his loft,
Ken killed your mother and then ran
around establishing his alibi.
'Cause he was afraid that
you wouldn't lie for him.
JULIE: I'm not lying. Ken
wouldn't hurt my mother.
You're into homeopathy.
There's Lycopodium, Iris, Satrum.
Leave my things alone.
Well, they're expired, anyway.
You don't use them?
No. Just put them down.
You know, your mother was right.
You have no judgment when it comes to men.
- How would you know what my mother...
- Your last fiancé...
- What was his name?
- Junker. She paid him $30 grand to get lost.
How would you know about... That was a loan.
- She knew...
- A con when she saw one.
Is that why she wrote
Ken a check for $100,000?
Ken ripped up that check.
Doesn't that tell you something?
Well, what's one check when
you can marry the checkbook?
How dare you!
Ken loves me! Is that so hard to believe?
He understands me! He loves me!
We're sorry.
We'll show ourselves out.
She's not covering for him.
He's covering for her.
JASON: I never gave her treatments.
Julie's an attractive young woman.
She doesn't need Botox.
I saw Julie's homeopathic stash.
All the treatments for migraines.
And the heavy curtains in her suite,
to block out the light.
She suffered from migraines.
I wouldn't know.
EAMES: We checked with the hotel pharmacy.
It's been four months since she
refilled her migraine prescriptions.
She found something better, didn't she?
She found Botox.
EAMES: We heard for some
people, it works miracles.
That day that Nan died, Julie came to you.
She said she had a bad one
and you just wanted to help her.
She said they hurt so bad that they
make people want to kill themselves.
GOREN: She asked to buy your whole supply?
EAMES: She threatened to make trouble for you?
I just wanted to help her.
And then later, I realized...
You helped her commit murder.
GOREN: The happy couple.
We brought you new engagement rings.
Julie Turner, you're under arrest for murder.
You're gonna have to come with us, too.
Ken, don't leave me.
It's nice being loved so much.
Ken!
I just told Helen Grimwald Nan had concerns
about Julie's ability to run the hotel.
Nan might've been enticed to sell it
before Julie could run it into the ground?
Yes.
Did Julie know what her mother was thinking?
I don't know.
We talked about other things.
Like about the $100,000 check?
Julie told us about that.
Not one of my finest moments. I acted rashly.
Ripping up the check was a noble gesture.
I mean, giving Julie back
the engagement ring.
But Nan would've made our life a living hell.
Julie didn't tell you?
EAMES: Let's see if we have this straight.
Her mother was planning to sell
the hotel out from under her
and she drove her fiancé away.
Did we miss anything?
I know what you're implying.
But Julie is just not capable
of hurting her mother.
So, again,
what time did Julie show up at your loft?
And this is an answer that you
wanna give a lot of thought to.
I... I called her just after I left the gym.
She was out walking.
I told her to meet me at my place.
She...
She got there just after 10:00.
Sounds like the right answer.
Whose idea was it to lie?
Julie was afraid she'd be accused.
I... Now, I told her that was ridiculous.
But she was so upset. She...
I said, "We should just say
that we were together."
I knew she'd never have hurt Nan.
I bought enough for one headache, okay?
I was under a lot of stress with the
wedding preparations and the redecorating.
Redecorating your mother allowed you to do
while she was making provisions
to sell the hotel?
Just a rumor.
- My mother had complete faith in me.
- Your mother...
I…
No. No, it's too easy.
Why? What's too easy?
To get you to go on about your mother.
You should wait for your lawyer.
I don't need a lawyer to tell the truth.
No, you need a lawyer
because it's hard for you
to know what the truth is.
It's not your fault.
I mean, how could you,
with a mother like Nan?
Don't patronize me. I've had enough of that.
Hey, I'm trying to let you know
that there's a lot of sympathy
for you in this room.
You had a parent that lied to you.
Undermined you.
Questioned your judgment to the point where
you didn't even trust it yourself.
She didn't want you to be happy.
I did not hate my mother.
I did not kill her.
I was with Kenneth.
That's not true.
Ken told us.
Julie, we can see that you're
not a cold-blooded killer.
You were provoked.
I didn't kill her.
And she drove Kenneth away.
Kenneth told us that he
broke off the engagement.
That was just a test.
She wanted to see if he'd take the money.
A test? Like the $30,000 she loaned Junker?
No, she was right about him.
That he took the money?
That and he was cheating on me.
According to Nan.
She showed me pictures, okay?
So if she had anything on Kenneth,
she would've shown it to me.
So it was just a test. And he passed.
Then she realized I was right.
She realized he loves me.
This is Mr. Edwards, her family lawyer.
Your father's just outside, Julie.
He doesn't want you to say another word.
Until we get a criminal attorney,
she's reasserting her right to remain silent.
What do you mean, we can't post bail?
Most of the money is in the family trust.
Normally, Julie would have access to it,
but since she's charged with killing Nan...
There's gotta be something
I can use for collateral?
There's not enough that's yours to pledge.
There's gotta be something we can do.
Well, if she were to assign you
power of attorney over the
trust, temporarily...
Well...
(STAMMERING)
I don't want it to appear as though
I'm losing faith in her.
Perhaps you can bring it up with
her, from a legal standpoint.
Well, that's your call, William.
Yes.
Now, as far as a defense attorney,
I want the best you can get.
She can't tell us what it is
or what it isn't,
what she should tell us, what she shouldn't.
She's a pathological liar.
Whatever story works,
that's the one she goes with.
Whatever works for her.
She's not lying to us,
she's lying to herself.
Are you hoping the truth is in these boxes?
We're looking for the evidence
Nan had against Kenneth.
What makes you think she had anything
more than a mother's instinct?
Well, her husband said
she did her due diligence.
Last time, that meant
photos of Julie's fiancé.
The evidence against Julie lays
out in a nice, straight line.
Juries like straight lines.
Whatever Nan had, it's not here.
And there's no evidence
she hired an investigator now,
or three years ago to take photos of Junker.
Well, maybe she kept it in-house.
So, what's your thinking on this murder?
They're trying to find out
who Mrs. Turner hired
to take the snapshots of that...
What's his name? Junker.
And the Captain thinks it was you.
Well, you want a job done right, hire a pro.
What can I tell you? Legwork 101.
(MEN LAUGHING)
So when it was Kenneth's turn,
she came to you?
You would've thought.
I even offered but Mrs. Turner said no.
Why do you think?
Mrs. Turner didn't want another incident.
You mean, with Julie?
She was violent?
COOPER: Yeah.
She attacked her mother?
Well, they had this huge argument
when Mrs. Turner showed her the pictures.
I thought it was over.
But that night, they're on their
way out to go to some dinner,
and Julie hauled off and punched her.
Nearly broke her jaw.
So this time,
Mrs. Turner wanted to be more
supportive of her daughter.
She even took her to Florida the weekend
before she died. Just the two of them.
Come back happy as pismo clams.
(COOPER CHUCKLES)
I don't think Julie did it.
We'll pass that on to the DA.
Thanks for coming in.
Yeah, one last thing.
This punch-out over the photos,
did Kenneth know about it?
Yeah, he asked me about it once.
He found it amusing.
Well, you know where to find me.
Kenneth told us he didn't think Julie
was capable of hurting her mother.
Gee, you think he was lying?
He knew she could be provoked.
With rumors of Nan selling the hotel,
with Nan paying off another fiancé,
he got her to do his dirty work for him.
If she gets caught, his hands are clean.
So much for nice straight lines.
I gladly posted bail today.
Anyone who knows my daughter, knows she could
not possibly have committed this crime.
REPORTER: Julie! Julie, did you do it?
She has no comment, gentlemen.
No comment, please.
I just wanna say how much I miss
my mom. I loved her very much.
WOMAN: Do you have any other comments?
It may amuse you to know
her lawyer's already putting out
feelers for a plea bargain.
I'm inclined to accept.
Even if someone put her up to it?
That doesn't lessen her culpability.
Who is this someone?
Her fiancé.
He created a circumstance
which he knew in the past had
caused her to attack her mother.
If her fiancé were trying to control
her, wouldn't she lash out at him?
Not if he made her believe
Nan was pulling the strings.
If you take Julie's plea,
if you put the weight of this
murder on her shoulders alone,
we lose our leverage
against any other suspect.
I'll hold off responding to their plea offer.
But sooner or later, I will
take the bird in hand.
Kenneth, he knew
that if he could trick Nan
into paying him off,
Julie would snap.
And the way to trick Nan
was to let her find out about
his, you know, bad behavior.
Nan and Julie spent the weekend in Florida.
She wrote the check when she came back.
Kenneth was in the city alone.
Whatever he did to set Nan off,
good chance he did it that weekend.
At this point, I don't think
we should count on Kenneth.
But who else can testify for me?
Well, that's why I approached Mr. Carver.
About a plea bargain? Absolutely not.
Will, consider manslaughter.
If Julie said she had help from...
Well, from Kenneth, for example.
I would never hurt Kenneth, ever.
My daughter doesn't have
to perjure herself to win.
If you're afraid to try this case,
we'll find someone who isn't.
Friday night he had sushi for one.
Phone calls to Julie in South
Beach every couple of hours.
So lovey-dovey.
Do you have a charge there for Cafe Brasilia?
MARISOL: 1:00, table for two.
Did you see who was number two?
No.
This is Kenny? He's so handsome.
Everybody's having a, you know, a good time.
This is a good time place.
I like these photos. Who took them?
Mercedes.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
You remember this guy 3 Saturdays ago?
Oh, yes.
This guy asked me to take a picture
of him and his date, like a surprise.
So, I do.
What did his date look like?
They were kissing. I see
only the back of his head.
He was wearing a baseball hat.
- His head? The date was a man?
- Yes.
Did he buy the photo?
This guy buy it right away. Okay?
Kenneth outed himself.
He sent the photo to Nan anonymously.
He knew that it would
get her to pay him off.
Why didn't Nan just tell Julie?
She had proof, in living color.
No. If she did, Julie
would've dumped him herself.
Kenneth's plan wouldn't have worked.
He had to make Nan appear unreasonable.
He had to make absolutely sure
that Nan would never show Julie the photo.
Julie goes to jail, who's left standing?
No.
It explains everything.
JULIE: We're both innocent, okay?
I told Mr. Behrens I'm not
interested in a plea bargain.
Neither are we, but we're compelled
to explore mitigating circumstances.
I'm not some puppet.
No one can manipulate me
into A: Something I didn't do,
and B: Something I would never do.
C: and D:
You attacked your mother three
years ago, and Kenneth knew it.
That's...
I was a different person then.
Anyway, Kenneth didn't know.
GOREN: He knew.
He talked to your house detective.
This is Mr. Cooper's statement.
While you and your mother were in Florida,
Kenneth went to a nightclub.
This is a photo of his
reservation. You see his name here?
Kenny.
While he was there,
he had a photo taken of himself.
A compromising photo which
he sent to Nan anonymously.
This is the statement from
the hostess at the club.
And this is the statement of the girl
who took the photo.
Please. Kenneth kissing another man?
Believe me, if my mother had that photo,
she would've shown it to me.
Even if it meant hurting you?
I've gotten over worse.
Kenneth didn't want you to get over this.
And there's a reason why your
mother didn't show you the photo.
Because she did love you.
She was afraid it would destroy you.
We found out Kenneth served
on a tourism board last year.
Did you know that?
No.
Your father was on the same board.
Did he mention meeting Ken?
No. He was only on it for a few months.
What does this have to do with anything?
That benefit where you met Kenneth,
how did you happen to go?
My father bought me a ticket.
He thought I should get
involved in good works.
Your father has your best interest
at heart? He gives you good advice?
Yes, he does.
He's always there for you.
He was standing next to you
on the courthouse steps.
Yes.
He probably asked you not
to take the plea bargain.
That a trial would vindicate you?
Yes, he did. He believes in me.
What are you getting at?
We noticed, from the trust accounts,
your mother paid your father
a monthly allowance.
I don't know. That was between them.
Who signs those allowance checks now?
Well, because of this nonsense...
You signed power of attorney
over to your father?
If you go to prison,
what'll happen to the hotel?
- I'm not going to prison.
- If you do,
who will control the hotel? Your father?
Yes.
Because he has power of
attorney, he could sell it.
- He wouldn't.
- But he could
and there would be no one to stop him.
No. No, my father did not do this to me.
Don't get upset and just sit and listen.
Your father knew your temper.
He knew what buttons to push.
He used Ken to provoke you.
I'm not listening to any more of this!
- BEHRENS: Julie.
- Let her go. Go ahead, Julie, run.
Just run.
(CRYING)
You push her one way, she goes the other.
Those are the exact words
your father said to us.
Imagine the insight that he gave Kenneth.
No wonder Ken understood you.
Oh, this can't be true.
My father loves me.
GOREN: Your mother loved you.
She didn't show you the photo,
she couldn't show you the photo,
because the other man kissing Ken
wasn't just any other man.
No. No, my... My father's not gay.
This is a monstrous lie.
Julie, come on, you've known it all along.
Even as a kid,
this image that your parents
presented to you,
of a happy marriage,
and what you saw with your eyes
was out of sync with what you felt.
Oh, God. What's happening?
What's happening to me?
Look, in my own life,
I know what it's like to have your
judgment, your sense of security,
undermined by your parents.
Because they were hiding a truth
or denying it to themselves.
You can survive that.
My client's ready to admit her
guilt in her mother's murder,
but obviously, her father's involvement
has changed her situation.
As I said, we're willing
to consider mitigation.
But we still have to make
a case against Mr. Turner.
Do you have a plan?
We've discussed one.
We found a clause in your
mother's trust agreement.
You need my help?
Well, only if you're up to it.
Julie!
Julie, if I'd known you were waiting
for me, I would've come home sooner.
How are you, honey?
I have news, Daddy. Good news.
Great. Would you like a drink?
No. I'm going back on the wagon.
Well, now that is great news.
How'd it go with the district attorney?
Have they come to their senses yet?
Not yet, but Daddy, the good news.
There's a miracle.
After the meeting, I went to the doctor's.
I'm pregnant.
Does anyone else know this?
I just talked to Kenneth.
Daddy, he was so happy, he cried.
- And then we decided...
- Decided what?
In the morning, we're going
to City Hall to get married.
Oh, no. Oh, no. You can't rush this.
You've got a trial.
Kenneth doesn't want to wait.
I'm sure he doesn't.
Julie,
did you ever show the family
trust papers to Kenneth?
Maybe once, why?
GOREN: That's it, reel him in.
TURNER: Because there's a clause in the trust
that says that, if in any case
that you can't administer the trust,
say you died, or went to prison,
it would pass to your child,
or your child's guardian.
That will be Kenneth if you marry him.
Well, I'm sure Kenneth would
take good care of things.
No, no, no, no.
Kenneth is not the kind of
man you think he is.
What do you mean? I thought you liked him.
(STAMMERING)
I do. But you can't marry him.
I swore to your mother
I would never tell you this.
She was convinced you wouldn't
be able to handle it.
Handle what?
Your mother received a photograph of Kenneth
in a compromising situation.
He's the father of my child now.
I think I can forgive him an indiscretion.
Not this one.
He was with another man.
Got him.
Daddy, why didn't you tell me?
You seemed so happy.
You'd let me live a lie?
- I thought that...
- Whoa, whoa, where's she going?
...if you found out about
his preference later,
- Where's she going? ...
- you'd learn to live with it.
Is that what mother did?
Learn to live with it?
TURNER: What are you talking about?
No. no. We gotta get in there.
We gotta get in there!
JULIE: You never had anything for me.
Ever. You never loved me.
Mom did, but you didn't.
TURNER: Julie.
You bastard! How could you do this to me?
Our whole life was a lie!
I was just a child.
Mom loved me!
Hey, if anyone deserved it...
She wasn't ready.
- Detective...
- No, no, no, I know that anger.
I should've seen it coming.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)