"You got into fights, you
spent four years in solitary.
"What do you have to say
for yourself, Mr. Dietrich?"
So I said, "Well, what can I say, Warden?
"l just like to have a good time."
Yes, another milestone.
Eight hours as a free man.
Mark.
I'm Chantal. Can you sign something for me?
I saved it all these years.
You looked so hot.
Naomi, give me a pen.
So, is this really the bar where you
and Mandy hooked up that night?
Baby, it was 15 years ago. It was
called something else back then.
Hey, Penny, take a picture of me and Mark.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. Here, look.
"I'm Mandy. Don't choke me so hard, Mark."
Mark?
I brought you coffee.
Miss?
Oh!
One thing I learned in prison, Mom,
is not to kill the girls I have sex with.
I want you to feel good,
Mark, good and powerful.
Is this how you want me? Yeah. Yeah.
I've been watching you
running around the reservoir,
watching your butt in those
little silver running shorts.
...running around the reservoir,
watching your butt in those
little silver running shorts.
Is all you're gonna do is watch?
Shut up. Shut up.
I'm gonna fill your mouth with
sand, so you start choking.
Get all tight.
I'm going out now.
What's the matter, Mom? I know
you've been watching me. What is it?
You're a malignant narcissist.
What did you say?
Never mind.
Have a nice night.
And try not to hurt anyone.
I don't remember, all right.
It was 15 years ago.
Come on. I just want to see
where you killed Mandy.
I'm gonna kill you if you don't knock it off!
Where's your coke?
Just show me. Okay, like, you hooked
up with her at the bar that night.
She was wearing a little
black dress, like this.
I'm sick of this crap!
Mark, wait up. Wait up.
Hey, Mark!
Mark, wait up!
Mom, where'd you hide the coffee?
Mom.
No. No, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no!
No.
A co-worker found her. No forcible entry.
She lived alone till Dietrich moved in a
month ago. "My son, the Yuppie Killer."
He's why we're here. Anybody seen him?
Not since yesterday.
The neighbors heard them
arguing on and off though.
Life with a psychopath. I'll talk
to the co-worker when she's ready.
Well,
the killer caught her behind the ear. She...
She crawled to here.
The...
The back of her nightgown is, is...
Is bunched up, but the
front has been pulled down
to cover her.
Someone was worried about her modesty?
The girl Dietrich killed in the park
didn't rate that kind of consideration.
That lady's ready.
I talked to Laura last night, just to
make sure that she wanted a ride to work.
We're fact-checkers for a
publisher in Long Island City.
Was she expecting company last night?
No, Laura didn't socialize much.
Especially since her son came home.
How was that going, between her and Mark?
Well, she was hoping for the
best, you know, but they argued.
And then she just stopped
talking about him altogether.
Mrs. Dietrich's cell phone is missing.
Has anyone been reading this paper?
No, it was out in the hallway.
I brought it in.
I'm gonna need this bagged, exactly as is.
We...
Let's go for a ride.
I… I’m…
I'm gonna need a Polaroid of this, please.
You all set?
Mark, how you doing?
I'm sorry I had to deliver
the bad news over the phone.
Yeah, you figured out my mom
lent me her phone, huh?
Uh-huh. We wake you up?
My girlfriend and I were just waking up, so...
Where are we going?
You know, Mark, Detective Eames
thought that you were good for this.
I thought you went on the lam.
Except you left your Xanax
behind and your mom's money.
It was on her dresser.
Are you ready?
You found her like this?
Yes.
See.
Why?
I just...
I mean, can we cover her up? She
wouldn't want to be seen like this.
She was a very modest woman.
We need to go downtown,
so you can sign some papers.
I meant to ask you. Did
your mother have any enemies?
She got some phone calls, a few years back,
from the brother of the girl.
Mandy Johanssen, the girl
you strangled in the park.
By mistake.
I wrote a letter to that family,
telling them how sorry I was.
But you can never be
too sorry for some people.
Last night, where were you again?
With my girlfriend, Chantal Fielding.
Does she know about you?
She knows it was a long time ago.
Gena will help you fill out the forms.
Oh, uh...
All those?
It's what you have to do when a
member of your family gets murdered.
You tracked mud in with your shoes.
Yeah, sorry.
It's horse manure.
Mark was really upset
when he heard about his mom.
I felt so sorry for him.
I felt sorry for his mom.
Did you ever meet her?
No. I only met Mark a couple of weeks ago.
I'm sorry, I dropped something.
So, what did you and Mark do last night?
We went out to dinner,
and then came back here.
Fell asleep watching TV.
Gee, you two sound just like my parents.
That's probably why Mark appreciates it,
'cause it's so, you know, ordinary.
Especially with a guy like Mark.
You know, he's a magnet for extreme attention.
Absolutely. You should've seen the
skank he was with when I met him.
Yeah, I know the type.
Murder groupies.
Mark said she started writing him in prison.
These women, they like to visit murder scenes.
It gets them hot.
You never
were tempted to, you know,
ask Mark?
No.
Because, you know, it's not that far
away. It's just on the bridle path
where they walk the horses. In fact,
it's where they found the girl Mandy.
She had a smell of horse manure.
Like this, you know?
Like the mud on your boots.
Like the mud on Mark's shoes.
How was it, Chantal?
Did you ask Mark to call you Mandy while
he wrapped a scarf around your neck?
That is so sick.
You know, Mark, he told us that there's
3 varieties of murder groupies,
victims, psychos, shrinks.
He said with you, he's got 3 mints in one.
Oh, that loser!
All right. You wanna know what he did?
We went into the park,
and then he freaked out.
I had to walk home by myself.
And what got him upset?
I don't know. He was whining all night
about his mother being mad at him.
What time did he show up here?
I don't know, about 6:30 in the morning.
He curled up like a little
baby and went to sleep.
Look, if I killed my mother,
- I'd be in South America by now.
- I just wanted you to know
- You said yourself, I didn't run away.
- that your attempt to deceive
us didn't go unnoticed.
- You forgot one thing, the morning paper.
- Look, my mom has it delivered.
The first officer to arrive on
the scene found it outside.
Where you put it, when you brought it
in, when you came back from the park.
No.
You read the sports section,
you killed your mom.
- No!
- You slipped the sports section back
into the newspaper.
Put it back outside, only, you put
it back in the wrong section.
- At this point, Mark's invoking his rights.
- No, no, no.
- Look, I wanna tell them what happened.
- No, no, no, Mark.
I just wanna get it over with.
I got home, I was drunk,
and I blacked out, okay.
I came to. I went looking
for my mom and I found her.
And she was already dead.
- I got scared.
- And you're saying that
there's this huge chunk of time
that you have no memory of.
I'm saying that I passed out
in the living room. I...
I did not kill my mother.
Your mother told her friends you fought.
Yeah, well, when I first got out, yeah.
All that lecturing and moralizing.
- But not lately.
- So that was the problem.
- No, we were barely speaking.
- That's the problem, right there.
- She'd given up on you.
- Yeah, right, so what do I care?
She called me
a malignant narcissist.
That was the last thing she said to me.
She was the only one I had left out
here. Why would I want to kill her?
I mean, why would I want to do that to myself?
When someone is killed
by receiving a blow to the head,
it sends up a fine spray of blood
that's unrecognizable to the...
to the human eye.
Once the lab gets done with their
microscopic inspection of your clothes,
we'll have you cooked six ways to Sunday.
She was my mother.
There was no way I killed her.
Why did you stop?
Look, when you tell a suspect
that there's incriminating
evidence on the way, they...
They get quiet. They...
They start to try to remember
what they missed.
You know, they don't keep
claiming their innocence.
Or he really doesn't remember killing her.
Mark's mother,
she called him a malignant narcissist.
That's a clinical term that
psychiatrists use amongst themselves.
She has no background in psychology.
She stopped talking to him.
She withdrew.
There's something going on with her.
Mark Dietrich should've gotten
life for choking that girl.
He caught a break, but not this time.
Just get the evidence and bury him.
The only change that I can think of is,
we stopped riding home together 3 weeks ago.
I thought she was taking a class.
She was always home by 9:30.
She made notes. "Remorseless,
charming, predatory."
Anybody we know?
"Shallow emotional affect,
"rehabilitation is rare."
You know, I...
Look, what, was she fact-checking
a psychiatric text?
No. We only check statistical data.
Rolls of nickels.
Do you have any vending machines
that only take nickels?
No. What costs a nickel these days?
Microfilm machines.
They use them in the library
to copy newspapers.
These are the books that she checked
out of the psychology section.
"Nurture-Born Killers,
"Patterns of the Sexual Predator."
Maybe she liked seeing Mark's name in print.
No, that's the thing. Mark's
name wouldn't be in here.
These books are about
chronic sexual offenders.
Mark's strangling of Mandy Johanssen,
it was called a one-time incident,
completely out of character for Mark.
What'd you find?
A clerk said Mrs. Dietrich
checked out newspapers
from the summer of '86 to the fall of '87.
Besides Mandy's murder in September,
there was another Central Park story
that ran that whole year.
The Reservoir Runner.
2 months earlier in July, she was dragged
into the woods and raped by 4 kids.
Maybe Mrs. Dietrich thought Mark
had something in common with them.
Something that made her withdraw from him.
Something that
compelled her to do research 3 weeks ago.
Something she saw or heard.
Well, 3 weeks ago,
that's before he started seeing Chantal.
She said he was with his prison pen pal.
The word she used was skank.
What happened with Mark?
You corresponded with him for what?
7 years.
Did he open up to you?
About Mandy?
It was an accident.
Mark needs to feel powerful,
but he doesn't need to kill.
If only his mother had given him
that kind of understanding.
I read about what happened to her.
She wasn't good for him.
You met her?
I didn't need to. I saw her apartment.
Lots of beige’s, neutral tones. It's stifling.
When were you in her apartment?
Like 3 weeks ago.
Well, that is interesting,
'cause that's when Mark
said that his mother turned cold on him.
But he couldn't figure out why.
I can.
I left my camera in his room.
She must've seen the video.
A video of you “healing” Mark's wounds?
I helped him give a voice
to his sexual fantasies.
Like what? About
choking
with a scarf, like Mandy?
He had a whole scenario
about silver running shorts
and filling my mouth with sand.
Once you get to know him,
Mark's a very creative soul.
Thanks, Naomi.
We'll be in touch.
The Reservoir Runner was described
as wearing silver running shorts,
but there was nothing in any
of the articles about sand.
Laura Dietrich heard her son's fantasies
about a runner in the park.
She goes to the library and she
confirms some of the details.
And she's a fact-checker.
Her next move would have been to the source.
The detectives who broke the case.
Mark Dietrich's mother? No kidding.
Never made the connection.
She said she was checking facts
for an article on the case.
Which facts in particular?
What the victim was wearing, was she choked?
Did she ask about sand?
She asked if the attacker put
sand in the victim's mouth.
But that wasn't made public, right?
Well, not at the time, no.
This have to do with the murder?
Laura Dietrich might've suspected
her son committed the rape.
It may be why he killed her.
That would be tragic because
he did not do that rape.
My partner and I got those guys.
There was semen found on the victim,
semen that didn't match any of them.
Did Mrs. Dietrich ask about that?
No, but if she did, I would've
told her it was a gang rape
and that we only got 4 of the guys.
Now, maybe Mark Dietrich, the Yuppie Killer,
was running with the homeboys that night,
but I doubt it.
Well, how do you explain that he knew
unpublicized details of the rape?
He was incarcerated in the same facility
with those 4 punks, wasn't he?
Cons tell each other everything.
But like you said, Detective Marston,
you know, I can't imagine a yuppie killer
shooting the breeze with 4 homeboys.
Look, we got taped confessions.
A lot of people worked a lot of hours
to get those animals off the street.
Us guys don't remember
what it was like back then,
but I've had a lot of women tell me they
were afraid to walk out in broad daylight.
Anything I can do, give me a call.
I remember. Marston and his partner
Roscoe were heroes around our house,
the way they got 4 kids
to confess in one night.
Yeah. I'd like to see how they did that.
I'm just saying, Nishan,
your friends are gonna tell the tale.
You finished with that can of
soda? You want another one?
Uh, no.
I ain't mean to leave it there.
I'm sorry. I'll clean it up.
- Come on, you were there.
- Man, I told you,
we didn't go anywhere near the reservoir.
We didn't rape no woman.
You're not helping yourself out, kid.
Your friend Nishan already said
he pulled down her silver shorts.
No, that ain't right.
And he said you held down her left leg.
I didn't. I didn't touch her never.
Monty, if you keep denying while all
your friends are cutting deals,
it's gonna go real bad for you.
Don't you wanna help us?
Yeah, I do.
All you gotta say is that
you touched her left leg.
Just touched it.
You don't have to admit
to anything else, just that.
And then you can go home tonight.
Um, do you have the tape of this confession?
They wanted him to say
he touched her left leg.
This is the confession
that played for the jury.
And then Nishan took down
her shorts and got on her.
What'd you do?
I touched her leg. Her right
leg. It's all I did.
Left leg, right leg. The point
is, the kid admitted he was there.
There were inconsistencies
in all 4 confessions.
And not one of them admitted
actually raping her.
Look, if they didn't do it,
if they weren't even there,
why in the world would they confess?
Because they were afraid to disappoint.
Disappoint who?
Marston and Roscoe. Look.
I'm just saying, Nishan, your
friends are gonna tell the tale.
You finished with that can of soda?
You want another one?
Uh, no.
I ain't mean to leave it there. I'm sorry.
So, Marston is drawing
attention to the soda can,
so that when anyone watches it,
they know that Nishan
had something to drink.
So nobody can say he was denied food and
drink. He's being a smart detective.
These kids were interrogated
for 30 hours with no lawyers
and almost no contact with their parents.
Marston's being polite. He's being very nice.
But look...
Look at the kid's reaction.
You got someplace I can throw
it away. I'll clean it up.
I'll clean it up.
The kid thinks that Marston
is reproaching him
for leaving the can on the table.
He is desperately trying
to please the one guy
he thinks can get him out of trouble.
I mean, the jury never saw this.
Never saw the way that Roscoe
and Marston played these kids.
All they saw was the finished product.
These confessions, they're nothing but vapor.
Mark Dietrich is the real thing.
He did this rape.
All 4 recanted their confessions.
Once their lawyers got ahold of them.
Two dozen witnesses saw them in the park,
running in a pack, snatching purses.
Dietrich knew the details.
I agree with Detective Marston's explanation.
Dietrich shared a prison
yard with the 4 rapists.
So, years later, he's having sex,
he just happens to dredge
up what they told him?
Now, that is incredible.
Tales of forcible sex excite him.
There's an easy way out of this.
The department still has Dietrich's
DNA from the Mandy Johanssen case.
We run it against the unknown
DNA from the reservoir rape.
I can just feature what
that little psycho told you.
She especially liked the part
about the silver running shorts.
I'm a sack artist. Improvisation
is the key to my creativity.
Almost as much as the bit about
stuffing her mouth full of sand.
If I understand you, you've never
actually seen this alleged video.
No. But his mother did.
She even looked up the true
story that inspired it.
These are the newspaper articles
that she checked out of the library
and books.
That's how she found out about the,
you know, the stuff
about malignant narcissism.
She even called the detective
who investigated the case.
She thought you were good for it.
If she thought that, she would've told me.
- You ever seen this woman?
- No.
You sure?
Your DNA matched the semen
on her running shorts.
Yeah. Okay, yeah, I remember her now.
I met her in the park. So?
We were warming up before
jogging. We started talking,
went back to her apartment.
Where?
All I remember is, it wasn't
close enough. And there was a bed.
We had sex. I must've
dripped on her shorts.
And then she went back to the park to jog,
and I went home to sleep.
What, you had consensual sex with a
runner that you met at the reservoir,
the same night the Reservoir
Runner was raped?
And it never, you know, crossed your mind
to say anything?
Well, how would he know
that's who he had sex with?
Her name and photo were never released.
I still wouldn't have known.
You never exchanged names?
It was the '80s.
Women were a lot more fun.
I don't understand. Is there
some doubt about who raped me?
This man's DNA matched the
semen on your running shorts.
This guy doesn't look like somebody
who'd bash me in the head with a rock
and put sand in my mouth.
Miss Stephens, if you can't
remember anything about the attack,
who told you about the sand?
Detective Marston.
So he's kept in touch with you.
He's called every few months.
Has he called you recently?
A couple of weeks ago.
He said he's worried about me.
I didn't know policemen like that existed.
DNA match, huh? Where do
you want me to start?
The samples were improperly stored.
Some genius blew his nose in the petri dish.
You gotta hear Dietrich's explanation.
He hooked up with Jane
Stephens before her run,
went back to her apartment to have sex.
Yeah, I can go with that.
Just for drill, you should check with her.
But she doesn't remember
what happened that day.
He knows that. Because you've monitored
her condition over the years.
You didn't see her that first night.
She lost three-quarters of her blood.
She doesn't need to remember what
they did to her. That's my job.
Detective Marston, we understand
there was extraordinary pressure
to break this case. Those
kids fit a profile...
Forget it. There were no
mistakes, no rush to judgment.
We matched the DNA.
Dietrich has no evidence to back up his story.
The DA says it's open and shut.
You know,
AI Roscoe and I went over to Jane Stephens'
apartment the day after she was raped,
just to look for a number
of her next-of-kin.
We found a condom wrapper
on the floor next to her bed.
Now, maybe, that's what Dietrich
used to have sex with her.
Ask AI Roscoe, I'm sure he'll remember.
He could've just said he was wrong
about the kids, a good-faith mistake.
What's he afraid of?
Yes.
Okay. Thank you.
I found AI Roscoe.
He's at the Saint Albans Parish cemetery
up near Ghent. He died 2 weeks ago.
His handgun discharged
while he was cleaning it.
Wait a minute, I don't understand, Detective.
Why are you volunteering
this information?
Because you're going to find out about
it anyway. It's exculpatory evidence.
Well, was there anything else
besides the wrapper?
- You remember the brand?
- No.
All your boy needs to know, is I
saw a wrapper. The simpler, the better.
Are we clear?
My father didn't like talking about that case.
That's why he moved us up here,
away from all the attention.
We looked at the police report
of your father's death.
It had all the...
the earmarks of an accidental shooting.
He would've done that for you.
For the insurance.
I just hope I'm doing the right thing.
I got this in the mail, the day after he died.
He was police chief here until last year.
I want my kids to remember him as a hero.
"it's something I've been
running from for 15 years.
"Last weekend, Ted Marston called.
It's all going to catch up.
"Before Ted and me began our
interrogation of those young men,
"we agreed that regardless of their innocence,
"we were going to get
confessions out of them.
"That's what we did. Even though
the more we questioned them,
"the more it was obvious
they were innocent.
"I'm ashamed of what I did.
I can't live with it anymore."
Some good-faith mistake.
They premeditated framing those kids.
Marston was looking at
prison time if word got out.
Or if Laura Dietrich got the case reopened.
This letter is of no value as evidence.
Mr. Roscoe isn't here to authenticate
it. It can't be used at trial.
Marston knows that the only person who
can tie him to the frame up is dead.
There's no evidence to tie him
to Laura Dietrich's murder.
And thanks to his condom wrapper story,
we can't even make an ironclad case
against Mark Dietrich for the reservoir rape.
Marston's sitting pretty snug in the saddle.
We need to put a burr under the saddle.
You are considering vacating the
convictions on the rape, aren't you?
I was a kid.
I was trying to keep from going to jail.
Detective Marston said the other guys
were gonna put the weight on me, so
I just said I touched her arm.
Detective Marston suggested you say that?
Yeah.
He said he would try to help
me, so long as I play along.
Mr. Carver, you asked us here
to discuss a new development.
We matched the semen on the
victim's shorts to a suspect we...
we've come to believe acted alone.
Are you preparing to vacate the convictions?
Vacate, what does that mean?
Your record will be clean.
It means, Nishan, that you spent all
those years in prison for nothing.
Ten years because you trusted
Detective Marston.
Well, that changed you in ways
that you never wanted. I...
I don't know what could
compensate you for that.
Oh, I do. I know exactly.
A $100 million. Those punks
are suing for $100 million.
I hear the city and the department
are prepared to settle,
but that proposed settlement
doesn't include you.
You see what's going on here?
I'm being set up.
We need a strategy.
The Detective's Endowment cannot
get involved if you were derelict
or if you acted out of bounds
of your official duties.
What's that supposed to mean?
You're the Detective's
Endowment, I'm a detective.
You'd better just talk to the DA.
I'm gonna go broke defending myself.
You gotta have a talk with the Endowment.
I'm sorry.
Look,
we had suspects. The city was in a panic.
Women couldn't sleep without worrying that
some guy was gonna rape them in their beds.
This isn't fair. These guys were heroes.
We need to stand by our own.
It's not just the DA's office.
It's public perception.
What if we had him help us break Dietrich.
Would that change the perception?
We both saw how he handled
those kids. He's good.
And nobody knows the reservoir
case better than him.
I think she has a point.
What're you talking about here?
We need to get Dietrich on the reservoir rape,
if we wanna get him for his mother's murder.
You want my help?
Yeah.
You'd be staying ahead
of the curve, you know,
doing what you always do, getting
at the truth like any good cop.
All right. All right.
Anything to make sure that the
right guy goes down for the count.
Where you wanna do it?
We were back there, when we started talking.
No, no, the witnesses said
they saw her warming up around here.
I'm just telling you
what I remember, all right.
Mr. Dietrich, as I explained
to your attorney,
we need to eliminate you
as a suspect in the rape
in order to defend ourselves
against this lawsuit.
How you doing, Detective?
Mark, this is Detective Marston.
He knows this case inside out.
Maybe you've heard of him.
He's the one who got the
confessions out of those kids.
Thanks for helping us out today.
You know, Mark is not so clear on how
him and Jane Stephens
got back to her apartment.
Uh-huh.
This path hooks back up to the traverse.
Her place is on West 81st, so
they would've cut through here.
You okay?
Come on, I'll put my arm
around you. You won't slip.
No, no, no, I...
What's wrong, Mark?
I'm not going down there.
Not with... Not with these on.
Oh, no, sure, sure, sure.
Here you go.
They cleaned it up since the
last time you've been here.
Cut out a lot of the underbrush,
put up a light.
The rocks...
Rocks are still here.
And the ground,
still sandy.
Right over there, is where they found her,
half-dead, barely a pulse.
Look, I don't know anything about that.
I don't wanna stay here.
Mark, you don't wanna help us anymore?
I mean, what are we supposed to make of that?
I told you, all right, I talked to the woman,
we went back to her place
and we had sex, okay?
I mean, didn't you see
the condom wrapper there?
Right? Isn't that what he told you?
I might've confused it with
another rape victim, Mark.
I mean, I work a lot of cases.
But this girl's apartment, the bed
was made, everything was tidy.
The doorman saw her go out.
If he would've seen her come back with you,
don't you think he would've said something?
Why don't you say something? I mean, what
did you let them bring me here for?
- Mark, I think you should...
- What? You're fired, okay?
He sees the writing on the
wall, same as everyone.
You know what you need to do here, Mark?
You need to cut yourself
the best deal you can.
I'm not going back in.
No, there's a way of telling the
story, Mark, that can work for you.
You hooked up with a girl on the path,
you brought her down here
for a little intimacy,
consensual intimacy.
I, I, I see where this is going.
This is a good story, Mark.
Things started developing between you two,
and all of a sudden, she hurt you.
Squeezed you a little too
hard, got too tough,
and you lost it.
The sex was consensual. A straight
assault with mitigation,
isn't that right, Counselor?
Under those circumstances, yes.
And all you gotta say, Mark, is she hurt you.
She hurt you, and you got scared.
Isn't that the way it happened?
You say it, and everything falls into place.
She hurt you, and you got scared.
She hurt me. I got... I got scared.
Look, I didn't wanna hurt her.
I just... I got scared. I got scared.
That's very good. You're almost home free.
All that's left to talk
about is, is your mother.
My mother?
Well, you helped Detective
Marston clear up his old case.
Now he wants to help you with this
other thing. I mean, we all do.
I didn't... I didn't kill my mother.
What you said is, you don't remember.
What's it gonna look like to a jury?
Please tell him that he has
practically no chance with a jury.
You have to stay out of court, my friend.
You have to talk to us.
I would... I wouldn't kill her.
It's obvious you care about your mother.
Even in death, you cared
about her, you had respect.
You remember? You remember what you
told me that morning that you saw her
in her nightgown?
About her modesty?
Oh, he was so concerned
about her being covered.
I mean, doesn't that say something?
Tells me, you're a good son, Mark.
The way you pulled her nightgown down.
After she was dead, to cover her.
A good son would do that, a respectful son.
Yeah.
How did you find out about that stuff?
Isn't that what you're talking about?
It was pulled down over her panties.
You tell me.
It was bunched up like this?
Maybe in the heat of the moment, you...
You just forgot to do it.
Maybe you thought about pulling
it back down, you know,
so you could implicate someone.
Someone like Mark.
And what, you were in too much of a hurry,
you just forgot to yank it back down?
You think that I killed... What,
you think I'd kill her? You're nuts!
As we speak, we're executing search warrants
on your home, your office, your car.
Oh, no, no, this is bull.
Yeah, no, we staged the picture 4 weeks ago.
We pushed the nightgown
back up just to trick you.
What're you coming after me for? You
got this loser here, he's good for it.
Yeah, for the fact he didn't do it. You did.
You're under arrest for murder.
You son of a bitch, you killed her.
You killed my mother!
Get out of here.
You'll never make it stick.
A cop killing a witness,
isn't that the death penalty?
It certainly is.
What you're gonna wanna do here, Ted,
is cut the best deal you can.
There is a window of
opportunity, Mr. Marston.
But given what you've put this city through,
I'm not disposed to leave it open longer.
You have from here back up to
that path to make up your mind.
Okay.
I'll take the deal.
I'll take it.
I'll get back to you.
This must've been a very
lonely place 15 years ago.