Joel.
Yeah.
This is Rick. He's taking
over your route on Monday.
Yeah, sure, how are you doing?
Rick's gonna ride along with you today.
I thought we were doing that tomorrow.
Tomorrow Rick's got his physical.
You pay attention. Joel
knows all the shortcuts.
I'm not worried, all right?
It's gonna be what it's gonna be.
Hey.
Luke!
Wait.
What?
I want you at work at 2:00.
Dude, we're good.
Mr. Halliwell likes to check
the shipment himself.
If he's not here to sign for it,
you don't deliver it, got that?
Uh-huh.
You can put those over there.
Tepper. His last name was Tepper.
No, I don't know him.
Why're you turning?
Shortcut.
Geez! Hey, what's the matter with you?
What's the matter with you, assface?
Rick, let it go.
This little punk thinks he owns the streets.
Excuse me.
Keys.
Rick, they just want the drugs.
We stay cool, we're gonna be okay.
Shut up! You talk, I waste him.
Hurry up!
These, too.
Go. Go, go, go.
Okay. Okay. We're gonna be okay.
Hey!
You talked.
Witnesses saw three males,
late teens, early twenties.
One on a skateboard, and one on a bike,
one driving a van, dark gray, dark
blue or black, take your pick.
No one grabbed the plate numbers.
The shots came from this side.
Which one was standing here?
The bicycle guy.
He was covering the passenger,
probably shot him first.
Maybe the passenger was the bigger handful.
Or a bigger question mark than the driver.
Their last delivery was at Houston and Pitt.
The next one was on the Bowery at Prince.
He had no business being on this street.
Unless the driver had his
own delivery schedule.
Maybe Joel was showing
the new guy a shortcut.
Joel couldn't sit still in traffic
for more than 10 seconds.
He was always looking for a shortcut.
Did he know he was gonna
have a passenger today?
No. It was a last-minute thing.
So what's the damage here?
Well, all I can see that's missing
are four boxes of somatropin.
Somatropin. That's human growth hormone.
Athletes use it to bulk up.
That's not a legal use of the product.
How much were the four boxes worth?
A little over half a million dollars.
Now, the boxes were ordered
by four different pharmacies.
It's interesting how they all
turned up on the same day.
That's because they were all
ordered on the same day last week.
By four different pharmacies?
That's a little too interesting.
Could Joel have faked these orders?
No. The company has safeguards.
The orders have to come directly
from a licensed pharmacist.
Maybe Joel had a helper
in one of these pharmacies.
Xavier's worked for me for three years.
I know his wife, his children.
He's a good person.
You know anybody else who has
access to your order forms?
No. Could I see this phony order?
I actually placed this order for somatropin.
It's not a forgery.
You just remembered you ordered it?
Well, I had a flood back here last month.
Defective fire sprinklers.
Had to replace a lot of my stock.
Now seeing the paperwork
reminded me of the somatropin.
I'm sorry for the confusion.
Was there anything else?
- No. Thanks for your help.
- Sure.
Well, Mr. Halliwell,
I just wanna make sure
that I'm reading this right.
It says here, somatropin is contraindicated
for people with diabetes.
What happens if they take somatropin?
Well, without a doctor's supervision,
you run the risk of diabetic coma.
That's what I thought. Thank you.
We need to call some hospitals.
We've had four young males with severe
diabetic episodes in the last 48 hours.
We still don't know what triggered them.
You might wanna try and look for somatropin.
Are any of the kids still here?
Only one, Ryan Hendrickson.
His friends brought him in seven hours ago.
He'd already slipped into a coma.
We've stabilized him, but we haven't
determined how much damage there's been.
Are his friends still here?
His parents are in the waiting area.
And there's a young woman.
She was with him when they brought him in.
Over PA: Dr. Johnson,
please call extension 2198.
Miss DeSantis?
Can we speak to you over here?
We need to find out what happened to Ryan.
His diabetes messed him up.
He took something just before, right?
Something he wasn't supposed to?
Melinda, we think Ryan took a
growth hormone called somatropin
to help him build up his muscles.
That's why he's in a coma.
We need to know where he got it,
so other kids don't end up
in the bed next to him.
Ryan injected this stuff
he got from this guy Lane.
Lane Ruddock.
Lane said Ryan needed
to get bigger and stronger.
Why? Was Ryan doing sports?
He wrestles.
On a team at school?
It's not a school thing.
Come on! Dude, if you gotta
clothesline him, sell it.
Don't just stand there, move into him!
And, Jace, you have got to sell getting hit.
Grab your throat like you got
a badger stuck in there.
Come on, give me the face of pain. Sell it.
You Lane Ruddock?
What, the neighbors again?
Look, we got a right to wrestle, okay?
It's safer than hockey.
What do you mean, this?
We don't have a problem with this.
In fact, I've always wanted to try it.
Come on, come on. Climb in with me?
It's okay. Look, what're
you people doing here?
You know, what's that move...
You know, the one where
you take the other guy,
you spin him over the top of your head?
- What, the flying helicopter?
- Flying helicopter.
And then you plant him head down on the mat,
it's so extreme.
You know, I'm surprised
more guys don't end up like,
well, your buddy Ryan,
in a coma, on a respirator.
What? Hey, look, I had nothing to do with it.
Detectives.
Who are they?
Those are our buddies. They're
searching your parents' house.
We found 1 box. Two-third's full.
The somatropin, where are the other 3 boxes?
Hey, buddy, you better answer her question,
or you're going smackdown for two murders
all by yourself.
I didn't kill nobody, okay? I swear.
Those guys, they fronted me 1 box.
That was it. It was just 1 box.
Excuse me. Could you get
that box for me, up on top?
Thank you very much.
Drop the box.
What's going on? What're you doing to my son?
Arresting him.
Seems he went into the
pharmacy business for himself.
We have Lane Ruddock. We have the box
of stolen somatropin you sold him.
We have an eyewitness who puts
your van at the crime scene.
Am I forgetting something?
- The sneaker.
- We have a sneaker print in your van
that matches a sneaker print in
the cargo area of the truck.
That's it for now.
We'll have an update once we
grab up your accomplices.
You know, I don't wanna tell you
anything you already know, Luke,
but this is a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity you have here
to tell us your story.
Now this opportunity has the shelf life
of, like, one, maybe two hours.
By then, we'll have all
your buddies in custody.
Oh, the tales they will tell.
None of them with a happy ending.
- An hour, Luke.
- Two at the most.
Hang on a second.
Do I have your permission to
talk to them about it?
My client's ready to cooperate.
He had no prior knowledge of
any plan to kill the drivers.
He wasn't even aware
his accomplices were armed.
He didn't come forward before because...
Because he was afraid for his life.
We know all the disclaimers by heart.
What does he have to say?
Nothing, until the DA
signs off on the agreement,
which is as follows:
20 years in a medium-security facility
in return for his testimony and
his plea to second-degree robbery
and 4 counts of forgery.
4 counts of forgery?
4 boxes, 4 forged order forms, 4 counts.
Do I need to repeat anything?
No. We'll be right back.
That's a deal I can live with.
What?
The kid's copping to forging 4 order forms.
One of the pharmacists, Halliwell,
he told us his order was
legit, it wasn't forged.
One of them's lying.
My bet, it's not this kid.
Just got the good word.
His accomplices are in custody.
Two weapons recovered.
One's the same caliber
as the slugs from the victims.
The kid's stuck to his story.
He dummied up 4 orders of growth hormone,
including the order from
Halliwell's Pharmacy.
If Halliwell didn't order this
stuff, why tell you he did?
Because if he told us the truth
that the order was faked,
he knew we'd be back. He
knew he'd have to testify,
he knew he'd be under more
scrutiny than he wanted.
What do you think he's hiding?
Mr. Cardenas, is Mr. Halliwell here?
No. You just missed him.
Oh, rats.
So, maybe you can help us
with some information about this
flood, with the sprinkler system.
You should wait for Mr. Halliwell.
It's not that complicated.
The flood was just back there where
you keep all the prescriptions?
Yes.
Well, the sprinkler system
runs through the whole store.
Why wasn't the whole place flooded?
Well, Mr. Halliwell said
that the back sprinklers
are on a different waterline than the front.
Excuse me, but...
Don't worry, he does this all the time.
Were you here when the sprinklers went off?
No. It happened overnight.
Mr. Halliwell was already mopping up
when I got in on Saturday morning.
Do you know why they went off?
Well, he said it was 'cause they hadn't had
the scheduled maintenance done on them.
Something about, you know,
insurance not paying.
Was there a lot of damage?
Well, yeah, the whole back was wet.
We lost a lot of inventory.
How much?
Well, I don't know. Mr.
Halliwell took care of that.
He's the one who keeps
track of the inventory?
For the prescription medicines, yeah.
Thank you.
And who fills out the prescription
mostly, you or Mr. Halliwell?
I count out the pills. And
I do the ointments.
Mr. Halliwell does the fluids,
IV drips, cancer meds.
It's very toxic stuff.
Hey, what are you doing.
You're gonna set that off.
It's not going off because there's no water.
Your boss disconnected the front
sprinklers from the water line
so when he set off the sprinkler system,
only the back of the store got wet.
Mr. Halliwell did it on purpose? Why?
Why don't you just tell us what
you saw that Saturday morning?
Just that everything back there
was all wet, that's all.
Where were the drugs?
I don't know. He told me to
take the rest of the day off.
When I got back on Monday morning,
everything was back on the shelves.
I got my file on Halliwell over here.
He put in a big order six
weeks ago, I know that.
You sure you don't want
any cake? It's really good.
No, thank you. Sorry to pull you
away from your birthday party.
Every year I tell my assistant,
"Please, no parties."
But, hey, what can you do?
Just smile and eat cake.
Yeah.
So what did Halliwell order?
Oh...
Doxorubicin, gemcitabine,
dactinomycin, ifosfamide, BCNU.
What kind of drugs are those?
Chemotherapy drugs. Cancer.
Did he order any other drugs?
No.
Oh, he said a fire sprinkler went off,
and his supply of chemo
drugs got contaminated.
Just the chemo?
That's what he said.
Well, our records show
he bought almost $180,000
worth of drugs from you.
Mmm-hmm.
Is that considered a large purchase?
Well, it's triple the amount he bought
from us in the previous quarter.
- $60,000.
- Mmm-hmm.
Why such a big jump?
Well, I did my homework.
I put together that he sold 4 times more
chemo drugs than he was buying from me.
I was losing business to a competitor.
A competitor? Do you know who?
Well, he wouldn't tell me.
When did you have this conversation with him?
About two months ago.
You know, on second thought,
I think I'll have a piece of cake.
Be right back.
This competitor he's worried about?
There isn't any.
He's Halliwell's only supplier.
So Halliwell's doing a neat trick,
turning $60 grand worth of cancer drugs
into over $200,000 in sales.
His customers might not think it's so neat.
Jim, I'm sure you realize
that commitments were made
based on the one you made to us.
And I intend to live up to it.
I'm glad to hear that.
I never expected any less from you.
I just need to renegotiate the terms.
The amount of the gift every month,
it's just too much.
How much would you be comfortable with?
I need to cut it by half.
I really need some relief here.
I'll see what I can do.
People consider you someone
they can count on, Jim.
You don't wanna risk disappointing them.
How did you people get my name?
From the state Medicaid.
You and your wife have your prescriptions
filled at Halliwell's Pharmacy?
It's just me now. My wife
passed away two months ago.
We're very sorry.
Mr. Lowell, if you don't mind our
asking, what did she die of?
Claudine died of ovarian cancer.
She was diagnosed two years ago last March.
She had surgery and...
Then she went on chemo.
Here. Smell this. It's a brandy wine.
We planted them three months ago.
That was the last day she was outside.
What was your wife's prognosis
when she was diagnosed?
They said that she could beat it,
she was in the early stages.
And there was no sign of
improvement during the two years?
No. The cancer just spread.
It got worse.
The suffering, the pain and the nausea.
What did her doctor say?
"Every cancer is different."
That's what he said.
Then he'd go and write another prescription.
You didn't happen to keep any of them?
No.
What would I do with that stuff?
I mean, it didn't do us any good
when Claudine was alive.
Two years from diagnosis to death,
with a survivable cancer, a
full course of chemotherapy.
And her doctor's giving her good odds.
Yeah, odds don't mean anything
when the medication you're
taking might as well be water.
That's Halliwell's neat trick.
He's diluting the drugs.
We talked to the families of eight of
Halliwell's customers who died of cancer.
They all said the same thing.
There was no improvement, the
medications weren't helping,
the cancers just got worse.
How long has he been at it?
We checked the drug company's records
and Halliwell's sales records.
He's been selling more cancer
drugs than he's been buying
for at least four years.
We could be talking about thousands
of diluted prescriptions.
And hundreds of deaths
that might've been prevented.
What about the drugs
Halliwell is dispensing now?
They're at full potency.
His conscience finally got to him.
More likely the drug company
salesman did, when he told Halliwell
he noticed the discrepancy between
his sales and his purchases.
That's why he had the flood.
Making a case against him solely
on the basis of sales records
will turn into the battle
of the bean counters.
We need physical, medical proof
he diluted those prescriptions.
None of Halliwell's customers thought of
saving a sample of their old prescriptions.
The dead ones might've.
Since I needed soft tissue for the tests,
I only looked at people who
died in the last six months.
Of those, I identified 14 cancer patients
who statistically should still be alive
if they'd received the right
dosage of chemotherapy.
Nine families gave me permission
to exhume the bodies.
Only nine?
Well, you must have some bedside manner.
There's a reason I work with dead people.
After putting their livers under the
microscope, here's what I have.
Five had very low
concentrations of chemo drugs,
75% lower than it should have been,
had they been getting the
dosage they were prescribed.
And the four other victims?
Well, the results on three were
inconclusive for a variety of reasons.
On the other hand, number nine showed
an unusually high concentration
of the drugs doxorubicin and ifosfamide.
This number nine actually have a name?
The medical examiner just told me
they wanted to do some tests on Claudine,
to see how the medicine she was
taking affected her cancer.
I said if it's gonna help somebody
else, sure, go right ahead.
You don't want anybody
going through what she did.
No, ma'am.
You were frustrated and angry
the drugs weren't working.
Yeah.
It must've been discouraging
for the both of you.
Anyone in your position...
You might, at some point,
think that death was inevitable.
Mr. Lowell,
there's no easy way to say this.
We think we know why the
drugs weren't working.
We believe Mr. Halliwell
was diluting them for profit.
Your wife never got
the full dosage, Mr. Lowell,
or the full benefit of the chemotherapy.
You thought we were gonna say
something else, didn't you?
That we found out that your wife died
of a massive dose of cancer drugs.
Doxorubicin and ifosfamide.
Maybe that the pain was unbearable,
the drugs weren't working.
You had no way of knowing that Mr.
Halliwell was diluting them.
So, you thought
that you would do the one thing
that would stop Claudine's agony.
So you and your wife, you made a decision.
And you used the rest of the
medicine that she had left
and injected it in her IV.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
I killed her...
I killed her for nothing.
Oh, God.
You know I hate hypotheticals.
If there's a factual basis to your question,
then let's deal with those facts.
Like, hypothetically,
if one of the nine exhumed bodies died
as a result of an assisted suicide,
then, yes, that's murder. And, yes,
I'd be duty-bound to prosecute it.
Well, then, forget we brought it up at all.
It's not that easy.
If we use the other eight
exhumations against Halliwell,
there is no legal way to hide
the results of the ninth,
from me or anyone else.
Like you, I'd hate to put
some poor widower in jail,
but once the cat's out of
the bag, I have no choice.
Well, then we don't use
the exhumations at all.
Those exhumations are good evidence against
Mr. Halliwell and I will be using them.
So we can't convict Halliwell
without sending Lowell to jail.
Apparently not.
If it weren't for him,
Lowell and his wife would never have even
considered suicide in the first place.
Carver says he has no choice.
Let's give him one.
Let's give him better
evidence against Halliwell.
Look, I was noticing here.
Some of the pharmacy's customers
have the same address.
- The Brightest Star Home.
- Sounds like a nursing home.
It's up in Westchester.
Halliwell's home turf. He's
even ripping off his neighbors.
That's what's interesting.
According to the Medicaid records,
Mr. Halliwell was practically giving
the meds away to these people.
Mr. Halliwell has been
filling our prescriptions
for our residents for many years.
At less than cost.
That's our arrangement with him.
An arrangement. Does he have a
financial interest in the home?
No.
I see there's a Reverend Mills,
heads the board of your trustees.
Are you owned by a religious group?
We are a nondenominational residence.
But you're owned by a religious group.
The Church of the Sacred Redeemer.
Are you a member of the church?
I'm an elder.
And Mr. Halliwell?
He's an elder also.
So supplying drugs to the residents here,
that's his gift to the church.
And this arrangement, that's
a pledge he made?
A very generous pledge, yes.
A couple thousand dollars
prescriptions a month
doesn't sound very generous,
especially from a church elder.
There's more to it than that, right?
Jim Halliwell has pledged
$1.5 million toward a recreation center.
$1.5 million bucks. When did
he make this pledge?
Four years ago.
His generosity to the church
has set a terrific example.
I see it's inspired your employees.
These charities they're involved in,
AIDS babies, the indigent sick.
One of the employees collects clothing
and other items from the residents.
Yes, once they've passed away,
whatever the family doesn't want.
Whatever's in the room, whatever
would normally get thrown away.
Yes.
Could we meet this employee, you know,
to give him a, you know, "attaboy"?
Kenny'll be home from school next week.
He still doesn't know what
he's gonna do with his degree.
So, I would really appreciate
if you'd talk to him,
give him some career guidance.
Well, that would be fine.
Just have him give me a call.
Good stuff. Thank you, Jim. Penny.
See you on Sunday, Reverend.
That's quite a compliment,
sending you his son for advice.
The Reverend told our committee
he's diverting funds
from the volunteers' bazaar to the
planning group for the recreation center.
Why is that?
He said some people weren't
living up to their pledges.
He told me to talk to you about it.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
What's going on, Jim?
Business has been off,
and I told him I had to cut
back on our monthly giving.
We can't. We made a commitment.
Well, it's not forever.
We're not the only ones.
Other people have had to cut back.
Other people buy pews.
We're building a recreation center.
What kind of example are we setting?
Well, we can make it up
to them in other ways.
We can volunteer more time at the church.
We don't just go to church with these
people, Jim. We're on the PTA with them,
the chamber of commerce.
You want everyone to know
we're pleading poverty?
We're not poor.
Jim, people respect us. They look up to us.
They like us, our kids. We can't back out.
I only take what the families let me
and I give it to homeless groups,
shelters for runaways, battered women.
What else besides clothes?
Old purses, unopened toiletries.
Clock radios.
Sure, yeah. Small appliances,
kitchenware, everything gets used.
What about over-the-counter
medications, like aspirin?
Sure, vitamins, cold medicines.
Prescriptions?
No. No, we have to throw those away.
That's expensive stuff.
I mean, all this is nice, but those
medications can save people's lives.
You see first hand how people suffer
just because they can't
afford the right medications.
Like doxorubicin, and
interferon, and aldesleukin.
I know what you mean.
You do?
When someone dies at the home, of cancer,
the drugs that they have left, they just
get tossed away, doing no one any good?
I mean, aren't you a little tempted
to slip them in your pocket,
and make sure they get to the
people who really need them?
That's against regulations.
But it crosses your mind.
How about…
Mrs. Barlowe who passed away 3 days ago?
They told us she was taking
aldesleukin, for renal cancer.
That's a treatment for AIDS, isn't it?
And you just threw it in the trash?
Yes.
Then it would've been in the
dumpster when we checked.
You see, we did a little dumpster diving.
It's pretty nasty.
But we didn't find any of Mrs.
Barlowe's medications.
Well, look, maybe society thinks
what I'm doing is illegal...
But it's not immoral.
How old are these prescriptions?
Some of them might've been
filled a couple of months ago.
I thought these drugs could help people.
Not these drugs.
We were able to recover eight more chemo
prescriptions that came from the rest home.
Of the 23 we had tested, half were diluted.
The labels are partially scraped off,
but they're still identifiable as
coming from Halliwell's Pharmacy.
It's a fine piece of detective
work, but I can't use it.
The medications have been
through too many hands.
I couldn't prove to a jury
beyond a reasonable doubt,
Halliwell's the one who
diluted them. I'm sorry.
The exhumations are still our best evidence.
Good news, Charlie.
Well, these might not convince a jury
but they might convince someone else.
This is an incredible story.
Well, you have the lab
report right in front of you.
And as you can see, the vials
still have Mr. Halliwell's label.
But there's nothing wrong with the medication
Mr. Halliwell is dispensing now?
Apparently not.
Then I don't understand how I can help you.
We believe Mr. Halliwell
diluted the drugs to pay off
the $1.5 million pledge
he made to your church.
You know, you two make a very good team.
Look, if Jim had given me any hint
that this pledge was a hardship,
I never would've accepted it.
But so far, he's kept up
his end of the bargain.
How's he been doing the last six weeks?
Well, he's been wanting to cut back.
He told me business hasn't been good.
I bet.
I'm sure you're both terrific detectives,
but I can't reconcile the
Jim Halliwell you describe
with the one that I know.
Jim and his wife Penny are
both pillars of the community.
How long have they been
pillars of the community?
I really couldn't say.
It's something you grow into.
Can you say when he became a church elder?
When was that, about four years ago?
That sounds about right.
I can't help noticing, Detective, the way you
pull together all these different elements.
Good stuff.
It's good stuff.
Reverend,
what I can't help noticing, is that's about
the third time you've complimented us.
Is that how you got Jim Halliwell
to pony up a $1.5 million bucks?
Ultimately, the gift has
to come from the heart,
but a little encouragement goes along way.
And making him a church elder
went all the way to the bank.
Those kinds of things are important to Jim.
Jim and Penny are very
involved in the community.
They're well-regarded, and they
take justifiable pride in that.
They wouldn't wanna
disappoint their neighbors.
They'd be ashamed.
Well, you know, Detective,
shame is a very underrated emotion.
In the big city, it's very easy
to go unnoticed by others.
So your conscience becomes your only witness.
And for most of us, that's not enough.
And I'm sure every Sunday you play
that card for all it's worth.
Thank you very much for talking
to us. One more thing.
Assisted suicide. What's
your church's position?
It's contrary to God's Law.
A sin.
Thank you.
I filled the syringe
with the chemo medicine,
all the way up to the top,
and then I injected it into her IV,
and then I filled the syringe again
all the way up with the rest of the medicine.
What happened after you injected the drugs?
She was feeling worse,
her breathing became hard,
and she kind of, like,
seized up.
Yeah, she stayed like that,
in a coma
for two days.
It took her two days to die.
How did you get the idea
to use the cancer drugs?
Well, when Claudine first
started using the chemo,
the doctor told her to be careful,
because the medicine is a poison.
If you use too much, you could die.
You never discussed what you
were doing with anybody?
No.
Did you buy extra medicine from Mr.
Halliwell to make sure you had enough?
No.
Claudine and I, we didn't want
anyone knowing what we were doing.
We just did what we had
to do, you know, just...
Just the two of us.
Mr. Lowell, it took Mrs. Lowell
2 days to die?
Yeah. 2 days.
I can't imagine what he went
through, waiting for her to die.
That must've been the worst hour of his life.
Hour? He said two days.
Well, I'm pretty sure I
heard him say an hour.
Maybe I need a prescription for my hearing.
- Reverend.
- Jim,
I'm really glad you're back on board.
It'll make all the difference.
Thank you, Reverend.
Hey, Jim?
Can we have a word?
Hello.
Aren't you gonna introduce us?
Penny, this is Detective...
I forgot your name.
I'm Robert Goren, and this is
Detective Alex Eames.
- My wife Penny.
- Nice to meet you.
What it's about is one of
your customers, Frank Lowell.
Maybe you don't remember him.
No, I know who he is.
Then you know his wife Claudine died.
Of ovarian cancer, yes.
Actually, that's not what killed her.
Mr. Lowell admitted to us
it was an assisted suicide.
He pumped her full of
doxorubicin and ifosfamide.
I'm sorry to hear that.
But it's really none of my business.
Well, no, apparently, it is your business.
Mr. Lowell made a statement.
He said he came to you. He told
you his wife was getting worse,
she was in constant pain,
and he asked you to give him something
to take her out of her misery.
You told him to give her
all the cancer medication that she had left,
in one big shot.
That's not true.
It's right here in the statement.
You told him how to kill his wife.
That's assisting a suicide.
Well, that's ridiculous.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Nothing wrong?
Excuse me, Reverend, didn't you tell
us assisting a suicide is a sin?
Well, yes, but...
Well, there you go. It's a sin.
But it's all lies.
I never talked to this man about suicide.
Come on, Penny.
Oh, that's it, run away.
You better get yourself a lawyer
'cause the next time you see us,
we'll be arresting you for murder.
This is crazy. I never murdered anyone.
Jim wouldn't help anybody commit suicide.
"He told me to give Claudine
all the drugs at once.
"That's what I did. An hour
later, Claudine was dead."
That's what Frank Lowell told us.
He's lying.
You keep saying that.
No, he is lying, and I can prove it.
How?
There's a fact in here
you can prove isn't true?
Show me this untrue fact.
Is it on this page or...
She didn't die in an hour. She couldn't have.
Why is that?
The drugs wouldn't have worked that fast.
We know how much doxorubicin
and ifosfamide she had left.
Our experts said it was enough
to kill her in an hour.
It's impossible.
Listen, I've been a
pharmacist for over 20 years.
I know what I'm talking about.
Well, how long? Two hours?
Twelve? One day?
I don't know. But there's
no way she died in an hour.
Well, I'm sure we'd all
like to know why that is.
I'd just be speculating.
There's no way that she
would die in one hour.
I mean, that's not speculating,
that's certainty.
There was something wrong
with her drugs, wasn't there?
No.
You diluted her drugs, didn't you?
That's why you knew she
wouldn't die in one hour.
You wanna know how long it took her?
You know how long it took for the
poisons to eat away at her heart,
and her lungs?
Two days.
It was a mistake.
It was an honest mistake.
An honest mistake he made for four years.
You even diluted the drugs that
you sent to the old age home.
- No.
- Jim,
they found the vials. They showed them to me.
Tell them why you did it, Jim. Go ahead.
Tell them you did it to pay
off the $1.5 million pledge.
Go ahead.
Who knows, they might forgive you.
I'm sorry.
I just didn't wanna let you down.
Please forgive me.
You're under arrest, Mr.
Halliwell. Please forgive me!
Penny!
The final tally was 26,000 prescriptions.
He plead to one count of fraud and
tampering for every patient affected.
1,200 counts.
We agreed to a sentence of 15 years to life.
His chance to be the pillar
of a whole new community.