In New York City's war on crime,
the worst criminal offenders are pursued
by the detectives of the Major Case Squad.
These are their stories.
...until George finally pulled me aside
and explained the difference
between hegemony and hominy.
In any event,
the reason that I crashed this
wonderful gathering, George,
was to thank you for your years of service
as Chairman of the Department
of American Studies.
Well, have you made a
decision on my replacement?
No.
You know, if Sanders doesn't get the chair,
he's threatening to leave.
George, it has to be my decision
along with the regents'.
I mean, Sanders is a brilliant teacher
when he bothers to show up to class.
But with lectures and talk shows...
He even did an ad for the Gap.
And where is he today?
Probably still working on that rap record.
- Dr. Winthrop?
- Well, what can I do for you, Mark?
I need to talk to you about another
extension on my dissertation.
Hmm. I was hoping you could
speak to the new chair...
Well, as soon as there is one,
you can speak to him or her yourself.
FELLOWES: I can't believe he said rap record.
Sanders will flip his afro.
Hello, Mark. Were you waiting for one of us?
Mmm-mmm.
So, if Winthrop's soured on Sanders,
does that put you in the lead?
Winthrop doesn't much like me, either.
My critique of patriarchy in academia
hit a little too close to home.
Oh, donnez-moi un break. I thought
the politics at Oxford were insane.
You know why the battles
in academia are so vicious?
It's because the stakes are so low.
Are you sure?
I distinctly heard him say him or her.
And "her" can only mean Dr. Fellowes.
I talked to her last week.
She said it was obvious I'd
never finish my dissertation,
and it was time to let
someone else have my spot.
I'd hate to see that happen, Mark.
A decade of hard work down the drain.
Now if you were head of the
department, would you...
But I'm not head of the department.
That's up to Winthrop.
You know that.
How dare you characterize
anything I do as a rap record.
Call it whatever you want.
I prefer "danceable education."
I expect my professors to be
in the classroom, teaching.
I'm not your professor.
Just because you run this
university like a plantation,
don't make you massa and we your field hands.
I came here to discuss the future of
American Studies at Hudson University.
I am the future of American Studies.
And if you don't make me
head of the department,
I will leave.
And sue you for discrimination. Dig?
We may be here awhile, Kate.
I'll make coffee.
How did you get in here?
What are you doing? No! No!
DETECTIVE PONDS: The guard saw
them come in at around 9:15.
We'll need a list of everybody
with keys to the building.
Any idea what Winthrop was
doing here with his secretary?
Well, the guy who should know,
the vice-rector, Mr. Frisch,
well, he doesn't know.
Nothing in his book.
Just a breakfast meeting with
something called the "AS Committee."
Ask Mr. Frisch what that is.
The killer came out from
the front. Winthrop...
he raised his arm,
took the first blow to his wrist from a...
a blunt instrument
with a round striking face.
The killer chose a weapon
that would have meaning.
A gavel.
The killer wanted justice.
Winthrop came in the room.
The killer was already waiting.
Winthrop turned on the light,
and the killer attacked him.
The secretary had gone to make coffee,
she walked in on it.
She tried to get away.
Mr. Frisch, when's the last
time you spoke to Mr. Winthrop?
Around 5:00.
And that meeting you asked about,
it was a search committee for the
American Studies Department.
They're deciding on a new
chairman for the department.
Does Miss Robbins live alone?
I believe she has a roommate.
LIN: Oh, my God, what am
I gonna tell her parents?
They're supposed to come up
from Charleston this weekend.
Did you see her last night?
When I came back from the gym,
she was working on her computer
and listening to a CD.
And she was listening on these?
Yes. I think there was
something wrong with the CD.
Why do you say that?
She kept pressing stop
and play, stop and play.
Well, there's no CD in here.
Did you see her leave?
Yes.
She grabbed something out of her printer.
She said she had to go to Winthrop's office
for a couple of hours to work.
(PHONE RINGING)
Here's the last document she printed.
Hey, it's lyrics.
The writer came of age in the '60s and '70s,
probably in the Bay Area, Oakland.
Here, "Flipping Pancakes for Preschoolers."
That's the Black Panthers' breakfast program.
And he works for Hudson University.
Okay, how do you figure that?
Here, "Massa will go the way
of the Dutchman's mercenary
"who gave his name to the plantation."
Henry Hudson sailed for
the Dutch East India Company.
He's the Dutchman's mercenary,
and the plantation is Hudson University.
And massa would be Winthrop.
So the writer's middle-aged, African-American,
from California, works at the university.
And wanted Winthrop to
disappear like Henry Hudson.
Hmm.
You could tell all that
just from these lyrics?
Do you know why Dr. Winthrop had his secretary
transcribe the lyrics to your CD?
You're asking the wrong person.
Unfortunately, we can't ask the right persons.
GOREN: You're up for the chairmanship
of your department, right?
Winthrop was meeting
with the search committee?
The committee had already voted
to approve my recommendation.
Well, maybe Massa Winthrop was hoping
your lyrics would change their mind.
What is this about?
Your whereabouts Tuesday night.
I was in my office, here, grading papers.
These papers here?
Yes, sure, those papers.
"Bitch: Gender Metaphors in the
American Literary Tradition."
These courses sound like a lot of fun.
I try to keep things lively.
This is cool here, what
you wrote in the margin.
"Civilization, an old bitch gone in the teeth."
Did you make that up?
No, Ezra Pound did.
EAMES: Can anybody vouch
you were here all evening?
Valerie Goodman, she's one
of my teaching assistants.
Good old Ezra Pound.
VALERIE: I was checking footnotes
for Professor Sanders'
next book until about 10:00.
He told us he was grading
papers on gender metaphors.
That sounds right.
He made an interesting
notation on one of the papers.
"Civilization, an old bitch
gone in the teeth."
It's by Ezra Pound. Did you know that?
No, but it sounds like Pound.
Professor Sanders knew it was Pound.
Why wouldn't he?
Well, he would. But you see,
the person who made the notation,
the person who actually graded the paper,
attributed the quote to T.S. Eliot.
Professor Sanders wasn't in that
night grading papers, was he?
True or false, Miss Goodman?
And we don't give incompletes.
He said he had a dinner with some people
from NYU about a job offer.
How long was the dinner?
He came back around 8:30.
- He was in a bad mood.
- Why?
He didn't say. He just
shut himself in his office
and got on the phone.
Then he left at 9:30.
He told me if anybody asked,
he was grading papers all night.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, Valerie. Thanks.
Doesn't sound like he got that job offer.
That would make him more desperate
to get his promotion here.
Except Miss Goodman alibis him
for the time of the murder.
He made a call from his office.
Professor Sanders is a charismatic teacher
surrounded by impressionable minds.
Students lie for him.
Maybe one of them killed for extra credit.
Doorknobs in Winthrop's office
had been wiped clean.
No witnesses who saw anybody leave
the administration building.
Any candidates for the extra credit?
We've cleared Sanders' teaching assistants.
Now we're looking at the PhD
students in American Studies.
Sanders is their adviser. He's
probably known some of them for years.
How's this for a dissertation topic?
"Fighting in the Captain's Tower.
"The Influence of T.S. Eliot and Ezra Pound
"on American Popular Culture."
Sounds like the same guy
who graded Sanders' papers.
Yeah, and confused Eliot
and Pound. Mark Bayley.
He's been working on this
dissertation for 10 years.
Don't universities put a
clock on these things?
Bayley's gotten five extensions.
And a nice chunk of change in student loans.
BAYLEY: Professor Sanders travels a lot,
so I offered to grade those papers.
Is that why your thesis is taking so long,
you're too busy doing favors
for Professor Sanders?
My thesis is coming along fine.
"The old bitch gone in the teeth."
That's Pound, right?
No, Eliot.
Professor Sanders says it's Pound.
EAMES: You sleep here?
I'm between apartments.
Besides your student loans,
how do you support yourself?
I work at the library on Saturdays.
Well, at least you eat healthy.
I told you it was Pound.
Maybe that's why your
thesis is taking so long.
When'd you quit?
You've got nicotine gum.
Two years ago.
When does your current extension
run out? At the end of this semester?
It's just a technicality.
Winthrop's phone logs have you
calling him every day about it.
You were practically stalking him.
That's not true.
Anyway, extensions are up to
the chair of the department.
The new chair.
Your hero, Professor Sanders.
Sanders call you Tuesday
night to see Winthrop?
No, I was here Tuesday
night. Nobody called me.
What about your girlfriend?
What girlfriend?
The one who bought you these shoes.
- I bought them.
- No, you didn't.
Those are the kind of shoes
you buy. Converse, Vans.
Come on, these are...
Well, they definitely have a woman's touch.
I bought these shoes myself. I had a wedding.
You wore tan shoes to a wedding?
Yes, I wore tan shoes.
You people are wasting my time.
Not just any tan shoes.
$2,000-a-pair John Lobb tan shoes.
We could just ask.
(SIGHING)
See anything you like?
I don't see anything I don't like.
My wife thinks I need a new
pair of everyday shoes.
Well, I should say.
Darling. These?
I don't know. The whole ankle-boot thing...
I know. You really liked the
pair that Mark was wearing.
He said he bought them here recently.
Not him, his girlfriend.
Mark never pays for anything
unless he has to.
Do you see the shoes here?
Not the exact shoe.
Oh, I'm starting to get frustrated.
Well, you'd have a record
of what they bought, right?
I mean, you could look it up.
Mark's early thirties, curly hair.
Student at Hudson, orange backpack,
chews gum, nicotine gum.
Oh, yes, yes. He came in
wearing skateboard loafers.
But his girlfriend, she's a stunner.
Then again, I'm a sucker
for the take-charge type.
Oh, you noticed that about her.
She must've made him try on 30 pairs.
She was whipping him into shape.
Not that he seemed to mind.
Oh, here they are. It was a pair
of double-buckle Williams.
Look at how Elizabeth spells
her last name. Hitchens with an “e”.
Is her number on there? I want
to ask her to dinner Saturday night.
What a good idea.
Excuse me.
Isn't that the Hudson University switchboard?
She did say something about
being a visiting professor.
A professor?
Well, he didn't tell us that.
Your cousin's a very bad boy.
Thanks.
HITCHENS: Terrible business, this murder.
My colleagues at Oxford gave me
dire warnings about America.
And this just confirms their worst fears.
Well, we hope it doesn't
sour you on our country.
Oh, heavens, no. A little
danger keeps you on your toes.
This place doesn't look all that dangerous.
Hudson's taking good care of you.
Actually, an Oxford alumnus volunteered it.
He's spending the year abroad. So
rather than having the flat sit empty...
How lucky for you.
Well, I assume that my good fortune
isn't what brought you here.
You are obviously here to talk
to me about Winthrop's murder,
which I'm sorry to say I know nothing about.
We're going with the theory it's
somebody at the university.
Well, everyone knows that academics
are all talk and no action.
Does that include you?
If it did, I would've stayed in my
cozy little office on Manor Road
lecturing women's writing
and punting on the Cherwell on the weekends.
No skinny-dipping in Parson's Pleasure?
Very good, Detective.
Did you memorize the Oxford
tour guide on your way here?
No.
No, I spent a couple of weeks there once
chasing coeds.
Took you that long to catch one? I'm shocked.
Well, that's very funny, Professor.
Does Mark Bayley find you funny?
He might, if he had a sense of
humor. I don't know him that well.
Well enough to buy him a pair of shoes.
Just a gesture.
You know graduate students.
They never have a pot to piss in,
and Bayley was on his uppers, literally.
I see you like opera.
These tickets for Don Giovanni.
Yes. Not my favorite.
I lean towards Penderecki.
I hate to be a spoilsport, but did
you see Bayley Tuesday night?
No. Why would I?
EAMES: You might have, if you
were having an affair with him.
Well, that would be
against university policy.
The bottom line, she didn't alibi Bayley.
No. But she lied about
having an affair with him.
Men only let two kinds
of women buy shoes for them,
their mommies and their significant others.
Hitchens' work visa expires in three months.
Any extension has to be supported by
the new chairman of her department.
Assuming Sanders would support her
and that she even wants to stay.
She's bought a new subscription
for the opera.
She's applied for a driver's license.
She's making herself at home.
I didn't tell them about the shoes.
It's that big detective who noticed them.
That big detective is smart.
He traced the shoes to the store.
The whole thing's coming apart.
People think Sanders had
something to do with it.
Now he won't get the chairmanship.
It'll blow over.
What?
Nothing. Just have your gum and get into bed.
I doubt if Roland Sanders would
want to keep Elizabeth on.
He once accused her of being an apologist
for Australia's shabby
treatment of the aborigines.
- She's Australian?
- Mmm-hmm.
A graduate of the University of Sydney.
Well, you could never tell by her accent.
What else do you know about her?
Well, she ran an educational
foundation in Australia.
Rising star at Oxford.
If she's a rising star at Oxford,
why leave in the first place?
I don't know. Whatever her
plans, they don't matter now.
Sanders has no hope of becoming
chair. His candidacy is tainted.
Who's next in line?
Christine Fellowes. It's pretty much a lock.
In theory, I wouldn't be opposed to
offering someone of Elizabeth's caliber
a permanent position.
In theory. What about in practice?
I'm not head of the department yet.
Please, the regents will decide on Friday.
- But you're already packing.
- Well...
Let me help you with this.
Penderecki. The Devils of Loudon.
You like opera?
I'm getting to. This was a gift.
There was a beautiful performance
of Don Giovanni the other night.
You would've loved it.
I did. A friend took me.
Friends with good taste, huh?
One more thing.
This professional student, Mark Bayley,
would you give him an extension
if you became chair?
He's already written a
thousand pages of his thesis
and he's nowhere near done.
He needs to go.
Professor Hitchens will be sorry.
Why would she? She thinks he's an idiot.
Oh, no. I think she's
been able to overlook his shortcomings.
They've become close friends.
At least, that's what we heard. I...
Your source is wrong.
Elizabeth wouldn't violate
university policy.
Not if she wanted to be asked back.
In American literature,
the descent into madness
is usually preceded by obsession.
A consuming obsession. Example, anyone?
All right. I'll get you started.
Moby-Dick.
What characterizes Ahab's obsession?
Yes, in the back.
The dogged, unrelenting pursuit of evil.
Interesting, evil.
I always fancied it was man's
unrelenting pursuit of his own potency.
All right, everyone, I expect
you to make a dent
in Moby-Dick by the end of the week.
Sometimes a whale is just a whale.
Nothing is ever just something.
Not even detectives.
Or professors.
Or graduate students, for that matter.
That sounds a bit ominous.
Well, it's certainly not
good news for Mark Bayley.
We're about to arrest him
for Winthrop's murder.
Am I expected to run and warn him?
Because you've seriously misconstrued
my relationship with him.
But you can settle a bet for me.
My partner thinks that
Bayley acted alone.
But I think that...
I think that Professor Sanders...
he put him up to it.
Why do you think that?
Well, Sanders,
he had the most to gain
from Winthrop's murder.
And the killing, well, it required
qualities that elude Bayley.
Planning, organization. I mean, you agree?
Well, you're not wrong about Mark.
There is a reason why
he hasn't finished his thesis.
He has no discipline.
I heard his thesis runs a thousand pages.
T.S. Eliot and Ezra Pound have a love
child and his name is Bob Dylan.
I mean, donnez-moi un break.
This is what passes for
scholarship in this country?
So you don't think
popular culture's fair game?
Well, Mark's is the worst kind
of pop literary analysis.
Pathetic attempt to synthesize
high and low culture.
It wouldn't butter your parsnips.
You're right. We did
Misconstrue your relationship.
No, Mark.
Well, just tell them you don't know anything.
You don't know, you don't remember.
Yes, those are all good answers.
No, I can't see you tonight.
Look, Mark, you'll be fine.
Yes, same here.
Who was that on the phone? It was Bayley.
Why is he calling your cell phone?
I was calling him back, silly.
He's worried because his great mentor
Roland Sanders has fallen out of favor,
and he wants me to put in a
good word for him with you.
Why does he think you can help him?
Well, he's under the strange
delusion that you and I are friends.
GOREN: Hey, that's quite
a woman you got there.
A real take-charge lady, Elizabeth Hitchens.
I don't know.
The clerk at the shoe store said
she had you jumping through hoops.
I don't remember.
Well, let's face it, Mark.
That's exactly the kind of
woman a guy like you needs.
Somebody that helps you,
you know, keep those thoughts focused.
Do what has to be done, right?
I don't know.
Like killing Winthrop.
I mean, that was her idea.
No. It wasn't anybody's idea.
We're pretty sure it wasn't Sanders'.
I'm sure it wasn't yours.
I mean, even Hitchens thinks
that someone would have had
to put you up to it.
What do you mean, she thinks?
Well, she said that you
didn't have any discipline.
That's why you...
Well, you never finished your thesis.
The title, "Fighting in the Captain's
Tower," that's Dylan, right?
Ezra Pound and T.S. Eliot fighting
in the captain's tower.
Desolation Row.
The whole album's a touchstone
of American literature.
That's my thesis. Exactly.
What Hitchens said, exactly,
is, "Donnez-moi un break."
I'm trying to remember what else she said.
"The worst kind of pop literary analysis."
She said it was brave.
"A pathetic attempt to synthesize
high and low culture."
No, no. You're making it up.
Oh.
How did she put it?
"it wouldn't butter your parsnips."
I'm not making it up, am I?
She used you, Mark,
to kill Winthrop, to discredit Sanders,
so the promotion would go to her
friend, Christine Fellowes.
Her close and intimate friend.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
What did I do?
You want to tell us what happened?
She told me to...
She planned it.
I'll get a stenographer.
She told Winthrop to meet her at his office.
Why did I listen to her?
How did you get in the building?
She gave me a key.
She took it from Professor Fellowes.
She said she never uses it.
You still have it?
No. I gave it back.
Mark, are you all right?
Call the paramedics!
There's no pulse. He just stopped breathing.
Bayley died of anaphylactic shock
brought on by an allergic reaction.
- A reaction to what?
- They don't know yet.
We're waiting for the tox report
and Bayley's medical records.
Before he died, he implicated Hitchens.
His statement's of no use now.
Have you heard from Scotland Yard?
They have no outstanding
warrants for Hitchens,
no open investigations.
Bayley's allergic reaction was to
peanuts, specifically peanut oil.
The nicotine gum. She spiked it
with a needle through the packaging.
She knew he was a liability.
When I went to her class,
she knew what I was doing.
She knew I'd use her words to turn him.
We can't assume she knew he had an allergy.
It's in his medical records.
He might have mentioned it to her.
What I had in mind was proof she knew.
Well, it depends if Bayley eats alone.
Two months ago, he was rushed to
Emergency from a Thai restaurant.
Peanuts are a common
ingredient in Thai cooking.
VANA: Yes, I remember them.
He got very sick. They should have told us
- he was allergic to peanuts.
- Who ordered?
The woman. She ordered
som tum. Green papaya salad.
Thai chili, fish sauce and peanuts.
Well, it's clearly marked which dishes
have peanuts. Didn't he see this?
Sure. But the woman ordered in Thai.
So Bayley wouldn't understand.
She speak fluent Thai?
Yes, but low-class.
Did she say how she learned it?
She said she lived in Thailand 15 years ago.
(STAMMERING)
She say where?
I asked. She laughed. She said in Chatuchak.
Chatuchak is the location
of the Lard Yao Maximum Women's Prison.
I did a search for Australian women
who had been imprisoned in Thailand.
I found one who matched Hitchens.
Nicole Wallace.
She and her French boyfriend
were convicted of killing eight
male tourists in Thailand.
She'd seduce them, they'd rob
them and he'd kill them.
At the trial, she testified against him.
He got life, she served 10 years
and got deported back to Australia.
It could be her.
The Australian Consulate's getting me a
passport photo of the real Elizabeth Hitchens.
The one who was studying
at the University of Sydney
while Nicole Wallace was in prison.
Wallace passed herself off
as a professor of literature.
- Quite a feat.
- Well, maybe it was catching up to her.
That might explain why she's
desperate to establish herself here.
Then where's the real Professor Hitchens?
Nicole Wallace killed
the real Elizabeth Hitchens,
applied for a passport in her
name and went off to Oxford.
This woman's very, very good.
Oh, good, you're both here.
Can we come in?
We heard. It's official.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Now that you're chair of the department,
you can give your friend that
permanent job she's wanted so much.
Well, I don't know about that.
GOREN: She's a real catch.
Now I could be wrong,
but there can't be many Oxford professors
who've spent time in Thai prison.
For eight murders, no less.
Are we meant to take this seriously?
It's thanks to her you got your promotion.
She helped Mark Bayley kill Winthrop.
You can stop right now.
Bayley told us the whole
story before he died
from poisoning.
I don't believe any of this.
Prove it for yourself.
She stole the key to the
administration building from you
and gave it to Bayley.
I would've noticed.
She slipped it back on your key ring.
Except Bayley gave her back
the wrong key by mistake.
He gave her his spare to his office.
You've really outdone yourselves, Detectives.
Well, let's check Bayley's office.
This should be the administration key.
It's you who outdid yourself, Nicole.
That is your name, Nicole Wallace?
This is utter nonsense, Christine.
It's a trick. I didn't take your key.
(WHISPERING)
You did sleep with him.
You lied to me.
For heaven's sake, Christine.
I can't have you here.
You're relieved of your
duties as of immediately.
In that case, you're under arrest.
For what?
You just got fired. You're in
violation of your work visa.
Nothing has happened to Elizabeth Hitchens
because I am Elizabeth Hitchens.
I mean, do you honestly think that
I could fool the dons of Oxford
for one minute if I wasn't who I say I am?
You had plenty of time
to read in Lard Yao Prison.
My dear woman, there is more to literary
scholarship than reading books.
Nobody said you aren't bright, Nicole.
- Elizabeth.
- Nicole.
The game's up. You botched the key exchange.
Bayley gave you the wrong key.
You know bloody well that that's not true.
No, I don't bloody well know.
But the real culprit does.
Now you see the problem.
You can't expose our trick without
exposing your own culpability.
EAMES: And you know what that's called,
your being an expert on the
modern American novel and all.
Yes, well, I never much cared for Heller.
Look, you can bang on all you want,
but I am invoking my right to be silent.
No, you don't have that right.
I know what rights are, and I'm also
invoking my right to an attorney.
- No, you don't have that right either.
- What are you talking about?
EAMES: You're a foreign national
with no green card, no tourist visa,
no valid work permit.
GOREN: That makes you a person with no status.
I can keep you as long as I want to.
Until we build a case against you.
You wouldn't dare.
What do you mean, I can't see her?
I have been retained by the
university to represent her.
She's in this country illegally.
She is here employed under the
terms of a valid work visa.
I reinstated her.
I found out the police changed
the lock on Bayley's office
so that it could be opened with a
key to the administration building.
The whole thing was a sham.
We still believe Miss Hitchens
is here under false pretenses.
You're not entitled access to her.
We'll see.
I'm walking down the block into federal court
and filing for a writ of habeas corpus.
If you really are Elizabeth
Hitchens, this will be easy.
Just tell me the name of the
educational foundation in Melbourne.
I don't have it in my papers.
I'm sure that that's a lie.
And if I am impersonating Elizabeth
Hitchens, don't you think
that I would have committed her
entire work history to memory?
That's my
social security number and my birth date.
Yes, it's remarkable
the fountain of information that can
spring from those little numbers.
Home address, next of kin,
mother's maiden name, mother's address.
Tell me, Robert, how often do you
get up to the Carmel Ridge Center?
Once a week.
And a phone call every day.
How old were you when you first realized it?
No.
You want to play, then it's
gonna have to be tit for tat.
You have to tell me something true about you,
about Nicole.
All right.
I did meet Nicole before I left for England.
She told me things.
Where is she now?
I don't know.
Carried away by dingoes? It
happens a lot in Australia.
What did she tell you?
She told me that she
enjoyed being under the thumb
of her French boyfriend,
that relinquishing responsibility to him
gave her the unimaginable freedom
to commit violent crimes
without any guilt at all.
My turn.
How old were you when you
first realized your mommy
wasn't like all the other mommies?
Seven.
Were you ashamed?
And frightened. It's my turn.
How old were you when your
father first molested you?
It's the only explanation for
your intense hatred for men.
The murders in Thailand were an attempt
to correct the tragedy of your childhood.
To punish your abuser,
absolving yourself of guilt
by using a man to kill other men.
And not that you think much of women either,
but since your mother was
too scared
and too drunk,
too self-absorbed...
- No.
- To protect you.
None of those things happened.
None of those things are true.
No, that's why you can't form connections.
That's why you use sex as
an exercise in self-hatred.
That's why when you came back from Thailand
you supported yourself with
prostitution, didn't you, Nicole?
I am Elizabeth Hitchens. I am a professor
- of literature at...
- No. No!
When I met you,
you wanted me to know who you truly were.
How smart, how funny, how charming you are.
You wanted me to know you, Nicole Wallace.
The sparkling little girl
who survived horrible abuse
with her wits intact.
(DOOR OPENING)
- HARDIN: Professor Hitchens.
- (WHISPERING) Nicole.
I was retained by the
university to represent you.
The federal court has issued
a writ of habeas corpus
Ordering your immediate release.
I advise you to leave with me. Now, please.
That foundation that you
asked me about in Melbourne,
it was the George Hurstwood Foundation.
Come on.
I'm sorry, Detective.
There was nothing I could do.
No, the foundation, it's called
the New Covenant Foundation.
Why did she say the George Hurstwood?
She was trying to tell me something?
George Hurstwood.
Well, it's Sister Carrie.
It's a novel by Theodore Dreiser.
(STAMMERING)
George Hurstwood was a saloon keeper
who stole money from his boss' safe.
Nicole used the name of a thief to...
(STAMMERING)
I need to call Melbourne.
Okay. Thank you. Yes, we'll be back in touch.
The Melbourne police
recently started investigating
the financial affairs of the
New Covenant Foundation.
They suspect that five years
ago $400,000 were embezzled
by the then-president of the foundation.
Elizabeth Hitchens. The
real Elizabeth Hitchens.
Nicole Wallace stole the
identity of an embezzler.
I'm sure she didn't know it at the time.
She found out when she heard
about the investigation.
She knew the Australians would
catch up to her in England.
They'd extradite her back home.
That's why she wants US citizenship.
Because non-violent financial crimes
aren't covered by US extradition treaties.
If she became a citizen, the
Australians couldn't touch her.
She's not a citizen yet.
She's gone.
I came here, the door was
open, her things were gone.
I'll call the airports.
(FELLOWES CRYING)
What did you think, she'd have
scones and a glass of sherry for us?