Just 8 days more to go.
I'm going crazy thinking about it.
Me, too, sweetheart.
That's enough of that.
You are so funny.
He never wants to see me again?
Your father's upset. You didn't
visit him while he was away.
I had no access.
She took me off the visitors list.
Jack, you know I only do what Milt asks.
Stop. Just stop.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
I'm sorry, Jack. He's...
Don't worry.
Milt wants to make sure
you get what's coming to you.
Don't forget your brothers
behind the wall now.
I'll keep it real.
I'm gonna miss you, Milton.
Same here, brother.
Come here.
Maybe your luck will change
now that you don't have to play me.
But who will make dinner for Mr. Milt?
We'll figure something out.
Tonight, I want him all to myself.
Oh, I don't want to set off the
security system when he gets here.
You want me to show you how?
Uh, no. Just turn the stupid thing off.
Okay.
Look at this.
Two years here turned me into a lean machine.
So what's the first thing you're
gonna do when you get out?
Oh, Milt!
Oh! You're the only one.
My little sweetheart. The only
one!
Baby.
Must be the little blue pills.
It's like it has wings on it.
Wings!
Oh! Must be dinner. I'm famished.
I'll get it. You go take your shower.
Pam?
Pam!
No!
Those bastards!
You bastards!
These entry wounds,
chest, shoulder, knee.
The shooter had no control
and couldn't resist ripping her earring off.
Like some subway punk.
He sprayed the doorway in an arc,
even hit the upper window.
You know, the shots came from down below,
but not at the bottom of the stairs.
Check the service entrance.
Well, I got 5, 6, 7, 9mm casings.
He rang the doorbell up there
and ran down here to hide?
No. He rang the doorbell down here.
He thought the service
entrance was the main door.
Here.
She answers the door. He's surprised.
He shoots wild,
probably one-handed,
cocked to one side.
Like in the gangster flicks.
He's not used to the recoil.
He loses control of the piece.
She'd ordered dinner.
The security cameras must have been off,
so she had to go to the door
to see who was there.
Why were they off?
The security system's very sophisticated.
My wife, less so.
She must have turned it off
when she sent the maid home.
Well, let's talk about who might
have wanted your wife dead.
Any candidates?
Nobody. She was an angel.
We had just finished making
beautiful love. They were after me.
All due respect,
even in a snowstorm, no one
would mistake her for you.
You think that's funny?
I have enemies everywhere.
Like your ex-business partner.
You were convicted of hiring
a hit man to kill him.
Do I look incompetent? Hmm?
If I wanted him dead, he would have been dead.
Your conviction was a
frame-up, by your enemies.
Exactly.
My competitors.
In the clothing business?
This "Winter Clothes For All Seasons."
This is the original store.
Yeah, up in Harlem. That's my
dad on the left, and that's me.
Who's the man whose knee you're sitting on?
Our tailor.
Morris Swope.
Long gone.
So you built the chain from one store.
And the bastards came after me
because I refused to be undersold!
Chang. Chang! Nitro.
Worried about being poisoned?
Can't be too safe.
Great wealth meets great paranoia.
Not a healthy combination.
Pierre's, the restaurant
Milt said they ordered from,
had no record of any order.
He told his wife he ordered dinner.
That's why she opened the door.
And knowing what was coming,
made beautiful love to her.
Well, that's what made it
more exciting for him.
Going by his trial testimony,
the man's all about suspicion and revenge.
Revenge for what?
Don't tell me the lovely Mrs. Winters
was cheating on the old coot
while he was still in prison.
Apparently not, if you
believe the cook, the maid,
the driver, and the Pilates instructor.
Milt loved Pam. Pam loved Milt.
Everything was hunky-dory.
Well, there might be one Winters
who's not closing ranks.
Milton Junior.
He was called as a character
witness at his father's trial,
but he never showed up.
My mother taught me if you can't
say anything nice about someone...
So you skipped your dad's trial.
And the reason you didn't visit him in jail?
Pamela had him take my name
off the visitors list.
She had him wrapped around her little finger.
I won't say she had it coming, but...
You know, usually, in a murder investigation,
people try to hide their
joy at the victim's death.
I'll try to remember that.
You're an only child, right?
Yeah.
Well, with his wife out of the
way, you stand to inherit.
Dad made a point of cutting
me out of his will years ago,
so I wouldn't be tempted to kill him.
That's my dad, always looking out for me.
Well, at least you've learned not to
take his peculiarities personally.
How can I? Dad's sick.
A brilliant businessman, but sick.
So he would've protected himself from Pamela.
Well, I'm sure.
With a pre-nup?
Pre-nups, plural.
I heard he was having his
lawyer redraft the originals.
Well, assuming Pamela would
go along with a new pre-nup.
Gee, suppose she said no.
I don't care how many subpoenas
you pull out of your ass,
you have no right to stick your
nose in my legal business.
That's the point of getting a
subpoena, to give us that right.
The material you're after is covered
by attorney-client privilege.
That privilege was waived when you discussed
redrafting the pre-nup with Mrs. Winters.
Who said anything about redrafting?
Your son.
What?
That rat.
He talks to you, and he doesn't
talk to me? I can't believe this.
Look, if you're gonna get upset,
why don't you just wait outside,
and we all talk to your lawyer.
I see what you're doing.
You people will do anything, say
anything to pin this on me.
The worst scum in the pen have
more honor than any of you.
I loved my wife.
I loved her.
You loved her so much,
you were drafting a new pre-nup.
A pre-nup that increased
her stake in his estate
as reward for her fidelity
during his prison stay.
Not that Pamela cared. Money
was the least of her concerns.
What? It was your idea
to give your money away?
I mean, guys with your
pathology, they usually
build an armor around what they have.
I'm not taking this bait.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm not afraid of this whole
machinery of justice.
I'm not.
"Money was the least of her concerns."
Very nice. I almost believed you myself.
I meant every word of it, Milton.
Pam turned out to be a lovely girl.
"A lovely girl."
You should know.
What are you saying, Milt?
I know what you did, you son of a bitch.
Milt, let... Let go.
I know what you did.
This pre-nup does speak toward his goodwill.
Who's doing this to me?
He's dead.
Oh, my God. Who's doing this to me?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
9mm casings.
Looks like we got a bold
shooter on our hands.
A bold shooter on a bicycle,
according to the limo driver,
who unfortunately didn't see his face.
Bastards!
The bastards are striking at everyone I love,
and you're doing nothing to stop them.
Them?
My enemies, you idiot. I'm the target.
You know, it looks like he's the
one that took all the bullets.
Jack Duvall was only important
because of his relationship to me.
I'm going home. Rashid!
How did he ever get the
impression people don't like him?
Duvall's files were off-limits.
Even his lunch orders fell under
attorney-client privilege.
Yeah. Luckily, the privilege doesn't
extend to his bank records.
All we got out of the secretary
is that Milt was Duvall's only client.
What about Duvall and Mrs. Winters?
Secretary have anything to say about them?
Just that Duvall always
kept his office door open
whenever Ms. Winters came in to see him
and that he never gave her his private number.
Well, Duvall knew how crazy Milt is.
Look at this.
Over the last few months,
Duvall issued a dozen checks
from his escrow accounts, all for under
$10,000, all to small businesses.
For losses from fire damages, accidents.
He was helping settle insurance claims.
A travel agency in Mott Haven.
A beauty salon in Morrisania.
They're all in the South Bronx.
Where a lot of kids learn how to
shoot from watching gangster flicks.
Have you ever seen this guy?
He's a lawyer, Jack Duvall.
No, I don't have much use for lawyers.
Well, this lawyer
wrote a $9,000 check to JC's Beauty Spa.
And that's you, isn't it?
I'm Solomon.
JC is my wife Jaqueetha.
It's her place.
She had a gypsy cab, dollar
van accident a while back.
It could be for that.
Why don't we ask Jaqueetha?
I want you to soak your hand in this.
Is that what it was for?
A gypsy cab accident a while back?
I whiplashed my neck. That's what it was for.
Those guys are crazy drivers.
You're lucky they had insurance.
Is this your son?
Uh-huh. My boy.
And there he is again.
He must be, what, 14 in that picture?
He's grown a lot.
You must be what, 16?
19.
Taye, why don't you go
upstairs, do your studies.
We'll let you get back to business.
I recognized her first.
She testified at the trial of
the boy's real father in '87.
Dempsey Powers. You would've been in Germany.
I remember hearing about him,
the South Bronx Drug King.
He had an interesting MO.
He used to shoot his victims straight
down through the top of their head
to destroy the slug so it couldn't
be traced back to his gun.
When they came to arrest
him, he shot his way out.
Wounded 9 cops. My dad spent
the summer visiting hospitals.
But that isn't why he's in jail, is it?
No, he claimed self-defense.
Told the jury the cops were
in the drug business with him
and were out to kill him.
They bought it. He's in jail for
killing 3 dope dealers.
And now the mother of his kid is getting
money from Milt Winters' lawyer.
You know, it's funny.
Two guys who think that
the world is after them
found each other.
Hey look, I was real kind
to that old white man.
Gave him a cigarette once. Maybe
that's why he sent money to Jaqueetha.
Yeah, $9,000 for a loosey?
Hey, it's different
economics inside this wall.
In fact, uh, what am I getting
for this little sit-down?
Two extra phone calls a week for 6
months and an extra hour of TV a day.
- Extra TV.
- Yeah.
Living large, Dempsey.
The point is, I'm still living,
after all the bullets the
crooked NYPD threw at me.
Yeah, well, that was before our time.
We were in the South Bronx.
We just happened to drop your name.
And I got to tell you,
there's still all love for DP on the streets.
I'm a legend.
A living legend.
In the South Bronx, but in here you're what,
a guardian angel?
Is that why Milt Winters had his lawyer
send over $200 grand to businesses
that belong to your family
and friends?
Maybe it was reparations for the slave trade.
First week Milt was here, some
guy tried to shake him down.
That guy ended up with a
screwdriver in his neck.
Milt was never bothered again.
Milt carried himself like a man,
so he was treated like one.
Especially with you watching his back.
He ever talk to you about his wife?
I would never turn on my friends.
I'm not the NYPD.
This punk's a waste of time.
Yeah, but we're just talking.
You know, we noticed that
your son's only been up here
4 times in 16 years.
Greenhaven's too far.
Yeah? Help us out with Milt.
Maybe we can talk to the DA.
Move you someplace closer
where your son can visit.
Come on, Dempsey. What do you think?
You know what, I'm going to watch some TV.
Oh. So you're gonna... You're gonna pass up
seeing your son to protect
some rich white man.
Wow! You know,
I think you should sit down,
make yourself comfortable.
I think we're gonna search your cell.
You know what?
You can search all you want.
You can plant all the phony evidence you want.
I ain't afraid of you.
You got that?
I ain't afraid.
We found this inside the mattress.
It's probably marked.
Cards, girlie magazines.
Dempsey Powers' entire world, and kids in
the projects think he's a living legend.
This isn't much worse than what they have.
Except he gets 3 squares a day.
He's short 4 cards.
Queen of diamonds.
Jack of clubs.
Deuce of spades.
Ace, hearts.
Queen of diamonds, Milt's wife.
Jack of clubs,
Jack Duvall.
It's a hit list?
Deuce of spades, Milt Junior.
His own son?
He's on a paranoid fugue.
He's cleaning house.
Like any good paranoiac,
he wants to be there when his enemies go down.
I don't know, Dad. You
call me out of the blue.
I've had so much loss these
past two weeks. I need you, Son.
I need you close to me now.
Let me think about it, Dad. I got to go now.
How about a ride uptown?
No, it's okay. The water taxi
will get me there quicker.
See you, Dad.
Son!
Clear!
I didn't believe them when they told me.
- You bastard, how could you?
- No!
No, it's them. These cops are
trying to kill me. They're after me.
For once, you're right.
We are after you. Milton
Winters, you're under arrest.
I told you, I'm a bike messenger.
People are trying to jack me all the time.
That's why I was carrying the piece.
What about these? We found
them in your mom's apartment?
Don't know nothing about them.
You don't know what this is?
Huh? How about this one?
This one?
They're playing cards?
No, Ahmal, signals from Dempsey Powers.
You see, some...
Some rich white dude paid him $200 large
to have you kill these people.
You all are whack.
And you're an amateur,
'cause pros don't keep evidence
in their mama's apartment.
I didn't do these homicides,
but whoever did, he's no amateur.
He's gangsta.
Gangsta?
No. This fool was too busy
styling to shoot straight.
He punched out bullets
using a 90 degree flip.
Or maybe the modified John Woo 180 cock.
Whichever,
he had no control.
He put more bullets in the door
than he did in this woman.
She looked dead in the picture.
This isn't a movie.
You did a murder in the course of
a robbery. That's a death penalty.
I didn't rob nobody.
You took an earring off the woman.
Didn't Dempsey tell you not
to mess with the bling-bling?
I'm telling you, I don't even know DP.
Your brother Luther spent time
with him up in Greenhaven.
Is that how you met DP?
Visiting your brother up in Greenhaven?
How am I gonna get all the way up there?
Subway only stop at 241st Street.
All right, you don't have to flip on DP.
Try this.
You have these three cards.
We know that there is a
fourth, the ace of hearts.
Who is it?
Who is the fourth hit?
I got no ace.
I'm done.
Give me a lawyer.
Even if this boy flips on Dempsey Powers,
we have no corroboration
other than generic playing
cards from a generic deck.
I suggest we have a
conversation with Mr. Powers.
About what? A plea bargain?
What else would we talk to him about?
We're gonna cut a deal
with a guy who shot 9 cops?
He's already serving life with no parole,
and he's merely the subcontractor here.
Milt Winters is the author of
these murders. These are his targets.
And am I wrong to assume
that unless we identify the fourth target,
Milt Winters will find
somebody to finish the job?
On what planet
do you think Powers is going to cooperate
with either the police or the DA?
He hates us. He doesn't trust us.
Dempsey thinks that we're capable of anything.
Let's not disappoint him.
As you probably know, Milt Winters'
lawyer was shot outside the DA's office.
Not the smartest call.
The place was crawling with officers.
My partner's old man
was in the 4-0. Same precinct
where you shot all those cops.
You mean, the crooked cops.
What's her daddy's name?
Maybe he was on my payroll.
The officers got a good look at
the person who killed the lawyer.
Recognize him?
Oops.
That looks just like your son Taye.
My son had nothing to do with it.
We have the murder weapon.
If you think it was easy
to plant fingerprints in '87,
just think about what we can do now.
You're a devil.
You should see me in a blue dress.
Yeah, well, I ain't afraid of the devil.
You should be afraid of my partner,
afraid for your son.
I give you what you want,
you all leave me and my son in peace?
I'll make sure we do,
you tell the grand jury what you know
and testify at Milt's trial.
Oh, man.
Old Milt may have come to me for some favors.
But, you know, being a man of peace,
naturally I turned him down.
I would, um,
be willing to talk about those favors.
The ace of hearts,
who is it?
Milt lost a lot of weight in prison.
Got himself healthy.
He started thinking that his doctor
kept him sick all those years,
to bleed him dry.
It's the ace of hearts,
his heart doctor, Dr. Chang.
Dempsey said no such thing.
That's a lie. He and I are brothers.
Your brother told us who
your fourth target is.
If you want any leniency from me,
you'll call off any attempt
on your doctor's life.
My doctor?
It's a trick. Can't you see?
My brother did not betray me,
would not betray me, ever.
You don't trust your own son,
but you trust Dempsey Powers.
More now than ever.
I've told him for 30 years
to lose weight, to exercise.
So what does he do in prison?
He loses weight. He exercises.
So now he wants to kill me?
You don't sound alarmed by this.
Would alarm help?
Milt is the one who lives in fear.
You mean paranoia?
The fear of death.
His father died of a heart attack at 37.
Milt thinks he lives on borrowed time.
How old was Milt when his father died?
16.
Somehow he kept his father's store going.
Right. Somehow.
Dr. Chang, we'll assign
a couple of detectives to keep an
eye on your office in the city.
I don't work in the city anymore.
Don't live here either.
I moved to Staten Island a year ago.
I hardly come into the city at all anymore.
Does Milt know you spend all
your time on Staten Island?
Yes.
He even made a donation to
the hospice I started there.
Okay. Thank you, Doctor. Someone
will take you back to the ferry.
If bicycle boy
wouldn't visit his brother because
the subway didn't go to Greenhaven,
how did he figure on getting to Staten
Island to shoot the good doctor?
It was a delivery in one
of these offices over there.
I don't know what office you're talking about.
You wanted him to tell you where
he was making his delivery.
That's what he just did, so he's done.
You can't just come over here
and point it out to me, Ahmal?
No, I'm fine right here, man.
Wait, are you afraid of the water?
I ain't afraid of some water. I just
don't... I just stay away from it.
Well, you go over bridges, don't you?
I don't take bridges.
What about the ferry?
I just don't go on water, okay?
I stay right over here, on the hard land.
That's the biggest bunch
of nonsense I ever heard.
This is your big day. You're
gonna take a ride on the ferry.
- No, no, leave me be.
- Come on.
- It's right over here. Come on.
- Leave me be. No.
No, no, no. Please, please.
Please, I don't, I swear. I'm gonna
pee myself. Please, just don't.
Okay. All right. All right, calm down.
Ahmal, calm down.
Come on. You don't have to
take the ferry. Come on.
Come on. It's going to be all right.
You can stay right here on the hard land.
He was supposed to do the hit on Milt's son.
He hesitated.
He waited for the son to get
away from the water's edge.
Now, there's no way
that he's gonna take a job
shooting someone on Staten Island.
Fourth victim, the ace of
hearts, it's not the doctor.
Milt's having somebody else killed.
Dempsey wouldn't lie to us about that.
But he would lie to us if he
was having someone killed.
He's playing us.
Yeah, he's playing all of us.
Milt contracted those 3 hits.
The fourth one is Dempsey's choice.
We may be overestimating Mr. Powers' cunning.
The idea he used Milt Winters' killing
spree to hide a killing of his own is...
Overestimate a guy who put
9 cops in the hospital?
You can't be serious.
And cover the personnel at Greenhaven,
starting with the warden.
Dempsey might have already made his move.
I checked homicides going back 2 months.
This one,
last week, in Queens. Eduardo Escobar.
Shot once straight down
through the top of the head.
Dempsey's MO.
Who the hell is Eduardo Escobar?
A subway mechanic. Married last month.
No priors, no known connection
to Dempsey Powers.
If someone killed Escobar
on orders from Powers,
isn't it reckless to advertise the
fact by using Powers' calling card?
Reckless and bold.
The act of someone proud of his
connection to Dempsey Powers.
I didn't kill no Eduardo Escobar.
You gonna plant the gun you're
looking for, or just powder burns?
Don't believe everything
your father tells you.
I don't have to tell you anything.
My father told me that, too.
You keep following his advice,
and you'll end up just like him.
Ma!
Downstairs is clean.
You won't find anything.
Taye has his father's mouth, but
my husband and I raised him right.
You got a lot of new books.
History of Cuba.
Cuba Today.
My final essay on parts of the world
where police don't practice racism.
Definitely his father's mouth.
Come on, Taye, let's let them do their work.
This kid's inherited more
than just his father's mouth.
Dempsey does nothing by accident.
Spanish, Cuba
probably figure into their long-term plans.
And killing Eduardo Escobar
somehow gets them there.
No. I never seen this man before.
Eduardo had no enemies.
He was gentle, always helping people.
What about this one? You ever see him?
No. Who are they?
Just men.
This is from Calabria, in the south of Italy.
Did you go there for your honeymoon?
No. Puerto Rico. We got married there.
When did you go to Italy?
I went last year.
Well, Calabria's pretty rough country.
People usually don't go there
unless they have family...
You don't have family there, do you?
No.
So you went with somebody?
It was before I met Eduardo.
It's got nothing to do with this.
Calabrese hard head. Have you
ever heard that expression?
When I was a kid, I had a
barber who was from Calabria.
He told me that the people
were very stubborn.
He said that when you
take something from them,
they don't give up until they get it back.
Who is he, Ms. Escobar?
Tony.
Tony Sirvino.
He thinks that Eduardo stole me from him.
What does Mr. Sirvino do?
He works for the city.
The Department of Correction?
Yes. He drives their bus.
An escape?
After Dempsey testifies
for the grand jury tomorrow.
Tony Sirvino's scheduled to
drive his bus back to Rikers.
Sirvino grew up in the South Bronx.
He went to school with Dempsey, and
Dempsey keeps tabs on his people.
And he had his son kill Mr.
Escobar as a favor to Mr. Sirvino?
This is... Brilliant.
Once Dempsey got the contract from
Milt to make these three hits,
he orchestrated everything.
The checks from the lawyer, the playing cards,
everything, to lead us back to him,
so we would bring him before the grand jury.
He knew he'd be transferred
from Greenhaven down to Rikers
and driven back and forth
to the courthouse.
Sirvino helps them escape,
and Dempsey's on his way to Cuba with his son.
Beyond the reach of extradition.
I suddenly have a new found
respect for Mr. Powers.
I ain't afraid of you.
Well, you should be afraid. Using
your daddy's MO wasn't very smart.
- Blood or no blood...
- Taye.
- I'm Winston Malik,
- ...he's gonna take it out of your hide.
- your father's lawyer. Now I'm yours.
- Or your mom's.
But if you...
I ain't giving you no reason to kill my pops.
Taye's invoking his rights.
He doesn't have anything more to say.
Unless his son cooperates,
we have no case against Mr. Powers.
And once Mr. Powers finds out
we got wind to his escape plan,
I doubt he'll testify to the grand
jury tomorrow against Milt Winters,
and then that case will be gone, too.
We haven't told Junior what
we know about the escape.
We should be able to keep Powers in the dark
until after he goes in
front of the grand jury.
But once we derail his escape, he'll
never testify at Milt Winters' trial.
We can use his grand jury testimony.
Grand jury testimony is not admissible
at trial. I need Mr. Powers to appear.
I'm betting that Dempsey Powers...
I'm betting he knows
that if he escapes to Cuba,
his grand jury testimony
can't be used at trial.
He never intended to betray Milt.
There is an exception, isn't there,
that allows a grand jury
testimony to be used at trial
if the witness has been threatened
into recanting his testimony?
But who's going to threaten Dempsey Powers?
His good friend Milt.
Question. "What did Mr. Winters tell you?"
Answer from Mr. Powers.
"He was always complaining about all of them.
"His wife, his son, his lawyer.
"He wanted to get rid of them."
That's what your brother, Dempsey,
told the grand jury just a
little over an hour ago.
Down the street from here.
Question.
"Did Mr. Winters solicit your help
in dealing with these individuals?"
Answer from Mr. Powers. "Yes.
"He offered to pay me $50,000
each to get them killed."
Save your breath.
Are you still convinced Mr. Powers
is looking out for your interests?
More than ever. This doesn't mean squat
until he says it at my trial.
And no way on earth he rats me out.
My son, in a heartbeat, but Dempsey, never!
I'm so curious about this unquestioning trust.
Is it based on anything?
Greenhaven.
He looked out for me from day one.
You paid for that protection.
I was happy to share with him.
He had so little. I had so much.
The only thing that you had so
much of in prison was fear.
And Dempsey could smell it.
And he used it to gain your trust.
I'm not wrong about Dempsey. I know people.
And Dempsey knows you.
He told us that he was checking you out.
He was looking for an in on you.
And he found it in an article
about a retailing miracle
known as Winters Clothing.
I…
I have it.
It's here.
"Faced with his father's
unexpected death, 16 year old Milt
"not only kept the family store afloat,
"but it turned into the flagship
"of the city's most successful
chain of men's clothing stores."
There was a photo that was in the article.
That's what tipped Dempsey off
that you had help keeping the store afloat.
That's right. Your dad's tailor, Morris Swope.
Yeah, Uncle Morris.
The man who looked out for
you when your father died,
who showed you the ropes the first time
that you were alone against the world.
But Dempsey told us that he took one
look at that photo and he knew.
He knew how to come at you.
And it wasn't by being
a bully, or a flatterer,
but as Morris Swope,
the reassuring protector.
Dempsey told us that it cracked him up.
He pictured you sitting on his
knee, like a wooden dummy.
He got around your natural suspicion
by modeling your one
positive adult relationship.
He took you for a couple hundred grand
and sold you out for immunity and a
few extra hours of TV every week.
Sure, he's going to spend the rest
of his days in relative comfort.
But you?
You're looking at the death penalty.
I mean, that just doesn't seem fair.
To be fair,
Mr. Winters, I'll settle
for life without parole
in return for your admission of guilt.
You think about it on your way back to Rikers.
What's your name?
Sirvino.
You make these too tight, Sirvino,
I'm gonna slap a brutality suit against you.
Milton! They got you.
I'm not sitting near this man.
It's okay, Officer, we're old friends.
Have a nice ride, gentlemen.
The toughest guy in Greenhaven, a rat.
Milton, be cool. Be cool.
Cool? You spent the morning ratting me out.
For what? More TV?
That's what friendship's worth?
Milt,
don't worry, man, don't worry.
It ain't gonna happen.
I won't testify against you in court, okay?
You already did.
They playing you, Milton.
Just chill out and trust me.
Just chill.
Sitting on your knee.
Very funny, huh?
What the hell are you talking about?
I don't care what hole
they put you in, Dempsey,
I'm gonna reach out to you.
You're a dead man.
What are you doing?
You know what, Milt?
I ain't going back to Haven.
Just be cool. Be cool.
You're breaking out?
Shut up.
Wait. Take... Take me with you.
We're a team, right?
Sidney Poitier and Tony Curtis.
Shut up.
Don't leave me. Dempsey, don't leave me.
Don't leave me behind.
It's a slice, Milton.
Okay, okay, okay. Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
Just put it down.
Just put it down. It's empty.
It's over.
What the hell's going on?
Tony Curtis speaks.
I told you to keep your mouth shut, fool.
We got Milt's death threat on tape.
Which makes Mr. Powers' grand
jury testimony admissible
at Mr. Winters' trial.
And we've got Mr. Powers
for the Escobar killing.
You know, it's a shame.
All this trust and loyalty,
look where it gets you.