In New York City's war on crime,
the worst criminal offenders are pursued
by the detectives of the Major Case Squad.
These are their stories.
Sorry I'm late.
I wanted to find that wine you like, and
I had to go all the way to the bowery.
Al, honey?
What?
No way.
(PHONE RINGING)
Pick up. Pick up.
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPING)
It's me.
I thought things were really great,
and now I find this typed
letter not even signed?
You have to talk to me, AI.
If this has anything to do with my
parents coming, it's really not okay.
I'm not mad,
I just wanna talk.
Maybe he's just scared of committing.
The way you talk about your dad.
It's not my dad. It's him.
He's got somebody else.
I could just kill him.
If you could find him.
Oh, I'll find him.
Watch this.
Al, this is Leslie again.
You don't call me in the next 12
hours, you're in big trouble.
(SIGHING)
I know what's been going on at school.
Like that ever works.
I gotta go to the gym, see you.
Please, honey,
just call me.
Please.
If you don't have enough money why
don't you put back the vermouth?
You can't make a martini
without vermouth, okay?
How much you need?
Oh, no, that's okay.
COUNTERMAN: She needs 80 cents.
Here.
If you give me your address,
I'll send you the money.
Forget it.
NEAL: Thanks for letting us in.
I don't know why she didn't
meet us at the airport.
NANCY: Leslie?
Yoo hoo? It's Mom, we're here.
What's this?
NEAL: Leslie?
Her purse and her wallet
and her keys are here.
Please call the police.
Maybe she's visiting somebody in the...
Just call them now. And use your cell.
And don't touch anything.
Missing woman is Leslie Dornan.
Neighbors haven't seen her since yesterday.
She have a boyfriend, girlfriend?
Not according to her folks.
Her father's a cop?
Pittsburgh PD, retired.
Guess he knew which strings to
pull to get Major Case here.
This turns into anything, we'll
put you in on the collar.
Go ahead, impress me.
It's Aramaic.
GOREN: It's the language
that Christ spoke in.
Parts of the Old Testament
were written in it.
But don't ask me what it means.
GOREN: This is Aramaic too.
Mr. and Mrs. Dornan?
Is that your daughter's handwriting?
I don't know. I can't tell.
This wall-hanging here?
My mother brought that back
from Turkey. It's the Lord's Prayer.
But I don't think that
Leslie knew that language.
EAMES: The last time you talked
to her, how did she sound?
NEAL: She sounded fine.
Leslie wouldn't hurt herself.
She loves life, she's a fighter.
The detective said you didn't think
Leslie was involved with anybody.
NANCY: No, she wasn't.
Well, she definitely had a regular visitor.
This is hair gel.
He liked to sit here and watch TV.
He'd rest his head against the wall.
Those are scuff marks.
He liked to put his feet on the table.
Well, he's tall.
Six, 6'4"...
If she had a boyfriend...
Why didn't she tell you?
EAMES: How about you tell us
about her boyfriend?
Al? They broke up last Tuesday.
Leslie came home, his stuff was gone.
She was furious.
She kept leaving messages on his phone,
how she was gonna make trouble for him.
Let's start with Al's full name. Alan what?
It's not Alan. It's Ali Al-Javad.
He's Moroccan.
He's a grad student at Hunter.
Is that why she didn't tell her parents
about him? Because he's Moroccan?
Her dad could be pretty intense.
She must have really liked him.
He made her feel so special.
He bought her expensive gifts, antiques.
I noticed the coffee table.
That was a gift?
Yes. He had me buy that for
her in Amsterdam last summer.
He just gave you a bunch of money
and told you to buy what you want?
No. He gave me the name of the antique store.
They took care of the shipping.
Who picked up the coffee table on this end?
JANEY: We all did.
We took my brother's van to
the customs broker in Jersey.
Just the table. Nothing else?
Yes.
If you're trying to freak
me out, it's working.
(sighing)
How did Al and Leslie meet?
You're embarrassed. Did
he pick her up in a bar
or maybe a chat room?
It's not sleazy.
It's the Singular Singles website.
You can see their video,
hear what they have to say.
It's not like a total pick-up.
I love dancing salsa and singing karaoke.
EAMES: This is the boyfriend, Ali Al-Javad.
My dream girl is a full-figured American lady
who loves to laugh.
Give me some mail.
No, he's not Moroccan.
When Moroccans speak English,
they sound French.
I'd put this guy further east.
How about we put him in this seat?
You talk to his college?
Well, he registered two years ago.
Took a full load the first semester and then
one class each semester after that.
Just enough to satisfy the
requirements of his student visa.
And then he found a girlfriend.
Someone vulnerable,
grateful for the attention.
Somebody who'd be afraid
to ask too many questions.
He moved in with her,
everything's in her name.
He stays off the radar.
He's a sleeper.
(scoffing)
Maybe, just maybe, this
guy doesn't like school.
Maybe he's just here for a good time.
We still have a missing woman.
A 33-year-old single woman who'd
been drinking, who'd been dumped.
I mean... Someone
is trying very hard to convince
us she committed suicide.
This is the translation off the wall
writing. It's from the Old Testament.
The Song of Songs.
"Night after night on my bed,
I have sought my true love.
"I have sought him but not found him.
"I have called him but he has not answered."
They wanted to write a suicide note,
but they couldn't fake her handwriting,
so they wrote it in Aramaic.
Ali took a flight out of Newark
to Germany Tuesday night.
The day before Leslie disappeared.
One of his buddies must
have taken care of her.
He left the country
the same day he left her?
Well, whatever job he had
to do here, it was over.
Look at this itinerary. He had
to connect through Atlanta and Paris.
No. He could have flown direct
from JFK for half the price.
Maybe he was hooking up
with somebody in those cities.
Or maybe it was about leaving out of Newark.
He had something to do in New Jersey
before getting on that plane.
The table.
The table he had Leslie's
friend buy in Amsterdam,
it was shipped to a customs broker in Jersey.
An antique that he could have
bought in SoHo for less money.
It was a dry run.
He was testing the customs inspection.
He brought something else in.
He had to take delivery of it or
maybe hand it off to somebody
before leaving the country.
AUDREY: Tuesday, yes,
Mr. Al-Javad picked up a crate of
household goods from the Netherlands.
Did Customs inspect it?
Inspect?
Oh, the crate?
You're kidding, right?
I guess we are.
How large a crate was it?
Three foot by three foot.
Weight, 80 pounds.
The container the crate was shipped
in, where would that be now?
Ali's crate was loaded in first.
That would put it somewhere in the back.
You know, we get about six million
containers a year coming in,
(DOG BARKING)
and we only check about 2% of them.
The more I know the less I sleep.
This corner here is positive for explosives.
Do you have any idea how much?
Judging by the way Homer's
bouncing around, I'd say a lot.
So much for sleep.
The lab tests from the container
came back positive for Titadine.
It's a high-yield, high-grade
form of dynamite.
Titadine.
There was an advisory
on that stuff last year.
8 tons of it were stolen
from a factory in France.
Most of it's unaccounted for.
Until this morning.
The Feds and the Joint Task Force
are gonna be all over this.
You're not suggesting we bow out.
Hell, no. We've got a
suspected homicide to clear.
Where are we with
Mr. Al-Javad's accomplices?
We found a number of prints
from the rental van.
I like this guy. Jorge Galvez.
His prints were on the inside
of the cargo area of the van.
He's got a juvenile record
in Baltimore. It's gang related.
Then he served three years
here for assaulting a motorist
over a fender bender.
A rageaholic.
Since he was paroled two
years ago, he's been clean.
Not even a parking ticket.
His last year in prison he worked
in the library, he got his GED.
Something put him back
on the straight and narrow.
A religious conversion?
He wouldn't be the first person
to find God behind bars.
Some people find Allah.
Some people find Jesus.
There are a lot of teams in the league.
Galvez finished his parole, but maybe
his PO is still in touch with him.
ABE: Jorge hasn't worked here
since a year ago last spring.
What happened to him?
He went to the hospital. His appendix burst.
After that he disappeared.
His last paycheck I mailed to
his apartment, it got returned.
EAMES: You meet any of his friends?
Just the people from the
prison outreach program.
GOREN: What about his religious friends?
His parole officer told us that he
converted to Islam when he was in prison.
And I can see that you sell halal chicken,
meaning it's slaughtered
according to Muslim tradition.
I know that your community
has had a rough year
and we are not looking
to make things any worse.
There's a missing girl.
Jorge might be involved. We need to find him.
I took him to our mosque, helped him with
his Arabic so he could read the Koran.
Jorge had this big chip on his shoulder.
He'd talk a lot of trash about
America, how oppressed he was.
I told him, you stop breaking the
law, you won't feel so oppressed.
When Jorge went to the
emergency for his appendix,
who took care of him? A girlfriend?
A nurse. He was at Mount Sinai
for over a week.
A week? I like your health coverage.
(scoffing)
Our health coverage is my wife's chicken
soup. We don't cover hospitals.
Somebody had to guarantee that hospital bill.
I just signed the hospital papers.
The prison outreach program
that I was working with at the time,
they had a fund for that sort of thing.
Have you seen Jorge since?
No. Once his parole was up,
we didn't keep in touch.
Excuse me.
(INAUDIBLE)
That's a smart question, Randy.
That's your name, right?
Randy asked why the Greek Bible
is called the Septuagint.
Septua means 70
and the story is that it took 70 scholars
to translate the Hebrew Bible into Greek.
At the great library at Alexandria
in Egypt, right, Mr. Edwards?
Right.
The library and its 700,000
books were destroyed by fire
over 1,300 years ago.
My mother was a librarian.
They just built a new library
on the site of the original.
This time with state of
the art smoke detectors.
You've been?
I've read about it.
I'm one of five people who actually
reads the Smithsonian magazine.
Six.
Yeah, one of six.
I should get back to class.
Substitute teacher.
You must like punishment.
I like making a contribution.
I wish you could make one to our case.
He had an uncle in Baltimore. A dry cleaner.
He was talking about hitting him up for work.
I hope that helps.
Jorge's uncle, the dry cleaner,
died three years ago.
So either Jorge lied to Edwards
or Edwards lied to us.
What's this?
It's the Smithsonian article on
the new library in Alexandria.
When Edwards mentioned smoke
detectors, it didn't ring a bell.
You actually read this when it came out?
The magazine's the perfect
size for my treadmill.
There's nothing in here
about smoke detectors.
And since there's no reason Edwards
would mention a detail like that...
He's been to Egypt in the last year.
The State Department would know.
The Egyptian consulate in
Munich issued a tourist visa
to Ethan Edwards a year ago last June.
A week later, they issued
another one to Jorge Galvez.
They both got passports in April last year.
They both left the country in the same week,
and they both got back two months ago.
Sounds like they had a meeting of the minds.
Edwards' co-workers, at the outreach
program, they knew he was a Muslim,
but he didn't become political
until he met Jorge Galvez.
The school board have an address on Edwards?
Just a PO box.
I'll get Carver working on a
subpoena for the postal records.
You two call the task force.
- Bedroom clear!
- Bathroom clear!
MAN: Living room clear!
(SIREN WAILING)
This is not good.
It's rat poison.
Rat poison's an anticoagulant.
Suicide bombers in Israel, they
use it to mix with the shrapnel
when making bombs.
The idea is
when their victims are wounded,
they bleed to death.
A suicide bomber.
When the hell did this kid decide
that's what he wanted to be when he grows up?
Doesn't look like he's planning to grow up.
EAMES: This is the crate
they shipped from overseas.
The K-9 unit came up positive for explosives.
Once we get all this weighed, we'll know
how much Titadine we have to worry about.
Edwards lived here alone
until a couple of weeks ago,
another man described as male, Hispanic.
Galvez.
EAMES: We couldn't get a positive ID.
At this point, we're not sure which
one's the actual suicide bomber.
It could be a suicide bomber,
or they might try and use
a remote-controlled device.
Well, I'm going with a suicide bomber.
You see here, here and here.
Something was taped to the wall.
The paint was ripped off
when it was taken down.
And duct tape residue.
The sheet was used as a backdrop.
And...
These three marks.
Probably a tripod.
I think they made a
video tape.
A suicide note.
The Bureau feels releasing any information
to the public is counterproductive.
It might even provoke these people
to step up their operation.
They already know we got their scent.
We weighed that crate, they
have 50 pounds of Titadine,
they made a vest, they're good to go.
Agent O'Dell, it's established
practice to let the eyes and ears
of the American public help us
deal with terrorist threats.
For once we have more to offer
them than a color scheme.
We have the actual photos of the terrorists
which the District Attorney will
recommend be released to the media.
I'll let my people know that.
We're still tracking down Galvez's
associates and relatives here
and in Baltimore.
We got some background on Edwards,
he might have family up in Westchester.
Which one is the designated martyr?
Galvez took electronics courses in prison.
He probably assembled the bomb.
Which leaves Edwards the job of carrying it.
What are his qualifications?
Theology major at Manhattan
University with a minor in languages.
He speaks Spanish, Arabic, working
knowledge of Greek, Hebrew, Aramaic.
Everything you'd need to study
the Bible in the original text.
He volunteers in soup kitchens.
He mentored kids in inner city schools.
How can a man with that background
murder innocent people?
Well, that's probably why he
made a tape. To explain himself.
We can always ask his parents.
JOE: it's because of his religious beliefs,
that's why you singled him out.
Mr. Edwards, will you please
just answer my question?
He called last July. He was in Phoenix.
He'd just gotten back from
traveling around Europe.
And Egypt. He got a visa for Egypt last year.
Yes, he visited Egypt.
Why aren't you telling us
anything? Is Ethan hurt?
We spoke to Ethan three days ago.
GOREN: He's working as a
substitute teacher in Queens.
Did you know that's what he was doing?
No. If Ethan wanted us to know he
was here, he would've told us.
Mr. Edwards, I need you to
unlock the door to the garage.
(DOG BARKING)
This woman is missing.
Leslie Dornan.
Maybe Ethan
knows what happened to her.
Is she his girlfriend?
No.
It's complicated.
Ethan would never hurt anyone.
He's a very ethical person.
Well, he's certainly familiar
with the Ten Commandments.
He's got the Torah, the Koran, the Bible
with notes written in the margins.
He followed a path of study.
He probably would've been a minister
if it weren't for his father.
Your husband doesn't like religion?
Joe's a chemist. He likes tangible things.
And Ethan embraced the intangible.
Have you ever talked to him
about his conversion to Islam?
He said it made him feel
centered and connected
to something bigger than him.
When was this picture taken?
That's the summer I took Ethan to
do volunteer work in Appalachia.
He was just ten.
Did your husband take that picture?
No. Joe didn't go with us.
It wasn't a good time in your marriage?
Maybe it brought you and Ethan closer.
When Ethan was traveling,
maybe he contacted you
more than your husband.
He sent me e-mails. He called me once,
after the attacks.
I wasn't sure where he was.
Did he talk about the attacks?
He wanted to know if anyone
we knew had been hurt.
He sounded very shaky.
He wanted to come home,
but he said he had things he had to do first.
You're probably the one person
that he's afraid to disappoint.
Oh, he knows that couldn't happen.
You said that Ethan was
looking for a connection to
something bigger than himself.
Now, if he found people
that offered that connection,
he might be persuaded to do things
that he found morally repugnant.
What things?
A suicide bombing.
Oh, my God, no.
Oh, Ethan.
You can help us bring him in.
As we reported earlier, Vera Edwards,
the mother of fugitive terrorist
suspect Ethan Edwards,
Suffered a massive heart attack
after being informed that her son might
be a member of a terrorist cell.
A spokesperson for St. Peters hospital
says that Mrs. Edwards remains
in very critical condition.
In fact...
We're monitoring the hospital, the
parents' house, phones, e-mails.
In the hopes he'll reach out
to his dying mother?
CARVER: Detective Goren feels that
she's a role model for Edwards.
They've got something.
You raised me
to believe you can't take
without giving back.
So really, this is a path
I was always meant to walk.
Tell everyone that there's a message coming,
and America better read it carefully
because it's being written
in a language it understands.
(BEEPS)
It was e-mailed to his parents.
It's clean, nothing embedded, no
way to trace where it came from.
This is a streaming video, right?
Like the videos on Singular Singles?
The software to process
and send a streaming video,
are they all the same?
No. There are different kinds.
And each one would have
a signature on the video?
Sure. Why?
Hello, I'm Khalid.
I'm a stock analyst with an MBA
from Wharton School of Business.
I enjoy sports...
This is the only video
I found on Singular Singles
that uses the same software
as the Edwards video.
I like romantic dinners and long
walks in the city at night.
Let's give him his long walk.
Get his phone number and
address from the website.
I got pizza.
(DOOR RATTLING)
Police!
Get him down, get him down!
He was gonna kill Edwards.
GOREN: Keep Edwards from talking.
Talk about what? We got the bomb.
One of the bombs.
This vest weighs about 40 pounds
and minus the shrapnel.
We've only got about 20,
25 pounds of explosives here.
There's another vest out there.
EAMES: Our search of Khalid's
place didn't turn up any leads
to Jorge or to what their target might be.
These items were in Ethan's knapsack.
We're not sure what this is.
"1/55@31 ."
It doesn't correspond to any address.
The Bureau is assuming Galvez and Edwards
were planning a coordinated attack.
The first man detonates in a crowd.
The second man waits for
rescue personnel to arrive
or targets the crowd
fleeing the first explosion.
All we need is when and where.
Well, they'd pick a confined space
to maximize the concussive power
of the shock waves bouncing off the walls.
If we assume Galvez sticks to the plan.
DEAKINS: Do we have a choice?
The task force turned up
an e-ticket in Khalid's name
for a flight out of JFK
to Madrid tomorrow night.
If this follows the MO, it means his
part of the job would be over by then.
Which puts the target date for the
operation within days from now.
Step into him fast.
You're an American citizen,
Ethan. Born and raised.
Free to worship in
a religion of your choice.
How can you sit there and let
Jorge kill innocent Americans?
Well, maybe what they say is true,
you're a traitor.
The worst kind of scum.
No, I'm not a traitor.
One nation under God.
My allegiance is to God, to Allah.
Killing in the name of God is good?
It's better to kill in the name of oil?
I don't get it, Ethan.
Your family told us you were upset by 9/11.
It was a mistake.
It was too much.
But then America sent gun ships and
killed hundreds of innocent people,
women, children.
9/11 was a terrible lesson
that no one learned.
So we need what? A refresher course?
Look, I'm sure that he has it all worked out.
Anyway, this is all,
you know, big-picture stuff.
My partner and I, we're here
for the little picture.
For Leslie Dornan.
Her parents just wanna bury her.
You know, it just occurred to me that
you haven't asked about your mom.
You don't wanna know how she is?
How is she?
EAMES: We're working on the
barter system here, Ethan.
You give us something, we give you something.
You're afraid.
No, you're afraid that
you're gonna fail this test.
That those other guys were right.
Who?
What are you talking about?
Well, the reason why
Khalid tried to kill you.
To protect the operation. I accept that.
He knew it.
And the other guys at the
training camp, they knew it, too.
Ethan, when it comes right down to
it, this is really not your fight.
I mean, you don't have centuries of injustice
and colonial oppression
to harden your resolve.
I'm a Muslim.
It's my fight, too.
You know,
I read the Koran a long time ago.
When I was in the army,
I was stationed in Germany.
And there was this girl who lived
near the base, she was Turkish.
She was Muslim. I wanted to impress her.
And you know, it's really
not what you'd expect.
For example,
they recognize the right for women to
vote, to own and inherit property.
To divorce their husbands.
And this was written what?
Like 1,300 years ago.
It's the true word of God.
Well, you would know. You've
been looking for the true word.
You've been searching for God.
But there's one thing
that I couldn't find in here.
And that's the part where
Allah, you know, tells
everybody to just go ahead
and indiscriminately kill innocent people.
I mean, that part, that's not in here.
I mean, where is that?
Must be in some secret chapter.
But it isn't because I didn't
miss it, did I, Ethan?
I mean, it's exactly what
my Muslim friends told me
is that it's not in the Koran.
That there's no sanction for
what you were planning to do
and what Jorge still plans to do.
No, we weren't...
You weren't what?
Let me show you something.
This x-ray is of a suicide
bomb victim in Israel.
This victim has no external
injuries, no shrapnel wounds.
Just this white mass.
Emergency room doctors
call this the white butterfly.
It's what the heart and lungs
and other internal organs
look like after they've been turned into soup
by the concussion from the bomb.
Ethan, what I want to know is
you went searching for God,
how did you end up looking for targets?
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
That's probably news about your mother.
Oh, by the way,
this x-ray is of a five-year-old girl.
I was sent by God.
So are we.
(door shuts)
We have to consider another option.
Sodium Amytal.
Truth serum?
I've seen it used on Soviet
defectors, and it didn't work.
If we inject him, we'll lose his
trust, and it'll waste time.
Ethan is a difficult subject, and we
have nothing to leverage him with.
We have his sense of morality.
His sense of morality is what
got us here in the first place.
The FBI has access to it, doesn't it?
I'm not getting squat without
authorization from Justice.
The new FBI.
Well, isn't that what the President said?
You're either with us or against us?
He sees the world in high
contrast. It's black and white.
Our way or the highway.
ETHAN: He has no idea what we sound
like to the rest of the world.
Washington's still making up its mind.
Progress?
So, you gonna lead us out of our ignorance?
I just want America
and the West to stop trying
to control the destiny
of my Muslim brothers and sisters.
Surgery?
So, you think by blowing yourself up
is a step in the right direction?
Martyrdom has a lot of symbolic value.
Buddhist monks set themselves on fire
to protest their religious persecution.
A man did it at the Pentagon in the
'60s to protest the Vietnam war.
And they were understood loud and clear
because they didn't muddy it
up by killing other people.
You ever think about that
instead of a suicide bomb?
Well, I'm sure things made a
lot more sense six months ago.
You know, they were much clearer...
I'm just tired.
GOREN: No, no, no, no, no.
You had doubts
long before you ran into us.
About how all this killing squares
up with the will of a merciful God.
Of course I had doubts.
I'm not a psychopath.
Well, you had more than doubts.
You knew you were lost.
GOREN: "Night after night on my bed,
"I sought my true love.
"I sought him but not found him.
"I call him but he does not answer."
In the trade we call this a tell, Ethan.
You didn't write the verse
on Leslie's wall by mistake.
You wrote it 'cause you were
calling out to God,
and he's not answering.
And you haven't felt this lost
since that summer you went to
Appalachia when your parents separated.
And that is your personal struggle,
your jihad,
to find connection to something
bigger than yourself.
And nothing's bigger than God.
And the moment you realized
you lost connection with him
was when you were watching
Jorge kill Leslie.
It wasn't supposed to happen.
He was just gonna talk to her.
So if Leslie had to die
to protect your mission
then maybe there was something
wrong with your mission.
Something unjust.
And that's what was going through your head.
I wouldn't kill innocent civilians.
EAMES: Well, Leslie's dead.
And more innocent people will
die if Jorge sets off his bomb.
There's only one way back to God.
There's only one way to make
your parents understand
that you're not about this or this.
If I tell you where she is, what do I get?
We'll tell you how your mother's doing.
I'll write down the address.
If you tell us where Jorge is,
how we can stop him,
we might let you know where your mother is.
Whatever happens is God's will.
EAMES: I hope this doesn't turn
out to be the consolation prize.
GOREN: These hairs
under Leslie's fingernails.
- Yeah.
- Blond hairs,
short, razor cut, black roots.
Jorge's gone blond.
I have shoe prints here.
Boots.
Anyone do boots?
(CAMERA CLICKING)
What do you think, military issue?
Regular army, mid '90s. Brand new.
Probably came from a surplus store.
He's got a crew cut.
He may be wearing military...
Clothing.
Ethan said they wouldn't kill civilians.
Civilians.
Tomorrow's Veteran's Day.
The Veteran's Day parade down Fifth Avenue.
That's a two mile long target.
The note we found from Ethan's backpack,
1/55, first of the 55th.
That's the mechanized infantry battalion.
And 31
could be 31st street, their
muster point for the parade.
Why that battalion?
First of the 55th were deployed to the Gulf.
These are Desert Storm veterans.
Authorities are still seeking
information on the whereabouts
of suspected terrorists Ethan
Edwards and Jorge Galvez.
Police are investigating reports
that Galvez was spotted
in his native Baltimore.
Other sources tell us authorities now believe
the suspects may have fled the country.
In other news...
(BAGPIPES PLAYING)
We have a possible ID. East of
Madison, south side of the street.
Hey. Desert Storm, right?
I can tell by your uniform.
I was 171st Armor.
You were with the 55th mechanized division.
GOREN: You got your ID?
You know, they're checking IDs.
You wanna smoke?
You know, I quit seven years ago,
but being back in the uniform
really plays a trip on my head.
You got a light?
EAMES: Police! Clear! Out of the way!
(GOREN SCREAMING)
(gun firing)
MAN: Get those people back.
Mark the perimeter.
God's will.
Let's hope so.