In New York City's war on crime,
the worst criminal offenders are pursued
by the detectives of the Major Case Squad.
These are their stories.
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
Kyle, this is Malcolm Bryce.
My brother Kyle.
So you're the high school teacher
we've heard about. Welcome!
(SPEAKING IN SHELTA)
(CHUCKLES)
My nephew says you look like a Protestant.
Oh, by birth. I'm not really religious.
No matter.
Let's get you set up with a Protestant drink.
Come on.
Oh, you look so pretty today, Fiona.
Is that him? Is that the teacher?
What does your Mr. Bryce teach?
He's not "my" Mr. Bryce, but he
teaches geography and history.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, the friendliest one
was your cousin, Aidan.
Mary and Paddy's eldest, right?
Poor Aidan.
He likes talking to people who
don't know about his accident.
He was hit by a horse when he was a kid.
Lost the family jewels.
- Ouch.
- Yeah.
That's why he's never been married.
You think they suspected anything?
No.
Wallach. Hold on.
It's your office.
This is Lawson.
Oh, Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
How could you involve her
in something like this?
And you, Fiona, you're 12 years old.
You have your whole life ahead of you.
It doesn't always seem like it.
Don't be smart.
They're not charging her, but only
because it's her first arrest.
- You're a different story.
- Come on, girl, get in.
Please, this time let me take her.
She belongs with the family.
Get off your high horse, Ann.
Fiona and me ain't the only ones with trouble.
What are you talking about?
It's known.
What?
MALCOLM: Look, can't we just talk about it?
Yeah, 10:00.
We'll work it out.
Paul, I didn't hear you.
Ann, we've come too far to give up.
I have to, Malcolm, for everyone's sake.
I thought this was important to you.
I'm sorry, Malcolm. I have to go.
I'm sorry you're disappointed.
(INTERMITTENT WHIRRING)
Ann Lawson, probation officer
for juveniles in Manhattan.
Just a guess, but it probably won't
match the tread marks on her chest.
Oh, God.
By my count, she's been run
over at least 3 times.
And that accounts for all the abrasions.
The door's ajar on the driver's side.
Yeah. These bruises on her front.
She was standing right by the door.
She heard, she turned.
Wham. She didn't have time
to get out of the way.
Or she didn't try.
Maybe she recognized the car.
Or she was drunk?
No, I don't smell any alcohol or food.
Ah. Hot peppers,
blue cheese.
Buffalo wings?
Well,
someone who ate Buffalo wings held her hand.
The left hand, actually.
It wasn't a handshake.
No.
It was someone who knew her well.
Sure, we're famous for them.
Best wings south of Buffalo.
You see her in here last night?
With somebody who ordered your famous wings?
Yeah. Booth 17, back here.
She was with an older guy.
He got here before she did though,
did all the eating and drinking.
Did she seem anxious or nervous to you?
Yeah, all of that. She
didn't even take off her coat.
Sounds like older guy
was getting the brush-off.
How did it end?
She left after half an hour.
He did a couple minutes after that.
I guess he thought he could
still change her mind.
Is that what he looked like he
was doing outside with her,
trying to change her mind?
Well, he came back 20 minutes
later and he looked upset.
Then he asked for directions
to the E train and took off.
If he came here by subway, why would
he need directions back to the subway?
Unless he took a cab, or
drove and had car trouble.
No. He would have had to have a tow.
No, maybe his car trouble
was that his car disappeared.
Maybe he filed a report.
You said your car was parked
across the street from Benson's?
Yes. As a matter of fact,
I was there last night.
Well, as a matter of fact, we knew
that. What were you doing there?
I was meeting a friend.
What's this?
"To Daddy, love, Paul." That's adorable.
- Your son?
- Yes. He's very adorable.
So you're married?
Uh, divorced.
This friend with no name is just a friend?
Her name's Ann. Ann Lawson.
We had a date, very casual.
I don't see what this has to do with my car.
How did your paths cross in the first place?
We met at a conference
on juvenile delinquency.
It's an interest of mine and, you
know, she's a probation officer.
You're an anthropologist, aren't you?
Well, I have PhD's in
anthropology and sociology.
Fearsome Gods. That's a South American tribe.
Wasn't this a bestseller?
Oh, yeah, for non-fiction, years ago.
You participated in blood rituals and warfare.
I didn't participate. I observed.
Uh, The Jukes.
Another best seller?
Well, it was in 1877.
Uh, I'm getting the feeling you're
really not interested in my car.
No, see, we're very interested.
Your casual date was run over last night
in a parking lot near Benson's.
My God, I...
We're especially interested in the
fact that your car was stolen
just around the time Miss Lawson was killed.
And you think...
I'd better, uh, talk to a lawyer.
Make sure he has our card.
The woman dumps him, he runs her over,
reports his car stolen, then ditches it.
That's not much of a plan.
He's not much of a liar, either.
His interest in juvenile delinquency?
No. He has no background in criminology.
DEAKINS: Then maybe it's about her
work, one of her probationers?
She had 43 open cases. She hadn't
violated anyone in over 3 months.
All right. The DMV record on Bryce's car.
It shows an accident 3 months ago.
The driver was Paul Bryce.
The adorable kid was driving?
Bryce was happy to let us believe
that he was still a little kid.
Let's see if he has an adorable record.
He's got a sealed juvie record.
He might be one of her probationers.
Maybe Bryce met Lawson through his kid.
Or maybe not. The kid isn't
one of her current cases.
(PHONE RINGING)
Deakins. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Which exit? Thanks.
Bryce's car just turned up off
the Whitestone Expressway.
Look.
Ann Lawson was Paul Bryce's
probation officer
for over a year.
6 weeks ago she transferred his
case to another probation officer.
There's no explanation.
- Where you going?
- To Mom's.
Paul, I heard about Ann. You
wanna... you wanna talk?
Talk? I know where you were last night.
You just couldn't leave her alone, could you?
You just couldn't.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Hotwired?
No. That's what they wanted it to look like.
But these wires are for the wipers.
This was definitely an amateur.
I mean, first he reports the car
stolen then gets it washed.
Then goes back to the car theft scenario,
ditches the car and pulls the wrong wires.
How tall do you think Malcolm Bryce is?
6'5", give or take.
The last person to sit in this car
was 5'10" at the most.
5'10". What an adorable height.
Ann asked me to reassign Paul
Bryce to lighten her caseload.
How'd Paul end up on probation?
Uh, when he was 15, he stole
a car with another kid.
There was a firearm found in the vehicle.
It was Paul's first offense.
He got 18 months’ probation.
Here, this is hers.
Did he get along with Miss Lawson?
She never said otherwise.
There's nothing in the file.
The file. Do you... do you
mind if I have a look?
It's locked.
She didn't like people poking in her things.
Ann was very private.
These kids, they often form attachments
to their PO's, isn't that right?
No. We intervene before
things get out of hand.
In any event, we don't
arbitrarily reassign kids.
Did Miss Lawson ever talk
to you about Paul's mother?
No.
Her phone logs show only one
phone call from Mrs. Bryce,
the day before Miss Lawson
had Paul transferred.
JANET: It was about something Paul told me.
He said Ann was taking him to an
exhibit at the Whitney on a Saturday.
It was wishful thinking on his part?
Yes. I called Ann.
Apparently she had no idea.
He had a crush on her.
Is that why she transferred him?
She said that he would do better
with a male probation officer.
How did Paul take it?
I think he suspected that I
had something to do with it,
because a few days later
he moved in with his father.
Your ex-husband, he told us that he had
an interest in juvenile delinquency.
Is that because of what happened to Paul?
Well, that's how Malcolm
deals with personal problems.
He studies them.
There would have had to been some
kind of sociological force at work?
Yes.
By the way, do you know where your son
was the night Ann Lawson was killed?
He was at Malcolm's.
First the good news. We found your car.
Oh, good. Was there anything in it?
We'll get to that.
And now the bad news.
About your casual date with Ann Lawson,
we were told it would have been
inappropriate for her to date you.
Well, she did. I met her at this bar...
It wasn't a date. It's about work, your work.
What? What are you talking about?
Your study of criminal
behavior among juveniles.
Ann was helping you.
She...
Maybe she gave you sealed records.
You didn't want to get her
in trouble so you lied to us.
That was before you found out she was killed.
With all your sneaking around,
it's no wonder we got the wrong impression
about you and Ann. Anybody would.
Especially someone with a juicy adolescent
crush on their probation officer.
Oh, I get it. Paul ran her over.
With his... with his skateboard?
No, with your car.
You see this damage?
Ann's blood and hair
were found in the radiator.
And then there's the rear
view mirror and the seat,
which was adjusted for someone
roughly around 5'10...
Paul didn't do this.
I had the car, I drove it to the bar.
But he knew you were meeting with her.
And seeing how smitten he was over her,
once he saw the two of you together,
he just had to vent. He had to.
He had the extra set of keys,
he took your car and Wham.
Paul is not a criminal.
His rap sheet says otherwise.
He made one mistake.
There's a big difference between one
bad judgment and a criminal mindset.
Paul does not have the predisposition
for antisocial behavior.
That's learned over years and
years through generations.
I went out and I got my own copy.
It's The Jukes Family of New York State.
"The true story of a genetically-linked
clan of paupers, harlots,
"misfits and petty criminals."
It's inspired a whole
generation of behaviorists,
and maybe it inspired you.
Look, Professor,
now, maybe it's just hit home
now that your son was...
Paul didn't do it.
I did.
I was in love with Ann and I
begged her not to break it off.
But she wouldn't listen.
She walked away. She just walked away.
And I killed her.
He just took the rap for his kid.
What a good Dad.
What it did was it gave us an open
invitation to search his place.
Make sure the warrant covers the kid's room.
Other than a pair of moldy shoes in
the kid's closet, it's slim pickings.
This is a family tree that Bryce
has been putting together.
It's pretty rough, and it's
got his own shorthand.
But there's one name here,
L. Devlin.
Now, there was a Devlin on the
list of Ann's open cases.
Yeah. "Devlin, Lane."
This docket number, it's a criminal case,
but not a delinquency file.
Well, this might be why.
If L. Devlin is the same person,
he or she was born in 1975.
One of her old probationers?
Back for an encore?
Aunt Trina will be claiming
her this afternoon.
Dad wants the viewing tomorrow night.
The last time I saw her, we fought.
I shouldn't have. She didn't deserve it.
Oh, now.
You didn't know.
Dad, he wants to know
on account she was run over.
Open casket?
Daddy, we need to see her to say goodbye.
Listen to me, cousin.
Ann was a sister.
She'll have pride of place,
so everyone can see her.
Now, you'll have to use your skills
on the left side of her face
but you will make her pretty.
Now, you can do that, can't you, cousin?
MAN: Lane Devlin was
picked up for shoplifting.
Her and her 12-year-old.
They tag-teamed the store?
It was cute.
Kid's up front, spilling her
Slurpee, making a diversion,
while Mom's stuffing
battery packs into her purse.
The kid's got a hell of a role model.
Her mom's got priors for bad checks.
What we can't figure,
is why her file was with a juvenile
probation officer in Manhattan.
You mean Ann Lawson. She's Lane Devlin's aunt.
Lane called her when she
and the kid got popped.
And she came and bailed them out?
Apparently, it wasn't the first time.
The little girl, where did she end up?
Back with her mom. Lawson told us
she was going to seek custody.
Her and the mom had a real squabble about it.
Lane Devlin's other relatives, uh,
you wouldn't happen to have
run across any of them?
We've had dealings with two of her brothers
for possession of stolen property,
and she's got a cousin doing
time for a short-dollar scheme.
I gotta get back in.
This clan of misfits and petty
criminals Professor Bryce was studying
was Ann Lawson's.
Yeah, a study that he was
afraid to tell us about.
Maybe one of these criminals isn't so petty.
I didn't talk all that much to her,
her being down in the city, busy with her job.
She was in law enforcement.
That must have made for some
tense moments at family dinners.
She got along with everybody.
She was all for the family.
EAMES: A family she never
mentioned to her co-workers.
Why would she?
What do you people want from me?
I'd like a glass of water.
Is that okay?
No, no, that's okay. I can get it myself.
I need to run some names by you,
starting with your brother Evan.
Hi.
You're Fiona, right?
I'm Bobby.
I'm sorry about your Aunt Annie.
What are you reading?
A schoolbook.
Atlantic County School District.
That's South New Jersey.
You went to school there?
Just for a semester.
Bucks County, Pennsylvania.
You went to school there, too?
Last year.
Is that why your Aunt wanted
you to move in with her,
because you move around so much?
Would you have liked that,
to live with your Aunt?
I wouldn't have liked
living away from the family.
Well, wasn't your Aunt family?
She didn't live with the family.
She went to live outside, with them.
You mean outsiders,
like me?
Being an outsider is not such a hot thing.
They're suckers. Outsiders are suckers.
I can't imagine Ann being
killed over a custody battle.
Even with her criminal record, Lane
had nothing to worry about from Ann.
Unless you factor in the
family's criminal record.
You see them all checking us out?
I'll bet you that every one of them,
either by blood or marriage,
is related to the Devlins.
These RV's, campers, trailers.
This is their winter camping ground.
Come spring, they'll hit the road.
They're Travellers.
Travellers. I can't say that
I know that much about them.
That's how they like it. They're insular.
They have their own language, Shelta.
They're like a tribe. They're
scattered across the country
in family groups maintaining
a nomadic lifestyle.
With the rep of being scam artists.
Roof and driveway repair
fraud, that sort of thing.
They also do seasonal work, anything
to support life on the road.
And one of them used Professor
Bryce's car to kill her
over the custody of this little girl?
Well, one thing the Travellers
are not known for is violence.
Well, depends on how far
Ann would go to get custody.
I mean, she was telling Bryce everything.
Not just names and birth dates,
but financial arrangements,
their frauds, their travels,
the kids' neglected education.
That's a powerful piece of
evidence in a custody fight.
That might be what she intended to
use it for when it was finished.
But it could also link the Devlins
to hundreds of crimes across the
country from here to Missouri.
If someone wanted to stop
Miss Lawson from talking,
can you tell who would have the
authority to order such a thing?
Well, this symbol here...
here, it indicates a tribute
being paid to a K. Devlin
by other members of the family.
It means he could be the alpha dog.
Ann's older brother Kyle.
Bryce likes to get up close to his subjects.
He lived with this South American tribe.
He would have insisted on meeting Ann's tribe.
For a pair of cops investigating a
murder all the way down in the city,
you're spending a lot of time bothering
the very people who loved my sister.
She was a part of our family too, Mr. Devlin,
her being a probation officer.
If you have any ideas,
like about this boyfriend
of hers, Malcolm Bryce...
I don't know much about him.
He drove up here with Ann. Didn't he?
He charged some gas about 3 weeks…
ago, last Saturday, right?
At a station about a mile from here.
Yeah. Ann brought him
around for a cup of coffee.
Seemed a decent sort.
What did Ann tell you about him?
Just a guy she fancied. High school teacher.
Why do you suspect him?
Well, let's just say we're
not not suspecting him.
- This your truck?
- That's my son's.
Yeah, it looks like there's
a little mix-up here.
These packages say,
"50-year-warranty shingles."
- Yeah.
- They look a little thin to me.
- He's using a new amalgam.
- More like 20 years.
That's a spun glass core and the like.
And the like? This roofing tar?
Is that new too?
Because, I don't know,
it feels like crankcase oil.
I'll mention that to my son.
Hey, you know, it's kind of odd
that you called Bryce a high school teacher.
That's what he said he was.
Really? Because he's a college
professor. Teaches anthropology.
They study social groups. Tribes, clans.
Even extended families. How tall are you?
What's that to you?
Don't make us look it up
on your driver's license.
5'11...
You're all legs.
That's why you sit so low in the seat.
You don't mind, do you,
getting out of my truck?
You know, it might interest you to know
that Malcolm Bryce wrote
a book a few years ago
about a tribe of fierce warriors.
He's writing a new book about a new tribe.
It's no matter to me.
He started drawing a family tree,
and it looks like a clan of modern day nomads.
You know, itinerant tradesmen,
roofers and the like.
This isn't your tribe,
is it, here, you think?
You know, because, look, it says KD.
That could be you,
and then PD, ED. That must be your sons.
And then there's these little
squiggles next to the names.
You know, I think that's Bryce's
shorthand for criminal records.
Professor Bryce was putting you and
your kin under the microscope.
You know, like bugs on a pin?
Yeah, well, he should study his own tribe,
with that kid,
that car thief that was
panting after my sister.
Where'd you hear about that?
From Ann. He was trouble.
And we're finished talking.
Right?
If I understand you, you no longer
consider Paul a murder suspect?
Yes.
We believe Paul was home the
night Ann Lawson was killed.
But he needs to tell us about any
contact he had with her family.
This call to Rockland County from your
mother's phone on a Saturday 3 weeks ago.
How'd you get this number?
I found it at my Dad's place,
on some driving directions.
He was going somewhere with Miss Lawson?
Yes.
Some guy answered. He said
he was a friend of Ann's.
Kyle something.
He said that her and my Dad had just left.
What else did you talk about?
He asked me if I was one of Ann's kids.
He just... he kept talking. He was funny. I...
Told him all about how you feel about Ann.
And about your Dad.
Yeah.
I think he was a little drunk.
Why do you think that?
They were having some party.
I heard music in the back,
lots of people laughing and singing.
Kyle told us it was just a cup of coffee.
Might be something about that party
he doesn't want us to know about.
Here's the first one.
It prides me to know that we'll
be one blood from now on.
It's good for everyone, cousin.
(SPEAKING IN SHELTA)
TED: Sheriff Mulroney's right.
There must have been over
100 people at the Devlin's.
Lots of Indiana plates.
The Sheriff said he had his
deputies keeping an eye on things.
Yeah, well, you always got to
keep an eye on the Devlins.
Kyle hired you to take pictures.
It must have been a special occasion.
Uh-huh. Yeah, he said it was
for a confirmation party.
It was a very nice affair.
Right.
It was for his granddaughter, Fiona,
and a friend's grandson, a kid
from Indiana, Eric Brennan.
It looks over the top for a confirmation.
The flowers are all wrong.
Roses, rhododendrons, foxgloves.
The flowers of Ireland.
In the girl's hair. Ivy, faithfulness.
The blue dress, the lavender bouquet.
All that's traditional for an Irish bride.
This was an engagement
party for these two kids.
An arranged marriage. That's what
Ann wanted Malcolm to see.
An arranged marriage, between children?
This is just a betrothal.
The actual marriage will take place
when they reach a legal age.
Until then, the boy, Eric Brennan,
will live with the Devlins.
The whole idea's so primitive. An
arranged marriage in this day and age.
Yes, especially in light of the
stunning success people have
choosing their own mates in this day and age.
It doesn't matter what we think.
It's what Ann Lawson thought.
She had a history of intervening
on behalf of the little girl.
It might be what finally pushed her
into spilling her guts to Bryce.
I don't know anything about the
Devlins. Ann never told me anything.
She told you.
She showed you.
And then she took you
right into the heart of it.
The last free-living tribe of
nomads in America. What a subject.
What a book. Might even get you
back on the bestseller list.
Look! Just stop!
All Ann wanted to do was to save a little
girl from the life of petty crime.
Come on, what'd you do?
You just kept on pressing her.
Look, I swear I had no
idea they'd go that far.
I wanted to understand my son.
Ann started telling me about her family.
I encouraged her, maybe I pushed her too far.
Did you push her to take you
to this engagement party?
Well, I told her there'd be no book
without firsthand observation.
Did anyone threaten her?
Well, she was worried about Kyle's temper.
You know, she found out, you know, that he
knew and, you know, her niece told her.
You got no cause taking my daughter away.
I make sure she goes to school, I
make sure no one is harming her.
I am a good mother.
This is what they're worried about.
That's a good-looking
son-in-law you'll have there.
I know what you think.
Nothing indecent goes on.
This is just a promise.
Anybody even ask Fiona if
is this is what she wanted?
Fiona's a child.
It's up to her elders to decide
what's best for her for her future.
Well, maybe she had some little dream
about what her future might be.
Something that she talked
to your Aunt Annie about.
This is our tradition.
It's served us well. There's
no reason to change it.
How'd it do for you?
The husband your Dad chose
for you, where is he?
He's in prison, isn't he?
Five-to-ten for burglary?
This kid from Indiana,
how'd your Dad pick him?
He just pull his name out of a hat?
He does what's best.
Hey, Kyle found out who Professor Bryce was.
He found out that Ann was talking to him.
Dad would not harm his own sister.
She was family.
Even in death I heard him
making the arrangements.
He wanted her to be beautiful.
He wanted her to have pride of place.
What did he say exactly?
The left side of her face.
He told them to use their
skills to make her pretty.
There was a police report filed last summer
with the Indiana State Troopers
by Eric's grandfather, Colin Brennan.
Mr. Brennan reported the theft of 7
RV's owned by the Brennan family.
When the police recovered the
vehicles 3 months later,
they traced them back to Kyle Devlin.
Mr. Devlin stole them?
The state cops never had a chance to find out.
Brennan dropped his complaint. He
said it was all a misunderstanding.
To be settled amongst themselves?
No, it's not that simple.
The outside world is fair game,
but not the family.
Devlin wouldn't want anyone
in the family to know
that he stole from a fellow Traveller.
Ah, I see. Restitution would
have to be done quietly.
$200,000 doesn't change hands
without the family noticing.
He'd have to disguise it.
Yeah. It's tradition
for the family of the bride
to pay a dowry to the family of the groom.
Devlin arranged this marriage
and used his granddaughter
to cover up his crime.
If they were confronted
with what Devlin did...
Why would they believe us? We're outsiders.
But they'd believe Ann.
You said there's no evidence she knew.
Well, maybe Professor Bryce
misplaced some of his notes.
First of all, I want to say
thank you to Colin Brennan
for entrusting young Eric to our care.
ALL: Here, here.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Now just one more word, if I may,
about our sister, Annie Devlin.
She didn't always agree with our way,
but her love was always true.
You're back in our arms, Annie,
never to leave again.
Here, here.
And one final wish here.
That the man who killed her be met
with justice, merciful and swift.
This is a private function.
Yes. We're sorry about that.
But we have some news that we
need to share with your family.
We took your advice
and took a closer look at Malcolm Bryce.
We arrested him for the murder of your sister.
Well, that is good news. And I appreciate
your coming down here to tell us.
There are just a few loose ends to tie up.
We never got a formal ID by the family.
There's a picture for you to look
at and then a form for you to sign.
This might not be a good idea
for your daughter to see.
You saw her after the mortician
did his work, isn't that right?
You had no idea it was this bad.
No, I didn't. But that's her.
GOREN: It's pretty shocking
if you see it for the first time.
Especially what happened to the...
to the left side of her face.
Thanks.
Last thing. We need some help
deciphering some notations
that we found on these
papers in Bryce's office.
You remember he was writing
a book about your family?
Well, it looks like your sister was helping.
It might even be the reason why he killed her.
Anybody can snoop through county records,
make up stories.
The Devlins don't go talking
family business with outsiders.
I should hope not.
Well, maybe he made it up. Let's see.
It concerns someone named Aidan. Is he here?
I'm Aidan Devlin.
And next to your name, there's a notation.
It says, "sine prole."
Now, that's Latin.
It means you have no children. Is that right?
It is.
Next to it is a symbol.
I think it means an injury.
You have no children
because of an injury.
Annie was a good girl and all,
but she shouldn't have been
gossiping to strangers.
It isn't right.
Well, at least, we know now
that Bryce wasn't making it up.
What about this? It's next to your name.
It says, "debere." That's more Latin.
It means a debt.
Next to it, there are
initials, “CB.” who's that?
That would be me. I'm Colin Brennan.
Oh.
And this debt?
It's a dowry. It's nothing to worry about.
Actually, anthropologists, they
have a special symbol for dowry.
Bryce would have used it.
So no, this is definitely a debt.
Underneath it there's another
notation. It's the number 7.
And it's got this little
circle thing next to it.
Bryce used this symbol in his other book.
It meant that...
A pig was stolen from a member of the tribe.
Which just means that the debt
is about 7 stolen pigs.
You're not a pig farmer are you, Mr. Brennan?
No, I ain't.
I sell recreational vehicles.
So, maybe the debt is about 7 stolen RV's?
Is that why he owes you money,
because he stole 7 RV's from you?
I told you, it's a dowry.
Yes, you did. What about it, Mr. Brennan?
Your cousin here steal from you?
He did.
Well, how much does he owe you?
$220,000.
I'm guessing it's as much as the
dowry for your grandson's wedding?
I can't believe I let you talk me into this.
Colin, listen...
I only agreed to help you save
your honor before your family.
But your family can't
keep their mouths shut.
Come on, Eric. The marriage is over.
The Devlins won't be welcome
in our parts anymore.
And you still owe us the money.
I should have known.
I should have known it!
You can't trust those Brennans!
This is all a misunderstanding.
I'm sorry, Lane. I never
wanted this to happen.
But Ann wanted it.
To stop the marriage.
Haven't you caused enough hurt?
No, haven't you?
When you discovered
that Ann was telling Bryce
the history of the Devlin family,
or maybe I should say the
terrible misdeeds of Kyle Devlin.
That she was going to throw
a wrench into your deception,
stop you from marrying off your
granddaughter to hide your thievery.
Don't listen to this cop.
No, you're right. He's right.
Don't listen to me.
Listen to Ann,
who only ever tried to help her beloveds.
Tried to keep them out of
trouble, keep them in school,
help them to have a good future.
Ann, who got in his way.
Ann, who you disposed of as casually as you
disposed of your granddaughter's future.
This is nonsense.
You said that you never saw
the injuries to Ann's face.
But before the family could claim the body,
you described those
injuries to the mortician,
telling him to use his skill
to make her pretty.
That is not true.
Yes, it is. It's true.
I heard it.
I was told about her injuries.
No, you saw her when you ran her down.
It wasn't me. I didn't do it!
You weren't there that night,
Kyle, the night Ann died.
I came by with your supper. You weren't there.
You stop these hysterics.
I didn't kill Annie.
But she is the one who turned her back on us!
The car that killed Annie wouldn't
happen to be a Buick, would it?
Yes, it was.
Kyle, you old car thief, that set of
master keys you borrowed from me.
Am I ever getting them back?
Is that it? That's it? That's the loyalty?
Huh? You side with them?
You side with the bitch that brought
people in here to spy on us!
To kill the life, our life!
It was you or her.
Your ways or hers.
It was self-defense. My beloveds...
Shut your yap, Kyle!
Take him. Get him away from here.
Our pleasure. Kyle Devlin,
you're under arrest for murder.
Come on now, you're not going to stand
there and let them do this to me?
Paddy! Joseph! Save me!
(KYLE SPEAKING IN SHELTA)
Maeve, for God's sakes, I'm your brother!
Lane, be a girl! Help your father!
Bronson, save me. Maeve! Hey!
You know, I just realized something.
What's that?
All that Ann gave up?
It must have been hard for her.