In New York City's war on crime,
the worst criminal offenders are pursued
by the detectives of the Major Case Squad.
These are their stories.
I've been warning those people.
For 15 years, we were vulnerable.
Your resume says that you
served with the Army Rangers
in the '80s.
Who was your CO?
Sorry, fellas, can't go
into operational details.
I do have combat experience.
In an advisory capacity.
Suffice it to say,
I'm looking for an opportunity
to get back on the front lines.
Okay. We'll make our decision
in the next couple of weeks.
Thanks for meeting with us, Dan.
Okay. I'll look forward to working with you.
Yeah. Thanks.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
My bus took forever. You get him in bed okay?
He fell asleep listening to his radio.
I left you some tuna in the fridge.
Thanks, sweetheart.
See you tomorrow.
Not if I can help it.
Dr. Croydon, Victor's looking for you.
He found some papers you were
burning in the oil furnace.
He says that's illegal.
What is he talking about?
You tell him snooping through
my garbage, that's illegal.
- Hey, Matson.
- Hey.
There it is.
Thanks.
Morning, Dr. Croydon.
Don't you worry, I'll get Victor that message.
(DOORBELL RINGING)
Let me just rinse up.
I thought you'd be here earlier.
(BANGING)
(THUDDING)
AKHRASS: Her name's Connie Matson.
Part-time home care nurse.
She was Air Force until 3 months ago.
We found her discharge papers.
Page 2, section 5.
"Special Duties: Anthrax Vaccination Program."
That's why I called you in.
You did the right thing.
She was stationed just down
the road at McGuire AFB.
You'd think an Air Force nurse
could do better than night
shift as a home care.
And here's why.
General discharge. 2 medical leaves,
each less than 30 days. Maybe drug rehab.
No. I didn't see any track marks on her arms.
If it's drugs, it's probably
amphetamines. Go pills.
Air Force keeps them around like vitamins.
Maybe her go-go lifestyle got the best of her.
It's gel from an ice pack where
the seal must have been broken.
"For use with food and medical supplies.
"Conforms to US Military specifications."
Right down to the serial numbers.
HENDRICKS: The ice pack was
traced to your dispensary.
You worked in the infirmary together.
It's even known you fraternized with her.
Right, is the Lieutenant right, Airman?
Were you fraternizing with Matson?
Yes, sir. Before I was married.
Well, she didn't have any
contraceptives in her apartment,
no condoms, no evidence at all
that she had a boyfriend.
Not even that she was pursuing
a heterosexual relationship.
You were her beard?
Because a young, unattached
woman, gay or straight,
would be harassed here.
Yes, ma'am.
And lately she was having
a tough time in the world,
and she came to you for help.
Something she could sell?
Boosters for the anthrax vaccine.
She said she had a buyer for them.
Anthrax vaccinations and the yearly
boosters are tightly controlled.
And someone would buy them on the black market
because they'd want to stay off the radar.
And once they're vaccinated, the next step is
getting the anthrax.
Could be a nut job with a roll of stamps
or a terrorist with a crop duster.
I see a lot of inquiries in Matson's
file about her military record.
Hospital, medical group...
Prospective employers.
Yeah. And then there's this one,
Haznostics Incorporated up on Fordham.
They made two inquiries.
"Haznostics."
GOREN: "A testing facility for
environmental hazards and bioagents."
Well, anthrax certainly qualifies.
There was no anthrax in the nurse's apartment.
But the lab found five spores
on the money she gave to her Air Force buddy.
Same South African strain
as the anthrax in Dr. Stern's collection.
Dr. Stern who says he doesn't know anything
about missing anthrax.
Whoever gave the nurse
the money to buy the vaccine,
already has the anthrax.
Haznostics.
EAMES: What position did she apply for?
Nurse in our clinic.
She has experience treating
exposure to bioagents.
Does that happen here often?
No.
We do environmental testing for
insurance claims, workers' comp.
But you never know.
Has any of your employees ever
been vaccinated for anthrax?
Anthrax isn't something we've dealt with,
but I think Dr. Croydon...
Dr. Dan Croydon, our lab director.
He was vaccinated a few years ago
during a posting in South Africa
for the WHO.
Has he kept up with his boosters?
His last one was 4 years ago.
He'd no longer be protected
against the virus,
unless he got boosters we didn't know about.
I see he worked at the Army bioweapons lab
at Fort Detrick in the early '90s.
I like this guy.
What's this notation for?
His wages are being garnished.
He fell behind in his child support.
I really like this guy now.
Is he here today?
He took his son to Jones Beach.
Every morning, 7:00, Dr. Croydon's out
the door, comes back an hour later.
You ever seen him with this woman?
No. Dr. Croydon's hit a dry
spell lately, you know?
You call him a doctor, but he's not a
doctor. He's a scientist. A lab rat.
But he makes you call him "Doctor"?
- Yeah.
I know his type. Goes off on people...
That's him. He even threatened
to have the super arrested.
For what?
Super caught him burning
garbage in the furnace.
We need to check the furnace room.
EAMES: Directory of government agencies.
He's highlighted a few,
FBI, Homeland Security.
Could be targets.
Found one picture of his son.
Looks at least 5 years old.
He's an equal-opportunity deadbeat.
His wife filled out this
healthcare form 2 months ago.
He hasn't mailed it in yet.
It's "the Great Flu Epidemic."
The flu epidemic of 1918 killed
22 million people worldwide.
Excuse me, who are you?
And what the hell is going on here?
We just executed a search warrant.
A search? A search for what?
Evidence of a crime.
- Do you know a Connie Matson? She's a nurse.
- No.
EAMES: She applied for a job at your lab.
I don't hire the nurses, and you
haven't answered my question.
What are you searching for?
Well, this, for one. You
highlighted some of these agencies.
Any particular reason why?
They offered me work.
You people have no idea
who you're dealing with,
but you'll find out. I promise you.
Oh, speaking of unfulfilled promises,
make sure you mail this.
It doesn't sound good, Dan.
Maybe we should take them up on their
invitation and go and talk to them.
I know these people. It
doesn't matter what you say,
they twist it around
until it suits the conclusion they want.
I refuse to play their game. I won't do it.
The lab says there was no trace of
anthrax at all in his apartment.
Might just mean he's not
as careless as we thought.
This is the lab report from the furnace.
They found ashes of paper products
and traces of bentonite.
I give up. What's bentonite?
An anthrax dispersal agent.
It keeps it from sticking to surfaces,
like the inside of an envelope, for example.
And then there's this
they found in a corner of the furnace box.
It's the plastic package
used for self-adhesive stamps.
Postage stamps and bentonite.
And a hit list.
Next stop is a mailbox.
We notified the Feds.
The HAZMAT people are checking mailboxes
near Croydon's home and his job
and along the route he takes to work.
If Dr. Croydon has anthrax,
can we say with certainty how he got it?
The anthrax on the money was from a
strain developed by the South Africans.
Croydon was in South Africa in the late 1990s,
same time as Roger Stern.
Sounds as sure as next week's weather.
"The idea that American
companies export anthrax
"to such despotic regimes as Iraq
"with the approval of our
government is insane.
"But that's what's happening now.
"And one day these bioagents will reap
terror, and we will be unprepared."
It's a letter to the editor he wrote in 1988
when he worked for the Defense Department.
Must have made him popular
with his colleagues.
Well, he got reprimanded. His career stalled.
Now he has an ax to grind, a point to prove.
We were posted in South Africa for 3 years.
Dan's work was water quality.
No anthrax, far as I know.
Far as you know.
Was there a lot you didn't know?
Let's just say that Dan was a
disappointment and leave it at that.
You mean personally or professionally?
Because he had a prestigious job with the WHO,
a PhD from the Strathcona University.
Was there something wrong with his PhD?
He never finished his thesis.
His problem is he never
finished anything in his life.
He'd rather quit or run away.
I know the type. You know,
he neglects his child support,
irresponsible, self-involved.
You know, he just needs a personal crisis
to carry out his threats.
Anything like that going
on in his life right now?
My son said
that his job interviews
haven't been going very well.
GOREN: Just one more thing.
I noticed a diagnostic code
on your husband's medical claim
for post-cancer treatment.
I was diagnosed with breast
cancer 6 years ago.
When you were in South Africa.
I came home for treatment with my son.
But not with Dan.
He was having too much fun
jetting around the world,
doing important work.
When I finished chemotherapy,
I filed for divorce.
The man that she described
fits the profile.
A wounded idealist who's nursed
his grievances for years.
Which doesn't get us any
closer to an arrest warrant.
We turn up the pressure.
We drive him into our arms.
REPORTER 1: Mr. Carver, is it
true you're looking for anthrax?
We're looking for evidence in
the murder of Connie Matson.
REPORTER 2: We've been told an employee
of Haznostics, Dr. Daniel Croydon,
is a suspect.
CARVER: Dr. Croydon is not a suspect.
While we have no clear evidence
linking him to the murder,
he remains a person of
interest to us. Thank you.
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
I recognize that we live
under the rule of law,
but I have a right to due process.
They call me a person of interest,
as if that entitles them to ransack my home
and smear me in the press.
All without a shred of evidence.
I've prepared a handout for the press.
It contains a chronology
of the government's campaign against me.
Dr. Croydon, would you be
willing to take a blood test
to prove that you haven't
been exposed to anthrax
or recently vaccinated for anthrax?
Dr. Croydon wants to come in,
but I've advised him not to.
Well, if you're afraid he's
gonna incriminate himself,
then we'll make it off the record.
I have no fear of incriminating myself.
Is that a yes?
There are over 1,200 different
strains of Bacillus anthracis.
And if your so-called experts told you they
could pinpoint where this one came from,
you should fire them.
No, see, they compared it to an anthrax sample
which is known to have come from the
South African biowarfare program.
I'm sorry, I should be discussing
this with other scientists,
not with you.
We're going on two motives.
The first is extortion.
The suspect needs money.
Say, because his wages are being garnished,
or he's stuck in a dead-end job.
Only a mediocre mind would think
that's a plausible motive.
I can't wait to hear your other theory.
Vindication. The suspect feels victimized.
This is how he's settling the score.
That's another mediocre idea,
for someone with his qualifications
would find the proper forum
to air his grievances.
Oh, right, like sending
a letter to the editor.
When you were forced out, why
didn't you raise a real stink?
It was a waste of my energy.
I had a family to take care of.
GOREN: Oh, right. Nothing comes before family.
Right.
Maybe you just didn't feel up
to taking on the government.
You know, that's another
aspect of the profile.
Sometimes they compensate
by pumping up their resumes.
With non-existent PhD’s.
That's a clerical error.
One other aspect of the profile,
passive-aggressive personality.
(SCOFFING)
The kind that kills with anonymous letters.
That's not me.
It's in everything that you do!
You neglect your child support,
your medical claims...
No, I forgot.
You want to be seen as the victim.
No, I told you, I...
Well, you won't. You'll be
seen as the malcontent,
a fake, a loser
who won't even take care of the
basic needs of his family.
Damn it. I told you, I just forgot!
Oh, you forgot to come home with
your wife when she got cancer?
She didn't have to come back to New York.
They have hospitals in South Africa.
She did it to undermine me.
You... you bastard.
You bastard!
Good day.
Dr. Croydon will be a hit with the jury.
He's not ready to give it up yet.
He had a lot of fight left in him.
We stay on him. We wear him down.
He'll break. He'll make a mistake.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Deakins. Yes.
Which room?
Thank you.
Son of a bitch.
There's a note on the desk,
but it's not signed.
He's broken now.
The ME's leaning toward a finding of suicide.
She found booze and anti-anxiety
medication in Croydon's blood.
- There was a note?
- Yeah.
"I tried to serve my country.
"But now they've engaged
"a former member of the Army
Criminal Investigation Unit
"to implicate me in an anthrax plot.
"This man has used his badge to ruin me.
"Thanks to him, I've lost
my job, my home, my son.
"My innocence doesn't matter to him."
And that's where it ends.
Detective, he took the coward's way out.
His note, his anger,
is directed outward at me.
But depression, suicidal depression,
is anger turned inward.
He was drinking, taking pills. He...
He succeeded at killing
himself, but he never...
This guy, he never finished
one thing, not even his note.
Well...
The anthrax booster was found,
unused, this morning
by Canadian customs in a knapsack
on a New York-Montreal train.
There was also a small vial with
less than 2 grams of anthrax.
They think the owner
lost his nerve and got off the train
before it reached the border.
It doesn't look like Croydon
was the guy, after all.
EAMES: We still have a homicide.
FBI has taken jurisdiction.
You guys clean up your paperwork.
I would never say anything in
front of the Captain, but...
Everything pointed to Croydon.
You didn't listen, Bobby.
You didn't listen to what his wife said.
EAMES: Admirers?
Reporters. They want a comment.
Can they print a hand gesture?
You get any sleep last night?
I've been trying to tie up loose ends.
Look, you know,
if you don't incinerate bentonite
at a very high temperature,
it leaves a residue.
Now, Croydon...
Croydon's lab has a 2,000-degree
industrial furnace.
So why did he use an oil furnace
that only burns at 400 degrees?
He would have known better.
I had Latent take another look
at Connie Matson's cover letter to Haznostics.
Her fingerprints are under
the ink, not over it.
She only handled the blank page.
Somebody else wrote the letter,
printed it, mailed it.
This evidence, it's manufactured.
Croydon was set up.
Now he's dead, and, just as
mysteriously, he's been cleared.
It doesn't make sense. If
somebody wanted to ruin the guy...
Is that what you think
they wanted to do? Or this?
"innocent man driven to suicide
"by ruthless and incompetent detective."
SERVER: You must really like Veal Parmesan.
It's the fifth night in
a row you've ordered it.
I just like watching you write it down.
Hello, Bobby.
I would call you Detective Goren,
but given your press coverage lately,
you probably want a low profile.
Keep your hands on deck.
We don't want you playing with
your pistol under the table.
Nicole Wallace.
Hitchens, same as it was and always will be.
Yeah. I thought we cleared all that up.
Your identity, your pathology.
Oh, right, your little theory.
But like many of your theories lately,
wouldn't butter your parsnips.
What will they do with you, Bobby?
Do you think they might find a
nice tunnel for you to guard?
(LAUGHING)
Well, you know, there is a bright side.
I mean, you'll have more time
to spend up at Carmel Ridge.
Oh, you're just hitting all the marks.
I was right about you, Nicole.
Elizabeth. And you were wrong about me.
Just like you were wrong about Dr. Croydon.
Read the papers, Detective. Your
insights have no currency anymore.
Is that what this is about?
Do you remember what you said about Moby Dick
and the unrelenting pursuit of evil?
I know why you were unrelenting
about Dr. Croydon.
I know what it was about him that
stuck to your hide like a harpoon.
He ran out on his poor sick wife.
Cheers, Bobby. This was
everything I'd hoped for.
Careful, your salad's wilting.
HITCHENS: Oh, I was hoping you'd join us.
This is Robert Goren, my friend
I was telling you about.
This is my husband, Gavin Haynes.
Oh, nice to meet you. Elizabeth tells
me you're one of New York's finest.
Oh, not these days. So you're married to...
I told you, Gavin has made an honest woman
and American citizen out of me.
We should give you our number, and you
should join us for dinner one night.
Oh, better yet, you should
jot down our license plate.
You can find us that way.
She's a remarkable woman, isn't she?
(LAUGHING)
Oh, gosh.
She wouldn't have dangled herself
in front of me like that
unless she felt completely protected.
With Gavin Haynes as her
husband, she would be.
She planned this return from the
minute that she disappeared.
Stern, Buzz Davis, Connie Matson...
Who knows how long that she knew them.
Resourceful girl like her would have held on
to their numbers till she needed them.
And then there's Croydon.
The perfect background.
The perfect personality.
DEAKINS: Perfect fall guy.
CARVER: She framed him with planted
evidence, and she killed him.
And Ms. Matson, is she also responsible?
Croydon. She picked a man
I already didn't trust,
I already didn't respect.
That's how she blind-sided me. She...
She picked a man like my father.
She... She got me. She got me good.
Then let's get her back.
That's Nicole and her French boyfriend
during their killing spree in Thailand.
Well, outside of being blonde and pretty,
that girl doesn't have a lot
in common with Elizabeth.
You have any more recent photos?
There's that.
I noticed your marriage went unnoticed.
Was that her idea, to keep it a secret?
She told me that she had an ongoing dispute
with the Australian tax people
over a fund she ran in Melbourne.
It's actually not her dispute.
It's Elizabeth Hitchens',
whose identity she stole.
She tell you about her little
stint at Hudson University?
She was very sorry she got
dragged into an academic feud.
A feud? She was responsible
for the murder of 2 people
and killed 2 more in the last 2 weeks.
If you had one iota of evidence...
You don't see it, do you?
We're just picking on your poor innocent wife.
I hear a familiar voice.
Sweetheart, I tried to call you at the spa.
They told me, but I was
wrapped up in something.
GOREN: Don't worry.
You did a good job inoculating
him against the truth.
Sooner or later, she is going to turn on you.
She probably turned on people for good reason.
I don't intend to give her that reason.
But I've humored you, Detective, up till now.
But I know about all your methods.
You drove an innocent man to commit suicide.
I'm warning you,
don't try it with my wife.
A week after her marriage,
Hitchens got an expedited citizenship hearing
before an administrative judge
and pledged allegiance a week later.
Unless we prove beyond a reasonable doubt
that she is, in fact, Nicole
Wallace, she's out of our reach.
ME heard back from the Australians.
Nicole Wallace got vaccinated
for anthrax in 1996,
in Bendigo.
Apparently, that's the
heartland of sheep country.
Do you have an atlas?
Her last booster was over 2 years ago.
ME says it protects up to 2 to 3 years later.
If we could test her blood, we'd know if
she handled the South African anthrax.
There's no probable cause
to compel a blood test.
6 years ago, Croydon investigated
an anthrax outbreak in Australia,
in the state of Victoria,
which happens to be where Bendigo is.
6 years ago, Croydon's wife was
in New York battling breast cancer.
He would've been in Australia by himself.
They could've met.
Nicole could've found out
that he ran out on his wife.
Factor in your credibility
problem, Gavin Haynes.
The way he was mooning over her,
he'd spend his last dime
keeping her out of trouble.
She seemed to be moony over
him, too, in her own way.
Question is, how far will
she go to protect him?
As you can see by the date, the Australians
filed their extradition request
2 months before Ms. Haynes'
citizenship was granted.
She wasn't aware of it. Your office
just didn't perform its due diligence.
You can't revoke her citizenship,
and because this concerns
non-violent financial crimes,
she can't be extradited.
That's true, but this is one of
several irregularities involving
the administrative judge who presided
over her citizenship hearing.
Ms. Haynes, did Judge Burbank ask
you for a financial consideration?
STYMINGTON: Now wait a minute!
The judge paid off the
mortgage on his country home
2 weeks after Ms. Haynes became a citizen.
We're very curious how he did that.
Did we bribe him, is that
what your question is?
No.
If you'll give me a minute,
I'll be right back.
You're sure you don't know about this?
I mean, if Gavin did anything...
I know.
He wouldn't be so bloody reckless.
Well, he just might, Elizabeth. He loves you.
Now, you may not be in
trouble, but he would be.
Bribing a judge is serious business.
Judge Burbank?
Elizabeth Haynes.
You did my citizenship hearing.
Yes, I remember, Mrs. Haynes.
Could I have a word with you in private?
This may come as a shock to you,
but you're being investigated
for taking bribes.
Excuse me? Where did you hear this?
They suspect my husband of helping
you pay off your little shack here.
I have no way of knowing if he did or not,
but I will not let anything happen to him.
You name your price, whatever it is,
but under no circumstance
will you implicate my husband.
If I'm hearing you clearly...
You heard me clearly, Judge.
I'll be in touch with you tomorrow.
Love the garden.
Hello, Nicole.
If you insist on calling me that name,
I'm afraid I'm going to have to ignore you.
Nicole, Elizabeth, Wallace,
Hitchens, Haynes, whatever.
All of you are under arrest
for attempted bribery.
Since we believe she
obtained her citizenship
using a false identity,
she's a foreign national
with no status and no right
to the usual protections.
How long is that going to fly?
Hopefully long enough to get
probable cause to test her blood
for anthrax exposure,
proving once and for all
that she is Nicole Wallace.
What a clever pair you are, with
your phony extradition request.
And that judge, oh, he was very convincing.
I'd keep an eye on him if I were you.
He might actually be taking bribes.
You know, let's put aside
Elizabeth Hitchens' crimes.
Let's talk about Nicole
Wallace and her crimes.
That's the anthrax you left
on the train to Montreal.
Along with the booster Connie Matson
got for you before you killed her.
Where did you find her, at a
bar near the Air Force base?
You slept with her, is that
how you gained her trust?
Fire up your imagination
all you want, Detectives,
you won't provoke me.
And then there's Dan Croydon.
You find out where he was staying.
You invited yourself up to his room.
You commiserated with him
and then suggested that
he vent his outrage on paper.
You made sure he was good and drunk,
and then you got him in the
shower and strung him up.
All that, and she can bake a cake, too.
Really, Detectives.
Hold on.
There's a leak in the anthrax bag.
It spilled onto the table.
It's okay. It's not weaponized.
It'll stick to the surface.
It won't float around.
EAMES: I'll get a HAZMAT guy up here.
It's an emergency kit.
They give us these things
in case something like this happens.
Your hands.
You touched the table here.
So did you.
We were vaccinated after 9/11.
There's no problem.
But you... You touched your face,
your mouth, and...
Yes, please save me.
I've been mortally contaminated
with what? What is this,
confectioner's sugar?
You don't believe it's anthrax.
Fool me once, Detective.
I doubt even you would throw
around bags of lethal anthrax.
Well, there's a detection kit.
It's easy to find out.
Give me your hand.
If you just wanted to hold my hand, Bobby,
you really didn't have
to go through such measures.
Is it everything you imagined?
Don't flatter yourself.
I see in you what your other conquests don't.
Right, the famous Goren vision.
A little shortsighted lately, though,
with one glaring blind spot.
Well, we all have our off days.
Just a couple of drops on this strip,
and then we'll see if it's anthrax.
Did it ever occur to you
how much you despised him?
Who? Croydon?
No. Daddies, Bobby, the subject is Daddies.
I was stunned to discover
divorce decrees were matters
of public record here.
While reading between the lines
of your parents' divorce,
I gather your Daddy was quite the bon vivant.
He liked a good time.
Tell me, Bobby,
when he ran out on your poor mother,
it was her you blamed, wasn't
it, for driving him away?
Yeah. Yes, I did.
You were 11.
You thought Daddy was fun and exciting.
Boys are supposed to look up to their Daddies.
But now you worry you're too much
of a chip off the old block.
Is that why you haven't married?
You're afraid that maybe you'll be the
model husband that your Daddy was?
No.
You remember the rules. Tit for tat.
And what about your father?
Did you ever confront him
for what he did to you?
Did you ever bring him
to account for his abuse?
You never even admitted it to yourself.
This doesn't concern me.
You've become the abuser
of that sparkling little girl.
You pimp her out.
You make her sleep with men and
women she doesn't want to,
what, to serve your pathological needs
and theirs.
Well, this will come as news to Gavin.
You know, we've fooled ourselves
into thinking we're in love.
Thank God Detective Goren
is here to save us.
No. You just listen to me!
Just listen to me now!
My, how you hate being contradicted.
I believe that there is a part of you
that loves Gavin.
The decent part of Nicole
that's hidden in that bunker you call a heart.
You know, the last time you sat here,
you confronted the truth.
It hurt,
so you had to shoot the messenger.
Hmm?
If I could be wrong about Dan Croydon,
then how could I be right about you?
Well, you blew it, Nicole.
Your one chance for happiness with Gavin.
One chance,
and you had to come back to me?
You couldn't leave well enough alone.
That's the price of denial.
Look, it's positive for anthrax.
- You don't seem concerned.
Maybe you didn't hear me.
- I heard.
You've been exposed to anthrax.
No cause for alarm, Detective.
I've been vaccinated for anthrax
along with millions of my fellow Australians.
Including Nicole Wallace.
Yeah. She was vaccinated
in 1996, in Bendigo.
One year before she met Dan Croydon.
And her records show
that her last booster was over 2 years ago.
On the other hand,
there's no record that shows
Elizabeth Hitchens
has ever been vaccinated.
So if, in fact, you are Elizabeth,
you would be alarmed.
You'd be screaming for medical help.
You might still have enough time to
put on a convincing performance.
(CLEARING THROAT)
This is proof of what? Nothing.
Not quite. It's probable
cause for a blood test,
which will reveal your recent exposure
to the South African anthrax.
And that, Ms. Wallace,
is proof of everything.
Well, of course I've been exposed to that.
Isn't that part of your little charade?
This? No, that's a different
strain of anthrax.
A genetically impaired harmless strain.
You don't seriously think he'd toss
about bags of lethal anthrax, do you?
Don't think for one second that
this is the end of us, Bobby.
When the blood test came back positive,
I thought she'd jump at a plea,
but she's insisting on a trial.
Sure, with Gavin Haynes footing the bill.
Well, it's your turn in the barrel now.
I'm done with her.
Here, have one.
What's this?
Scones.