Sir, everything all right?
Yes, sure, Officer, I'm fine.
Peter Bonham. New York
District Attorney's office.
We're here to interview a witness.
Where's your witness?
He's a no-show.
You gentlemen be careful.
Yes, sir.
Now can we go?
- Too bad he didn't show up.
- Hmm.
He was probably scared off.
I should've gone by myself.
I could've put three more
burglary raps on Walters.
Peter, do you need a feather
in your cap that badly?
Excuse me.
Hello? Yes, who's this?
What? Oh, my God. Well, where...
How is...
Yes, yes, yes, I'm writing it down. I will.
Did you call 911?
I'll be there.
Just, please, call 911.
it's Linda. They said she passed out.
- Where?
- Some tenement uptown,
she was meeting a pro bono
client, they can't wake her.
They found my number in her wallet.
They called you before they called 911?
It doesn't sound right.
You should try calling her
on your cell phone.
Linda? Oh, thank God.
Where are you?
I'll explain later. I'll see you at home.
She was having lunch at Chanterelle.
That is really weird.
Maybe not.
What are you talking about?
The phantom witness. Now this phone call.
No. No.
It's just probably some stupid prank.
Who do you think is doing this?
Someone you prosecuted?
Maybe it was one of your old clients,
maybe they feel you didn't argue
their case with enough zeal?
Mommy? Mommy, I made you a drawing.
Oh, sweetie, that is beautiful!
It's your office, Mommy. And that's me.
Can you draw a picture
with you in Daddy's office?
No. Your office is yucky.
Well, Sara, if you draw me a nice picture,
I'll put it in my office
and then it won't be so yucky.
Okay. Mommy, come help me.
Okay.
The seats are right behind the dugout.
Linda's at a trial attorney's
convention in San Francisco that week.
- I have to be with Sara.
- Ah, just bring her.
You know, you could stuff
her full of hot dogs.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Shut up, you do.
Mr. Bonham, what happened? Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah. The brakes, I couldn't stop.
- You said the brakes?
- Yeah.
I kept pressing down but nothing
happened. What are you doing?
I know something about cars.
No wonder your brakes didn't work.
Somebody punched a hole in your brake line.
The lines had been perforated
so the brakes would go out on your way home.
I take the FDR home. I could've been killed.
Do you drive your car to work every day?
Oh, just Wednesdays. I pick up
my daughter at her swimming lessons.
I take her out for Chinese food.
Did you trace the address
of that tenement uptown?
It was an abandoned building.
I can't believe...
Ron, if you hadn't told me to call
Linda on her cell phone, I...
The no-show witness, who did
he have information on?
Eric Walters.
Walters is looking at two-to-four
on a simple burglary.
Until we know what's what, I'd like to
post a patrol car in front of your home.
No. I don't want to alarm my family.
Anyway, Linda's out of town
this week in San Francisco.
I'll send Sara to stay with her grandmother.
That still leaves you.
I have a carry permit for it.
I do not intend to be a sitting duck.
His list of cases, larcenies,
fraud, possession.
All low-profile nonviolent crimes.
I take it he's not one of your starters.
Peter may not be the most brilliant
prosecutor in our office,
but right now he's the one in the most danger.
Let me know what you find out.
I got no beef with Mr. Bonham.
He's got his job and I got mine.
What's that, burglary, accessory to murder?
I don't get with no murder.
Someone used your name to lure Bonham
to a phony meeting at Hunts Point.
That's like saying somebody picked
his name out of a phone book.
Hey, man, Mr. Bonham gets killed,
I don't see it helps my case. Does it?
Eric, be quiet. It was nice talking to you.
I wonder how many other inmates
have asked the same question.
If a prosecutor dies during a case?
No inmate's asked for information
on that specific question.
What about the legal issues it would raise?
Most likely the right to a speedy trial.
A Sixth Amendment issue.
Everybody here wants to know
about the Sixth Amendment.
Big caseload, Counselor?
I'm just working on my own case.
Really? You were charged with rape?
You're researching People v. Williams.
That's all about a defendant's
access to a victim's sexual history.
What do you want, Detective?
Have any inmates asked you
about the legal impact
of a prosecutor's untimely death?
That would be privileged information.
There's no privilege for jailhouse lawyers.
I can make the argument there is
if the client had an expectation
his communications with me
would remain confidential.
Oh, brother.
No, actually, Eames, he has a very good point.
But in this case,
rule 1.6 of the ABA
Code of Conduct would apply.
Even if the client told me
of an impending crime,
the code doesn't impose any
affirmative obligation on me.
It's my call.
And the code also says
a lawyer must refrain from
morally reprehensible conduct.
Since you have discretion
to breach the privilege,
not doing so when a life is at stake
is morally reprehensible.
Artie Kahn. He made bail last week.
You called my lawyer, right?
We talked to your other lawyer.
Other lawyer?
The one in Rikers. The one you told
you were going to whack your
prosecutor, Peter Bonham.
I never told him that.
I just asked what would happen
if Bonham up and died.
And you said it just like that,
out of intellectual curiosity?
Yeah, out of that.
It just so happens, somebody's
been trying to kill Bonham.
They cut the brakes on his car.
- No way.
- Yeah.
Whoever did this would've gotten
brake fluid on their hands.
Brake fluid leaves a residue.
No matter how much you wash,
you can't get it off.
You can't see it either.
You know what this is?
It's a towelette thing.
It's a special towelette thing.
It has a liquid on it that
reacts with brake fluid residue.
If you have any brake fluid residue
on your hands, it shows up.
Go ahead, Artie. Wipe your hands.
I didn't cut no brake line.
Then why the questions about
Bonham dropping dead?
Because two weeks ago I was at Rikers,
on the phone,
and there was a guy on the phone next to me,
talking about Bonham having an accident.
Is it this guy?
I didn't really look, you know.
I had my back to the guy.
You were listening.
What did he say, his exact words?
He was gonna pay good money for
Bonham to have an accident.
A permanent accident.
Did you know that they're shooting
chicken eggs through a shower head,
boiling it, mixing it with sea
brine and calling it caviar?
Hello, everybody?
Ah, our dedicated civil servant.
Honey, the play starts in 45 minutes.
I'll just change shirts.
Oh, a Detective Goren called you.
He said he tried you at the
office, but you had already left.
I'll call him tomorrow. Something wrong?
Well, I can't find the Pomerol.
I asked you to bring it up this morning.
I thought you said any old Merlot.
Could you be a sweetheart
and get it from the cellar?
Sure. Okay.
Oh! We found the best place to buy caviar.
In Istanbul. Have you been?
No. We're always wanting to travel,
but with Peter's busy schedule...
I came down to get a bottle of wine.
I was about to turn the
corner when I heard a noise.
He shot at me. I...
I shot back. He was trying to kill me.
There's one round missing.
Serial number's been filed off.
I got burglary tools in here.
Lock-pick set, diamond
chisels, cordless drill,
the guy was trying to make it
look like a burglary gone bad.
This is what we're supposed
to think he was after.
Gary Burke. Work ID. Bartender downtown.
He's gonna be late.
Burke was feeling lucky. Stopped
by the OTB this afternoon.
Must be a couple grand's
worth of bets here.
Check the locks for lubricant.
Both sides of the door.
Yes, sir.
Just covering all the bases.
Do you use the basement door often?
No. I think the lock's rusted.
Oh, well, it's working fine now.
Well, of course it's working. This man's
a burglar. He knows how to open locks.
Why assume he's a burglar?
Well, he came for the safe. Didn't you see it?
We did.
What do you keep in there?
Nothing. It came with the house.
We only lock it because of Sara.
Well, how would a burglar know about it?
Oh, we've had workers down there.
They always ask about it.
But you don't think it was a burglary.
No, but he brought burglary tools with him,
maybe to help with the cover story.
Cover story? What do you mean?
We have an ID on the intruder. Gary Burke.
Either of you ever seen him before?
No.
You ever prosecute him?
He has along rap sheet, muggings,
drug possession. No burglary.
No, I don't recognize him.
You didn't answer my question.
What's going on here?
Someone's put a contract
out on your husband's life.
You can't be serious!
The phone call, the car, it's all...
it's all part of it.
Oh, my God, Peter.
But he's okay now, right? I mean, he's safe.
It depends on how determined this person is.
And we have no way of knowing that.
Mr. Sanchez, what are they doing here?
They're cops.
Lori lives here with Gary.
- Where's Gary?
- He's gotten himself into trouble.
What trouble?
The trouble somebody gave him
a lot of money to get into.
I don't know about any money.
The $2 grand he spent at the OTB?
The $3 grand you spent on new
dresses, new shoes, new handbags.
Gary saved up his bar tips.
You're really good at keeping secrets.
Me, I just run off at the mouth.
For example, I'll probably tell
Gary that you were out all evening.
Gary knows I was with my friends.
Look at your hair.
It looks like you just
walked out of the shower.
I know I'm gonna say something
to Gary about your hair.
I went to the gym. I took a shower there.
Really? They let you smoke cigars at the gym?
Because you smell like cigar smoke!
I know I'll just blurt that out to Gary.
Gee, Lori, thanks to my partner's big
mouth, Gary might get the impression
you're fooling around with some guy who
smokes cigars and lets you use his shower.
Please, don't tell him that. He'll hit me.
Okay.
Let's go from the top.
Where did the money come from?
I don't know.
Gary got a lot of calls from this buddy
of his in prison. JoJo Martinez.
Please, you can't tell Gary I said anything.
I don't think you have to
worry about Gary anymore.
Gary Burke was apprehended
while trying to shoot one of
my colleagues, Peter Bonham.
Mr. Burke hasn't yet decided
to cooperate with us,
but we'd like to give your
client first crack at a plea.
A plea? Why? You think he's involved?
Yes, we do.
Of course, if he'd rather wait for Mr.
Burke to implicate him...
Give me a minute to talk to my client...
Vince, shut up. They're playing you.
Gary Burke is dead.
How do you know that?
PNN, Prison News Network.
That's the same place we get our news from.
Yeah. One of their reporters
heard you on the phone a couple of weeks ago
putting out a contract on Bonham.
Screw that.
Why would I want to hurt that man?
Because he's about to put you away for life?
You're facing your third
felony drug conviction.
Bonham told us he turned you
down for a plea bargain.
That's hardly a motive for murder.
I don't need to kill this
DA to beat this rap.
- JoJo, let me handle...
- Don't "JoJo" me.
The hell with all of you.
That's a nice... What you're wearing.
I mean, where'd you get
that from? Is that from Peru?
What do they call that? A serap... A serape.
No, it's a...
S-s-s-sweater.
It's a sweater.
Right. Somebody make that for you?
I was reviewing Mr. Martinez's case file,
and I noticed you missed a filing deadline
on a motion to suppress drug evidence.
He specifically asked me not to file it.
And why would he do that?
I don't know. I tried to talk
to his mother about it.
What does she have to do with it?
She's paying his legal bills.
$200 bucks a week.
Or I should say, she was.
She stopped three weeks ago.
But I still have to do what Martinez says.
It sounds like JoJo's getting
ready to cut him loose.
That only makes sense if he's
trading up for a better lawyer.
Better lawyers cost more than $200 a week.
It begs the question
where is Mr. Martinez getting the money
to pay for better representation?
Same place Gary Burke got his money?
JoJo's mom might know.
I don't know anything about a new lawyer.
I just do what my son tells me.
He asked you to stop paying Mr. Quitoriano?
I just got behind, that's all.
You made JoJo's sweater.
He was wearing it when we were talking
to him. It's a nice-looking sweater.
This one's even more stunning.
Eames, look at the sleeve.
This raglan sleeve is laid in so effortlessly.
Under the seam, at the armpit,
it's like a little pouch?
I see it. You can hide something in there.
Hmm, and there's another one in this sleeve.
Just big enough for messages,
money, drugs.
You don't tell us the truth,
you could have your visiting
privileges revoked.
Please, it was just messages.
What was in those messages?
Were they about the new lawyer?
I don't look.
But JoJo did get a new lawyer.
How is he paying for it?
He said it wouldn't cost anything.
That the lawyer would work for free.
He said she's the best.
The new lawyer's a woman. What's her name?
I don't know.
JoJo said she can fix everything
when she gets back from California.
All right, Mrs. Martinez. Thank you.
And no more sweaters, okay?
Bonham's wife was supposed to
be in San Francisco next week.
JoJo's new lawyer.
JoJo's payback for having her husband killed.
Talk about pro bono.
Oh, hi, sweetheart.
I didn't know you knew Alfonzo.
John? Just from court.
He was just asking me
about the shooting, so...
Oh.
I have a hearing in an hour.
Do you wanna get lunch?
Peter, can I talk to you?
The police suspect Martinez is connected
to this attempt on your life.
Their suspicions are completely
without merit, of course,
but, regardless, I want you to recuse
yourself from Martinez's drug case.
That's not necessary. I can remain objective.
Who are you kidding? They think
he tried to have you killed.
Linda, could you explain to
your husband why he should...
Don't talk to her!
You wanna have me relieved,
make an application.
Unless a judge tells me,
I am not stepping down.
Peter, I don't think that
he was being unreasonable.
Can we just get lunch?
I can't, actually, I have a deposition
at 1:00. So, I'll see you tonight.
Linda Bonham's involvement would explain
how Gary Burke got into their house
using a door with a rusted lock.
Not to mention, she was working hard
to sell the burglary cover story.
She's one of the most respected
trial attorneys in the city.
She is married to a second-rate prosecutor.
She may be ready to trade up
to something better.
That's what divorces are for.
She's the bread-winner, she'd
end up paying him alimony.
Until you present me with
incontrovertible proof that she's involved,
I will not be applying for warrants,
issuing subpoenas nor presenting
evidence to a grand jury.
I will not embarrass Peter Bonham.
So, Linda sent poor Peter down to
the cellar to fetch the Pomerol
and that's when the bullets started flying.
It was her idea to send him down there?
Yes.
How well did you know the Bonhams?
Oh, not well.
I met Linda at a brunch.
We had common interests.
Linda Bonham's interest is in the fact
that Allison's sister is on the
board of the Canterbury School.
She's trying to get her daughter admitted.
I already told her they live
far too east of Park Avenue
to stand a chance of being admitted.
Being partner in her law firm
doesn't count for anything?
Well, some law partnerships
are forged in the courtroom,
- some in the boardroom...
- And the bedroom?
Oh, Jerry, knock it off.
Oh, no, please, my partner
loves rumor and innuendo.
Don't take my word for it.
Ask Rodney Brooks.
He's a litigator at Linda's old law firm,
and I'm told that he was one of her
stepping stones two years ago.
I was a jerk, okay?
Linda had just moved to a
new firm and made partner.
People were envious, they
were taking shots at her...
She slept her way to the
top, that sort of thing?
Right. So, one night at the cigar club,
I don't know, I had one Gibson
too many, I made up a story.
You know, like I said, I was a jerk.
Linda's successful because she
is smart and ambitious. Okay?
You handle civil lawsuits, right?
Ms. Bonham ever work with you?
Sometimes. She's good at prepping witnesses.
I work mostly with expert witnesses.
But ordinary citizens who've
never been on the stand before,
Linda was the best.
You ever work with a witness
named JoJo Martinez?
I wouldn't remember.
He stuttered.
That rings a bell.
Sure, about four years ago,
a landlord-tenant suit.
I don't remember the guy's name,
but Linda helped him get over his stutter.
Could you dig up a file on him by
tomorrow? We could send someone over.
Oh, sure.
Martinez's hesitation before words
starting with the letter "S"?
It's the mark of a former stutterer.
That's his name on the witness
list for the lawsuit.
That's how he knows Ms. Bonham.
That's how she came to hire
him to kill her husband
in return for money and
future legal representation.
The floor is yours, Mr. Quitoriano.
You send me an offer in writing,
my client will make a statement.
I'm sure it's just routine.
You know how the police...
They questioned our friends, my colleagues,
they're trading in gossip, it's humiliating.
If you weren't one of the best
defense attorneys in the city,
they wouldn't be doing this to you.
They're doing it to you, too,
Peter. Your own people!
I doubt the DA's office
is even aware that...
Is Ms. Bonham home?
What do you want?
Linda Bonham, we have a
warrant for your arrest.
What? What possible grounds could you have?
I wanna see the warrant.
Put your hands behind your back, please.
For God's sake, is that necessary?
It's for her own protection.
Peter, it doesn't matter. Just call
Bill Stanton, tell him what's happening,
and tell Sara that I am at work.
She'll be at the Major Case Squad.
You're insane to think that
I would ever hurt Peter.
The insanity is you thinking
you'd get away with it.
But I have no motive!
I'm sure we'll find it, maybe in one of these.
All your electronic gizmos.
Maybe we'll find a boyfriend's number
or a message that you forgot to delete.
You know what confounds me?
With all these gizmos,
people still think they
can get away with murder.
What's more confounding is sometimes they do.
Your phone has a display for caller ID?
Yes.
When you get a call, you check
the display before answering it?
Yes. I don't understand - what...
You screen your calls.
Excuse us a minute.
Peter Bonham got a call
that his wife had passed out,
the call to lure him
to the abandoned building.
He called her to see if she was all right.
He called her on her cell phone.
His number would've been
displayed on her phone.
She would've seen it was him calling.
If she was really involved in a
scheme to lure him to his death...
She wouldn't have answered her phone.
That's right, she wouldn't. But she did.
Because she didn't know about any scheme.
It's him.
He's framing her. He wants to get rid of her.
Divorce is out of the question,
he wouldn't get a dime.
And he can't have her killed,
he'd be the obvious suspect.
But he can send her to jail for life.
So far it's working, all the
evidence points to her.
It won't be easy to get him.
He can't know we're on to him.
Martinez said he got $20,000 to
arrange the hit on Peter Bonham.
We just wanna trace it to Linda Bonham.
Just dotting all the "I's."
Let me know what you come up with.
How long are we keeping him in the dark?
Until we have an incontrovertible
case against Peter Bonham.
Starting with tracing
the $20,000 back to him.
I'm just finding the usual checks,
groceries, mortgage, doctor.
Which doctor?
A Dr. David Kipper on Park Avenue.
He was writing him checks every month.
Yeah.
I've got 11 charges on Bonham's credit card
to Kipper in the last year. Yeah.
Look at the deposits made
to the Bonham's account.
Just the same amount every couple
of weeks. Probably paychecks.
Bonham's covered under the
same city medical plan we are.
He pays the doctor,
the insurance company sends
him a reimbursement check.
Well, there's no record
he deposited those checks.
She's finally asleep.
Maybe we should have her
stay up at my mother's.
I'm worried that she'll hear
things at her school.
It's pre-school, Linda.
They talk about Sponge Bob,
not stuff like this.
Peter, if you want me to sleep in
the guest room, I'll understand.
No, no. Don't be silly.
Sweetheart,
I need to tell you this.
I have never cheated on you. Never.
You know that, don't you?
Sure, of course.
And the police said that I was ashamed of you.
I mean, that's just not true. I have
always admired you for what you do.
You don't have to say anything.
And when I made partner, I was happy for us,
it just meant that our life
would be better. And Sara's.
The insurance company says
two years ago Bonham stopped
depositing the reimbursement checks
and started just cashing them.
He's been hoarding the money.
How much are we talking about?
About $25,000.
All from routine doctor's visits,
check-ups, little aches and pains.
He's used his insurance money to
build a war chest to frame his wife.
Two years ago
Bonham won a conviction over
George Kolinsky for a drug case.
Kolinsky got 20 years.
Hired a new lawyer and appealed.
The conviction was overturned,
most of the charges were set aside.
Kolinsky ended up serving a year.
All thanks to his new lawyer.
Linda Bonham.
The guy's a prosecutor. He knows
losing a case is part of the game.
There's losing. And then
there's losing to your wife.
And then there's getting your
balls handed to you on a platter.
His wife had just made partner,
there were rumors of infidelities.
The guy stayed with her for two years,
sleeping in the same bed,
just waiting for payback?
This guy's a poster boy for
passive-aggressive personality disorder.
He doesn't confront his wife, he doesn't
argue with her, he doesn't contradict her.
Instead he uses us, the police,
the DA's office to nail her.
It's time we let Mr. Carver know
he's prosecuting the wrong person.
We can't tell him without Bonham finding out.
You want me to keep Carver out of the loop?
Okay. We'll tell him when we're ready.
Any idea when that will be?
Bonham's done a great job of burying his wife.
There is someone who might be
able to help us dig her out.
JoJo Martinez.
My client laid everything
out in his statement.
He called Miss Bonham twice. That's
when she told him what she wanted.
She sent the money to his mother,
and Gary Burke collected his
share from Mrs. Martinez.
How did you know when to call Miss Bonham?
She s-s-sent the notes to my mother
with the phone number and when to call.
The notes your mother sewed into the sweaters?
My mother didn't know what was going down.
The number you called, you still have it?
No. It was different numbers both times.
C-c-cell phone numbers.
How did you know it was Ms.
Bonham that you were talking to?
I mean, did you recognize her voice?
No. She just s-s-said who she was.
And it was the same lady both times?
I guess. I don't know. The s-s-second
time she called she said she had a cold.
Was there any chit-chat or just business?
Just business. She told me what she
wanted me to do and that was that.
The numbers he called were
probably prepaid cell phones.
Untraceable.
And the woman he talked to?
Most likely two different women.
Most likely prostitutes Bonham
hired for the occasion.
The times the calls were
made corresponded to times
when Linda Bonham was home alone.
With no verifiable alibi.
Bonham thought of everything.
What's that?
It's Martinez's statement. I'm improving it.
3 calls?
Didn't you just tell me Martinez made 2 calls?
Well, now he's made 3.
I need to get this re-typed.
Don't expect me to beg for a plea
bargain for something that I didn't do!
Miss Bonham, I'm offering
this out of consideration...
I'm innocent.
I know you hear it from defendants
all the time, but I am innocent.
We have Mr. Martinez's statement.
He says he talked to you.
It's just not true.
Let's show her the statement.
It's on the second page when he
talks about the phone calls.
He lists the calls, date and time.
If there's anyone who can verify
you didn't get the calls, tell us.
Well, these first two,
I might have been alone.
But this third one, I remember
this Sunday, I was with Peter.
We went to Connecticut for a drive.
- You sure?
- Yes, yes.
We talked about getting a summer rental.
We even got lobster rolls at a food stand.
Ask Peter. I did not get a phone call.
This whole thing is a pack of lies.
Well, we'll certainly
look into it, Ms. Bonham.
Why not ask Peter right now?
Yes, ask him! Please, just ask him.
It's Ron. Could you come down to the office?
Yeah, thank you.
This date here. It's a Sunday.
That's one of the times Martinez
said he talked to your wife.
Do you remember where you
were that afternoon?
I was with Sara in Central Park.
With Linda?
No. She stayed home.
So, you weren't in Connecticut?
Peter, don't you remember?
We stopped to eat right outside of Guilford.
Ms. Bonham, I'm sorry.
Peter, what's the matter?
You have to remember.
- Linda, let's go.
- No.
- Peter.
- Linda, please.
We dug for clams with Sara.
Oh, my God, no, you...
You son of a bitch, you...
That's enough, Linda.
Oh, my God! How could you?
I need to...
Now she knows.
She knows it was you.
What's he talking about?
What are you talking about, Detective?
Well, you just couldn't resist.
Resist what?
Letting his wife know that
he's the one who framed her.
What?
That's not true.
Martinez never said that he
called your wife that Sunday.
That was me. I revised the statement.
The truth is, is Linda was
in Connecticut with you.
Not only did you stop for
food, you stopped for gas.
$12 worth.
It's right here on his credit card bill.
Maybe you forgot. Maybe you didn't.
But you could either confirm
your wife's alibi
or confirm Martinez's statement.
It's a tough choice.
Oh, I see.
It was brilliant, Peter.
You put that little wife
of yours in her place.
Her and her big salary,
her successful law practice.
All the things that she accomplished
with no regard for you,
for your... your feelings.
When she took the Kolinsky appeal,
how did she rationalize it?
Did she tell you
that there were important
constitutional issues at stake?
And when she beat you, did she go "Aw,
shucks, honey, it's not personal."
Who was she kidding? It was personal.
She crushed you.
And not in the privacy of your
own home but in a courtroom.
In front of your colleagues, in
front of the whole legal community.
Not only that,
it's on the damn record.
There.
Where law students,
lawyers, judges,
your friends and neighbors
can read about it
from now until eternity.
Everyone knew. Everyone.
They would look at her
and then they look at me.
My own daughter looks at me
like I'm some kind of a joke.
Well, you showed her, didn't you?
Peter Bonham, you're under arrest for murder.
How long had you suspected?
Only a few days. We couldn't take
the risk of him finding out.
Please, no explanations.
I've got to first deal with Peter Bonham.
But I will get back to you, Detective.
He'll get over it. Just like Peter Bonham.