[Man Narrating]
In the criminal justice system...
all defendants are innocent
until proven guilty,
either by confession,
plea bargain or trial byjury.
This is one of those trials.
I went to dinner with my boyfriend.
Then we went to his apartment.
He dropped me here around 7:00.
I saw Lauren's door was open.
[Sniffs]
She's not an early riser, so...
I looked in.
Her eyes were open,
but I saw blood, and I knew...
right away.
When's the last time
you spoke to your sister?
Yesterday.
Around noon I called her cell.
She said she was seeing Ken
for dinner.
That's Ken Jackson,
the all-star forward.
Apparently Lauren had been dating him.
They weren't really dating.
He's married.
They were involved?
Yeah.
But she knew it couldn't go anywhere.
It's not a suicide. I wouldn't
bring you down here for that.
[Gaffney] Lady Derringer? I
hear they make earrings to match.
So convince me. Women rarely
shoot themselves in the head.
Some women are too vain.
That's not evidence.
A model who bunks in a Soho loft with
her kid sister, hangs with celebrities.
Let's talk about the wound.
No powder burns
or stippling.
And there was no visible blowback
on the weapon.
I'd say she was shot
from over five feet away.
What's this on her hand?
"Spin"?
Hot new nightclub
in the meatpacking district.
Caters to A-list celebrities.
That brings it back
to Ken Jackson.
How many miles to the gallon
you think that thing gets?
If you have to ask,
you wait for the hybrid.
[Door Closes]
Well, here we go.
Mr. Jackson. Sorry, guys,
no time for " signings.' '
Ain't about autographs.
We're from the D.A.' s office.
Lauren Ford?
You know her?
Women. Look, they all
claim they know me, man.
R-R-Right.
Well, you know, I don't want to
jam you up with a tabloid thing.
It ain't a great place to talk.
Look, I don't know her. Okay? Okay.
Why don't you come down to the station
with us, answer a few questions.
We'll straighten everything out.
[Sighs]
Look, I saw her a couple of times,
you know what I'm saying?
And the last time
would have been-
Couple days ago.
Mm-hmm.
So tell me what she said. The last time you
- you had sex, right?
Look, man, you know my wife will kill
me if she knew I was talking like this.
Well, we're not
gonna tell your wife.
All right, so how do we fix this?
Look, how much she want?
Money's not gonna help
Lauren Ford. She's dead.
[Exhales]
So I better get a lawyer?
Or we could keep talking.
Make this go away.
Yeah, right.
Every major paper,
plus ESPN, Fox, CNN-
Blood's in the water,
and the sharks are out.
Well, we're not
spreading any rumors.
Jackson is interviewing
heavy-hitter defense attorneys.
That's the leakage. Couldn't
even wait to be indicted.
The M.E. Report says,
"In view of lack of stippling
at the site of the entry wound,
"the bruises
and minor vaginal abrasion,
possible rape and homicide
should be considered.' '
Damn. Could he be
any less committal?
[Kibre] That's an M.E.
I'll never put on the stand.
The latent prints on the gun are hers,
but they're in her own blood.
How could she shoot herself,
get blood on her hand,
and then pick up
the gun?
Bits and pieces that'll never
get a grand jury to indict a celebrity.
They'll want something
that could be a tabloid headline.
The M.E. Found semen in the victim.
A D.N.A. Match could put
Jackson at the scene.
But we have no probable cause
to get a sample from Jackson.
Well, that's all in the news. We
gotta do something. Shake the trees.
[Man]
Welcome. I'm Rex DaSilva.
First, let me level.
I'm pursuing this case.
Usually it's the other way around,
but your situation intrigues me.
Hey, there is no situation.
I'm completely innocent.
Not completely.
Hey. Now, we talked all that out.
[DaSilva]
Ken. Ken.
In a perfect world,
innocence would assure acquittal.
It's not perfect.
So tell us what will.
For starters, perceptions.
Tiffany's beauty
- Wherever you two go, there'll be a focus on Tiffany.
But Tiffany, when you glare at Ken
with those hard, lovely eyes,
you're telling the world
he's done something bad.
You don't know him.
I do.
That ruby ring-
Six karats?
- Seven.
- A recent gift?
From now on,
before you look at Ken,
look at that ring.
It's magnificent,
and Ken gave it to you.
Feel good about that.
Yeah.
Now the world knows Ken's a good guy,
a loving husband.
You're saying, " I know he's innocent.' '
This grand jury-
Can I go in there and just
clear all this mess up?
Not if I'm your lawyer.
[Tiffany] Forget "if.' '
You are his lawyer.
So what does he do?
He speaks to no one
who isn't now in this room.
He goes about his life with caution.
They'll be after Ken's D.N.A.
Don't spit, chew gum...
or leave behind a locker room towel
where they can get it.
And keep your secretions
to yourself.
His secreting days are over.
[Kibre] Mr. Mebane, you were at one
time a teammate of Kenneth Jackson's?
Yeah, before I was traded.
Did you know Lauren Ford?
No, I never knew her.
I just know about the reporter.
Did Mr. Jackson date a reporter?
I think it was more than " date.' ' Last year
there was talk some reporter might sue him.
Sue him for what? It was on the down
low, but I heard they liked to play rough.
You know, I guess it got out of hand.
- Do you know this reporter's name?
- No, just that she worked out of Philly.
Okay, thank you, Mr. Mebane.
Are there any questions?
Yes, sir.
Mr. Mebane says that he got traded.
Didn't Ken Jackson
force you off the team?
No one forced me off the team.
Come on. A nyone who reads the sports
page knows that these guys hate each other.
- Yes?
- When do we get to meet Ken Jackson in person?
[Laughter]
I don't care what some ballplayer said
in a grand jury.
I meant what I said on the phone.
I won't discuss Ken Jackson.
You wasted a trip to Philly.
Well, we don't plan on eating
cheese steaks and going home, so-
So subpoena me. Fine.
That's not what we'd prefer.
This is the upside
- The information you give us is of no value and we go away.
Was she raped?
She had sex shortly before
she was killed.
Now, Ken Jackson claims
that it was consensual.
He threatens, she submits-
To him that's consensual.
Obedient.
Is that how it went?
Two months into my job,
our head of sports news said...
that Ken Jackson would do
a one-on-one interview.
He asked specifically for me.
Saw you on the news.
Liked what he saw.
And I was flattered.
After the interview he asked me
for a drink in his hotel room.
Ken opened some champagne
and started to lay out some coke.
I knew where it was going,
and I wasn't up for it.
I started to leave.
Suddenly he had a gun.
There was no menace in his voice.
He just aimed at me and said,
"Get undressed.' '
When he was done he asked
if he could call me-
like we'd had fun.
I'd like you to talk to our D.A.' s.
It's his word against mine,
and he's a star.
There must be others.
Find them.
[Chattering]
[Cameras Flashing]
First of all, to my teammates
and my fans-
and mostly to my beloved wife-
I was unfaithful.
It would be a lie to deny that,
and I'm truly sorry
that I've let you down.
With all of my heart,
I regret all the pain that I've caused.
- [Clamoring]
- This lady, Lauren Ford-
Her death is a tragedy,
but I had nothing to do with it.
[Reporters Shouting Questions] Because of the ongoing
investigation, Mr. Jackson won't take questions directly.
Isn't he right now the target
of a grand jury probe?
We can't know that because
grand juries operate in secrecy.
But if there is a probe,
Mr. Jackson will be happy to testify.
You'd let him?
I would encourage it.
Sadly, the district attorneys believe
that celebrity cases bring votes.
That's the only reason why
this woman's tragic death...
is being exploited in the first place.
Are there any other questions?
I loved him saying Jackson
will testify. It's smart.
We can't reveal grand jury witnesses,
so people won't know
he never showed up.
So we've run out
of grudge-bearing players.
What about the reporter?
Shaky.
She's threatening to come down
with a case of selective amnesia.
His D.N.A. Would sure help.
Well, we're not any closer
to probable cause.
Well, maybe we can get his D.N.A.
Without probable cause.
[Pop]
[Girl]
Thank you, Mr. Jackson.
What's your name, man?
Corey.
I'm Elizabeth.
I'd like Tiffany to sign too.
Sure, honey.
[Man] Ken, we need you for
some product shots. All right.
Enjoy it, Ken.
Leave a little lip on the bottle.
[Applause]
Wrap it up. We're due
at a mall in Newark.
- Punch it up, y'all.
- [Together] Punch it up!
Okay, kids, Ken has to go.
Thanks.
[Audience Groans]
Thank you.
Come on.
Damn.
[Cheering]
That's it. Yeah. Yeah.
What a catch.
Hey, how much
- How much for the hat? Sorry?
My kid's a fan.
I'll give you 20 bucks for the hat.
Twenty bucks?
Tell you what.
Heres 100 bucks.
Take the boy to Atlantic City.
Better idea.
Leave him.
Go on your own.
My spies saw a lab report.
They got Ken's D.N.A.
They'll try for a match with
the semen found in the victim.
So what? Ken went
public that he cheated.
Yes, but still
- a match links Ken to the events of that night.
Maybe there was someone else
around that woman.
We should offer a big reward for information
- Half a million dollars.
- Tiffany- - They should be looking
to find out what really happened.
When they did that in the Simpson case,
it only served to heighten suspicion that-
Don't compare me with him.
Look, I'm innocent.
Now, you must believe that.
Of course, but it's a fool's move
in any game to overreact.
- This may simply go away.
- How would that happen?
The prosecutors have a problem
unique to a celebrity case.
Grand juries like sitting there
hearing dish about famous people.
It's their 15 minutes of fame.
Once they vote, it's over.
You're saying they might not vote at all?
First MichaelJackson investigation,
they sat for months,
and then voted no indictment.
We stay calm. All right?
And see where this goes.
[Kibre] So in comparing samples
of Mr. Jackson's D.N. A...
to semen samples found
on Lauren Ford-
Frequency calculation indicated
that one in every 1.5 million...
would be expected to have
the same profile as the donor.
And this tells us what,
Dr. Spellman?
Kenneth Jackson had intercourse
with Miss Ford shortly before her death.
Thank you. Any questions?
Did he find Ken Jackson's D.N.A.
On the gun?
The gun was not offered for D.N.A.
Evidence. So why is this a big deal?
Ken admitted he had sex with her.
Tiffany says in here
the woman was stalking him.
Okay, you've heard forensic evidence
that states that the victim...
was shot from at least five feet away.
You've seen photographs of bruises
and vaginal abrasions.
I really think it's time for you
to consider taking a vote...
on whether or not
to indict Kenneth Jackson.
That woman in Philadelphia told her
roommate that she was raped with a gun.
Can we use this as evidence?
No.
Hearsay is not allowed.
But
- [Clears Throat] I would like to remind you...
that this grand jury
will reach an expiration date,
and at that time it's entirely likely...
that a whole other group of people
will get to decide...
whether or not to indict Kenneth Jackson.
Congratulations.
How'd you move 'em off the dime?
Well, it's hardly cause
for celebration.
We were two votes short
of a no bill.
Close calls are as good as any.
With our felony murder charge,
Ken Jackson might use
the Phil Spector defense.
What, because they were seeing each
other, guns are acceptable foreplay?
The media can also spin that
as an accidental death.
We can't address all the possible media
spin. Get a warrant and haul him in.
A perp walk plays right to charges
of overzealous prosecution.
Then no arrest warrant.
Let him surrender.
And no cuffs on our hometown hero
when he's arraigned.
Happy now?
[Crowd Clamoring]
[Cheers, Whistles]
Look, this is wrong.
I didn't kill her.
[DaSilva]
Come on. Come on.
Given the defendant's
obvious resources,
we assert that he's a flight risk
and request remand.
Mr. DaSilva?
Where could this man
possibly hide?
Ken Jackson
is here today voluntarily-
out of respect for Lauren
Ford's family and the law.
The State's case is so weak, they
dare not issue an arrest warrant.
Mr. Jackson voluntarily surrendered?
We extended that as a courtesy.
Then, Your Honor,
shouldn't they extend
the further courtesy of reasonable bail?
So it would seem.
Bail is set at $500,000 cash.
[Gavel Raps] Excuse me,
Ken. Can I get an autograph?
Thank you, man.
[Gaffney]
Go through all court filings-
complaints, civil settlements,
school records.
How far back?
High school.
Flag anything that shows
a propensity towards violence.
He's an athlete. His career choice
betrays a propensity toward violence.
Guess Cilla wasn't into jocks.
Not true.
Hey, we just got our asses
handed to us in an arraignment.
I need some work out of you, not quips.
I looked into Ken Jackson's
college records.
He was suspended from playing
his senior year.
Meaning?
Means he had to sit out games.
How many? Four
- and the record says it was for curfew violations.
Okay, I'm not that big of a sports fan.
What exactly does that mean?
No college takes a star player out of games
for coming in late. He did something else.
There's a single name on the witness list-
Hope Elizabeth Newhall.
She's currently a graduate student
at Hudson University.
I'm close to my postgrad degree.
I don't wanna screw things up
by getting involved.
Well, your college records say that
Ken Jackson was briefly suspended,
and you were a witness.
What's the big deal?
That's all it says?
I was a witness?
They cut Kenny some slack?
That's what they do
for star athletes, right?
But then again, you're cutting him
some slack right now, aren't you?
Look, if you wanna give Kenny...
another chance to skate,
that's fine,
but I'll bet you any amount of money
whatever happened,
you weren't treated fairly,
were you?
No.
So you weren't actually dating Ken?
No. He and Tiffany
were a campus couple.
[Kibre]
How did you meet him?
A big party, somebody's house.
I went with some girlfriends.
Ken was there without Tiffany.
He started coming on to me.
We ended up in a room
on our own.
We kissed a little bit,
but I was nervous.
I told him I wanted to get something
to drink just to get out of there.
He said, "Look at this.' '
He was holding a knife-
sort of playing with it.
He could see I was really scared,
and I could tell he liked that.
He asked me, very calmly,
to perform oral sex on him.
I'd never done that before.
I was frightened, and he-
He-
He got rough?
He said he'd make me mind him
like a dog.
And afterwards he was like-
He offered me a ride home.
He actually thought I would see him again.
Okay. We checked,
and there's no police report.
You never told them?
I called the campus police.
They took me to the dean's house.
The coach was already there.
He and Dean Erhardt
grilled me for hours.
When I told them that I'd had a
vodka and orange juice at the party,
they said underage drinking
was a crime.
Meaning what had happened
was your fault.
They said I'd be expelled
if I told anyone.
These witnesses, Diane Harris
and Hope Newhall,
must be allowed to testify.
Their statements support the defendant's
pattern of conduct, pursuant to Molineaux.
Judge, please see this for what it is-
Two women grabbing their 15 minutes
of fame on perjured testimony.
I've read your memos. One
woman describes rape with a gun.
The other one
talks about some knife.
Therefore I will only allow the testimony
of Miss Harris, the reporter. Next?
I filed a request to access psychiatric
records on all alleged rape victims.
Yes, I've obtained those records
and I read them in camera.
I find that some of them are relevant,
especially those of Lauren Ford.
The psychiatric records
of a dead victim?
Why are those relevant?
Because Lauren Ford received counseling
for previous suicide attempts.
Four years ago, my sister locked herself
in the garage and started the car.
She'd just broken up with this guy.
And your parents took her to an E. R? They
treated her and then she got some counseling?
They told my parents
she had a marginal bipolar disorder.
After that she took a bunch of Seconal
while she was living out of state?
Over a guy.
I never met him.
Look, she did not shoot herself.
I've thought about it a lot
and I'm certain...
she didn't do that.
There are no possible grounds
for a motion in limine...
to keep the suicide out?
What do I argue, that she
had a depressive disorder?
I've never filed a nol-pros
in my career, but-
Forget it.
You're not filing one now.
We don't indict a star athlete
without a good reason.
I just got a call
from the police in Philly.
They're bringing Diane Harris in
for an interview.
Our last remaining hope ducked calls,
ducked a subpoena...
and now has to be delivered
in a police cruiser.
At least you got her.
Make it count.
I didn't want to say anything
in front of the boss, but, uh-
About a year agoJackson gave
Diane Harris a million dollars...
to shut up about the rape.
Hey, I was abused, humiliated-
I was owed.
A million bucks? I'm on
camera. My living is my image.
That station pays zip, and I
needed clothes, a car, a condo.
Really? Well, invite Lauren's
family over to see your closet.
Tell them, " I won't put away Lauren's
killer, but check out my Manolos.' '
This nightmare is costing me my job.
I'm ruined.
Do you understand that?
I don't give a damn.
Can I go?
You're served.
Show up in court or sit in jail.
Fine. I won't remember a thing.
[Gaffney] There is a way to
help yourselfhere. Yeah, right.
I mean rebuild your image.
Amber Fry
- The "other woman" for whom Scott Peterson killed his wife?
On the stand she became the courageous
witness who helped to put him away.
Ken's lawyers will destroy me.
[Kibre] Not if I have you
tell your version first.
It starts with the prosecution.
We won the spin.
Like I'd get some favor from you?
Personal feelings aside,
it's in my best interest
to make you look good.
Either that or I treat you as a
hostile witness and tear you a new one.
Your choice, Diane.
This would be my first time on a jury,
and I would willingly give up the time.
This is a big case.
You mean it seems important?
[Woman] Violence against a woman? E.R.
Nurse, volunteers at a rape crisis center.
Outspoken, advocate.
[Gaffney] Miss Claros,
have you yourself ever been
a victim of a violent crime?
Fortunately not,
but I've seen plenty of victims.
Gone.
Your Honor, we respectfully
challenge juror number 157.
Juror number 157 is excused.
[Gaffney] Ms. Prokolsky, do you
believe a man can rape his wife?
Or his girlfriend?
Sure, if he wanted it and she didn't.
I mean, I'm sure it happens.
She's indecisive.
[Gaffney] How do you know?
Well, then, I mean, there's,
like, accusations- Snoop Dogg-
and, like, I mean,
I think she could have lied,
I guess.
She's a ditz.
She's good for us.
We want her.
[Kibre] Mr. Leone, I see
you're employed by a bank.
Do you believe celebrities are easy prey
- C.P.A. He'll want absolutes.
For false accusations? Hold the
prosecution to an impossible standard.
Happens all the time. People make false
accusations against anyone with money.
Lawyers have ruined this country.
[Laughter]
I wasn't referring to you,
of course.
[Chuckles]
No problem.
Your Honor, the People
are satisfied.
Your Honor, my client
is satisfied with this panel.
Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen, you are now seated in
the case of The People v. Kenneth Jackson.
[Gavel Raps]
Can you match that demographic?
Three days I'll have them cloned.
The prosecution is gonna show you a gun-
A.25-caliber Lady Derringer...
with a single partial print-
Lauren Ford's print,
in her own blood.
Lauren Ford fired the gun,
and took her own life.
Boring.
Real evidence has been made banal by
TV crime dramas. This is not a murder.
It is a suicide. [Woman] Look
at this peak on "suicide.' '
Mmm. Hot word.
Uh, Rex, we're getting a bump on "
suicide.' ' Why don't you go there?
Make 'em feel it.
So, let us now view Lauren's
desperate yearning...
for a man she could not have.
The feel of a hard-bodied athlete,
the caress ofhis strong hands.
Oh, they're loving it.
That's pay dirt, Rex.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen, when Ken
told Lauren that they were through-
that he was breaking it off-
Ken didn't know that Lauren Ford
had a history of depression,
that there were prior suicide attempts.
When Ken told Lauren that he was devoting
himself to his wife and his family,
he never, ever thought Lauren Ford
would take her own life.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you are confronted with tragedy,
not a murder.
Thank you.
Understand, these Ken Jackson high school
records are mostly handwritten notes.
There's no computer database. I hope
you're not prepping me for bad news.
Not at all.
We have something.
There was a mediation
before a guidance counselor.
What kind of mediation?
We don't know,
but we found handwritten drafts
for a counselor summons.
One is for Deborah Jackson,
Ken's mother.
Another for Erlene Henderson.
These two people were definitely
involved in the mediation.
Was Erlene Henderson a student?
There was no one in the student body
or the faculty with that name.
Maybe if Ken's mother was summoned,
Erlene Henderson is someone else's mother.
Find out who she is.
[Kibre]
Are you currently employed, Ms. Harris?
Until recently I was a local newscaster
on Philly 5 at 10,
but I've been fired.
For what reason were you fired?
I've been the subject of a scandal
that involved Ken Jackson.
I'm showing you what has been
previously marked as People's 19.
Do you recognize this item?
Yes.
That's the check that
TiffanyJackson wrote me.
[Kibre]
May I publish it, Your Honor?
[Judge]
You may.
Why did TiffanyJackson...
pay you one million dollars?
Objection. Calls for speculation.
If you know.
Because her husband, superstar
Ken Jackson, raped me.
[Kibre]
It was hush money, and you took it?
Yes. I said nothing
about being raped at gunpoint.
Why talk now?
Because Lauren Ford was raped,
like I was, and murdered.
Objection. Move for mistrial.
Denied, but the jury will disregard
that last statement.
No more questions, Your Honor.
How is your career, Miss Harris?
You heard me.
I was fired.
I'm not talking about local TV.
This case has made you sort of
a national celebrity, hasn't it?
Unfortunately.
"Unfortunately"?
How unfortunate is all this?
You weren't paid for these
recent interviews and articles?
Some. A few.
Hmm.
How much for this one?
I don't remember.
50,000, wasn't it?
If I bring in the publisher,
what's he gonna say?
Yes. Fifty.
Ken Jackson is like
a cottage industry for you.
You make one false accusation
and you're set for life-
profiting from a woman's tragic death,
and Ken Jackson's misfortune.
Objection. Badgering
the witness. Sustained.
One simple question, Mr. DaSilva.
I don't need another question.
She's already given us
the answer.
[Gaffney]
Impact on thejury's hard to say.
Look at Father Shanley's trial
in Boston.
The only witness took a payoff,
but the jury still convicted.
They figured if someone got paid,
something must have happened.
We might get lucky.
We got Tiffany's birth certificate.
She was born Tiffany Ingram, and her
mother's name is Erlene Henderson.
All right. Check out her school
records. Maybe they haven't been cleaned.
I did that.
An incident report.
Victim Tiffany Ingram
alleges that 12th grader Ken Jackson...
attempted a sexual assault on her-
at gunpoint.
I'll draft a motion.
Evidence of a similar crime
on Mr. Jackson's wife?
We've also found Byron Holmes, the
school security guard, who was a witness.
The incident was never proven, and
Mrs. Jackson retracted the allegation.
Which is why we call it a prior
bad act and not a prior conviction.
We should have been given notice of this
during discovery. We would have prepared.
You're seriously arguing
unfair surprise?
If you don't like that, Judge,
how about marital privilege?
- They weren't married when this occurred.
- [DaSilva] They're married now.
At this point, no way am I forcing Mrs.
Jackson to testify against her husband.
Yeah. Tiff and I will talk about it.
All right.
What?
DaSilva says the prosecutors are bringing
that security guard from our high school.
Damn.
Tiff, the man is going to testify.
Now, what is he gonna say?
I was mad at you. L-
I don't remember what I said.
So I guess we're gonna have to wait
and see what he remembers.
- Ken, do you think that they know things we don't know?
- Like what?
Like there was some witness.
Like somebody saw something.
Even if it weren't true,
there are people out there...
who would lie just because we
are who we are. Hey, listen.
Ever since I've been accused,
you and I have both known they were wrong.
Yeah.
Baby, all we gotta do is be strong,
and stick to the plan.
But I'm so scared for you.
I'm gonna bring us through this.
Okay?
[Kibre] Officer Holmes, do you
remember the defendant? Who doesn't?
- And his then girlfriend, Tiffany?
- Yes, ma'am.
Did Tiffany Ingram...
report that she had been assaulted
by the defendant?
Objection. Hearsay.
Approach.
I'm assuming that you
have found an exception.
It's admissible as an excited utterance.
"Excited utterance.' ' Please.
If she can lay the proper foundation,
I'll allow it.
But be careful, Ms. Kibre.
Please describe Tiffany's demeanor
when she reported the incident.
She was very upset.
What did she say?
Objection.
Overruled.
She said that Kenny
had sexually assaulted her.
Did she say a weapon was involved?
She said he threatened her
with a gun.
Thank you.
Did Tiffany have any visible injuries?
Her hair was mussed.
She was crying.
Did you take her to the hospital?
No.
- Did you find a weapon?
- No.
In fact, two days later,
didn't she come to you and recant?
Yes. She said that she
made the story up.
She said that they were fooling around
and he pulled out a gun.
She was scared.
It was a misunderstanding.
Thank you.
Your Honor, redirect?
Proceed.
Officer Holmes, when Tiffany came
and recanted the story of the rape,
did you notice anything
different about her?
Uh, how was she dressed?
Her clothes looked nice. New.
Anyjewelry?
She showed me a ring.
Said she and Kenny had made up
and they was engaged.
Uh, well-
Was it...
the same ring
that Ms. Jackson is wearing now?
Nah, he gave her that
for cheating with the dead woman.
[Laughter]
Everyone knows that.
- [DaSilva] Objection.
- [Judge] Thejury will disregard.
No more questions.
I was called a liar.
Humiliated.
I want to respond.
Look, they want to hear me,
not her.
I'm the celebrity.
I've been accused.
Every time they ask a question
you look at me for the answer.
Watch what you're saying.
It's true, baby.
- Without a ball in your hand, you can't think.
- Damn it, now, that's enough.
Now, I'm sick of being
bitch-slapped by you.
I don't want you being questioned by them.
You understand?
I'm sorry, honey.
Let's just settle down
and listen to our lawyer.
All that matters is we win.
I understand Ken's feelings,
but I think it should be you.
You can be like Hillary Clinton-
The wronged woman telling us
to forgive what she's forgiven.
Asking that we believe in Ken
as she believes in him.
In my opinion, you're the voice
that everyone's waiting to hear.
So you knew about Lauren Ford?
I was aware of Lauren.
People tell me things.
People enjoy telling me
hurtful things.
Did you ever meet Lauren?
No, but I once talked to her.
- The night she died, she called.
- Objection.
- Hearsay.
- Goes to state of mind.
Proceed.
What did she say?
Ken had just left her.
I could tell she was crying.
But why call you?
She said she couldn't
live without him.
I actually felt sorry for her.
She was so-
She was so miserable.
She begged me to leave him.
She...
said she hated me, that she would
kill herself and ruin our lives.
Thank you.
So after hearing a woman
threaten to commit suicide,
you called 911.
No.
No? What did you do?
This wasn't the first woman
who was obsessed with my husband.
Well, did you ever
tell the police this, uh,
story?
Those police who were looking to
get famous off arresting my husband?
You say this isn't
the first woman who was...
obsessed with your husband.
Did any others call?
Others have called.
Sent little love notes,
left voice mails.
But none had ever looked me in the eye
and said I'm taking him away from you.
Looked you in the eye?
I meant called me on the phone.
Freudian slip? Phone records
show a call from Lauren.
Ken comes home,
tells Tiffany Lauren's become a problem,
then Lauren calls and threatens.
Says she'll go public,
reveal Ken's gunplay.
They'd lose millions
from their endorsements.
Or it was jealousy.
She loves him.
[Scoffs] Please. It happens.
In any case,
none of this matters.
It does to me.
Who you calling?
Please.
Thank you.
Hope I didn't drag you
from too far away.
Not at all. I live over on 110.
Chablis?
Thank you.
Park view?
No, an old family brownstone.
My father was a surgeon
over at Westside Presbyterian.
Too bad we can't toast to victory.
No, that wouldn't work.
Mr. DaSilva,
I'm one of those people who needs
to be certain about things.
An honest prosecutor needs certainty,
just as an honest defense attorney
needs doubt.
There was a moment in court-
A moment that supports
Ken Jackson's innocence.
So you know what I mean.
It's nothing I can act on.
Nor can l-
Except to say that
if there were an admission-
Is this the offer of a plea?
If the truth could emerge,
I would lobby for a plea.
There's a personal quotient involved-
a marriage-
something I'm not part of, something
they may not be willing to share.
Well-
Clearly-
The offer of a plea...
would have to come
before I could even suggest it.
A plea?
After all we did to indict this guy?
Forget it.
You sold that jury a pattern of conduct,
and I think you'll get a conviction.
I can't stop thinking
that it was Tiffany.
Off what? A slip of the
tongue? Female intuition?
You haven't talked to anybody?
I just want a judgment
based on the truth.
Stop dreaming.
You're not in the certainty business.
The winning argument is the proof.
What actually happened,
who did what to whom,
are things that we never know.
I hate that.
Learn to live with it,
'cause it's all we got.
[Judge]
Jurors, please be seated.
It's still not too late. Forget
it. Have you reached a verdict?
[Woman] We have, Your
Honor. Kibre is reasonable.
We ask the verdict be withheld,
and try to work something out.
Tiff is not gonna plead.
I got her into this mess.
Will the jury foreperson and
the defendant please rise.
In the matter
ofThe People v. Kenneth Jackson,
charging murder in the
first degree, is he guilty,
or not guilty?
We the jury find the defendant,
Kenneth Jackson, guilty as charged.
- [Spectators Murmuring]
- No!
[Whispering]
No. I can't let them do this.
It's all right, baby. It's okay.
Ken-
No. No. It's all right. I
love you. I've got your back.
There's no way I'd ever
let them punish you, ever.
[Howling]