In the criminal justice system,
sexually-based offenses
are considered especially heinous.
In New York City,
the dedicated detectives who investigate
these vicious felonies are members
of an elite squad known
as The Special Victims Unit.
These are their stories.
You got us lost.
And we haven't found
one thing on the list.
So what?
It's just a stupid Scavenger Hunt.
It's supposed to teach us how to use
the GPS in case of an emergency.
I wanna get my tracking merit badge.
"I wanna get my tracking merit badge."
You're never gonna make it
in seventh grade, Randall.
I think we go this way.
Holy cow, Marcus.
What? You see a snake?
No.
It's a lady.
She needs help.
I can get my first aid merit badge.
It's too late, dork face.
She's dead.
Julie Donovan, 17.
Two boys found her.
Cause of death?
Probably blunt force trauma
to the head.
Probably?
You don't sound so sure.
She's covered in bruises
and ligature marks.
Hard to tell what killed her,
beating or strangulation.
Any fluids?
I found semen inside of her,
so we should have the perp's DNA.
And this baseball cap
was next to her body.
That's a "C," victim could be
from Cincy or Chicago.
Her learner's permit
says she's from Long Island.
Side straps kinda big,
this could be the perp's hat.
Hey, lookee here.
What you got?
Busted cell phone.
Killer beat the crap out of her,
and kept whaling on this.
That kind of rage, he knew her.
And left her to die in the dirt.
It's pathetic.
- It's worse than that.
- What's that?
Her lips.
I'm telling you, you're wrong.
It's not Julie.
There must be some mistake.
Because, uh, she's all I got.
Her mother left her when she was two.
Drugs.
She's with her friends now.
And, uh, she didn't call me.
She forgets to call me.
Anybody you know
who doesn't like your daughter?
No, everybody likes her.
She's uh... it's a problem.
What's that a problem?
Well, when she turned 13,
she started getting into hip-hop and, um...
And what?
Black guys.
No offense.
I didn't like it.
But I didn't want to fight
with her about it.
Because I don't want her
to run off like her mother.
How did you handle this?
I told her that as long
as she kept her grades up,
I didn't care who she hung out with.
Are you ready, Mr. Donovan?
Detective?
We got a hit on the DNA.
You know?
You know who did this?
Mr. Donovan, you need
to go home and let...
I wanna know who murdered
my daughter.
I'm sorry, but we can't do anything...
Tell me who killed my daughter!
You know who did it,
you tell me who then.
Please, it's my baby.
DNA in the victim belongs to Mike Kona.
Collared for two burglaries and
a rape charge that was later dropped.
Guy's a world champion fighter.
What is he, boxer?
Uh, technically,
he's a mixed martial artist.
Mean them cats try to kill
each other in a cage?
You know, where I come from,
we don't call that fighting.
You know, these guys
are the greatest athletes in the world.
You sound like a fan.
I'm more than that.
Get out of here, that's not you.
- Bet your ass, it is.
- "Naptime wins in AC"
What, they call you Naptime because
your boring stories put everybody to sleep?
Cause of my right hook.
When it hits your head, it's lights out.
This was my last amateur fight.
You know, I was gonna quit the force
and go pro?
- What happened?
- Tore my ACL.
Now the only Naptime you get
is when you fall asleep at your desk.
I still train.
There's only one MMA gym in Manhattan.
Sometimes Kona works out there.
You think he could
be there right now?
He has a title fight
on pay-per-view tonight.
I bet he's already at the garden.
MADISON SQUARE GARDEN
WEDNESDAY, OCTOBER 17
He's out, he's out.
That's it.
I love you, baby!
- Hi, baby.
Make room for the champ.
I don't care if you are cops.
Get out of my way.
Move down, boy.
- What the hell are you doing, bud?
- Mike Kona, you need to come with us.
What for?
He didn't do nothing.
Stay out of this, Traci.
Hey, look, bud, I just won
a championship fight.
Why don't you cut me a break, huh?
Sure, the same kind
of break you cut Julie Donovan?
Let's go.
- I never seen that girl before.
- Really?
It's funny, cause we found
your semen inside of her.
Only one way for that to happen.
You know, your rap sheet
says you're charged with rape last year.
- You a good guy rapist?
- That charge was dropped.
- It's really not what you think.
- It never is.
Look, bro, man to man.
I want to believe you,
but the facts are just making it real hard.
Look, the rap sheet
says you raped Traci Bell.
Guess you couldn't fight off
the urge to rape again, huh?
I didn't rape Julie.
And I certainly didn't rape Traci.
She's my fiancee.
- Well, they said it was rape.
- Who's they?
The cops.
We were both really drunk
and making a loud racket
underneath the sheets at this motel.
I guess someone heard my screams
and thought I was in trouble.
It was all a misunderstanding.
Yeah, right, like it was
a misunderstanding last night
when he raped another girl
and then killed her.
Kona wouldn't have done that.
Then how's he get his DNA inside her?
Listen, I'm not going to help
you build a case against him.
Look, if you're afraid of him
and think he'll hurt you...
Honey, didn't you just hear me?
I'm a screamer.
I got this boy wrapped around my finger.
Well, if you're not afraid of him,
then why'd you drop the rape charge?
Because he bought me
this big fat diamond ring.
Now I get it.
You guess he's your ticket
out of this dump.
- Are you calling me a gold digger?
- No, I'm calling cold.
Your fiance raped and murdered
a young girl, and you don't give a damn.
Probably one of those
groupie sluts he was banging.
And you don't care
if he messes around?
Not as long as I'm number one.
You ever see Kona with this girl?
No, but I haven't checked the tape lately.
What tape?
I bought one of these nanny
cams at the spy shop.
It's a picture frame
with a video camera in it.
If we ever got married,
I wanted proof he was cheating.
- For what?
- For the divorce.
Open the back of the frame, and there's
a pullout USB flash drive.
- You look so hot, Kona.
- Yeah?
- Smile, baby.
- No pictures.
Come on, just one.
I said no pictures.
No pictures!
Oh, we got a sneak preview of the rest.
You know, we don't want to embarrass you,
but if Julie sold that picture,
your new nickname would be Tiny.
And I thought the camera was supposed
to make everything look bigger.
She didn't respect you, man.
She was gonna show
the whole world your privates.
So you take her to the park.
She starts screaming and won't shut up.
Then you grab her by the face
and rip off her lips.
That would shut her up.
- I just gave her a little slap.
- Uh-huh.
You guys are crazy.
You never saw me hurt Julie.
We had sex, that's it.
You say sex, we say rape.
She wanted it.
You saw the tape.
The little nympho was all over me.
That's for a jury to decide.
This is Mr. Sullivan.
He represents prestige fighting alliance,
Kona's league.
Yeah, well, you got
an uphill battle on this one.
I don't think so, big guy.
Copies of the membership card swipes
from the gym Mr. Kona was at last night.
Someone else could've swiped his card.
Video on these tapes was taken
from the gym's surveillance cameras.
Showing exactly when Mr. Kona
arrived and left.
We still got him for battery.
The girl is dead.
The only way to make that charge stick
is by playing that tape in an open court.
It's a hell of a thing
for a grieving father to see.
Cut him loose.
I'll have your badges
for putting Kona through this.
He's lucky we didn't bust him
for the battery.
I see you on the street,
pretty boy, you're dead.
Well, bring it on.
Come on, Mike, don't waste your time.
Kona would've beat your ass.
I would held my own
for a couple of rounds.
I'd like to see that, but don't expect me
to cry at your funeral.
What the...
Hey, hey, drop that gun!
Drop it.
Somebody call a bus!
Terry, what the hell did you do?
It was for Julie.
How was Terry Donovan's arraignment?
No bail, Judge sent him to Riker's.
Poor guy.
Maybe the jury will go easy on him.
Guy's a murderer.
If he does 20 years, he'll be lucky.
DNA came back on the baseball hat
found at the crime scene.
Matches a Jadon Odami.
He's a sealed juvenile record,
that's all we know about him.
Uh, Captain?
I pulled some video footage
from the smashed sim card
on Julie Donovan's phone.
Somebody's buying me lunch
for this one.
Well, there's Jadon Odami
dancing with our victim.
Looks like they about to get it on.
Maybe Jadon was her boyfriend.
I guess he didn't like sharing.
check how Julie goes between, uh,
Jadon and the other guy.
When was this shot?
Time date-stamped was
from the night of the murder.
Okay, so she does Kona,
then she goes to this party
and hooks up with the killer.
Only question is where?
Banner says Kappa Delta Alpha.
KAPPA DELTA ALPHA
FRATERNITY HOUSE
HUDSON UNIVERSITY
THURSDAY, OCTOBER 18
Kappa Delta Alpha's
one of the oldest fraternities on campus.
Looks like you guys study real hard.
We had a little party
a couple nights ago.
Was he there?
Sure.
Jadon rushed the frat last semester.
What's up with that flag?
Uh, KDA was founded by a direct descendant
of Jefferson Davis
We're very proud of our heritage.
You know you lost the war.
Why would a young black kid
want to pledge this fraternity?
A certain special interest
group made wavers.
You mean Al Sharpton
picketed your ass.
Yeah, he forced us to let
the brothers in.
Free room and board.
The brothers?
You got a lot of balls
saying that to my face.
No, they're real brothers.
Jadon and Ezra Odami.
I'll take you to their room.
Did you see Jadon or Ezra
with this girl at the party?
They were practically having sex with her
on the dance floor.
I told them to leave her alone.
Why?
Cause she was white?
Because she looked underage.
Was I right?
She filed charges?
She couldn't.
She was found murdered.
Hey, man.
What's going on?
Dudes, that girl you hooked up with
at the party.
- She got killed.
- Hey.
I will not tolerate this type of chaos.
Chasing students around campus housing.
Would you rather have
a murderer on campus?
- Murderer? Who?
- His name is Jadon Odami.
Uh, Jadon.
Yes, he and his brother Ezra exemplify
Hudson's commitment to diversity.
That's rich white guy speak for I'm gonna
let a couple of poor ghetto kids
get a taste of the high life.
Can we see their files?
Usually you'd need a warrant.
But we'll forego the formality
since I'm expelling them.
What happened to innocent
until proven guilty?
Come on, Detective.
You said you were looking for a murderer.
I have a duty to protect
my students from thugs.
I haven't seen that many thugs
with straight "A"s.
Jadon and Ezra graduated high school
at the top of their class.
Yeah, well, that's not saying much.
Check out the address of their school.
Look familiar?
Prison school.
RIKERS ISLAND
ISLAND ACADEMY
THURSDAY, OCTOBER 18
20 years at this school,
Jadon and Ezra were my best students.
They're good kids.
Your warden says Ezra
has three robbery collars.
You call that a good kid?
Those robberies were survival crimes.
They only stole for food
and a place to sleep.
Doesn't help the victim, does it?
Those boys would never hurt anybody.
Much less kill them.
If you're so sure they're innocent,
why don't you tell us where they are,
so we can help them get off the hook?
Look, I don't know where they are,
but once you read their files,
you won't be so quick to judge them.
The teacher was right,
the system failed Jadon and Ezra
the day they were born.
The system didn't make them
commit murder.
Well, look at the hand they were dealt.
Addicted mother, different absent fathers,
both in prison.
Life with mom was a revolving door.
Foster care when she was high,
back home when she cleaned up.
They got beat on by a bunch
of their foster parents.
These brothers were ticking time bombs.
They were just kids.
You know, they didn't have a chance.
What are you, a social worker now?
They lived in 19 different foster homes.
Someone's gotta help them.
Well, wait until you have
your own family.
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?
It means that when you have
a daughter Julie Donovan's age,
your heart'll stop bleeding
for the mopes who killed her.
You're saying that I don't give
a crap about the victims?
We keep it civil around here,
or you're gone.
All right, go cool off.
We need to find Jadon and Ezra.
Let's start with their biological mother,
Janelle Odami.
She lives at the Marcy projects.
You boys look in need.
I'm gonna let the Mexican here
feed the cat his Horchata for twenty.
And the brother, since we tight,
I'm gonna let you hit it for ten.
Damn!
Hey.
Hey, I ain't finished.
Pack it in, unless you
wanna stay at my place.
You just cost me twenty bucks.
- Your name Janelle Odami?
- Your name nasty ass pig?
Lose the attitude.
We're here about your sons, Jadon and Ezar.
My babies.
The teacher said they were geniuses.
They must have got it
from their fathers' side.
Hey, uncle Tom,
what's it like in the house?
Least I ain't selling it.
Damn, white, black, I'm getting
it from all sides today.
Hey, man, her pimp
called me a Mexican.
- Is that good or bad?
- Run.
- Pipe down, lady.
- Run, baby.
No, mama.
What are you doing here?
Giving myself up.
I killed that girl.
So why'd you kill Julie Donovan?
I don't want to talk about it.
What, you got the stones
to walk in here and confess to a murder,
and you don't wanna talk about it?
Look, I already copped to it.
What, you need me to fill out
your paperwork too?
I'm done with him.
Jadon, where's your brother?
Ezra's got nothing to do with this.
You're looking at life.
You talk, maybe we can do
something for you.
No.
Thanks.
Thought you might wanna say good-bye
to your mother
before we take her down
to central booking.
What they lock you up for, ma?
You know how it is, son.
Crackers got nothing better
to do than mess with my broke ass.
How you been?
Doing all right.
How about you?
This heroin's got your mom
by the soul, baby.
Took me to places that Jesus won't go.
Come here, baby.
I'm so sick and tired
of being sick and tired.
All she's put him through,
and he still loves her.
When you don't have anything,
you take what you can get.
Visiting time is over.
You know, you could help me out here.
If I tell you what happened...
You let her go?
You talk, she walks out of here tonight.
I'm hurting so bad, Jadon.
I don't wanna kick in prison.
I need to get well.
Deal.
That's my baby.
Always looking after his mama.
ARRAIGNMENT PART 38
THURSDAY, OCTOBER 18
Docket ending 2500,
People V. Jadon Odami.
One the charge of murder
in the second degree, how do you plead?
Not guilty, Your Honor.
That's not what I told you to say.
You were coerced during interrogation.
Your Honor, there was no coercion.
- The defendant freely confessed.
- Really...
what, his mother just happened to pop
in during the middle of his interview?
Your Honor, I killed Julie Donovan.
I plead guilty.
Listen to your attorney, son.
You fired.
Okay, he's not my lawyer now.
If you plead guilty,
you'll have to sign a waiver of appeal.
Which means you can't change your mind.
That's cool.
Your Honor, the people
have no objections.
In order for me to hear your confession,
you'll have to give the court
the details of your crime.
Me and my brother were
at a party at the frat house.
This white girl was dancing
with me all night..
After we had sex, I was walking her home
and tried to rob her.
She started fighting me off,
so I beat on her.
She wouldn't stop yelling.
So I grabbed her face and squeezed it.
Something snapped
and everything went red.
Is the allocution sufficient, Ms. Novak?
It is, Your Honor.
Very well.
Your plea of guilty is accepted.
Sentencing in two weeks.
Next case.
You're here early.
Someone's gotta close up
the Julie Donovan murder.
Where you been?
We locked up Jadon Odami last night.
He plead guilty at arraignment.
But the other killer's
still on the street.
Jadon said he was solo.
Got a friend at family court.
Snuck a peek at Jadon's juvie record.
Every one of his crimes,
he had a partner.
- Guess who?
- Ezra.
Give that man a gold star.
Look, you got both your little angels
on video dirty dancing with Julie.
Maybe she wasn't in the mood
fro a threesome,
- things got rough, she got dead.
- And we got played.
Count on that.
I'm gonna grab breakfast.
Good luck finding Ezra.
Want to head down to Rikers
and talk with Jadon?
What's the point?
He's doing a life sentence for his brother.
He's not gonna give him up.
Guess I gotta find Ezra myself then.
Now, why would two brothers from Brooklyn
wear hats with the letter "C" on it?
Maybe it's a gang thing.
You know, if you're right,
then Ezra's hanging out with his homies.
That's his only safety net.
Well, what gang?
They're representing with a "C."
If they were crips,
they wouldn't wear anything red.
I got a guy at gang crimes.
He'll hook us up.
They're the new kids on the block.
The "C" hats...
Real popular with the corner Hustlers.
Tell us about them.
Very small, very well organized.
Almost impossible to infiltrate.
Blood in, blood out.
And they mean it.
Yeah, we got a couple of members
we wanna run by you.
Jadon and Ezra Odami.
I read about Jadon in the paper.
That your case?
Yeah, Ezra's in the wind,
and we think he's hanging out
with his fellow gang members.
Corner Hustlers center out
of the Marcy apartments.
That's where their moms lives.
You'll have a good luck getting
anyone in the projects to talk.
These guys run the place.
Hey, I thought the Latin kings
ran the place.
It's a war between the two.
I bet the kings wouldn't mind
ratting out the competition.
MARCY COURTS
BROOKLYN, NEW YORK
FRIDAY, OCTOBER 19
We're sitting ducks.
We're like honey to bees, man.
- Here come the bees.
- Yo, this is Latin king country, son.
What are corner Hustlers
still doing in Marcy...
- Gun!
- I ain't got nothing, man!
I'm just playing, man.
I ain't got nothing, man.
Yo, what's...
What is this?
It's for my art classes, man.
What, you a gang-banging Picasso?
Man, I gotta express myself.
You gonna be expressing yourself
from Rikers, you don't tell us where he is.
Man, he used to hang out here, man.
But I think he got out before the beef.
What beef? / Yo, I could get shot
for talking with you all.
You're lucky we didn't shoot you
for reaching up under your shirt... speak.
Cat names Jimmy Mac started a crew
in Rikers Island about five months ago.
Called the Corner Hustlers.
Yeah, red hat with the "C."
It's their thing.
- What's Jimmy Mac's rep?
- That dude's crazy.
He makes his crew rape girls
before they can roll.
We don't need that kind of heat in Marcy.
So the kings put a price on his head.
Jimmy Mac.
AKA James McDonnell.
Guy's a real scumbag.
His greatest hits
include pimping, assault, and robbery.
He's a repeat offender.
He catches one more felony,
he's going away for life.
McDonnell's the leader
of the Corner Hustlers.
He could've ordered
an initiation murder.
Jadon and Ezra killed Julie
to get into the gang.
Just found McDonnell, he was at Rikers.
What for? / Jumping the turnstile
at the station right by the park
where we found Julie's body.
He posted bail an hour ago.
He should be getting to the queens
borough plaza any minute.
Let's go.
Corrections dump juvies off here
like it's a school bus stop.
Hell of a place to start over.
Heads up.
Here comes the bus.
Yeah, we see it.
There's Jimmy Mac.
We got him.
There's nobody around him.
Pick him up.
Ezra, stop!
Ezra, you're going away for a long time.
Stop.
Hey, stop your truck!
Help.
I can't get out.
Hey, you.
Hey, hey, stop the truck.
- Hey, stop the truck.
- Yo, yo, help.
- Stop the truck.
- I don't wanna die like this.
- Yo.
- Yo, help.
Yo.
Hey, stop the truck.
- Let me out.
- Hey, somebody's in there.
- Where's my brother?
- We ask the questions, punk.
- Just tell me Jadon's all right.
- I said no questions.
Don't you understand no means no?
Maybe not, him and his brother did rape
and murder Julie Donovan.
- I had nothing to do with that.
- You just a wannbe cop-killer, huh?
You got things all wrong.
Hey, I don't care
how good your grades were.
Or how tough your life was.
You threw it all away
when you fired on us.
- I wasn't shooting at you.
- Oh, really?
Then who were you trying to kill?
J-Mac.
I swear, I wasn't trying
to hurt anyone else.
- Just him.
- Why?
Doesn't matter.
Get your head up,
we're not done with you.
Boy's the leader of your gang,
why would you wanna whack him?
Jadon and me only joined Corner Hustlers
in Rikers for protection from other gangs.
J-Mac's from the same project,
so we figured he'd look out for us.
Yeah, a little cat like you
must've needed protection.
What, McDonnell take care of you?
Yeah. Till me and Jadon got
into Island Academy and started doing well.
We got scholarships to college, and
McDonnell told us to sell drugs on campus.
- So you're a drug dealer too.
- We never did it.
Jadon told him to get lost.
McDonnell went crazy, and said the only way
we're leaving the gang was in a body bag.
Blood in and blood out.
You were gonna kill McDonnell
to get out of the gang.
I was gonna kill him cause he set
my brother up for that girl's murder.
Then why was Julie's blood
on your brother's baseball cap?
I don't know.
May...maybe she wore his hat home
from the party.
You gotta believe me.
J-Mac killed Julie.
If J-Mac's the killer, I suppose
we gotta led Jadon go.
Really?
For a smart kid,
you're really stupid.
Ezra, Jadon confessed.
- That's great work, guys.
- Thanks Cap.
Get your fives typed and over to Novak
so she can start prepping for trial.
I don't think those boys had anything
to do with Julie Donovan's murder.
I swear I didn't see him smoking crack.
I think the real killer died
in that garbage truck today.
One brother confessed and the other one
tried to shoot you.
What more do you want?
Jadon and Ezra had too much to lose
by killing that girl.
Then why would McDonnell
wanna frame them?
Because he's a psychopath.
He was pissed that the Odami boys
were leaving the gang
and making something of themselves.
Pin a murder on them?
They're right back in the gutter.
I'm sure that's what the defense
is gonna argue,
but we work for the prosecution.
- And if they're innocent?
- That's for the jury to decide.
- That's not good enough for me.
- Let it go, Chester.
This case is closed.
I know you're an insomniac,
but you ought to go home.
Why are you here this late?
Paperwork for trial.
You gotta watch yourself.
If you get too obsessed with these cases,
you'll lose more than sleep.
- Like what?
- Family.
What, are you trying to bust
my chops again?
I'm dead serious.
This job nearly cost me mine.
Well, I don't have to worry about that.
No family?
Or too many families.
Depending on the day.
You a foster kid?
You need any help?
You wanna risk the Captain
getting pissed at you?
Wouldn't be the first time.
All right.
In my gut, these boys are innocent.
But I don't know how to prove it.
All right. Well...
Fresh pair of eyes never hurt.
Stop it.
What was that burst of light?
Go back.
It's a camera flash.
She look pregnant to you?
Yeah.
What's she doing at a frat party?
Taking pictures of Julie?
I never seen her before.
Take a good look at her.
I got no idea who she is.
I'm trying to help you.
Come on, look at it.
Who is this, Jadon?
Hey, watch yourself.
I'm looking at life, so I'm not worried.
About taking yours.
You might now know this,
but I'm on your side.
Look, dude.
My moms, the state, the schools...
They all failed me and my brother.
I got about this much left of me,
and I'm gonna use it to do this time,
so just leave me alone.
I came up through the foster system.
As soon as I was old enough,
I took the police exam.
I don't think I'd pass the background check.
When I was in the Academy,
my cousin and I went out drinking.
And we got in a fight.
One guy was hurt bad.
My cousin told me to take off.
He knew if I got arrested,
I'd get kicked off the job.
What's this bedtime story
gotta do with me?
He took the collar for me,
so I could have a shot.
You did the same thing for your brother.
And if I did,
why would I give him up to you?
Because Ezra didn't do it.
It was McDonnell, Jadon.
He set you up.
I wanna see Ezra.
Who beat you up?
Doesn't matter.
I can handle it.
No, you can't!
Look, why is he here?
I said I did it,
get him out of here.
I know you didn't... dude,
why you saying you did? / Shut up.
How could you think I did it?
Because... I... I came back to the room
two hours later, and you weren't there.
When the cops got my DNA
off the hat Julie took,
I figured it was a lucky break.
Better me than you.
So I confessed.
Why?
Every time I passed that flag
in the living room,
and listen to those rich kids bitch
about their perfect lives,
I wanted to start knocking dudes out.
Maybe it's better I'm locked up
before I do something I regret.
You don't belong in prison.
Who is this?
Look, I wasn't lying, I don't know her.
You confessed to murder.
You're getting sentenced tomorrow.
She may be able to finger McDonnell.
If we don't find her tonight,
you're going down for life.
I think I've seen her around Marcy.
What's her name?
No idea.
We gotta find somebody in
the projects who can ID her.
I think I know someone
who'll talk to us.
APARTMENT OF JANELLE ODAMI
479 MARCY AVENUE BROOKLYN, NEW YORK
TUESDAY, OCTOBER 30
Janelle, open up.
It's 2:00pm Tuesday afternoon.
I didn't mean to interrupt
your beauty sleep.
I been working nights.
- We know.
- Cleaning offices.
By the Grace of God
and Narcotics anonymous,
I got nine days clean and sober.
Well, that's good.
Do you know her?
I don't know nothing,
I ain't seen nothing.
So I can't tell you nothing.
What kind of piece of trash mother lets
her kids get taken away over and over again,
then when she finally gets a chance
to help them, she turns her back?
Don't you dare talk to me like you know
what I've been through.
Every time children's services
snatched my boys,
it took all I had not to kill myself
the second the door shut behind them.
If you really care about your boys,
you'll tell us who this girl is.
Jadon's in for murder.
Ezra's being charged
for attempted murder of a cop.
Tell us who this girl is, right now,
or your boys will never see daylight again.
You stole the first half of their lives,
give them back the rest.
When I get 90 days clean and sober,
I'm gonna surprise Jadon and Ezra
and take them to Red Lobster.
Her name is Latrice Munez.
She lives in the building
right behind this one.
Unit 412.
Yeah, I'm Jimmy Mac's bottom bitch.
McDonnell was pimping you out
as his number one girl
with what you're carrying?
You're damn right.
Shoot, I still got it.
Tell us about Julie.
She thought being a ho was mad fun.
Like being one of them rap video hos,
or something like that.
How'd you meet up with
a white girl from Long island?
At the fights.
She got off watching dudes
pounding each other.
So I helped J-Mac turn her out.
Why did you take a picture
of her at the frat party?
McDonnell wanted photos of her
having sex with Jadon and Ezra.
For proof he wasn't getting Georgia'd.
Look at you throwing around gang, Papi.
Acting like you know your thing.
Little girl, I was through with it
before you knew what to do with it.
Enlighten me.
A pimp has sex with a new girl
before she actually turns a trick,
it's called getting Georgia'd.
It's like the pimp got played.
McDonnell wanted to make sure
that Julie did what he said.
So he made me take the pictures.
I picked up Julie at her place.
This was when we was leaving
for the party.
She was really feeling Ezra too.
She was all up on him that night.
She was supposed to do both brothers,
and then say that they raped her.
J-Mac was gonna blackmail them
for their tuition checks.
Why'd he beat her?
After she had sex with Ezra,
we bounced.
Julie told J-Mac that she wasn't gonna say
that they raped her.
He just started beating on her like some
type of animal, or something, you know?
I never seen him like that before.
So I just took the pictures.
Why?
Insurance.
So he'd never come at me like that.
Never.
Get Jadon down to court,
and I'll have him withdraw his plea.
What about Ezra?
I'll drop the attempted murder charge
because he wasn't shooting at you.
But there's nothing I can do
about the gun possession.
About the gun...
It got lost in transport from the scene.
Without the evidence,
I'll have to drop the gun charge too.
Just make sure they're both
in court at the same time.
Stuff happens.
Hey.
Thanks again.
Hey, no problem.
I talked to the dean,
you guys are back in school.
So that's the big surprise?
No.
I have another one.
Hey, Fin. Where the hell are you?
We've been waiting.
I'll tell them.
Hey, come on, man.
You gonna tell us what
the surprise is, or what?
I'm taking you guys to Red Lobster.
Come on.