In the criminal justice system,
sexually-based offenses
are considered especially heinous.
In New York City,
the dedicated detectives who investigate
these vicious felonies are members
of an elite squad known
as The Special Victims Unit.
These are their stories.
32-year-old white female.
Blunt force trauma.
Victim's missing vehicle
pointed to a carjacking.
You locate her vehicle?
A burned-out hull
in the next county.
Did the pathologist uncover
distal skull fractures?
Yes, he did.
The scene's staged.
Was there evidence
of sexual assault?
Nothing probative.
Was she in a relationship?
A fiance.
We looked at him.
I'd take another look.
A lot of overkill for a robbery.
The rage is personal.
Were the signs of lividity consistent
with body position?
You get a chance to look
at those photos I sent you?
There are 82 members
who would be glad to help.
Present to the group.
Take advantage of our expertise.
Vidocq's swamped.
There isn't an open slot for a year.
Chester, stop being so stubborn.
Ten years is a long time
to hold on to a case.
I'm asking you, Pen.
Your victim was dumped.
Sort through everything.
Determine what belongs and what doesn't.
If he made mistakes,
I didn't find any. / Not yet.
- Also re-interview any witnesses.
- There weren't any.
That's not exactly true.
There was one.
- What are you selling, Brett?
- Criminal defense.
Yeah, hard to imagine.
You've worked sex crimes
longer than most,
and you're still passionate.
We need you.
Yeah, well, it's harder to care
when your clients are guilty.
Ours are accused of SEC violations,
not diddling some four-year-old
on a playground.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
No more late-night calls.
No more rape victims and dead kids.
How do you sleep at night?
I don't.
Captain, it was a cop shooting.
Everyone's using their cell phones.
How did the press get wind?
They followed the line of brass
out of one PP.
So we have one dead cop
and one wounded. Why are we here?
Because I fought for it.
- Control this crime scene.
- Who's our victim?
Precinct Detective Edward Kralik.
- Any suspects?
- One.
You are not allowed to question him,
nothing searched without a warrant,
and you keep me on speed dial.
Who the hell is he?
Detective Chester Lake.
(kylee322@nate.com)
(ashaa@nate.com)
(nanjidoo@nate.com)
Law & Order SVU
9x19.Cold
번역수정
한상희(fithelestre@nate.com)
한글교정
임재영(dreamimage@nate.com)
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON NBC:  2008/05/13
- I see the circus is in town.
- What do you expect?
When cops shoot each other,
clowns come out. It's entertainment.
What's got him riled?
Guilty by association.
I count at least five GSWs.
He's officially dead. Can I take him?
Forensics hasn't finished mapping.
Let me get you an ETA.
Don't move! / Who the hell you think
you're talking to, Detective?
You... you're stepping
in my blood evidence, Inspector.
If you're finished,
Warner wants the body.
We're almost done.
We're freezing the scene in time.
- Virtual crime scene.
- It's called "scanstation 2."
I don't know how we lived without it.
You'll be able to look
from any angle you want.
The lasers are capturing
every detail in 3-D.
It can show us where
each other shooter was standing.
Can it tell us who pulled
the trigger first?
No, only Lake can do that.
Wish we could ask him.
No harm in checking on his condition.
MERCY GENERAL HOSPITAL
365 WEST 32ND STREET
TUESDAY, MARCH 18
Hey, how you feelings?
I took through and thorough
in the arm and the leg. I'll live.
Feel up to talking?
No.
Doesn't look good, Chester.
You need to give us your statement.
No, I don't.
- This isn't going away.
- I don't expect it to.
But I know you won't question me,
at least not for the next 48 hours.
- You're invoking.
- Section 118-09,
no superior investigating
officer can talk to me for two days.
It's called coerced testimony.
You go down this road,
there's no coming back.
What's this about?
Give us something.
Are you interrogating me, Detective?
No.
I'm watching you drown.
We can't clear Lake
without his statement.
If it was justified,
why not just say so?
He invoked, and his silence
proves nothing.
What do we have on Edward Kralik?
Well, he came up through the ranks.
Unspectacular, but solid patrol officer.
Promoted to Detective.
He works out of the one-four.
According to witnesses, Lake and Kralik
were going at it outside his precinct.
How do they know each other?
Came up through
the same Brooklyn house.
Any history of beefs between them?
- None that we found.
- Then dig deeper.
A verbal argument between two cops
doesn't escalate to murder
without some damn good reason why.
You find anything
at Lake's apartment?
Ticket stub for a train
from Philly dated yesterday.
- What was he doing there?
- Good question.
We dumped Lake's phone.
From the roaming charges,
he's been in Philadelphia
at the same time every month.
- Have any idea why?
- I said I don't know.
What do you mean?
You're his partner.
Do you know everything about Olivia?
No, but I'd notice
if she disappeared once a month.
We'll find out. I left messages
with the Philly numbers.
- I'm expecting callbacks.
- So we'll follow the evidence.
Since Lake's not talking, maybe we can
reconstruct what happened in that lot.
Thought you fell in.
I'm not used to sitting to take a leak.
That's the price of turning a vacant lot,
into OK Corral.
You know you shouldn't be here, Fin.
Neither should you,
but here we are.
I'm all ears.
I got nothing to say.
Well, my partner would never shoot anyone
except in self defense.
You don't know me, Fin.
And you never made any effort until now.
All you had to do
was pick up the damn phone.
I would've backed your play.
I had it covered. / Yeah, those holes
in your body say different.
What's going on in Philly?
Really good cheese steaks.
You got us running blind, man.
We're trying to save your ass.
If you don't walk me through this,
you're going upstate.
I hope you know what you're doing.
OFFICE OF THE MEDICAL EXAMINER
TUESDAY, MARCH 18
I'm ruling Detective Kralik's
death a homicide.
Five gunshot wounds.
One nine-millimeter projectile
hit the left lung and pierced the heart.
The second lodged in the victim's spine.
Either one could've killed him.
Center mass hits
from a right-handed shooter.
Problem is the non-fatal shots
came from behind,
penetrating the upper-right thigh,
right buttock, and upper back.
You think Kralik was running away
and Lake shot him in the back?
Dropped him in his tracks,
finished him off with two to the chest.
It's possible.
There were shell casings
all over the crime scene.
They had to be crouching and rotating.
Would that explain the back wounds?
It's a reach.
What does Lake say happened?
Nothing, which is why
we're spinning our wheels.
Did ballistics test-fire Lake's gun?
All five shots came from his glock.
They're checking both guns
for ejection patterns,
and matching trajectory
to wound tracks.
Maybe that'll give you some answers.
Or maybe we should start accepting
that Lake murdered Ed Kralik.
You find anything on Lake's
movements? / Not yet.
What's got your undivided attention?
It's a cold case file
I found in Lake's desk.
One of ours? / No, this is
from Brooklyn, ten years ago.
He was still working on it.
There's recent notes. He said he wanted
to re-interview the first responders.
How's that connect to the shooting?
Ed Kralik was one of them.
The notes mention
what they talked about?
- I don't think they got that far.
- Excuse me.
- I'm looking for Detective Munch.
- Right there.
- May I help you?
- I'm Penelope Fielding.
You left messages on my voicemail,
so I caught the first train in from Philly.
Is Chester all right?
He's stable.
How do you know him?
What hospital is he in?
Uh, he's not seeing anyone right now.
What's your connection to Lake?
We belong to a group called
The Vidocq Society based in Philadelphia.
Once a month, we hear cold case
presentations from law enforcement,
and redirect focus on
unsolved homicides.
Explains the frequent trips out of town.
Okay, why would a cop
spend his free time
trying to solve other people's cold cases?
Freedom.
We work without politics or bosses.
Olivia, Elliot... my office.
You think you could manage
to read Detective Lake his rights?
I miss something? / I specifically
told you not to question him.
He's under the 48-hour rule
and shielded from interrogation.
Don't worry.
He didn't say anything.
Yeah, and lucky for you.
Because if he talked,
it would've been inadmissible
and under immunity.
Okay, so how are we
supposed to put this down
when most crimes are solved
within the first 48?
You know what?
That's not my problem.
So you either follow orders,
or just stay out of the way.
This isn't my call.
Lake killed a cop in what appears
to be an unprovoked shooting.
So why not wait for the rest
of the evidence to get processed?
What is the rush?
If it were anybody else,
he's already be in shackles,
so just do your job.
He's running.
He hasn't been gone long.
IV's still pretty full.
I'll get hospital security
to help with the search.
I'll call Casey, get a subpoena
to dump Tutuola's phone.
You think Fin warned him?
Who else would've told Lake
we were coming?
Searched the hospital from the ground up.
Units are parked outside Lake's home.
Dumping my phones
was a bitch move, Stabler.
Yeah, I called him.
I didn't think he'd run.
- You should've stayed out of it.
- Take it easy. / He's my partner.
Who you helped evade arrest.
Dial it down
or you're both going on report.
Lake is not our problem anymore.
The fugitive apprehension team
will take it from here.
All those guys do is workout
and shoot guns. They're gonna kill Lake.
Well, that's not how
FAT works, Detective.
Kralik's got a lot of friends on the street
that'd like to see Lake dead.
You gotta at least let me look.
Where you gonna start?
You don't even know the guy.
I know he didn't do it.
Three bullet holes in
the victim's back say different.
You ever think the force
behind the first two spun Kralik?
We're trained to keep firing
till the subject is down.
And you're assuming
that the fatal shots came first.
Have ballistics run both scenarios,
see which one fits.
- You check out Penelope Fielding?
- She's legit.
She ran the regional lab in Richmond,
consults at Quantico,
and volunteers on Vidocq.
Well, get her statement
and show her the door.
Lake's only connection
to Kralik is a cold case.
- Maybe she can help.
- I know all about the Vidocq society.
So does the Brass, and they don't want
them anywhere near this.
They've solved a lot of open homicides.
Easy to do when you pick and choose.
Yeah, but Lake has held on
to this case for ten years.
He must've talked to her about it.
Limited access only,
then I want her gone.
Undocumented female,
Alisa Hernandez, 14.
Found raped and strangled
in a vacant lot ten years ago.
Last seen leaving school with
her best friend Cecelia Cruz.
When questioned, the girl said
they split up and didn't see anything.
Cecelia was lying.
Her statement's full of elliptical pauses,
which indicated invention.
Well, she was scared.
The victim was in the country illegally.
A good bet is that
her best friend was too.
Lying makes sense when
you're running from immigration.
I also suggested he re-examine
the crime scene
for what should be there
and what shouldn't.
Like our dead cop.
He responded to the call even though
it was outside his patrol sector.
- That's suggestive.
- Why?
When I was in uniform,
I went to a lot of calls that weren't mine.
Alisa's killer used a condom
and tried to wipe the body down.
- A lot of rapists do.
- They didn't ten years ago.
DNA was just starting
to get convictions.
But a cop would have
forensic knowledge. Like Kralik.
We know Lake confronted Kralik.
Phone dumps show he got a call
to his cell from a payphone
a 1/2 hour before the shooting started.
If Lake knew the guy was a killer,
he wouldn't have met him
in such an isolated spot.
Not if he thought this was finally
his chance to get the truth.
So we run Alisa's rape kit.
If Kralik's our guy,
Lake's off the hook.
EVIDENCE WAREHOUSE
WEDNESDAY, MARCH 19
I thought you got federal money
to get rape kits into CODIS.
It was 12 million bucks.
We had 20,000 kits.
You do the math.
Here it is.
"Hernandez, Alisa.
Homicide, 11-10-97."
- What happened to it?
- Evidence storage got flooded.
A couple of refrigeration units
got burned out.
I told all this to the other two dicks.
- Tell me you got names.
- Detective Lake.
Said he wanted it pulled
and sent to the lab,
but you can't fast-track a specimen
without command approval.
- Who's the other Detective?
- Kralik.
Wanted to confirm the request was made.
Captain Cragen of Manhattan SVU
wants this DNA sample rushed,
so I'm gonna take it in myself.
I was getting the cold shoulder
in your precinct, so thanks for coming.
Bosses think you'll make us look bad.
If you get me the 3-D scan
and the ballistic measurements,
I can recreate the most likely
scenario for what happened in that lot.
Our people can do that.
How long will it take them?
How many cases do they have
that are just as pressing as this one?
- There is no other case.
- That's what you'd like to believe.
I ran a lab. The world doesn't stop
because you want it to.
I can't help you, Pen.
Proving Kralik's a rapist
isn't gonna be enough to clear Chester.
I know he didn't shoot first.
- Has there been any word?
- Nothing.
Lake got shot twice.
He should be easy to find.
- He's a resourceful guy.
- You should know.
You seem pretty angry.
Yeah, before today if anybody had asked
if Lake was involved,
I would've said no,
and I would've been wrong.
You think he doesn't trust you.
When in fact he's been trying
to earn your respect.
He said you were a hard person
to know. / Like he's easy.
You have any idea
where we can find him?
You could try his ex-partner,
Wesley Meadows.
They kept in touch.
I haven't heard from Lake
in six months.
Same damn conversation,
The Hernandez murder.
- He was obsessed about it?
- Haunted.
His first case.
Poor kid gets yoked midday
and nobody sees nothing.
What about her best friend,
Cecelia Cruz?
Lying through her teeth.
Two girls walk home from school every day
except the day one gets done?
- Sell me a bridge.
- You try to re-interview Cecelia?
Lake tried, but her family skipped.
Can't say I blame her.
Always thought she was a victim too.
- You think Cecelia was raped?
- We saw some bruises,
couldn't look us in the eye,
and couldn't stand to be touched.
My gut was screaming.
Remember seeing officer
Edward Kralik at the scene?
- That the guy Lake popped?
- Yeah.
Sorry, ten years is a lifetime ago.
All I remember was hitting the wall.
Since most of the neighborhood
is illegal, nobody talked.
Hernandez family still around?
No.
But I heard they got amnesty,
so you might be able
to track them down through tax rolls.
DARRATY'S FRUIT PACKING
733 HUNTS POINT AVENUE
BRONX, NEW YORK
THURSDAY, MARCH 20
Why are you bringing Alisa up again?
I'm trying to move on,
live with it somehow.
We're very sorry,
but there's new evidence
that may tell us what happened
to your daughter.
I know what happened.
She got murdered in a country
that I told my family was safe.
I convinced them that
this was a great future for all of us.
Now I'm here all alone.
Where is your family, Mr. Hernandez?
They went back to El Salvador.
I couldn't leave.
Somebody should stay with Alisa,
visit her grave, remember her.
Detective Lake never forgot.
He's been working on the case
for ten years.
- It didn't help him solve it.
- Until now.
- You found her killer?
- We believe so.
We think Cecelia Cruz
witnessed the attack.
We need to talk to her.
No, you're wrong.
She would've told me
if she knew anything.
She was 14 years old.
A scared little girl
who was in a lot of trouble.
She had no place to turn.
How doesn't someone lie
about murder?
Because she was raped too.
Dios Mio.
Why didn't Lake tell me this
when he called?
- When was that?
- Last night.
He wanted to talk to Cecelia,
but he didn't say why.
Where is she?
She works as a seamstress
for a designer downtown.
STREBOR CLOTHING DESIGNS
144 WEST 28TH STREET
THURSDAY, MARCH 20
What the hell's going on here,
three cops in two days?
So I was annoyed
when Cecelia said she had to leave,
but then the cop explained
it was about a rape.
Is this the guy?
Yeah, he was in pretty bad shape too.
Started bleeding on the floor.
Cecelia had to help him out,
said she was taking him to a hospital.
How long ago?
1:00 am ... like I said,
we're on a deadline.
Guy's bleeding out,
she doesn’t call the cops.
What is Lake doing
involving a civilian?
City-wide alert out.
She's now his hostage.
We notified ESU that Lake
could have a civilian with him.
It's hard to believe
he'd be so reckless.
- Any leads on his whereabouts?
- The tip lines are going crazy.
He could be long gone
or anywhere in the city.
Not if he's bleeding out.
What about hospitals or walk-in clinics?
No one matching Lake's description
has been admitted or treated.
News reports are saying Lake
took a hostage. Who gave them that?
How about your partner after he took
Cecelia Cruz with a warrant on his ass?
And with Kralik dead,
it just doesn't make sense.
Lake had to have a good reason.
For putting a witness in harm's way?
I'm open to suggestions.
How about a third shooter?
31 shots were fired in that lot.
Same brand of ammunition,
all NYPD issue.
10 came from Lake's gun
and Kralik emptied
his 15-round clip.
Remaining six bullets
came from an unknown source.
Lake fires seven bullets
into Kralik's direction.
Three shots standing
and four shots crouching.
Five direct hits.
The other two were found in a wall.
The first two hits spun him,
and based on his wound tracks,
Kralik was already falling to the ground
when the last three bullets
entered his body.
That proves Lake didn't shoot
him in the back.
Lake then rotates 30 degrees
and fires at what appears to be a void.
You find any shell casings
in the void area? / No.
The third guy policed his brass.
Did the bullets that hit Lake
match Kralik's gun?
The third shooter fired
six shots at Lake.
Two plugged him.
The other four were found at the scene.
- That gun in the system?
- Sorry.
If it's a cop,
I'm thinking drop gun.
That'd be my guess.
Looks like Lake took
Cecelia Cruz to protect her.
Another dirty cop means
somebody close to Kralik 10 years ago.
He have a partner in Brooklyn?
Sean Lassiter.
Died on the line last year.
We should talk to Kralik's widow,
see who his friends are now.
Tread easy.
Everybody's already heated enough.
KRALIK RESIDENCE
68 REMSEN STREET
BROOKLYN, NEW YOTK
FRIDAY, MARCH 21
- What do you want?
- Let them in, Bill.
Mrs. Kralik, I'm Detective Stabler.
This is my partner, Detective Benson.
Very sorry for your loss.
- Please sit down.
- Thank you.
Elliot Stabler.
Bill Jensen.
That's Tom Crane, Dave Foster.
Find that bastard Lake yet?
It's not their job to find him,
it's mine.
You're with the fugitive
apprehension team?
My unit usually brings them in
without incident, unless they fight.
I know he's a friend of yours.
- So I just want to make that clear.
- Guy's a hump.
Look, I want to find out
what happened that night, don't you?
No. Word is he busted his stitches.
We wait it out,
maybe he'll bleed to death.
Yeah, I told you that puts us behind...
- So what? Who...
- Stop it.
All of you.
That is not what I want.
I need to understand
why he killed my husband.
Why did he do it?
We're working on it.
Mrs. Kralik, was there somebody
that your husband was close to?
Are you looking at us?
- Why?
- Did you know him in Brooklyn?
What does that got to do with anything?
If you're looking for a way
to justify murder, you can leave right now.
Get out.
That woman has no idea
who she was married to.
If this comes out,
it will kill her.
Cops seemed pretty riled.
- So let's check them out.
- And then what do we do?
Dig up some dirt but hope we find a gun
that matches the slugs from the vacant lot?
All Lake had to do was ID the shooter.
You can't be sure that he saw him.
It was dark out,
there were bullets flying.
- What is your problem?
- He didn't trust us.
And maybe for good reason.
Look, all the evidence pointed
to his guilty.
Which means that we should've
taken a hard look at Lake, not Fin.
Oh, so I shouldn't have dumped
his phones?
Fin's a straight shooter, Elliot.
All you had to do was ask him.
I think you need to make this right.
Nothing on Jensen, Crane, and Foster.
They all three came from Brooklyn.
I'm waiting on their jackets.
- How long have they known Kralik?
- Jensen for Ten years.
Crane and Foster worked his precinct.
They transferred out last year.
Well, maybe we should be looking
at the academy roles,
see who Kralik was close to.
That was the lab. They made
a preliminary DNA match to Kralik.
They found his blood underneath
the victim's fingernails.
She fought back.
Maybe that's why he killed her.
Well, they found a second semen sample,
but it was only a partial profile.
It's too degraded.
The guy's gonna skate.
We can still get him on the attempted
murder of a police officer.
That's a parole sentence, Munch.
Well it won't matter
unless we find out who he is.
ESU has Lake pinned
in an abandoned building.
Is the subject armed?
I repeat, is the subject armed?
Confirmed.
Suspect is armed.
Hold your position.
Manhattan SVU, Lieutenant.
How'd you find him?
BOLO on the female.
Cashier noticed when she bought
too many medical supplies.
The FAT pinpointed their location,
but with the hostage,
it's our OP now.
- Hey. Get your ass back here.
- Hold on, hold on, hold on.
That's Detective Lake's partner.
I don't give a damn
if it's his long lost brother...
Want this take-down to go blood-free?
You let him work.
Let him go.
You'd shoot me in the back?
If I have to.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Take it easy. It's my partner.
He's not gonna use that gun.
Only cause I'm low on ammo.
Okay, hand it over and let's go.
Looking forward to the perp walk?
Somebody's gotta take credit.
Might as well be me.
- Yeah, they're getting into position.
- And you know what's next.
They're gonna throw in a few flash bangs
and we'll both be blind and deaf.
Whatever happened to
hostage negotiation?
Listen, she brought you those bandages.
That makes her an accomplice
to the felony skip.
You see where I'm going?
You want to put bracelets on my wrists.
I'd rather do that
before someone gets hurt.
I'm already hurt.
I'm not going into custody
so I can be an easier target.
Lake, we followed your breadcrumbs.
We know Kralik is a rapist,
and we can prove it.
Did you see the hump that shot you?
Didn't get a good look.
I was just trying to fight for my life.
How'd you get lured?
I got a call from a guy named Bill Jensen.
He said he had some information.
Then when I showed up,
the son of a bitch just opened fire.
I don't know his name,
but I'll never forget his face.
He raped me.
Are you ready to say that in court?
I'll tell whoever will listen.
Captain, Kralik's shadow
during his academy days was Thomas Crane.
- Why him?
- Well, I pulled his jacket.
Excessive force, sexual abuse,
intimidation complaints.
Why does this bastard
still have his tin?
Well, all his victims
had sheets and recanted.
CCRB cleared him.
What's his present assignment?
The Fugitive Apprehension Team.
Son of a bitch.
Squeeze that trigger,
you'll be dead before the slug
leaves the pipe.
Alisa and I got caught
in the middle of a fight
on our way home from school.
That's when the police came
to break it up.
What happened next?
Two cops, told us they would
give us a ride home,
so we got into the back seat.
They took turns raping us.
If felt like it went on forever.
What happened to Alisa Hernandez?
She fought back.
scratching and clawing.
He punched her, but...
she wouldn't stop screaming,
so he put his hands
around her throat and squeezed.
Is one of the men who lured you
and then brutally raped you in this room?
Yes.
- Thomas Crane.
- Why didn't they kill you too?
I begged for my life,
promised never to tell.
He was angry
that officer Kralik lost control.
When they started fighting,
I ran away.
Thank you.
Nothing further.
When did you become
a US citizen, Miss Cruz?
- Objection. Irrelevant.
- Witness veracity, Your Honor.
- Answer the question.
- You don't understand.
We didn't have the money
for amnesty then,
but I've been trying ever since.
In other words,
you're here illegally.
You went to school here,
you saw doctors here,
made money here,
but you paid no taxes here.
Is there a question, or is counsel
just going to pontificate?
Is the DA's office
helping you with immigration
in exchange for your testimony?
Objection.
Withdrawn.
Nothing further.
The jury's looking at my witness
like she did something wrong.
People feel strongly
about immigration on both sides.
That's why your forensic testimony
needs to be solid.
Is this partial profile enough
to say he's a match?
Yes, but it leaves you
wide open on rebuttal.
Okay, why?
All human cells except
platelets have 13 loci.
The semen the lab tested
presented only nine,
which means it was
significantly degraded.
I'll need probabilities
as to the DNA match for Crane.
I can't give them with what we have.
Okay, without it, he walks.
Thomas Crane raped
and murdered a young girl,
and we gave him the badge
to hide behind while he did it.
I know what you want me to say,
but the science doesn't support it.
When the defense gets these lab reports,
they might have enough
for reasonable doubt.
- Can you live with that?
- If I have to.
Because I sure as hell
won't risk my reputation
for a verdict we didn't earn.
TRIAL PART 46
THURSDAY, MAY 8
We found blood and skin
under the victim's nails.
As you can see from the overlay,
13 loci match.
Is there any doubt the DNA belongs
to Detective Edward Kralik?
None.
The second sample found was semen.
The lab took a buccal swab
from Thomas Crane
and compared it with swabs
from the victim Alisa Hernandez.
Here, nine loci match.
although it's a partial profile,
in my opinion, it belongs to the defendant.
Thank you, doctor.
Nothing further.
I have no questions.
I interviewed Detective Kralik
about his presence at the crime scene.
He said he couldn't remember,
and then he got hostile.
Didn't you have a very loud
and public brawl with the deceased?
He threw a punch after I collected
the cigarette butt he tossed.
Why did you do that?
Well, I thought he was guilty
of rape and murder.
I wanted to compare
his DNA to the evidence.
So what happened next?
Well, I called in to get the rape kit
pulled from storage and sent to the lab,
but I got lured and then ambushed by
two shooters before I could have it done.
How were you lured?
Well, I got a call from a cop
saying he had information
about the Hernandez murder.
He called himself Jensen,
But I IDed the caller as Thomas Crane
in a voice print line-up.
And you're sure that the second shooter
was the defendant, Thomas Crane?
Positive.
Nothing further.
Two shooters.
You must be a hard man to kill.
Well, I was lucky.
Did you find the gun matching the bullets
at the crime scene in my client's possession?
It's easy to toss a gun in the city.
Yes or no.
Not yet, no.
You call the lab to move the evidence.
What were you told by the desk officer?
That I needed a boss to request it.
Was that all you were told?
I don't recall.
You weren't told that the evidence was
too degraded and contaminated for testing?
No. / Objection. Your Honor, I call
for an immediate mistrial.
There's a serious cover-up
going on here,
and I have proof
that this witness perjured himself,
and the prosecution violated Brady.
Your Honor, that's ridiculous.
no one lied.
Counsel is accusing my office of conspiracy
in front of the jury just to score points.
Enough!
In my chambers now.
DNA is the rock on which
the people built their case.
They don't have a credible witness.
Cecelia Cruz's immigrant status has
nothing to do with her eyewitness testimony.
And yet they've placed
more emphasis on biological evidence,
which I discovered was compromised.
Is that true, Miss Novak?
No, the evidence was tested
by lab protocol.
Then where are the reports?
Because I don't have them.
Incomplete.
They're not finished.
And the dog ate my homework.
I will turn everything over
as soon as it is done.
See that you do.
- And the conspiracy?
- Detective Lake perjured himself.
He was told that the sample
was too degraded for testing
- by the evidence intake officer.
- Who's not a DNA expert.
If it's so degraded,
how did we find two separate profiles?
I think you want to win so badly you'd
plant the evidence and frame my client.
Oh, the OJ defense.
That's original. Good for you.
Knock it off.
I grant the missing lab reports
are suspicious,
but you can't accuse sworn officers
without hard evidence.
The prosecution tried to sandbag
the defense, Your Honor.
And you'll have those reports
by close of business today...
Or Miss Novak will be in contempt.
- Anything else?
- Yes.
Just to show that I play by the rules,
I'm issuing a subpoena for Penelope Fielding
as a witness for the defense.
TRIAL PART 46
FRIDAY, MAY 9
Ms. Fielding, can you list
your credentials for the jury?
I hold a masters in population genetics
and statistics.
I ran a state crime lab,
and I work with law enforcement.
When you ran the lab,
which departments reported to you?
Fingerprints, ballistics,
blood spatter, trace and DNA.
What's your opinion
on partial DNA profiles?
They can be an invaluable
investigative tool.
Really?
A suspect list can be narrowed
of even cleared using partial profiles.
"A partial profile is outside
all scientific standards
and should be viewed
skeptically if at all."
Who wrote that,
Ms. Fielding?
I did.
An article published
in a journal of applied sciences
criticizing multiplex PCR
and, I quote,
"The disturbing trend
of using partial profiles
in the criminal justice system."
In your expert opinion,
Ms. Fielding,
does the DNA found on Alisa Hernandez
match my client, Thomas Crane?
- I can't answer that.
- Why not?
The sample is the equivalent
of less than a single human cell.
So I can't say with any certainty
that it matches the defendant.
Nothing further.
- Have you reached a verdict?
- No, Your Honor. We're deadlocked.
Your Honor, can we poll the jury?
Madam foreman, how do you find?
Guilty.
Not guilty.
- No, Hector.
- Let go of her.
Hey, what's going on here?
US immigration enforcement, ma'am.
Please step back.
- Where are you going with my witness?
- I can't tell you that.
You'll have to take it up
with a federal judge in dispensation.
I'm sorry I never told you
about Alisa, Mr. Hernandez.
Please believe me.
I'm sorry.
Where are you taking me?
Don't do anything stupid, Hector.
We can't win, can we?
No, I promise I will re-file the charges
and I will try him again.
Hey, Fin, we're heading out for a drink.
You wanna join us?
No, somebody needs to check on Lake,
he's not answering his phone.
Look, the situation got a little heated
and I want to say I'm sorry about that.
You're a bulldog, Stabler.
Quick to assume,
slow to admit when you're wrong.
Makes for a good cop,
but a lousy human being...
- Fin, hear him out.
- Stay out of it, Liv.
That being said,
I know what it cost you.
- Appreciate that.
- I'm not done.
The problem is you will still be
the same rat bastard tomorrow,
and nothing you say
will ever change that.
What's that?
Fin's transfer request.
CHAMBERS OF
JUDGE ELIZABETH DONNELLY
FRIDAY, MAY 9
You wanted to see me,
judge Donnelly?
Yes, the, um...
The DA is declining to re-file charges
against Thomas Crane.
He raped and murdered Alisa Hernandez
and he gets to keep his badge?
Because of your actions, counselor.
With all due respect, ma'am,
this doesn't concern you.
It does now.
I'm being called before the bar.
At my insistence.
Why?
Because you lost perspective.
And because I sit
on the peer review board,
and I cannot allow you
to commit a Brady violation
and lie to the court
without consequence.
The reports weren't finished, Your Honor.
I sent them back.
You lied to Petrovsky,
and now you are lying to me.
The lab reports
were dated and stamped.
We are civil servants, Casey.
No one is falling
on their sword for you.
What I want to know... is why.
Because the bad guys can't always win.
And he deserved to pay.
And so do you.
How much trouble am I in?
Censure.
Possible suspension.
For how long?
A year.
Maybe more.
What should I do?
Something else.
I have to go.