[Man Narrating]
In the criminal justice system...
all defendants are innocent
until proven guilty,
either by confession,
plea bargain or trial byjury.
This is one of those trials.
Take off your belt.
What? Why?
Just take it off.
Watch, tie,
shoelaces.
Those too.
- Oh, you don't understand. These were a gift.
- In the bag.
- What now?
- Your hand. Pick up your coat.
Gimme your right hand.
Index finger.
[Machine Beeping]
Move over there.
Mr. Duvall,
nice big smile.
- [Machine Beeps]
- Prints accepted. Turn around.
You don't have to do that. You have
any sexually transmitted diseases?
What? No.
Then let's go.
Where are we going?
Central Booking.
T. B? Hepatitis?
Of course not.
Lice?
No.
History of seizures?
L- l-I wanna make a call to my mother.
Phone privileges are handed out in the
order in which you were booked, so...
you have to wait a while.
I think that's for me.
You Kibre?
Tracey.
It's solid.
From what Novak told me, you two
did good work on this. Thanks.
We're looking for eight to 10 for the guy
who beat Novak and took her off this case.
Let's see if we can't do
a little better for Mr. Duvall.
Yep.
How's she feeling?
Casey? All right, considering. We got the guy
for murdering one woman and raping another,
so just tell us, please, there's no
chance of him walkin' outta here tonight.
I'd be shocked if he made bail.
- Of course he made bail.
- It was two million dollars.
Chump change.
We're talkin'about the Duvall clan.
That family's influence is one of the few
things left that dates back further than I do.
- Money doesn't mitigate murder.
- Hey, you get no argument from me.
You should have seen Gabriel's
mother in arraignment court-
that sense of entitlement, not to
mention the fact she completely dis-
Assistant D.A. Kibre, this is
Eleanor Duvall. How do you do?
Tracey was just leaving.
Hmm.
Pleasure.
Pretty girl.
Come on, Ellie.
You don't like wasting time
any more than I like having it wasted.
I don't expect you
to put a stop to this nonsense, Arthur,
but I do ask you
to be compassionate.
Gabriel is my only child.
He's a good boy.
Who's gotten himself
into a heap of trouble.
Oh, hokum.
Attacking those women? Please.
He couldn't have done it, Arthur.
He was raised better than that.
Well, I'll keep my eye on things.
But you keep your eye on him.
I won't blink.
[Speaking Spanish, Laughs]
[Continues In Spanish]
[Giggles, Continues In Spanish]
The only people who care
about old money are old money.
Heard she paid Branch a visit. She
not a fan of our courthouse? [Chuckles]
I believe the word she used was " unclean.'
' Still no hint of a plea from Whitaker.
Leaving me to wonder what trumps
D.N.A. Evidence and a solid witness?
Nina Zergin's grand jury testimony
was unshakable. So was she.
She risked everything
to come forward on her rape.
We're gonna get this guy, Casey.
We found the D.N.A. Of Gabriel Duvall and Marguerite
Beauclaire, the deceased victim, on the tissue.
Which was pulled from
a precinct trash can.
Would you be surprised if half the
perps in New York left D.N.A. On it?
Uh, w-wait a second. Can you speak
to the technique that you employed?
The defendant's sample was large
and easy to develop. We used S.T.R.
- What about the victim's D.N. A?
- [Woman] There we were dealing with a degraded sample.
We had to use a composite I.D.
That included S.T.R., S.N.I.P. -
And mitochondrial D.N.A., which can't be
used to positively I.D. Someone, correct?
In and of itself, no, but when read in
conjunction with other analysis, it can.
- Do the People have any further evidence?
- No, Your Honor.
Thank you. We'd like to call
our own witness, Your Honor,
to dispute M.E. Warner's opinion.
There's no need. I'm well aware of the debate
regarding the validity of a composite identification.
The dust hasn't settled
in the scientific world.
When they are ready to accept it,
so will my court.
Can you still go forward with your
indictment without the D.N.A. Evidence?
Without it, we cannot meet our burden.
Well, then the count charging Gabriel Duvall with
the murder of Marguerite Beauclaire is dismissed.
But the one count of rape remains.
[Kibre] He didn't commit a
murder and leave nothing behind.
- If it's out there, I'll find it.
- Yeah? When?
Listen. Everybody knows you were handed
a crap case. Don't take it out on me.
[Man] Suggestion? Yeah?
I grew up with rich kids like Gabriel.
There's one thing
that they all have in common-
is that none of them were raised
by their own mothers.
So you're saying nanny?
[Kibre] Look into it.
Better yet, look into anybody
who ever worked for the Duvalls.
I just got off the phone
with the civil clerk's office.
Six years ago, a sexual harassment suit was
filed against an employee of Everton Consulting.
- Tell me it was our guy.
- Gabriel does freelance work in their I.T. Department.
Another opportunity for you
to work your magic with the ladies.
You don't look like lawyers.
Well, uh, we're D.A. Investigators.
Mind if we ask you a couple
questions? [Woman] About?
The sexual harassment suit you filed against Gabriel Duvall
- We know there was a settlement.
Is this a criminal case?
Mm-hmm.
So confidentiality clauses
don't apply?
- I dated a lawyer.
- Hmm. What inspired the suit?
Gabriel worked out of a cube
right next to the ladies'room.
Every time I'd come out,
he'd be standing there waiting to talk.
I felt bad for the guy,
so I'd say we'd talk later.
Well, the next time I'd go to the bathroom,
he'd ask me if it was "later" yet.
Sounds persistent, not dangerous.
He'd say things to me no one in
their right mind should say at work.
I went to Human Resources,
but they wouldn't act.
Amazing what family money
lets you get away with.
[Gabriel] It was consensual.
[Whitaker] Not according to Nina Zergin.
She's saying that you raped her,
and then you gave her $5,000.
If I raped her,
why would she take the money?
Why were you having sex in an alley?
I wouldn't bring a girl like that home.
Ajury's gonna love that. People
have sex in all kinds of places.
It was convenient.
I think that's enough for one night.
Oh, darling, you've hardly touched
your dinner. I wanted meat loaf.
Would it be all right if I was excused?
I still have to unpack my books.
Gabriel's very particular about
routines. Well, he hates staying here.
But with the press camped out on his doorstep
- Anything you can do to make him comfortable.
We've gotta keep him on his game for his
testimony. Oh, that won't be necessary.
Well, you didn't invite me here
just to chat.
We both know this is going
to trial. This Nina girl-
is her testimony
all the prosecution has?
Nina called the community center.
By the time I arrived,
she'd already started
to clean it up.
She was in hysterics
when I found her.
Nina.
Nina, are you hurt?
[Sniffles]
- Were you here when they did this?
- She was at work. The night shift.
What does it say? It's
what they call me now...
in the street, at the market-
[Sobs]
"Prostitute," " whore.' '
She's not safe here.
Hey, come on. Let's get you to a
hotel until we can relocate you, okay?
[Sniffles]
Okay.
They did this
to keep me from talking.
Now I have no reason left not to.
I can't believe you're not going
after them for witness intimidation.
How would we prove it-
trace the spray paint on Nina's walls?
- Anyway, it only strengthened her resolve and showed us what they're thinking.
- Which is?
They're scared.
Did you find our nanny yet?
Eva Wilke.
We know she was German.
She left the Duvalls when Gabriel
was packed off to military school.
But she went back
to Germany years ago.
Well
- [Sighs] Before Nannygate,
weren't most houses with staff hiring
undocumented workers? [Gaffney] I checked that.
According to Immigration, the Duvalls have sponsored
a series of aliens over the years. All legit.
There was that nanny, and an
Irish maid named Julia Lonegan.
She's currently in the Bronx at
the, uh, Fayerweather Nursing Home.
You seem a lot younger
than most of the residents here.
C.H.F.
- It's a technical term for a lazy ticker.
I got tired of being a burden on everyone
I loved, so I checked myself in here.
Let me ask you.
You came over from Ireland.
Came to work for the Duvalls
from 1971 to 1974.
- Yes.
- Not the best time to be in Belfast.
My brother was killed in the uprising. My father
knew someone here who worked for the Duvalls,
so I went from being
Catholic schoolgirl to housemaid.
So why did you stop working for them?
Because they asked me to.
You're here about Gabriel.
[Ravell] What makes you say
that? It's just a matter of time.
I'm sure he raped that woman.
He was only 14 years old when you stopped
workin' for the Duvalls. How would you know that?
Because he raped me too.
Both women are here?
In two separate rooms.
I hate putting Nina
through this again.
Well, it might help us
find a signature. Signature?
Serial rapists often exhibit a repetitive behavioral
pattern. Sometimes they're not even aware they're doing it.
If we can establish Gabriel's, we tie
the two rapes together. And we've got him.
- It's right here.
- The nanny was away, so I was giving him his bath.
He was 14
- a little old for you to be bathing him, isn't he?
Gabriel was forgetful. Uh, he was
a little bit touched, you know?
Sometimes he went days without washing, and
the children at school were making fun ofhim.
So I would draw the bath
and wash his hair, and he'd do the rest.
Okay. And this time,
it was different.
I know it wasn't right,
but Mrs. Duvall insisted.
I tried to hand him the washcloth, but
he wouldn't take it. He seemed confused.
- He was-you know.
- Erect?
He asked me to "take care of it,"
and then he said, " Please.' '
He kept repeating that word:
"Please.' '
He said it over and over again.
He had his pants down
around his ankles.
[Quietly] Nina, you take
as much time as you need.
He pulled my underpants off,
leaned into me.
Inside I could feel a burning.
I was crying-
not just from the pain, but because
of what he was taking from me.
Then he stopped.
I'm sorry.
He stopped-
To wipe away my tears.
I didn't even realize
I'd started crying.
I was what they used to call
a"good girl" in those days,
and what he was doing,
it hurt me.
And he wiped away your tears?
Yes. A nd then he started to rock
me in his arms and stroke my hair,
like a mother does a child.
He stroked my hair
and whispered, "Shush.' '
He was finished,
but he held me like a baby.
Is that when he gave you the money?
He put it in my hand
and closed my fingers around it.
Why would he do something like that?
I felt it was my duty
to tell Mrs. Duvall what had happened.
She called me a whore,
threw me out of the house.
I had nowhere to go.
I couldn't go home.
I'm ashamed to admit it,
but she gave me a great
deal of money, and I took it.
Did Gabriel see this?
He was standing there in the doorway.
Does the nameJulia Lonegan
mean anything to you?
She worked for us.
I fired her.
Thank you, Rita.
I'll take it from here.
[Clears Throat]
She's saying Gabriel raped her.
That's ridiculous. Why should I give
credence to lies? Well, to you it's lies.
Ajury can see it
as convincing testimony.
She demanded money. I gave
it to her. She went away.
Apparently
not far enough.
Gabriel may have
had difficulties in the past,
but he worked very hard
to overcome them.
No one will talk. That's
just it. People are talking.
It's time you did
some talking of your own.
The investigation into Nina's rape
alluded to several other attacks,
all ending with the victims
receiving money.
We getJulia's story in,
and it opens the door to nailing
Gabriel for the other rapes. [Knocks]
Tracey, you might wanna
take a look at this.
[Mrs. Duvall On TV] Talk about the
South Bronx Youth and Recreation Center.
To which you have made
a sizable donation.
But I wouldn't be worth my weight if I
didn't mention the trial. Your son, Gabriel-
Unbelievable. Is facing
some pretty serious charges.
We're an easy target.
There's talk of more allegations
from a former employee.
Well, when you open
your home to someone,
you're putting yourself in
a potentially vulnerable position.
[King] So you're saying there's
no truth to her accusations?
People hear the name Duvall
and think "idle rich,"
but what I really am
is a widow and a mother.
I trusted someone,
and she's betrayed my trust.
[King] You're saying she wanted money?
[Inhales] Well, I'm not at
liberty to discuss the case.
These women, most of them
work the night shift, cleaning offices and-
and stores and-
and fancy homes like this one.
They can't afford to be here, but they
are, because they have to believe...
that Eleanor Duvall isn't the
only one to be heard. [Horn Honks]
There he is!
Duvall, you gonna take some questions?
Hey, come on.
[Protestors, Reporters Clamoring]
[Man]
Rich rapist!
- [Woman] On behalf of your- -
[Reporter]Just make a statement.
- Get a shot.
- [Man] Put him in jail!
[Man #2] He's guilty!
[Clamoring Continues]
You all right? [Man] Pervert!
[Whitaker] No, no, no. Come on.
Let's get inside. Gabriel, come on.
I'd really like to get you
to a doctor. Gabriel? What?
- A little farther over, that rock could've taken out your eye.
- Oh, it's not just a rock.
See, intense heat and pressure have transformed the shale into a
- a conglomeration of minerals.
You see how it glints?
Yeah. I'm- I'm gonna call a doctor.
[Shatters]
[Shards Clinking]
[Clinking Continues]
I can't say that I'm surprised. What
- that Trillin imposed a gag order, or that it took him so long to do it?
[Woman] Don't tell me to calm down.
I've been waiting for over an hour.
- Where's this Kibre person anyway?
- She's right here. What's this about?
Eleanor Duvall's
smear campaign.
If you're here to come forward about something Gabriel did to you
- He didn't rape me.
He raped my mother.
Julia Lonegan's my mother.
She helps you and gets called a
money-grubbing whore on Larry King.
What can we do? Stay away
from her. You've done enough.
- [Knocking]
- Got your messages. What's up?
I had a visit today
from Julia Lonegan's daughter.
Didn't know she had one.
Neither did I.
Checked her birth records.
She's gonna be 31 in May.
Julia didn't get married until a
year after the birth, which means...
there's a good chance that Meg is the product
of her mother's rape and doesn't know it.
- How can you be sure?
- Well, Julia said she was a virgin when Gabriel raped her.
If Meg is his daughter, I want to prove it.
- You're not gonna tell her.
- Oh, come on, Casey.
I got handed a dog here:
A murder charge that evaporated, a rape
victim with nothing more than her word,
no D.N.A., no witnesses- and to back it
all up- an alleged rape from 30 years ago?
You try what you have.
Well, without Meg's D.N.A.,
I have no chance in hell.
My mother already told you everything.
What more do you want?
We need a D.N.A. Sample. I
won't let her give you one.
Not from your mother,
from you.
Oh, my God.
Your mother told you
about Gabriel Duvall.
When?
This morning.
A cop called her asking for my work
address. She hung up on them and called me.
It was you who called.
Your mother is the only one that
had the right to tell you. I just...
made sure that
it happened that way.
I already have a father.
The man who raised you and the man who
loved you will always be your father,
and nothing
is ever gonna change that.
This isn't happening.
That monster raped my mother.
Your mother found the courage
to tell us what happened.
Your mother found her voice.
Don't be the one to silence it.
[Quietly]
Thank you.
The D.N.A. Is a match. In 1974,Julia
Lonegan was raped by Gabriel Duvall.
- Allegedly.
- She'll testify to that fact.
We're talking about something
that may have happened 30 years ago.
There's no bright-line rule that determines
when Molineaux evidence is too remote.
The complainant is a woman who is currently under a
doctor's care. She's taking a series of medications-
H.C.T.Z., benzos
- all of which have been proven to cause confusion in the elderly.
Take it up on cross.
- And I'd hardly call 55 " elderly.' '
- Well-
I'll issue my ruling on the admissibility
of the Molineaux evidence after lunch.
[Whitaker]
Thank you.
[Door Opens]
Ladies first.
Eleanor, sorry I'm late.
We went over. Mm-hmm.
Where's Gabriel?
Oh, just takin' a walk.
We're gonna meet back at
the courthouse after lunch.
Was that girl there?
No.
Neither was the mother. I suppose
she's expecting some inheritance.
We'll burn that bridge when
we come to it. So where are we?
If the judge doesn't allow Julia
Lonegan's testimony, it goes away-
jury never hears about it,
and your position stands.
In other words, it never
happened. Nina's word against his.
On the other hand, ifJulia's testimony does get in,
along with the fact that her daughter's D.N.A. Is a match,
a jury could believe it.
And if they believe that
Gabriel raped Julia, there's a-
there's a good chance that they'll
believe he did the same to Nina Zergin.
What are we going to do?
Convince them otherwise.
Gabriel was 14 at the time,
and Julia was 23.
I mean, who's to say
that she didn't seduce him?
Mr. Whitaker, where, oh,
where can your client be?
- I believe he's on his way.
- Believing and knowing are two very different things.
The defendant's violating the terms
of his release. You're correct,
and I'm issuing a bench warrant
for his arrest.
Now let's proceed with our
discussion while we await his arrival.
I've reviewed your
supplementary briefs, and...
I believe that the crime
was simply too remote.
But Your Honor
- The timeline isn't all that concerns me.
Even if Mr. Duvall had been tried and convicted
of rape at the time, he was a juvenile.
- Right.
- We're not asking for a juvenile conviction to be admitted,
simply the substance of the bad act.
And either way,
the records would have been sealed.
Julia Lonegan's testimony is out.
I don't know which is worse
- losing Julia's testimony or having to tell her that we did.
You can't second-guess it.
Why not?
Only took us a couple of days to screw up what
had took her 30 years to try to make right.
She didn't have to come forward. We would
have pushed her, and you know it. [Sighs]
Give me a good old-fashioned
homicide any day-
Then you don't have to
look your victim in the face.
Did you check
your pager?
Gabriel Duvall was just arrested.
He jumped a woman down on Varick.
Son of a bitch did it again.
Well, not quite.
They caught him before he got
the chance to follow through.
She fits his pattern:
23 years old, domestic.
Where is he now?
[Ravell]
Lawyer still hasn't showed?
L-I don't need Mr. Whitaker here
to explain this misunderstanding.
Whoa. You-you slow down. We can't discuss
this case without your lawyer present.
- This is a waste of time. Let me explain.
- Can't! Against the rules.
L-I was agitated because of what happened in the
judge's chambers. Like we said, we can't hear you.
Can you imagine the gasket Whitaker would blow
if he thought we were questioning his client?
Forget the lawyer. I'm worried
about his mother. [Ravell Chuckles]
Well, I believe I can explain my own actions without
my mother. [Ravell] We've advised you of your rights.
That girl you say I attacked wanted to
help me. That's what those people do.
When I was a child and I got excited,
my nanny took care of it.
She didn't want me touching it.
She said it wasn't allowed.
It's like she said: If someone doesn't
make it go down, you have to cut it off.
Gabriel, shut up.
You two, out.
Well, since he asked so nicely.
- [Sighs]
- I want you to take me home now.
Can't do that this time.
What do you mean?
They're not taking that woman seriously?
She hit on me. She says you attacked her.
[Hits Table] That's a lie! Calm down.
- Gabriel- - Is this a
trick? This must be a trick.
They're paying her to do this
so they can keep me here!
Now your sex life has caught up with you, and you're
gonna have to pay for it unless you listen to me right now.
[Quietly] There's one
way I see us beating this,
but I'm gonna need you
to go along with it all the way.
Happy? What can I say?
Christmas came early this year.
You know I'm getting the interrogation tossed
out. [Scoffs] It was more like an opera.
They couldn't keep your guy from
singin'. No. They crossed the line.
I don't need his words. His actions
speak for themselves. We'll see.
In case you forgot,
this is where we talk plea.
Oh, I wouldn't be serving my client
well if I recommended an admission.
You're nuts.
No.
My client is.
I'm filing notice of an insanity defense.
[Dr. Olivet] How about
this one? [Gabriel] Excited?
No, wait. That's wrong.
Funny.
I'm not sure.
What do you do when you can't tell what
someone's thinking just by looking at them?
I listen.
To their voice?
No. That can be misleading.
People sometimes employ sarcasm.
It affects their tone.
I listen to the words.
Do you think people
always say what they mean?
Why would they say it
if they didn't mean it?
I know that one: Surprise.
That's right. How did you know?
At home we have books on nonverbal communication
- body language.
You work hard at reading people.
I try. But the books, they're limited.
For example, your arms are crossed. That's
an aggressive stance. Are you threatened?
No.
Well, you see?
Human behavior isn't discernible,
because it isn't fixed.
You can never really know what a person
means by how they look or what they say.
Ten different people
have 10 different smiles.
I know you don't want to hear it,
but I agree with the defense's evaluation.
You're saying he's autistic. Asperger's Syndrome
does fall within the spectrum of autistic disorders,
but there is a debate as to where it fits.
It's a convenient time for a diagnosis. Well,
A.S. Was virtually unknown until a few years ago.
In many cases,
it went undiagnosed or ignored.
So they're gonna use it as some
kind of an excuse? It'll be hard.
There's no known connection
between A.S. And violence.
- So this isn't typical behavior for someone with this syndrome?
- Absolutely not.
As a matter of fact, most people who suffer from A.S.
Are much more likely to be the victim than the aggressor.
So you want me to feel sorry for him?
Liz, he raped and ran.
I'm here to make a psychological
assessment, Tracey, not defend his actions.
A.S. Certainly isn't the cause, but it could be
a factor in Gabriel's aggressive sexual behavior.
Or a last-ditch effort to set
a serial rapist and murderer free.
[Sighs]
Your calendar just opened up. I'm
not gonna be calling you to the stand.
[Kibre]
Can you point to the man who raped you?
May the record reflect
that the witness has identified...
the defendant, Gabriel Duvall.
The record shall so reflect.
Thank you, Nina.
Miss Zergin, you-
you said that you were coming from
the subway when you were attacked.
Is that correct?
Yes.
- Was the train crowded?
- It was 3:00 in the morning.
Did you happen to notice if Mr. Duvall
was riding in the same car as you?
I don't know.
I bring a book along with me to read.
- Are you saying that he wasn't there, or that you didn't see him?
- I didn't see him.
- So you didn't talk to Mr. Duvall?
- Objection. Asked and answered.
Mr. Whitaker,
you've made your point.
So when you were leaving the train,
did you, uh, happen to
ask anybody for the time?
[Voice Breaking]
Oh. L-
Did you ask Mr. Duvall what time it was?
[Sobbing]
Yes.
So he was on the train with you?
I didn't remember.
Did you look at him
when you asked him?
I must have.
Did you smile?
- Objection. Relevance?
- I'll allow it.
I don't know.
Don't you usually smile
when you ask someone for a favor?
- Objection!
- Sustained.
You looked at no one but my client.
You spoke to no one but my client.
You singled him out, and you asked
him what time it was, yes or no?
[Sobs]
Yes!
No further questions.
When in doubt, blame the victim.
They're gonna need a lot more than that.
It's an addendum to
the witness list. Who?
Dr. Elizabeth Olivet.
When you meet someone for the first
time, you make a series ofjudgments.
You take into account their expressions, the tone of
their voice. How is it different for someone with A. S?
They find it more difficult
to read social signals.
So asking someone for the time
could be confused with a come-on.
- Objection. Relevance.
- Sustained.
How does A.S. Affect
sexual development?
In the social aspect of sexual development, people
with Asperger's tend to lag behind their peers.
- [Whitaker] Uh, can they ever catch up?
- Most people do if they receive proper care.
In my opinion, Mr. Duvall did not.
Can you elaborate on that?
All pubescent boys experiment:
Touch themselves, masturbate.
Gabriel wasn't allowed
to mature through this process.
- [Whitaker] What stopped him?
- [Dr. Olivet] In order to keep him from touching himself in public,
his nanny would
manually cause him to ejaculate.
Under what circumstances
did Gabriel allow this to occur?
- Objection. Hearsay.
- Overruled.
He told me that his nanny would
"take care ofhim"in the bathtub,
and then wash the tub
down with bleach.
Are people with A.S.
Especially sensitive to odors?
And tastes and sounds, yes.
There's been testimony that Mr. Duvall's first
sexual experiences culminated in the smell of bleach.
On the night in question, Miss Zergin was coming
home from work smelling of cleaning liquids.
Doctor, can you state with a reasonable degree of psychiatric
certainty whether Mr. Duvall could have made a connection...
between Miss Zergin and his first
sexual experiences with his nanny?
It's possible.
Thank you.
There's no genetic marker for
A.S., is there? That's correct.
No physiological evidence one can point to
that indicates someone has it? That's right.
No blood test you could
run, no brain scan? No.
Could a person fake the symptoms of A. S?
I'd like to think
that I can tell the difference.
Well, how do you tell the difference
between a man with a genuine disorder...
- and a rapist looking for the perfect excuse?
- Objection.
Sustained.
Nothing further.
[Whitaker]
I want you to take the stand.
We can't always have what
we want, Mr. Whitaker.
I understand your concerns, but we have
to think about what's best for Gabriel.
You want me to say
that my son is crazy.
Not crazy. Different.
It's important that a jury hears
a mother's side of the story.
Gabriel, dear, why don't you see if
Mrs. Judson can make you something?
No, I think I'll stay.
If I have to, Eleanor,
I'll subpoena you.
You'll do no such thing.
What's more,
I won't have you talking
some absurd defense strategy...
in front of my son without my consent.
- You're fired.
- I'm afraid you're not my client.
- Gabriel, am I fired?
- No.
- He doesn't decide what happens.
- He's my client. He decides everything.
And he's still in the room.
Stop talking around me.
I repeat, I have been forced to be here
against my will. I'll ask the question again.
When did you first notice
that your son was different?
Well, I don't know what you mean.
All children are different.
Isn't it a fact that Gabriel
has always had difficulties socially?
Gabriel was and is a perfect son.
I have nothing else to say.
So you never saw any signs
of abnormal behavior?
We're all built differently.
That's what makes us unique.
Did you ever take Gabriel
to a specialist? Certainly.
One said it was
marginal cerebral palsy,
another thought
it might be motor issues.
And now you say it's this.
[Scoffs]
I mean, every few years, another German comes
along, and they name a new disorder for him.
[Chuckles] My son is sensitive
and highly strung, nothing more.
So you sought help, but when you didn't
hear what you wanted, you did nothing.
Well, there was nothing to do.
My son is fine.
Nothing further.
Uh, no, no. You-
You listen to me now.
When Gabriel was 10,
a boy pushed him down in the dirt...
and stole a book
that belonged to Gabriel.
Gabriel hit the boy
and broke his nose.
When he came home, he was covered
with blood. He was so upset.
He was all apologies, tears.
He's fragile.
He hates violence.
He couldn't possibly do the
things they say he's done. Hmm.
Thank you, Mrs. Duvall.
That's all.
When Gabriel showed up bloodied on your
doorstep, you're saying he felt remorse?
Yes. My son is a human being,
not a monster.
He felt regret for his actions?
Oh, deeply.
So he can tell the difference
between right and wrong?
- Objection.
- Overruled.
My son is not a person
who doesn't feel things.
We taught him compassion. Did you also
teach him that it was okay to rape?
Certainly not.
So when Gabriel raped Nina Zergin,
he knew what he was doing
was wrong?
No, you're twisting my words. Uh
- She's turning everything inside out.
If you can, please answer the question.
How can you expect me
to answer a question like that?
My son did not rape that woman.
He did not rape anybody.
My Gabriel is a good boy.
Why won't anybody listen to me?
Yes or no, ma'am?
Withdrawn.
We all know that speeding
is against the law,
but what do you do if you find
yourself driving without a speedometer?
How do you know
when you're breaking the law?
Gabriel Duvall is living his life
without a speedometer.
He suffers from a form of autism
that hinders his ability...
to see the difference
between right and wrong.
He lacks the ability to appreciate the
nature and consequences of his conduct.
Nina Zergin says she was raped.
Gabriel Duvall believes there was consent.
How do you punish a man for a crime
he didn't know he was committing?
By finding him not guilty
by reason of insanity.
Gabriel Duvall thought
he picked the perfect victim.
Nina Zergin is an immigrant.
She's here illegally.
She works the night shift cleaning
bathrooms in an office building.
An easy target-
She's an invisible woman.
This city is filled with them.
The defense attorney says that Mr. Duvall
raped Nina Zergin because he's insane.
Well
- [Scoffs] If that's true,
then why did Mr. Duvall travel
nine subway stops to find a victim?
Because he knew
what he was doing was wrong.
So he chose a victim
he thought no one would notice.
Don't prove him right.
Thank you.
Monday morning
quarterbacking?
We know Gabriel did the rape, not to mention
the murder we never got a chance to try him for.
He showed absolutely
no remorse.
You don't have to convince me, Tracey.
I didn't sleep last night either.
I have to remind myself that our
job is to try him, not to fix him.
I just want this one to be over. So
you think the jury bought the diagnosis?
Maybe. Doesn't mean
they buy his innocence.
They're back.
- Has the jury reached a verdict?
- [Woman] We have, Your Honor.
[Judge Trillin] On the sole
count of rape, how do you find?
We find the defendant guilty.
[Howling]