[Man Narrating]
In the criminal justice system...
all defendants are innocent
until proven guilty,
either by confession,
plea bargain or trial byjury.
This is one of those trials.
She was in love with him.
I tried to warn her.
All clichés are true.
But naiveté shouldn't be
a death sentence.
Everybody in this office knows that
Kurt Lascher murdered my daughter.
- You've known for 19 months.
- Unfortunately, Mrs. Blaylock,
knowing and proving
are very different things.
- Her blood-
- Was in the car, but that's inadmissible.
You know that.
It was contaminated.
So you're saying what?
A murderer gets to walk free
just because he's famous?
No, I'm saying it's very difficult to
convict a murderer if there's no evidence.
Well, that's why I'm here-
evidence.
I found this in her trench coat pocket.
It's an obstetrician's card.
There's a date on the back.
It's for the day before she disappeared.
This is great.
We'll look into it.
Yeah. It's not right.
I mean, can you stand there
and tell me that this is right?
No.
No, I can't.
[Moaning]
- [Ringing]
- [Moaning Continues]
[Ringing Continues]
What?
What time?
Listen, I have an 11:00 rehearsal.
All right. All right.
I'll have Roberto pick you up on the way.
And, Peter, you were supposed
to make this go away.
Remember that part?
[Phone Beeps Off]
[Sighs] Who was that? My lawyer.
A little late, don't you think?
Uh-huh.
He just got a phone call.
I have to surrender in the morning.
Surrender to who?
Why?
The police.
They think I killed Dede Blaylock.
It's a different prosecutor-
a broad with a hair up her ass.
- Just handle it.
- Oh, that bitch! We agreed.
- Absolutely no press.
- [People Chattering]
Back up. Give 'em some room.
Give 'em some room. Back up.
Give 'em some room. Give 'em some
room to get out. What happened?
- Thank you.
- [Woman] How well did you know her, sir?
Can you just please let us through?
Kurt, you know I would never
have agreed to this perp walk.
Shut up, Peter.
She didn't call 'em.
I did. [Man] Did you kill
your girlfriend, Mr. Lascher?
Did you kill your girlfriend?
[Chattering Continues]
[Man] Please, sir. Thank you.
Docket 101604, People of the State
of New York versus Kurt Lascher.
Charge is murder in the second degree.
- How do you plead, Mr. Lascher?
- Absolutely not guilty.
[Judge] Save the rewrites
for the paying customers.
A simple declarative "not guilty"
is incredibly sufficient.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- People on bail. Ms. Gaffney?
It's a murder, Your Honor.
The defendant has a nine-figure net worth.
He has a Gulfstream jet that can
take him out of this country at will.
We ask for remand given that he is
the living definition of a flight risk.
Ray Charles could have
seen that, counselor.
However, I'm loathe to remand
someone when there's no body.
But I can make it expensive. Bail is
set at five million dollars. Short date.
- What?
- And Mr. Lascher will surrender his passport.
- [Man] Did you kill your girlfriend, Mr. Lascher?
- Did you kill your girlfriend?
[Branch]
Clearly a defendant who is terrified...
at the prospect of dealing
with the criminal justice system.
The man is custom-tailored scum,
Arthur. He's a producer, Jack.
And the reason I had you
hand this case offlast year...
is because I didn't see how a jury
would convict this guy...
without the blood evidence,
not to mention without the body,
and I didn't want my executive assistant
to lose a celebrity case at trial.
Why would I want one of
my bureau chiefs?
Because it's a very strong circumstantial
case, and we know he did it.
Come on, Tracey.
Ajury won't know that.
Are you absolutely certain there's
no way we can get the blood in?
The people at the lab told me categorically
that Dede Blaylock's blood...
was in the rental car,
but couldn't swear under oath to
a reasonable degree of scientific certainty.
Exactly what they said
a year and a half ago.
It's circumstantial,
but the circumstances are compelling.
[Kibre] Another circumstance:
Her mother found...
a gynecologist's business card
in one of her coats.
The doctor will testify that
Dede Blaylock was pregnant.
Will this doctor testify that
Kurt Lascher was the father?
[Sighs] Well, let's see if
we can even indict this jerk.
Has he indicated he wants
to testify before the grand jury?
Kelly gave Behrens
a 19050 at the arraignment.
My guess- Behrens will say
that Lascher is going to.
I'll notice him to appear
- [Branch] He'll miss the date.
You'll reschedule. Lascher'll be sick.
You'll get the indictment.
Which sets up a motion to dismiss
for failure to give Lascher...
an adequate opportunity
to testify before the G.J.
A case this big,
some judges might give it to them.
- It's just delaying the inevitable.
- Since when is anything...
inevitable with the law?
[Woman] Second line in.
Wanda, Carrie. [Piano]
Delay? That's it? Delay?
Kurt, delay is
a guilty man's best friend.
Don't you ever sit in judgment of me.
It's not my job. I'm your lawyer.
You ask, and I'll answer.
[Man]
Take five, people!
[Ends]
Why did the little bitch get pregnant?
[Scoffs]
Slate myself?
Dede Blaylock.
She was just chasing a dream.
Once Lascher started sniffing around-
- She was in love. He was in lust.
- Tracey Kibre's got a hard-on for Lascher.
Kibre?
I never had a case with her.
Yeah, she's tough, smart.
Hates to lose. I'm tellin' ya,
I wouldn't want her after my ass.
I would have kept my mouth shut
- [Salazar] You seen enough?
Yeah.
Anyway, it's not our problem.
Oh?
What is our problem?
To make sure Kibre's got
all the evidence that's there,
reinterview everybody the homicide detectives
talked to, go over all the paperwork.
Yeah, see if the precinct guys
screwed up. Yeah, it happens.
You know, Lennie, I was a precinct
detective before I got shot five times.
If it wasn't for this squad,
I'd be on permanent disability.
- I'd be retired.
- So don't kick a gift horse in the mouth.
Well, it helps pay the alimony.
So who's up first?
Vic's roommate,
Karen Masters.
You have any idea how many sessions
it took for me to get through this?
Excuse me?
With my shrink.
Your pregnant best friend goes out
to dinner, and she never comes back.
Some new evidence has come up.
And?
The D.A.' s going to the grand jury.
They'd like you to testify.
Whoa. Nobody ever said
anything about testifying.
- Wait a minute. Are you an actress?
- Only when I'm not being a paralegal.
I've seen you in a commercial.
You saw my Land Rover?
I knew it was some kind of car.
Which one- But you were great.
You want to see my reel?
I'm just kidding.
I know you're nervous about testifying,
but grandjury testimony is sealed.
Nobody in the business
will ever find out.
Kurt Lascher will.
I'm gonna have to think about this.
You guessin' she's an actress-
That's a no-brainer.
You saw her damn commercial,
and you remembered her face?
No, I got TiVo. You push the magic button,
there's no commercials.
Who's next? Maître d' of the
restaurant where they ate.
And Lascher's been a regular here
how long?
Since you were walking a beat.
Twice a week, sometimes more.
What about women?
Two a week, sometimes more.
- What about this woman?
- I figured this was about Dede Blaylock.
Nice girl.
Fell in love with Lascher.
Not a smart thing to do.
- So she came in more than once?
- Once a week for three or four months.
She used to tell me
this was their place. Delusional.
The Homicide guys came around
two or three times...
after she disappeared,
but then nothing happened.
- What's going on?
- The D.A.' s taking this to the grand jury.
- You're going to have to testify.
- Oh, great.
Why don't you take us through
what happened the last time she was here?
The night she disappeared?
Yeah, the night she disappeared.
Well, they seemed happy.
Lascher had a couple of vodkas,
and then he ordered
a magnum of Cristal.
She said they had
something to celebrate.
They had a magnum?
They drink the whole thing?
Well, she just sipped at one glass,
but he turned it into a dead soldier.
He get smashed?
Lascher never got smashed.
Check that.
He never looked smashed.
- He did some coke in the men's room.
- Oh? How do you know that?
Because he's been doing coke in the
men's room ever since I've been here.
Anyway, he came back to the table...
and sent his chauffeur home,
then tells me to get him a rental car.
- He do that often?
- Try never.
Never is an absolute.
He'll testify to never? In the
12 years he's been working there,
he said he never saw Lascher
send his driver home.
He didn't even know
Lascher had a license.
And Dede just had the one glass of
champagne? Yeah. She didn't even finish that.
I mean, she sure acted like
she had a bun in the oven.
Based on the fact that Lascher
made his last child support payment...
for his illegitimate son
three months ago-
Seventeen and a half percent of
his annual income for the last 18 years.
A pregnancy would probably
really piss him off.
- No wonder he drank the whole magnum.
- [Kibre] I'm probably gonna be able to get...
the grand jury to indict, but when we go to
trial, we're gonna need a lot more to convict.
I want you to enhance the case.
And welcome to the squad, Detective.
You're one ofJack McCoy's favorite cops.
Thanks. It's better than hanging out
at the O.T.B.
- You're really worried.
- I'm always worried.
They were dating for about six
or seven months.
I'm not quite sure how long they were going out,
because she didn't tell me when they first got together.
- And why was that?
- It was Kurt Lascher.
He's notorious.
Notorious. For what?
[Karen]
Okay. How's this?
He's also 33 years older than Dede.
I knew she was gonna get hurt.
I didn't think she was gonna get killed.
What did you say to her
when she told you she was pregnant?
That I would go with her
for the abortion.
And what was her response?
She said she was having the baby.
- Was she upset?
- She was ecstatic.
She said they'd get married,
and... I lost it.
I told her she was kidding herself.
We started fighting,
yelling at each other.
I left.
I never saw her again.
Thank you, Karen. Questions?
Uh-
[Clears Throat]
- Mr. Duzshinsky?
- Did she say...
whether she had told Lascher...
how many other men
she had slept with?
What? In her life?
No, no.
The week she disappeared.
- She wasn't sleeping with anyone else.
- Oh, you know?
What, you are psychic too?
She's an actress.
No wonder Russians hate jury trials.
Can you imagine 12 Duzshinskys
trying to reach a unanimous verdict?
[Door Opens]
Here it is.
Thank you.
Murder two.
You wanted enhancement?
I got you enhancement.
It's all irrelevant and totally inadmissible,
but it certainly enhances your perspective.
Today, Ted. Did you know that
Lascher used to be an attorney?
What do you mean, used
to be? He was disbarred.
In 1968, he was working
for Texana Oil as a lawyer.
He drew up over 200
leases for ranchers in Oklahoma.
Every one of them had a fatal flaw
in favor of the ranchers.
He quit Texana Oil
and goes to work for the ranchers.
- How many of them signed up?
- A hundred and eighty-one.
Contingency?
Thirty percent.
It cost Texana Oil $68 million.
Sixty-eight million 1968 dollars.
22,666,000.
22,666,000 for him.
Texana Oil went after his ass.
Full ethics investigation.
Disbarred.
- Why didn't they sue?
- Bad publicity. They made a deal.
He surrendered his license
but kept the money.
That's how he produced
his first plays.
Lascher had been skating
his whole life.
- Is the calendar out?
- We got Anderlee.
- Amanda's my kind of judge.
- I want to get the Texana Oil story out.
Don't leave any prints.
[Behrens] I've already
drafted our motion to dismiss.
What grounds? You were deprived
of an opportunity to testify...
and an assistant district attorney
plowed ahead and voted the indictment.
All right, all right. Best case?
It should buy another
60, maybe 90 days. What?
By then it'll be almost two years
since she disappeared. Oh, no. No, no.
It's out of the magazines.
Out of sight, out of mind. No.
No. News management.
I want to get my side out.
So you call Dominick Dunne,
invite him to dinner at Alain Ducasse.
I'll buy a bottle of La Tâche.
Kurt-
Peter, please.
I know how to control the press.
The D.A.' s are already talking to him.
There's a Vanity Fair article coming.
Oh, really? When were you
planning to tell me that?
I just found out this afternoon.
What's the spin?
Good-looking woman D.A.
Takes on the king of Broadway.
You're fired.
Excuse me?
I need a woman.
Here's what's going on, Kurt.
The fat lady's about to sing.
You're being arraigned in two days...
on a criminal charge
of second degree murder.
There's gonna be a trial.
Twelve people,
who probably can't even afford
to go see one of your plays,
are gonna decide whether you go
to prison for the next 25 years.
- You're not gonna let that happen.
- If I decide to take the case.
But I'm not going to unless I know
you're going to help me.
I don't care if you did it.
I'm not interested in proving
you innocent, just not guilty.
I have to keep as many damaging facts
away from the jury as possible.
Why am I being arraigned again?
I was arraigned.
That was on a criminal complaint.
This time, it's with the trial judge
who will advise you...
on the indictment
and the actual charges.
You really want to know?
Yeah, I have to know.
I liked her.
We had a nice short run.
My life's an open book.
I've been a bachelor for 19 years.
I'm not known for my parenting
or my monogamy skills.
She walks into the Des Artistes
and lays that on me?
So what did you do?
I ordered a magnum of Cristal,
thought about how
to make her disappear.
You sent your driver home.
Get a rental car delivered
to the restaurant.
I told her we were gonna drive
up to Connecticut to celebrate.
We got in the car and headed up.
She wouldn't shut up.
So I finally I told her
I'm never getting married again.
It was nothing against her,
but I'd never subject anybody...
to being married to me.
And I told her
she couldn't have the baby.
She flipped out.
Started yelling and screaming
up the West Side Highway.
I hit her, knocked her head
into the windshield frame,
and that's how the blood
got in the car.
She was out cold.
So I drove up to northern Westchester,
went out to Allen Watross's place,
because I knew that there was
a very deep abandoned well,
and Allen was never there
during the week.
I strangled her,
threw the body down the well,
drove home.
Nobody saw me.
Obviously.
- Any other questions?
- Dozens.
- Hundreds.
- Fine.
- I have one.
- How much?
When are Briscoe
and Salazar coming in?
Tomorrow or the day after.
They have four more names to reinterview.
- Is it just me, or are the cadets getting younger?
- And taller.
Notice of change of counsel.
Who?
Maggie Dettweiler.
I've heard she's good. Is
she that good? She's better.
[Piano] Graydon set a land
speed record for a cover story.
I talked to Nick. I told him all about
Brunei and the sultan's party girls.
It's all in there.
Good.
Unfortunately, it's the only good thing
in there for us in a 3,000-word story.
Your quotes weren't.
He makes you sound like Rasputin.
You may have forgotten that his daughter
was murdered by her boyfriend.
And that expression-
"I'd like to strangle this bitch"?
I would lose that
from my physical palate.
You may have noticed that thejudge
and both prosecutors are all bitches.
Why do you think you're here?
So, what's my
seven-figure defense?
This is a girl who went
to Brunei twice. Mm-hmm.
She spent nine months singing
in Japan when she was 19.
Oh, so she's a slut. Who knows
where she is? If the shoe fits.
What's the significance
of the Brunei trips?
Am I missing something?
You know about the sultan?
Yeah, he's, what, like the third
richest guy on the planet?
He's also very generous to his friends,
especially his male friends.
He flies in young girls
as party favors.
Dede was there for five weeks
the first time, two months the second.
- A lot of parties.
- And a lot of favors.
- Is there anything else?
- Japan.
- What aboutJapan?
- She spent six months there when she was 19.
- Doing what?
- Singing.
- She's a singer?
- Not before or since.
How come this wasn't in her file?
Didn't they check her passport?
Never found it. [Briscoe]
And it's still valid.
And we know she doesn't mind
long flights.
- Are you sure, counselor?
- What? That Lascher murdered her?
That she's dead.
Is that your justice-is-blind look?
Oh, the voice that launched
a thousand appeals.
- What's it like working for a Republican?
- Better than working for a killer.
- Alleged killer.
- Oh, yeah.
Sticks and stones
may break his balls,
but I gotta insist
on a victim to convict him.
Necessity is the mother of invention.
If you're talking "multi-illogical
alterizations" of this crime,
let's just say Dede Blaylock didn't have
a good discriminative taste in men.
Any names?
Oh, yeah.
How about Michael Feltscher?
How about Sean Murray?
A road company Michael Bolton
with no pipes.
How about Matt Mandebach?
A B-level producer.
But there's something else.
There's something-
Some actress-model-
- Oh, Amy Woodbury.
- Disappeared without a trace.
That's right. [Man] A friend of
mine out in Los Angeles there-
Robbery Homicide- tells me
that this guy Matt Mandebach...
was and still is the main suspect
in her disappearance.
- When did they go out?
- When she got back from Japan.
Okay. It is not worth as much...
if we hand them the name
as if they find it themselves.
They already have it.
Name and number.
Kibre does?
The cops.
When they searched my house,
they found her Filofax.
She was obsessive about phone numbers.
If she knew him, he's in there,
especially if he was a producer.
So I'll ask for it.
They will go through every name in that
book before they hand it over. Trust me.
You're batting a thousand.
Excuse me?
Your case just got worse.
Your vic may not even be dead,
but if she is, there's a lot better suspect
in there than Kurt Lascher.
Who's that? [Briscoe] One Matt
Mandebach, who was and is...
the prime suspect in the disappearance
of a model...
named Amy Woodbury
in L.A. Five years ago.
God Almighty!
He'd been dating Dede Blaylock
right around the same time.
The cops go to question Mandebach
about Amy Woodbury,
Dede Blaylock's in his apartment.
[Briscoe]
It gets worse.
Don't see how it could.
Mandebach was in New York
when Dede Blaylock disappeared.
You didn't know about this guy?
[Kibre] The police assured me...
they'd followed up
on all the physical evidence.
An address book isn't physical evidence?
[Kibre] Let's not take our eyes off the prize.
Lascher did it.
We know he did it.
Everything else is immaterial.
Exactly.
Exactly wrong.
Beyond a reasonable doubt.
I think you're gonna have trouble
meeting that burden.
Are you sure you don't want
to reconsider this?
- We have an indictment.
- Well, an indictment doesn't mandate a trial,
especially in an election year.
If I lose, I'll resign.
I'm sure I'll find that very comforting
on election day when I lose.
[Kibre] The police are
checking the names in the book.
I'm just asking for additional time
so they can complete their investigation.
You know, silly me. I was always
under the ridiculous illusion...
that a trial was a search
for the truth.
Oh, please, counselor. A trial is
a search for admissible evidence.
- Your Honor-
- Would you just let me rule in your favor?
- Just make a copy and give it to them.
Isn't this what Xerox machines
were invented for?
I really don't see how this request
can be rationally turned down.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- Okay, any other alarms...
or diversions?
Great. Let's set a date
forjury selection.
It's a hundred fifty thousand
through the verdicts,
a hundred-thousand-dollar bonus for
an acquittal, 50,000 for a hung jury.
Is he kidding?
And if you're not kidding,
you must be insane.
A quarter of a million dollars
for a jury consultant?
- It's a simple cost-benefit analysis.
- Oh, really?
250,000, 25 years to life.
Who do you think
your ideal juror is?
[Sighs]
Educated, upper middle class, older,
a theatergoer, male.
- What do you think of Mr. Lascher's profile, Lin?
- It's a hundred percent wrong.
[Man] Yeah, your ideal juror is a high
school graduate, middle-aged, middle-class...
married female
who wants to be a theatergoer.
- You're trying the victim?
- Yeah, well, we'll be pointing out...
certain character shortcomings
of an extremely alluring,
missing, alleged victim
who could be anywhere in the world.
Exactly. A nd who do
middle-aged women despise?
Pretty girls in their 20s
who go out with older men.
[Kibre] Are you familiar with the term
"May-December romance,"Mrs. Phelps?
- Of course.
- And how do you feel about them?
I'm sorry. Are you asking me
whether I want to have one?
No, um, I'm just, uh,
asking how you feel...
about them in the abstract.
Relationships are relationships.
Whatever makes people happy is fine with me.
So, you would have
absolutely no qualms...
about an older man going out
with a much younger woman?
- It takes two to tango.
- I think Ms. Kibre agrees with me. Watch.
- Thank you.
- She's gone.
The People are going to excuse
Mrs. Phelps, Your Honor.
[Anderlee]
Jurors one, two, three,
six, seven, eight, nine, 10,
12 are excused.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
[No Audible Dialogue] [Clears
Throat] Sidebar, Your Honor.
It took Mr. Stotti
less than an hour...
after Mr. Lascher recognized
Mr. Mandebach's name...
to reach a senior commander
of the L.A.P.D...
who informed him
that Mr. Mandebach...
was the prime suspect
in another Missing Persons case.
- The victim is also an actress.
- Your Honor, I don't see what-
Go on, Ms. Dettweiler.
The fact is,
is that he is a much more
likely suspect than Mr. Lascher,
being that he did live
and still does live...
two blocks away from
the alleged victim's apartment.
- Is this true?
- I have no idea where Mr. Mandebach lives, Your Honor.
Excuse me.
I'd say that could be the definition
of a nonresponsive response.
- Of course they know about Mandebach.
- Sit down, Mr. Lascher.
I'd say, this doesn't seem to be
the N.Y.P.D.' s finest hour, Ms. Kibre.
I can't believe I missed a damn Filofax
on the evidence locker list.
There were 219 items on that list.
I missed it too.
She's here, with pictures.
I just had to thank you for finally
getting that bastard in front of a jury.
It's not gonna be easy to convict him.
I hope you know that.
He's guilty.
They'll see that.
Mrs. Blaylock, did Dede ever mention
a man named Matt Mandebach?
I never heard of him.
Dede told me everything.
L- I just wanted you to remember.
This is what he took.
Kurt Lascher did not take
Dede Blaylock's life.
The last time he saw her, they shared a
wonderful meal and a bottle of champagne.
In fact, the State will be unable
to prove that she's even dead.
All they will be able to tell you is that
no one has seen her for the last 18 months.
But if Dede Blaylock is dead,
the State has had information
about another suspect-
a much more compelling suspect-
who was never even investigated.
[Beeping]
Thank you for your attention.
How did it play?
Well, they're not crazy about
the alternative killer theory.
The State has had information
about another suspect-
a much more compelling suspect
- who was never even investigated. [Beeping]
- I guess I'm taking that out of the opening.
- But look at this.
As a matter of fact, the State will be
unable to prove that she's even dead.
All they'll be able to tell you is that no
one's seen her for the last 18 months. [Beeping]
I'd open with, " Ladies and gentlemen,
where's the body?"
Ladies and gentlemen,
where's the body?
All rise.
Give your attention,
and you shall be heard.
The HonorableJudge
Amanda Anderlee presiding.
No. To my personal knowledge,
Mr. Lascher never had a rental car
dropped off at the restaurant.
Thank you. Oh, sorry.
One last thing.
Do you think Kurt Lascher
is a dangerous misogynist?
Objection, Your Honor.
Calls for an opinion.
Withdrawn.
Your witness.
How long has Mr. Lascher
been coming to your restaurant?
Apparently for more than 20 years,
but I've only been there the past 12.
[Dettweiler] Have you seen him
with other women over those years?
- [Maîter d'] Many other women.
- Mm-hmm. And has Mr. Lascher...
displayed a variety of moods
with those other women?
What was the 911? One of our
witnesses is changing her story.
What? Who?
Briscoe and Salazar are on it.
- Have you ever see him get angry with any of those women?
- Yeah.
Did he kill any of them?
Objection!
- Withdrawn.
- Since it's after 4:00,
we'll resume at 9:00
on Monday morning.
- [Woman] I want to see your badges.
- We don't need no stinkin' badges.
What? What did you say? I said, "
Yeah, people need to see our badges.' '
I told that D.A.
What's her name? Gaffney?
Gaffney.
I told her...
I had to speak to her
about changing my testimony.
Last year, you told the detectives
why you left the show-
that stuff about Lascher
slapping you around.
- That's why I have to talk to the D.A.' s.
- Talk about what?
I lied to those cops last year,
but I can't lie under oath.
You think there's any way
to get her new story in?
Not on direct.
It's beyond prejudicial.
It will probably get him a mistrial.
But if we got Maggie Dettweiler
to ask the wrong question-
Even if it got in, Anderlee
would instruct the jury to ignore it.
It's completely irrelevant.
Irrelevant?
It's the definition of irrelevance.
It's pretty hard
to un-ring a bell that loud,
no matter how the judge
instructs the jury.
I've got to figure out how to start
pushing Maggie Dettweiler's buttons. What?
Dettweiler will never ask questions
she doesn't know the answer to.
Any lawyer can be made
to ask the wrong question.
[Woman]
I had appeared in eight Broadway shows,
three national touring companies
and six dinner theaters,
where I started in the chorus,
and then I was a featured dancer-
Let's just keep it a little simpler.
I'll say, " Ms. Sterba,
"you were a veteran stage
dancer and singer...
"when Kurt Lascher asked you
to play the lead in Separate Beds,
"but you had limited acting experience.
Is that correct?"
And then you'll just say, "Yes.' '
And then I'll say,
"Well, why do you think he did that?"
Because we were
having an affair?
- Just make it a statement, not a question.
- [Gaffney] You should lower your eyes a little.
- You know, try to look a little embarrassed.
- Yeah, okay.
Then I'll say, uh, "Well, that seems
like a huge career move for you.
Why did you leave the show
before it opened?"
- You want the whole story?
- No. No. No.
How about, "He terrorized me
during rehearsals, so I left"?
He terrorized me during
rehearsals, so I left.
[Kibre]
Okay, just stop there,
and then you look at the jury
and tell what he said to you.
- In rehearsal?
- No. Don't say anything about that.
Just the threat.
The way we discussed.
- He terrorized me during rehearsals, so I left.
- [Mouthing Words]
And then I look at thejury.
Kurt Lascher is a monster.
Oh.
[Clears Throat]
Kurt Lascher is a monster.
One night he told me that he could make
me disappear, like that. [Snaps Fingers]
Thank you, Ms. Sterba.
Your witness.
You've testified that you
left Separate Beds...
because Kurt Lascher
terrorized you?
Among other reasons.
Let's talk about those other reasons.
Isn't it true that you left because
Mr. Lascher ended your affair?
No.
No?
No. It was something
that he told me...
that was so disturbing that it made it
impossible for me to continue.
A moment, Your Honor?
Am I gonna hear something here
that's gonna hurt us?
I called her a stupid cooze.
Sue me.
So your testimony is that you
threw your whole career away...
because Mr. Lascher,
in a moment of anger,
made a disparaging
personal comment?
No. He did that every day.
The day I quit,
I was playing a woman
who had been beaten by her husband.
We were rehearsing a scene.
You bitch.
- Mr. Lascher.
- [Sterba] Kurt told me...
that I should make the audience understand
that I still loved my husband.
He said it was like
when you strangle a dog.
- Your Honor- - [Sterba]Just before
they die, they fall in love with you.
They look into your eyes
and wag their tail.
Objection, Your Honor.
[Clears Throat]
Sidebar.
Overruled.
You can hardly object
to the answer to your own question.
- Then I move for a mistrial.
- Motion denied.
But I will instruct the jury to disregard
Ms. Sterba's last statement.
You will not refer to the statement in
any way or let it color your deliberations.
The People rest, Your Honor.
Pissed off voice message from Briscoe.
They're 11 years back, and there's nothing.
Well, call him and remind him
I said to go back 15, and do it faster.
No, it would be a huge mistake.
I agree.
- And I have no choice.
- It's exactly what Kibre wants.
- She could go anywhere on cross.
- Just let me explain the dog thing.
I would not like to be convicted
just because I wanted to manipulate...
a performance out of
an untalented chorus girl.
She was pretty compelling
on the stand.
Yeah, I would lose
the "untalented chorus girl" descriptor.
You may be a ballbuster,
but when you're right, you're right.
Fourteen years, three months. You're
not only right, you're lucky too.
Oh. Lascher the dog lover.
I've loved dogs my entire life.
I grew up with 'em.
The idea that I would hurt a dog,
or any animal, is ludicrous.
But you did say what
Ms. Sterba said you said?
Yes, I did.
I was giving her direction.
Penny Sterba is... great in bed,
but she's a lousy actress.
I would have said anything
to get a performance out ofher.
But an inexperienced actress, uh,
confused direction with reality.
Thank you, Mr. Lascher.
Your witness.
- Let's talk some more about dogs.
- Objection. Irrelevant.
- Ms. Dettweiler opened the door, Your Honor.
- Overruled.
You've testified that
you're a true dog lover.
- My entire life.
- Then why do you kill them?
That's ridiculous.
I'd like this entered
as People's 67,
but I'd like Mr. Lascher
to verify its accuracy.
- I'd like to see that.
- So would I. Sidebar.
This compounds other irrelevant
and immaterial...
material already entered
into evidence.
Again, Your Honor, I must strenuously
object. And again, I must overrule.
Your client has no one to blame but himself.
Step back. You may approach.
Do you recognize
those documents, sir?
Oh, for God's sake.
- I take it that's a "yes"?
- This is completely out of context.
[Kibre] Let the record
show that the defendant...
is looking at a bill for $150...
for putting three dogs to sleep...
on May 4, 1989
in Mt. Kisco, New York.
I had just moved back to the city.
These were country dogs.
They would have had to been
walked on leashes.
So you killed them.
One might conclude that one of your
problem-solving solutions is killing things.
Is there a question in there,
Your Honor?
Your Honor, I have no more questions
for New York's favorite animal lover.
Not guilty. Guilty.
Guilty. Not guilty.
Eight guilty, four not guilty.
This is ridiculous.
Eight of you want to convict
somebody of murder...
for euthanizing his own dogs?
Me? I'd like to give him a medal
for keeping my shoes free of all dog crap.
I can't get the image ofhim
strangling a dog out of my head.
- He said he was just trying to elicit a performance.
- Please! W ho's kidding who?
This guy's a sociopath. And we all
read that article in Vanity Fair.
State police called an hour ago.
But they found the body a week ago?
Six days ago.
Home inspection of a mortgage company.
The bottom of a well on an estate.
Are they sure it's Dede Blaylock?
The dental records match.
We'll have the D.N.A. In the morning.
Four days late and a dollar short.
It doesn't make any difference.
It's in the hands of a jury.
If they acquit, he walks.
What, your jury's still out?
Five days.
Well, they, like juries
all over the tristate area,
will be rendering verdicts tonight
and tomorrow.
You know this.
I know this.
How?
Because play-offs start tomorrow.
Not guilty.
Guilty. Guilty.
Eleven to one.
Please, you know in your heart
he killed her.
I'm not even sure she's dead.
She could be in Japan or Brunei.
She's dead, she's dead, she's dead,
and Kurt Lascher did it!
Fine. Let's just
pick this up in the morning.
No, no, no. Let's stay here
until we get this settled.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
have you reached a verdict?
- We have, Your Honor.
- How say you?
We find the defendant,
Kurt Lascher, guilty.
[Murmuring]
Thanks.
Never saw it coming.
Thank God.
That was a buzzer beater.
That was a three-point buzzer beater.
You convicted a guy on cruelty to animals,
not evidence.
Life's a bitch.
Yeah, and some days,
the one holding the scales
is blind, deaf and dumb.
[Howling]