[Man Narrating]
In the criminal justice system...
all defendants are innocent
until proven guilty,
either by confession,
plea bargain or trial byjury.
This is one of those trials.
He destroyed my life.
There's still a part of me
trapped in that room with him,
terrified, in pain,
wondering if he's gonna kill me.
And on my worst days,
I wish he had.
I was 12 years old
when he raped me,
and every day
I have to deal with what he did.
LyleJoynes isn't safe.
He's not! He's sick!
And he will always be sick!
You have to send him back!
Thank you for your testimony,
Miss Bell.
- Ms. Gaffney?
- LyleJoynes has previously been held for offenses in Manhattan and Queens.
He's classified as a level-three
sexually violent offender.
And since his release, he's moved
back into the same home in Astoria...
where he assaulted Denise Bell
12 years ago.
Not revoking his parole
would be an invitation to tragedy.
Has Mr. Joynes complied
with all his registration requirements?
Absolutely, sir. I'd like to ask,
where's the violation?
What has he done wrong?
The D.A. Is just speculating here.
A dozen kids live in the neighborhood.
His parole states no contact with children.
[Man] Thank you, Ms. Gaffney.
I'll review your memo.
Mr. Joynes,
you can make a statement.
They keep harassing me, sir.
I can show you the hate mail.
They even vandalized
my mother's house.
I mean, that's why I'm living there. L
- I gotta take care ofher 'cause she's ill.
I worked hard for my early release.
I go to therapy five times a week,
and I'm genuinely sorry for what I did.
I was another person then-
real mixed up.
- I'm on a program for chemical castration, so
I don't even have the urge anymore- - He's lying.
- You're out of order, ma'am.
- My name is Karla Grizano.
I'm an attorney representing
the people of this neighborhood.
- Joynes is just looking for another-
- Ms. Grizano! Sit down.
Are we supposed to wait until he re-offends
before this system works?
Yeah! [Woman] That's right!
What the hell happened in there?
You didn't make much of a case.
The case was fine until you spoke out.
Look, I agreed to do this,
even without clear evidence
of a violation.
They're just bureaucrats.
They don't care about these people.
Well, you didn't help
by pissing them off.
After reviewing the evidence,
we do not find sufficient probable cause...
to believe that Mr. Joynes has violated
the conditions ofhis release...
in any important respect.
Now, as much as we sympathize
with the community's position,
we hereby dismiss
the notice of violation.
Let the son of a bitch live next to you!
He can rape- He can rape your kid!
[Chattering, Arguing]
- Nice try.
- Get outta my face.
[Elevator Bell Dings]
Thanks, Frank.
[Clears Throat]
Hey, you Gaffney?
- Chris Ravell. Nice to meet you.
- They said you asked for me specifically.
- That's right. Over here.
- What happened?
Weren't you working some case
about that child molester, LyleJones?
Joynes. Yes.
God, what did he do?
He got himself murdered.
Joynes left his shrink at 5:05.
Got killed 20 minutes later.
Therapist says he was catching
a train at 14th Street.
And stopped to loiter
at a jungle gym?
We're sure he wasn't mugged?
Nah, no robbery.
Witnesses say they saw
a man walk up to him,
words were exchanged
and, bang, six rounds.
My guess-
Joynes knew his killer.
Any obvious suspects?
You see his sheet?
The line of people who hated
this guy goes down the block.
Witness saw a white male,
180 pounds, 5'10", brown hair.
Nobody got a better look?
What do you expect?
Guy runs by waving a gun,
you're hittin' the deck.
And nothing off the canvass?
Nothing.
Somebody got a look
at the, uh, shooter's car-
a blue Olds Cutlass.
I'm-I'm sorry, Detective.
Are we done?
- My lieutenant's pulling me on to something else right now.
- Then who's working this case?
Look
- [Clears Throat] The murder of this pervert's not a high priority around here.
All I'm saying is...
I'm not gettin' much help.
Well, then, you could team up with
one of the detectives from our office.
C.S.U. Swabbed mucous
offJoynes's forehead.
The killer spit in his face
before he shot him.
So we're talkin' about a
vigilante. [Kibre] I think so.
So what's the plan?
Start with the people from his neighborhood.
Look for a match to the D.N.A.
You really think those people
are gonna volunteer to help?
I'll open an investigative grand jury.
In other words, a fishing
expedition. Oh, come on, Arthur.
We can't endorse street justice.
We have to send a message.
The press has already
picked up on the story.
And, as you know, they're ready
to canonize the man who did it.
Well, make sure you have solid
probable cause on any D.N.A. You collect.
Believe me, if I find a smoking gun,
I'm not gonna let it get suppressed.
If I find the shooter,
I want a conviction.
And I want results... fast.
Or we move on.
They swabbed my mouth,
gave me some kind of receipt.
Said if it didn't match,
I'd get the sample back.
They called it voluntary.
Yeah, but it's some cop askin' me.
What was I gonna say? No?
- They can do this?
- It's obviously coercion,
but, yeah, they can do that.
The D.A.' s strategy here is simple.
They ask you for a voluntary sample.
You refuse.
They feel justified in asking you
to testify before the grand jury.
So what? I'd still refuse.
Well, then they serve you a subpoena,
which means you have to show up.
If the D.A. Thinks
you're withholding information,
they can use that
to get an order for your D.N.A.
Hey, look. I don't like it either,
but I got nothin'to hide, all right?
- I didn't kill the creep.
- That's not the point.
- If it gets 'em off my back- - You know, they found
Joynes's body beside a playground, for God's sake.
Well, you think anyone here is gonna
shed a tear that piece of crap's dead?
No.
You know what? They can't treat us
like we're the bad guys, you know?
'Cause they're the ones who got him
out of jail in the first place.
Jimmy is right.
They cannot do this to us.
Roy, you're okay. You're off the hook,
'cause you bent over for 'em already.
Okay? But no one else
should cooperate.
Karla, you think that'll work?
They're sensitive to politics here.
We embarrass the D.A.' s office,
stall the investigation,
they could drop the case.
You were good in there.
Karla?
When I shot him,
my hand didn't even shake.
I shouldn't have spit in his face.
That was stupid.
But he gave me this look, like, uh-
l-l-I find him leering at a bunch of kids,
and he's lookin' at me
like I'm in the wrong place.
You protected your family. Your beautiful daughter
- She's safe now.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
[Engine Starts]
Jimmy, when the cops come
and knock on the door,
call me before you answer it.
[Door Closes]
Is this the last house?
We got this one and one more.
I'd like to get a little bit more out of
this guy than just a D.N.A. Swab, you know?
He lives this close to the vic.
What are you gonna do-
squeeze his shoes?
If you don't mind, I'm gonna take
the lead. Feel free to jump in.
You're the boss.
That's not what I'm sayin'.
Yeah, well, that's what I'm hearin'.
When it's my case, I like
to drive things, you know? That's all.
You know, before I got shot,
my badge was as gold as yours.
Used to see him fighting
with his crazy mother all the time.
So you were around
back when Denise Bell got raped?
Oh, yeah.
I won't ever forget it.
What it did to that poor girl.
Her family.
I saw them bring her
out ofJoynes's house.
Didn't recognize her,
she was so badly beaten.
- [Groans]
- His mother still lived there after that.
Can you believe it? Someone
should've wasted Joynes back then.
Any ideas who did waste him?
If I did know, I wouldn't tell you.
Well, sure. Most people
are glad the bastard's dead.
So why don't you bother them?
Mr. Colby, would you volunteer
Has anyone else?
A few. People
who want this over with.
My client's not volunteering
anything, Detective.
We know you're fishing
for a murder suspect.
It's about eliminating suspects.
Mr. Colby gives us his D.N.A. Saves
us a hassle. Saves him a trip downtown.
For a grand jury, right?
That's blatant intimidation.
My client has answered
your questions.
Well, sorry it didn't work out.
Mr. Colby, we'll be in touch. I hope you give
this some thought about where this is going.
- What's going on?
- Nothing, sweetheart.
We're just talkin' some business.
Your mom made you some breakfast.
You can let yourselves out.
[Door Opens, Closes]
Colby matches the general description of the
shooter, and his alibi sucks-home watchin' TV.
What about the car?
Uh, no match, no hit on the gun,
nothing registered in Colby's name.
But he lives two doors down from Joynes
with a 12-year-old daughter.
So maybeJoynes looked at his kid,
and that set him off.
- It's not a hard scenario to see.
- It's still not enough for probable cause.
If we could tie him to the gun-
Check out his family and friends.
See if he's got any access to a.38.
So Grizano-What's with her
"woman of the people" act?
Oh, she spoke out of turn atJoynes's
hearing, pissed off the parole official.
I think she liked the attention.
Well, if she likes an audience,
maybe you should invite her to lunch.
The publicity from this could be
devastating for District Attorney Branch.
Prosecuting the case
doesn't make us advocates forJoynes.
But that's the perception.
You let pedophiles
back into the community...
and then don't do anything
to protect families?
Then you harass them?
Is this for real, Karla?
What's that supposed to mean?
Our negative publicity works for you.
Gets your name in the paper.
Kelly, what law school
did you go to?
Boston College.
Huh. Good for you.
I took night classes in a
storefront law college in the Bronx.
I did it while raising my son
without his deadbeat father.
So spare me the cynical attitude.
You don't get it.
I have a connection to these people.
I am the only one-
the only one standing up for them.
We're gonna get an order
for your client's D.N.A.
What's that gonna win you?
These people felt helpless.
The courts wouldn't protect them.
That failure resulted in a killing.
Whose fault is that?
Our detectives discovered
that Mr. Colby had access...
to a.38-caliber handgun,
the same as the murder weapon.
The gun was registered to Mr. Colby's
brother and kept at his place of business.
It's now missing.
Can they prove my client took the gun?
Can they even prove that it was
the weapon used in the crime?
I don't think it's the only.38
in the five boroughs, Your Honor.
A gun store clerk
has identified Mr. Colby...
and said that he purchased.38-caliber
ammunition on the afternoon of the murder.
This is a grand jury order,
and I tend to allow them latitude
in their investigation.
Your Honor, it's an abuse of power
to unfairly target my client.
Ms. Kibre has been threatening residents
with grand jury subpoenas...
if they refuse to cooperate.
I'm sorry, Ms. Grizano.
I'm sensitive to coercive tactics,
but I don't like coincidences either.
Your Honor-
Motion denied. Mr. Colby will submit
a blood sample for D.N.A. Testing.
Make it quick.
[Sobbing]
Listen to your mother.
Do your homework.
If anybody lays a hand
on you in there, I swear-
Sweetie, I'll be fine.
Let me hold your ring for you.
Almost forgot.
Don't make any statements.
I'll see you at the arraignment
in the morning.
Maybe talk to my brother
about bail.
I'll handle it.
All right. Let's go.
No shame, Jimmy.
[Crowd Shouting, Chattering]
[Man]
Mr. Colby, are you the vigilante?
Did you kill LyleJoynes?
Can we get a statement, Mr. Colby?
Anything you'd like to say
toJoynes's victims, Mr. Colby?
Can we get a statement?
Anything at all, please, Mr. Colby.
Anything. A nything you'd like to say
to theJoynes family?
Mr. Colby's bail has been set
at $300,000.
His family, his friends, his neighbors
have raised the money...
and will post that amount today.
He pled not guilty. How do you
reconcile that with the facts?
Is there any question
why a law-abiding citizen...
was forced to protect his family?
Did Mr. Colby attempt
to contact the police?
Of course he did.
His neighbors did.
I even appealed to the district attorney,
and A.D.A. Kelly Gaffney couldn't...
and wouldn't put LyleJoynes
back into prison where he belonged.
Ms. Gaffney, any comments?
The D.A.' s office is not commenting
at this time. Please let me through.
[Chattering]
This office has a stellar reputation
for being tough on sex crimes,
and here we are letting some lawyer
from Queens sully that.
Arthur, we have a solid case
for murder two.
We have D.N.A.,
motive and intent.
Who's your judge?
Rebecca Steinman.
I'm well aware
of her reputation.
She got elected for throwing
the book at sex offenders.
This isn't the same thing.
She probably admires a guy like Colby.
I want you to offer man one.
I want this yesterday's news.
- First-degree manslaughter?
- Ten to 15.
Short of all charges dropped,
my client doesn't want to hear it.
Colby traveled from Queens
to Manhattan to huntJoynes down.
That's clear premeditation. The facts
come out, "defense of others" won't play.
And I won't argue it. We're going
to be asserting E.E.D. Instead.
Extreme emotional disturbance?
That's creative.
An E.E.D. Defense drops the charge to
man one. It's the same as our offer.
My client wants his day in court.
Does he?
Or is that what you want?
You're gonna see him walk
on an acquittal.
He admits he kills a man,
and you seriously think a jury
is gonna find him not guilty?
You ever hear of Bernie Goetz?
All these reporters been calling me.
Restaurant's packed.
All this publicity.
Did you see us on the news?
Yeah, you looked good.
Um, Tony, can we use
the office for a minute?
I'm in the middle of payroll.
Ten minutes. Be a sport.
- When do I get the bail money back?
- When your brother's acquitted.
First right thing he ever did in his life,
and still it's gonna cost me.
Uh, Karla, I've been thinking,
and, uh, I don't regret what I did.
I'll face whatever they give me.
You're giving up?
No, I'm just saying...
I'll take the D.A.' s deal.
Well, you better think about that.
They offered 18 to 20.
Eighteen years?
[Scoffs]
I thought-
I thought so too,
but that's as low as they'd go.
[Scoffs]
Jimmy, I told them to shove it.
We're gonna go to court.
We'll beat this thing, okay?
Just like I said.
Okay. Okay. But my defense-
I don't like sayin' I was crazy.
No, not crazy. You lost control.
It doesn't matter what we say.
No jury's gonna send you to prison
for killing that monster.
Trust me.
You say murder two, Ms. Kibre.
I think there's an adequate justification
for a jury to consider E.E.D.
Your Honor, E.E.D. Might as well
stand for " excuses, excuses defense.' '
It allows the jury to ignore the facts
and decide the case...
based on their feelings
of sympathy for Mr. Colby.
We've submitted multiple reports
from psychological experts,
and they say my client's
been emotionally disturbed.
These reports
are of dubious psychological value.
So put your expert on the stand in rebuttal.
I see a sufficient legal basis here.
And there's the other motion I filed-
the gag order for Ms. Grizano.
- Oh, right. - Your Honor, I would
like to be heard further on this matter-
Save it. The spotlight's off. From
here on, try your case in the courtroom.
Some residents may testify, especially
ones who contributed to Colby's bail.
Well, I want someone to do a registry and record
check of every person in that neighborhood.
I'm on it.
Everything, Sigrun.
Down to the "D"
their kid got in chemistry.
We should also compile a summary of every case in
the past three years that used E.E.D. As a defense.
Uh, I'll do it.
Yeah, also research
Grizano's last few cases.
You know, I remember at the parole hearing, Joynes
said he kept hate mail from the neighborhood.
- Now, if any of it tied to Colby- - Let's
talk toJoynes's mother. See what she's got.
Mine.
They're animals-
how they treated Lyle.
We're sorry for your loss.
They painted terrible things on my door.
Sick things. Broke my windows.
Mrs. Joynes, your son mentioned that he kept
notes and letters sent to him by your neighbors.
Do you know where those are?
Vile words.
Oh, the things they said about him!
Lyle was a nice boy.
E- Except with dogs.
Didn't like dogs.
Did he maybe keep them
in a secret place?
- The notes?
- [Inhales]
I don't think this room's been cleaned out
sinceJoynes went upstate.
Yeah, a lot of hand lotion
and comic books.
- Stunted adolescence.
- You think she did something to him?
She who? The mother?
You know, turned him into a freak,
like the movie Psycho.
Does that poor old lady
look like Mrs. Bates to you?
Stuff her and put her in a fruit cellar,
I can see it.
- Can I help?
- Yeah, you wanna zip it?
All right. But in two years, I'm a
prosecutor. You're working for me.
- Get Gaffney.
- What do you got?
- Hypos. Steroids.
- I don't get it.
He was injecting testosterone.
Puttin' the lead back in the pencil.
Score one for Colby.
Maybe he had a point.
[Gaffney] We found a few threatening
letters toJoynes in a kitchen drawer.
I'm having them analyzed
for fingerprints.
Well, hopefully we'll get a hit. Take some
of the heat off this steroid discovery.
The M.E.' s office double-checked
the autopsy report.
Turns out the serum testosterone levels
in Joynes's blood were abnormally elevated.
So he was definitely shooting the stuff.
And violating the terms of his release.
Probably looking for his next victim.
Well, it's not enough to justify murder.
Colby didn't know about it.
Well, whether or not the defense
knows about it, we have to turn this over.
Notify Grizano.
We'll argue to keep it out.
What's the point of me checking it
if you know this stuffbetter than I do?
[Laughs]
This kid's smarter than her old man.
Bye.
[Door Closes] So that son of a
bitch was shooting testosterone...
so he could-
so he could do it again?
We need the jury
to hear about this evidence.
But you need to have known
Joynes was using the drugs,
otherwise we can't get it in at trial.
Okay, but l- I didn't know.
Are you sure?
It's possible a package for him
was delivered to your house by mistake.
You know what I mean?
You opened it. You realized-
Karla, I don't want to lie.
Jimmy, this is important evidence.
I know, but I shouldn't
have to lie, you know?
I did the right thing.
Everybody says so.
People respect me now.
If I lie-
I want people to know
the whole truth about that deviant.
Jimmy, it makes what you did
all the more right.
He was injecting testosterone to counter
the effects of the Depo-Provera?
The chemical castration was a major
condition ofJoynes's early release.
This violation was obviously
an act of predatory behavior.
And it's obviously inadmissible.
It has no probative value.
It's relevant to an atmosphere of fear
that led to my client's loss of control.
Was he aware of the steroid use
by Mr. Joynes?
Well, um, I knew-
I mean, uh, I had seen him
receiving packages in- in the mail,
which the postman said
contained mail-order drugs.
[Sighs]
Um, no, I didn't actually know.
I'm sorry. The evidence is out.
Hey! Grizano!
When am I getting an interview
with your client?
Hi, Mike. You know we can't talk to you.
The judge would hold me in contempt.
Well, how 'bout we don't tell her?
Uh, you're not talking to anyone.
Give me a minute.
I hear you lost out
on the testosterone.
You're gonna run the story?
My lead for tomorrow.
That judge is siding with a dead pedophile
over a neighborhood hero.
Not allowing that evidence in
says as much.
I hear rumors about a safe streets committee
drafting your name for city council.
Fifty-third District?
News to me.
Come on.
Colby's rocket fuel for you.
[Laughing]
Hey, I still want my interview.
Everything okay?
Better than okay.
We all remember
how he hurt little Denise,
so we watched Joynes
around the clock.
If we had turned our backs,
it could've been one of our kids next.
Did Mr. Colby
help monitor LyleJoynes?
Oh, yeah. He helped organize shifts
and took it very seriously.
Told me he cut back
his hours at the restaurant...
so he'd be at home when
his daughter got out of school.
So he had real concerns
for her safety?
Oh, he was terrified for Brianne.
I mean, it was no secret.
That creep had a thing for girls her age.
[Grizano]
Thank you.
Did Mr. Colby ever tell you
he wanted Mr. Joynes dead?
We all wanted him dead.
You think we had any options left?
Could you please answer the question?
I'm proud ofJimmy.
He stood up for us.
If Mr. Joynes had so much
as looked wrong at a child,
he would've been sent back to prison.
- Did you know that?
- It wasn't that simple.
Oh, sure it was. You could've called
Joynes's parole officer or the police.
The police patrolled the neighborhood to
protectJoynes, not us. You people didn't care.
When you letJoynes out of prison,
you put every one of us in one.
Mr. Baker, if you so firmly believe...
that Mr. Colby did the right thing,
why didn't you pick up a gun
and killJoynes yourself?
They changed the route.
The bus dropped me off early that day.
So your father wasn't there
to meet you like he usually did?
No, but it's only three blocks.
I used to walk it by myself.
You mean before LyleJoynes
moved back into the neighborhood?
What happened
when you passed by his house?
I saw Mr. Joynes
sitting on his porch.
- What was he doing?
- Smoking a cigarette.
- Did he talk to you?
- He asked me where I lived.
- Did you tell him?
- He already knew.
He said I was Jimmy Colby's daughter.
Said he grew up with my dad.
I only talked to him for a minute.
Did he say anything else?
He said-
He said he'd come visit my house.
We'd be friends.
I ran home and locked the door.
[Grizano] Did you tell your
father when you came home?
I'd never seen him so mad.
His face got red.
He punched the wall.
It scared me.
Mr. Joynes didn't seem bad at first,
not like everyone said.
I didn't know.
[Grizano]
It's okay, Brianne. You did great.
No more questions, Your Honor.
Brianne.
You're very brave
to come and talk to us today.
Are you okay?
Now- [Clears Throat]
When you told your father
that Mr. Joynes had talked to you,
did your dad say that
he was going to hurt him?
Objection. Hearsay.
Overruled. You may answer.
I don't know.
He made me go up to my room.
Did you hear your dad leave the house?
Not then.
I wanted to call my friend Rachel,
but my dad was on the phone.
I pulled the LUDS. The, uh, call in question
was placed to Karla Grizano's cell phone.
Colby called his attorney?
Spoke for nine minutes.
Now, that's enough time to get some legal
advice before committing a major felony.
Make that two felonies
if she knew he planned to kill Joynes.
Oh, there's no way to know that.
She'd claim privilege.
Well, privilege or not,
I don't think she was in the dark.
Maybe we take a look at Ms. Grizano.
Closing arguments are in the morning.
Jury'll have this case by lunch.
I'll hustle.
Ladies and gentlemen,
as you deliberate,
we need you to focus on the two
most important questions in this case:
How could they let that monster out?
How could they let him prey
on our children...
and not expect
reasonable people to act?
[Kibre] MaybeJames Colby is a
good man who killed a bad man,
but your solemn duty is to render
a verdict based on the law.
Not on sentiment. Not on sympathy.
The defense claims
a justification for murder,
but that is the first step down a slippery
slope of exceptions and excuses...
that others will use to twist the law
to their own ends.
Who will be safe...
if we justify people
murdering other people...
in our streets or in our homes?
And if that happens,
how will we ever be able to tell
the good men from the bad?
We got lucky.
We found the getaway car.
Vehicle's registered
to her ex-husband, Dominic Grizano.
I thought the car fleeing
the scene was a Cutlass.
Well, this year's Buick
looks pretty similar. Easy mistake.
- And Grizano had access to it?
- We talked to the ex.
It's his car per the settlement, but he's pretty
sure she has a key. We're lifting some prints now.
Found this under the driver's seat.
578 Perry?
Wait. That's the address
ofJoynes's therapist.
Colby's getaway car,
and his attorney is behind the wheel.
Helped her own client commit murder.
Dare I ask why?
Reaping the rewards
of Colby's notoriety.
Win or lose,
Grizano's star has risen.
She's been playing the press
with an eye on the city council.
Fifty-third District,
from what I hear.
Charlie Kleber's seat.
You know, I'm not sure Colby's aware
of her political ambitions.
Maybe if he knew that
she was using him to step up-
Can't approach him
without his attorney being present.
- But what if we did it in front of her? Moved for a mistrial?
- Based on what?
Rumor that she wants to run for office?
You already say you can't tie
the car evidence to the day of the murder.
Still might be enough
to get her disqualified.
We'll get more evidence.
The jury's out.
You're right up against a verdict.
No time.
We get Colby convicted,
we'll have more leverage to flip him.
And this case is a slam dunk, right?
We don't convict him,
Colby and his attorney take a walk.
We should be nailing Lady Macbeth,
not some working stiff from Queens.
The car alone isn't enough
to get her on the murder.
If Colby gets convicted,
we'll offer him a deal.
If he gets convicted.
You taking bets?
On verdicts? Never.
Possibility of that woman
walking away from this-
I want to get her.
You have something in mind?
What if Colby spoke up
before the verdict came in?
Went to the judge, told him that
he wanted new counsel and said why?
- That his lawyer was an accomplice?
- Yeah.
Then the judge would rule a mistrial,
Colby would take a deal,
and we'd get Grizano.
How do you provoke him?
How about we make
Colby believe that Grizano...
deliberately got him indicted?
Like maybe she tipped us off
to some evidence.
I've got a connect at The Ledger.
I think I got something that might work.
[Grizano]
How you doin', Jimmy?
How do you think I'm doin'?
A reporter called me. He said, um-
He said someone told the police
where I got the gun.
- An anonymous caller.
- What?
No one at the restaurant even knew the gun
was gone until the police came to search.
Except you.
You're the only one who knew.
Don't fall for this trick, Jimmy.
Be smart for once in your life.
Why would the reporter lie?
The D.A.' s behind it.
They're bluffing.
Don't you get it?
They want you to react.
- How?
- Turning us against each other.
Getting you to take a plea.
Look at me.
Their best deal is going to send you to prison,
and I'm not gonna let them muck it up.
We are so close, Jimmy.
I don't sleep at night either.
But I'm here.
I'm right here, standing by you.
I took Brianne out
for ice cream last night.
You know, I want her
to remember me as, uh-
- No, don't go there! Don't-
- They're gonna convict me!
No way. I've got that jury
on your side.
Three of them had tears in their eyes
when Brianne was on the stand.
They're going to acquit.
Trust me, Jimmy.
[Sighs]
Mr. Colby.
Excuse me. L-
I need to talk to you.
No. You're not supposed to be-
Just a minute of your time, please.
No, I'm not allowed to speak to you
without your lawyer present.
That's why I need to talk to you.
Well, if you have a problem with your counsel,
you need to bring it up to the judge, not me.
No. Please!
Listen, this is highly inappropriate!
I'm sorry. I can't.
Yeah.
Did anyone see you talking to him?
He approached me on the street.
Oh, great. So only half the city
witnessed it! Why didn't you walk away?
I did. He was very insistent.
Oh, he was insistent.
All Grizano would have to do
is get Colby to say that you approached him,
get some witness to back him up
and then report us to the bar.
Let's just see if he talks to the judge.
Tracey?
What?
The clerk called.
The jury's back.
[Gaffney]
I think Colby'll flip.
I'm gonna need more than a hunch.
Tracey, we need him. We've got nothing
on Grizano without his testimony.
I'm not gonna pressure him in court
and have it blow up in my face.
All rise.
Be seated.
As you know, we have a verdict.
I'm going to bring in thejury.
Better be right about this.
Your Honor?
Yes, Ms. Kibre?
Your Honor, we'd like to ask
that the verdict remain sealed.
- What?
- This is highly unusual.
Yes, I understand that.
These jurors want to go home.
If you're trying to somehow delay-
New evidence has come to our attention
which implicates Ms. Grizano...
as a coconspirator in theJoynes murder.
Your Honor,
this is totally without basis.
We're opening a grandjury investigation
into her role in the crime.
Oh, come on!
There's a manifest necessity to seal
the verdict until this matter can be resolved.
This is an illegal ploy to get me
disqualified as Mr. Colby's counsel.
Your Honor, this man is facing
conviction and sentencing.
He may go to prison
for the rest of his life.
It's our duty to make sure that there was
no conflict of interest with his legal advice.
I want this evidence right now.
We found the car Ms. Grizano used
to chauffeur her client to the murder.
- Your Honor, these are outrageous lies.
- Enough, Ms. Grizano.
All right. In view of this claim, I'm
going to excuse the jury for 48 hours...
and seal the verdict until
I can review this evidence.
Then I'll decide
whether we have a mistrial.
What about Mr. Colby's counsel?
Given the possibility of a conflict,
he should be allowed to dismiss
his attorney should he see fit.
Kibre, I'm gonna file
misconduct charges at the bar.
- Your Honor?
- Jimmy, sit down.
- Your Honor, I want a new lawyer.
- You're asking to dismiss your attorney, Mr. Colby?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Because you believe there's a conflict?
Yes, ma'am, I do.
Ms. Grizano, where are you going?
Counselor, we're not done!
Come back here, or I'll hold you
in contempt! Officers!
Mm-mmm.
I had to talk to someone.
He went after my kid.
Brianne couldn't see it,
but he was-
Seducing her?
Yeah. I was out of my head.
I was so angry.
Karla was like this calm voice
at the other end of the phone.
I didn't know what to do.
She said I should killJoynes.
The people would thank me for it.
She picked me up.
We drove into Manhattan.
She knew where he'd be.
Afterwards,
she got rid of the gun.
I went home...
and hugged my daughter.
I thought I was doin' the right thing.
He consents to a mistrial,
testifies against Grizano,
we'd drop the charge to man one.
It's a serious crime,
so I can offer you five years.
I'll take it.
I just want this to be over.
And then we're going to indict
Karla Grizano for murder.
Short meeting.
Came all this way for nothing.
Grizano rejected the plea?
Didn't even want to hear it.
I'm happy to go to trial.
You know, I never asked you-
What did you think Colby's verdict was?
You mean the sealed verdict in the
back of some file cabinet somewhere?
I don't speculate.
Four days of deliberating?
I know what I think.
Yeah? Well, you're wrong.
They convicted him.
[Howling]