[Man Narrating]
In the criminal justice system...
all defendants are innocent
until proven guilty,
either by confession,
plea bargain or trial byjury.
This is one of those trials.
Tracey, this is Jack Miller.
He's a columnist with-
The Ledger. I know.
I read your stuff.
Well, you're not gonna like this.
Jack got an anonymous call
this morning...
from somebody claiming to be
an officer at the 8th Precinct.
He said that an NYU freshman
named Lucas Rice...
was beaten and raped
by two police officers...
with a nightstick.
[Groans]
This guy's telling the truth?
I talked to him for 20 minutes.
I asked a bunch of questions.
Everything checked out.
Why'd he call you? He said he wanted
to go public with what happened...
without sellin' out the department.
You know, the blue wall crap.
- What do you think? - I think the
you-know-what's about to hit the fan.
So I get here, and before
I know what's going on,
the doctor comes up
and he's telling me,
"I'm sorry. Your son just passed away.' '
Like that. Just-
No emotion. Just-
If you'd like to speak with a counselor
- About what?
About what it's like to lose
an 18-year-old son for no reason?
Hold it a second.
Sir, you're not supposed
to do that. This is my son.
Sorry.
[Crying]
- [Man] All we know is he was in custody.
- Custody?
They were holding him at the 8th
Precinct on an assault charge.
He came back from the bathroom,
started moaning, passed out.
Somebody called an ambulance
and here we are.
What happened to him?
A blunt instrument was inserted-
shoved, really- into the rectum.
The colon was perforated
and the mesenteric artery ruptured,
causing severe internal bleeding,
a decrease in blood pressure,
ultimately leading
to cardiac arrest.
Something pierced his rectum,
caused internal bleeding and he died?
- Something like that.
- Any other cuts or marks on the body?
The lip was cut, the eye was bruised,
but most of the damage was done internally.
Well, there was this fight
in a gay bar in the West Village.
It got crazy. The kids hopped-up
on X or meth or somethin'-
- And you arrested Rice for assault?
- [Officer] No. We did some crowd control.
Mike Bressler and Scott Davis
made the arrest.
So Bressler and Davis brought him in,
booked him. Then what?
Don't know. I heard the kid
moaning in the holding cell.
I asked if he's okay, and he just
kept moaning, so I called an ambulance.
- What happened to your eye?
- Got scratched outside of a club. No big deal.
- Is the kid okay?
- Not really. He died two hours ago.
Now that this is all over the media,
the public has a right to know...
that the federal, state and local governments
are working in concert to uncover the truth.
And to the extent that a crime
has been committed,
to bring those responsible to justice,
whether they're wearing uniforms or not.
And as deputy police chief, I'll do
what I can to make sure that happens.
However, if an officer really
raped and killed this kid,
it may be better for the U.S.
Attorney's office to take control.
I don't think it's appropriate. This case
is loaded with federal issues, Arthur,
not to mention
the obvious conflict of interest.
- Conflict of what?
- You work with police officers every day. We don't.
And when they commit crimes,
we prosecute them.
Why not avoid the appearance
of favoritism altogether?
Besides, we have better judges,
better jury pools.
Better lawyers.
I've heard that speech before.
I was hoping that we could resolve
this amicably. Well, you thought wrong.
This is a Manhattan homicide and the Manhattan
District Attorney's office is in charge.
So the, uh, speech
about working together...
is a bunch of crap?
You're damn right it is.
You heard about
that NYU kid- Rice?
- Sure.
- Sickening, if what they say is true.
It's hard imagine two cops doing-
It's your case.
Well, I thought the feds
would handle it.
It's ours, for now anyway.
- For now?
- The longer it takes, the less control we'll have.
We need to resolve this before every
damn son of a bitch with an agenda...
starts screaming about
what a mess the N.Y.P.D. Is.
With all due respect,
I'd rather not get involved.
I know some of these guys at the 8th.
It's not a comfortable-
Comfortable? You think I give a damn
if you're comfortable?
This isn't a request.
You might work for the D.A.,
but you're still a cop,
and you still report to me.
[Ravell] You guys arrested
Rice, right? Yeah, for assault.
He sucker punched Petro in the face
and took off into the crowd.
Me and Mikey found him outside
a little later, so we busted him.
So you saw Rice throw the punch? Yeah.
Yeah, not bad for a fag either.
Hit him pretty good.
Well, nothin' worse than
gettin' drilled by a queen, right?
But if you're gonna get hit,
better it'd be a wise guy, a gangbanger.
Guys who won't bust your balls
so much, you know?
Nobody was busting
anybody's balls, okay?
So don't be puttin' words
into my mouth.
- I was just-
- I know what you were just doing.
You guys see anything else that might
help? No. We didn't see anything else.
We're done. Come on.
Look, I'll meet you back at the office.
I've got some stuff I gotta do.
Right.
Chris, if you wanna work this
on your own, just give me the word.
Oh, it's nothin' personal, Hector.
All right. All right.
I read your statement this
morning. What statement?
The one you gave to the A.D.A.
That wasn't a statement.
We were just talkin'.
Just talkin'.
A kid dies of a punctured colon
three hours after being in police custody?
Come on, Danny.
You're not that naive, are you?
You got a question or what?
Yeah, I do.
Why didn't you tell anyone
Rice sucker punched you?
Didn't think it was relevant.
Really?
Not relevant?
[Sighs]
Look, Dan.
- I'm just trying to-
- Take down a cop.
I know.
Come on. Off the record.
Did you get a little payback
on that kid or what?
Talk to my lawyer.
[Sighs]
Any of you guys working that night?
Well, you can talk now, or you can wait until
the D.A. Drags your ass in front of a grandjury.
I guess they didn't see anything either.
You're probably right.
'Cause if they did, they probably
wouldn't be stupid enough...
to cover for a punk like you.
See you soon.
I'm sipping my coffee,
minding my own business...
when I see Petro comin' out
of the bathroom.
He looks at me and he says,
"I broke that punk like a little bitch.' '
And then he, you know,
starts doing this with his hand.
Did he say anything else?
No.
Was anyone else involved,
Officer Lemay?
Don't know.
What about Tolbert?
Like I said, I don't know.
What Petro did to that kid
- They can call me a rat all they want. I don't care.
But Petro's as far as I go.
When you talked to the reporter
from The Ledger,
why did you tell him that
there were two cops involved?
I got no comment on that.
We're done, Tracey.
There was another guy
in the holding cell with Rice.
You two were in the
same cell, right? Yes.
Did you happen to see which officer
took him to the bathroom?
This is a pretty uncomfortable situation for
me. Nobody around here knows I was arrested.
We'll be as discreet as possible.
I appreciate that.
My lawyer says I'll be able to plead out
to a misdemeanor possession charge,
go to some counseling
and be done with it.
- But if I have to testify and this
becomes public- - Maybe we can help.
Even if you drop the charge, the defense
lawyer will know I had coke on me.
I mean, look around.
This isn't exactly a hotbed of liberalism.
Like I said,
we're gonna try to help you.
You just gotta stop playing games.
Did you see who took Rice
to the bathroom or not?
[Dog Barking]
Chris.
Hey, Billy. How you doing?
What can I do for you?
We need to talk about Lucas Rice.
You fellas want anything to drink?
No, thank you.
No, thanks. If you change your mind,
give me a holler. I'll be in the kitchen.
Thanks, sweetie.
[Baby Coos]
How old's your baby?
Three months.
Her name's Serena.
Lucky guy.
Beautiful wife, baby.
What can I do for you, Chris?
So, Tolbert,
why don't we talk about
what happened the other night?
The more you tell me,
the more I could help.
As a friend, I'm telling you,
get on the record in a hurry.
The longer you play super cop,
the worse it's gonna get.
The truth is gonna come out
sooner or later.
I got nothing to say, boys. Sorry.
Then tell us about Petro.
He's a good guy.
[Scoffs]
And a good partner. Who'd sell you out for
three cents if it could save his Italian ass.
And why is that?
I know how these guys think, Billy.
What they say
when you're not around.
They make you think
you're friends, one of the boys.
- But the second you turn your back, you're anotherJew.
- Or spic.
It's not like that.
Besides, like I said,
I got nothing to hide.
So you bringing Rice to the bathroom and then
taking him back out 10 minutes later, all banged up-
that's just coincidence?
Thanks for stopping by, boys.
Talk to your lawyer, Billy.
Maybe we can work something out.
But don't wait too long.
[Door Opens]
[Door Closes]
So Tolbert brought Rice to the bathroom
and helped Petro get his revenge.
Maybe.
Why maybe?
Tolbert's a good kid.
I worked with him for a while at the 31.
I mean, he's not the kind of guy-
He's a down-the-middle family man.
Just talked to a kid named Crawford.
Claims he punched Petro that night.
So Rice-
Didn't do a damn thing.
I only want good news, Hector.
Fine. Blood in the holding cell's a match.
- What about the bathroom?
- Luminol destroyed the sample.
[Sighs]
- Nightsticks?
- Clean.
- Petro's clothing?
- Found blood on his belt.
Match?
Tolbert.
Tolbert?
Well, he-he got cut at the club, right?
Probably wiped it off
and touched Petro or somethin'.
Or Lucas scratched him in the bathroom while
he was fighting desperately to save his life.
Well, they're partners. There's a million
ways something like this could happen.
As far as I'm concerned,
there's only one.
Bressler and the others
were busting Petro's chops...
for getting his ass kicked
by a gay kid.
Petro laughs along,
while planning his revenge.
They get back to the station,
Tolbert takes Rice to the bathroom,
holds him down.
Rice fights for his life, scratches
Tolbert's eye, while Petro does his thing.
- Can you prove it?
- In a perfect world-
I'd be a two handicap
and have a full head of hair.
We only have two witnesses so far.
Credible?
Solid, not perfect.
Indict 'em.
- Indict? We don't have enough-
- We have plenty.
Arthur, I'm all for beating
the feds to the courthouse,
but I don't wanna get my pants pulled
down in front of a hundred million people.
Then buy a new belt, 'cause I want
an indictment by the end of the week.
- For first-degree murder.
- First degree?
Death in the course of
a criminal sexual assault.
Both defendants shall be remanded.
Your Honor, these men are
respected members of the N.Y.P.D.,
have strong ties to the New York area,
are fathers to small children.
To separate them from their families based on
nothing more than innuendo is reprehensible.
- I know the press is here, Mr. Grace, but enough already.
- These men are the victims...
- of a politically motivated witch hunt.
- [Judge Alverio] Next case.
- I'm not finished, Your Honor.
- I'm warning you, Mr. Grace.
- I can't sit here with my mouth shut while
you send two decorated police- - [Raps]
You're now in contempt.
That's a thousand dollars.
Contempt? Because I won't
let my client be sent to jail?
[Raps]
That's another thousand.
- A small cost to pay for a man's freedom.
- One more word and I throw you in jail, so help me God.
Come on. Let's go, all right?
Let's go.
You did what you had to do.
Hang tough.
You wanted to get fined? We
need to get our story out there.
Level the playing field.
[Buzzer Buzzes]
When can I get out of here?
If you're willing to testify
against Petro, tomorrow.
He's my partner.
Doesn't mean you can't.
Sure it does.
I'm not flippin'.
We're talking about
first-degree murder, Billy.
But I'm innocent. So is Danny.
A guy hits you,
you get a little payback.
That's how it works.
So you beat him up?
I hit him a few times.
That's it. I didn't rape him.
You know, I'm not a-
I'll never do something like that.
So you have no idea who, um-
No.
Mmm.
[Buzzer Buzzes]
I mean,
you know what those drugged-up gay boys
do to each other at those clubs.
So who knows
what happened that night?
Who put what where?
Exactly.
You know,
given this kid's lifestyle,
those internal injuries could've been
the result of rough gay sex,
not police brutality.
But they have two witnesses.
- Yeah. Neither of whom saw a damn thing.
- Could offend the jury.
- So what's the alternative?
- For your client or mine?
Look, Tim,
if we present a joint defense,
we'll win this thing.
Take a look at this.
"I'm a handsome,
18-year-old paradox.
Outgoing, yet introspective.
Shy, but adventurous.' '
- "Prudish and freaky"?
- I know. It-
They're going to allege that Lucas's injuries
were the result of rough sex.
This isn't about Lucas.
This isn't about Lucas's love life.
This is about two sadistic cops.
I agree. Absolutely.
But I still need to talk to Lucas's boyfriends
so I can contradict the defense,
just in case they decide to go forward
with this ridiculous assertion.
Um-
I knew he was gay.
I don't know any of his-
I mean, I never really paid attention.
I never really got into that.
The best part?
We're gonna go through
all of this... stuff,
get humiliated, and it's not
gonna mean a damn thing.
- Oh, that's not true. - Not a damn
thing. Those- Those cops are gonna walk.
Code of silence and all that.
Mike, I'm no psychic,
but I'm sensing you saw more than what you
told the grand jury. I didn't see anything.
You're really willing to ruin your career
over some mutt like Petro?
You know, maybe when this is over, you should
go to Internal Affairs and do this for real.
First off, watch your tongue.
Second, if you don't, we might have a problem
- you and me off the clock.
Petro could rot in hell, as far as I'm
concerned. But Billy Tolbert, he's a good kid.
I agree.
About what?
Petro's a punk and Tolbert's a good kid.
Well, you see anything that
might support that position? No.
You see Petro carrying a nightstick near
the bathroom? Doesn't matter what I saw.
I'm not yappin'.
What can I do for you,
Detective? That obvious, huh?
I only sell to cops.
Oh, and actors too,
if they have one of those
SAG cards.
I need you to look at a few photos.
For what? It doesn't
matter for what. Just look.
Any of these guys been in here recently?
Aw, come on, buddy.
I work with cops every day, huh?
Give me a break.
You want we should talk about this
in front of a grand jury?
Okay, okay. Fine.
Him. Black cop.
Came in last week.
You remember what he bought?
A nightstick.
So?
Nothin'.
Nothin'?
At least on the record.
What does that mean?
No one's willing to testify.
But the consensus is, Petro's a bad guy
and Tolbert's getting the shaft.
Anything else?
No, nothin'.
So your cop friends won't talk?
Well, you could subpoena them, but-
Officer Lemay was suspended
three years ago...
for getting into a fight
with Petro over a woman.
Great. There goes
our key police witness.
Lemay is our primary witness.
But even if he's telling the truth,
the jury's not gonna believe him.
They'll think he's just trying
to get back at some guy...
who used to date his ex-girlfriend.
So he's useless?
What about Tolbert?
Supposed to be a good kid.
Except for the fact that he helped
rape and murder Rice,
he's a perfect gentlemen.
We'll flip him.
But he's gotta do hard time.
Nobody walks away from this
without some pain.
[Ravell]
You all know why we're here?
I'm supposed to say you're
a dead man if we go to trial.
But since we all know each other,
I'm not gonna play that game.
- I appreciate that.
- I'm not gonna lie either.
- We have a good case.
- But I'm innocent, Chris.
[Sighs] Is that why you bought
a nightstick the day Rice died?
- What?
- You bought a new nightstick at the store on 23rd Street.
Clerk picked you out of a photo array.
So don't tell me you're innocent.
The good news is
I didn't tell anyone yet.
- What do you mean?
- I was waiting for Billy to come clean.
So no one knows
about the nightstick?
You think I'd be here right now
if Kibre knew about that?
But my generosity ends
in two minutes.
What do you mean
you've been hearing rumors?
Well, you know, it might be
a load of crap. But if it isn't-
Well, it's like I told you before,
Tolbert's old school.
He might as well be a paisan.
Only he's not.
Look, if he flips, it's over.
And if it's over, well-
We're talking about
your life here, Dan.
[Ravell] I know you didn't
want this kid to die.
I know that.
You werejust doing yourjob,
trying to be a stand-up partner.
Talk to him, Billy.
Tell him what happened.
[Ravell]
I get this.
You're just trying to prove
you're a real cop.
As real as the Irish and the Italians.
But that's stupid.
Come on. You know how these people are.
How much can you really trust them?
The melanzane.
You know what they're like.
Look, you have a wife and kid at home.
Who cares about
all this blue wall crap?
In or out?
Good news.
Tolbert's on board.
[Stammers]
Oh.
- What's the matter?
- Petro plead guilty this afternoon.
He what? We took first-degree
murder off the table, so-
So you don't need Tolbert anymore? No.
- I tried to call you, but-
- You should've tried harder.
Now Tolbert's hanging in the wind
with nothing to offer.
Well, sorry, but I had a few things on my
plate, as you can imagine. So just deal with it.
- Deal with it?
- What-What'd Tolbert say?
What difference does it make?
What did he say?
Nothin' much.
Jerk.
My only wish is that some day,
when his life has ended,
that he be forced to account for his
misdeeds in a more powerful court,
and that the suffering
he encounters then...
will approach the suffering
my son Lucas endured...
in that windowless bathroom
in the 8th Precinct.
Mr. Petro?
[Clears Throat]
I betrayed my family,
my fellow officers...
and importantly, Lucas Rice.
I can't begin to express
the sorrow and shame I feel.
I know the pain I have caused his family
and friends will never disappear.
As such, I am prepared to accept
whatever punishment this court deems just.
Finally, I would like to say
that my partner, Billy Tolbert,
was not involved in this crime.
He's a great police officer
and a great man,
and he should not
be held accountable for my actions.
Thank you.
This admissible?
Better not be.
I'll draft a motion.
I told you. Tolbert
wasn't involved. What?
Petro just admitted that he wasn't
involved. Petro's a sadistic sociopath.
Who cares what he said?
Who cares?
You really get off on this,
don't you?
What? Sending guys to jail
who torture and kill college kids?
Yeah. I get off on that. No, no.
Tracey, he tried to break it up.
That's why his blood was on Petro's
belt. He was just trying to help.
Help?
Did you really just say that?
[Sighs] We are talking about a 24-year-old
guy here with a wife and a baby.
No! We're talking about
an 18-year-old freshman...
with a mother and a father
and two sisters.
- You lost the motion.
- Judge said it was hearsay. Can you believe that?
Petro stands up in open court,
says Tolbert had nothing to do with it,
and the judge says it's inadmissible.
What a country.
So you want Petro to testify?
- I need him to testify.
- Can't do it.
He's doing 25 years to life. There's
not much more they can do to him.
Sure there is.
What the hell is this?
It's a federal indictment.
What?
Civil rights offense resulting in death.
The U.S. Attorney got
D.O.J. Approval on this?
Yeah. Apparently the folks
in Washington...
think that killing our clients
will advance some federal interest.
I was 48 out of a hundred yesterday.
Pretty good.
It's all in the concentration. If I
focus on the front of the rim, I make 'em.
If I don't-
Like putting-
All about routine.
Danny's not gonna be able
to help, is he?
Can't. The feds just indicted him.
But he's already doing 25 to life.
They wanna kill him.
They indicted you too.
So even if I win this trial-
We have another one right behind it.
Can't catch a break.
Every time l-
There's more bad news.
You mean good news.
Good news?
Another chance to be useful, which
means another chance to cut a deal.
Ten years. He'll do six.
In exchange,
Tolbert will testify against Petro.
If we agree to drop the charges?
His lawyer isn't stupid.
Six years for helping rape and kill
an 18-year-old kid?
Whatever it takes to put
a needle in Petro's arm.
[Chuckles]
I can hear the campaign speech now.
I'm asking for a favor, Arthur.
I'm sorry I can't accommodate you, Curtis.
- Arthur.
- Say hello toJoanne for me.
In case you needed
any extra motivation.
[Glasses Clinking]
Sorry I'm late.
[Clears Throat]
What's on your mind?
Billy Tolbert.
I know him.
He's no Sunday school teacher, but-
Look, he took that kid
into the bathroom. I know.
But that is not murder.
It is when the kid dies.
I was wondering if you might
pull a few strings, help him out.
Help him? We need to take him down.
Him walking makes things worse.
Look, he's a cop.
Thermostat's turned up way too high.
So you're just gonna throw him
under the bus?
Don't have a choice.
Oh. Oh. Are you drunk?
Tolbert bought a nightstick
the day Rice died.
What?
He went to the supply store on
23rd Street and bought a nightstick.
The clerk picked him out
of a photo array.
When did you find this out?
Today.
Today?
Right. Today.
[Elevator Bell Dings]
[Door Opens]
Not only did the defendant
instigate the attack,
he covered it up as well,
by disposing of the murder weapon.
Rather than protect
Lucas Rice from harm,
he tortured him, he raped him
and he murdered him.
It's- It's inconceivable.
It's unimaginable.
And yet it is real.
It's too real.
Just ask Paul Rice, his father.
When he came back, his lip was cut,
and he was moaning.
I asked if he was okay,
but he was disoriented.
Then he passed out.
Is the police officer who took Lucas from the cell
and then brought him back 10 minutes later here today?
Yes. He's sitting right there.
Thank you.
The night in question, you had been arrested
for disorderly conduct and possession of cocaine?
Yes.
It was dark in the
holding cell, right? Yes.
So it's impossible to say for certain that
Officer Tolbert was the man who entered that cell?
No, I'm certain. Like I said,
he had arrested me
earlier that night.
So I remembered what he looked like.
Plus I saw the name Tolbert
on his shirt pocket,
and I started laughing to myself.
Laughing?
My criminal law professor's name
was Kevin Tolbert.
I thought it was, you know, ironic.
[Grace] Know what else is ironic,
or perhaps just coincidental?
The drug charge was dismissed
in exchange for your testimony?
Yes.
Nothing further.
Were you fired from yourjob recently?
Yes.
Why?
I told the managing partner
I had to testify at this trial.
When I explained why, he fired me.
And if you had pled guilty to the drug charge
and not testified, what would have happened?
Nothing. He never would
have known I'd been arrested.
Thank you.
The People rest, Your Honor.
The defense calls Martin Addas.
My club caters to gay men
into rough trade.
We don't market ourselves
as such, but we-
What does, uh, rough trade mean?
[Addas] It's a term for men who enjoy having
rough sex with tough, blue-collar guys.
It's not exactly S&M,
but it's, uh, still rough.
Have you ever seen any of your patrons
engaged in this type of sex? Sure,
in the private rooms.
Have you seen patrons
using sex toys?
Sometimes.
What's the largest male sex toy
you've ever seen at your club?
Pretty big.
- [Grace] As big as a nightstick?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Did you ever see Lucas Rice
engaged in a sex act in your club?
No.
Nothing further.
You think thejury's gonna buy
that gay sex bit?
[Grace] We don't have a
lot of options. Sure we do.
What are you talking about?
I wanna tell the jury
what happened.
That's not a good idea.
Why?
I didn't know Petro
was gonna rape that kid.
He asked me to take him
to the bathroom. That's it.
I thought he was gonna make him apologize
or smack him around a little bit.
I had no idea he was-
He went crazy that night.
He kept saying, "You like it,
don't you, you little bitch?"
So I opened the door
to see what was going on.
I couldn't believe-
I pulled him off
and he just started swinging.
He hit me in the eye.
But I didn't-
I just grabbed his arms,
and I just looked at him.
But he didn't-
he didn't even see me.
It's a good story, but it's murder.
You should've sold him out when
you had the chance, but you wanted to-
[Sighs]
You needed to be part of something.
I was a part of something.
Not like you think.
This-your color-
never goes away.
Not with these guys.
You got one shot to get out of here.
And the truth ain't it.
Did you see anyone
attack Lucas Rice?
No.
Did you attack Lucas Rice?
Of course not.
It's highly unusual to escort
an inmate to a private bathroom.
Not if someone's sick.
It's also highly unusual to leave an inmate
unattended in a private bathroom.
I was at a desk 15 feet away,
so he wasn't unattended.
I wasn't that worried about him.
Yeah, well, obviously.
Otherwise, you wouldn't
have helped rape him.
[Grace] Objection. Sustained.
Watch it, Miss Kibre.
Mr. Tolbert,
why did you purchase a nightstick
the morning Lucas died?
- I didn't.
- You didn't?
I didn't.
Well, a store clerk, Mr. Whitney,
who has nothing to gain by this,
picked you out of a photo array.
I didn't buy a nightstick that morning.
I swear to God.
On my daughter Serena's life.
All I ever wanted to be
was a police officer.
Tolbert's lyin'.
Tolbert brought Lucas into the bathroom knowing
Petro was gonna beat the hell out of him.
He told me everything
the day we talked about a deal.
And you're telling me this now,
the day before the trial's supposed to end?
I tried to call you. But I got a
lot on my plate, as you can imagine.
I'm calling you as a witness first thing
tomorrow morning. A witness? I can't testify.
Oh, the hell you can't.
LfTolbert lies, I can impeach.
He said that he brought Lucas
into the bathroom,
handcuffed him to the sink,
so his partner could get some payback.
- Payback?
- Petro thought Lucas punched him,
so he wanted revenge.
And where was the defendant
during the attack?
Outside the door...
to make sure
no one else went in.
- And after it was over?
- He brought Lucas back to the cell,
cleaned up the bathroom.
[Kibre]
Cleaned up the bathroom?
There was blood.
Petro's nightstick was on the floor.
What did he do with the nightstick?
He threw it in a Dumpster
on 10th Street,
and then he bought
a new one the next morning.
[Kibre]
Thank you.
You worked with Officer
Tolbert for five years? Yes.
Within the N.Y.P.D., he has
a reputation for honesty, doesn't he?
I suppose.
[Grace] How would you feel if
Billy Tolbert was your partner?
[Scoffs]
How would I feel?
- Would you object?
- No.
Because you trust him.
Because he's a-
he's a good cop.
What the hell was that?
A good cop?
Are you trying to get fired?
He asked a question, I gave an answer. You
practically told the jury to acquit him.
I was telling the truth.
The truth?
If you wanna stay here, Detective,
you better figure out...
where the hell that damn blue wall ends
and reality begins.
On the count of
murder in the first degree,
we find the defendant not guilty.
[Spectators Murmuring]
On the count of
murder in the second degree,
we find the defendant guilty.
[Grunts]
Oh, baby.
[Cries]
I love you.
Serena loves you.
We'll be okay.
Be strong.
I love you.
[Handcuffs Closing]
Congratulations.
Thank you.
[Ball Hits Basket]
[Ball Hits Basket, Bounces]
[Ball Bouncing Continues]
[Howling]