In the criminal justice system,
sexually-based offenses
are considered especially heinous.
In New York City,
the dedicated detectives who investigate
these vicious felonies are members
of an elite squad known
as The Special Victims Unit.
These are their stories.
Come on. Come on.
Sorry.
Jeez, Damien.
What are you doing here so late?
Finishing a grant. You?
End of the quarter financials.
I... I need some caffeine.
You wanna come?
It's on me.
I'm going to bed... alone.
- Oh.
- Sheila, are you okay?
I think so.
My bag fell.
Oh, my God.
Looks like she was dressed
for her dream date.
It ended when the perp strangled her
repeatedly with her own pantyhose.
By the ligature marks,
I'd say three or four times.
He choked her and let her come back?
- Got off on it.
- Yeah, it gets worse.
The killer sliced off her breasts.
Took him a couple tries.
Hope she wasn't awake.
No, no spatter.
She was already dead.
- We find her...
- Severed parts?
Not yet.
Killer must've walked out with them.
Well, here's how he got in.
The lock's been tampered with.
Check out the scratches.
No blood trail.
He didn't cut her out here.
So he kills her, he jimmies the lock,
he grabs the body to the elevator shaft,
hacks her up.
Place is filthy.
Explains the dirt on her dress.
No, it doesn't.
The soil on her dress
is clay-like and crystallized.
Nothing like that in this place.
So he killed her somewhere else
and dumped her here.
No, she let herself in.
- How do you figure?
- These are hers.
Burglary tools.
Murder is a high price to pay
for breaking and entering.
Ran our victim's prints, got a hit.
Tina Snow, 21, went to Hudson University.
College student? What's her record for,
drunk and disorderly?
Trespassing, breaking and entering.
Explains the tool kit.
Rap sheet says she was pinched
at a storage unit on one charge.
The other an electronics warehouse.
Anything worth stealing
where she was found?
High-end art gallery
in the same building.
Maybe she's upping in the ante.
Was she busted with a partner?
No, both collars she was solo.
Maybe this time she had a partner.
Who turned on her.
Mutilating her breasts is personal.
Rape kit was negative.
But tox screen bumped.
Tina's blood alcohol was
three times the legal limit
and she had GHB in her system.
Date rape drug.
So why get her drunk,
slip her a roofie, and not rape her?
Maybe he couldn't rise
to the occasion.
Liv, Elliot, see if Tina
was hanging with anybody new.
Start with the roommate.
Apartment of Tina Snow
412 East 53rd Street
Monday, October 15
Oh, my God.
She was into some freaky stuff,
but I never thought she'd wind up dead.
What kind of freaky stuff?
She stayed out all night.
Never went to class.
Hudson was threatening to kick her out.
For bad grades?
Didn't pay her tuition.
See her stack of pinks?
12 grand or she couldn't graduate.
Her parents wouldn't help her out?
They live in Arkansas.
They didn't like their daughter
moving to sin city.
Could explain why she was heisting.
A lot of ash here.
What was she burning?
Got me.
Every week she'd get a note card
in the mail then light it up.
- Do you know who sent them?
- No.
- But it was something dirty.
- She was hooking?
No, I mean what she did was dirty.
Every time she got a card, she'd go out
and come back all covered in muck.
Found these flecks of mica
in the soil sample from the victim's dress.
They're from finely-ground
Manhattan schist.
Well that narrows it down to Manhattan.
More significant's what I didn't find.
No pollen, no plant life.
- Tunnels.
- How you figure?
Dude, plants can't live without sunlight.
Okay, well there's got to be
hundreds of miles of tunnels.
Any idea of which ones
are full of schist?
They're all full of schist.
- Got something?
- Maybe.
if we can get some
writing off burnt paper.
That'd be a definite maybe.
- Chester, hit the light.
- Got it.
Well, the paper's definitely burned...
But the writing's still there.
We just can't see it with the visible light.
If I hit it with the right
non-visible wavelength...
Presto.
"Astoria platform, 10, 15, 19, 30."
Today is October 15th.
19:30's military time for 7:30pm.
- Which was an hour ago.
- There's no Astoria stop in Manhattan.
Actually there is.
Waldorf-Astoria Platform
New York Subway Tunnels
Monday, October 15
The Waldorf-Astoria used to have
a private subway for its guests.
The platform is shut down now.
Let me guess. Your people built
all the buildings and the subways too.
Hey, iron work is iron work.
200 feet above the ground or below.
Waldorf is a great place
to pull a high class rip off.
Get dressed up, mixed in with
a formal event,
and then escape through
the abandoned tunnels.
Yeah. Peel off your coat and sit down.
Your husband out?
Like it was this afternoon.
I must have said something that
gave you a terribly wrong impression.
You must never think anything like that
about me, Walter
Okay. / No, it's not okay.
Not if you don't believe me.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to be nice to me.
Can't be like the first time.
Police!
Run!
Come here.
Hey, hey, show's over.
Where you going, spider?
I got nothing to say.
This'll do all your talking for you.
This is Agent Mayhem reporting
for the silk and cyanide corps.
"Agent Mayhem?"
Your rap sheet says your name
is Edgar Rabinowicz.
Also says that you've been busted
for trespassing, burglary,
and resisting arrest, Edgar.
But Agent Mayhem's got a nicer ring to it.
I like it.
It's much more you.
So you had a week's worth
of fun on that video.
Now tell me, exactly what
is the silk and cyanide corps?
We're secret agents of adventure.
- Like James Bond.
- Exactly.
But our playground's the city.
Danger lurks around
every bend of the tunnels
and every rooftop.
Sounds like a death wish to me.
Let's see how far you went with Tina.
Slow down, Agent TNT.
I'm leading this mission.
Can't you keep up with a girl?
Shut up, bitch!
Good job.
You beat him again.
You got a temper, Edgar.
She challenged your authority.
She emasculated you
in front of the entire group.
Pay her back by making
her one of the boys?
What are you talking about?
You strangling her
and cutting off her breasts.
I didn't kill her.
Does that dress look familiar to you?
That's the dress she was murdered in.
Oh, look.
Here it is on your video.
She was alive when we left her.
- Where was that?
- At a bar.
- After our mission.
- What bar?
The Mata Hari.
Tina got hammered.
Ask Cecilia.
- Who's that, one of your secret agents?
- She's the bartender.
Mata Hari Bar
187 East 47th Street
Monday, October 15
Yeah, they were here.
They're kind of hard to miss.
They're a little overdressed
for our crowd, so...
When did they leave?
He left around 11:30, midnight.
And what about her?
Tina. Yeah, she's, uh,
she's always here till last call.
She hook up with anyone?
Well, you know, she's a hottie.
So guys are always hitting on her.
Why, is... is Tina in trouble?
Cecilia, Tina was murdered last night.
Oh... oh my God.
There... there was this guy.
He was a total dick.
He threw his beer bottle on the ground
when I cut him off.
I... I thought he was gonna hit me.
- Well... did you get him thrown out?
- No.
No, she calmed him down.
He... he was really into her though.
- Did she leave with him?
- I tried to stop her,
but he told me to piss off, so...
Okay, can you describe him?
Look, look, I don't want to get involved.
Cecilia.
You were the last person
to see Tina alive.
That guy might've killed her.
What do you want from me?
To sit down with a sketch artist.
Okay.
Yes, ma'am, you think
it's a channel 10 news anchor.
Oh, well I wrote it down
and we'll check into it, thank you.
Three hours and 238 tips later.
Half of them think it's the local news guy.
At least we know where he was
on the night of the murder.
Special victims.
Benson.
Cecilia?
Who?
The guy... the guy from last night.
The one with Tina.
- You're at the bar?
- I'm closing.
No one else is here...
Cecilia.
Liv, come here.
That's blood.
Well, when will you be done?
Cecilia's been missing for four hours.
She'll probably be dead by then.
CSU found thousands of prints at the bar
but none in blood.
- So we have no leads?
- You guys'll want to see this.
I ran your crime scene image
through symbol recognition software
and got Venus De Milo.
And that's the inspiration for these...
Which I got off the Internet.
All of these were created
by Robert Morten.
He's doing eight life terms
in Sing Sing, no parole.
Then it's a copycat.
Someone who's into Morten's artwork.
Tina Snow's arm's tied behind her.
She resembles the Venus De Milo.
Morten tortured his victims for 12 hours.
That means if this guy's serious
about copying Morten's work,
Cecilia's got eight hours left.
Let's go talk to the artist.
Sing Sing Correctional Facility
Ossining, New York
Tuesday, October 16
I'm flattered you like my work.
Perhaps I can help
if I know what you're looking for.
Your partner's name.
I worked alone.
Let me rephrase it.
Your new partner's name.
Does this motivate you?
Sorry about that.
He's a little careless.
He gets like that when women get hurt.
Women like Tina Snow,
Cecilia Strayer.
Oh, no.
They're sublime.
What I could do with those.
But obviously I'm innocent.
You mutilated women.
There's beauty in everyone.
Sometimes you have to dig deep to find it.
Women with no arms and no breasts
are so attractive?
Aren't they?
The Venus De Milo speaks to me.
It's my latest work.
Well somebody's been copying your work.
Why don't you tell us who that is?
Show me the crime scene photos
and I'll give you my critique.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
Don't touch those.
"Breslau, Klein, and Skobin."
They're your attorneys?
Read them and you'll be violating
my attorney/client privilege.
Fan letters are fair game.
Bet your copycat's been sending
you little love notes?
We got your names from this letter
you wrote Robert Morten.
Yeah, we purchased one of his paintings.
The value is gonna soar now
that it's been found at a crime scene.
We're huge fans of outsider art.
Don't you find it vital, raw?
It's sick.
Morten ever tell you about his killings?
Robert didn't kill anyone.
The new murder proves it.
Ma'am, you've written Morten every week
for the past three years
and visited him numerous times.
He's my fiance.
As soon as he's released,
we're going to get married.
He's never getting out.
We're working on appeals.
We?
The Free Robert Morten Committee.
Who else is on this committee?
I'm the president, and our
vice president is Jasper Grice.
I didn't do anything.
Associating with other convicts.
That's a parole violation, Jasper.
I haven't seen Robert since I got out.
Joining his fan club...
not that's just a violation of good sense.
He took care of me.
Three years as his cellie...
you were his bitch.
What do you want?
- Where's Cecilia?
- Who?
Okay, we know you killed Tina Snow.
What did you do with Cecilia Strayer?
We know about your special
relationship with Morten.
How do you think we got to you?
Robert told us.
- He did?
- Oh, yeah.
He told us everything.
How you killed Tina Snow
to make him look innocent.
Yeah.
Yeah, I killed her.
I killed her and I left her
in an elevator shaft.
Tied her hands behind her back.
Choked her with her own pantyhose.
Then I cut her.
Where's Cecilia?
You got a second?
- What the hell?
- It's not your guy.
- Well, he just confessed.
- His supervisor alibied him.
Grice was working off the books
loading lumber for the last two night.
He knew about the pantyhose.
We didn't release that to the press.
We got a bigger problem.
911, what's your emergency?
Detective Olivia Benson.
Better leave Robert alone
or she'll end up like that college girly.
And don't tell me...
it came from a prepaid cell phone.
Yeah, no way to trace it.
TARU said they could tell by the pitch
it's a guy but that's about all.
I don't like it.
He knew Olivia by name.
Captain, if we back off now,
Cecilia's dead.
What time did the call come in?
Right after you picked up Grice.
- He knows something.
- Let's find out what.
You gonna take me to lock-up now?
- You lied to us.
- No, I didn't.
Well, your boss told us that you were
loading lumber the night Tina died.
You pathetic wannabe.
You're a leech.
You suck up to guys who got the balls
to do what you can't?
You do however have the chance
to be a hero.
A hero? / All you have to do is
tell us where Cecilia is.
Goes right in your file.
Listen to me. That way you'll forever
be linked to Morten.
Where is she?
She's issue number 10.
What does that mean,
"issue number 10?"
Le Morte.
The graphic novel inspired by Robert.
These comic books depict the eight murders
that Robert Morten committed.
Each cover matches a photo
taken at the crime scene.
- That's really twisted.
- Not as twisted as this.
The series doesn't end at eight murders.
There are five more.
See, in the comic book,
Morten doesn't get caught.
He keeps on killing.
Check out issue 9.
Look familiar?
The cover matches Tina Snow's death.
That victim died in an elevator shaft
just like Tina.
Our murderer is staging crimes
to match these covers.
Somebody's taken up
where Morten left off.
Show him issue ten.
That's the exact same image
as the bar where Cecilia was kidnapped.
Now Morten killed his real-life victims
12 hours after he took them.
If our theory's right, Cecilia's got
two hours left to live.
Who's the sicko dreaming these up?
"Story and art by Harrison Thomas."
Grab him up and push him till he breaks.
Apartment of Harrison Thomas
580 West 44th Street
Tuesday, October 16
You can't just come in.
- You have no right.
- The warrant says we do.
On what grounds?
Tina Snow's crime scene looks
exactly like a murder in your comic book.
What.... thousands of people read
my graphic novels.
This one came out of your sick mind.
Where were you two night ago
around 2:00 am?
I was working on the next edition
with my inker.
Hey, get out of my stuff.
Oh, Ted Bundy Undies.
I don't know what's sicker,
you thinking this up or people
actually paying for it.
It's called freedom of expression.
Till somebody gets killed,
then it's called murder.
Murder is a part of our society.
It's human nature.
Unfortunately, that's why
I'm still employed.
Liv, come here.
"I take her to the only place
that feels right."
Where is this?
That's Robert's childhood home.
Upstairs, Morten's bedroom.
She's alive... barely.
Manhattan SVU, we need a bus
- at 612 West 48th Street.
- Cecilia, stay with me.
You're gonna be okay.
How are you feeling?
I'm... confused.
The last think I remember was...
working with the sketch artist.
You had GHB in your system,
and that causes amnesia.
- Was... was I raped?
- No.
But somebody attacked you with a knife.
What? Is my um...
You have some cuts on your chest
but everything's intact.
You're going to need
some plastic surgery though.
If I would've never talked to you,
none of this would've happened to me.
Oh, my God.
My life is so messed up.
This...
Cecilia, is there anybody that I can call?
Your mother or your father?
There is... no one.
Just go away.
What happened with the comic book creep?
His alibi checked.
Liv.
So he keeps selling his sick fantasies
while Tina's on a slab
and Cecilia's scarred for life?
Harrison Thomas didn't kill Tina
and he didn't attack Cecilia.
- Find out who did.
- Liv, I got your pizza.
- I didn¡¯t order a pizza.
- It's got your name on it.
Well, I'm not hungry.
Throw it out.
Hey, you gotta recycle that box.
Dude, don't you care
about the environment?
It's not empty.
There's a pie in here.
I'll eat it.
No such thing as bad pizza.
It's double pepperoni.
It's gonna kill you.
Call a bus and the bomb squad.
I'm good.
I'm just a little banged up.
You could have a concussion.
You're seeing the Doc.
We got five headed to mercy including Lake.
But most of them just have
cuts and bruises.
We're lucky nobody got killed in there.
You're off the case.
Captain, that's exactly
what this guy wants.
That bomb had your name on it.
Right, but look around.
You think taking us off the case
is gonna make him stop?
- How's your ear?
- I got two.
Bomb squad said it was a pipe bomb
made out of PVC and black powder.
Lightweight but deadly.
Yeah, except the dumb ass
didn't seat the blasting caps just right.
Captain of the bomb squad's
gonna do a floor-by-floor.
- Gonna take at least an hour.
- That's great.
Where are you going?
Somebody try to bust my eardrums,
I'm gonna bust they ass.
- You guy's okay?
- We got lucky.
You might be luckier than you think.
Similar knife blade was used
to cut both Tina Snow and Cecilia Strayer.
But Cecilia's wounds appear to taper
as they move away from the midline.
You're saying that the killer pulled away
as he cut Cecilia?
No, by the angle and depth
of these wounds
I'd say they were self-inflicted.
Cecilia cut herself?
I'd bet on it.
Captain, you've gotta let us find out.
Get yourselves cleaned up while Novak
gets a search warrant for her apartment.
Apartment of Cecilia Strayer
216 East 40th Street
Tuesday, October 16
There's trash everywhere.
This place is a dump.
Beautiful girl.
This sketch is signed "R.M."
Robert Morten.
They knew each other.
Maybe they're pen pals.
Got an awful lot of letters here,
all with the same return address...
Robert Morten.
These go back a lot of years.
Son of a bitch.
Employee ID, Breslau, Klein, and Skobin.
Cecilia worked at Robert's law firm.
Legal visits and correspondence
aren't on inmate logs.
That's why we didn't put it together.
She played us.
Cecilia was the last person
to see Tina the night she died.
She gave Tina the GHB.
She lures her down to the basement,
gets her to pick the lock, kills her,
and then covers it up
by faking her own assault.
Robert told Cecilia to kill for him.
You think he told her
to commit suicide?
Maybe it's in the letters.
"Dear Cecilia, thank you for your letter.
Your father was a good friend.
He spoke of you often.
His little sunny girly."
How did Morten know your dad?
When I was 17,
I found out my father didn't die
in a car crash
like my mother told me he did.
He was in prison for bank robbery.
"Your daddy said you had eyes
like summer
and hair as soft as lambs' wool.
You were the best thing
he ever did in his life.
I'd love to see if you look like him.
Please send me a picture."
That was a good one.
You really had her going.
She wanted it.
She drank it up like punch at the prom.
"Dearest Cecilia,
your letters are my salvation.
I don't know if I could survive
another day in here without you."
"You're the only one who can help me."
He told you to get an internship
at his law firm.
So I could visit him
without being monitored.
He needed me to help him
with his appeals.
We had complete privacy.
Complete privilege.
Sounds cozy.
Oh, it was.
She was a virgin.
I plucked her.
Robert loves me.
But he didn't want to see you anymore.
No, he was just having doubts.
I know what it's like
growing up without a father.
Wishing that you had a man
who loved you...
Unconditionally.
I used to feel like...
like there was part of me
that was missing.
I felt hollow.
And then I met Robert.
And he filled that hole.
Yeah.
But when he left you that hole
got much, much bigger.
"You'll never understand me.
You'll never truly know me,
my art, my soul...
the depths I can reach are far
beyond your shallow grasp.
If we were soul mates,
you'd be like me."
A killer.
- I never killed anyone.
- Well, I know you did.
But what I can't figure out is why Tina?
What made you pick her?
You know, she looks a lot like you.
Who were you really
trying to hurt, Cecilia?
You know what I think?
I think that you were trying to hurt yourself
when you killed Tina.
You were killing yourself.
I wish I would've died.
Tina was a gift.
An artistic offering to me.
You think Cecilia killed for you.
I can prove it.
She took trophies, didn't she?
Tina's breasts.
I know what she did with them.
I got something.
I think we have enough evidence
to charge Cecilia Strayer with murder.
Elliot, I brought you this far.
At least give me a peek.
You sick son of a bitch.
Take it easy.
Don't give him what he wants... relax.
Relax.
Take the garbage out of here.
Hey, tiger.
Let's do this again sometime.
Warner verified breast tissue
as a match to Tina.
- Where's Olivia?
- Home getting some shut-eye.
You get out of here too.
Don't need to tell me twice.
Good night.
You should be resting.
Not supposed to sleep with a concussion.
Besides, I wanted to check out
the surveillance video.
Anything?
Well, we got the guy on tape,
but the ball cap hides his face.
Hey, do me a favor. Call Liv,
give her an update. I have to go home.
My pregnant wife is looking
for peanut butter and tacos.
Dude, say no more.
Thanks, dude.
Benson.
It's Chester. I've gone over
the surveillance video a hundred times.
There's no good face shots.
He knew there were security cameras.
He planned for a shift change.
Everyone was focused on going home,
not spotting a bomber.
Yeah, nobody remembers
and ordinary pizza guy.
Hey, wait.
I got something.
There's a tattoo on the perp's neck.
It's hard to tell
but it looks like a circle...
- With a line through it?
- Yeah, you know him?
Yeah, that comic book geek
Harrison Thomas.
- He had a tat like that...
- Inside!
Bitch, I told you to leave Morten alone.
10-13 I've been stabbed!
- Hand on, Olivia. We're coming.
- He's got a knife.
Get all available units
to Detective Benson's apartment.
You'll never beat Morten.
He's smarter than all of you.
Morten's a genius.
You really beat the crap out of him.
But how many others are out there
willing to kill for him?
What does he have over them?
Morten's a sociopathic serial killer
who exploited a vulnerable girl
for his own thrill.
Cecilia never would've murdered Tina
if she hadn't met Morten.
A bad influence isn't a defense.
People V. Rosa.
A judge found a convicted pedophile
coerced Angel Rosa
into murdering his own mother.
- Rosa got off with time served.
- The svengali defense?
No, mental disease.
Like Rosa, my client
had no control of her actions.
She felt compelled to do
what Morten wanted.
Angel Rosa was 15 and the pedophile
had been sexually abusing him.
Cecilia was 17 and Morten sexually
abused her while he was incarcerated.
Is this true? / Cecilia Strayer got
an internship at Morten's law firm
so she could have booty calls
under the cloak of privilege.
- At Morten's behest.
- That's enough.
It distresses me
that attorney/client privilege
was flagrantly misused
to conduct sexual liaisons.
However, in light of case law,
I am allowing the defense of not guilty
by reason of mental disease or defect.
Trial Part 38
Tuesday, October 23
Tell us about the time
you tried to end your life.
I couldn't stop crying.
And the world had this...
dark ring around it.
I felt like it was closing in.
And how did you try to stop it?
I drank some vodka.
Thought it might make me feel better,
but it just made me more depressed.
And what did you do next?
Sometimes cutting releases the pain.
But the pain was just too much.
So I took some GHB.
I figured I'd either bleed
to death or overdose.
Either way I'd be gone.
Why did you want to die?
Robert.
Did Robert Morten tell you
to kill yourself?
He got into my head.
I kept hearing him say
that I had to kill someone...
And then I'd be free.
The pain would be gone
and everything would make sense.
Life, beauty, love.
I know this is hard,
but please...
- Show the court where you cut yourself.
- Objection!
Goes to state of mind.
I'll allow it.
Please.
Statuesque with porcelain skin.
I should've brought my sketchbook.
Did you tell Cecilia Strayer
to kill Tina Snow?
Whatever happened to foreplay?
Did you tell Cecilia to kill Tina?
No.
Did she ever tell you she was going
to kill someone for you?
No.
It's a subpoena for your testimony
as a rebuttal witness for the prosecution.
That's a new one.
- What do I get in return?
- Nothing.
And if I refuse?
We'll hold you in contempt of court.
I'm already serving
eight life sentences.
Contempt of court's
hardly gonna make it worse.
Oh...
You need me.
Or you wouldn't be here
at 10:00 on a Tuesday night.
What do you want?
Possibility of parole.
Transfer to the federal prison system.
They have better food,
better accommodation,
all together a better class occupant.
It's a win-win.
I bet Cecilia was very convincing.
Did the jury cry?
Deal.
On the gate.
We're gonna be a great team,
you and I.
Trial Part 38
Wednesday, October 24
The prosecution calls Robert Morten.
There he is!
- We love you, Robert.
- We're here for you, Robert.
Quiet. Any more outbursts
and I will clear this courtroom.
Do you swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth,
so help you God?
Absolutely.
Mr. Morten, did you ever tell the defendant
to commit murder?
Yes.
That's not what you told me.
You are under oath, Mr. Morten,
and subject to the penalty of perjury
if you do not tell the truth.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Let me ask you again.
Did you tell Cecilia Strayer to kill?
Yes. I've told many
to express themselves.
No one had the emotional
fortitude to do it until Cecilia.
- Did you tell her to buy the GHB?
- I wouldn't do that.
Did you tell her to get the knife?
Each artist's tools are their own.
I wouldn't want to influence
her artistic choices.
You think of yourself as an artist.
I think my work speaks for itself.
People's ten, Your Honor.
This is a photo of the crime scene.
Would you compare this artist's
work with your own?
Objection, the witness is not an expert.
The murder scene closely resembles
crimes perpetrated by Mr. Morten.
Who better to critique them?
I'll give you this latitude, Ms. Novak,
but don't stray far.
You may answer the question.
At first blush, you might think
this is unique.
But it... it lacks understanding...
Depth...
with the human canvas,
you have the opportunity
to do true action painting.
Where's the energy?
Where's the spatter?
This is lifeless dreck.
A cheap knock-off of my work.
Whoever did this...
is a talentless hack.
But I did this for you!
- Counselor, control your client.
- I love you.
- Order!
- Get your hands off him.
He's mine!
- It's been fun, girly.
- Mr. Morten, please!
- You're nothing like me.
- I did everything that you wanted.
I love you.
Please tell me that you love me!
- Order!
- I was right.
- You could never understand me.
Get this woman
out of my courtroom right now!
- I love you.
- Let's go. Move it.
- Get her out of here.
I love you, Robert! Please!
I love you.
I love you, please.
- Well, you were great.
- Did you like it?
Bet you didn't know
what was gonna happen next.
You put on quite a show.
You got her off.
She's going to a psych ward.
Is that a frown on your pretty face?
Actually I think Cecilia's going
exactly where she belongs.
So are you.
You're backing out on the deal.
No, you're being transferred
to a federal prison.
I thought you'd be a sore loser.
You're gonna love Florence Supermax.
23-hour lockdown.
No visitors, no mail, no phone calls.
No human contact for the rest of your life.
You can't do that to me.
Why don't you wave bye
to all your fans?
- But you made a deal.
- And it's a masterpiece.
How do you like my work?
You used me.
You set me up.
It¡¯s not fair!
This isn't right!