[Man Narrating]
In the criminal justice system...
sexually based offenses
are considered especially heinous.
In New York City, the dedicated detectives
who investigate these vicious felonies...
are members of an elite squad
known as the Special Victims Unit.
These are their stories.
[Boy Shouting]
Yeah!
[Grunts] [Laughing] That was sick, bro.
Dude, you're such a wuss.
Take your skirt off
and try it again, man.
I racked myself on that one.
Just not your night, huh?
Maybe it is.
"C" note! [Laughs] Sweet.
Come on. Let's buy some beers.
Yes, dude.
Oh, my God, they're everywhere.
One hundred
- I love this so much. Nice. Two hundred.
Oh, man.
Dude, she's dead.
Talk about putting your
money where your mouth is.
How many bills?
Five. All hundreds.
You I.D. Her? Jane Doe.
No wallet or I.D. On her.
Definitely raped.
Panties torn, bruising to the breast.
Condom lubricant
on the thighs.
- Hell of a lot of blood. She stabbed?
- Just a head laceration. Scalp wounds bleed heavily.
So she choked on the money?
I think she died of heart failure.
Found these pills in her pocket. Digoxin.
He scared her to death
by raping her.
He's going for felony murder.
Probably a prostitute, but what's
with the money-in-the-mouth thing?
I've never seen that before.
Maybe it's the perp's twisted way
of paying her.
[Man] Detectives. You got something?
Footwear impression in blood.
Not a full shoe print,
but a distinctive waffle-tread pattern.
[Benson] One of the skateboarders? Nah.
Their sneakers are flat-soled.
This is more like a rubber-soled slip-on.
Think you could track the blood?
I'm way ahead of you.
Already called for K-9.
[Man]
Let's seal off the whole floor.
[Barking]
Good boy, Barnaby.
Perp lives here, I'm pinning
my shield on the pooch.
Open up. Police.
[Locks Clicking]
What the hell do you want?
Is there anybody inside?
How is that your business?
Answer the question.
I'm alone.
[Fin] All clear. Check this out.
- There's dried blood on the sole.
- Hey. That's my purse.
This your money too?
I found it.
- You robbed a corpse.
- She was dead. There was nothing I could do to help her.
- So you helped yourself to the money?
- She couldn't take it with her.
Neither can you.
This makes exactly $5,000,
all in hundreds.
Any prints? No, just your skate
punks and little Miss Grave Robber.
Captain doesn't want the press
to know about the cash.
You run the signature
through VICAP? No matches.
We're thinking that our victim
is a prostitute.
Munch and Fin are canvassing
the working girls.
Ask if any of them use this brand.
Condom wrapper, stuck to one of the bills.
The victim's prints are on it. Took
the condom with him. Smart rapist.
I don't think there was a rapist.
This could be consensual sex
gone bad.
How'd you get that off the wrapper?
It's from The Box.
It's a sex club run by women.
Come again?
That's the idea.
It's a party where women live out
their sexual fantasies.
This place is three blocks
from the crime scene. Thanks.
[Benson]
So what, exactly, do you offer?
Oh, whatever you want. Striptease,
role-play, girl-boy, girl-girl-
No rules. But no sex acts on premises.
If you want to hook up afterwards,
that's your business.
Sounds great.
How do I join?
Well, apply with an erotic essay describing
your sexual interests, and a photo.
You keep photos
of all your members?
We destroy them
once you're accepted.
We just want to insure applicants
are height-weight proportionate.
And you definitely pass that test.
If you're worried about privacy,
don't be.
Guest lists use code names. All you
have to show is a membership card.
And what about men?
Can they join?
No, but members can bring dates...
if they're into guys.
- Ready to sign up?
- I don't think so.
We're not doing anything illegal.
Ladies, I'm not here to hassle you.
This woman was murdered last night
a couple of blocks from here.
Do either one of you recognize her?
Didn't a girl complain
that some guy got rough with her?
Our bouncer threw him out.
He was a real sadist-
whipping this girl.
She told him to stop and he
didn't. You see this happen?
No, but I got the word
to 86 the guy,
so I escorted him to the street.
He go quietly?
No. He didn't want to.
He flashed a wad of cash in my face.
You know, you can't bribe me. I showed him
the door. He kept hanging around outside.
What for? He said he was waiting for
the woman who brought him to the club.
I told him to move on.
Did he?
Not until I have him
some encouragement.
How much encouragement?
I just roughed him up a little.
I checked his bag of tricks. The freak
had cuffs, whips and a big-ass knife.
What did you do with the toys?
I gave them back.
Even the knife?
No way. Then he gave me some sob
story about needing it for work.
Says he's a chef
at that restaurant Soriello's.
This is insane.
I can't believe that little bitch
called the cops.
It was just a game.
What kind of game?
A little master-slave action.
She was lookin' for it.
She just walked up to you and begged
you to beat the crap out of her?
Yeah. With a leash
around her neck.
She said she wanted to play.
She got sassy,
so I lashed her with my crop.
She flips out, had that
security goon beat me up.
I don't get off on being hurt. So you
can dish it out but you can't take it?
- So you hung around for a little payback.
- No, I went home and put ice on my face.
Were you alone?
Yes.
Once Lola calms down,
she'll drop the charges.
And after a couple of more months
in the scene,
when her sexuality is more evolved,
she'll be ready for me.
This your Lola?
Whoa. I like it rough,
but not that rough.
And that's not Lola.
[Benson]
All right. Thanks.
I checked with The Box. Five
women use "Lola" as a code name.
Any of them African-American?
One.
Her real name is Sarah Miller.
She's an ad exec.
- Fin's checking on her whereabouts now.
- He's wasting his time.
[Phone Rings] Sarah Miller
is on a slab in the morgue.
Benson.
Thanks.
That was Fin. Sarah Miller never
showed up for work. Never checked in.
Right.
[Engine Starts]
[Knocking]
Not at home or at work.
You satisfied?
We'll find the super,
get him to let us in.
[Woman] Who is it? Who's there? Police.
Sarah Miller?
[Locks Clicking]
Yes?
I've taken six showers
since last night.
I was so upset
I couldn't even call in sick.
I didn't know what to say.
So I stayed home.
You think that man who attacked me
killed a woman?
Well, can you tell us
what he did to you?
We were flirting.
Then he got rough.
He grabbed me.
Forced me on my knees.
He pushed his crotch in my face.
And when I started to leave,
he started whipping me.
Do you remember seeing him
with any other women at the party?
After it happened,
I hid in the bathroom...
until a friend of mine
told me he was gone.
But earlier I saw him coming on
to a couple of girls.
Could she have been
one of those girls?
[Whispering]
I know her.
She kept me company
in the ladies' room.
She say if he bothered her?
You've got it wrong.
She's the bathroom attendant.
[Man]
It's Marguerite.
My daughter.
Ma petite fille.
When she didn't come home,
I thought she went straight
to her secondjob.
Where's that?
An office building on Broadway.
She was a cleaner.
Eight years.
[Sobs]
Never missed a day.
Did she suffer?
She had a massive heart attack.
It would have been very quick.
Her heart was always weak.
She had rheumatic fever,
but the doctor said
if she took her pills-
[Sobbing]
Marguerite.
We'll take you home.
[Murmuring] [Man] It's unbelievable.
Monsieur Beauclair.
Your wife called me.
I am so sorry.
Thank you.
I guess it took a murder
to finally get your attention, huh?
- And you are?
- I'm Mildred Quintana.
I run the New Americans Justice Center.
And I think it's a travesty
the police department...
doesn't care
about undocumented women.
Miss Quintana, you got it backwards. We
don't care what a victim's legal status is.
Oh, really? Then why is that sick son of
a bitch still raping women in my community?
What makes you think that all these
women were attacked by the same man?
Well, you found money
on the body, didn't you?
He's attacked 16 women
in the last three years-
and those are just the ones
I know about.
All of them undocumented cleaning
women raped on their way home from work.
So why didn't you come to us?
I tried.
I went to my precinct.
I told them women
were being attacked.
I even gave them
a description of the rapist.
Do you know what they said?
That their hands were tied
without a victim.
We can't do anything
without a complainant either.
Is there anyone who's willing to
step forward? No. They're terrified.
These women would rather suffer
than risk being deported.
Well, staying silent isn't gonna
make him stop.
Let us talk to them and explain that the
police are different from Immigration.
No, no. This is not going to work.
These women come from a place where the
police are corrupt, justice is for sale,
and no one gives a damn
about poor people.
They are not going to trust you.
Then he'll keep attacking them because
he knows they won't say anything.
You came to us.
You want us to help you?
We need their names.
[Knocking]
[Locks Clicking]
Hi. Yolanda Martinez?
Never heard of her.
Please. It's very important.
I don't know no Yolanda.
Yes, my name is Amina Asante,
but I am quite sure I have never
been a victim of a crime.
Yes, but I'd still like to talk to you.
Sorry.
Go away.
[Speaking Korean]
Please go.
Miss Zergin, it's important.
Mildred Quintana sent me.
She told you?
Yes, because she knows
that I can help you.
Come in.
I wasn't going to tell anyone,
but it hurts so much
to keep it inside.
It'll get better if you
go to counseling. I can't.
If anyone finds out
I'll be an outcast.
In my religion a woman
must be a virgin when she marries.
You're Muslim?
From Bosnia.
Do you have any family here?
My brother Milan.
Oh, you have to go before he comes
home. He's become very traditional.
Nina, I promise your brother's
not gonna find out,
but I need for you to tell me
what happened.
I can't. He's raped
a lot of women, Nina.
The one who he attacked last night died.
Please help me stop him.
I work nights,
cleaning offices.
I was on my way home,
coming up from the subway.
He dragged me into an alley.
Raped me.
Did you see his face?
I'll never forget it.
The way he looked at me afterwards-
He smiled.
Said thank you.
Then handed me cash,
like I was a prostitute.
It was more money than I make
in six months.
I lay there in that filthy alley thinking,
"At least I can pay the rent.' '
Nina, you have nothing to be ashamed of.
Then why do I feel so dirty?
Every day I think I should
burn the money.
Do you still have it?
I couldn't spend it.
Please- get it out of here.
Hold on. I'll get it.
[Door Opening]
It's my brother, Milan.
He's early.
[Man] Nina. [Speaking Bosnian]
Who are you?
Police. I'm looking for witnesses
to a hit-and-run last night.
I didn't see anything.
That's what I just told her.
Sorry.
Thank you for your help.
These bills have never been
in circulation,
so I should be able to lift
some great prints.
Spray on a little ninhydrin.
Steam accelerates the reaction.
I got your prints.
Lot of smudges.
- [Man] And three good ones.
- [Beeping]
All right, the first print's unidentified.
Probably your victim's.
- And two hits.
- Who have we got?
Tobias Gaynes.
No. Wait. He's a bonded employee
of Manhattan Bank and Trust.
- Probably a teller.
- Who's the other one?
Jason Whitaker.
Criminal record?
No. He was fingerprinted
by the Bar Association.
[Man] Come on, come on, come
on. Somebody bid into my set.
Please. Yes.
[Beeping]
Oh! Oh, nice suck-out, ass-wipe.
[Stabler] Excuse me. Oh. Online poker.
Idiot chased an inside straight draw,
and he hit it on the river.
You have me at a disadvantage.
Detective Stabler.
My partner, Detective Benson.
What can I do for the N.Y.P. D?
- Tell us where you were last night.
- Nowhere exciting, that's for sure.
- What are you guys investigating?
- Rape-homicide.
Well, uh, how did my name come up?
[Stabler] Fingerprint
hit. Oh. On what exactly?
- Money.
- The way I gamble, my print's on a lot of dough.
[Laughs]
But I'll hit a streak soon.
Back to the question.
Last night.
I'm afraid I can't answer that.
Well, it is your fingerprints on that money.
Why don't you explain it to us
or we'll bring you in?
You can't.
And I have nothing more to say.
So you thinkJason Whitaker's
your perp? My gut says no,
but, uh, he got pretty rattled when I
told him his prints were on the money.
Rattled how? He said he
couldn't talk about it.
Sounds like he's protecting
one of his clients.
No, Whitaker's prints...
were on the money because
he gave it to our rapist.
Yeah. He tries to clear himself, he's pointing
the finger at his client. He can't do that.
Can you get a client list? Yeah. You
know what firm Jason Whitaker works for?
Uh, yeah.
Granger, McCullum and Kerstetter.
Wait, wait. As in Lionel Granger? Hmm.
Hey, Lionel, have you got a sec?
What's up?
Well, I was just wondering about one of your associates
- Jason Whitaker.
Wondering if he's available?
You've got good taste, Casey.
Between you and me,
he'll make partner this year.
He's corporate, right?
Trusts and estates.
Well, just one estate-
the Duvall family.
As in Clay Duvall
of the ball bearing fortune?
Eleanor Duvall
took quite a shine toJason.
Y-You know, I've seen her
on some of the best-dressed lists.
She spends a lot on clothes, but she
gives even more of her wealth away.
Might as well.
Family's dying out.
No kids?
Just one son, Gabriel.
Probably leave it all to his
cats. He's that eccentric?
He can discuss quantum theory,
but he can't balance his checkbook.
It's a good thing
Mom's there to bail him out.
[Clock Striking]
[Woman] The portrait was
my mother-in-law's idea.
She gave it to my husband
as a wedding present.
I'm Eleanor Duvall. Nice to meet
you. Detective Elliot Stabler.
What can I do for you?
Actually, I'm looking for your son.
Gabriel?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, he hasn't lived here in years.
Huh. This address
is on his driver's license.
[Laughs] Oh, he never remembers
to update those things.
Unfortunately, he never remembers
to pay his parking tickets either.
Well, I'm not surprised.
Gabriel has all the money he needs,
and he never remembers to pay the bills.
His head is in the clouds,
or on those computers.
I'll write you a check.
Mrs. Duvall. Mrs. Duvall?
I'm sorry. He's gonna have to come
down and deal with it in person.
Yes, of course.
I'll give you his address.
I paid those tickets.
I know I did.
The canceled checks
must be here somewhere.
I should have scanned them
onto my hard drive.
You're a computer guy?
Uh-
I freelance, but this is my real work-
teaching computers how to see.
See what?
Visual data-
To process it the same way
humans do, through optical clues.
The algorithms are complex-
very hard to create.
Some people say impossible,
but I'll do it.
The canceled checks are here somewhere.
I just can't seem to find them.
We can sort this all out
down at the precinct.
I only have two hours,
then I have to get back.
Not a problem.
It'll take 15 minutes.
I have to be back by 8:00.
Promise.
Your coat?
Yes, right. My coat.
Liv, I got him.
Go get Nina.
Is Nina home?
Are you joking?
I saw you arrest her two hours ago.
What?
The police-
Coming home from work, I saw two
cops with guns put her in a car.
Did they say where they were
taking her? Why are you asking me?
You're the one who did this.
- We never had any problems until you showed up.
- We didn't take your sister.
Then who did?
The neighbors confirmed
the brother's story.
Two cops took Nina away, but there's no
arrest in the system, no outstanding warrants.
Munch and Fin talked to her boss. He
said Nina didn't show up for work tonight.
So what are we dealing with?
Impersonators? Feds?
I talked to the F.B.I.
They don't have her.
How much longer
can we keep Duvall?
We're running out of reasons to hold
him, and Elliot's running out of patience.
He's some kind of oddball genius.
Won't shut up about computers.
Once we let him go, we're never gonna
get him back here without his lawyer.
Is that him?
Is that why Nina disappeared?
Did you tell him who she is?
Miss Quintana, we really can't
discuss it. Hey, I'm not stupid.
You have a suspect.
Nina is gone.
Something terrible has happened to her.
I should never
have given you their names.
We'll find Nina,
and we'll arrest the rapist.
I have to go.
I'm late for dinner.
Got a date? And I'm hungry. I
can't disrupt my eating schedule.
I get hypoglycemic and use up
the glycogens stored in my liver.
If I don't have glucose,
my blood sugar plummets.
I'll get you something to eat.
What?
What do you want? Burger? Sandwich?
No. It's Thursday, meat loaf night.
The Gainsvort Diner blue plate special is meat
loaf, mashed potato, mushroom gravy and green beans.
But I don't eat the green beans.
I don't like green.
I'll tell you what. I'll have my
paperwork done in a few minutes.
You'll have plenty of time
for your meat loaf.
No, they run out. I have to go now.
I can't disrupt my eating schedule.
My mentation will be affected, and my
research requires absolute concentration.
Give me a few minutes. Meantime, you
want a cup of coffee, maybe a can of soda?
No, I don't want anything.
I have to go. That's my boy.
See, Gabriel's too smart for your tricks.
He's not gonna leave his D.N.A. On a soda can.
Come on, let's go.
Just being polite.
Oh, no, no. Yeah.
This is just about parking tickets.
Next time you want to talk to my
client, why don't you call me first?
I can't get a cab. I lost my wallet.
Can you take me home? Sure, sure.
You can drop me off at the diner. Have
some meat loaf with me. It's very good.
They make it with pork, beef and veal
- Is that him?
Let's go back inside. They grind
it up separately, of course.
Trichinosis
- Wait a minute. Are you talking about food?
- What the hell is wrong with you?
- Who is that woman? Why is she shouting at me?
Do I know her?
I'd remember if I'd met her.
[Whitaker] Shut up. The police may be through
with you, but I am just getting started.
- [Stabler] Stay out of this.
- You're gonna pay for what you've done.
Hey, come near my client again,
I'll have you arrested for harassment.
Oh. Do I look scared to you?
Hey, you're out of your league. Why don't
you just stick with your wetback washer women?
I'm gonna take the stairs.
You tell me when you find Nina.
Did you tell Whitaker that Nina's
an undocumented janitor? No.
Then why did he mention
wetback washer women?
Because someone's been leaking
information to Whitaker about our case.
They checked our file,
sold Nina out.
Could be anyone in this precinct
- in the department, for that matter.
I think I figured out where Nina is.
Nina.
Why did you turn me into
Immigration? I didn't.
They're deporting me
back to Bosnia.
My parents were killed in
the war, our home destroyed.
I have nothing there. You
did this. It wasn't me.
Oh, I don't believe you. Who else
could have? It was the rapist.
Nina, listen to me.
We have a suspect.
We were about to have you
make an identification.
Don't stop trusting me now.
Please get me out of here.
Nina Zergin applied for
political asylum three years ago,
but her claim was denied.
We were about to deport her
when she disappeared.
You left her alone for three years.
Why pick her up now?
We received information
linking her to a radical Islamist cell.
From where?
Anonymous tip on our hotline.
She's a cleaning woman,
not a terrorist.
Your mystery caller? That's the defense
attorney of the man who raped her.
Can you prove that?
If I could, I'd charge him
with witness tampering.
Nina still needs to be debriefed
by Homeland Security.
When she comes up clean,
will you cut her loose?
I can't. The deportation order
is legal. My hands are tied.
The Violence Against Women Act has a
provision granting temporary asylum...
to victims of crime
who cooperate with prosecutors.
You file that paperwork,
she's all yours.
Am I really legal now?
Temporarily.
After the trial I can petition
for permanent status.
Thank you.
Your help is all the thanks I need.
Did you tell Milan I was raped?
No, but you should.
[Speaking Bosnian]
Who is this?
This is A.D.A. Novak.
She's a lawyer that works with us.
You freed Nina?
It was nothing.
She never should have been locked up.
Thank you.
Ride back to the office?
[Novak]
No, take them home.
I got a stop to make.
Casey. My boss said you were interested,
but you don't waste any time.
Neither do you. Please sit
down. What can I do for you?
Bring in Gabriel Duvall for a lineup.
Who's looking at him?
The rape victim you were about to have
conveniently deported.
I got her status legalized,
so she's not going anywhere.
Where are we going tonight?
We having dinner?
Special Victims.
I made you a reservation.
I don't know.
Just take your time.
Number two.
He raped me. I'm sure.
We'll give you some privacy.
Good job.
Looks like your boy is going down. She'd
say anything to remain in this country.
She just picked my client because he's
wealthy and he's in the society pages.
We have the money. With my fingerprints
on it, not Gabriel Duvall's.
What, are you gonna charge me?
Come on, Casey. You got nothing.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Jason, they're gonna put me in jail.
Can't you do something to stop
them? Gabriel, don't worry.
You arrest my client now, the judge will
dismiss him at arraignment. Uh, Mr. Whitaker?
Mrs. Duvall, you shouldn't have come
down here. Everything's under control.
- It doesn't look under control to me.
- Mother, these detectives think I've committed a crime.
Well, Mr. Whitaker is going
to set everything straight.
Gabriel will be coming home
with us, won't he?
Let him go.
Sweetheart, are you all right?
[Gabriel] I think I have a cold. I don't
know why. I've been taking my vitamins.
Even echinacea. Well, this
place must be full of germs.
I'll have Mrs. Bianco make you
some of your favorite chicken soup.
Darling, where are your manners?
Use a handkerchief.
Gabriel, that's disgusting.
Throw it away.
[Whitaker]
Here we go.
Well, that sucks.
Maybe not.
[Woman]
Present for me?
[Stabler] That snot could close
a dozen unsolved rape cases.
There's more on this tissue
than Gabriel Duvall's mucous.
Looks like mascara
and foundation.
Marguerite Beauclair's makeup...
was smeared all over her face
when her body was found.
I'll type the cosmetic brand,
see if I can match it...
to what Marguerite used,
but I'll need extra time.
You just get us what we need
to nail this bastard.
If the tissue links Gabriel Duvall to
Marguerite's murder, the case won't go to trial.
- He'll plead out.
- Will Nina still get asylum if she doesn't have to testify?
- [Phone Rings]
- Yeah, I'm pretty sure, but I'll check with Immigration.
Novak. Sex Crimes.
Yeah, send him up.
Flowers.
- You holding out on me?
- No, I'm not seeing anyone.
If they're from Jason Whitaker,
they're going straight in the trash.
- Hey, you feel like a cup of coffee?
- Every second of every day.
Good. I'll go.
Thanks.
Yeah, Agent Tim Harriman, please.
Oh. Right. Could you have him call
Casey Novak at the D.A.' s office?
Thanks.
- [Glass Shatters]
- [Groaning]
[Sharp Groans]
No.
[Groans]
- [Glass Shatters]
- [Groaning]
Casey, I had to go three blocks
to find an open coffee shop.
If you went home, I'm gonna kill you.
[Siren Blaring]
How's she doing? Head
trauma. She's still out.
- You see anything?
- Perp was gone when I got there.
- D.A.' s office has a lot of surveillance cameras.
- I'm on it.
[Knocking]
What do you want?
You can't come here.
Let me see your hands. What's
going on? What do you want?
Give me your hands. My lawyer said
you're not allowed to talk to me.
You have to get out of here.
Now get out.
You're a smart guy, right?
Wear gloves?
Gloves? I don't wear gloves.
I don't like the way my hands feel.
Where were you tonight?
You have to leave me alone...
or I'll callJason. Go
ahead. Call your lawyer.
Call your mommy for all I care.
They can't protect you from me.
- I didn't do anything.
- Answer my question. Where were you tonight?
I just got back from the diner.
Roast chicken, creamed corn, carrots.
Shut up!
You better pray
somebody saw you there.
[Beeping]
[Door Opens, Closes]
- Hey.
- Olivia.
Hey, don't get up. It's okay.
Don't move.
What happened?
You're in the hospital.
You were attacked, Casey.
You've got a concussion
and a couple of broken ribs.
Who did this?
I was hoping that you could tell me.
But didn't anyone see?
There were so many people there.
Where?
In the squad room.
No, honey.
That was this afternoon.
You were attacked at night-
after dinner in your office.
Remember? We were talking
and I went to get coffee and-
You don't remember?
No. No, it's all blank.
It's okay, Casey.
It's okay. It's just gonna take a
while for your memory to come back.
[Sobs]
Did he- Did he rape me?
No.
Why can't I remember?
You don't have to.
We're gonna find this guy.
Elliot's at your office right now,
going through surveillance tapes.
Okay?
[Man] We got a main camera, and
then we got cameras by the elevator.
Now, your partner said Novak got a call
from Security about a flower delivery?
There he is. He signed
in. You check the log?
Just scribble.
Security guy describe him?
Doesn't remember anyone.
Prints?
Guy never took his gloves off.
Come on, Gabriel.
Show me your face.
[Man]
That your guy?
I'm from Sarajevo.
I was tortured by Karadzic's
murder squads.
I don't scare easily.
Then doing a hard 20 in Attica
shouldn't be a problem for you.
Lock me up.
It takes a real man to beat
a woman half to death.
She got what she deserved. What,
by trying to help your sister?
She made my sister untouchable.
She took away her future.
How'd she do that?
Tell me how she did that.
That lawyer forced her to relive
her humiliation in public.
Now the world knows
she's no longer a virgin.
Your sister was raped.
She's gotta deal with it.
So do you.
A man will never have her.
She shamed herself...
and our family.
So this is about you?
I got our honor back.
You got nothing back.
You have no idea what honor is.
You're no better
than the man who raped Nina.
[Grunts, Groans]
Beating that lawyer wasn't enough.
I should have killed the bitch.
My sister Nina will never testify.
[Handcuffs Ratcheting]
Elliot. In my office, now.
You barged into my son's house
in the middle of the night.
You threatened him.
I was investigating an attack
on an assistant district attorney.
Which he did not commit.
I didn't know that at the time.
But you would have,
if you had investigated.
The captain tells me that you have been
a policeman for almost 20 years.
That's commendable.
Thank you.
Do you like your job, Detective?
Yes, ma'am.
Then I suggest you stay away
from my son.
The police commissioner is a friend.
So is the mayor.
Don't make me call them.
Is there anything else,
Mrs. Duvall?
I think an apology is in order.
I'm sorry.
Not to me.
To Gabriel.
In light of the circumstances,
I think it would be inappropriate
for Detective Stabler to have...
any further contact
with your son,
but please tell him
that Detective Stabler...
is sorry for the misunderstanding.
Very well.
Good night, Detective.
Good night, ma'am.
Captain-
Save it. I probably...
would have thrown Gabriel Duvall
out the window.
We may have a bigger problem anyway.
What?
Nina Zergin. Her brother says
she doesn't want to testify.
She backs out, Gabriel walks.
I'll talk to her.
Let Novak do it.
She's not back at work. I don't
think she wants anyone to see her yet.
Exactly.
I can't speak to you.
L-I promised my brother.
I know how hard it was for you
to tell me what happened.
I know what it's done to your family.
But no matter what you decide to do,
nothing will stop me from prosecuting
the man who raped you.
What do you want me to do?
Testify in the grandjury.
Once I get an indictment,
we can arrest Gabriel Duvall.
Casey. Casey, I'm so sorry. L-
Oh, God. I heard what happened.
Why don't you save it
for someone who cares?
No joke. I'm serious. You are making
me late. I have grand jury time booked.
I don't think you'll be using it. Judge
Trillin's ordering you removed from the case.
On what grounds?
I want you as a defense witness.
[Branch]
Hell of a strategy.
Nina lost her virginity,
was afraid of what...
her traditional Muslim brother
might do if he found out,
so she lied about being raped.
Whitaker wants to use Milan's attack on me
to bolster his case.
He's violent, therefore Nina's afraid, so she made
up a story about being raped by Gabriel Duvall.
It's a compelling argument.
I can win this motion.
"A," I'm up in front ofJudge Trillin.
He loves me.
"B," the way I look,
I'm gonna get the sympathy vote.
Casey. I'm taking this case
away from you.
You can't-
Not after what I've been through.
No one wants to win this case
more than I do.
Which is exactly why
you can't try it.
Whitaker was right.
You're too emotionally involved.
I've already reassigned the case.
To who?
Tracey Kibre.
She's a homicide A.D.A.
She's not used to live victims.
Nina won't be able to relate to her.
Well, she'll have to,
'cause Tracey's putting Nina...
in the grand jury tomorrow morning.
Remember, there are no surprises
in the grandjury.
You know what I'm going to ask you,
so just answer my questions...
and everything'll be just fine.
Okay. I'm ready.
Good.
- Hi, Nina.
- Miss Novak. So glad to see you.
I just want to wish you luck.
You're up.
Okay.
Casey. I thought you were
off the case.
I am.
You looking for Kibre?
Yeah.
Warner finished the analysis
on the tissue from Gabriel's pocket.
It had more on it
than just the dead girl's makeup.
D.N.A. From her blood?
Her tears.
Go collar the son of a bitch.
[Chattering]
My mother relayed your apology,
though I do appreciate
this personal delivery...
of the proverbial olive branch.
Would you care to join me? I recommend
the pork chop, but not the peas.
Right. They're green.
Stand up.
I'm not done with my dinner.
You're done.
I thought you were ordered
to stop this harassment.
You're hurting me. You haven't
begun to see what hurt is.
Gabriel Duvall, you're under arrest
for the rape of Nina Zergin,
and for the rape-murder
of Marguerite Beauclair.
You have the right to remain silent.
If you give up that right, anything you say can
and will be used against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
[Howling]