In the criminal justice system,
sexually-based offenses
are considered especially heinous.
In New York City,
the dedicated detectives who investigate
these vicious felonies are members
of an elite squad known
as The Special Victims Unit.
These are their stories.
Hey, kid!
Stop!
Hey.
I said, stop!
Oh, my God!
What did you do to him?
Nothing.
I'm just trying to help.
Did that man hurt you?
No visible injuries on the kid.
Blood's not his.
Voucher the cloth.
We'll run DNA.
Hi, how you doing?
My name is Elliot. What's yours?
Tommy.
Hi, Tommy.
What's your last name?
Hey, what's your mom's name?
Mommy.
Okay, I'll tell you what, buddy.
We're gonna get you home, okay?
I want my daddy!
Okay, we're gonna find him.
We're gonna find him.
Tommy is been like that for an hour.
He will not let go.
The whole time at the hospital
he screamed if Elliot tried to put him down.
- He checks out okay?
- Medically,
but there's no telling what he's been
through until we find his family.
Fin, anything from missing persons?
No kids Tommy's age
are missing in the tri-state.
Patrol's going door to door,
but there's over 600 apartments
on the block where we found him.
We'll have them keep canvassing.
A three-year-old can't get too far
without somebody
in the neighborhood recognizing him.
Unless he doesn't live there.
from somewhere else
and dropped him off
on the upper west side.
Or somebody killed the parents
and didn't want to hurt the kid
so they dropped him as far away
from the crime scene as possible.
That kid could be from anywhere.
I'll call a buddy from channel 10,
see if we can't get his photo on the air.
Well we can have him
do a live story and really milk it.
Think it'll traumatize the kid?
Not if Elliot keeps holding him.
If you recognize Tommy,
please call the NYPD tip line
at the number on your screen.
This little boy needs his family.
You couldn't be more right, Detective.
And I hope one of our viewers can help.
We will keep you up to date on Tommy,
the boy with no last name.
From Manhattan SVU,
I'm Jackie Judd.
Cragen wants us to drop Tommy at ACS
and start running down leads.
I think the kid's gonna freak
if I leave him.
Well, we can't take him with us.
Well, have Fin and Lake help you out.
I'll stay here and man the phones.
Oh, Elliot, he's so exhausted.
He needs to rest.
Not to mention a bath and fresh clothes.
I'll take care of that.
STABLER RESIDENCE
72-12 CASTLESIDE STREET
GLENOAKS QUEENS, NY
THURSDAY, NOVEMBER 15
It's been a long time
since we did this, huh?
15 years.
You ready to do it all over again?
Still think it's a girl?
I haven't been wrong yet.
That's true.
But you really want a boy.
I want it healthy.
Just want a healthy baby.
Tell the truth.
Well, the little guy is cute.
I mean, you got to admit that.
We can't keep him.
I know.
He's such a good boy.
But I can't seem to keep him
in the house.
- There he is.
- Oh, Tommy!
There he is.
Come to mama.
- Ma'am, please.
- Tommy, Tommy!
- It's me, Tommy.
- Come on, ma'am.
- Sweetie, what's wrong?
- Can you get her out of here?
- Don't you know your own mother?
- Let's go.
You have to go now.
She sounded legit on the phone.
I didn't know she was from planet zero.
Right, anybody more local?
Desk sergeant's setting up another one.
All right, well, uh...
He's not gonna be part of it.
We're gonna be in here.
Is Tommy here?
Where's my son?
Sir, calm down.
I'm Detective Benson.
Can you tell me your name?
I'm Jake Keegan.
I'm Tommy's father.
And why didn't you report him missing?
I thought he was at home.
My cousin said he saw him on the news...
Where is Tommy?
Why can't I see him?
Sir, can you just give me one minute?
You're welcome to sit down here.
Elliot, check out the possible with me.
You got it.
Hey, Tommy.
I want you to jump on to that table.
Okay? Go.
Hey, look out the window.
You recognize anybody?
Daddy.
You found him.
Daddy!
Tommy, hey!
How'd you go three blocks
without anybody seeing you?
I don't know how he got the door open.
Sir, have you tried to get
in contact with your wife?
Yeah, I called Leah at home,
left a message on her cell.
She didn't answer.
Did something happen?
When we found your son
he had blood on his clothes.
Oh, God.
I gotta go home.
Okay, we'll go with you.
And your son, he should stay here.
We got a room he can play in.
Okay.
Leah must've left the door unlocked.
That explains how Tommy got out.
Leah.
- That's blood.
- Wait outside... wait outside.
I gotta find my wife.
Leah.
Oh, God... no.
I'm sorry.
There's no pulse.
That's not my wife.
Do you know who she is?
It's Jodi, our nanny.
But she was supposed to be off today.
She was raped then beaten to death.
Based on the liver temp, I'd say
time of death was around 11:00 this morning.
Forensics?
I found fresh semen on the comforter
so we've got DNA.
Gotta love a perp
who leaves a calling card.
Some old stains too.
I'll need Jake Keegan's DNA to exclude him.
Well maybe we shouldn't exclude him.
You think he did it?
He would be the first dad
trying to diddle the babysitter.
Jake.
Need to ask you
a few questions about Jodi.
Can this wait?
We need to look for Leah.
When was the last time
you spoke with your wife?
This morning when I went to work she said
she was going to be home the whole day.
Leah's credit card was used to gas up
on the New Jersey Turnpike at 12:30 pm.
Do you know of any reason
why your wife would be in Jersey?
Security camera at the toll booth shows Leah
driving with a man in the passenger seat.
She must've been kidnapped.
Is there any way we can trace the car?
We did.
It's yours.
Let's go. / No, you stay here.
Tommy needs you.
We'll call when we have any news.
Come on, I'll take you back
to the station house.
There was a second charge on the card
for a motel room in Morristown.
HOLLAND MOTEL
MORRISTOWN, NEW JERSEY
THURSDAY, NOVEMBER 15
A guy checked in alone.
He was a young guy,
kind of rough-looking.
Oh, here it is, room eight.
Give me the key.
- Police.
- Hands up where we can see them.
- What the hell?
- Show me your hands, as swipe.
- You're safe, Leah.
- Safe?
Who are you?
What do you people think you're doing?
Wait a minute... wait a minute.
- You know this guy?
- Yes, he's my boyfriend.
You have to understand.
I love my husband,
but he's a workaholic.
I was lonely.
Matt made me feel very special.
I've got to get home to my son.
Hold on.
We need to talk about Jodi.
Look, she's a nice kid.
A Mormon from Utah.
I don't know anyone
who'd want to hurt her.
End of story.
Look, please can I go home now?
You know, it would've been nice
if you were this concerned about Tommy
before you ran off to that motel.
Now you had Jodi come in
on her day off
so that you can go and screw
your boyfriend, right?
- That's it... I gotta get out of here...
- Leah, we're looking for Jodi's killer.
Now, you knew her the best
so I need you to sit back down
and answer our questions.
I'll answer yours but I'm not talking
to detective dick.
How did you find Jodi?
- We advertised in the papers.
- In Utah?
Everyone knows that Mormons
make the best nannies.
They're from big families,
they don't drink, they don't smoke...
And they speak English.
So aside from you and your husband,
who else had the key to your house?
Just Jodi.
Would she open the door
to a complete stranger?
No, absolutely not.
Utah's a far different world
than New York City.
She was from a small town
but she wasn't naive.
It must've been someone she knew.
Do you have any idea who?
I only met two friends.
They were Mormon nannies.
Becca and Kimberly.
They used to take the kids
to the playground together.
BRADBURN PLAYGROUND
435 COLUMBUS AVENUE
FRIDAY, NOVEMBER 16
Oh, my heck.
That's so awful.
Do you have any idea
who killed her?
Not yet.
She make any new friends here
in the city?
Um, a few girls at relief society
but she spent most of her free time with us.
- What about boys?
- She was engaged.
Her fiance Paul was
on his mission in Peru.
Drew, be careful.
Don't swing so far out.
That's why we're here.
When our boyfriends get home,
we'll go back to Utah.
Must be hard being so far away.
Was Jodi lonely?
If you ladies know something
you have to tell us.
Jodi was acting weird
the last few months.
She started dressing different.
Short skirts... kind of slutty.
And then she stopped
coming here to meet us.
You know where she went instead?
Nowhere... she was on
the Keegans' computer.
She said she missed Paul.
She wanted someone to talk to.
Ever go beyond talking?
We stopped by the house
one day last week
to see if she wanted
to take Tommy to the zoo.
Some man was coming out of the house
and Jodi was kissing him.
This website that she went on,
you know the name of it?
Faceunion.com.
Morales dumped the Keegan's computer
and pulled up
all of Jodi's faceunion activity.
Hot young nanny looking
for grown-up playdates.
She got a lot of emails
from three guys.
One of Jodi's playmates
is Taylor Breville,
a junior at Faulkner College.
Then there's Rafael Gardner,
also known as Casanova.
And the last one
calls himself Jesse James.
Killer name.
Who is he really?
Ah, Gilbert Matthews.
415 6th Avenue in the village.
I talked to Jodi online.
We hooked up a couple
of times last month,
but then I stopped
going over there.
Why?
We were getting busy
and when I came up for air,
this little boy was watching us.
She put him back to bed
but it creeped me out,
so I split and never went back.
Where were you yesterday morning?
At a motivational seminar in Yonkers.
Paid 250 bucks to hear Donald Trump.
- Looking for Taylor Breville.
- He's not home.
- When will he be home?
- Christmas.
Taylor's in India, semester abroad.
What's this about?
Someone's been using
his faceunion account.
Caleb, get your butt over here.
Have you been using
Taylor's computer again?
Sorry, mom.
I took his internet privileges away
after I caught him using my visa card
to pay for his Warcraft subscription.
He's incorrigible.
Please, lock him up.
Yo,Rafael.
Man, you need to really update
this photo.
Talk about bait and switch.
What's the problem?
That's me.
Yeah, 30 years ago.
- What's this about?
- Jodi Simmons.
You been chatting with her
on the internet.
You ever meet her face-to-face?
Yeah.
We had a very fulfilling relationship
on the internet,
and then she wanted home.
You bang her, Casanova?
If you mean were we intimate, yes.
- Anything else?
- Yeah, one more thing.
Did you kill her?
What?
You're saying she's dead?
She was murdered yesterday.
When did this intimacy thing happen?
We got DNA from the body.
Is it gonna match yours?
We had sex and then I left.
I would never hurt her.
We were passionately in love.
- Maybe your passion got out of hand.
- I'll say.
36 emails in eight days?
"My darling, I will make you feel
like a real woman.
Your soul will melt with my hot kiss."
That's quite a claim you're making.
What can I say?
I know what woman want.
But Jodi just wanted a hook-up.
I don't believe that.
You weren't her only playmate.
These are just a couple of guys
she was boning
when she was in love with you.
Jodi wrote to Gilbert
that his picture made her hot
and she wanted to rip off
Taylor's underwear with her teeth.
You're lying.
She loved me.
She's into young hot guys.
Not you, gramps.
- I'm not old.
- I know that, Rafael.
But young women like Jodi,
they're foolish.
She should've seen
that your love was real.
Hey...
She was lucky to have you.
She led me on, you know?
She said she wanted me.
Of course she did.
And you believed her.
So you went over
to her house to see her
and then what happened?
She laughed at me.
She slammed the door in my face.
Pushed my way in.
I was so mad.
I lost control.
I don't...
Next thing I remember...
The little boy came in...
and he's crying.
And I see what I had done and...
I ran.
I could've made her so happy.
She wouldn't even give me a chance.
All she could see was my age.
Perfect timing. Get a little DNA sample
from our buddy in there.
- Icing on the cake.
- Be happy to take a swab.
I'm sure it'll match
the semen on the sheets.
But that's not why I'm here.
Okay, what's up?
You had EMS voucher
the blood on Tommy.
- It was from Jodi.
- Figured.
Bet you didn't figure this.
I took DNA from Jake Keegan.
I also took a swab from Tommy Keegan
to prove that the blood on his face
and clothes wasn't his.
They don't share any common alleles.
Jake's not Tommy's father.
- He has the right to know.
- It's not our place to tell him.
Jake is raising a child
that isn't biologically his.
He's married to a woman
who's being unfaithful.
You think that ignorance is bliss?
First of all, Tommy is his son.
And Jake is the only father
he's ever known.
Now they love each other.
Why do you want to mess with that?
Because it's not fair to Jake or Tommy.
If Leah Keegan wants
to tell her husband that Tommy's not his,
that's her choice, not ours.
What do you mean?
Tommy's not my son?
You know, Leah and I had
some bad times together.
But I stayed... for Tommy.
And now he's not my kid.
I'm sorry you found out this way.
I don't know, is there a good way
to find out that your son isn't your child?
I used to see myself in his face.
You look happy.
When was this?
I just rented this place out at North Fork.
Great fishing.
Tommy and I would just...
spend the whole day together
out on the dock.
You know, he's look at me with this...
This love in his eyes.
That was the best week of my life.
When I got back I put
an offer in on the place.
The deal just came through last week.
I was gonna get Tommy
a little rod and reel for Christmas.
Look, it doesn't mean
that you love him less.
What happens...
when he gets older?
All he wants is his real father.
There are plenty of adopted kids that
don't care about their biological parents.
- Even the ones that do...
- I didn't adopt him.
I watched my wife give birth to him.
I cut the umbilical cord.
He was mine.
He still is.
You must have kids.
Yeah.
What if you found out that one of them
wasn't yours after all the years of
hugging them,
and holding their hands.
You know, wiping their tears.
How would you feel?
I have a doctor's appointment tomorrow
but my car is still in the shop.
- So I guess I'll ride my bike.
- Okay.
You're not listening to me.
- Sorry?
- My appointment tomorrow.
Yeah, I'll take you.
Okay.
Hey, when we were separated,
did you see anyone?
Did you?
Yeah.
Who?
I went out on a couple of dates.
No one you know.
Did you sleep with him?
- Why are you doing this?
- Just answer the question.
What is the point of all this, Elliot?
Are you asking me if this is your child?
Yeah, Liv.
KEEGAN RESIDENCE
229 WEST 72ND STREET
FRIDAY, NOVEMBER 16
Okay, so if the officers let you go,
you two gonna start acting like grown-ups?
Okay.
Yeah, all right.
We got it.
Thanks, guys.
What happened?
Matt showed up
and wanted to see Tommy.
- He's the father.
- That's what she says.
It has to be Matt.
He's the only other man I've been with.
I doubt that. This bitch cheated on me.
She cheated on you.
Don't talk about Leah that way!
We're in love.
And we have been for years.
She was gonna ask you for a divorce.
- When? After she spent all my money?
- Jake, please.
Where'd you get your clothes, huh?
The gap's not good enough for this whore.
She needs Prada and Pucci.
You even have a job?
- I'm an actor.
- You mean you're a waiter.
- I can take care of Leah.
- You can't afford her.
She spends more money on shoes
than you make in a whole year.
At least I spend time with her.
This loser is screwing my wife
and I'm paying for it.
- Hey! Hold on.
- Stop it. Stop it.
You're not getting my son.
- Okay, that's enough.
- Let go.
Daddy.
Tommy, it's okay.
Just go back to bed.
- Did you have a bad dream?
- Don't talk to my son.
- Your son?
- Stop it.
Not in front of Tommy.
Come on, sweetie.
I'll tuck you in.
Arrest this son of a bitch.
He assaulted me.
He tried to take my kid.
Arrest him.
We're gonna take you both in.
What a mess.
- It's gonna get worse.
- Yeah, how so?
Since Jake and Leah were married
when Tommy was born,
the doctrine of presumptive paternity
means that
Tommy is Jake's child
in the eyes of the law.
What about Matt?
He's the biological father.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
Legally, Jake is Tommy's father.
Matt doesn't have any rights,
not even for visitation.
- If Jake and Leah get divorced?
- It doesn't change anything.
Jake's gonna have to pay child support
for Tommy and alimony to Leah.
So let's say Matt and Leah live together.
Jake's money will be footing the bill?
Yeah.
The law looks at
what's best for the child.
So even if a woman tricks a man
into fatherhood
by secretly stopping her birth control pills
or putting a hole in the condom,
that man is still responsible
for that child.
So Leah lies to Jake,
she doesn't get punished,
but he suffers.
- What do you want to do?
- With the cross-complaint?
Well they both threw a few punches
and took a few hits.
It's a push.
Cut them loose.
Family court just called.
Matt Kramer filed for custody of Tommy.
Poor Jake. / Doesn't Matt deserve
a chance to know his kid?
- Tommy's not his kid.
- Biologically he is.
And more importantly, Tommy has a right
to know where he came from.
It's not for us to decide.
Judge wants both of you at family court
for an emergency hearing.
I gotta pick up Kathy,
bring her to the OB for a check-up.
- Elliot.
- Yeah.
What's Tommy doing here?
When I ran into Jake downstairs,
he said he was double-parked.
Asked if I could bring Tommy upstairs
for his appointment.
I don't have an appointment with him.
Tommy, why'd your dad bring you here?
Daddy went away.
Where's your mom?
Mommy went away too, like Jodi.
Leah, Jake, it's detective
Benson and Stabler.
She's gone.
Ah, damn it, Jake.
Tommy did say his father went away too.
- You thinking murder-suicide?
- Yeah.
So where's Jake?
The lake house.
It's on the North Forks.
It's about two three-hour drive from here.
Jake dropped Tommy off
a half hour ago.
I'll call the local sheriff
to watch the house.
I'm heading up there. / Hey... hey...
what about Kathy's appointment?
I forgot.
I'll take her.
- You Stabler?
- I call you too late?
What, the ambulance?
No, that was for one of my boys.
Stepped in a gopher hole,
broke his leg.
We got your guy right out back here.
He had a gun,
but my boys tackled him.
Can I talk to him?
Be my guest.
He's your prisoner.
You're right.
About what?
About Tommy.
I was up all last night
just watching him... sleep.
He's my son.
So then why'd you do it, Jake?
Leah told me she wanted a divorce.
And Matt filed for custody.
I was gonna lose Tommy.
I begged her not to take him away.
She laughed at me.
I snapped.
Man, I knew Tommy would hate me.
I couldn't live with that.
So you came here to die.
- What do you got?
- Is Jake Keegan in custody?
Yeah, you get Kathy?
- Picked her up right on time.
- Unlike some people.
Yeah, okay, well call me,
tell me what the doctor says, okay?
I will. Love you.
I love you too.
Liv, Thanks.
No problem.
Kathy.
Kathy?
SVU portable to central.
Go ahead, SVU portable.
53 at 141 and Mccombs,
the victim is a pregnant wife of an MOS.
Rush a bus and the fire department.
10-4.
Advise fire department that the victim
is pinned. Kathy.
Copy that. EMS is en route.
Oh, God.
Hurry.
Please hurry.
- We need to check you out.
- No, I'm not hurt.
- You could have a spinal injury.
- No, no... really, I'm fine.
You should go to the hospital.
Don't worry about me.
Please help her. / Jackson.
You've gotta get inside there.
Please hurry.
- You're gonna have to stay back.
- We've got a loaded bag, Cap.
- You can't go any closer.
- That's my partner's wife.
The passenger airbag didn't deploy.
It needs to be deactivated
before anybody can go in there.
I understand that. She's pregnant
and the baby could be in distress.
I'm not gonna get anybody killed here
if that bag blows up.
- How's the other driver?
- Just a scratch.
Car reeks of booze.
Wipe the tires and stabilize the vehicle.
Bag's dead.
Legs are encased...
we're gonna have to cut her out.
- Why can't you use the jaws of life?
- They will but they...
They gotta stabilize her head and neck
before we can do anything else.
Heart rate's up.
It's not enough room to get her BP.
And she's still unconscious.
- What about the baby?
- I can't tell.
Access is pretty tight over there.
I got out, I can get back in.
Watch your head.
Watch it. Let me help you.
Watch yourself... watch your head.
Good.
You gotta cut the roof.
- All right, go... let's do it.
- Okay, listen to me.
Place one hand on either side of her head
and hold her neck steady.
- Okay.
- Good.
She's waking up.
Kathy, honey.
- Kathy, try not to move.
- Olivia?
Try not to move, okay?
- Try not to move.
- What happened?
We were in an accident,
but everything's okay
and we're gonna get you out of here, okay?
Hurry.
My water broke.
- What are you doing here?
- There's been an accident.
- Who?
- I'll tell you on the way.
Department chopper's waiting on us
at the sheriff's office.
What happened?
I need you to fit this around her neck.
The chin goes here.
I'm gonna put this around your neck, okay?
Sorry... sorry, sorry, sorry.
It's a contraction.
Oh, God!
Sweetie, put your head back.
Don't move, okay?
- There you go.
- Good work.
Now keep your hands on her.
Keep her steady.
You're doing great, okay?
Kathy?
Kathy, honey? Kathy?
Uh... Look.
Blood.
She needs fluids.
- Get me an IV kit.
- Got it.
You gotta get the IV in.
I'll talk you through this.
Find the biggest vein
you can in her arm.
Okay.
I don't feel anything.
She's too dehydrated
just look for the blue.
Okay.
Okay, I got one.
Now take the needle and slide it in parallel
to her arm towards you.
When you see a flash of blood,
you got it.
- I don't see blood.
- Well push harder.
I see blood. I'm in.
Now pull out the needle.
Okay.
Tape it.
Okay, hook up the tubing.
It's connected.
Now squeeze the bag.
One... two...
One...
two...
Okay.
She's back.
- Nice work.
- Kathy, you're doing great.
All right, ma'am. Ma'am.
We're gonna need to take off the roof.
Now there's gonna be a lot of noise,
but you're not in any danger.
Here, take this coat.
Put it over her face.
Okay, we're through.
Kathy, you okay?
Are you okay, Kathy?
Oh, I'm having another contraction.
Kathy, you're doing great.
You're doing great.
Her contractions are coming
every three minutes.
There's nothing we can do.
Look, you need to give her something
to slow down the labor.
We don't carry those drugs on board.
Olivia.
Olivia. Elliot's on the line.
Here.
El...
Hey, I'm here, babe.
You doing all right?
Yeah, Olivia's taking
really good care of me.
Listen, I'm on my way.
We're taking a chopper.
I'll be with you soon.
I love you.
I can't hear you.
I love you too.
Okay, Cap.
All right, we're ready now.
Now just try and stay still, ma'am.
This baby is coming now.
I can't help it.
- My legs.
- And we're gonna get you out of here.
We're gonna get you out.
Okay, we're ready to go.
Oh, they're getting stronger.
Now squeeze my hand.
You're gonna squeeze my hand
and you're not gonna let go, okay?
We are gonna do this.
We're gonna get you out
in two seconds now.
- Okay, Kathy...
- Hang in there.
You're doing great. You're doing great.
Hang in there, honey.
Almost there, honey.
Almost there.
There you go.
Okay, legs are free.
I'm gonna need you to exit the vehicle
so we can get the long
spine board in here, all right?
No, Olivia, don't leave me.
Sweetheart, I'm gonna be right here.
I'm gonna be right next to you.
You're gonna be okay.
You got her?
Come on, come on.
Nice and easy, guys.
Now ma'am, I'm gonna lean you forward
just a little bit, okay?
- There we go.
- Nice and slow.
Good, good.
You got her?
All right, she's out.
Strap her in, guys.
Take it easy. Nice and easy.
Be gentle.
Okay, honey.
We're almost there.
All right, take it easy.
Are we ready?
All right, it's almost over.
Just try to stay still, okay?
All right, on three.
One... two... three.
Easy, guys.
Easy, easy.
All right, bring her down slow.
Bring her down slow.
- I'm right here, Kathy. I got it.
- Let's get her to the bus.
- Come on, let's go.
- I'm right here, honey.
I'm right here.
You're doing great.
She's lost a lot of blood.
Patrol is holding traffic at every cross
street between here and mercy.
You'll be to the hospital in ten minutes.
Try to stay still.
This baby is coming now.
Just hold on ten minutes.
I can't.
Go.
Unbuckle her.
We have to keep her airway clear.
She's fully dilated
and the baby's crowning.
Get behind her and let her
push against you. / Okay.
I'm right here.
- I'm right here.
- Okay, push.
You're doing great, Kathy.
You're doing great.
Okay, I can see the head.
I can see the head.
- You're doing great. You're doing great.
- Breathe. Come on, breathe.
Okay...
push.
That's it, baby.
Keep pushing.
The shoulders are almost out, honey.
Push.
- One more push. One more push.
- Okay. Okay.
Good... good girl.
Good girl.
That's it.
Hey, that's it.
Baby's out.
It's a boy.
We did it, we did it.
You did it, you did it.
You did it.
Kathy... Kathy...
- What's happening?
- Her BP's crashing.
She needs O2 and more fluids.
Call it in.
Keep the baby warm.
Proceed. Patient is coding.
Please advise.
Proceed with full code protocol.
I'm pushing epi now.
Trauma route 3, standing by.
Copy that.
Trauma route 3.
Elliot.
It's a boy.
Hey little man,
welcome to the world.
I'm your daddy.
You are his father.
I know.
How's the baby?
Great.
Pick a name?
Kathy wants to name him after me.
Just what the world needs,
another Elliot Stabler.