In the criminal justice system,
sexually-based offenses
are considered especially heinous.
In New York City,
the dedicated detectives who investigate
these vicious felonies are members
of an elite squad known
as The Special Victims Unit.
These are their stories.
Push it back, Frankie.
Push it back.
It's coming out of
that apartment down the hall.
Engine 99 to command, we got a fire
and a taxpayer on the first floor.
Hallway's knocked down.
We're going in.
Come on, baby.
Open up for me.
Let's get it done, ladies.
10-45 in the bedroom.
Command 99.
We need EMS on scene.
She's not breathing.
No pulse.
Engine 99.
10-45. Code one.
Send a Fire Marshal and PD.
Frankie, cut the hose
so we can get her out.
On my count.
1, 2, 3, go!
Stabler. Special Victims.
Was she dead
when you found her?
Yeah. Nobody could survive that smoke
for more than a couple of minutes.
What makes you think
she was raped?
Her panties were pulled down
and her dress was ripped.
She had a big gash on her head.
Must have been unconscious
when the fire started.
Thanks.
Any luck?
Yeah, I got a name.
Jenna Ludlow. 25.
She lived here a couple of months.
Kept to herself.
Nobody heard any screaming
or fighting last night.
So he raped her, knocked her out,
lit the place up to finish her off?
No, she was dead before the fire.
There's no soot
in Miss Ludlow's nostrils.
CSU find a murder weapon?
There was a lamp on the floor
next to Jenna's body.
Perp must have bashed
her head in with it.
You guys are this good,
what do you need me for?
Other than to turn the world on
with your smile, how about a pelvic?
Done. Fluids present.
And there's thick mucus
at the cervical os.
She has an STD?
No. Bun in the oven.
From the looks of her belly,
she wasn't too far along.
Wonder if Jenna knew
she was pregnant.
크리스 멜로니
(엘리엇 스테이블러 형사 役)
딕테이션
이근양(kylee322@nate.com)
싱크편집
최자앵(ashaa@nate.com)
마리슈카 하지테이
(올리비아 벤슨 형사 役)
한글번역
(@nate.com)
리차드 벨저
(존 먼치 형사 役)
다이안 닐
(케이시 노박 검사 役)
아이스-티
(오다핀 "핀" 튜튜올라 형사 役)
아담 비치
(체스터 레이크 형사 役)
B.D. 왕
(FBI 정신분석의 조지 황 役)
타마라 튜니
(멜린다 워너 검시관 役)
댄 플로렉
(돈 크레이건 경감 役)
Law & Order SVU
9x18. Trade
번역수정
박수진(cafelattte@hotmail.com)
한글교정
임재영(dreamimage@nate.com)
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON NBC:  2008/05/06
Is anything salvageable?
Whatever traces evidence wasn't burned
the fire boys washed away.
And we get hosed.
We'll gather and sift,
but I hope you find a good witness.
Prada shoes. Gucci.
She was living the life.
All good things come to an end.
Eddie Brancato,
Fire Marshal.
Shame about these oak ceilings.
Varnish is a natural accelerant.
You light them up. These beams are
like fuses on a Roman candle.
Where'd the fire start?
Right here.
And it was no accident.
I don't see any signs
of an accelerant.
That's because you're looking
at what's here.
Now look for what's missing.
Drapes.
Destroyed.
Actually after the fire bug lit them up.
Any idea what he used?
It's in the air, Detective.
The nose knows.
- Alcohol.
- Jellied methyl alcohol.
Otherwise known as Sterno.
Your victim kept it under the sink.
Two pack.
- Missing a can.
- Hey. Check this out in the kitchen.
What do you got?
Dishwasher was shut.
Contents untouched by fire or water.
- Maybe we just got lucky.
- Jenna had company last night.
Those glasses could have been
sitting there for a week.
A single woman with a full-time job?
Trust me.
Well... digs like these?
Must have been some job.
Found a site where Jenna
advertised her services.
This discount suit cost 250 bucks
at Morty's suits for less.
But with my personal touch,
you can look like you spent two grand.
Size doesn't matter, guys.
The size of your budget, that is.
I'm Jenna Ludlow,
and I'm gonna help you dress... to kill.
Dress to kill... too bad
she didn't get to help Munch.
Are you insulting
my sartorial splendor?
- Well, if that means clothes, yes.
- Easy, fellas.
Now, what kind of a living
could Jenna make being a stylist?
With the right clientele, big bucks.
She only had $300
in her business account.
I'm not surprised,
with all those Gucci bags in her closet.
I don't know how
she could have afforded them.
She hasn't made
any deposits in months.
Cause someone else has been
making them into her personal account.
Ten large wired in
for the last three months.
- From where?
- Liechtenstein.
Yeah.
Conveniently untraceable.
Jenna had an offshore sugar daddy.
Payments started right about the time
Jenna must have got herself knocked up.
So she blackmails him
with the baby.
He comes over, they fight,
he rapes her, he kills her.
Well, how do we find
count Liechtenstein?
Go to heaven.
Heaven Moskowitz.
Jenna's been writing her a check
every week for 200 bucks,
and the memo line
reads "therapy".
Heaven only knows
who Jenna was sleeping with.
I can't talk to you about Jenna.
Doctor/Patient privilege.
- You're a doctor of... what?
- Angel healing.
You got a license to practice?
I'm certified by a higher authority.
I'm sorry, but cherubim
don't have legal standing in this state.
What Jenna and I discuss in this room
is between us and the angels.
What's this about?
I guess you didn't get
the 411 from on high.
Jenna was murdered this morning.
No, it can't be.
It's before her time.
It usually is in our line of work.
Your guardian angel is supposed
to protect you from untimely death.
You see, that's the problem
with guardian angels.
They're never around
when you need them.
I know you think this is a big joke.
But Jenna believed.
I taught her how to speak to the angels.
About what?
Her future.
Jenna had a choice to make.
Together, we asked
the angels for help.
What choice?
I don't listen to words.
I... feel them and spirit them
to the other side.
You feel anything about
Jenna having a boyfriend?
I see... Africa.
Possibly Ethiopia.
Great body.
Is his name Fabio?
Pierson.
Six million people in this city.
And Pierson is the best your angels can do?
Okay. Cleopatra says to try
the commodities exchange.
EASTERN COMMODITIES ECXHANGE
249 VESEY STREET
MONDAY, JUNE 4
What's special victims unit
doing down here?
We're looking for
somebody named Pierson.
A first name would really help.
We think he's African,
maybe from Ethiopia.
And we were told
that he has a great body.
Ethiopian? A great body?
Someone's yanking your chain.
Sounds like your guy trades coffee,
so you're probably talking
about Pierson Bartlett.
Okay, what can you
tell us about him?
Fourth generation
coffee trader.
Family had seats here in the exchange
since it was founded.
You see him around here?
No. But he might be
up in the grading room.
Looks like the world's
greatest coffee break.
They're all traders.
They sample the coffee and cocoa
to make sure it's up to trading standards.
- There's Pierson Bartlett over there.
- Thanks.
- Mr. Bartlett.
- Hold on. Last cup.
- Great body.
- Excuse me?
The coffee.
But I'll bet yours is...
smooth and robust.
I didn't catch your name?
Detective Benson.
I'm Detective Stabler.
- What can I do for you?
- Tell us about Jenna Ludlow.
Why? / She was found
murdered this morning.
Oh, my God.
Jenna?
How do you know her?
She's my son PJ's fiancee.
They met when Jenna temped
in our office.
- And where is he now?
- Brazil.
That's... where most coffee is grown.
PJ works with me.
He took our corporate jet down
there on business last week.
Well, can you get him back here?
We need to ask him some questions.
He'll want to come home right away.
Oh, but, you know, Rio's a ten-hour flight,
so it won't be before tomorrow.
Well, we'd appreciate
a heads-up when he lands.
Yeah.
I'll call when I know.
CRIME LAB ONE POLICE PLAZA
MONDAY, JUNE 4
Dad's story checks out.
The Rio airport confirms
that Bartlett’s plane has been
parked there since last Tuesday.
I wonder if PJ knew about the baby.
Don't know about him,
but Jenna was planning to keep it.
How do you know that?
High levels of folic acid
in her system.
- She was taking prenatal.
- You got a lunch date with Ryan?
Special delivery.
Anyone you like for Jenna's murder?
Well, fiance was out of the country,
so probably a stranger,
maybe a push-in rapist?
I don't think so.
That's why you brought
over Jenna's clothes?
They were torn to shreds,
but there wasn't a mark on her...
no cuts, no bruises.
Nothing on her skin that
matched up with those tears.
- So I asked Ryan to take a look.
- Check it out.
Okay, so the tears start out smooth.
They get ragged at the ends.
Your perp used scissors
to start each tear,
then ripped it the rest
of the way by hand.
After he killed Jenna,
to make it look like a stranger raped her.
Because it was someone she knew
well enough to have sex with.
Let's make sure our fiance
didn't jet back here for a booty call.
"November-Six-Eight-Tango
-Five-Delta."
Left last Tuesday for Rio
and hasn't returned. / You're sure.
Aircraft just can't fly into
American Airspace willy-nilly.
They have to file
a return flight plan.
Did they file one for today?
Not until early this morning.
Mr. Bartlett's plane was scheduled
to depart Rio at 0600, local time,
which puts them in here at...
- Something wrong?
- Weird.
They should be landing
just before 3:00 this afternoon.
But they scheduled
a refueling stop... in Aruba.
Why's that weird?
Their G-4 can fly from here
to Tokyo without a pit stop.
Rio's a lot closer.
Your victim has some record.
Arrests? / Employment.
Jenna was a job hopper.
Temp agency said she never worked
anywhere for more than two months.
- She was fired?
- No. She'd request transfers.
"Receptionist at a White-Shore Law Firm.
Secretary to a plastic surgeon.
Event planner for a
Fortune 500 company."
All jobs where she
could meet rich men.
Looks like Jenna
was shopping for a husband.
And when she didn't find Mr. Right,
she'd move on.
Her last gig was at the Commodities
Exchange working for the Bartletts.
She may not have had a nose for coffee,
but she sure could smell money.
And she went after it
any way she could.
One guy dumped her, and she
sued him for breach of promise.
She could do that?
Be careful, my brother.
Being a player can be very, very costly.
Park Avenue surgeon proposed,
then he broke off the engagement.
Find out about her past?
Girl went wild. Jenna logged
a lot of hours at spring break.
Apparently, she's
into girl-on-girl action.
Not quite the pedigree
for a society doctor's wife.
The court let him off the hook,
but they let her keep
the engagement ring
for pain and suffering...
2 karat rock.
Big payday for getting jilted.
She was up for an even bigger on.
The Bartletts' net worth
is about a quarter of a billion dollars.
Our little gold digger
caught herself quite a big fish.
You think PJ killed her
to get off the hook?
You know, he should be landing soon.
Why don't we go pick him up
at the airport?
Thanks for the heads-up
you promised.
Sorry.
It slipped my mind.
Right. Hand your passport
to the customs officer.
What's going on here, Dad?
They're police officers, PJ.
My son and I are grieving.
You can talk to him tomorrow.
The last entry stamp in here
is for Aruba.
- There's nothing for Brazil.
- Oh!
So you were never in Rio.
You sent him to Aruba yesterday
after we told you Jenna was dead, huh?
So your plane could pick him up and
make it look like he was in Rio all along.
- Wait, I... I didn't kill Jenna.
- Let's go.
You're not taking my son anywhere.
So we'll take you both.
- For what?
- Obstruction of justice.
We don't have enough
to charge PJ with Jenna's murder.
Well, if we hadn't collared him,
that jet would be on its way back
to Brazil with both Bartletts on board.
So now they're just gonna waltz out
the front door of the courthouse
after a judge slaps them on the wrist
for the obstruction charge.
I think that PJ's soft.
We grill, and he'll give it up.
You think?
Because I think once you mention murder,
Richie Rich and Daddy Starbucks out there
are gonna lawyer up.
So what's your plan?
You guys are gonna get what we need
to charge PJ with Jenna's homicide
while you and I do
a little legal tap dance.
Casey, it's 2:00 in the morning.
You can't just snap your fingers
and expect us to PJ to Jenna's murder.
Well, then PJ walks.
It's your choice.
Let's wake up O'Halloran,
see what he can give us.
Why don't you call Munch, tell him to haul
his ass out of bed and get down here.
I apologize for the inconvenience.
My detectives were a little overzealous.
- So we're free to go.
- Yes. I voided your arrests.
It's as if none of this ever happened.
We still need to talk to you
about your relationship with Jenna.
I'll send detectives
to the exchange tomorrow.
In front of everyone?
Unless you'd rather answer
a few questions now.
Sergeant Munch, would you take
the Bartletts up to the lounge, please?
Yeah, but can I put on a pot of coffee
first, for the love of all things holy?
Gentlemen, could you please
have a seat upstairs?
As long as it doesn't take forever.
We've got a conference call
with Addis Ababa at the crack of dawn.
- We'll stall as long as we can.
- Good.
Any progress?
Warner called. She has the preliminary
DNA matches on Jenna's fetus.
PJ's the father.
What about the semen inside Jenna?
Confirmed match.
Also PJ's.
How did Warner know
that DNA belongs to PJ?
Wine glass from Jenna's apartment.
I pulled epithelial cells
from one of his fingerprints.
They show up in the system?
SEC prints all traders
before they're bonded.
So PJ and Jenna were having
a romantic glass of wine
before he whacked her
and faked the rape.
Tox screen didn't show
any alcohol in Jenna's system.
She probably wouldn't drink
when she's pregnant.
Explains why the second glass
and Jenna's prints
and nothing but cranberry juice.
Did you get any genetic material
off the lamp?
If there was any,
fire hoses washed it away.
- We're screwed.
- Oh, ye of little faith.
- I got something else to show you.
- Well, make it quick.
Munch has the Bartletts on ice back
at the station, and the clock's running.
It's, uh, 4:00 in the morning.
Are we done here?
I'm sorry. I have to ask you
a few more questions.
Can't you people afford anything
better than this high-acid crap?
Another shining example
of your taxpayer dollars at work.
This stuff is so vile, we won't
even trade it on the exchange.
You know, I took a coffee appreciation
course at the learning Annex,
and it turned out it was just
a bunch of Barista wannabes.
Yeah, those national chains
have ruined the American palate for coffee.
Can I ask you a question?
How do you make
a good cup of Joe?
Well, it starts with
the right water-to-bean ratio.
You can't rush the process.
CRIME LAB
ONE POLICE PLAZA
WEDNESDAY, JUNE 6
We sifted through the ashes
and found something interesting
on the desk in Jenna's apartment.
Everything there was burned
to a crisp.
What are you gonna do,
read a piece of toast?
Even burnt toast still
has bread underneath.
Put a charred piece of paper
between two photographic plates.
Keep them away from light
and develop the film.
And if you're lucky,
you get a negative
from which you can create
a photo duplicate of the original document.
credit card receipt.
Complete with Jenna's signature.
This receipt's one of the
few we found intact.
Most of the others
are in fragments.
But maybe there's something
you can use.
"By and between
the parties Jenna Ann Ludlow
and Pierson David Bartlett, Jr.
whereas the parties intend to be married
- and wish to enter this agreement..."
- It's a prenup.
It makes sense.
PJ was bringing home the coffee.
He wanted to protect his beans.
Or Daddy insisted on it.
I didn't insist that PJ get a prenup.
I just... suggested.
I bet your suggestions sound
an awful lot like orders.
I don't interfere
with my son's personal life.
Orders are for business.
Oh, I think this was business.
Your son got Jenna Ludlow pregnant.
Now, was she pressuring him
into marriage?
Getting married was...
was my idea.
So you have wine.
You make love to soften her up.
And then you lay the prenup on her.
It didn't work.
Uh...
She went ballistic.
She...
she said, "I'm gonna be the mother
of your child, you don't trust me?"
I guess ten grand a month just wasn't
enough for Jenna anymore, hmm?
PJ was wiring her money?
From one of your tax shelter accounts.
By the way, the IRS
says that those are illegal.
We were just trying
to put aside some cash.
Well, Jenna and her baby
were gonna cost you plenty.
Y... you think that my son murdered
his fiancee just to save a few bucks?
I think you found out about the baby.
And Jenna was gonna bleed
PJ for child support.
You didn't want her getting her
hooks into half your company.
So you told PJ to handle it.
No. / But you didn't think
that he would kill her.
And when he told you what he did,
you hustled him onto the first
plane out of the country.
Dad had nothing to do with it.
Going to Aruba was my idea.
Okay, look, I can help you out here.
But you've gotta cowboy up
and tell me everything.
Uh... after we fought
about the... the prenup,
Jenna threw me out.
I just wanted to get away.
Uh... we have a house in Aruba.
I asked dad if I could take the jet.
But it was in Rio, so he...
he drove me to the airport,
and he bought me a plane ticket.
And you didn't know
what happened to Jenna.
I swear, when I left her apartment,
she was still alive.
I wouldn't kill Jenna.
I loved her.
Don't say another word, PJ
Avery Hemmings.
How dare you interrogate my client
without counsel present.
Your client didn't ask for counsel.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- What did you tell them?
- The truth. I didn't do it.
You should have called me, PJ.
You defend PJ often?
We've been friends since college.
Their friendship explains
why she took his murder case.
Miss Hemming usually tries
SEC violations in federal court.
Well, she's in over her head
on this one.
Junior's DNA matches
the semen in Jenna and her fetus.
No, it doesn't.
PJ's DNA only matches the semen.
I jumped the gun.
Who's the baby's father?
Congratulations, PJ.
You were gonna be a big brother.
- What?
- If this is some kind of trick...
No. No trick.
DNA proves it.
Big Pierson here's
Jenna's baby daddy.
You screwed her?
You slept with my fiancee,
you son of a bitch?
I was drunk. She came on to me.
I never meant for it...
Hey. Hey, you... hey.
Take it easy.
Come on, back off.
Oh, God.
Somebody call an ambulance.
After what you did today, I should file
a complaint with the ethics committee.
You're lucky your cheap stunt
didn't kill my client.
We didn't throw PJ through that window.
His father did.
After your detectives baited them
so they'd turn on each other.
I need to see PJ
I've got to apologize.
He doesn't want to talk to you.
Then convince him... please.
All right.
I'll try.
Any more shenanigans, and I'll make sure
you spend the rest of your short career
tied up in lawsuits.
My son and I have had our problems,
Miss Novak, but he's not a killer.
I'm beginning to think he's right.
Are we looking
at the wrong Bartlett?
Well, marrying PJ
would make Jenna very rich.
But a paternity suit against Pierson Sr's
like hitting the mega millions.
Look at them.
He pushes his kid through a pane of glass,
and they're still thick as thieves.
There's no way
we're gonna split them up.
Then find something
that ties dad to Jenna's murder.
APARTMENT OF JENNA LUDLOW
450 WEST 22ND STREET
WEDNESDAY, JUNE 6
Soot is a natural fingerprint dust
under the right conditions. / Which are...
Any smooth surface that wasn't
hosed down during the fire.
Bathroom's the only room
that was spared. / Okay. Any luck?
Not yet.
But I put our chances at slim to none.
Well, Pierson Bartlett was here the night
Jenna died, so...
you gotta give me something.
You may have to settle
for more burnt toast.
Just another batch of photos
from the burnt papers on Jenna's desk.
So some more receipts,
phone bill, catalog.
What is it?
You're sure this stuff
came off the desk.
Yeah. Why?
- We were wrong.
- About what?
Why Jenna Ludlow was killed,
and who did it.
So you're dropping
the charges against my client.
In your dreams. I'm charging you both with
conspiracy to commit murder.
Conspiracy... this is insane.
Your divide and conquer strategy
blows up in your face,
and now they did it together?
You're gunning for disbarment.
Read them and weep.
Where did you get this?
It rose from the ashes
of your fiancee's apartment.
What is it?
It's a printed email about the Bartlett's
top-secret plans
to buy a coffee plantation
in El Salvador.
Apparently, their coffee's such a find,
it's going to make them even richer.
You wanna tell me
how Jenna got this?
You let that tramp
get her hands on this?
Well, she must have stolen it
from my briefcase.
- How can you be that stupid?
- Shut up.
Both of you.
Not only was Jenna
going to have your baby,
she was threatening to spill
the beans on your big deal.
Mr. Bartlett, you're
going to need your own attorney.
TRIAL PART 17
MONDAY, AUGUST 6
How long have you been in the coffee
trading business, Mr. Bartlett?
40 years. My great-grandfather
started the company in 1896.
Uh... this... was his cupping spoon.
I still use it to sample and grade coffee.
People's three.
You recognize it?
Yes. That's an email about our plan
to purchase a coffee plantation.
What's so special
about this email?
Nothing. It's just a piece of routine
business correspondence.
And yet the DA thinks
you killed Jenna Ludlow
in some sinister plot to silence her
when she got hold of it.
Sounds like something
out of a trashy beach novel.
Mr. Bartlett, did you have anything to do
with the murder of Jenna Ludlow?
No. / Thank you.
Nothing further.
What kind of coffee grows
on this plantation, Mr. Bartlett?
It's a new Arabica hybrid.
Mild, low caffeine,
class-one quality.
How much would you stand to make
if it were successful?
Oh, it depends on whether our beans
were picked up by one of the big chains.
Would it be fair to say
in the many millions?
From your lips to God's ears.
So if some competitor learned
about your special coffee beans
and bought the plantation
out from under you,
it would be a financial disaster.
We'd lose our initial investment.
And the millions
you stand to make.
Jenna Ludlow stole that email and
threatened to sell your trade secrets
- unless you paid her off, didn't she?
- That's not true.
But $10,000 a month
in hush money wasn't enough.
Like all blackmailers, Jenna got greedy,
so there was only one way to stop her.
Jenna wasn't blackmailing us.
That's not what that money was for.
What was it for then?
It was for the baby.
When did you start negotiating to buy
that coffee plantation in El Salvador?
February.
February 10th,
according to the email.
When did Jenna
tell you she was pregnant?
Uh, Valentine's day.
That's why I proposed.
People's exhibit ten.
The autopsy report on Jenna Ludlow.
Could you please read
the highlighted passage?
"Examination of victim's
uterus reveals a fetus,
estimated age...
ten weeks."
- She wasn't pregnant yet.
- Jenna lied to you.
She wasn't pregnant in February
when you started paying her off.
Jenna didn't get knocked up
until late March... By your father.
PJ, I got more news for you.
People's 18. The report from the lab
on the semen found inside Jenna's body.
"DNA testing confirms fluids are
from Pierson Bartlett Junior."
Note that sperm are immotile.
PJ, did you know
that you were shooting blanks?
- Objection, Your Honor.
- Overruled.
You're wrong. / I'm sorry, PJ
you've just got funky sperm.
Jenna was pretending she was pregnant
because you couldn't deliver the goods.
Then she figured, hey, why settle for you
when I can bang daddy and really rake it in?
- Your Honor, please, she's testifying...
- Jenna loved me.
No, Jenna loved your family's money.
And she hit the trifecta.
Marrying you,
having daddy's baby,
and learning the secret plans
to buy the plantation.
I mean, you and dad had no choice
but to solve the Jenna problem,
so what'd you do?
Did you plan it over a late-night latte?
- I didn't kill Jenna.
- Oh, so you're saying that he did it.
- Stay strong, son.
- Be quiet, Mr. Bartlett.
Did your father kill Jenna Ludlow?
No, he wouldn't... do that.
I bet you didn't think
he'd screw your fiancee either.
Did he kill Jenna?
Uh... I don't know.
PJ... please.
Mr. Bartlett,
I am not warning you again.
- I put you on that plane.
- Mr. Bartlett.
- I did everything I could to save you.
- Mr. Bartlett, please.
- Why are you doing this?
- Counselor, control your client.
Thank you.
There's nothing further, Your Honor.
I've seen CEOs who rape their employees'
pension funds get better treatment than this.
You're the one who screwed your client.
Did you even read the autopsy report?
Of course I read it.
Then maybe you should go back
to defending white collar criminals,
because a first-year law student
wouldn't miss the age of Jenna's fetus.
The trial's not over yet.
Oh, yes, it is. Only question is
how long the jury's out.
TRIAL PART 17
WEDNESDAY, AUGUST 22
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
you've been deliberating for nine days.
Would further deliberation
Help you reach a unanimous verdict?
No, Your Honor. We've been
hopelessly deadlocked from day one.
Then I have no choice
but to declare a mistrial.
Defendants are free on posted bail.
This court is adjourned.
We're refilling immediately.
Why waste everyone's time?
The verdict's not gonna change.
Hey, Dana, wait up.
Hey, Case, tough break.
You almost had him.
Yeah, 11 to 1 to convict.
You have any idea what
the hell happened in there?
Yeah.
You had one crazy-ass jury.
Crazy how?
Day one, I bring them lunch.
Everything's hunky-dory.
Second day,
they're all screaming.
At each other?
No, at the holdout.
Juror number four.
I felt sorry for her.
You took pity on the moron
who screwed my case?
Not for that. She's a single mom
with a disabled kid.
APARTMENT OF DEBRA JACKSON
712 WEST 181ST STREET
WEDNESDAY, AUGUST 22
Devon has cerebral palsy.
It must be tough.
We get by.
Why are you here?
I checked your bank account.
You deposited $25,000
the day the jury started deliberating.
And another $25,000 this morning.
I got an interest-only mortgage.
And I was doing fine.
Until the rates went up.
We lose this place,
we got nowhere to go.
And Devon can't live
in a homeless shelter.
He's gonna go to foster care
while you do 4 and 1/2 years in prison
for selling your not guilty vote.
I know it was wrong.
But I was trapped.
They were gonna foreclose
on us next month. Please... Miss Novak.
You tell me what happened,
and I'll cut you a deal.
You won't spend a day in jail.
The night we got the case,
a man called.
Said he knew all about my money problems
and that he could help.
Did he tell you his name?
Roger Fromm.
He's a private investigator.
- Get away from the shredder.
- Who are you?
- Police.
- Where's Roger Fromm?
He retired.
- When?
- About three hours ago.
Said he's just come into some money,
told me to shred all his records
and gave me a lousy thousand bucks.
Where'd he retire to?
The Dominican Republic.
This is a cross-cutter.
Everything in there is gone for good.
Here's a deal.
You're going to prison unless you
tell us who your boss was working for.
You think that cheap bastard
told me anything about his business?
I just answered the phones.
He never brought any clients
into this dump.
I know who paid him.
Pierson Bartlett.
I didn't bribe anyone.
No, that $50,000 payment
to juror number four was charity.
Your errand boy took care
of the bribery part.
Roger Fromm? / Your former
vice president of security.
I fired him four years ago.
He couldn't keep his mouth off
the business end of a bottle.
So now he's your personal bagman.
Is Mr. Fromm prepared
to testify against my client?
We have a sworn statement
from the juror he bribed.
But you don't have Fromm.
Come on, Pierson.
- We're not done here.
- Yes, we are.
Hey.
Take that steak dinner now.
Ouch. What was the bet?
That Roger Fromm
erased his computer memory.
He deleted the files,
but he forgot to scrub the hard drive.
- That's not Jenna.
- Yeah, but that's PJ.
How many more of these you got?
Hundreds.
With dozens of different girls.
Bartlett had his old crony tailing PJ.
Full-time for years.
So why is dad stalking his son?
Well, why don't you ask PJ?
His lawyer's never gonna
let us question him.
But you're not interviewing him
as a perp.
Stalking makes him a special victim.
TOWNHOUSE OF P.J. BARTLETT
49 EAST 69TH STREET
WEDNESDAY, AUGUST 22
So my father had me under surveillance.
Any idea why he'd do that?
Uh, sure.
He's a control freak.
And he has to be the boss
of everyone and everything.
Your father strikes me as somebody
who's used to getting what he wants.
Well, he did from me.
I wanted to be a painter, but ...
he made me go into the coffee business,
and he made Jenna get into his bed.
- Sure that wasn't her idea?
- Well, he's done it before.
Slept with one of your girlfriends?
Yeah. Yeah.
Right after my mom died.
I lost my mother and
my girlfriend in the same month.
You see, everything
with him is a competition.
If I make a big trade,
he's gotta make a bigger one.
If my girl's 25, he has to show up
with one who's barely legal.
Well, you won this round.
Jenna was marrying you,
not your father.
Yeah, well, he couldn't
let that happen.
My father and I were not
in a conspiracy to murder Jenna.
He killed her because...
Because he was jealous.
And he was your dad, so he wasn't gonna
let you go to prison for something he did.
He hired Roger Fromm
to bribe that juror.
He bribed that juror
to save his own ass, not mine.
And I hope he rots in hell.
When are you guys gonna arrest him?
As soon as we can tie him to Fromm.
Now, your father
paid for these pictures.
Which means that
he has to have a set.
Do you have any idea
where he would keep them?
You're gonna burn down my house.
Like you burned down Jenna's.
That'd be justice.
You have no right to do this.
No, the search warrant says we do.
There's nothing in there.
Do you think that we're here by accident?
PJ gave you up
because he knows what you did.
Last chance... gimme the
combination, or I'm going in.
The hell you are.
I have an injunction
invalidating your warrant.
On what grounds?
You violated PJ's right to counsel.
We weren't questioning him
as a suspect.
Nice try. But Judge Tatum saw
right through your little charade.
Avery Hemmings doesn't
know what she's talking about.
You didn't violate PJ's rights.
So get the judge to reverse the injunction,
and restore the warrant.
What's the point, you know,
Bartlett's already disappeared
- the photos from that safe.
- It doesn't matter.
We already have him for Jenna's
murder on his son's say-so.
How did Bartlett get here before we did?
You miss the chopper in his backyard?
- Congratulations.
- For what?
Whatever you said to big daddy,
he's rolling over on his son like road kill.
He fingered PJ for Jenna's murder?
Just waiting on you
to seal the deal, counselor.
What did Bartlett say to you?
That he can't protect his son anymore.
And that PJ has a violent streak in him.
PJ did throw the first punch
the day his dad put him through the door.
Bartlett also said PJ told him
he had to get out of the country
the night that Jenna died.
That's why he sent him to Aruba.
What a mess.
First we can't get
either one of them to talk,
not they're flipping on each other.
I'm never gonna get a conviction.
And so what?
If Jenna were alive, we'd be
collaring her for blackmail.
She's no innocent victim here.
She's a hustler.
Hustlers deserve justice too.
This discount suit cost 250 bucks.
How many times you
gonna watch that thing?
Until I figure out
how this little scam artist
had such a hold on two powerful
guys like the Bartletts.
Well, she was gonna bleed them
for millions.
Okay, so call the cops,
hire a lawyer,
but don't risk everything
by whacking her.
And I'm gonna help you dress...
to kill.
Wait a minute.
- What is it?
- You get the evidence inventories?
- Yeah. Right here.
- Come here.
- You see something?
- Well, I'll blow it up for you.
Look.
That lamp there was the murder weapon.
That means Jenna
made this video in her bedroom.
So then why didn't we find any trace
of the camera or videotape?
- Bathroom's clear.
- Yeah. How about the bedroom?
I opened the pillows, the mattress,
everything in there...There's nothing.
For someone who slept
with coffee traders,
you'd think Jenna
would have brewed better beans.
What do we got brewing here?
SD card.
I can play it on my laptop.
That bedroom cam
sure came in handy.
Jenna's got some big insurance policies...
The baby, and now home movies.
Maybe she sent a copy
of this to Bartlett,
and that's why he didn't
want us in his safe.
She puts this on the Internet,
it's a huge scandal.
Exchange takes away
Bartlett's seat.
It's bye-bye to his 100-year-old
coffee trading empire.
He tried to buy her off.
She decides it's not enough.
He whacks her.
You guys, in the bedroom.
The camera was hidden here
inside the wall.
But how did it shoot through plaster?
Didn't have to.
It's got a remote lens.
She probably hid it in the crown molding
on this wall, facing the bed.
Lens burned up.
The camera body's in perfect shape.
And... there's an SD card still inside.
We didn't come here to watch TV.
You should stick around, counselor.
You've never seen
a performance like this one.
Jenna had a secret booty cam.
You two have starring roles.
She made videos of us
having sex with her?
Including the last night you were together.
She threatened to sell them to the Tabloids
if we didn't keep paying her.
Dad, why didn't you tell me?
I was trying to protect you.
Well, you're not gonna
make us watch it, are you?
- No. Just the encore.
- PJ had already come and gone.
The killer showed up
after he'd already left.
Turn it off.
Why?
It'll prove we're innocent.
I said turn it off.
We can fast-forward it.
I'm not gonna sit here
and listen to this.
- I know exactly what you're doing.
- What are you still doing here?
He doesn't love you.
- I'm not gonna...
- I'm not lying to you.
You're a money-grubbing whore.
You don't know anything about me.
Get out.
I'm not going anywhere.
Who do you think you are?
Look, we're engaged. / What?
See that ring?
Get out. He loves me.
- He doesn’t.
- I said get out.
Avery killed Jenna?
Why? / You're not just gonna let her
get away, are you?
Front door's the only way out of here.
I've already alerted security.
They're not gonna let her leave.
Emergency stairs to the roof.
Avery.
Don't come any closer.
- I swear, I'll go over.
- Avery, what did you do?
I begged Jenna to let you go.
You wanna know what she said?
"He's mine, every last penny."
She was no good for you, PJ.
None of them were.
So you had a PI follow me?
- Why?
- To protect you.
All of those whores,
they just loved your money.
I loved you, PJ.
Ever since college.
I always have.
You almost got me sent to prison.
And my father.
That's why I bribed the juror.
I never would have let you get convicted.
I would never do anything to hurt you.
I said get back.
- Avery...
- Careful.
Avery, we can work this out, okay?
Why don't you just
come with me, all right?
- It's too late.
- No, it's not.
Please.
For me, okay?
Okay.
Come on.
Get away from my son.
- No.
- Bartlett, get back.
- She almost destroyed us.
- Me?
This is all your fault.
If you hadn't knocked up Jenna,
none of this would have happened.
Back away from her.
She's nuts. / Shut up, dad.
Haven't you done enough damage?
I love you, PJ.
I love PJ.
And I'm never gonna let you
hurt him again.
- Stop!
- PJ!
No!
No, no, please, no.
Please, no God.