[Man Narrating]
In the criminal justice system...
all defendants are innocent
until proven guilty,
either by confession,
plea bargain or trial byjury.
This is one of those trials.
You were on duty when
you heard a woman screaming.
You ran from the Winslow and stopped
- Down here.
He had a hold of her.
Where?
Uh, here. Here.
He had her up against the wall,
this homeless guy.
H-He was pressed against her,
and then she was screaming.
And then he started swingin' at me,
so I swung back.
But I didn't mean-
That-That's how come I called 911.
Let him finish his story
and then Mirandize him.
[Chattering On Police Radio]
A woman got jumped? Yeah, it looks like
her doorman beat and killed the attacker.
Officer Montez was first
on the scene.
The victim is a vagrant,
mid to late thirties, no I.D.
Got the call from 911.
A guy was down but still breathing.
Not anymore. The
doorman? Andres Voychek.
The guy was covered in the vic's
blood. The woman was pretty shook up.
Where is she now? We let her
go. She lives at the Winslow.
- Voychek was the doorman.
- [Voychek] Hey, what are you-
Please! Why are you doing this?
I ran across the street to save her!
I was just trying
to get him to stop!
Please! Why are you doing this?
Well. Let's go see
the woman he saved.
[Knocks]
Ms. Phillips? I'm Assistant
District Attorney Tracey Kibre.
This is Officer Montez
and my associate Kelly Gaffney.
I'm sorry if
- No, it's okay. It's just I had to clean off.
I understand.
It's been a very rough night.
We do need to talk to you
about what happened.
Did you talk to Voychek? [Gaffney] Yes.
- Then he's all right?
- He's fine. He's down at the precinct answering some questions.
You arrested him?
Yes.
For what? He saved my life.
Well, it's a homicide.
The man he beat is dead.
The man he beat attacked me.
This is crazy.
You have it all backwards.
Why don't you just
take a minute and we can-
How long are you holding him?
We can't answer that.
Then we're done here.
Oh, boy.
Every coin has two sides.
The flip being?
A homeless man is dead at
the hands of a servant of the rich.
A woman is saved from
a potentially deadly attack...
by an unsuspecting hero.
She has a point.
- At the end of the day, who wouldn't want their own personal Voychek?
- So now what?
We bring a case to the grand jury
that we all know should be dismissed?
Sometimes the best way to appease the
people is to let the people make the call.
Put the case before the grandjury,
but with a certain slant.
We do our duty. The case gets dismissed,
but not by us.
Terrific.
The system being manipulated
to protect our reputation.
We didn't build it.
We just fly it.
I know you're a smart lawyer,
but I don't think this is
such a good idea, Mr. Lumbard.
I'm not so hot
at public speaking.
You're not addressing Congress, Andres.
Just tell the people what happened.
Tell them the truth. But I told the
police, and that got me arrested.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I saved her.
And the grand jury needs
to hear that directly from you-
Your innocence,
your deep remorse.
That way, in the unlikely event this were ever to go to trial
- Trial?
But you said all I do is explain
to the grand jury and this is over.
I'm sure it will be.
When they hear from Abigail-
what you did for her-
there's no chance they'll indict.
Abbie will do that for me?
Yes.
She's very grateful.
That night you did what every guy
hopes he would do in his finest hour.
[Kibre] How long have
you worked at the Winslow?
Eight years.
Best of my life.
A-At the Winslow we look out
for each other.
And on the evening of February 21,
what happened?
I was on door.
Slaykoff, he had elevator.
We take shifts. Um-
I heard the screaming, and l-I just
started running toward the sound.
[Kibre]
And what did you find?
- This homeless guy, he-
- [Clears Throat]
Mr. Ashford.
He had Ms. Phillips by the wrists
up against the wall.
She was trying real hard
to fight him off,
but he was too strong for her,
so I grabbed him.
You pulled him away?
Yeah.
L-I figured he'd run, but instead
he started beating on me.
- And you fought back?
- I had no choice.
I am real sorry for how
it turned out.
Questions?
Had you ever seen
the homeless man before?
Once or twice, but not regular.
Were you afraid for your life?
I didn't stop to think.
L-I saw she was in trouble,
I did what any person would do.
Thank you, Mr. Voychek.
Excuse me, are you Ms. Kibre?
Yes.
They told me you're trying
the Voychek case.
The man he killed-
he was my brother.
I'm very sorry for your loss, um-
Oh, Justine.
[Woman] You're a hero to the
city. How do you feel? Justine.
[Justine] They're calling
him a hero. Did you know that?
I took off work today,
but they told me I'm not allowed inside.
Well, the grand jury testimony is sealed,
but you'll be allowed in the
courtroom if it goes to trial. Lf?
Uh- I read the papers.
I know what a good story
this makes.
But I also knew my brother.
There's no way he attacked that girl.
He had no reason to.
I had dinner with some friends
in SoHo.
And we shared a cab back uptown.
They dropped me off on my corner
so they could cut across the park.
When did you first see
the man who attacked you?
[Abigail] When I was a block from the
Winslow. He was walking towards me.
- I was gonna cross the street.
- Why didn't you?
Can you believe
I didn't wanna be rude?
I could see my building up ahead,
so I thought l-
I thought I'd be okay.
Do you need a minute?
No.
He pulled me into the alley
and down the stairs...
and pushed me up against the wall.
He had my hands above his head.
I could smell him.
It felt like a badjoke,
like this isn't what happens
to me, is it?
I was shaking and started screaming,
and then there was Voychek.
So Mr. Voychek pulled
Mr. Ashford off of you?
He had the guy by his shirt. But when
he let go, the man started swinging.
They fought?
I only saw it for a minute. But-
'Cause I ran up the stairs.
So you feel safer now?
For the first time in four months.
The man was stalking me.
Ms. Phillips, what do
you mean by stalking?
I'd get up to 15 calls a night.
Hang ups.
Sometimes he would just
sit on the line, listening.
At first I thought it was
a fax or a wrong number,
but there were never cranks
on my machine.
The calls only started
once I got home.
- Anything else?
- Letters full of personal information.
Like what I'd worn that day
or who I'd had lunch with.
Did you contact the police?
File a report?
I did call the police,
but I never followed through.
I wasn't gonna let someone
get to me like that.
The man who attacked me
was the man who was stalking me.
But how exactly did you
make that connection?
Just before he approached me
he said my name.
How else could he know my name?
I need you to pull Abigail Phillips's
phone records.
- The girl with the guardian angel? - We're looking
to tie the victim to some late-night phone calls.
The homeless guy?
Well, I guess you don't need an Upper West
Side address to reach out and touch someone.
I'm gonna need them today.
No problem. I'm fast.
That's what I hear.
You didn't like the grand jury? It was
like they were judging me on everything-
How I spoke, what I
was wearing. They were.
And you survived.
My guess? It's over.
A little help from my friends.
Thanks, Greg. The least I could do.
I can't tell you how good it feels
to have my life back.
Hey. Wait a minute.
I hate to ask, but could you
take Voychek something for me?
I don't know what says
thank you for saving my life,
but flowers are universal,
right? [Man] Thank you.
Oh, and this is for you.
He doesn't know I'm covering this
for him, does he? Haven't said a word.
Let's keep it that way.
I tied all those crank calls Abigail
Phillips's been getting to a prepaid cellular.
That's virtually impossible to trace.
Eh, for some.
Stop dancing.
What do ya got?
Not impossible if you have a taped
conversation coming from the same cell phone.
That 911 call the doorman
made at the scene...
came from the same cell phone
as all the calls Abigail's been getting.
Voychek's her stalker.
So a good guy does a good thing.
Will the grand jury see a problem?
All I see are coincidences.
There's no coincidences in murder.
After four months of calls and letters,
the girl just happens to get jumped
on his watch?
Not a straight line to murder two?
Andres Voychek was so obsessed with Abigail
Phillips, maybe he would kill for her.
That's where I'm heading.
I'll get a search warrant
to look into his apartment.
Every day there's another puff piece
about Andres Voychek.
Where he gets his uniform pressed,
how he takes his coffee.
And my brother, whenever they
mention him, is simply the victim.
He doesn't even get a name.
William.
He preferred Billy.
Justine, you're my only
connection to Billy.
I need you to help me
put a face on him.
How did he wind up on the streets?
Did he have a history of mental illness?
He was tested.
He had problems with focus, boundaries,
but there was no official name
you could hang on it.
I checked his police records. There's
no bookings for aggressive behavior.
No, just the opposite. It was him
who was usually getting roughed up.
Always wanting to make friends
with people who didn't want any.
Do you know where
he was staying most recently?
He mentioned the Bowery.
I wish I could be more specific.
Okay, well, thank you.
If there's anything more,
we'll call you. Okay.
Oh, sweet dog.
When did he go missing?
Um. The night Billy was killed.
The dog was his.
Winston.
I figured the least I could do
for Billy now was to find him.
- Uh, could I take one of those?
- Oh, sure.
Thank you.
Pretty nice for a doorman. [Salazar]
Wonder ifhe needs a roommate?
We're dealing with a freak.
Why? 'Cause he's anal?
No. Because no one but our guy
has ever set foot in this place.
You employing some sort of
female intuition technique?
Date enough in this town,
you get a sixth sense for freaks.
This guy doesn't get out much.
He doesn't need to.
He's got all his friends right here.
Wow. Good to have hobbies.
We should check out the storage space. The
landlord was kind enough to give us the key.
It's divided up into apartments.
I can't believe people
still hold on to this junk.
One man gathers
what another man spills.
Yeah, well,
it still looks like junk.
It's right here.
[Lock Clicks]
Ooh. Look at this.
That's not Abigail.
Looks like Voychek's
got more than one crush.
Let's just hope
this one's still breathing.
Her name is Blythe Cotton.
Blythe Cotton also lived
at the Winslow.
Voychek's playground.
March of last year she took off,
leaving five months on her lease.
Tell me this doesn't lead
to a landfill in Jersey.
More like Portland. She moved there
for a promotion. It checks out.
So Voychek exhibits a pattern ofbehavior.
But we have no evidence beyond some
year-old grocery receipts and some snapshots.
What are you saving for last?
How about a police report?
Ms. Cotton filed this two months
before catching her flight.
She was being stalked.
[Man] Great. I wanna get another. Um,
give me a big heroic smile. Thank you.
Are these boys bothering you,
Andres? [Laughs] Hello, Ms. Phillips.
How about a shot of
the hero and the girl?
Do you mind?
[Woman] Aw. This way, Ms. Phillips.
[Woman]
Over here. Over here.
Andres, over here.
[Woman] Can I get one more?
[Sniffs]
Hey. It's Kelly, right?
Yeah, good memory.
I was wondering if we could talk.
[Voychek] Um, I really don't
think it was that heroic.
[Man] How do you feel
about your new status?
First time in months
I've done the reservoir.
Yeah, I love to run. But the D.A.' s office
requires a vow against leisure activities, so-
For a while I didn't wanna risk it.
But now things are back to normal.
Well, the grand jury's still open.
That's just a formality, right?
I mean, I've got my life back.
- Ms. Phillips- - And once this is
over, Voychek can get on with his.
Okay. Abigail,
we traced the calls that
you've been getting to a cell phone.
William Ashford did not make them.
Of course he did. I told you-
Andres Voychek did.
That's not-You're wrong.
I wish I were.
- We searched his apartment. We found pictures of you.
- No.
- I saw them, Abigail.
- That's crazy. He's barely even looked me in the eye.
You know the type. He's awkward
but harmless. He's a decent guy.
We also found proof that
he's done this before. Stop.
Right now. I don't wanna hear it,
and I don't believe you.
Well, I understand why
you don't want to believe me,
but right now I'm concerned
for your safety.
I want you to pack a bag,
call a friend that you can stay with.
If you have any vacation time,
I suggest that you take it.
[Sighs]
When I made thejump over
to D.A.' s squad,
I never figured I'd be on
pooch patrol. [Dog Barking]
You never said why you made that
jump. You're right. I didn't.
Can I have some change? How do we
know whoever has the dog knows our vic?
People give their cars to valets,
their babies to nannies. But a dog-
A dog they give
to a trusted friend.
Hey. He friendly?
He looks rough,
but he's friendly.
Hey there, big fella.
[Dog Barks]
You had him long? Aw, he's not
mine. He belongs to a friend.
His name wouldn't happen
to be Billy Ashford?
[Laughs]
Looks like you're gonna be
dog-sittin' for a while.
Yeah, we think we might have seen
your friend Billy uptown.
Any reason you could think of
he'd be there? Say, upper 80s?
- Oh, yeah. Doin' a run.
- What do you mean, a run?
The buildings up there, they have funds.
Try to keep their stoops clean.
Yeah. We take turns hittin' 'em up.
If he's up there workin',
he'll be back soon.
I'm afraid he's not coming back.
Your friend attacked a woman.
Someone pulled him off,
beat him to death.
[Sighs]
Oh.
He was only supposed to scare her.
Who?
Some girl.
Billy was about pleasing people.
- You said he was supposed to scare somebody?
- The man said it was his girlfriend.
[Man] You know who this guy
was? We knew him from our runs.
A doorman.
Why? You told me to tell my story
to the grand jury. I did that.
Why-Why is this not over?
I can't continue representing you.
There's a conflict.
- What conflict?
- Abigail was paying me to represent you.
The prosecutors have filed a motion
to disqualify me. I won't oppose it.
Abbie was paying you for me?
She was concerned for you.
- I am not alone.
- Mr. Voychek,
I came to give you the name of
- Abbie, she's on my side.
I would never let anyone hurt her.
- You want to make me the bad guy, but she won't believe you.
- That's not what this is about.
I'm gonna call her.
- No, no, no. I'll go to her apartment
and explain- - No, you can't do that.
I have to talk to her.
No.
I'm advising you to stay away
from Abigail Phillips.
- What's this?
- An excellent lawyer.
I've spoken with him.
He wants to take the case.
You'll need him.
You go.
[Door Opens, Closes]
[Buzzes]
Yours.
True bill.
We got him.
Did you get my message?
The grand jury indicted.
A friend of mine went by my
apartment today and picked up my mail.
Did you read them?
One was enough.
Well, this will help.
I honestly thought he'd saved my life.
That was the point.
Killing William Ashford
was just a consequence.
He tried to run.
- Who?
- The man-
Mr. Ashford. He tried to run, but
Voychek held on. He kept hitting him.
- Would you testify to that at trial?
- Will it matter?
I've been in the papers, on TV,
calling Voychek a hero.
Who will believe me now?
[Bailiff] Docket number 267805,
People versus Andres Voychek.
Murder in the second degree.
Could representing counsel
and defendant please step forward?
[Judge] Mr. A dler. What's
prompted you to visit the plebeians?
I believe an innocent man
deserves the best defense.
If it comes attached
to a long line of zeros.
My client is a doorman,
Your Honor.
- How do you plead?
- N-Not guilty, sir.
Kelly Gaffney for the People,
Your Honor.
Based on the serious allegations
involving violence,
and the strength of the People's case,
we ask for a remand.
This was a tragic accident.
Mr. Voychek has no prior record.
He's had the same job and lived in
the same apartment for the last eight years.
Glad to hear it.
I'm setting cash bail at 500,000.
The building in which my client
is employed set up a fund.
- We'll post this afternoon.
- The defendant also stands accused of stalking Abigail Phillips.
The People ask Your Honor
for an order of protection.
Granted.
Mr. Voychek, you are to
stay away from Ms. Phillips.
No phone. No mail.
No personal visits.
Stay away means exactly that-
stay away.
[Gavel Raps]
[Bailiff] Docket number 267705,
People v. Sharaud Santos.
Probation violation.
[Judge] Mr. Santos-
Off to the press.
"Motion to suppress the box
found in Voychek's storage space.' '
Surprise.
[Voychek]
I don't remember.
[Adler] You hear a woman's screams
and don't remember what you were doing?
[Voychek] Like I said, I was
working. I was up front by the door.
Inside or out?
I don't know. Out, I guess.
Oh. So you could actually see
Ms. Phillips walking up the street...
before she was attacked?
No. L-I mean,
I didn't know it was her
until I ran over.
So, you were standing outside
on the sidewalk,
but you had no idea it was
Ms. Phillips walking toward you?
Maybe I was looking the other way.
Isn't it more accurate,
Mr. Voychek,
to say that you were acutely aware
of Ms. Phillips's comings and goings...
because you have
intimate feelings for her?
Why do you keep asking me that? No!
I already told you, no.
Okay.
Who believes him?
Okay. The rest of you, any thoughts?
He's all over the place, like he's
making it up as he goes along.
He can't look you in the eye.
He keeps looking up or down.
I'm sorry, but I don't trust the man.
Okay, this has been
a tremendously helpful exercise.
I wanna thank you all very much.
Now, if I could ask the ladies to kindly
step outside for a moment, please?
Thanks again for your time,
ladies.
Thank you.
[Door Opens]
[Door Closes]
That's what matters.
All we need is one.
Abigail is a beautiful girl.
I do not want you to deny
your feelings for her, Andres.
I want you to express them.
Your crush-
your chivalric love for Abigail Phillips-
is our defense.
Good news travels quick.
Nine times out of 10
not in our favor.
Yeah, well, the city wanted a hero.
Yeah, you know they got
a wolf in sheep's clothing.
[Scoffs]
Well, savor the moment.
Judge Hafner's about to rule on the
admissibility of our major piece of evidence.
The box was found in a storage
space in Mr. Voychek's building.
Meaning the search exceeded
the scope of the warrant.
The defendant has no standing
to challenge this search.
It's a common area
accessible to all the residents.
Ms. Kibre has a point. [Adler] Fine.
But if the area was accessible to any one
of the 86 residents living at that address,
then you'll have to agree
the tie between the box,
its contents
and my client is tenuous.
That should govern the weight, given the evidence,
not the admissibility. Let the jury decide.
The box contained pictures and personal
records of a woman that lived at the Winslow.
That same woman filed a police report
stating she was being stalked.
The report states that
her stalker was unknown.
[Gaffney] In light of the evidence,
we plan to call her as a witness.
That's your prerogative-
Not why we're here.
I reviewed the contents of the box,
and given their nature,
I believe their prejudicial effect
outweighs their potential probative value.
The box is out.
Uh, there was a total of
12 pictures of Ms. Phillips.
Six were attached to the fridge,
one in a frame by the bed.
And in any of those photographs...
was Ms. Phillips looking
directly at the camera?
No. They were all candid shots.
Thank you. That's all.
Exhibits, uh, 13 and 14.
Mr. Salazar, do either of these pictures
look familiar to you?
No. They were attached
to the refrigerator...
alongside the pictures of, uh,
Ms. Phillips. They could have been.
The, uh- the cat.
He belongs to Mrs. Raul
up on the fifth floor.
And the elderly couple
are the Harpers.
They've been in 10A for 20 years.
They, uh, always remember to give Mr. Voychek
a little something extra for his birthday.
- Objection. He's testifying.
- Let's find the point, Mr. Adler.
You assume Ms. Phillips's pictures
on his refrigerator...
mean that Andres Voychek
was stalking her?
I wasn't sent to assume.
I was sent to execute a search warrant.
That turned up pictures of a cat.
Now, did you think my client
was stalking it too?
Your Honor.
That's enough of that, Mr.
Adler. [Adler] Apologies.
So, you searched high and low,
and the only evidence
you discovered...
were a few pictures of residents and pets.
That's all.
You also said
he wouldn't make bail.
But an order of protection stipulates
- I know.
I'm sorry.
I understand.
But our case is strong. We have a
witness to the solicitation of the victim.
We have your testimony-
Abigail!
- Abigail! Did you get my letters?
- Officer-
- They won't let me see you!
- Get away from me!
Don't scream! You have to know I didn't
- [Gaffney] Mr. Voychek, please.
- [Man] Take it easy!
- She wants to talk to me! She wants to talk to me! Abigail!
[Man] Calm down! Abigail-
I'm- I'm sorry.
We've got a situation.
Abbie just called.
She and the friend
she's staying with ordered pizza.
When, uh, she answered the door,
she found dead flowers on her doorstep.
They were the flowers she sent to Voychek,
back when he was her hero.
Where is she now?
Checked in a hotel on our dime.
[Sighs]
Maybe we should have told her.
- What?
- That an order of protection is just a piece of paper.
What am I supposed to tell
Abigail Phillips? Trust me?
We request that
Mr. Voychek's bail be revoked.
Abigail wants to see me.
[Judge Hafner] Mr. Voychek,
you have explicitly violated
the terms of your recognizance.
[Adler] Your Honor,
if it even appears to thejury...
that Mr. Voychek is in custody,
they could draw a negative conclusion.
It's unfair to infer his guilt before he's
even had a chance to prove his innocence.
I'm not depriving him
of that chance, Mr. A dler.
I'm merely changing
where he spends the night.
I'm remanding the defendant.
[Gavel Raps]
[Dr. Link] It's usually an idiosyncratic
thing that attracts the stalker.
She's nice.
Helpful, yet unattainable.
But not unattainable
in his mind.
Well, he believes she understands him,
as he does her,
in a real and tangible way.
So why maintain the distance?
Like, why call and then hang up?
His calling would have
an erotic surround to it.
[Kibre] I'm sorry. Can you break down
the terminology for the rest of us?
If she answered, he'd be pleased
that he knew she'd be home.
If she answered again, he'd imagine
she was waiting for the call.
Or if there was
an answering machine turned on,
that she wanted to capture
his message.
Now, a woman in this situation,
is there anything at all
that she could do...
to avoid this unwanted attention?
No. There is no response
that would slow the progression.
Oh.
Doctor, in your experience,
have you ever known a stalker
who would set up a situation...
where he could then play
the role of a hero?
Absolutely.
The heroic act is a kind of...
reaction formation of
the stalker's building rage.
Rage? Rage fueled by what?
His belief that
the object ofhis affection...
doesn't understand
the depth of his feelings.
It's his way of showing her.
Thank you, Doctor.
How many phone calls would it take
to, uh- to make me a stalker?
That would depend on the case.
If Mr. Voychek did feel
an intense bond to Ms. Phillips,
it is possible he felt a similar bond
to others in the building, hmm?
Not to the extent of
his feelings to Ms. Phillips.
But a connection nonetheless.
Meaning, had any one of them-
any of them been threatened-
he would have risked his own life
running to their rescue.
- Objection. Conjecture.
- Sustained.
- Seems Mr. Voychek was only guilty of doing his job well.
- You've made your point.
Oh, well. Nothing further then.
So you lied?
No.
Well, Andres Voychek goes from
being the guy who saved my life...
to a depraved sexual predator?
That's what he is.
Which one? You keep changing
your mind. I can't keep track.
You bought him presents, you paid for his legal defense
- I didn't know.
If I had, do you-
He took away my life.
And quite a life it was.
You're recently divorced,
aren't you, Ms. Phillips? Yes.
This your personals page
on singularsingles. Com.
It got 30 hits on the first day.
You had so many potential boyfriends
to blame it on,
- it took the D.A.' s office to narrow down your playing field.
- Tracey.
Stop it. It's disgusting.
Mr. Adler's client
is looking at murder two.
He doesn't give a rat's ass
about tarnishing your reputation.
I'm all you've got, aren't I?
You're losing.
I didn't ask for this. Oh, my God.
He's not gonna walk?
Not if we're prepared.
We stay focused-
Tell me they won't acquit.
Oh, well.
A lawyer who does that is a liar.
[Gaffney] You're currently taking
the drug Geodon for schizophrenia?
Yes.
And you're a heroin user?
I was.
I'm in a meth program now.
Some people from the church,
they come to the Bowery where I live...
and got me signed up.
The Bowery?
That's where the defendant,
Mr. Voychek,
approached you and Mr. A shford?
Yeah, but I told him
it sounded all wrong.
He was really asking Billy.
Did Mr. Voychek ask Billy
to scare Ms. Phillips?
[Man]
He said that she was his girlfriend.
He told Billy where
she'd be and when.
Thank you.
You say it sounded all wrong,
and yet you, uh-
you didn't go to the police?
I did. I called my uncle.
Your uncle?
He was a cop once,
only now he's in Costa Rica.
You can reach him
through the U.S. Embassy.
- Is that how you reach him?
- I used to call him direct, before I lost my Spanish.
I can speak seven different languages.
Only not anymore.
I'm sorry. You-You do or you do not
speak seven languages?
[Man]
Just the one now.
Before I could speak Vietnamese,
French, Russian, Middle Eastern.
Mr. Johnson, can you say, uh,
"Good morning" to us in,
uh, Middle Eastern?
Not anymore, no.
Is that because Middle Eastern
is not a language?
- Objection. Your Honor.
- [Judge Hafner] Get to the point.
When you witnessed this supposed conversation
between my client and Mr. Ashford,
were you loaded?
I don't remember.
He knew that Billy would say yes.
- Billy said yes to anything.
- Mr. Johnson, that's enough.
You killed Billy!
Mr. Johnson, please.
- Shut up, you liar!
- You're out of order.
Court officers, restrain that man!
Mr. Voychek!
[Shouting]
Order in this court!
- Mr. Voychek, that's enough!
- [Voychek] He's lying! He's lying, Your Honor!
[Judge Hafner]
Sidebar.
Mr. A dler, I will have your client's
mouth sealed with packing tape...
if you can't find a way
to close it for him.
That's it.
One hour recess.
[Gavel Raps]
Ready to talk?
Come on.
We both have problems.
Is your client willing to deal?
I'll test the waters.
Why's he so eager to plea?
Case has lost its glamour.
No, I mean Voychek. He didn't
seem like a man ready to give in.
There's only one reason
he would want to-
To protect the very thing that
got him here in the first place.
Abigail.
How do you know Adler
is using her as bait?
'Cause that's exactly what
I would do. [Buzzer Buzzes]
No, no. No plea.
Let me take the stand.
Tell things from my side.
Li-Like in the grand jury.
I was a hero.
I can't let you do that.
Why not?
The fact that your last lawyer was
stupid enough to let you testify...
is exactly the reason
I can't let you testify now.
You'll perjure yourself.
People admired me.
She admired me.
I am not guilty.
So you don't want to accept the plea?
All right. Now...
you listen to me.
We still have a shot
at winning this.
Kibre puts Abigail on the stand,
I put somebody on her credit report
dating back to college.
We put a call in to her ex-husband.
On cross, we will systematically
tear her apart.
Her story, character.
Her credibility.
We'll paint her as a slut,
a piece of trash.
No!
I'll stand up and say I did it
before I'd let you do that to her.
You say I should plea,
I will plea.
Ravell's on line one.
Something about Abigail.
I wanna run the plea by her, but if
we wait much longer, it could go away.
Yeah. Where are you?
Uh, what are you saying?
Well, find her. I can't push for a plea
without the girl.
Abigail's apartment's
been cleaned out. She's gone.
- You've gotta be kidding me.
- Is there a case without her?
Not much.
She could be halfway
to Timbuktu by now.
If Voychek's lawyer doesn't know
Abigail's missing-
Are you suggesting we push for a plea
without our eyewitness?
What if Voychek doesn't take it?
Oh, he'll take it.
But what ifhe doesn't?
They ask for us to provide a witness
and we can't. We lose all credibility.
It's a bluff.
Other D.A.' s have gone there.
We're obligated to inform
his defense lawyer.
Only if we're absolutely certain
that she's slipped.
We don't know that.
It doesn't seem that complicated.
[Chattering]
Judge is ready to hear your plea.
Ravell's gonna call.
Some guy where Abigail works says she's
gonna come by today to pick up her paycheck.
A day is 24 hours.
Judge Hafner just gave you
five minutes to show your face.
Well, I'm willing to bluff,
but I'm not gonna lie
in front of a judge.
[Rings]
- Yeah. You got her?
- Alive and well.
Now go get the bad guy.
[Judge Hafner] Mr. Voychek, after
listening to your statement of facts,
I accept your plea to
manslaughter in the first degree,
with a sentence to be imposed
of eight years,
as negotiated by both sides.
[Gavel Raps]
I am not guilty.
It's still a lose-lose situation
for Abigail.
Some crimes don't end at sentencing.
Not for the victim.
We do what we can.
[Howling]