In the criminal justice system,
sexually-based offenses
are considered especially heinous.
In New York City,
the dedicated detectives who investigate
these vicious felonies are members
of an elite squad known
as The Special Victims Unit.
These are their stories.
Now, you sure it was a talking car,
not a talking fire hydrant?
Don't crack wise with me, young man.
I'm not some senile old bitch.
Then where is it?
It was right there.
In the bus stop.
Okay, Anna, the voice in trunk,
what did it say to you?
"Help me" and then a name,
- Savannah, Samantha.
- Sabrina?
- Was it Sabrina?
- That's it! Sabrina.
- Yo, Sanjay.
- Officer Tim.
- No kraut, heavy mustard.
- No, no, no.
You seen this girl today?
No, sir.
What about a car parked in the bus stop
about two hours ago?
Yes, the truck towed it away.
Great.
Twenty Frank to Central.
Possible sighting
on kidnap victim Sabrina farmer.
Notify SVU she might be in the trunk
of an impounded car.
They don't know which vehicle?
Lady couldn't give a description.
Traffic computers are down.
How do they even know it's in Queens?
It has to be here.
Cause Pier 76 is full.
And this is where Manhattan
is sending their overflow.
Anybody going through the paperwork?
Central called all the tow truck drivers,
told them we have a missing kid out here.
Where the hell is that infrared camera?
Emergency services on their way.
Better be quick.
There's a lot of cars out here.
Pop every trunk.
Heard your call on the radio.
Where should I start?
Take your pick. They've been putting cars
in every empty space.
Captain, ESU's got another camera.
Tell him to start two rows up
from O'Halloran.
Hey, guys!
I got something.
What do we got?
Just caught a blue plume
coming from one of these cars.
Rear row. That gray Impala.
If she's in there, get her out.
- She's barely breathing.
- We need oxygen.
- EMS is stuck in traffic.
- We'll take her.
Sabrina's CAT scan
didn't show any bleeding,
but she does have
a serious concussion.
Any idea what she was hit with?
Probably a rock.
There's dirt in the laceration.
When will she wake up?
Your guess is as good as mine.
- Was she raped?
- Yes. No fluids.
But several hairs and there's
significant bruising.
She's only 11.
Don't ask why.
It'll just make you crazy.
I'll call you when she's conscious.
Well, we can always go back.
and check the security cam
Well, we're just gonna see the same thing.
Sabrina leaving the bookstore alone
and nobody following her.
Why'd she go out by herself?
Maybe she couldn't find her mother
and went out there looking for her.
We got a hit on the Impala.
The driver's name, Saul Picard
from Mandeville, Louisiana.
Picked it up from escape rent-a-car
three days ago.
Good, well, if he's a tourist,
he's already left by now.
I doubt it. He's staying at the executive
apartments on West 73rd Street.
Manager said he signed
a month-long lease.
Apartment of Saul Picard
177 West 73rd Street
Tuesday, October 9
So detectives Benson and Stabler,
what can I do for you?
We're here about your rental car.
The one I returned yesterday?
That's not what the rental agency says.
I'm sorry, can I use your bathroom, please?
Uh, through... through the bedroom.
Thank you.
The guy's name was, um...
here it is.
Um, Mickey.
Well, what's the big deal about the car?
It was stolen, Mr. Picard.
Well, there's the receipt.
I'm not responsible for what happened
after I dropped it off.
Can you tell me where you've been
the last two days?
Here, working.
I went to the deli on the corner a few times
for coffee and burgers.
You're an artist.
Not what my critics say.
Have we met before?
Doubt it.
I'm here every few months on business,
but I live in Louisiana.
Oh, near New Orleans?
Other side of Lake Pontchartrain.
North shore.
But now I'm fixing to relocate.
Katrina destroyed my house two years ago,
and it's not the same down home.
I wouldn't blame you for trying to get away.
Can I see both your
credentials again, please?
You have my apology.
Thank you for obliging my eccentricity.
Thanks for your time.
We'll talk to the car rental company again
and, uh, try to figure this whole thing out.
Have a good day.
Yeah, that helps.
Thanks.
Anything from Escape Rent-A-Car?
Yeah, Picard's story checks out.
He returned the car to Mickey.
So how'd it wind up at a bus stop?
Mickey didn't have enough room
in the garage
and left it on the street
with the keys inside.
Came out. It was gone.
Why not report it stolen?
Well, he panicked.
He was afraid he was going to get fired,
so he doctored the computer records
to make it look like Picard still had it.
You get anything out of the deli
besides burned coffee?
The clerk said that Picard has been in
at least a couple dozen times
over the last three days.
Definite caffeine freak.
And a paranoid freak.
Asking for our IDs twice?
- Bad cause of OCD.
- And not to mention BO.
There shower was bone dry
like it'd never been used.
How about the bedroom?
Messy.
But no sign Sabrina was ever there.
All we got left is the Impala, huh?
No DNA. No prints. No nothing.
Except this.
- Looks like bacteria.
- It's pollen.
I found microscopic traces on the driver's
seat and on Sabrina's clothing.
All that proves is Sabrina was in the car.
No, sample was so minute,
it could only have been transferred
through extremely close contact.
- Like sitting on the seat.
- Yeah or during the rape.
What difference does it make?
Any of the last ten people
who rented the car could a left the pollen.
Only if they'd been down south recently.
Pollen's from a Louisiana Flatsdege.
Louisiana Flatsdege.
That grow anywhere near
Lake Pontchartrain?
Around the bayous of the north shore.
How'd you know?
Clear.
You're telling me.
His laptop and artwork are gone.
- So is his suitcase.
- All right, Picard's alibi check out.
What did we miss?
We missed something.
He returned the Impala.
He walks out of the rental office.
He saw the keys in the car.
He stole the car right back.
Oh, we screwed up.
No press, but I want every cop on the street
looking for this guy.
You know, if I'm Picard
and I got an 18-hour head start,
I'm on my way to Brazil.
Maybe that's where
he's been attacking little girls,
cause his DNA's not in the system
and the Fibbies got nothing on him.
Unless Sabrina is his first victim.
A rapist wannabe's most likely to want
to bust his cherry closer to home
where he's more comfortable.
Did we check with the Louisianan cops?
Yeah. They only turned up two warrants
for unpaid speeding tickets.
Speaking of which, did our friends
at Escape Rent-A-Car happen to mention
loaning a blue ford explorer to Mr. Picard?
When? / Yesterday afternoon about 3:00
before we put out the alert on him.
That's right after we left his place.
Yeah, from which, by the way,
he didn't check out.
Nor did he buy airplane tickets to any
exotic, non-extraditable vacation spots.
Sounds like our nut job's sticking around.
Hopefully not looking for his next victim.
Let's get the description
of the car on the air.
It's already done and sent to every police
department in the Northeast.
Special victims unit.
This is Detective Benson.
Captain, you want us to sit
on Picard's place?
- I don't think he's going back there.
- Thanks.
Sabrina's awake.
Mercy General Hospital
365 West 32nd Street
Wednesday, October 10
I was looking at some books
when he told me I was in danger.
He said mom was waiting
for me outside.
Then he went out
through the coffee place.
Explains why he wasn't
on the surveillance video.
What happened then?
My mom wasn't outside, but he was.
He said mom was hurt
and if I told him where I lived,
- he'd take me home.
- Okay. So you got into his car.
But he drove the wrong way.
I tried to get out,
but the doors were locked.
Did you ask him where you were going?
He said some place safe.
He was talking funny.
Okay.
What else did he say?
He said, "Hearken to the ark."
- "Hearken to the ark."
- Yeah.
Mostly I didn't understand him.
Sabrina, I'm gonna show you some pictures.
And I want you to take
a really, really good look, okay?
That... that's him.
He said his name was William.
Now, Sabrina, when you got out of the car...
Did you see anything?
Did you notice where you were?
It was...
a park.
I tried to run away, but he said,
"Stop, Francine."
And...
And what else?
What else did he say?
Okay, sweetie.
You need to rest.
So I'm gonna come back
and I'm gonna visit you tomorrow, okay?
Okay, Olivia.
Okay.
Tell me we've got Picard?
I wish.
Another girl's been kidnapped.
Eve Holland, 11.
Mom was next door shopping for clothes.
And left Eve in the children's section.
At least we know Picard's MO.
That's a great place to pick up kids
if you're a pedophile.
You know the girl?
Yeah. Right over there picking out
a few books.
- What? those books there?
- Could be.
She was sitting in that chair.
Quentin's Quest by William S. Falstaff.
I read this to my kids.
You and a million other parents.
Surveillance caught Picard on tape
escorting Eve Holland out 45 minutes ago.
- Son of a bitch.
- What?
I knew I recognized him.
That's Saul Picard.
He rapes kids and writes books for them.
William S. Falstaff.
That's a Helluva pen name.
Okay, where is he bringing her to?
What'd he say to Sabrina?
"Hearkening the ark."
Hearken to the ark.
Hearken to the arch.
- Secret of the Arch?
- Maybe he took her here.
The Arc De Triomphe in Paris?
There's one exactly like this
in Washington Square Park.
There's nowhere to hide
in Washington Square.
Maybe Brooklyn.
Prospect Park.
The arch at Grand Army Plaza.
Lieutenant.
Benson. Stabler.
Manhattan SVU.
Lieutenant Shea.
Anyone spot them yet?
No, but I got chopper up
and we're calling in some more manpower.
Victim was snatched
less than two hours ago.
So if we move fast, maybe we can find them
before he hurts her.
Well, we'll do the best we can,
but it's a big park.
Lieutenant, chopper spotted
something in the trees on lookout hill.
Mount up.
Lieutenant, look, we don't know
how this guys operates.
If he sees all the troops...
Okay. You go in first.
- Police. Don't move.
- Make it right.
Get out of the car.
Get out of the car. Shut up.
Shut up and put your hands
on the car over there.
Put your hands up.
Hands up. / Eve.
Eve, honey, can you hear me?
My name is Olivia.
I'm a police officer.
Can you sit up for me?
Are you okay?
I'm tired.
Okay.
Manhattan SVU to detail.
We have one in custody.
We'll meet you back at our car.
Okay, sweetie.
Come with me.
Good job.
What'd you give that girl
to make her go to sleep?
Alice swallowed one of the cakes,
and she was delighted to find
that she began shrinking directly.
You give Sabrina Farmer
one of those cakes
before you raped her
and left her in that car?
I had a car.
It got a tow.
Guy who towed its name was Joe.
- You're under arrest for the rape
and kidnapping of Sabrina Farmer
- He looks like a lot of guys I know.
- and attempted kidnapping of Eve Holland.
- My attorney is Lucien Deveraux.
- Of New Orleans.
- You have the right to remain silent.
- He's an expert on pralines.
- Do you understand me?
Did you hear the president's
speech last week?
Man, that guy'll do anything
to keep us fighting this Iraq war.
Oh, Nefarious war!
I see why arms were seldom used...
WINTER'S COMING...
TIME TO ESCAPE
- Oh, okay.
- Okay, what?
Do I have to do it now?
Cause it's gonna be really hard.
- I gotta get away.
- You're not going anywhere.
Gotta get away.
Elliot!
Get him.
Officer down.
Call a bus.
Elliot.
Elliot, you're okay.
A bus is on its way.
You're okay.
What's going on?
He's awake.
Kathy.
Welcome back, El.
What's going on?
You're in the hospital.
You're okay.
I'm not okay.
Where are you?
What do you mean?
I'm standing right next to you.
Oh, God.
I can't see you.
I can't see anything.
It's all a blur.
- Kathy?
- Right here, Elliot.
I'm right here.
Detective Stabler hit his head so hard,
his brain bounced off the front
and back of his skull.
How bad?
His CAT scan shows contusions
to the frontal and occipital lobes.
He's bleeding?
It's not life-threatening.
They're like bruises.
- Then why can't he see?
- The occipital lobe controls vision.
It's not uncommon with an injury like this
for there to be some temporary blindness.
- How temporary?
- Don't panic.
His brain should heal
in a couple of days.
And his vision should return.
He's seeing bright lights, shadows.
This is good news.
Captain, we got a problem in Picard's room.
Give me a minute.
His vision should return.
So you're saying that there's
a chance that it won't?
His MRI showed swelling in the optic nerve.
We'll know more in a few days.
- Who the hell are you?
- Special Agent Wayne Nelson.
I'm taking Mr. Picard into custody.
Mr. Picard is out
of the Bureau's jurisdiction.
He never crossed state lines
with either of our victims.
He did with the nine-year-old girl
he kidnapped in Mississippi.
Took her to Louisiana, raped her,
and left her there to die.
And his DNA is gonna prove it.
The girl Picard kidnapped
is Tiffany Lemarsh, nine years old.
Disappeared last week
from a bookstore
at a shopping mall
in Gulfport, Mississippi.
Found last night after four days
without food and water
in what's left
of Picard's house in Louisiana.
- Alive?
- Barely.
Neighbor's dog got a whiff.
Sniffed her out just in time.
They're charging Picard
with interstate kidnapping.
Feds faxed me the indictment.
Who called them?
- Didn't you?
- No.
We just picked him up this morning.
Never even got him into the system.
Then how do they know we collared him?
Can you do anything about it?
Feds' jurisdiction trumps ours.
We don't even get an extradition hearing.
Well, it doesn't matter.
This indictment's a crock.
Picard kidnaps Tiffany in Mississippi
and the feds indict him in Louisiana?
He raped her there.
It's part of the same crime.
The Feds can try him in either state.
Olivia, they're gonna drop the kidnapping
charge and let Louisiana try him for rape.
Because raping a child under the age of 12
in Louisiana is a capital crime.
I don't understand why you're so ticked off
about this, Casey.
The Feds are saving you
a lot of time and trouble.
The Feds are pushing
their own agenda.
Louisianan has the death penalty
and we don't.
That's why they want
Picard tried there.
And you're not about
to get screwed without a fight.
Look, I'm not going to let them
abuse their power
and emasculate
the authority of my office.
Problem is, I don't have
any legal standing to stop them.
But you do.
You mean as Mr. Picard's attorney.
The Feds want to extradite him
under the table.
That's a violation of due process.
You're a constitutional lawyer.
I never thought I'd see the day
when a prosecutor would ask
for my help.
Just get him back into my custody
and I'll have a judge
appoint a legal aid attorney
and you're out of it.
Deal?
You don't think I'm gonna pass up
the chance to beat those sneaky SOBs
at their own game, do you?
Thanks.
Um, Mr. Picard does have
some psychiatric issues.
Is it okay if our Dr. Huang evaluates him?
Can't hurt.
I got to war with the Feds,
I'm gonna need all the ammunition
I can get.
Metropolitan Correctional Center
Mental Health Unit
Thursday, October 11
Why did you attack detective Stabler?
Well, I saw the sign
on the truck in the park.
It said, "Time to escape."
A lot of people have seen that sign.
I know.
But the message was for me.
Have you seen any other messages?
Well, there... there was one
on a billboard.
It said, "You really need to get away."
So, uh...
Yeah, I pulled the car into a bus stop
and...
and got away as fast as I could.
Francine's sending the messages.
Who's Francine?
My sister.
Why is she sending you messages?
Because those boys raped her.
Are you okay, Saul?
I came home from school one day
and I heard them upstairs.
Listen, they...they are here...
I know those boys from school.
They're taking turns on her.
You like that?
You want some more?
She's screaming for help.
Stop it.
Leave her alone.
Get off her.
What did you do?
Nothing.
I froze.
I couldn't move.
Why'd they do such
a horrible thing to her?
She was just 11.
She was a little girl.
How old were you?
17.
But after that, I was never the same.
The stress of seeing your sister attacked
triggered you first psychotic break.
That's why you froze.
Doctors told me that
when they put me on the haldol.
- That worked?
- Sure did.
Till it stopped working.
- And when was that?
- Last year.
After Francine died.
Your doctors must've started you
on some new medication.
Well, only thing that worked was rispiridone.
But I felt like I was swimming
through wet cement.
You know, struggling to find every word.
Every thought.
So I stopped taking it.
And that's when the messages started.
And I saw those boys again.
The boys that raped your sister?
- Where?
- In that bookstore in Gulfport.
What happened?
I saw Francine.
She was in the store reading my book
Bridge to Nowhere.
Those boys were gathered around her.
She was in terrible danger.
- What did you do?
- Took her someplace safe.
But they found us.
Two of them held me down
and the other one raped her.
It was horrible.
I couldn't do anything.
But then I set a trap.
I took Francine to New York.
I knew they'd follow us.
Francine and me.
We lured them to the arch.
And this time, when they came to rape her,
I was ready.
I beat them with rocks.
I beat them so bad, they ran.
I saved Francine.
I made things right.
He's not a pedophile.
He's a schizophrenic.
He kidnapped those girls because
he thinks they're his sister Francine.
But will he ever realize that he's the one
that beat and raped Sabrina and Tiffany?
It's possible. But it's also possible
that he won't remember.
Right. So we have to wait
for his rispiridone to kick in.
If it kicks in.
What do you mean "if"?
Haldol helped him with
his schizophrenia for years.
Until his sister died.
It's possible that any medication we give
him won't work in times of great stress.
Are you saying he might not make it
through a trial?
Are you actually considering
putting him though one? / Yeah.
- After what he did to Sabrina Farmer...
- You heard what he said.
He believes that
his hallucinations are real.
He thinks that he saved her.
He belongs in a hospital.
I'll take that under advisement.
Casey, the man is sick.
Putting him in prison is no less
cruel and unusual punishment
than the Feds trying
to have him executed.
Text message from Picard's lawyer.
We don't have to worry
about the Feds anymore.
You don't think that's going
to stop Louisiana
from trying to get
their hands on him, do you?
Then maybe I should
send them a message.
Miss Novak, any comment
on the US attorney's decision
to drop the federal kidnapping charges
against Saul Picard?
We're pleased the Justice Department
has decided to stay out of state's business
and clear the way for us
to seek an indictment.
What will you do if Louisiana
extradites Mr. Picard
to face the death penalty?
I fully expect Louisianan
to file for extradition.
But we have Mr. Picard now,
and this is where he's going to stay.
Do you believe that capital punishment
is appropriate for the rape of a child?
What I believe isn't the issue.
Right now, that's not the law
of the State of New York.
If and when the legislature
makes that the law,
I will enforce it
to the best of my ability.
- Thank you.
- I hope you mean that.
Hey, mean what?
That you're not going to let
Louisianan have my client.
That's right.
I'm gonna try him here.
Why? / Because Louisiana
is not wasting any time.
Motion for extradition.
- Did you tell your client about this?
- Yes.
He wants to talk to you.
Rikers Island
Mental Health Wing
Friday, October 12
Mr. Picard.
This is Miss Novak.
Please call me Saul.
Okay.
Saul.
My medication is working.
So you understand what you did.
Yes.
Tell the other girls I'm sorry.
That I'd do anything to take it back.
- Would you like to make a statement?
- Yes.
Send me to Louisiana.
But you could face the death penalty.
That's what I want.
- Mr. Picard, that's not gonna h...
- I don't deserve to live.
Don't you understand?
If the state thinks that killing me
will stop one pervert from...
Doing what I did
to those poor little girls,
then it's worth it.
Please.
Let me go home to die.
You can't put Saul Picard on trial.
I don't have a choice, Barry.
Just because he's schizophrenic
doesn't mean he can't stand trial.
You know he's crazy.
Then file for a 730 hearing
and have his competency questioned.
He won't let me.
I'm his attorney.
I have to abide by what he wishes.
But you don't.
So now you're asking me for help.
He can waive extradition
if he's declared incompetent.
And if he's declared incompetent,
he can't stand trial and I can't allow that.
Then make a deal, Casey.
He pleads guilty and you send him
to a mental institution instead of a prison.
If you think Jack McCoy
is gonna let me get away with that,
you are crazier than he is.
So that's what this is about.
The new boss wants to show
he's tough on crime
and you want to be a team player
instead of doing the right thing.
The right thing?
Saul Picard raped an 11-yeal-old girl
and beat her to within an inch of her life.
No, Casey.
That's Saul Picard.
Look at him.
He's not the same man
who raped Sabrina Farmer.
Moredock has a point.
Picard didn't hurt Sabrina,
the fairy tales in his head did.
He wouldn't have had those fairy tales
if he stayed on his meds.
But he didn't know by not taking them
he'd turn into Godzilla.
But he was lucid when he made
the decision to stop,
- and that makes him responsible.
- Damn right.
There ought to be a law
for people like Picard.
Take your meds or we're gonna
force-feed them to you.
You think that you can prove
that Picard knew that he hurt someone?
Sabrina Farmer on the witness stand
is all the evidence I'll need to convict.
Then what, he goes back to Louisiana?
- If we let him.
- Don't let him, Casey.
I never picked you for being soft
on Capital Punishment.
It's a no-brainer. Death penalty's
never been a deterrent for murder.
Most killer strike once.
Animals who rape kids usually repeat.
Threaten to execute them for rape,
they have nothing to lose
by killing their victims to silence them.
But execute them, they'll never
hurt another child.
Exactly.
I'm gonna need your fives.
When do you want me on the stand?
Uh, I don't think I do.
I'll just use Sabrina and Elliot.
Oh, you don't need Elliot.
I saw everything that Picard did.
But you didn't hear what he said
and I need Elliot to show the jury
what Picard is capable of.
Well, the police surgeon said that
Elliot can't leave his house
until his vision's back.
Unless he has to appear in court.
Casey.
Elliot has a better chance
for a quicker recovery
if we don't stress him out.
Look, I know he appreciates you
looking out for him.
It's my job to look out for him.
He is perfectly capable
of making this decision on his own,
so I'll take to him myself.
Leave him alone, Casey.
I can't.
Coming.
It's Casey.
I know.
I can see you. Come on in.
I'm sorry, I...
Expecting a seeing eye dog and a cane?
Maybe.
To tell you the truth, so was I.
Have a seat.
It's...
It's just, uh, a little blurry.
But I'm getting better.
Better enough to drag you into court?
- Olivia said you were coming by.
- Yeah.
She was worried that you weren't up to it.
I'm a big boy.
And you're sure you can handle
facing Picard?
You know I'm gonna have
a child in a month.
That's scary enough.
It was the thought that I was never gonna
be able to see that child.
That terrified me.
So Picard...
bring him on.
Trial Part 38
Thursday, November 8
I was taking Mr. Picard to our car.
He tried to escape,
I attempted to subdue him,
and he head butted me.
What happened?
Uh, I fell backwards, head first,
through the rear window of the car.
How badly were you injured?
I sustained head injuries
that have left me temporarily blind.
Can you see the defendant now?
That's him right there.
Would you consider Mr. Picard dangerous?
I would consider him
extremely dangerous.
When Mr. Picard started attacking you,
was he saying anything?
He was repeating over and over,
"It's time to escape."
Mr. Picard told our psychiatrist
that a sign was sending him that message.
Did you see that sign?
- Yes.
- And was he distraught?
Yes.
In your experience as a police officer,
would you say that Mr. Picard
qualifies as an EDP?
Yes. / Would you please tell the jury
what that means?
EDP stands for Emotionally
Disturbed Person.
- In other words, he's crazy, right?
- Don't answer that, Detective.
He is not qualified to draw
that conclusion, counselor.
Did the defendant ever utter the name
Francine in your presence?
No.
Did he mention witnessing
his sister being gang raped
- and doing nothing to stop it?
- No.
Did he say it was his fault?
He never mentioned anything
about his sister in my presence.
Why?
Why... why should I?
Yeah, why should I trust God?
Control your client, Mr. Moredock.
One more time, sir, and I'll have you
removed from this courtroom.
He made me rape those girls.
I am your older brother, Francine.
I... I finally rescued you
from those boys...
- Just be quiet now, Saul.
- Why do you keep testing me?
Stop testing me, Francine.
Officers, remove the defendant.
You... you did this, Francine.
You brought him in to test me.
I can't face him.
Why do you keep making me face him?
Stop testing me!
Stop testing me, Francine!
- Your Honor...
- Don't bother, Mr. Moredock.
After what the jury just witnessed,
I am declaring a mistrial.
And before we start this freak
show up again, Miss Novak,
I'm calling for a 730 hearing
to determine whether Mr. Picard
is competent to stand trial.
You may step down, Detective.
We're adjourned.
Hey, Casey.
Casey!
What was that?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
You never wanted to try that guy.
I tried this case to the best of my ability.
Cut the crap.
You wanted Picard in the Loony Bin,
and you used me to put him there.
Elliot...
I'm fine.
Yes, sir.
I'll be right up.
You proud of yourself?
I don't need a lecture from you.
I know why you sandbagged Elliot
in court.
- Stay out of my desk!
- Where is he now, Casey?
Your schizo ex-boyfriend.
Is he locked up somewhere?
Get out of my office.
He's the reason that
you tanked the Picard case.
That man deserves to be punished
for what he did.
Wait, wait... what he did
to Tiffany Lemarsh or Sabrina Farmer,
or are you talking about
payback for what he did to Elliot?
You manipulated me and Elliot
to satisfy your own agenda.
Okay, you answer the question, Detective.
Who did you let it leak
to that we collared Picard?
Did you go straight to the Feds,
or did you back-channel it
through the Louisiana cops?
Oh, you're damn right I told the Feds.
They have a right to know.
No. You want Picard dead.
Louisiana kills him,
your hands are clean.
Those little girls are entitled
to some justice.
What you're talking about
isn't justice, it's revenge.
He's my partner, Casey.
And it's my case.
And how I handle it
is none of your damn business.
Because I don't answer to you.
We'll see.
Office of District Attorney Jack McCoy
Thursday, November 8
- Congratulations.
- For what?
The excellent job you did
as Saul Picard's defense attorney.
- Judge Bradley called me.
- Jack, I...
I told him he must be mistaken,
since I only have prosecutors
working in this office.
At least I thought I did...
until I got this.
- Who gave this to you?
- What matters is what's in it.
Five years ago, the cops responded to
a disturbance call in your apartment.
You told the officers it was mistake,
but it isn't true, is it?
My fiancee Charlie, he attacked me.
He was a schizophrenic
and he was off his medication.
When the police saw the cuts
and bruises on my face and neck,
they wanted to arrest Charlie.
But I thought I could help him.
So I identified myself as an ADA.
And I begged them not to take him in.
You abused the authority of this office
for personal reason back then?
Just like you're doing now!
Sick people like Saul Picard
shouldn't be put to death.
The last time I checked,
the supreme court still says
you can't execute a mentally ill
person in this country.
And what... what if a jury
found him responsible
because he was lucid when he decided
to stop taking his medication?
That's not your problem.
That's why he has a defense attorney.
No defense attorney could make a jury
see past what he did to those little girls.
So you weren't about to take
a chance he'd be convicted?
Because he belongs in a hospital,
not a prison cell, and you now it.
I'll tell you what I know.
You're going to stay on this
case through the 730 hearing,
and you're going to behave yourself.
Because if you don't,
I'm not only going to fire you,
I'll make sure the bar yanks your license.
And if you don't think
I have the juice to do it, try me.
Why did you rat me out to the DA?
Because you threw the case.
I had no choice after you
sold out Picard to the Feds.
Look, uh, Casey.
I'm as guilty as you are.
You were right.
I wanted revenge.
For Elliot.
Is he okay?
He'll be back to work next week.
How about Picard?
The judge ruled him incompetent.
Louisiana can't touch him now.
Do you think he'll ever get better?
I don't know.
I thought Charlie would get better.
What happened?
I got a call from the morgue
about six months ago.
A John Doe clipped by a passing cab.
No ID on him but my business card.
It was Charlie.
Maybe he'd be alive
if I hadn't make him leave.
Casey.
You had to save yourself.
What?
Picard made a noose out of his shirt
and tried to hang himself in lock-up.
New York State Mental Hospital
Saratoga Springs, NY
Friday, November 9
Hi.
Ms. Novak.
Call me Casey.
Why are you here?
I heard you tried to hurt yourself.
I'm not crazy.
I'm on my medication.
That's good.
I want to die.
You should have let them execute me.
I'd rather be dead than
live with what I've done.
You see, every day...
I get a little better.
And the better I get...
The worse I feel about
what I did to those girls.
Maybe one day you can forgive yourself
when you realize it wasn't your fault.
Wasn't it?