[Man Narrating]
In the criminal justice system...
all defendants are innocent
until proven guilty,
either by confession,
plea bargain or trial byjury.
This is one of those trials.
She had such great taste.
Simple, elegant, but edgy.
I was on my way to yoga
this morning,
and I saw her door was ajar,
so l-I opened it.
And there she was on the floor,
covered in blood.
Her face was-
[Sniffles]
It was awful.
We can talk later.
So-
[Clears Throat]
Steak knife was right about here,
five feet from the body.
How old?
Turned 18 a week ago.
Hell of a birthday present.
Pretty.
Yeah.
Especially for a guy.
Name's Carlos Martinez.
Rumor has it Carlos Martinez
got his ass kicked...
three nights ago
in a bar on 158th Street.
By whom?
A kid named Luis Ramirez.
Hey, you Luis?
Detective Ravell, N.Y.P.D.
We need to talk to you
about Carlos Martinez.
Okay.
He got killed last night.
Yeah.
Oh. I didn't know that.
- What happened to your eye?
- Basketball. I caught an elbow.
Aw, same thing happened
to me last year. Broke my nose.
Where do you play, the gym on
166th? No, the "Y" on 155th.
They play fours or fives
up there? Um, fours.
See, that's a better game. The
lanes don't get so crowded, right?
Yeah. We were hoping to
go down to the station,
clear up a few things. Yeah,
it won't take long, 10 minutes.
We can get a warrant if you
want. Uh, no, no, no, that's okay.
Ten minutes, right?
Not even. Come on.
[Luis] I met her at a club two
weeks ago. She had a black dress on.
She looked hot.
I saw the pictures.
Exactly.
So you know what I'm sayin'.
Hell, yeah. So, what happened?
So we smoked a- a-
Come on.
I'm Homicide, not Narcotics.
We got high, and then, um,
you know, we fooled around.
But I thought she was a woman
named Angelina.
I mean, she had-
Breasts.
Right.
But then my friend
tells me she's a guy.
And I'm like, " No way.
She's a chick and hot.' '
But he kept saying that I was wrong,
that I got played.
So, the other night we went
down to Club 186 lookin' for her.
Mm-hmm.
And then what?
And then we took her into the bathroom,
and we pulled down her skirt.
And you saw she wasn't a woman.
Right, and I flipped out.
So I started yelling, and she
slapped me. She slapped me.
So, I hit her back, and she ran
out the door. You go after her?
No.
Come on, Luis.
Don't lie to me.
I've been straight
with you, right?
Maybe I should talk
to a lawyer.
Sure, if you want.
You just give me the word,
and I'll stop.
But I gotta tell ya,
once lawyers get involved,
things get very complicated.
I mean, I can't talk to you.
You can't talk to me.
Which means I can't hear
your side of the story.
He's so damn cocky.
Luis, we know you did it.
[Scoffs]
What?
A guy saw you walking out of Carlos's
building with blood on your pants.
And on top of that, we found your hairs
in the apartment. D.N.A. Doesn't lie.
This is your last chance to come clean, Luis.
Otherwise I gotta call the D.A.' s office.
I didn't mean to kill her.
[Sobbing]
Of course you didn't.
She had a knife and I knocked it
away, and we just started fighting.
I didn't mean to kill her though.
I swear to God. It just-
It just kinda happened, you know?
[Sobbing] I didn't mean to
kill her. I swear to God.
You believe him?
Do I ever?
His prints are all over the apartment.
What about the knife?
Still waiting on lab results.
Well, either way, it supports
his self-defense claim.
Except he wasn't cut.
And he didn't call 911.
Well, charge him with murder,
but be careful.
I know. Men in tight dresses
make lousy victims. Exactly.
In light of the violent nature
and the gravity of the crime,
we request that Luis Ramirez
be held on remand.
[Judge] Ms. Mendez? Mr.
Ramirez has no criminal record,
works part-time
and is a student at City College.
His father owns a successful
plumbing business, employs 23 people-
- Keep moving, counselor. - Mr. Ramirez
has deep-rooted ties to this city,
in particular, Washington Heights.
My point, Your Honor, is-
Let me guess.
- He's not a flight risk.
- Correct.
In the audience today are his parents,
sister, friends and a priest.
Thanks for coming. Please be seated.
The defendant shall be remanded.
[Gavel Raps]
You couldn't cut this kid
some slack? He killed someone.
In self-defense.
Nice to see you again, Ana.
Yeah, nice to see you too.
I'd shake your hand, but protocol.
I understand.
Let's discuss this.
Who's she?
She used to work here.
She was a prosecutor?
Yeah, good.
One flaw-
Sometimes she thought
the defendants were telling the truth.
Angelina Martinez is the 26th
transgendered person assassinated this year,
yet no one cares
because she was transsexual.
Killing a tranny
isn't like killing a regular person.
It's less evil.
Almost acceptable.
[Continues, Indistinct] If the
self-defense theory falls apart,
she'll turn Carlos into a promiscuous
freak who liked to trick straight boys.
Yeah, and then hide behind some gay
panic theory. It's worked before.
How dare you accuse my son
of murder! And for what?
Because he got into a fight
with some joto? My son is-
- Hey, don't touch me!
- [Officer] Hey, hey!
Is everything okay here?
Yeah, it's fine.
Okay, let's go.
He left school when he was 15
'cause of the abuse.
Kids picking on him, beating
him up, calling him marica.
[Sighs] But he was always a good kid.
Were you close?
But... we lost touch last year.
He was upset at me, because
I refused to call him Angelina.
I just-just couldn't do it.
I tried, but it never felt right.
Even when he was dressed like that,
he was still my boy Carlos.
Did he ever mention somebody
called Luis Ramirez?
Not to me. But like I said,
we haven't talked in a while.
I met her two years ago
when she moved into my building.
Became best friends right away.
We just... connected.
Well, would Carlos ever lie
about his identity?
You mean with men?
With straight men.
She liked to flirt.
I know that.
It made her feel good to pass.
It was like the ultimate compliment.
Would she ever have sex with someone
without letting him in on the secret?
I hope not. Say she's at a bar
and some guy's chatting her up.
Does Carlos say, "Don't get too
excited, big boy, I'm a guy,"
or does she sit there, smiling,
pretending she's J. Lo?
I'd like to think
she'd be honest, but-
But what?
Last few months, she'd wait for
them to ask. It was like a game.
- What if they didn't ask?
- She wouldn't tell.
Did Carlos ever mention
a guy named Luis?
Only man she talked about, last few
months anyway, was some hottie named Julio.
Lived in Chelsea. Said he
was the man of her dreams.
It's hard to imagine having sex
with someone and not noticing-
It wasn't that kind of sex.
And you had no idea he-
No. And if I did,
I would've stopped.
Why did you go to Carlos's
apartment that night?
To tell her to stop lying about me.
So the two of you
weren't a couple?
A couple?
I'm not gay.
We did it once, like I told you.
Right.
So what happened when you went
to Carlos's apartment?
She started-
He started.
Carlos is a man.
We need a jury to look at this as a fight
between two men, not a man and a woman.
When I got to his apartment,
I wanted to go tell him to stop
lying about me, and he flipped out.
He grabbed a knife.
I slapped it away.
And we started fighting. You thought he
was going to kill you, so you beat him up.
Right.
How many times
did you punch him?
The victim was struck
15 times in the head and face.
Fractured nose,
cheekbone, jaw.
And we got significant contusions and
edema in and around the cerebellum.
Any offensive wounds?
Nothing substantial.
So it wasn't really a fight.
Oh, it was a massacre.
Victim may have been knocked
unconscious after the first punch.
[Gaffney] So the next 14 were
- Meant to kill.
It was ugly.
No doubt.
Can you testify
to the first-punch theory?
Not yet,
but I'll keep diggin'.
Man two, four to 12,
sounds reasonable to me.
Are you kidding? Why don't we just send
him to bed without supper and call it a day?
- He's a good kid. - Who punched a
110-pound girl 15 times in the face.
- After he pulled a knife.
- You want a deal, go to Bloomingdale's.
Their winter sale started
this morning. Just so you know,
we already have two witnesses
prepared to testify...
they hooked up with Carlos
under false pretenses.
- So? - So he was playing
a dangerous game and-
And what?
Got what was coming to him?
File a motion to exclude all testimony
relating to Carlos's sex life.
What the hell
is he doing here?
Help you, gentlemen?
We need to talk.
One of my employees told me that
my son got in a fight with some-
with... a transsexual...
at Club 186.
So I asked Luis about it,
and, uh,
he told me
he and this person...
met a few weeks back,
had a drink, and-
But he thought that
this person was a girl.
[Speaking Spanish]
So I asked Luis how many people knew
about this person, and he said a lot.
That Carlos was spreading lies about
him, telling people that they were dating.
So I told Luis we must speak
to this man right away.
I mean, this is a young man's
reputation we're talking about.
An honorable Latino man.
I understand.
We went to Carlos's apartment,
and I told him to stop lying.
"My son made a mistake.
He thought you were a girl.
I mean, déjalo ahí, you know,
leave it at that.' '
But he started yelling,
this little-
this little tulip.
Calling me a bastard.
"Chi chi cabrón," he kept saying.
"Chi chi cabrón.' '
So, I told him to calm down.
You know, I just wanted to talk.
But he grabbed a knife,
and before I knew it, he cut me.
So l- I grabbed his wrist...
and I slammed it against the wall.
And we fought.
And when it was over,
he was dead.
Luis never touched that boy.
He confessed
because he's a good man.
A loyal son.
Siéntese.
Two confessions
for the same crime?
It's better than none.
Well, maybe not.
The jury could eat it up.
A father and son so loyal
that they both confess...
to the same crime
to protect the other.
Well, loyal, maybe, but it
doesn't mean they're not guilty.
Well, since when does being guilty
guarantee a conviction?
Hold off on indicting the father
until you corroborate his story.
We need to make sure he's telling
the truth and not playing hero.
I was watching TVin bed when I
heard Orlando screaming at Luis.
Screaming?
[Speaking Spanish]
Right. Talking.
So I went to see what was going on, and
they were walking out the door. [Door Closes]
Go upstairs, sweetie.
Are you okay, Mama?
Yes, of course.
Did Orlando say anything to you before
he and Luis left for Carlos's apartment?
I'm an attorney. Anything
you say is 100% confidential,
so, please, speak freely.
He walked out
and slammed the door.
That is not what happened.
[Speaking Spanish]
I came to you, I told you that Luis
and I were going out for a little while.
And then I kissed your cheek.
And then I asked if you wanted anything
from the store, and then we left.
Remember?
Right.
Good.
I knew Luis didn't kill that boy.
- Luis couldn't kill a flower.
- Then why is he in jail?
He'll be out soon.
And my husband?
He'll be arrested in a few days,
charged with murder.
Then what? Then we convince
a jury he's innocent.
Now, we may need
to call you as a witness.
If so, all you need to do
is tell the truth.
You're all right with that, right?
If telling the truth
will get my son out of jail.
Hey, so I spoke to the lab.
Blood on the knife, D.N.A. Under
the fingernails match Orlando's.
Son of a bitch,
he was telling the truth.
Sure. About pounding Carlos to the ground
anyway. You don't believe the knife story?
A guy needs a story to tell, right?
He grabs a knife, he cuts himself.
All of a sudden it's
self-defense. You got proof?
I don't have proof
the Easter bunny doesn't exist,
but I'm pretty
sure I'm right there too.
The father's the real bad guy.
Except he's got a decent defense.
Yeah, his blood's on the knife,
but his prints aren't.
His self-defense story could fly.
If Luis changes his story
to jibe with his father's.
We'd impeach his testimony
based on his original confession, but-
Who knows
what the jury will believe?
[Sighs]
Flip the son against the father.
But do it soon, before defense
lawyers rewrite history on us.
Scare that kid so he serves up
papa on a Tiffany platter.
Only two people know what
happened in that apartment.
I represent one,
you represent the other.
[Latin]
Your point is?
There's no need to panic
or try to cut a deal.
[Sniffles] If we work together,
both of them will walk.
Work together?
Make sure that their testimony is consistent.
Especially with respect to the knife.
I represent Luis. I'll do whatever
I think is best for him. Understand?
[Laughs]
Is that what they taught you up there in
New Haven, how to act like a WASP bitch?
Thanks for the coffee, Pedro.
Life in prison is a long time
when you're 20 years old.
I get it. You're prepared to make him
a generous offer for his cooperation.
A fair offer.
Fine, fair.
Will he talk? Well, I
hope so. He's innocent.
Well, he's not that innocent.
If he hadn't taken dear old dad to the
apartment, Carlos might still be alive.
It's my problem. It's up to me to tell them
- To what?
To go to jail for 30 years for smoking
pot and having sex with a transsexual?
[Sighs]
You know, she was so-
Beautiful.
I mean, she looked like a model.
You saw her. You know.
She made me laugh.
I still hate her though,
for lying and tricking me.
But she didn't deserve to die.
And you don't deserve
to celebrate your 50th birthday...
in prison.
[Sighs] I wish I didn't tell
my father where she lived.
Just tell the prosecutor
what happened.
You're a good kid, Luis,
and a good son,
but you're an idiot
if you don't take this deal.
He came into my bedroom
and punched me in the face.
Started calling me a faggot.
I said I didn't know
she was a man.
But he kept saying
I was a disgrace.
Then he-Then he pulled me
out of bed and said, " Get dressed.
We're gonna find your girlfriend
and set things straight.' '
[Kibre]
You knew where Carlos lived?
Well,
the night that-
the night when we-
Okay.
When we got there,
I rang the buzzer.
She let us in. I apologized
for hitting her before.
So that she would let you in?
Yes.
Keep going.
When we got inside,
my-my father just-
He just pushed her, started
screaming at her, calling her a liar.
And then Angelina
just spit at him.
- And he-
- Did you try to stop it?
No, but I wanted to.
Okay.
What about the knife?
When he stopped hitting her,
he was afraid
she might be dead.
So he grabbed a knife, cut himself
and he threw it on the floor.
And wiped his prints off it?
Yes.
So your father punched Carlos
in the face 15 times...
because he spit at him?
Yes.
Are you prepared to tell a jury
what you've just told us?
Yes.
Are you telling the truth?
Man two, three to nine.
One to three.
Forget it. There's no intent
here, Tracey. You know that.
[Clears Throat]
You always open high.
Three to nine, best and last.
And in case you forgot,
when I say "best and last," I mean it.
Three to nine it is.
Luis?
Is that a yes?
Yes.
Before I put my client's liberty
in your hands,
I need to know
that each of you is prepared...
to acquit Mr. Ramirez if the People
do not meet their burden of proof.
If you cannot promise me that,
raise your hands.
Thank you.
Counsel, approach the bench.
Peremptories, Ms. Kibre?
Jurors Six and Eleven,
Your Honor.
Both Hispanic? Your Honor,
Batson clearly states that-
I know what it states. Ms. Kibre?
This has nothing to do with race.
In Hernandez v. New York,
the U.S. Supreme Court...
held that a prosecutor has the right
to dismiss bilingual Latino jurors...
based on a concern that such jurors
might not disregard Spanish testimony.
It's an excuse to create a jury with no Latinos
in violation of the Equal Protection Clause.
We have several witnesses
who will testify in Spanish.
Jurors Six and Eleven
have stated...
that they might disregard the English
translation of the court interpreter.
With all due respect,
this is racist. Maybe.
But I'm not in the mood to overrule
Justice Kennedy this morning.
Jurors Six and Eleven
may be excused.
I gotta tell you,
I don't like it.
I'm just trying to put the bad guy
away, not win the Nobel Peace Prize.
You excused those jurors
because you thought they'd sympathize.
Look, when you're first chair, you
can have whoever you want on your jury-
Latinos, lawyers, convicted felons
- go crazy.
But right now, you support my choices
whether or not you think they're aggressive.
Or cheap. I was being polite
when I said aggressive.
I'm sorry, but I think it's out of line
to hide behind Hernandez like that.
Well, I don't care what you think. Oh.
And neither does
Angelina Martinez.
- Angelina?
- Yeah, Angelina.
- What, so it worked?
- Yeah, we changed her gender.
Well, I guess
I'll be drafting a motion.
Miss Kibre filed a motion
to amend the indictment.
- In what respect?
- To change the victim's name from Carlos to Angelina.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Mrs. Martinez changed her son's name...
- to Angelina last week.
- You're kidding?
She felt it was important to honor
her daughter's identity posthumously.
You're not suggesting we refer to
the victim as Angelina in court?
Well, as of last week,
that is her legal name.
He was born Carlos
and died Carlos.
- But today she's Angelina.
- [Judge] I agree.
Your Honor
- You saw the certificate, Mr. Moreno.
In light of the name change, Your
Honor, I think it's appropriate...
that we refer to Angelina as a woman
and use all feminine pronouns.
This is ridiculous. You could slap a
Prada dress on a bull and call him Sally-
that does not make
the damn thing a she.
Carlos Martinez was a man,
anatomically.
To refer to him as a woman
is absurd.
Sure is.
The victim's name
is Angelina Martinez,
and he, or she, shall be referred to
as such at all times in my courtroom.
After that, you can call him or her
whatever you want. The jury will do the math.
Ms. Kibre.
You just used up
your "creative argument" quota, okay?
The defendant brutally beat
to death Angelina Martinez...
for one reason-
Because she had the audacity...
to tell a few neighborhood friends
that she was dating his son.
As the trial progresses,
you will hear testimony
from a witness...
who was in Angelina's apartment
the night that she was murdered,
who saw with his own eyes
what happened.
When he's finished,
you will have no doubt...
that Orlando Ramirez
is guilty of murder.
The name of the witness
is Luis Ramirez-
the son of the defendant.
[Kibre] What happened when your
father came home that night?
He said he heard about what
happened with Angelina at Club 186.
Then what?
I told him that I thought
that Angelina was a woman...
and that I freaked out
when I found out that she wasn't.
Anything else happen?
He said we need to speak
to Carlos about the situation.
Is that it?
Yes.
Did your father
punch you, Luis?
- Objection. Leading.
- Sustained.
What happened when you and your
father went to Angelina's apartment?
What happened when
you were inside the apartment, Luis?
May we take a break,
Your Honor?
Do you need a few minutes,
Mr. Ramirez?
- No.
- Continue, Ms. Kibre.
What happened
once you and your father...
were inside Angelina's
apartment?
Um, they started arguing
and Angelina pulled a knife.
- Excuse me?
- Angelina pulled a knife.
Angelina pulled a knife? In a sworn statement,
you said your father stabbed himself after he-
[Moreno] Your Honor. Please. Permission
to treat the witness as hostile.
May I please be heard,
Your Honor?
- Who the hell are you?
- Ana Mendez, counsel for the witness.
May I please have five minutes
alone with my client?
- I wasn't raised that way.
- What way? To tell the truth?
No, to testify against my father.
Yes, it's tough. I know.
But the truth is, we ran out of easy choices
the night you watched your old man kill Carlos.
You tell the truth,
you spend three years in jail,
or take the Fifth
and be tried for murder.
Your call.
I'm not testifying.
You're sure?
You're a fool.
Witnesses lie, Tracey.
Jurors know that.
They're not blind.
Thank you.
I know.
Just should have seen it coming.
He's been protecting his father
since day one,
telling anybody who'd listen
that he's some kind of Latino saint.
And then in return,
his father kicks the hell out of him.
It's not easy to be objective
about your father.
- Takes a lot of strength.
- Or in my case, therapy.
Now what?
We get ready for more lies.
- Orlando's testifying?
- First thing tomorrow.
Tell me again.
Whose genius idea was this...
to flip a young Dominican boy
against his father?
If he's good, he walks.
Then be sure he's not good.
When Mr. Martinez
grabbed the knife,
did you believe you were
in danger of your life?
Yes. Absolutely.
And I, of course,
was worried about Luis too.
So, how come you didn't just run out
of the room? There was nowhere to go.
The apartment was small.
The door was shut.
If I had turned to open it,
he would have stabbed me.
And, like I said,
I was worried about Luis.
I mean,
I couldn't leave my son in there.
I'd rather die than have
something happen to him.
Thank you.
The knife that Angelina grabbed was on
the table, in the living room, right?
Yes.
Strange place for a steak knife.
Objection.
- Sustained.
- When Angelina grabbed the knife,
you were seven feet
from the door, right?
Yes.
It's a small apartment.
But you chose not to run out the door because
you were afraid she might stab you or your son?
- Right.
- But Luis was even closer to the door than you were.
I mean, he could've been out the
door in one second. And you in two.
Is there a question, Your Honor?
There is.
Angelina didn't really grab a knife off
the table in the living room, did she?
- What?
- You're making that up, aren't you?
Objection.
Sustained.
[Kibre]
After Angelina grabbed the knife,
you claim she stabbed you?
- Yes.
- Did you need stitches?
No.
After she "cut" you,
you slammed her wrist
into the wall, the knife fell...
and you started fighting?
Yes.
So you forced the knife out of her
hand before you threw the first punch?
- Yes.
- How much do you weigh?
155 pounds.
[Kibre] And you were
afraid for your life...
even though Angelina- who
weighed no more than 110 pounds-
was no longer
in possession of a knife?
She might pull another knife.
Or maybe a gun.
Oh, well, that must be
why you punched her-
all 110 pounds of her-
15 times in the face and head,
because you were afraid for your life.
Yes.
[Scoffs]
Nothing further.
Jury's back.
That's way too fast.
On the sole count of the indictment,
murder in the second degree,
we find the defendant
not guilty.
Thank you.
Sorry about the verdict. What are
you gonna do? The kid screwed you.
Screwed himself.
How's that?
- I'm gonna try him for murder.
- Good.
I want you to find out
everything you can about this kid-
where he hangs out,
who his friends are.
Right now, he's looking
a little too clean. Sure.
I'm not a mind reader.
How did I know he was-
Apologize? What are you,
crazy? To that ass-kissing-
Yeah, well, that's okay by me. I like
Staten Island. The grass is greener.
Yeah, well, screw you too.
You all right?
Yeah, sure. Politics at the
precinct. You know how it is.
Yeah, we got more work to do.
Kibre's gonna try Luis for murder.
Even though the old man got a pass?
It's because the old man got a pass.
Oh, I knew that chick had balls.
Speaking of chicks with balls,
Kibre wants us to go uptown,
check out the tranny scene.
See if anyone knows
our buddy, Luis.
What do you mean they're trying
Luis for murder? Technically-
I don't care about technically! All I know is
my kid is in jail for something he didn't do,
and I'm paying you
400 bucks an hour.
To represent Luis
to the best of my ability.
Ay mujer! Just tell me how
I get my kid out of jail.
Are you willing to testify?
And say what?
That you killed Carlos Martinez all
by yourself, that Luis wasn't involved.
I'm not going back to jail. You
won't have to. Doublejeopardy.
You've been tried and acquitted. That
means you can say whatever you want...
and there's nothing Kibre
or anyone else can do about it.
[Latin]
Mm, never seen him.
Too bad. He's cute.
Don't you think?
- Not my type.
- Name Luis Ramirez ring a bell?
You know any other places around
here that, uh, cater to men,
who might prefer
a certain type of female?
I'll get on the stand,
I'll smile at thejury,
and I'll explain how I beat
the hell out of that mariposa.
Say Luis had nothing to do with it. That
he tried to stop me, that he was crying.
Hard to convict someone of murder when you have
a witness raising his hand, saying, " I did it.' '
Luis still brought his father to the
apartment knowing he was gonna kill that girl.
Luis watched a fight between two men. A fight
a jury has already decided wasn't a crime.
- He's still guilty of murder.
- Fine. You'll lose again.
Before you go, I should probably
tell you about some of my witnesses.
They're really tall.
Attractive.
Very feminine.
Great boobs. Penises.
I've got five men
who seem to know Luis-
or should I sayJulio-
very well.
Apparently he uses a different
name when he's in that world.
So what?
So Luis wasn't tricked.
He was dating Angelina for months.
But you already knew that.
So he was dating a tranny.
Doesn't mean he's guilty of murder.
Gives us great motive though. Man
leads a double life and gets outed,
so he and his father kill the "outer"
to ensure that his secret stays safe.
- Sounds pretty compelling to me.
- You're threatening my witness.
No. I'm just sharing information,
just like you.
Looks like your friends are finally gonna find
out just what kind of a man Luis really is.
The whole city is about
to find out that my son is a-
a faggot.
You're a disgrace to me.
To your mother.
To your sister.
To God.
It's not like I wanna be this way.
I just am.
You make me sick.
I can change.
- It's too late.
- What do you mean?
I'm done with you... forever.
You killed Angelina
because I loved her.
Don't do this to him.
I'm not gonna testify for that-
Orlando, please.
Let that joto rot in jail!
[Sobbing]
He loved Angelina.
I mean, really loved her.
He didn't know
his father was going to kill her.
But he did. And he lied on the
stand. He has to answer for that too.
He lied to protect the father who beat the
hell out of him and killed the person he loved.
Look, either way,
Angelina's dead.
And Orlando is sipping beer and
eating sancocho at his favorite café.
Man two, one to three.
Best and last.
I'll speak to Luis.
Talk fast. Offer's good
till 9:00 a.m. Tomorrow.
It's a good thing we know each other-
someone else might think you'd gone soft.
Whatever.
[Judge] Is there an
agreed-upon recommendation?
[Man] Yes, Your Honor, five years'probation
- [Mouthing Words]
With a condition of drug treatment
and counseling as deemed necessary.
[Judge] Mr. Timmins, I will
accept your guilty plea...
and hereby impose the sentence as described
by the assistant district attorney.
[Whispering, Indistinct] Please see the
probation officer before you leave. Thank you.
[Gavel Raps]
[Sobbing]
[Whispering, Indistinct]
My wife made me come.
L-
Your son hanged himself
three hours ago.
I'm sorry for your loss.
He always was weak.
Yeah, well,
he wasn't tough like you.
Not everybody's got the guts
to kill a 110-pound girl,
or sacrifice their only son...
on the altar
of their own pathetic pride.
L- I am a good father.
Ana!
[Sighs] I just want to say
I'm really sorry about Luis.
Thank you.
I never told that kid to lie.
You know that, right?
Yeah, I know.
[Howling]