(Ruriko) Hino Rintaro of "phosphorus" I mean I "phosphorus" of
ethics violations
(Ruriko) do not buy this photo
If you did not want to appeal?
(Hino Rintaro) Please return your
refuse
(Araki) a little and calm down.
Do you'll sell
in the photo much in? I wonder if in  50 million
(Ruriko) of Koch teacher more is not a Wakan
story.?
(Araki) 50 million I...
. It 's'll pays  (Ruriko)?
Rintaro teacher of ethics violations.
Nfufufu... ha ha ha...
There!
What's yo...
Eh! Lie!
That... you...
-Out... listen...
KikuChiyo's?
There KikuChiyo san's KikuChiyo san!
It's Yappa likely.
No, ~ Kawan not Na ~!
I what I'm old Anta customers
. To be taken to  Yes Ano ~ senior ➡
I'll I you were asked to
serving sake and I is only twice
No - You're still beautiful . and are you doing anything saying I'll quit
....
What say do wonder this
to strike in this dignified ➡
Do I Tteyuu  adult sex appeal?
A little...
(Araki) No ~
. Looking Innovation  something di - and it ➡
Na likely sucked
. Contrived ! Fufufu...
Hohoho... there
.
Is it not it about time
criminal comes time?
Well police come
Criminal? Fu ~ N
Here hey probably psychiatry
. And I come  patients Toka
Sometimes such
dangerous incident tangling of ➡.
Well then say... 's bother you
Hinorin
Next will come from since the telephone
. I keep prepared  50 million yen
Say hello
Ah...
Phew ~...
. Thank you
and let me hear the  senior wit.
The I Mom that baked
hands of geisha of any or example
Yes
And (Araki) you'll'm there that face ➡
many times fooled into
gold and people I'll'm Teru face
. to apologize to  (Ikumi) Yume乃?
Yes actually ➡ by now to do
party and the other day colleagues
There and I had teaser
And (Ikumi) so was it
Yes
.. And to have been saying
's  shy ➡
is forcibly ended up teaser
inconvenience In it there was no one with
No ➡'m co like to such
shy in the parlor
Hey I'm not
. Want to apologize  is I was the thing
(Landlady) dream viz Nyan Wait ➡ from being a complicated story
now
is multiplied by the  later voice masu I
En'noji president
(Yume乃) is hoo.
(Ikumi of the voice) would like to apologize
is more of me
It because I did not notice
until told to illness teacher of that child
. Even if living together  Yumechiyo Mr.
to ➡
unaware case There are many
. ➡ by increased contact with the mother
I think I symptoms are observed strongly
. Is  mother...
Yume乃 Mr. Good evening
there Good evening
(En'noji) AoiAkira Although it is
acquisition negotiations with medical corporation ➡
now it has compromise of nearly
amount
. It 's  (pond) Heh Decca have hospital.
How much?
(En'noji) is 60 billion in extraordinary
600 !?
I pretty to do but I hospital
(Hasumi) is with land because
cheap shopping or the
Ah so?
(En'noji)
So it is's a matter of subsidy
Ah and'm it a do ➡
I wonder if not-kun asked me one destination?
(En'noji)... and you say you and with?
I do want you to one treatment a patient
(Miyagawa) Is the patient?
Oh'm likely brain tumor
. It is a specialized field of Hasumi kun when it comes to
. What kind  Yes?
No disease of thing but I do not know that detailed
➡
You know I that Kusunoki Shozo?
Minister
'm A guy of one son
. On the facts and say  Kusunoki Minister ➡
it. It holds the approval rights of  subsidies...
're right.
That is, whether of five billion yen subsidy I get
➡
It is that
suffering from arm of  Hasumi Professor
It's a blatant Kimi I really do,
. There  This mouth was slipping
. I'm fine ? Hasumi you.
I it depends also on site...
Here I'll not say
that kind of negative thing
. Wonder if not me doing help  Hasumi teacher somehow
?
I would be happy
is everyone in here if you  successful?
(En'noji) please do not worry.
Hasumi-kun is
one of the best brain surgeon in Japan
. I'll have  rely on
. I understand
(pond) Ha ha ha...
Ja Do you try to toast
(En'noji ) Before that... you hoo
. You  rude
. My name is  pond coverage Secretary
Nice to meet you Araki.
(Araki) ⦅hey⦆
⦅Hasumi Do you
forgot my face? ⦆
Somehow
Araki you and Hasumi kun as was the synchronization of the internal
He psychiatry that because ➡
and I'm going to let you do
the after  Hino-kun.
(pond) N~tsu?
You mean the No such going to do
Hino-kun?
I excellent but I ➡
rather hear that you say  people
. It is under consideration to what to do  future
Likely to Fall-N
(Sound of clapping)
it will excuse me.
Good evening is Yume乃
(pond) Fufufu... dream viz Nyan
Another pond-chan wanted to meet
(Pond) me'll also it ~
rough What story?
No - it's another fun adult story
Well today is likely to drink a good wine
and
Ready to
«Yes»
No ~.
Hey Genki?
Long time
Oh and there was a little while ago
I mean by that Hino?
Araki is not it likely to
return to psychiatric
You what is...
. It!?  (Kaoru) it safe to have if
(Fukuhara)?
Lightheadedness little Standing
Whether you have not been told?
Not  nothing heard
I do have that bastard what thought
Hasumi teacher
(Hasumi) What is it?
Can you see my face?
Do not listen to  stupid is required
vision test..
Not required
Iran
Hasumi teacher
. And intend to move to the front without fear  Now both!
I'm you our ally
<This save Mayoe that lamb our
modern ➡
is a story of a doctor >
♬ ~
was  <My name delay
The Hino is Rintaro psychiatrist>
♬ ~
(Kaoru) Aizawa Akira is Mr.
thank you
. Crept
please.?
Surgery What it gonna be impossible?
Yes surgery is off-label
(Buzz)
(Miyagawa) Hasumi What does it mean
and professor surgery off-label?
Any
extraction difficult brain tumors operating until now ➡
Is not it came been  success
. Said TAMAE the  reason
. When I saw the  MRI image...
Left tumors of the temporal lobe has been
infiltration to the vicinity of the hippocampus.
The lumpectomy involves the risk of
fairly
. Wonder  to the risk of death does not mean there is
?
It is to put the female in the hippocampus
. There are
likely to lose  one is wrong if storage
In this op is not refuse.
What Is misuse?
You also would have noticed?
Rintaro teacher?
And (Fukuhara) is in now examination
Along or
(Miyagawa)
until the end speak in my room at
teacher of the room?
If you do not Morawa
is firmly in  Hasumi professor I do's trouble.
Yes?
(Fukuhara) that... I also ➡
I'm there
may want to talk
Is it a nice little?
Is it good?
I say
. Do you like to  Akira's dance?
Dance likes.
Thing I'd not so much remember
parlor and ➡
You have to know when dancing
Is likely or
. Do I started
dance from an early  When?
Probably from about the age of 21
I'd What was it doing
bad even from when I small ➡
Dance only I was me compliments for the first time
mom
I "indeed my daughter" and
. It is memories of
mom want to cherish
Also my first time in the parlor When I went ➡
I was impressed  to your dancing.
I look forward  also please come
Thank you
(Kaoru), please return it with the care
.. Please be  Hino teacher hey come
eh?
I came Hino
. Was copper ?
Look at this
[TV] (Hasumi) check the depth of the tumor.
(Hasumi) micro Cooper
[TV]
(nurse) Yes
[TV] and (doctors)
Hasumi Is teacher okay?
I do not still visible
Hasumi professor today also refused the operations of Toku患 of
Chairman
He previously a successful
brilliantly operating in the same case also there.
Should you can not  do not do it
A little while ago and had been strange fell way
in the examination room of Hino teacher
Is a simple dizziness did not think
Maybe even there I'm did was so
⦅Is not misunderstand⦆
You will misunderstand it've got to misunderstanding.
? It
Kind of relationship when from time What?
Since the beginning of the year
this year.?
number of operations is has decreased Gakutto
Ah....
So Speaking Hasumi teacher  was denied
vision test
Professor not wearing glasses
.
Visually impaired can not be corrected in the  That glasses
Professor's brain surgeon
You should be able to deal with
yourself if there is a problem in the brain
. What does it mean ?
Impaired vision can not be corrected with glasses
. It might be  psychogenic
visually impaired
You rude
(En'noji) huh...
(En'noji ) No dates
operations was decided?
Is being considered
. More than there is a street
risk that you would like  this morning....
It looks like you do not know
Eh?
And if sold on to
Kusunoki minister in matter of  this time ➡
talk  new hospital go to
smooth
Kimi ➡ for their parent-child
what it is difficult of life instead of also  it becomes benefactor
layers familiar if ➡
Kimi anyone complain there is no
on to become director of the new hospital
Ha...
I'm told you
To "cutting-edge medical Toshiminami International Center Akatsuki that could
The ➡
1 people also want to save
the future of many patients in the "I
. not it  a dream come true!
Ha....
What are you hesitating?
'm Not right that the "no"  to you
. You'll not say
Nante does not have to  storage
It is
I I that do that saved you from medical litigation
. Do not forget  Reyo Deku!
Take out a sure surgery schedule
until tomorrow.
I hope?
Was aware
(Less dream) mom
You say lesson
And (Ikumi) and'm going with a
care nice day
Yes
There sister Welcome back.
there mom
sorry to hurry preparation.
(Ikumi) If you're tired I'll say
When you have rest once in a while?
Lesson nor parlor
Unpleasant even...
and (Ikumi) say No I once in a while
I'm sorry
always inconvenience us over to
(Ikumi) No. I I also.
Rather Yare noticing until I'm sorry now anything
I guess Akira also thy ➡
even thy  Yume乃 ➡
Hey because Which also like
N~tsu?
Mom...
(Ikumi) N~tsu.?
♬ ~
Kukuku...
Ha ha ha...
Hahahaha...!
I Okkashii!
The Is the gone are brainwashed  until mom
Hinorin
Mom because I leave the parlor
. Probably very Even  mom?
I Who's the earn
Yume乃...?
Once you have it's psychogenic
What I wonder cause?
Chairman new hospital ➡
are you try to make  is I think I know
?
Yeah
. It will do is left director
of the hospital 's  rumor? Hasumi teacher
Well it Who information?
~ You are? Nurse station
Rumor treasury variety of
scary Na - a sense.
So wonder if friction of such hospital politics that not a you doing to
accumulation?
And wish I refuse
If so cornered that
They are different from
values and Rintaro
. To  the same doctor?
It's kind of Toko really insensitive.
That people are ➡ for ranks of
The Great White Tower Tteyuu University Hospital
many things because I come to the
sacrifice
Sacrifice Hey...
. Need to climb
until paying  such a thing You are kana is?
Probably the same
such Rintaro Even?
N~tsu?
Not at the expense of their own
by mom Even Rintaro?
All the same
. Of'm fighting Good luck doing  so
I'm sorry...
suddenly is started to say the strange thing
I'm there is Mizushima ask
What?
Hasumi teacher Good morning
.... (Fukuhara: Kaoru) Good morning
(Hasumi) Good morning
(Fukuhara) Professor please
(Hasumi) What is it?
It seems there is talk Hino teacher
Hino.? We are now meeting!
Brain to you Yes contact since
Do not worry.
What?
Will excuse me
Oh...
Hey! Hey!
And (Fukuhara) and rude
(Hasumi) It's what to do! Hey!
(Fukuhara) I'm sorry I
. Was  rude.
Sorry Hasumi teacher
(Hasumi) aha
Whether there is
popular because do up here
Bad, but your way is not get used unsatisfactory
.
Problems  vision It will nice day suffer?
(Hasumi) What can you do to Kimi?
You can hear the story
(Hasumi) not
So solve anything
. Clues  resolution might grasp
. Has blurred  your face.
this character can not be read
tunnel vision vision 0.01.
Head MRI findings abnormal None
optic nerve abnormality None
. I mean I  cause unknown
Do not see any solution
Hasumi teacher ➡
to try received a  my examination Do not you? I do want to say
in the  psychogenic visual disorder
?
It does not know yet
(Hasumi) Mr. region'm good at
.. Is  teacher I also doctor
Now you feel you can see painfully
Sympathy to It does not matter
If you give me me!
At this late hour it does not anyhow.
(Pond) Hello
[TEL] (En'noji) had somehow ➡
Great was the place where I thought
is trying Sashiageyo telephone
. But it is matter of  minister of your son?
It's obvious !
Minister waiting for the fast reply as possible
. I have  what linger.
Or
Do you want to miss this opportunity?
There is not outrageous
And I'm already in invested hundreds of millions of
. Do not make written me to shame if !
This fool!
Even if  So no... I only just thing
stomach hurts.
Ah... I want to drink tea
Hino teacher of tea...
Oh ~
Pond Secretary'm angry
Other than "yes" answer does not accept
!
Hasumi white  reply! The answer!
I'm a lifesaver of differents!
I found  (Hasumi).
So'm good
(Araki) What? Hasumi?
I end more than He is hate
Senior Let's reduce a little
'm With you saying
what the doctor like a thing
Please also heard what I have to say.
Yes Yes.
It 's  I
Ttsu~tsu Tatte was him and synchronization ➡
'll's another '10
quit that University Hospital
. And he has  Hasumi teacher to visually impaired
(Voice of Araki)
certainly Do not state it was funny
You should was something in the past
. You come into  tea.
The Haa...
. Is not it has expired  Ocha~tsuPa
or
What? It
"Medical accidents"?
(Araki) Oh
She was also Toku患 of En'noji
"Victims satonaka Mizuki's 31-year-old
President daughter of a certain famous confectionery maker"
Ah.
My was also a patient
Eh?
(Mizuki) ⦅everyone
and I have to say my ill⦆
⦅much I'm being monitored⦆
⦅Yeah⦆
⦅even now...⦆
⦅hate... Stop it! ⦆
⦅Oh Oh...⦆
⦅satonaka's⦆
(Mizuki) ⦅huh huh huh...⦆
⦅Let's calm⦆
⦅huh huh huh...⦆
⦅satonaka's Let's calm⦆
⦅huh huh...⦆
⦅Hey okay okay⦆
⦅Let's calm okay⦆
⦅okay⦆
⦅Let's slow deep breath⦆
⦅sound breathe⦆
(Araki) ⦅Yes Yes to⦆
⦅sound exhale⦆
(Araki) ⦅Yes Yes
Yes one more time ⦆
⦅sound breathe⦆
(voice of Rintaro)
"To satonaka's a paranoid ➡
short-term memory impairment is seen ➡
Examination initially was also suspected
schizophrenia "
Oh
" But Araki's attending physician ➡ from symptoms such as seizures
re-examine the implementation
temporal lobe epilepsy and diagnosis
brain surgeon
Hasumi's diagnosis of the same hospital also has the same ➡
Satonaka's diagnosis was determined "
Oh
. The guy  also at that time...
⦅Wait a little⦆
⦅will the surgical procedure'm
memory impairment remains⦆
(Hasumi) ⦅But this case is high
stability ➡
's best  selective hippocampus amygdala resection⦆
⦅Well need not
almost excised tissue outside of the brain⦆
⦅you'm me what Bibi⦆
⦅if you arm ➡
the hippocampus in  latest hippocampus multi-switching surgery conserving and ➡
'd Dekin
that  storage also to preserve⦆
⦅I ask Hasumi⦆
⦅Ask⦆
and (Hasumi) ⦅refuse⦆
(Araki) ⦅you to'm began to run from time to such
defensiveness⦆
(Hasumi) ⦅latest surgery expression that you says in
domestic It has not yet been established⦆
⦅any good? You⦆
The Tteyuu  ⦅storage Do not... ➡
I do the same as the life of the patient! You⦆
⦅Hey! ⦆
(Rintaro of voice) "resulting in hospital adopted Hasumi's opinion
lost  storage
Surgery was, but Mr. satonaka successful and developed sequelae was feared
➡ gone was. "
Is probably sufficient to speak only another Son
It and thereby to go back
feeling bad Doke Look
Huh...
. ➡  "patient family is the cause of sequelae as it's
medical accident
Hasumi It was closing in on
hospital to sue Araki both doctor.
But both after two months suddenly
settlement in unanswered form
Do not know
what was behind it. "
(Sound Araki is vomiting)
senior okay or
(toilet flushing sound)
(Araki) «braze saying go home»
Do you En'noji president is at stake
to reconciliation?
(Araki) «Dunno»
satonaka Mr. then...
(Araki) «After that you listen to Hasumi»
. (Sound Araki is vomiting)
and (Ikumi) Yume乃 enter .
and (Ikumi) Oh... gone to sleep
(Ikumi) Hey.
(Voice of Yume乃)
"mom thank you
Yume乃 also thank you"
. (Voice of Yume乃)
"But do not come out anymore."
(Ikumi) Ruriko
eh what use?
Not kun come bought  Jun-chan Is the little
cigarettes?
(Ruriko) What?
(Ikumi) Anta is much want?
Eh? what? Kind of talk?
I love
. Because  money to somehow I always ➡
again give me do not stay away
to Yume乃
Thank you!
Wow is ~ not it interesting.
I'll be in  50 million
likely but it is
100 million want Is the I do's ➡.  It Is gone coming up that I am a nice little
5000 万 sure to prepare
So Yume乃... ➡
The Yume乃 by
I promise not meet anymore
this street.
Eh!?
And 50 million Clen No Really?
Hey hey!
And 50 million Clen that? Hey!
It was found
. It 'was found
.'ll Be  promise
Fufufu ~!
Fu-N and
. Sorry
to  Oyobitate.
I will listen to business
Araki senior was asked to
10 年 matter before the medical accident
⦅"Satonaka san developed sequelae was feared
➡
= = has lost its memory "⦆
or also to me dead ?
What?
Six months ago it died the patient.
It likely was the I or
. Do not not put it, leaving the  somehow
I went to funeral
⦅Gonna come in what⦆ (mother of Mizuki)
⦅do with ? ⦆
Did you come  ⦅do with! ⦆
(Voice of Hasumi) I had to nothing but apologize
10 years....
At first, I was living from it satonaka Mr.
'10 ➡
did not like that only seems to be
. I'm  her mother ➡
daily ➡ from my daughter every day
"You really
Is my mom? ".
⦅Are you really
my mom? ⦆
It's so continued to be told so
Funeral day
saying toward me
Better yet...
⦅Better yet ➡
with  I also daughter  from 10 years ago... ➡
I should Kurere kill ...⦆ ➡ to
"Memory is the same as the life of the patient"
. Words  time Araki told me was true
. The important thing as  doctor ➡
life not only
life of its people I can save
➡ from the moment you notice
to the meaning of the word
my vision was carried out decline.
Hasumi teacher
. Enough to be trying to forget and deny  feelings
➡
extra that emotion will intensify
. The  first
its storage
➡ To break this vicious circle It is to accept.
Such thing is really to forget something you might not be able
. There is  memory that I in it is not also forget
Have not yet overcome memories
(Hino Kanako) ⦅ Rintaro⦆
⦅yo mom also working hard⦆
But I ➡
Was taught
from a lot of patients
Patients visiting the doctor's office everyone ➡
wore the  somehow compromise
➡ to face the painful memory hurts  pierced the heart
It
it has become in my support.
Hasumi teachers over a period of time from now
➡
I think good
If we accept  slowly
Okay
Teacher is already willing to accept
Why
body I sign comes into
. What to do if  you?
➡ above that no longer seemed so far
I have no value as the other
surgeon
I if ➡
to rest slowly to heal
(Sound to open the door)
= = this What are you and where Hasumi you.
What?
Minister of son of the condition is suddenly changed.
Let me toward the
immediately operating room's right to soon arrive
Ha...
and (En'noji) Hurry!
You do to be successful no matter what
op!
Please wait  president
(En'noji) there is no use to Mr.
.. And Pearl River to go  Hasumi-kun!
I understand .
Teacher should know!
What
If you overlook the surgery in the body occurs now
(Hasumi) is not but a doctor of do's
nothing
Hasumi teacher
(Hasumi) patients?
Please hurry to earlier operating room.
Let's look for another hospital
it is not too late 's it
(Hasumi) Mizushima-kun helped me
Yes
Was confusion state
CT in the lateral ventricle expansion is granted
your findings?
It will think or obstructive hydrocephalus.
Vital's the same opinion?
Has improved to  blood pressure 100 units
heart rate 80 units
. What to do if  you?
The craniotomy to do the tumor removed by
. If  sub tempo Lahr or approach via
corner...
. Do leave a  barely hippocampus?
I think resectable
Let me ask you to not rest everyone hand
Today I can not be surgeon
Actually
this half years my eyesight has continued falling
okay
Mizushima-kun is surgeon instead
I give all instructions.
Tempo Lahr-based
firmly secure the operative field ➡
so as not to damage the  before choroid plexus artery
Hurry
Yes
Was sorry that surgery...
Mizushima teacher will be surgeon
Mizushima is?
"" Memories of Yume乃 also my memories. ""
"" So all right now. ""
"" I we did not want to come anymore out ""
[TEL] (ringtone)
Akira of ~ N
Yes
Little The Come out
Huh...
nephew I do depends what the heck hours?
(Secretary) or let out state of
surgery monitoring
No, say I
I'm blood is weak
Fusiform gyrus is He saw
(Hasumi ) was shifted a little brain Bella ➡
to.  tempo Lahr-based deployment was found
.
Fixed off
(doctor) Yes
On
Bipolar
Dream Chiyo is a difference between 50 million
and Is the I give me to me
Mom?
So
So'm gonna be Anta no longer another
need
. Take care
Bawawa ~~ physician!
⦅Cormorant ~ ~ N! ⦆
Come  ⦅when back
⦅Fufufu...⦆? ⦆
⦅Mom! ⦆
Mom!
Wait ... Hey...
. What it is I do not need ?
Hey give me...
Please! I beg you!
Do not abandon me! I beg you!
Mom...
. It's seems Oh unlikely to have forgotten
. And of had brought candy
I had forgotten  Yes
Yes
No. I...
.. I do not need  it need not....
hey!
I do not need  anymore!
You do you do not need....
Goodbye
Huh huh huh...
Ah...
(Crying)
This is a call from Hino teacher
Yume乃's
Pretty upset Please hurry
has been
found
. It was if  Hello?
'm Teacher said the teacher...
. Do you there is  What? Akira-san
. Memories of even
Yume乃 memories of  mom also ➡
The ➡ it though was to cherish all
had gone  mom
Why...?
Why....
I do not need anymore
. Do you wherever  Akira-san now?
(Cry)
was exposed
completion of  hippocampus and amygdala
. Have happened  (Hasumi)?
It is violently adhesions  tumor
♬ ~
Micro Cooper
(nurse) Yes.
(Hasumi) Do not absolutely damage the hippocampus
. I understand
(Ikumi) Hino teacher?
There on whether Akira-san Irasshaimasu
?
Did you have something
Though we go out ?
➡ and  Ruriko Mr. Akira-san is not necessary
And I seem to have said so
Huh...
Actually, I...
⦅Money
because I always somehow ➡
again Give me do not stay away
to Yume乃⦆
⦅Please! ⦆
Is likely to do... I understand.
Or I would not go I?
No There is no such a thing
. Please contact if you are  if returned
. We want to  Akira-san and the story
. I understand
♬ ~
president.
Kusunoki is a volunteer like surgery is that although the successful
Or so! So whether so
.. By connecting the phone to a pond Secretary  it was found
(secretary)
No, ~ was good
No, - was it was good good
(Humming)
Hino teacher .
It 'was successful thanks to the Mizushima-kun
. Do you  likely!
It was really cheers for good work and
. Looked for the first time no longer be seen
What is?
Memories are stored in the brain
What we are dealing is not a
brain.
Is a storage heart It's life that do
's Mind thing that is in the
brain
I though you might deny
No negative does not .
I also do not know
Nante location of the heart.
And not know
and I have continued this work
. I'll wanted to facing the  anew
patient
Is likely or
. Let cure resting
slowly even for its.
(window glass break sound)
(sound window opens)
(sound)
Good evening.
Yume乃 Mr.
Money is required
Please me calmly is necessary
money
Other money is ➡ to
mom and I do not need
Nde not it was said  Suka?
So is not it necessary money! Is  Why
?
Akira probably because there would be discarded
!
To that mother!
The の do not know ?
Akira will want to be loved
also Anna mother!
Is not it necessary  So money!
You know
Will do Anta want eradicates
me?
Akira also my
came to say no longer need
Because Anta was fueled
I something I do not need anymore!
I ➡ by selling flatter to man nor like
every night around the man...
. And sprinkle
charm around the man  every night ➡
In Fundaku~tsu gold cheated...
Ja No I was what was!
What's the Wakan to you!
The No say  I do with get outta!
Huh huh...
Huh huh huh...
Yume乃's
I do not think
and Nante want to erase you.
I just ➡
I want to connect the  Yume乃 and Mr. Akira Mr.
two time
. Is  their own to life of his time ➡
It is not a Nante
anxiety are missing  gaping or?
To both the time of Akira's
also  Yume乃's time is important.
Fun also stored painful memory is also about you, including all
!
Hinorin really stupid
And'm suffering from the storage
Anta to also because I'll tell
painfulness of storage
(Open and close sound of the door)
( secretary) Kusunoki is a call from the minister.
It is En'noji
No, no...!
Neurosurgery team of the inner  because it is excellent
Yeah
. Thank you for a
(knock)
. In matter of example in the near
. In  later date
Yes excuse me.
Good morning.
(En'noji) Good morning!
No ~ ➡ by your thanks
story of the new hospital is progressing in leaps and bounds
. Or  your director room to the top floor of
south-facing? N~tsu?
Also'll look courtyard
president..
It from now Kusunoki minister and because providing
one seat ➡
Kimi greeting Shitamae
(Hasumi), but is the matter ➡
. The  actually rest...
(Miyagawa) President! Very!
About  knock Shitamae
sorry
.. Or  now see anymore?
N~tsu?
♬ ~
It's what do Hmmm ? This
What do I!
What do we This !
Good morning and
. Did copper ?
Hino teacher
This....