(Miyagawa) there!
You've got to  nephew what did it!
There!
Do not you come with  scratch
. Or  of you gave?
Do not it not to other than you
Honestly say TAMAE
name What I mean to?
Anywhere in the school? Is the name of the parent?
Address telephone number.
(Kiryu Kaoru) Fuka也!
(Kaoru) Fuka也 How did you?
Or out  Miyagawa teacher son was apologize for something inconvenience
?
Son of Kiryu kun?
(Kaoru) Yes
. I'll look'm troubled  this flaw
No Fuka也 likely?
There Fuka也!
(Miyagawa) I've been seen.
You'll get reimbursed
. It is not sorry
And (Yume乃) teacher ➡
Why do not me I  Kyu?
(Hino Rintaro) Yes
<Finally my
full-fledged examination and she began>
's this before and the same way.
I dodge that way
patient I psychiatrist
. I'm was  Yume乃's
. I wonder if not kun quit  Hey Hinorin
?
I do not have to something to trick  and Akira deceive the
.. Not a give embracing
Ja what!
I want to
story to fit with you face doing this way...
. And I told  So?
Guy can'm not me hug
something that of Anta
Because I just betrayed
What was this guy credit ➡
believe are useless! Do not believe absolutely!
This hypocrite!
Ah!
It huh huh huh...
Ha ha ha...
What it? You just have standing around?
There is also when you want to hit
to like that stuff and people
.. Please do until after the  care Do not say things like was found
.
To
together Once settled Let cup of tea
Really the habit you want to expel this patient
During this time together doing this way also
Akira's when I went to sea to ➡
me It is not a me passing
tea or
tired!
Please.
Yume乃's Yume乃 san!
Please come out Yume乃's
. «Let the
talk because I remains were there in»
(sound key is open)
that...
Teacher I
also something your annoying thing...
Hello Akira-san
please.
"When you face
with the patient's dissociative identity disorder therapist ➡
either of personality also Do not take
attitude of denial"
I why to this disease?
Why of whether the cause of the
Strangely happens when you ➡
Let looking together
"Because another person's personality might have heard
the conversation"
doing what ?
And I'm good only by the
talk  together
What?
Well....
Please tell me the
memories of time  Ja today was small
I was always drawn
picture alone
Because it was really shy and
. Was copper ?
This...
(Kaoru) Fuka也! Already!
A teacher
sorry also like this....
Ridiculous
Fuka也 kun Hello
This is my friend
(Kiryu Fuka也) there Ah...
I'm sorry
mess is gone
"Kaoru Kiryu of one son of
Fuka也 kun ➡
there are disabilities to
language accompanied by  savant syndrome ➡
➡ a special case
that autism spectrum
you have a  unique
wonderful view of the world "
Now you intend to move for fear not to before both!
I'm you our ally
<This ➡ save Mayoe that lamb our
Contemporary
is the story of a doctor >
♬ ~
<And My name is Rintaro Hino
psychiatrist that I was late>
♬ ~
(En'noji) during seppuku?
Do you want to apologize even cut  (En'noji)
belly?
(Ikumi) please please pardon
(En'noji) I'd like to
outing it than a dream viz Nyan ➡
I wonder if vacant?
I do not become soon a  pond coverage Secretary to be earnest
persuade
It is not to be Morawa
the permission of the new hospital
. I'm sorry  ➡
Yume乃 a while to
day off In I thought that trying to
and (En'noji) but what?
Or from a hole in the "are in the East"?
Well ➡ from me
I'll keep housed
in Kakea~tsu the union of  Shimbashi
Say that
but it I do not just...
There is not really sorry
Dream Chiyo.
This just can not refuse to.
Say if there is any reason
Yume乃 I'm sick
Disease? Whether in the hospital?
And (Ikumi) Home & Garden
. Is it sleeping  Ja in Okiya?
Doctor?
Hino teacher...
Hino?
(Ikumi) Yeah.
Out of Hino Rintaro or
(Ikumi) Yeah
Chairman!
(Kaoru) as usual and
Zu ~ Innovation ThatLookLikeThis
. Compared to the time  but the first ➡
little to come was the
gonna such do is I to know
Well still
Fuka也➡ There is what you're thinking
Rather read
'm okay
Now we may not know he is because we always put the sign of something
➡ to a little while ago Miyagawa teacher
Fuka也 is a bicycle Defeat to it I was to scratch the car
Miyagawa of Professor?
Thank Fuka也-kun!
I'm such that wanted to do
I can not Motto it
(Kaoru) teacher
There this! This is the
Is this what?
Maybe this'm a sign of
"I'm sorry"
. Do you  likely!
Is not amazing.
Also I led
one Fuka也 kun
It is truly mom
No, I'd like to think so...
. It's time  This happy
yeah
Depth . Shinya
Oh ~
Oh Oh...
(and the sound of open)
You do such mean by that? Hino Mr.
explained to me
Is under examination by President
And (Kaoru) there is son of'm
Fuka也!
The president will excuse me
was sorry
Yume乃 Where is it?
Can you after
because it is in it I went back another examination?
Yume乃 Where is he wrong?
It can not answer
I say it'll's president
. The  doctor there is confidentiality.
President himself do you do you say
to be broken it?
Whether such attitude that know how to call the
What situation?
Situation?
Fufu~tsu
I do can to
neck anytime you something?
Alrighty it came!
Chance arrival!
I rare pink elephant
. The No  elephant is like?
I interesting is hit by Tobi  elephant
Hello?
I'm sorry Ja?
(Fuka也) or or
. No  there is mom?
Fuka也!
I thought I was in here!
Today to go home anymore
There?
Fuka也 Fuka也
Fuka也 okay here you like?
Yes
(Kaoru) ne ne here mon's secret base
I was comfortable? Outside
. It was  "Dear Rintaro
paper look.
Very not good is this more impressed
to the study has been content to "
(Yoko) eh
" If the author Yoko Kawakami ➡ If you are interested in research at
our school
I want to welcome all means as please introduce
researcher.
Texas
Houston psychiatrist school ➡
principal
Margaret Goldman "
Teacher
. ➡ As had been talk before
because  was a very well-made paper
I We were allowed sent
of the alma mater.
(Yoko) Yes. How I'll reply
?
Because I  responsible to have patients also
➡
Please let me a little thought  and
I understand
(Knock)
please
. Do you  teacher now sure?
Please
That... is serious thing was how
?
Fuka也 is.... Was copper
Fuka也 kun?
And I have done  Are you what
.?
(Kaoru) Children Art Exhibition of
sculpture department of the Grand Prix ➡
I've taken !
Is not that was good!
Congratulations!
thanks you!
I was spear  Fuka也-kun!
Rough teacher I'm sorry
Let's celebrate together!
Pa ~ Innovation ne!
Yes!
Yeah
. (Voice of Machiko)  I'd thought
from a little before ➡
This child is probably savant
(Machiko) And might the owner of
synesthesia
It?
And I write on paper by interpretation !
This strange ➡ the secret of the functions of the brain
your area of expertise
And (Miyagawa) see.
It'll be used can be used
Machiko kun!
Thank you  (Miyagawa) and
. What ? I what I want to show
. It might Nasaru
bad  care
(Miyagawa) It attaches suck
facing saint Kimiko exactly
«You excuse me»
Good evening
(En'noji) Yume乃
There... I will be rude This
ahead
Circle like I'm sorry
Other day the outing also "is in the east" is also
condition worse Te by'd better go
. That's right has received
Hino examination me silently.
Hahahaha... Who is such a thing?
The'm healthy this street
(En'noji) Ja What is this?
Have taken  rough - well
Who taken?
Do know
That is why from time and Hino...?
Hey circle like.
The idea
useless and angry at such a thing?
Happy  But of me baked jealous
To one more time?
Dream viz Nyan...
(Machiko) Hasumi teacher
Thank you
. I ask  So then
Miyagawa professor.
Today ➡ regarding
my research to you
I would like to
the hope of  cooperation
I for some time than ➡
about the relationship between  mental illness and brain I have to study
. For  Among them
autism and brain function is ➡
To be the expert and we are proud
And (Mizushima Yuriko) is that so?
Yeah
. Patient you want to and  this time the subject is this person
Is
Kiryu Fuka也's also a Hino teacher of patient
Eh? okay?
Fuka也 kun ➡ yet
autism spectrum
has been awarded the Grand Prix
in this time children art exhibition
➡ has a rare talent have
kind to  its stereolithography. = = He probably ➡
Called savant syndrome will be diagnosed with
one of the people
Well? Hino teacher is likely
(Miyagawa) the people of savant syndrome ➡ the previous three-dimensional and landscape
eyes
you can can be left as it is kept in a storage
➡
Once listened only
➡ to be or can reproduce the music
There is a surprising memory  It amazing
(Miyagawa)
further ➡ You can feel the color to the character
and smell to  sound ➡ to be or feel or shape
some sensory stimuli causes
another sense ➡
You will be considered
to have both a  synesthesia
Such a person with a special ability is very rare
➡
research reports in Japan Kazusukunaku ➡
Ya by all means fMRI
Using SPECT ➡
➡ the
relevance of research with the active region of the brain
With the cooperation of Fuka也 kun we want to do by all means
. And the  a rare case or?
Yes become very interesting research
(En'noji)
Likes TAMAE spear all means
I is contrary to the
opposite?
Why you do not cooperate?
Do not a good story.
Fuka也 kun is also ➡ to inspection of
fMRI also SPECT
. You will not be able to withstand
(Miyagawa) Why?
Why?
Or
children with autism spectrum are suffering from what ➡
you know Even  teacher?
What do you mean?
They can not be the corresponding
to unexpected situation
Daily life also his procedure Street ➡
and I are sending
while valuing  life pattern
(Miyagawa) such It's on top of the aware.
ear big sound is ➡
A long time forced the same attitude in that machine ➡
is not the environment  Fuka也 kun is hardly withstand
. It would be to miss an  SPECT if
sedative agents
. Not playfully  Please out!
Have you thought
to become his body even once?
They how much every day ➡
and I think to have a hard time
to live  this society?
You you do not hear the story of  patient would not know
but ➡
Moment I'm
are desperately alive while using the air around for a moment!
You to ➡ you do not even try to find
its bitterness
you will not be able to leave
a  Fuka也-kun!
(En'noji)
helluva the aponeurosis but I Hino-kun
. I guess a position to criticize  Miyagawa-kun?
You Even if not a stuck
in one patient
. It is  mean?
'm Yume乃
(En'noji) also Kimi 's own
She has her circumstances
.. Or would not be served as of
doctor that match the state of  patient?
(En'noji)
Kiryu kun 's staff of the inner?
(Miyagawa) Yes
(En'noji) or not it is good
if Mitomere mom?
Please wait  hey!
(En'noji)
Hino Mr. nice if outside this charge
if now ➡
Forcibly if you take the permission of the mother ➡
I will break the bonds of
mother and child came to build great pains to here!
Mother for  Fuka也-kun is a lifeline to live
!
Please stop is  please!
The Pearl River take the permission Miyagawa-kun directly.
I Hino-kun is good
Take off from the charge?
Refuse
. To get out from the charge of  Yume乃
It also can not
. Do not do nothing but get quit  Ja
(Hasumi) again your
chilled Hino Mr. head Please answer
. I hope ?
Okay
(En'noji) So after the fact that
parties and
. I expect  Miyagawa-kun and
Certainly
.. Did you copper ? Rintaro
(Kaoru) Sorry, No
refuse.
Is Why?
All means thank you to cooperate
Is Hino?
Is not'm going
Is my thinking
Really sorry to
. It becomes difficult to stay here, too
to become the  (Machiko) refuse?
We knew  (Kaoru).
Your thinking again
Ie
Feeling because it does not change
Fuka也!
And rude
(Sound to play the finger)
damn it!
(Kaoru)
Fuka也! What are you doing hey!
Please return Fuka也
Anymore... I'm sorry.
➡ embittered also  Fuka也 kun
might
be that they've allowed to
Meeting
It has become emotional at you because of me
. I do sorry
. = = Since the Miyagawa teacher has refused direct
➡
Teacher Please do not anymore
worry
Is likely or
I'm sorry to
♬ ~
are open  please
(Sound door is open)
is an inconvenience...?
Ridiculous
You rude
Please.
Was what? Akira-san
Ano... ➡
By the  Fuka也 kun...
I wanted to apologize to me that child and
. Apologize ?
That... ➡ When I met for the first time here
and I'm  my
To ➡ had been messing
a miniature garden and animals?
Was me clean up
Do not even Fuka也 kun unpleasant face
. Not communicated well
and I want to apologize properly ...
. Please do not fret  Akira Mr.
That The thing
Yume乃's did not in your
but...
And ➡
Fuka也 kun I love to cause
those that are fallen
. Adult around  is not raised by noticed quite
➡
it
is a great personality of that child
. = = sensei... ➡
What is there was something ? It is  cute stuffed
.
There... that ➡
Could you pass
from this teacher to Fuka也 kun?
To me "I'm sorry
that time is not apologize properly"
. I will joy  Fuka也 kun This
Fufu~tsu
. Do you  Akira's okay?
Is the teacher than I what all right?
Eh?
Like a so  something is impossible to
Something had kana I
Actually, I have wanted to apologize
me even now Fuka也 kun
. It was said Nante  friend But ➡
I
nothing I can not give you the ➡ for that child
I'm a  bad doctor
. Is not  such a thing!
(Voice of Yume乃)
Fuka也 kun I'm like a certain
that want to convey something
It... ➡
And to be raised to understand is I think only
teacher
Akira-san...
Thank you
Thank Nante...
Psychiatrist is just
treat patients Well without ➡
I sometimes be saved
the words of  patients
now to like me.
Teacher...
♬ ~
Ja to Fuka也 kun Regards
Likely'm Akira-san
This is please give passing
directly from you to Fuka也 kun
Tomorrow house in I do the celebration of
winning Fuka也 kun
. also come comrades of  hospital.
Do not Come and if good
?
No But I such a place...
. I  Akira-san was a shy
My favorite comedians are saying
"Shy is
great talent given from God I "
talent?
Yes
When he said this
opponent would think this way
. Is  great talent
➡ that that way it is raised to think
most things opponent.  Tomorrow Us
celebration because it rest will have done from the day
. Tara  really in good.
Thank you
Ja I... am waiting
.. Waiting !
It... I was gone twice
. I think it was  this love? Is  (Araki) eclair
?
Yeah
(Araki) No, so much recently....
(Araki) there but we will pains why
. I'm coming  Hino-kun also here?
There such a thing is I do not say if there is a
confidentiality
(Araki)
opponent does not have you if confidentiality nor
Hettakure.
Also means you want to hear
something in him?
Well today by Kimi and
Crawling?
Or not willing to come back
to the hospital of Araki-kun?
You also ➡ in such
sweep and useless like a place
would not going to end
to hear the complaints of  patient?
Well yeah...
. Do not try aiming
the top of the  again Great White Tower?
♬ ~
Let's toast  Fuka也 kun
. Do you made is  this whole teacher?
Yes
Mash potato curry
What are Chat with Tandori - chicken ➡
Ponzu garland chrysanthemum Let's start
and so
.'m  Fuka也 toast
. It 's celebration of  Fuka也 Yes have been
. To celebrate the children's art exhibition
Grand Prix  Ja Fuka也 kun...
(5 persons) Kampa ~ Lee!
I'm sorry....
Fuka也 kun I'd like is that place was like
I would like to thank the teacher to such more of
Fuka也 and I
Really in today Thank you
and
. Although  I only want to be Fuka也 kun and
friends forever.
Thank you
Still someone to come?
There Madoka-chan?
Also was multiplied by the
voice I come Madoka Akira-san
At the same today and I have a another
simpleton report
Kawakami Mr. please
Yes.
Was decided to
studying in my Texas Houston psychiatrist school
Eh Rintaro study abroad destination of?
(Yoko) Yes
. Learn the
full-fledged empathetic treatment in  America ➡
We aim
a psychiatrist like  Hino teacher.
Wow ~ Congratulations!
(Applause)
Good luck  and
Good luck
.. Thank you  (Yoko)
Kawakami ➡
. Please do its best not work hard
Thank you
Really in it everyone
it became a lot care.
(Fukuhara) Kawakami!
I also sincerely support
. Let's toast again
celebrating  In Kawakami Yoko's departure
. In  Kampa ~ Lee!
(4 people) Kampa ~ Lee!
Little Fukuhara's
Okay? Not force.
What is the
I'm completely okay
Cheers!
Today Let's let them drink
big time
Well
. I guess are talking about what  Fuka也 kun yasuke and
. If you get used to  (Kaoru) Wataru helps those do you ➡
And to could do to know
more of that child thing
(Fukuhara) «Texas Houston! »
(Laughter)
(Fukuhara)« Texas Houston? »
(Madoka) recently very much
there say...
.. What to  brother?
And I tell if there is for
Hate...
. ➡ and I come flocked to
home on the day of rest to not even for
What do you mean going?
Brother ➡ because patients think
and I'll do not  cold chased away or Toka
➡
Patients is
I do not you just
I'm sorry...
(Madoka) The brother ➡
and I'm also  Yuriko Tteyuu
she
Nde such things like that... .
rude.
(Madoka) is not a brother perfectly useless unless
lock the door
«You know Rintaro
Madoka-chan came by»
«Madoka late ~ Lee»
(Fukuhara)
«to disturb you very much You »
huh huh huh....
It 'should I betray from
here before being betrayed
Fufufu... see you Hinorin
. I wonder not it going to quit  Kaoru hospital
?
In order to protect the  Fuka也 kun
. I did not come Yume乃 Mr.
today Speaking
Yeah....
(Fukuhara) - psychiatrists'm what is bad
in love!
Fukuhara kun were you still?
This is that if you shake off something
that says teacher ➡
I should have to confess  ~!
(Crying)
Kawakami Mr. I  Fukuhara Mr. favorite person
Eh !?!?
They both do What are you talking about this time
♪ ~ "You are like," said
♪ ~ If so transmitted
in trouble even without  ♪ ~ reply...
(Ruriko) huh...!
And you doing being chased by  help me
also debt collectors.
's Fine also killed Anta
mom? If it killed
? Ha ha ha
Anta has changed since appeared that fucking doctor!
Previous  is not it was more Yasashika~tsu!
It's not helped  mom
!
Did you love with him?
Crawling? Hino?
Do not laugh  whether it
...
He is trying to erase me
It cheats the Akira to
. Absolutely not allowed
(Ruriko)
anyway early 10 million yen
somehow to me unless anymore ➡
~ I would have been killed  Oh....
Ja...
. You can use  even this?
Hahahaha...!
That's funny pictures ~
Kiryu's
Would not get thinking
again?
Teacher thinking does not change.
The
will excuse me because there is that meeting
There? You have what? Fuka也 kun
Today I'm not is' s day of
promise
N~tsu? Is  Hiragana
?
(Fuka也) Contact
you.?
Wait a minute you would write on paper
Please.
N Is the same
Contact same N Is the
Fuka也 kun...
Was to
Chi
. I  and
Ri and
Pot
Ku
I
Contact same Is the N ➡
Ri by Chi was  ➡
pot rather I
a
is
physician
.-out .
to be  to
Ru and
. N .
It is  to
O
Pot and
Rather than
Is
Contact
And
Cormorants
Of
. N .
to
of the
one is
was
and
-out
and (Fuka也) pot and
. rather than  and
. was
. = = Chi
of
This
. also
soil..  is.
➡ of pot rather than blood
children is
Pot and
. Rather than
Seen
Was
Physician
. To  and
This.
or
et al.
a
physician
. I
cormorants
to the
-out
or
physician.
to
is
physician
. Ru .
-Out or you have to ➡
is not that
Its the
Cormorants
. To
Been
If
E
Et al.
physician
allowed
N and
allowed to
physician
. was  and
Chi
is
a
. to .
Do you
physician
sail
cormorants
ho.
Cormorants
. The
Contact
. Also
Physician
One is
Rather than
Or
. Also
. To .
is
a
physician
or
et al.
Conclusion!
Fuka也 kun
You Do not's Tsuyoiko
Fuka也....
Fuka也 kun believes properly
than us
♬ ~
I say I ne teacher
. And since is that  Fuka也-kun wants
♬ ~
Hey Fuka也
I do not have to put up
. The'm good I quit
Once hated
♬ ~
(Kaoru) please
. Let's go Ja  (Machiko)
. Do you go
Fuka也
(Voice of Rintaro) bike I think I was lying
.
Huh?
Oh is that a child was hurt?
➡ a bicycle that had  Fuka也 kun collapsed
I think what can an attempt to wake
He is not like
that the bike has fallen
So even without'm
bicycle he had defeated ➡
would wake  and it would be with
large people saw the appearance ➡
He will anger him
and I wonder defeated and
Different I and Miyagawa Professor
. The must offend  is ➡
not try to  understanding
and I'm a better of us
. = = He always always hard ➡
I've been working hard
is trying to get to understand to us.
Autism spectrum to worry
person or ➡
The most painful
for the family around  is ➡
it is that communication by  words can not be taken
. Miracle that is happening to  now Fuka也 kun The ➡
It is a hope for many people
hope?
How  thank you
. Please give to decipher
his sign
➡ in whether your power . I understand
[TV] (Machiko) Preface You'll
[TV] (Machiko) I because there is a big sound not afraid
I be.
It seems you Kaoru
And this is the so'm
Fuka也 kun
. ➡ Using this before  inspection
I was me why tell me
whether subject to inspection.
♬ ~
⦅or⦆
⦅the⦆
⦅also⦆
⦅Ru⦆
Me?
Parents who have children with autism spectrum ➡
it will stick blame yourself
. Not it was something in  nursing or ➡
pregnant something
of this child The ➡ that it is not for
I think we ended up .
But mom is not bad nothing
Fuka也 kun we know it
. ➡ for  mother of his
Have you come to no matter how
embittered ➡
Did you come, no matter how hard
Fuka也 kun and I know perfectly
.
So I think that I want to protect the mother
♬ ~
(Kaoru crying)
Kaoru
. Please do not quit  hospital .
Fuka也 kun We firmly growing
future ➡ together
We also let's growth
(Kaoru) Thank you
. Thank  ♬ ~
(Kaoru)
♬ ~.  (Yoko) things I Hino teacher
sincerely and I had to respect ➡
There was a thing that you want to refute  only one
eh?
Love think I'm not mental illness
transient
Ja... is
full-fledged mental illness
So it was perfectly good to ask them
fluoride to Hino teacher
Good luck
.. Please do your best also  Fukuhara's
(Fukuhara) Yes.
Ja
I was loved about you and
I was  Ha ha... I know
. I knew ..  Thank you Fukuhara kun
♬ ~
(sound pen fell)
(Araki) Look
Hasumi or you forgot my face?
(Hasumi) Araki.
Na'm not supposed to forget Fufu~tsu
(Araki) Wow ~
. I do How was the image diagnosis
of this child ?
➡ when given the problems of the  verbal
not only
left temporal lobe that  normal blood flow is increased ➡
parietal lobe is carried out  space recognition ➡
It was also up mainly
right of blood flow
. Children of the data appeared to
image  synesthesia is this only in beautiful ➡
I think almost no
even  probably the world.
Do not it amazing! You'll.
Was led ~!
What? Is it good to take credit of it all
Miyagawa?
I can ➡ only was conveyed the feelings of Fuka也 kun
mom
. Since it is  satisfied
better put out better!
Is it you doing going well
her treatment ➡ of that example in ?
(Sound to open the door)
Is there reserved for patients?
Is Akira's mom
Ah... this it is
Anta also a doctor?
(Araki) Yes
Psychiatrists flame if
Once out hand tut to patients?
Once Well yeah
actually put out hand tut ➡
Basically ➡ it becomes a case where I will
ethics violation
This guy
Nde not the kind of guy
. No Wakan  do with such a thing?
No because this guy is mon saint gentleman is like wearing white coats
Head
Ja What is this?
Hey!
I mean I Hino Rintaro of "phosphorus" of
ethics violation "phosphorus"
. If you did not want complained
not buy this photo?
Please return your  refuse
Calm down a little
. Do you who can sell
in the picture much in ?
(Ruriko) towards the Koch teacher not a Wakan
story!
I wonder if in  50 million?
50 million to...
. I think I pays ?
Ethics violation of Rintaro teacher
(Ruriko) Fufufu...!