(Hino Rintaro) Please wait
Yume乃 san!
Please do not go !
(Yume乃) teacher of the examination and the other...
♬ ~
and (Araki) of this section?
(Mizushima Yuriko) Total
(Araki) it 's not incense ➡
I'm anti-?
Likely.
Do not not died to be along or... had gone beyond
Right?
(Araki) Yeah
(Kiryu Kaoru) Do you already sure?
Ah... I'm sorry I'm sorry to
Huh...
. It 's is that Tatte got love ?
Mr. Yume乃.
Do not not died to be having gone
to the previous reverse transition
. Habit you had to say  come Toka
back at any time
(Kaoru) Do What a serious?
You serious I wonder Na guy Nari to
. Is is  treatment? Is carp?
The (Kaoru) I guess Which of?
I I'd have questions
When absorbing it'll not stop orchid while
What if I develop
So Which is?
I because  Mizushima teacher is not clear
My fault?
Guy... ➡
Might doctor quit going
of the
Na wonder it about the preparedness is
Haha~tsu! Oh Haha~tsu!
Fufufu...! Haha~tsu!
Oh!
Do you that this is Mr. Akira wanted to do most
?
Do I ?
No.
Yasuke!
Thank you  teacher this love
We became very well
Yasuke Hui
. Do not you like  stomach?
It was like
Yasuke is hungry?
Fufufu....
<While suddenly think that there is no
is supposed to improve symptoms ➡
about to become so misunderstood likely>
<But this moment ➡
Akira-san and Yume乃 san become one
It's like being>
Hui Hui Hui...
Oh wait to run?
Or do you run?
(Sound kicking the wall)
(En'noji) I'll do I'll do!
I'm a child that you can!
(Miyagawa) We kicked the
wall seems a long time to have come up with
tic symptoms
. I do do and how much do !
Say whether you guys absolutely
acquisition is good'll be successful?
(Hasumi) Chairman it...
(En'noji) I...! Probably it seems there are
its qualification to take the world
?
I think  yeah so good
fool Do not sympathize with such Toko
.. ➡ if there is a phone call from  this morning pond Secretary
Is the story... What
? Hasumi.
Secretary and acquisition talk was no longer
.. Accustomed to  horse
heh?
And I'm saying accustomed to  horse!
(Hasumi) Chocho... Eh!
Chairman please little calm
!
Miyagawa! Miyagawa closed the horse!
Where?
It's the top would have decided ! It's the top
!
E ~ !?
N~tsu!
Delicious
I ate for the first time this delicious omelet
. Do you like  either of omelet is
?
Hmmm
better it was to mix here of Gocha.
I It is also Let's make
And (Kayama) What?
Wait! Hag!
Wait ~!
(Ruriko) Oh!
Belly pain tut Oh!
Kana  (Kayama) tide
Goodbye Ruriko of ~ ~ N
. And intend to move to the front without fear  Now both!
I'm you our ally.
<This save Mayoe that lamb our
modern ➡
is a story of a doctor >
♬ ~
it <is Rintaro Hino My name delay Was
psychiatrist>
♬ ~
Can you come tomorrow?
Course
. I will return  today.
And because I got over
worry to mother of  Okiya
Sends Ja it
is okay
.. Is because not a  Another person
. Or may not be at  together forever...
Yes .
It's likely !
I leave pass  duplicate key
[TEL] (ringtone)
There
. Is the phone from  Yumechiyo mom
[TEL] (ringtone)
Yes Hino
mom?
Okay calm down
Thank you for waiting (door open sound)
(policeman)
. It is  Aizawa Akira-san?
Okay.
Ruriko Mr. Aizawa is
It is your mother?
Yes
Mother has been arrested in
without money eating and drinking in restaurants of Ningyo-cho
I you will become
identity underwriter?
What happens if you do not underwriting ?
Disposal until the determined will
detention
(Ikumi) or should not I'm?
(Cop) you?
Of good
I assume
. Please be brought
. I'm good not work hard
Say No... I want to work hard on your own
(Footsteps)
(Sound door is open)
(Ikumi) you!
(Ruriko) Akira of ~ N
Sorry Hehe~tsu I'm sorry
Mother without money and I had a
free eating Hehe...
. It was no helpless
crowded anymore stomach Even  .
(Ruriko) What in
and Is No Kitan take place like this
(Ikumi) I'll say good woman who was Nakitsui to
daughter bilking
.
Selling to photo  money wants of this butthead But!
(Ruriko) and bossy in!
It was copper  50 million!
50 million!
The Nante "gold is not met and the other again
Akira from a pay" ➡
admirable in and asked this lie with a woman
habit he!
Hey Akira also
place like this early out if Is the ➡
to ne Let's Kuraso together in  2 people?
Is a
also fun and two people like a long time ago!
How long will the get such a lie?
I'll quit  another
. Did you copper  (Ruriko)? Akira
I'm there were only mom
in?
And come back drunk  Ittsumo
It me be the mother?
The Akira'm was not how .
Everyone
➡ to go school to have lunch
and not come back  nor many days days days
...
And to lonely
. And lonely is lonely and lonely  .
(Ruriko) sorry I...
. to hear in silence  anymore!
From a not come back  ➡
because there is no  money ➡
Candy also gone ➡
around me is not nobody
. Crowded is  stomach...
Stomach
ketchup even gone crowded
. When you come back  man to take to have ➡
and I Iro waiting outside
. and I was good to be lay  An'nako
....
And even though I wanted to hug ...
. And to
was good with just me at  together...
. Working worked  So working
me even though there were only mom
is.... ➡ Te
in the hope that said
and I'm good to have  here....
The dance was like to
. Because mom dancing  was
nice
Well you can dance with
because mom was pleased me
Money was important
. Is  money and from me hug
mom as long.
Good child Even from me patted my head
. Mom
to be pleasing to  customers were also pleased me
Was me compliments are proud to me
. Of  mom I happy face it was like watching
are
Zu Motto and the
came that way alive.
But will stop another
I... ➡
from a familiar to me
Thank you mom
Yume乃...
Goodbye mom
Akira... No! Jada...
(Ruriko) Ya - Da ~...
Now I mom ➡
And because I'll hug
(Ruriko) Ya - Da ~...
.. I'm  mom was also lonely?
And if now it is understood
Mom
. I'm me variously put up
for me up to now
. Thank you  really.
I'll I  But without
patience anymore for me
From now ➡
You minute
return chants until  now
Yume乃...
♬ ~
UU... Yada...
ya ~ da ~...
Yada ~!
Ya ~ da ~! Ya ~ da ~...
(Chime)
(Hasumi) I became a horse
Horse?
En'noji of guy to Chima~tsu broken "accustomed to the horse," I in
and say Ya wants
Was screaming riding to me
And I "'ll aim for the top"
Hasumi teacher do you think
cause and what is it?
Are you not heard? . You
nothing
. I hear talk of  acquisition became useless
Is that story
. Was Gappori get
promised  subsidy
➡ in exchange for the son of the operations of  Minister it was do it but ➡
apparently flew
talk outdid is  The minister tax evasion.
I guess I see
it shock
. Although I heard in
direct phone  pond press secretary...
➡ in do  situation is funny. It 'was  Secretary in trouble in the dilemma
pond san.?
Problem is hospital
Chairman's Anna tone
we also troubled.
Did you have any symptoms
the other?
Have  face earnestly anger
in such a tone
Somehow Naranka Hino!
It is  but
I is in this street curfew
Wonder is so also said Tiger
. Whether laughing ? Thing of me.
You'll likely? . Hino not laughing
. Or not it is laughing !
Such face that I
Trying to steal from me to the future of
hospital steal Yume乃
Disappeared acquisition story of
hospital because of you
Also I such power to
It does not have any authority.
I on whether the bean paste in resentment
!? Hino-kun I'm plotting what
. Although  president I can not be a
your horses...
A (Miyagawa)
words modesty TAMAE Hino-kun!
Once Not Welcome
to my examination room?
Fool!
What I want to say, even with the sick?
Now the president and the president of the past
➡
not as
rational I do not think
. Is not that do Rassharu
something had a big stress to  mind?
You is I'm the stress!
you!
The wonder was allusion something  pond Secretary to
Hino
. I have no reason break suddenly
acquisition talk if that is not likely
'll's 60 billion 60 billion!
What's ?
Or even you guys Hino the same opinion?
Whether I would like to say Even sick?
There is no such a thing
. Is  but now you are no better than the king of naked
You such words are rude
!
I'm sorry
I just nobody around ➡
The current state of
that is no longer say is honest opinion...
Na to the description of the Hino naked king
All the blame of Hino!
Pond Secretary betrayed!
Hasumi also Negae~tsu!
Miyagawa's a traitor!
And everyone's neck!
I am the king!
(Hasumi) that crisp condition's what signs Na not it extraordinary
?
It has probably caused the
mild confusion It is acute stress disorder
Method of treatment?
Although  should I Kurere heard
my story...
I it's impossible.
(Machiko) Hino teacher aside ➡
➡ is
professor came to contribute to the hospital so far
Is not no
should be a  neck
. Rely everyone
Hino do with  I kana...
. It 'I want to be loved  Even I
.
Is not I'm in  Professor!
I different
I...
. I want to be loved by  patient
Anyway me thinking something Solution
.'ll Ask  and
I understand
.. = = there
. did you happened in ?
Cormorant I not good N ~
.
Medical condition that it is not struck the hand  something as soon as possible to ensure....
Is different! How do the Yume乃's?
[TEL] (ringtone)
Sorry
[TEL] and (ringtone)
Yes Hino
(Pond) Sorry is came immediately
. It was what  ?
Oh phone'm bad!
Can you wait
about an hour in it was found ?
Such time... can not wait!
UU and... panic verge of do it!
Hurry come to me!
You ask  is in immediately or likely
. Please calm down
to the  pond's deep breath
(Sound exhale)
(sound suck the breath)
later in .
I'm sorry to go unless
. I was cut
from a say expired  (pond) teacher!
Yet it's this Zama!
I'll gonna copper heck
Please pond calm Mr.
Do you had what the heck?
(Pond) TAMAE look at this this!
Is this a fact?
Different... misunderstanding What
. Exorbitant subsidies to  En'noji minister ➡
had been  request know
. Is
tax evasion charges in  But the Minister before the it took me
. I was off to a pipe of  So that...
En'noji Metropolitan.
I'm only were drawn together two people
. Things like touching the  method nothing Citra do
!
And'm Why
so scared Ja? Is  Did you mean bribery
?
We do not got Nanzo  gold!
You've hidden in  pond's something else?
Teacher also would have been hidden?
Yume乃 and things
The mean was hiding separately There is no
Only do intend insist
to be a relationship between the patient and the doctor?
It...
it.?
Or for her?
Do such of for teacher?
The
I'm Which of do not answer or not answer?
Secretary...
in the world and ➡
.'m Gonna be there also is good
better  not clear to
. Is  but I burdened by so doing
result ➡
You are struggling now You.
Of fate Bookshelf politician
Psychiatrist also wonder together?
Will it be
convinced as was so described in  conference?
I do say what if  Ja?
Do not enclose the  pond's belly?
Belly?
People as such when there is a secret is something notice
Yeah
. And even going to receive even any punishment
in order to win the trust of  opponent ➡
and ➡ all on this occasion
you would not should expose
to the light of day?
♬ ~
There Welcome back
Sorry
Mother and I have remembered
that when the dead
. And I
tableware When that day came back is had been washed all
So I was I thought I was working hard is
mother
it from the telephone is ringing ➡
And I knew
that jumped on the train
Fluoride
. It's not because of  teacher
If you do not give anymore forgive
. Would the  mother?
Teacher own
(Pond of voice) with respect to this acquisition
[TV] (pond) I absolutely do not do
involved.
[TV] (reporter)
would not do that ➡
actually Kusunoki Minister
➡ En'noji the president from you
Is not have
testimony I have been  introduction
[TV] (pond) certainly introduce I was going to
[TV] But Ken acquisitions ➡
All I is not involved
In restaurant called Hee 乃下 ➡
minister president
also do it but there is information that you have trysts with
(Reporter) So of cash I'm the delivery has been made
?
It is different !
I just had to talk  just fun.
(Reporter) irresponsible lie Please
honestly talk to quit!
It is not attached, such as  lie!
(Reporters)
Secretary What are you what hidden?
That's right  (Reporter)!
Do I Rassharu what hidden?
(Buzz)
This is the truth.
I ➡ In addition to this
do not do  absolutely secret!
Please believe !
[TV] Do not
trust me even this?
[TV] even this do you blame me
(Ikumi)
somehow poor I Secretary
(Small dream)
Oh Oh this Ja my dream ➡
Not a no
's far from that me grant
. If do  president also involved ➡
I do not know
I might  not me anymore come
. Do not say bad things  President
Even if is that person had a bad thing
to ➡
Because that person is I've been supporting us
Innovation - not things we are
. I hope ?
(Ikumi) small dream?
Thank you dream Chiyo
(Ikumi) circle like!
(Ikumi) circle like...
Ah this as it ➡
by twitching'm  something strange.
I was able to clean
. Do you say
and even if I have seen  teacher taste?
Yes
. I will
Delicious
Oh was good
[TEL] (ringtone)
there
Yumechiyo It is Mr.
[TEL] (ringtone)
Hello.
There a dream thousand generations
There is a teacher folding entered to ask
. Did you say by removing Dzura to  Secretary?
Eh?
I'll have been removed in
conference and I do not have  secret is
. Do not you see ?
I did not know
. Also Na Kimi's bad guy .
Or president it was not why stuck
to the acquisition of the hospital?
Are you trying to make me even Dzura removed?
There is no such intention
. I  a father of hospital
AoiAkira medical corporation
Father? Is the President?
Likely.
So I wanted Yari was absolutely
acquisition
Is why?
Mr. brothers?
Younger sister will have one person
so
'd Have me on 2 people big brother
Big brother two doctors of
. I  excellent
President also
Although I think that it is enough excellence.
I'll have not been to the other party at all
father is
. To could not study  I did not Ukara also
Medical University
(En'noji) knew myself
Oh I
is not expected to human beings do Even
even born grandson also wedding
. I was hiding  ➡
When you divorce even did not come even
once
Cheesy revenge is
. ➡ by
dismantling and the acquisition of important things of  father
I mean I thought
as I'll pay selling  .
(En'noji) Na would why a do
Yume乃 and is called ➡
Hasumi and it Is the gone are inspired by
everyone kun to Miyagawa
. I'll not at all interesting
by've been removed  miasma
. Mon not  glistening
Is likely or
All I It 's me took from
I no longer anything
Naa No of my disease?
I do not stop
to chat here Pikupikushi
. Do guy for me  psychogenic?
President I was surely too much hard work alone
You ➡ the
sorrow and suffering ever
Would not it came alive
instead of the energy of  anger.
It is a tremendous energy
Also ➡ of you could go to the top
far
probably because the energy was there
. Energy of  But anger is like a
flame.
Haphazardly
In order to continue to burn  we will burn a lot of things
And unawares the flame ➡
or would not it heresy
I started burning yourself
. Is it I was burned out ?
Come cry  fluoride.
So I was good, even if you can not something
acquisition
Another broke of
. And I do not can also  picryl
➡ What is in invested
gold for  all acquisitions.  Do I if I ?
I think whether not it nice
is  not do anything.
(En'noji) What?
Chairman
today Why here?
Or not it has been decided
Is because there was no  other to go where
It is not a certain here or
(En'noji) What?
Your important things is here.
You that you need to now is that seek
help
It is sometimes okay even graces
people
Human beings is not a bad thing
The more you're thinking?
Dream Chiyo
. Here Is Even do  there something
(En'noji) Yumechiyo?
There?
Dream Chiyo and'm was where conducted gone!
Yes only we will come now
I do what is me?
I do seems is here to'm  something
Do you know?
Now? Something?
Hino Mr.
Yes
Let me heal me.
That's the condition of the hospital return to
. I understand
(Araki)
'm already your role sorry
I can I want to ask the treatment of En'noji
If you have Yare be nice
thank you
.. or going to quit  you a doctor?
Are you  was already decided?
Yes.
Along or
Naughty me to
quickly'll never anything anymore to say
En'noji also Yume乃's mother's also'll see
I troublesome
Sorry
Fufu Tsu...
Mana I was open you now
first heart.
Is there something special
to Yume乃 Mr.
Mom!
What was to come Ya wanted to
That... I was now talking about listening?
Story? I do not want to hear again
Nante Anta story!
Ruri-chan! Different'm
guy'm also'm my patient.
Ruri-chan?
Patient...?
I thought you say
Bakka that it strange at  wonder!
I do ask to come as a  maid
No, Is because say
I have no place to go ➡. Do not also serves as  treatment
. You say  Anta also'm rather ~
Araki teacher to hear that ➡
The'm cure properly
Yes
And (Ruriko) you hope?
Because it is my turn and I Na go fast!
What Miten of
Senior
N~tsu?
Na because  you strange imagination live Na by
you different
Ruri-chan I see trouble.
You can Yare only thing you want to do of his own
. Become ?
Yes
Eh?
Fufufu...
So Do not because you different
Eh?
Sure to'm this on a do...
I go for the first time I also.
And I'm a death anniversary
of 28 th mother today
Do you was  likely
Teacher a little while ago for the first time I...
. I did not come  27 years
Why?
You may not yet talk
to you.
My father ➡ for you to go to overseas
work
I think that had a
love  between mother and a man
I was leaving a  long house..  (Rintaro It is my voice) of junior high school students ➡
without even the courage to ascertain
the thing  mother ➡
The words had blamed much mother
in my mind is not issued
. I think  and it it had transmitted
to mother
. And drove  mother to
suicide in the depression To ➡ was
I'm I a
without permitting such myself ➡
I did not come here much also
Mom I'm sorry
♬ ~
was good
is come your grave properly
Your thanks
Spirit I much ➡ habit of family doctors
had fled
from the fact that face the  yourself.
Really is I was scared that the face
But ceased to escape
I met with you
It is because you have me meet
my heart was empty
Akira-san
I was I have loved you
.
Healers as in without ➡
as one man to love you
To make you happy
over a period of this life
. Could you be  marriage?
♬ ~
Sorry suddenly in a place like
Absolutely today ➡ in front of mother
And I you wanted to tell
this feeling
Because it is kind of my
unilateral convenience ➡
answer is not to say that right now
. You answer  now
. = = teacher thank you
but I ➡
and the teacher can not get married.
Is likely or
. Do not be
. That  psychiatrist becomes love
that patients ➡
I think I Tteyuu  reverse transition?
Eh?
Fufu~tsu...
. It was written in the book of  teacher
It "love is transient mental illness."
But
feelings for my Akira-san...
I'm became lovers
Hino Rintaro teacher of psychiatrist
. Say Nante you happy
by applying a life in hot flashes in  patient Man ➡
can not be  credit
mom I'm sorry.
In front of the mother is gone it is terrible
to son
Teacher
Yes
. You may want to hear
one as  patient
. The  my illness
Yes.
Do you not yet healed?
I think it is getting better  No lot
.
But If I had that something was troubled
➡
Please come to the examination  anytime
. Thank you for
Ja
♬ ~
(voice of Madoka) Hula It was?
(Madoka)
What are you doing talking about? Brother
Idea opponent patient?
Okay.
Not a Is the What it ethical violation?
So once signed up properly
I married...
. Did you dumped by up  propose?
By me not say  many times
Madoka-chan
Also favorite things Rintaro is raised to make
and
Crawling?
Little because I remembered for my
Hey... Mizushima
(Open and close sound of the door)
(Madoka) Oh Oh Yuriko and I got back in amazed
There so Speaking ➡
➡ but beautiful lily flowers had been equipped
to  grave
You're there Madoka?
Thank you for
Huh...
. I different
There Yuriko
. And of had me offerings
flowers to  every year anniversary
Mizushima is?
Did not you also known such a thing  to pass the brother
?
So
with good year and I Hula is!
No At the same with this...
. You doing
Ttsu~tsu Do not not found  woman's emotions!
(Madoka) huh...
Huh ~
♬ ~
(small dream) «dream 乃姉's»
(sound door is open)
(small dream) is the customer.
Is this a can I to Yume乃 Mr.
Really?
And will you like things Rintaro?
Mizushima teacher what
If you do not like that of Hino teacher ➡
I'm not or came to see  bother
me?
I came look much the Rintaro.
I think  mine only become a teacher different
of want you to be happy
Patients my addition to Hino teacher should not to be saved
is ➡
There are many . and I
So...
Mizushima teacher
. You
thank thing  Hino teacher.
Yume乃 Mr.
And I do not my
now married far from
Geisha of work Good luck here
mom to also give back to not when the
. Do  is already good?
I have to get ready soon
Thank you, please return
♬ ~
(Fukuhara) Do you have any appetite?
Appetite there a
. Do you sleep well ?
Last night so much and
There? Fukuhara Mr. Why?
In just dumped ➡
might Eitel
is such a big hole in the heart  now
This.
But love
comedian of Hino teacher also has said,
"It's thought to Toka be happy at Toka love
useless
Happy I because it is another matter"
I always
and I said to Nante was dumped?
And if look how you can see it
is likely or
Fukuhara kun!
Not able to save the
patients in such a wild guess of examination!
Does not become  of empathy way also
be... I'm sorry
...  There
N~tsu? There
Fuka也 kun Hello.
(Kaoru) N~tsu?
And (Kiryu Fuka也) an
Et al.
. Is  to
. Was !
Eh?
Is your time teacher lecture
Well yes
Psychoanalysis is the science of empathy
All of mental illness is not a
disease.
's Center of the personality I am thinking
(Ruriko)
I even without gambling ➡
okay
. Also  I not gambling...
. To  belly Tsu was ~
a little bit more you know
only 100 times after noon break
. ~ N .
Cormorant ~ ~ N
What?
"I tendon want to eat
Tendon want to eat
katsudon if useless
It ➡ if useless
I want to at least eat egg bowl"
Ask....
your gun hoo
Ja eel bowl is?
Thanks ~~ cormorant!
(Araki) Ha ha ha...!
Terribly heart is damaged or ➡
many people who fell into
center of the disease due to lack  loving ➡
in treatment only, such as going to change
the view of  drugs and things ➡
= = to heal not the thing.
➡ by such cases the treatment's snuggle up to
empathetic
that  patient's condition is gradually getting better little by little
➡
not uncommon
. Why do  dream Chiyo?
Circle like a good feeling
Fufufu...
(knock)
Yes.
The (Ikumi) there...
. What  and?
Yeah
And treatment of (Rintaro of voice) mind ➡
or will the good
only  symptoms get better?
It to ➡
patients a to a more happy life not only
Would not it should lead ?
➡ In order to reduce the loneliness and sadness of the patients
even a little
'll  therapist can what?
➡ umbrella the day it rains
thunder is heard day ➡ to become a blanket wrapped around
would we to what is needed?
This treatment's just the
people love it ➡ not
is common to give want to all people
you think was happy ➡
It might
to be the most difficult issue in  life
( because Rintaro of voice)
Love is not troublesome
. also embracing
remain  his thoughts ➡
Opponent might just hurts
Love Some people say that obsession
Men and women of love and family of love also ➡
not only when  beautiful ➡
very also is when it becomes
to dangerous
while hesitation still I also as a psychiatrist ➡
Patients and we are facing every day
. If there is no  But true love ➡
you can not you have it large
and that such save  people
. Healing Anno salvation who the  people ➡
still ultimately that there is only love ➡
that we should love the people in  serious ➡
I will believe so
. Do you think if  everyone?
Please let the voice of the
everyone about this today
♬ ~