(Yume乃) ⦅much ➡ alone
much lonely...⦆
♬ ~
(En'noji) I'm going to take responsibility if Hino Mr.
?
(Hino Rintaro)
still embarrassing thing I ➡
to that seen  this kind of photo on
a lot of people are
. Or if you are  margin bite?
's Being questioned is gonna's ethical issues as a doctor
Hospital trust's play-off!
You can easily accused of at
therapeutic problem as  doctor ➡
There are
ready to  any number of take responsibility
. We want to discuss
and  But anyway the person before that.
Opponent to become
surely lawsuit would have no way to convince
. I think I'm  some misunderstanding has occurred
Misunderstanding?
Cherry blossoms to full bloom or not it good mood
you
. I whether that was also the
artificial respiration while  cherry-blossom viewing.
Certainly kiss was
. If Hanashiae  But fact is close to the accident
...
(Hasumi) Oke In Hino it around
. Dedokoro of  Chairman photo Nde Rassharu grabbed
Suka?
No copper Miyagawa-kun?
(Miyagawa) I ➡ photos from acquaintance
In did only got.
(Hasumi) acquaintance?
Are you my sold to magazines?
The Chi... You difference
(En'noji) Ja I Tteyuu who sold
!
Hino Mr.
Yes
...  Time being Kimi home confinement Shitamae Please wait
.
Also have
many that require patient's examination today
Your patient to delegate to
another physician in
. Ask entered
(Buzz)
(Araki) somehow it
senior...
everyone is for a while
senior What does it mean?
En'noji president to asked the of
Hino of the pinch saved me I
. Patients  senior I'm to do
?
I'll see in here to settle
that of  Well the time being you
. And you little... Stop it by what it !
You are mental sweating it would have been senior
something secret!
It 'because you can hold hands
doing so
Huh... lie did not say
Ja What does it mean?
There's a mon What I also Na
circumstances.
It 's  can not say to you
Anyway ➡ until Hotobori is cool
here is Oke left to me
. I'll continue to be
takeover properly in was found  ➡
patients Thank you the
What's'm the good you Really.
People to be left to other seniors from No
(Reporter)
Please let me meet the Hino teacher ➡
I want to receive the
comments about this article
(Kaoru) patient The
you will be trouble because your quiet to's.
Is part of the
empathic treatment that this is also good of Hino teacher? Be no  (Fukuhara) why
!
(Kaoru) Fukuhara kun!
Little Fukuhara teacher useless...!
(Buzz)
(Kaoru) hated!
(Reporters) to Yume乃's geisha
something to say is?
(Kaoru)
Please be quiet! Here is a hospital!
Please  here is left to me
. Did you mean what  Hino teacher?
If you want to be a good psychiatrist ➡
Do I did not
it 's should  love refrain? Teacher ➡
Is not that completely different it has been and that it was saying !
It is not sorry to
really is has become in such a commotion and
. Do you admit ?
But there is ➡
not a
love with something like accidents  Deaigashira.
Do you any, of what kind of kiss?
That is the kiss of as shown in the photograph
It in house arrest from
Araki teacher ➡ to my place
to Fukuhara
now be willing to  examination kun also support please.
kiss
love to be considered if it is...!
There!
There...
There is Mizushima ask
. I do want to have
Note  Araki senior
(Mizushima Yuriko) What do you mean?
Senior It 's an excellent psychiatrist ➡
actually'm in the treatment of eating disorders.
Today is not the senior of the bag contains a nothing food
Would probably going to
procurement somewhere
Quite wrong?
What worried the like have this place suddenly
worsening
⦅Feeling bad Doke hey⦆
If you are worried about that Is the
person?
I because it is okay
.. Ask the  senior
(door of the opening and closing sound)
found
Miyagawa is to not have courage than I thought
in small
Hasumi as surgeon
success of this earlier nor expected unlikely.
Although ➡ had connected the desire to Hino
it is this commotion
by skipping a Reality in  geisha
(En'noji) huh...
New hospital ➡ assume super-aged society
cutting-edge medical care, including psychiatric we want to continue to
deployment.
You to wonder if what I want leave the
director of this new hospital?
I think that live up  your expectations
All...
How
individual doctors I guess has become the
Now you Susumo afraid not to before both!
I'm you our ally.
<This save Mayoe that lamb our
modern ➡
is a story of a doctor >
♬ ~
it <is Rintaro Hino My name delay Was
psychiatrist>
♬ ~
Madoka?
I was gone copper  c'mon Madoka
?
(Madoka) As you can Nichanja not by
kind of
Eh?
Of said is
brother when dead  mom ➡
to me, "Do not worry because I'll have!"
I "I will protect!".
While saying such a thing and I know
here of crying alone
. I have no idea that it was crying  But
it once and for all?
The ➡ in bytes for me
➡ to study studying
and Is the me earn also  money
. In  Ittsumo rice also made me.
athletic meet both
brother classroom visitations
. Because they are also
Contact Nichangai without There are  mom ➡
I was also need not cry
Kind of older brother thing
had been respected
(Madoka) even if doing
brother is...
. believe !
Madoka...
♬ ~
(opening and closing sound of the door)
[TEL] (ringtone)
Hello
Teacher?
I'm sorry
The teacher can not meet anymore
. Please contact  do that No
anytime
But....
The promised is not it was or
and I'm much to your side
Teacher...
(Reporter) Yume乃 san!
And it will do come?
I Could you let  story heard?
(Reporters) Yume乃 san!
Please let me meet
(Reporter) Yume乃's in!
I will do there?
(Reporter) Yume乃 san! Mr. Yume乃!
(Ikumi) Yume乃, please return No
Contact cage
I'm more picky
(Reporter) Yume乃 san!
(Ikumi) Yume乃...
(Reporter) It 's and is
Yume乃's were sold that article?
I to the weekly magazine?
Of course not, to
such nitpicky thing
. Do you complained  Hino teacher?
Are you wanted me to be who I am? Dream Ayano yo
Shimbashi
. Na please come to  parlor
geisha paying
properly Hanayo If you wanted to hear the story in ➡.  Now the home was was back!
And sowed mom salt
Yume乃...
.. Please return  Contact
. You troubled  (secretary)!
(Ruriko) No Ann important story
to the president's!
(Ruriko) circle like for a while
. Excuse me ...
Crude is this face Forgot?
Or chrysanthemum thousand generations?
In to have become the various
care is  daughter
(En'noji) daughter?
'm Yume乃 of  daughter
Yume乃 of you?
That the child has been encounter in this eye I also not be silent
. And I was asked to consult on  personally
. Or  clogging gold?
Planning is...
(En'noji)
Shinbashi that chrysanthemum Chiyo who was fighting
a dream Chiyo and number one in the ➡
Do not I rubbed ragtag
. I  customers your way
. = = where me back not a place to come
of extortion racketeering.
It's not do bad things say
of respectability!
I wonder about to leave such et Toko here also leave
!
Leave  prepared!
Yume乃 I because I'm my daughter!
What about it!
I'm sorry by apologize for  worry.
(Pond)
and I've got to have become what teacher
.'m Troubled  in such a thing
You're probably a doctor?
Is probably my attending physician?
Are you trying to quit  doctor? Kimi
Teacher national politics is the same, even Doctor
. Is the most important thing to save  human ➡
It is not a qualification
Fufufu... Do not be not come so
. It.  Actually in trouble What
?
You are in trouble Become a  caught
Dilemma?
And he does say  detailed .. but ➡
you are caught
between the interests and the interests there .
As a politician? No wonder
Which it does discarded
. Once discarded  I compromised
Dilemma...
♬ ~
it...
It is this situation?
'm Likely
. Is it continues to hurt
are you stuck finger that ....
(Pond) painful painful painful
. There is no only
way folding chopsticks  one
Well it...
. Please think twice  pond's
The most important thing is what or?
It is the pond's own
. Assuming  truncate the interests of
one only ➡
Or is not not you there is no way?
Yeah...
Eh did you How so?
Will may here come
also press
And then I thought that it either will not go
for shopping
Thank you
Do not little either had too much to buy.
Araki teacher also
today was not that unusual
Along or
yeah
Ja be empty fried Tsukurokka
Thing that photo cherry me full bloom ➡
2 It's before about months?
Yeah
. Opponent  Rintaro has kiss
Yume乃's?
Or Akira-san?
It do not know
I was not aware
in those days still her illness
. Though told me  accident ➡
not been suddenly from the other side?
Yeah But ➡
It because became
opportunity to know where her unstable ➡
in that sense might have been
one step of practice
. The one-step of  practice?
Are you talking  Hey with it serious?
Course.
Rintaro that are doing'm a very cruel
Why?
Rintaro is not it not only seen her illness
Even because I'm a doctor
Rintaro be Even excellent psychiatrist
is ➡
everyone admits I also It is respected.
But I do ➡ When was her
I think I want you to look at
myself properly not just  disease
Wait a minute I think we
Mizushima said
Doctor and patient and I Na beyond the boundary
. The ➡ before becoming a relationship of  doctor and patient
Story When was that is there was
Aiu another
. Are you scared of more than  boundary is probably Rintaro
What do you mean?
Rintaro is ➡ to become a
good psychiatrist
came away the  much love
But ➡ What it
Yourself It's not what only
I do not want to hurt?
I'm sorry...
Where they apologize is a
really tight Iyo
. I'll tell a good thing  to Rintaro
. Kiss for  woman There are two types of of the
. I can not forget to death  Kiss and ➡
Die enough to forget want to kiss
I'm Done
Sky fried?
Hmm ~...
Of tomorrow also Hasumi teacher from early morning
instead operating variety of
Along or
♬ ~
just do not want to hurt the  myself huh...
The [TEL (Bell)
Hello.
(Ruriko) Good evening Hino teacher
(Ruriko) teacher hospital
to do will likely fired Even?
Very Hey
. Please say a  Aizawa Ruriko Mr.
requirements
. I wonder not meet with  tomorrow Okiya?
I am gonna want to come and I asked 50 million have
During this time
. I'm not'm
commotion of  or else with the weekly magazine far from
How do I
mother had put the that article I am you?
Ja tomorrow
♬ ~
(Ruriko) it did ready money?
No
. Did you come  Ja What the?
'm Not the case
and Tatte Tsu me defeated
Will not pass you the money
See ya's trial
. I'll sued  and Anta hospital
You gamble
treatment of addiction is the necessary disease.
Blap!
Huh ~?
And if you pass the  money
also in invested in gambling ➡
disease will cause worse
. In disease  Akira not only
to me ➡
con
likely either to Tatte Tsu so saddle I do not go!
The No even a Anta was instead of the
money by selling that photo?
If you become'm likely gold
what Even of sell
. Even though  mother...
Why? Hey!
You want to say
and I sold  until Akira or?
Hey not known .
'm That girl I'm living for me
Me and Akira mother and daughter variety of
. ~ Hey connected by a strong bond
(Ikumi) Anta What people The ➡
how far you gonna need is
care if Kizutsukere that girl
because Anta took En'noji
from me!
Huh?
(Ruriko) but its revenge!
Huh...?
Ikumi Anta in had all
Beauty knowledge also had all also horse of dance
Not lose like that in Anta talent there is in Akira
So
Anta the I'll annoy!
The'm my scapegoat that child
. It will only  money wanted
. Do not say that  irresponsible!
Whether that child was waiting much
the Anta return to ➡
I will not know ?
Public that child what was not good than
it is coming out in the ➡
become
geisha because of Anta debt ➡
remember dancing for Anta to ➡
impossible to Good luck Good luck...
. and...  until at length get sick.
➡ the habit of Anta do not know such hardships also
of that child
without
mother surface only when it is nice  convenience!
Mother...
Mother's just me
'm I win what now
(Footsteps)
(Ikumi) Yume乃...
. Out  Anna photos Though Chat was ➡
Much wanted to meet
. I Te  a ~ do Ha ha ha...!
Little to come
♬ ~
I'm a fool to want to be loved
to (Yume乃 of voice)
Akira also Anna crazy mother
I do not think so
. = = there along either.
Mon Anta also a
ultimate Oedipus complex
. It was suicide to  mom ➡
and probably got to  dragged still?
You might  likely
I now
'm purposely do stepped mines
Hey Is the I do with Hinorin ➡
Why I would forgive
I even doing what?
It because I came to the money up to
home ➡ Even during this time
Jan should I Tsukidase
to quickly police
There is not that your originally did
.
In the course of treatment you may not be able to control
the feelings
Fu ~ N
I do in because I'm sick mercy and
Different
What's the difference?
You do I want to be your power
. Do not say just  fine skill.
Anta want the only Akira of
patient salvation
I nuisance
do that because they know
Yume乃's
. Please believe
Yume乃 Mr. Akiyoshi san
people is important to me
. Both  is an important personality.
Can you I forgive also doing what
Ja?
Allows
. Can you love  this I even?
Stupid
Akira of came betrayed Motto Zu
because stupid
I'll betrayed from here
. Because 'll then be more terrible.
I Do not me doing ...!
President! It is very
. I'll got from  to (En'noji) Koreka
now Yabe-kun What
Eh?
If you do not observe the  But Hino...
And (Machiko) Professor
Not a okay?
Anyway It's neck if Leave her alone.
But President!
And yea there was
ethics violation him to really...
'm His place're plenty
I also your place
♬ ~
(chime )
(reporters) Hino teacher ~! Could you comment on word
Yumeno's
?
Hino sensei! To comment!
(Reporters) Yume乃's will open the conference in the matter of the articles of mom and
example
(Reporter) «Thank you all means
comment! »
(Reporters)« teacher! To comment! »
(Reporters)
Come« right? »
⦅Well I can you forgive also doing what
? ⦆
Doctor called
Hino Rintaro to entice me ➡
and I doubt my in dissociative identity disorder came closer to say that there
Daughter fooled
... it is in the damaged goods.
Please ask everyone
Daughter I was not a something originally
heart disease
Hino Rintaro ➡ been hurt
to the doctor that
and I had been to
sick  really.
➡ in such a shameless doctor
University Hospital
Do you allowed
and Nante are examination wearing white coat?
[TV] daughter
misanthropy to the ringing got ➡
It has become not be out
also  parlor
[TV] such daughter is... a pity
Hino teacher It I have involved
to ridiculous parent and child also.
Too much
.. When it was true is  (reporters) talk...
rude ne!
You'll have decided to  Really!
You (reporters) rather than a mother!
Please tell me now you feel
's  Yume乃 Mr. Yume乃
. Are you thinking you sue  Hino-san?
It is of course!
I complained  Hino Rintaro and
Toshiminami University Hospital!
(Buzz)
we have served as a chief of
classroom  Toshi the Southern psychiatric ➡
My name is  Miyagawa
. I will
question  Yume乃 san.
You but we ask
it's dissociative identity disorder ➡
Is the same personality and personality that are  now conference
➡ when taken  this photo?
And I do not know the meaning of  questions
. If you could What  was mentioned earlier
your illness ➡
This photo when you have been taken ➡
possible was  another personality of also I was wondering whether there
(Ruriko) I want this child to say I
are saying a lie? You!
(Miyagawa) is the possibility of a problem
If
if you were another personality ➡
Storage will not do and than ambiguous
(Reporter) Na is also such a thing
and (Reporter) How do I do that?
Do you do if a  (reporters)?
Please say clearly!
(Reporters)
please say clearly!
Do you do not answer?
(Reporter) 's Rintaro Hino!
You (reporters) whoa's Hino
(Machiko) It is butchery Once done enter
now please through from a good
Miyagawa professor will have me hit the
question to defend the Hino teacher .
course is to defend the hospital
Yume乃's ➡.
Is fine, rather than answer.
(Miyagawa) Hino! What you came to!
Thank you Miyagawa teacher
But because it is already quite
(reporters) just the right ➡
. It.... We'll listen to  both of opinion
(reporters) Please answer me!
And probably did cheat  (reporters)
Yume乃 san!
She does not have a lie
(Reporters) but it is that of multiple personality
What dissociative identity disorder?
Please be
more detailed description of the pathology of  Yume乃's
About it we can not answer
.
(Reporter)
or is that pretty heavy?
And'm sincerely not
a problem that should be answered here
. But we Haru recognized
the story of Mr.  Well then Yume乃?
Yes
(Reporter) Please speak properly recounted
please!
Please be
description (Reporter) For more information properly!
All responsibility there for me is a
psychiatrist
She does not have any responsibility
. How do I take I  (Reporter)
responsibility?
What are you wanted to be forgiven
to say that (reporters) say of such a tone
?
(reporter) psychiatrist or will do it is correct?
Little... Gappori to take it likely
alimony it's this minute
Hey Anta also let Yan say something
.
(Reporter) and I think you have much silence!
Please answer firmly  (Reporter)!
(Reporters) do you do such mean by that?
Teacher!
I'll answer  order to... in order
(Ruriko)
did you how little Akira?
(Reporter) Yume乃 san!
And (Ruriko) Akira Wait!
(Reporters) Yume乃 san!
Please wait (Reporter)!
Talk! A little more talk!
Hey you!
Please let  story heard!
(Reporter) was the teacher!
Comment Thank you!
I'd like a little while ago of continuation!
(Reporters) word thank you!
[TV] party who in the middle of the conference would stand a
seat ➡
I do not know  truth yet.
[TV] But psychiatrist has also been
appeared several times on this program ➡
like this...
Too awkward
. Also Na Hino ended
I do not have is
way that wished himself
♬ ~
Welcome back
. over  sorry worry.
'm Really
Another hospital
Nobody defended by I'm ➡ not me
Rintaro Matters
. Know
. Did you speak with  Yume乃's?
Likely...
. I thought that it is not
appetite because are made  rice It 's a little
Thank you for Mizushima
♬ ~
(Female voice) ➡ Look at that conference
I thought it was
I Na wonder there is  something circumstances
I was not a bullet
things that patients
Hino teacher The  Yes
there today Hino teacher
..
I think is our patient's ally?
Today since the Araki teacher will
clinic
. Do Is not it  (male)
Hino teacher?
You return
(Kaoru) eh.?
We also Let's return
there... hey that ➡
. So please be seen  Araki teacher.
(Woman) I mon good teacher
(Kaoru) How to Let Fukuhara teacher
King Hasumi
It's how you first of condition?
Ah to dive back
(Araki) along or
Naa Araki
. Do not involve the Hino
to you of ill
Ill?
(Hasumi) satonaka Mizuki's ➡
... have I been asked to you was surgery
(Araki) go back
All's my responsibility
. Not matter that you need to apologize  no but ➡
this street
was not sorry
hate... ➡
blame me
she believe me ➡
All of the decision was left to me
. I  So my responsibility
. Braze said to you
Even her mom?
And do I have to come (Mizuki mother)
⦅is ➡
not a you! ⦆
Probably  ⦅Araki teacher! ⦆
(Mother of Mizuki) ⦅Better yet ➡
I also ten years ago ➡ with daughter
I should Kurere kill ...⦆
⦅Mizuki mother crying⦆
(voice of Araki) to
funeral I I also had done .
did not put any
or so...
Naa ➡
came back here  Why suddenly?
Hino's the end
it is not coming back anymore
. Are you trying to be pandering to  seriously En'noji?
Oh
. It 'was Misokona~tsu
(Araki) and UU...!
It (sound to vomiting)
Araki...
Araki senior?
And (Fukuhara) it is
vomiting blood yourself now inspection.
I'm sorry teacher but have been told to watch
to
It was found [TEL]
. Will head from  now
♬ ~
Contact - Hino-kun
The "Hino-kun" is not it by senior
So I said to
any state?
Arterial bleeding gastric ulcer caused by overeating.
And I was hemostasis at the time being endoscope
a little bit a hole in the stomach in the ➡
it because I was Toko
dont have to  laparotomy
(Kaoru) properly Araki teacher of thing
management to please I Hino teacher
. Is not got angry
because of  senior.
Also quite painful mon I'll gastric ulcer
Fufufu...
Rintaro it because I'm a just
clip do not let the other talk
. I wonder if not us to only two people a little
and Is the I'm bad Hey
. = = I'll only 5 minutes
crawling to
.. you  rude.
Nephew bed Raise bed
Is good good good your-pain Tatata...
It straightforward to hear
What is the reason?
Or if you what you are
in place like this?
What did you do  Yume乃's?
Without mound  contact.
Black thing I'll eat
I have all to you instead of
Black thing?
Kind of guy Toka's hospital politics's Toka gold
En'noji is ➡ by medical corporation acquired certain
I'm going to the hospital  psychiatric center
Bottom of director to the ➡
The'm was going Matsuriageru
the you that are selling name
Know No Could completely
. I'll underwriting
is I  kind of mush is all
So nothing to the worrying
You're white concentrate on her without.
It is absurd
Nante fight the hospital for me
. Even ask them shaved
life in  such a thing ➡
I do not have at all the happy
I do not want to be the same regret with me .
same regret?
I wonder...
. Patients  they have reverse transition ➡
I did not able to save
Reverse transition?
That she... ➡
committed suicide six months ago
It was also possible to
operating in (Araki voice) Other hospital
. Did not run me it I'm .
She believed in me
I was in love with her.
That's what's my responsibility
Even if it was the responsibility of the
senior ➡
she or would hope
the appearance of today's seniors?
♬ ~
(crying)
Huh ~...
(Araki) Yume乃's
. 'Em for saving absolute .
It is possible to save you own
➡'ll not save you to only
Yume乃 san
I understand
♬ ~
since then in  all here Do you that there is no
contact also?
(Ikumi) in Which personality ➡
Anokowa every night
I'd come back here
. I guess had copper
. You think they'll come back  surely
Hmm ~...
. = = it might have no
what you can do to the teacher of psychiatry.
(Small dream) Fufufu...
♪ ~
(pond) it
.. Where where  ♪ ~ pond chan here
♪ ~
♪ ~ pond chan here
hand of the sound to better?
Where Where
to  ♪ better to become a ~ hand?
♪ ~ pond chan here
hand of sound towards I
caught  ♪ ~
!
It is me
Hahahaha...!
what…! The motherfucker
(Small dream) Hahahaha...!
(En'noji) Hahahaha...!
Eh Shoyume tea ~ N
. Na What a small dream of  Shoyume chan do?
The No I want you to tell me  (small dream)?
Oh I felt that if teaching ~ ➡
It 'might be raised grant
(Small dream) Really?
What Chapter! Number one?
Is good! Oke is whole thing! Yup!
Eh! Fufu~tsu
pond chan cool
Fufufu...
Ah...
En'noji...
(En'noji) Yes.
(Pond) Planning is Haa...
(Pond)
me bad, but I have given up that story
With that story?
'S matter of acquisition of  example
. I played  promise
Minister to resign in tax evasion and
. Might
inspections enters also over there Once  poor and
Now The Iyo Yaba.
The Haa...
I bad
Idiot!
such are easily give up!
About this story is probably talking about over there came with
?
And Korah nephew'll not a  joke pond!
I do think that it has play taiko Dondake
own way until now!
Somehow travel!
I do not able to go back anymore!
Cho... hey!
Pond!
And (pond) Calm down!
Ya'll ➡ everyone
to wonder a fool  thing of me!
Therefore Ya to  fool!
♬ ~
mom I is still
bad psychiatrist.
[TEL] (ringtone)
Hello
Is the emergency as soon as possible to the hospital
. I I can not be something
examination in  curfew
Patients it's you 's to be useless to say you have
Did you mean... Yume乃's?
Now, coming soon.
(Kaoru) a teacher Thank you
It (knock)
It came well
Thank you for waiting..  Please you
. I was  worry
Where did you have?
Did you appear blindly
What are the  Hinorin Anna place?
No I wanted to see what a terrible lie Tsukuka
?
Different
It is because you were worried
After sloppy Mihanashi?
Can not it just
Why?
Is absolutely
➡ simply because you came here
I can I'm really happy now
Also It was good to meet
. Of came there
ask  Hinorin
. What ? Is  Why
from inside my ➡
and of want to turn off the  Akira.?
Because Akira is
not go what one well with're
Even when that conference ➡
and I wanted to ruin
I ➡ in the bad guys
thoroughly the Hinorin. = = pretty damage was received
Yet ➡
The  Akira was the way in the middle.
Akira-san did you a
interfere in what way?
Very strange feeling
My mind or ➡
is I no longer Wakan  Akira of mind or
. Like  yourself not the my
Yume乃's
It personality It is an integrated.
Your disease has become very well
Yume乃's share the Akira's mind
. If we increased  such time ➡
the time there is no  storage
eliminated soon You
mind of Akira something you'll have to say I do not need
Yume乃's.
Why I got to
deny so much Akira-san?
Is okay
Akira's wounded storage also ➡
you will be overcome and you if
kit  now
.. Because  I will be in force...
it's annoying.
Hinorin
you will have already noticed
Akira is in love with Anta
First time...
. Born  and of came to like the people for the first time
man
Morning also day and night also ➡
➡ Anta in in full the head
... rather Wakan do I do if .
Of painful
♬ ~
So turn off the other Akira
. To erase  ask you...
Off to
Yume乃's
You
enough loved as it is is a person worthy to be
. of either  myself also please give love
.
Hinorin can not you love?
Thing you thought carefully
. It has me not be a  man and a woman?
You can not be it
I... ➡
I makes you important
Because you're important ➡
I I want to save you
to save you ➡
I must be stomach
healer
In order that I'm in the treatment's ➡
= = To not become a relationship of men and women and I do not go
. and to gently what  Ja?
Is promised is not it or
"Much you are in your side" I
Another friendly lie to quit
Because only hard
♬ ~
Hehe~tsu...
Thank
teacher goodbye
♬ ~
Please wait Yume乃 san!
Please do not go !
Teacher examination anymore...
♬ ~