This is the story of a psychiatrist
that save the lost ones.
Please Dr.! Help me!
I do not want to go over there anymore!
All the guys over there, everyone hates me.
Today, all the members are setting up a machine gun
waiting for me
A Machine gun?
Those guys are reporters
When I don't answer personal questions,
they'll deliberately fire into my heart
Did you sleep?
There is no way I can sleep, can't I!
Even the Prime Minister uses improper words, right?
Yeah!
That bastard ....
The nervousness of the sleeping disorder
produces a look of excitement
since the nerves and muscles are likely to become stiff
He's suffering these symptoms for being always
concerned about his professional duties
Doctor....
I can't do it anymore.
I want that news Secretary to quit right now
The first step is to closely emphasise with the patient's heart
Ike-san.
I can see that you have been trying really hard until now.
Now, it is really important the timing
to pass casually for what you want to request from him
It was really hard,
since you've been trying this hard
how about stopping?
If I could do that I wouldn't be suffering this much!
You're right.
The healer at this time, do not divert the sight from the patient
In some cases he can hold gently the man's hand in between
Doctor...
Ike-san
Doctor...!
Here.
It's hot, hot...hot!
Ike-san.
I want the minister to make all the reporters have a troubled face.
In order to not be bothered by them,
how about trying to make a cheerful face?
cheerful face?
I think that's imposible
Just consider stretching your face, just try it, please
The time for the diagnosis is generally 50 minutes
The best I can do with this limited time
it's to try to connect with the patient's stiff heart
even momentarily
and make it feel carefree;
that's my job.
It's time.
ok?
It's perfect.
From the human, in this world,
the amount of people that live with a broken heart
are overflowing in this city
wealthy and happy people too,
healthy people too,
lovely lovers too
Anyone is an afflicted lamb
Sheep! Let's move forward together!
This world is a long interminably prairie!
Never rush,
It is good to have rest when you get tired.
But, it's dangerous if you stray from your companions.
Then, together, with no fear, move forward!
I'm you ally.
Hey! It's seems like someone is going
to jump off from our floor!
Jumping off!
Jumping off!?
She's jumping off!
The train from Gotanda
Jonan street 5th floor, nro 3 dep 1
Jonan arc Mansion.
On the 5th floor, at the rooftop
we have identified a women standing outside the fence
the agre is from late 20's to early 30's
Currently we're trying to persuade her from the roof
with your permission
wait wait, .. who are you?
You can't enter now
I have some business to do.
Are you a resident?
Gather together!
Star the preparation for the air mattress!
Yes, sir!
This is too soon, don't hurry it.
If you have problems, let's discuss it first.
How about trying to talk about it first?
You're life continues from now on!
Just try to carry those strong fellings a little longer!
Try to do your best! to keep on living!
Please stop trying so hard!
I think you've been already trying really hard, haven't you?
You don't have to do it anymore.
Do not come!
If you come I'll jump off!
State of excitement
The possibility of hallucinations' use and drug dependence is unknown
I'm REALLY going to jump from here
But before that
Would you like some tea?
What? who are you?
I'm just on my way
It's just that while walking down there
I just wanted very much to drink tea with you while talk together
Since I've come this far.
Are you a fool?
Certaintly ..
This is really impressive
it's much higher from what I thought from the ground.
If you feel .. I guess it'll be painful
Pain? I do not feel such a thing.
nothing at all.
I might be already dead
She is in a severe depression
When the time comes, let's fall together.
Here
Have some
I want to die alone!
Do not interfere!
yes, it's still scary, right?
How about quitting this?
Maybe it's not that bad a double suicide.
Eh?
When the time comes, we'll fall together,
didn't you just said that ?
Fall with me
I understand.
Let's fall.
Are you OK?
She has been really confused until now
She doesn't even understands herlself anymore
from now on, I don't know what behaviour she may have,
so, please convey this to the doctor of the location where you'll take her
so they can take care of this
Understood.
Let's go
Ah? Please, could you...
Are you ok?
Ah, Thanks you.
Can you stand up?
I can't stand up on my own
Ah, ok
One, two, three, let's go
Yes, let's go
Sorry
Let's go slowly.
Can you understand me?
Are you OK? Ōtomo, transportation!
This is the story of a doctor
that saves the modern stray lambs
Sorry for the delay
I'm a psychiatrist, Hino Rintaro
Psychoanalysis is the science of empathy.
Not all mental disorders are a diseases
I take into consideration the individuality of everyheart
trying to get close to each personality,
if it's possible to emphasise with them
to gradually come to settled down
the disjointed patient's heart
This is what I learned in the USA
This is psychology of self
So, emphaty, it's what we need
In the field of counseling, the relationship
with the patients is not with the heart,
but with the body
with the body?
In other words,
there may be a demand/request for sex.
And to satisfy that would be bad, right?
So, if such situation happens, you cleverly answer
"That you could fall in love with me, makes me happy"
"Since I also like you, please hurry and get better soon!"
just say something like that.
Excuse me, Dr.
Yes?, Kawakami-kun
If when I say that, the patient,
becomes just more turned on
if their feelings just increase
if the patient begins to hold real
feelings of love about the doctor,
What should I do?
If it's during treatment, it doesn't matter, right?
Since we already now that by empathy, the patient's condition
can improve.
Once it becomes serious, it would be really bad...
Fukuhara-kun, what is it?
Eh..
There is also the danger for the psychiatrist
of holding romantic feelings for the patient, isn't it?
You're right, if that's the case, marry the patient
Please, dedicate your life to the patient
But, you can't marry all the patients , right?
Yes.
In fact, in the United States
love between a psychiatrist and a patient is not uncommon.
However, I seems to me as an abuse
of the position of power and not a humanitarian act.
What do you think?
Indeed.
In the opinion of some researchers
The state of love is transitory,
It is a condition, such as a mental illness.
It is a very dangerous condition in which you are deprived of reason.
For example, in the process of treatment,
even if the feelings happens to resemble love
Finally, the patient,
by no other than the doctor, is treated
for the love condition
And that leads to a happier life,
that's the duty of a psychiatrist.
That's the Dr. that discouraged a
women who wanted to commit suicide this morning
Dr. Hino Rintaro, right?
Then, let's stop for today.
Doctor, doctor... Please Doctor!
Ah Doctor!
How did you do to persuade her?
Please, give us a comment
I have no comments.
That was.just..
I didn't persuade her
I just fell with her, just that.
Dr. one word, please!
Excuse me
One word...
one word please!
Dr.!
going down, going down!
Please this way
The Dr. is really busy!
Dr.!
Dr. Please!
A star attraction?
Your body is all right?(after the jump) Dr.!
Please!
Please Please!
Everyone, thank you for the interview
Sorry, but
since the patients that came are already waiting..
Okay! Please give him space.
Dr. this way.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Dr. Rintaro, from the rooftop of the building
a woman wanted to do bungee jumping?
..something like that
Are you OK?
I was really scared, you know.
You'll become a more and more popular Dr.
Do not just focus on  fault finding the Prime Minister
How about a more productive question?
Don't make that face that says "The future of Japan is dark"
Please, a more bright  face, brighter!
That's nice, that feels good.
Eh.. possibly he was..
Hino-kun
What?
It seems that you were also called tonight.
What for?
It is a dinner with the director.
Ah, that was it.
At 6:00 hs, don't be late.
With the director
at 6:00 hs
It's common to have something like the opinion of experts on TV.
You're companion has arrived
Then, ah he's already here
Yes.
Ah, director,
today, for your invitation..
The coverage today was really impressive, right?
Couldn't you've done a better comment?
You look a litlle ill, don't you?
You can come to my psychiatric to received a scan of your brains.
That's probably an exaggeration.
I'll take care of the Director Ennouji and
the vice-director of the hospital
Yumeno, you're accompanying the Psychiatry Prof. Miyagawa
and the other guest.
Yes.
Good night.
Good night
good night.
And the other person? maybe a celeb doctor?
pfft what! No title? He's like a practice doctor?
A men with an income with less than 10 million anual
should'nt wish on coming here
Don't say that.
Now, put up your spirits and let's go
Yes
Hiro-kun, it's your first time coming here?
Then, please, enjoy it.
Good evening.
I'm Yumeno. Good evening.
We're waiting for you two.
Come in, come in.
it's been a long time, director.
Please, let me.
Here you go.
Madoka-sama, hasn't your looks/face become more widened?
These guys are our professors,
I have taken them here before, you know
I don't mean that face
This face.
where does the face ends?
and where your head starts?
You're noisy
Here 's the borderline, here.
Professor Hasumi, you don't enjoy sake, right?
Would you like a non-alcoholic beer?
Herbal tea.
Yes, please wait.
I looked at the photos on
Miyagawa Professor's "Medical Perspectives".
you've done another thesis publication, right?
You... I'm impressed
Did you read such a difficult book?
Well, I had a little interest in the area of the money for medical treatment .
Hino-kun, you've failed at accustome to such a place by now too, right?
Eh?
Aren't you becoming a professor?
I'm going to try to push the position for Hino-kun,
in the next Professor election.
Please to meet you, I'm Yumeno.
Please one, in order to get acquainted.
No please, don't be concern.
I must.
Since the work of a geisha would disappear.
Now please, Professor.
No, I'm still not a professor...
...talking about that, Prof. Miyagawa, what do you think?
Once a professor, with a series of meetings
and a long list of patients, you can't match the faces
and you won't be able to give your especial treatments any longer, Hino
Would it be right?
Probably not.
Well certainly,
If you have time to attend the conference,
since even one person, requires many examinations
Well, he said it himself, it is still impossible for him to become a professor.
Yet, if Hino-kun would become a professor,
he would be popular even with young people
The students of the medical school would increased dramatically.
Although it is the words of the director,
I disagree.
Even if he is a star attraction,
the psychoanalysis that he learned in the United States
and that he alleged that comes from the latest of biological psychiatry,
It's retrograde.
According to your words,
The specialty of Miyagawa Professor seems to be,
not even hearing the talk of the patients,
and administrating the medicine based only on the image diagnosis.
Due to this biological treatment
there are a lot of patients that can't be saved.
Probably I'm a little bit better, right?
If that would be the case, then the customers
would be more pleased, right?
Look, look,
This the gift has been..
Dr. look at this
Keep taking the medicine
Ok, the next one
Your image diagnosis has been criticized.
Patients lie,
Image diagnosis do not lie.
And from the first time when talking to the patient
the misdiagnosis is born.
The lies really do not exist in the hearts of people.
There are even many people with
a normal brain that are suffering.
And the understanding of that truth from the patients
It's not that the work of a psychiatrist?
It's annoying, shut up!
Are you trying to insult me, a professor!
One would expect a psychiatrist
not to be this childish.
Which is correct?
Neither is wrong.
Well, in the tone of a friendly competition
between psychiatrists, let's bring our spirits up.
Now, the number one and more popular in Shinbashi
Yumeno-chan will dance for us..
She's number 2
I'll take that.
Now Yumeno, too, have one full
Thanks you.
Dr., I'll serve you one drink.
ah
Now, next is Shinbashi famous train game
let's forget the melancholy of this sad world
C'mon C'mon C'mon ....
It's the departure time!
See? It's quite fun if you try this, right?
Yes, director.
Huh ... What am I doing?
"Pain? I do not feel such a thing."
"nothing at all"
"I might be already dead"
Are you coming in too? Please,
I'll be returning by now.
Please don't say such a sad thing
warm warm warm!
Now, let's play!
ah, the exit, exit, exit..
Yasuke , I'm home~
Rintaro
You're late.
It's you Mizushima, you surprised me~
I sent you mail saying I'll came and make dinner, didn't I?
Eh, sorry.
What? Are you drunk?
I can't believe it.
Sorry, sorry, I'll eat it tomorrow.
Here, this is a gift~
I don't need it.
Just take it, don't restrain.
Yasuke ~.
Huh ... what was that?
Really? At last a girlfriend?
Madoka-chan long time.
What?
So this was the relationship with my brother?
What silly thing are you saying
Since operations finished early,
I just thought of coming and make dinner.
mm I see.
Ah Madoka~.
Brother, brother
wait, are you OK?
Hey, I saw it on a variety show
When you fell from the rooftop,
did you hit in the head?
He's just drunk
so, I've been asked by the
people from my part-time job
they want your sign (autograph), you know?
so, just a few words, write something good, ok?
My favorite comedian
says this words
"Although I like famous sayings
I hate the guy that says the wise sayings"
That's good, write it down
Madoka-chan, since I prepared all of this
don't you want to take some?
wow, great!
Right?
Just all the things my brother likes.
Yeah, maybe..
Will be ok? You haven't eaten at all.
I just saved something.
Ah, ok then.
here we go
Rintaro, you just can't sleep in a place like that.
it's hopeless..you!
Do your best
From Hino Rintaro
mom..
Rintaro, what are you doing?
My mom..
Dr. Hino
From the Nishi-Azabu's mental health clinic
a letter of introduction has arrived from Dr. Enami
On your patients with PTSD (Posttraumatic stress disorder),
by all means please Dr.
they want you to try the EMDR (Eye Movement Desensitisation and Reprocessing).
I understand.
Kawakami-kun
Yes.
It's your first time with EMDR?
Please ask Fukuhara-kun the books on that, to be informed.
Yes.
Dr. you have a present from Agawa Mayuko.
Agawa Mayuko-san?
Dr. thank you so much for the other day.
You were able to come here.
Hello.
This is just a token from the heart but,
please accept this.
Thank you, I'll take care of it.
My daughter was very bright not so long ago.
And yet..
to cause such a big commotion
Why on earth did she do it?..
No matter how many times I ask her, she doesn't say anything
Mother
Let's calm a little.
Agawa Mayuko-san.
Where would you like to have some tea?
Since the other day there were too many people,
I was thinking of having our talk just
the two of us at a calm place
So, let's go
since here there are many interferences.
interferences?
wait Dr.
excuse me.
Dr. this will become another problem.
We cannot afford to send her home in this state.
Dr. Hino.
Please wait, Mayuko-san!
Please give me 50 minutes of your time, please.
50 minutes?
Hino-kun what are you doing?
Hey! Hino, stop it.
This is bad.
If you are accused of sexual harassment
it's my  responsibility as the chief Professor!
Hey stop it. Let her go.
Hey take him
Yes , please.
Let's go Dr. Hino!
ah... Mayuko-san!
Dr....
Mayuko-san I'll be waiting!
Dr!
I'm hungry~
The tip of my nose is itchy.
Ah a sweet bean jelly.
Here
Professor Miyagawa was really severe,
are you ok?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
This is just experience.
With this, I really understand
the suffering of that guy's patients
To deprive the freedom of patients in such a thing
It's barbaric, the lowest
This is good.
It's good
Hello? Are you listening?
Please say something,
Akira-san
If you escape from me ...!
Don't think about it~
I know.
Yumeno!
Yumeno, I just have an urgent business.
Here, please, take care of the medicine.
Answer me
Yes.
A smile suits you beter, you know?
see you later.
Although the introducer for the director is
the attending doctor, Professor Miyagawa,
could you please take his place.
Miyagawa Professor?
He's just about to leave for an academic meeting
Come again?
Are you ok?
Masuda Ikumi-san, please enter.
Hello.
eh... Masuda Ikumi-san.
Do you hear me?
Masuda Ikumi-san
I've been asked by that person to come and
take the Insomnia medicine
I'm sorry, but we can't get you the medicine
if you're not the person.
Yumeno-san
Your serving of sake made me drank too much,
but the pretended train was fun.
pretended train?
She is the number two Geisha in Shinbashi?
She has a surprisingly plain feel.
That's a bussiness that functions properly well
since that dinner party requires a lot of energy
to have such a calm reaction.. just like that..
There's anoother person, acutally
a Prof.Miyagawa's patient
Ok, Please ask them to enter.
How many hours do I have to wait!
Ouch!
Ah! can't be!
Dr.!
Eh!
Since being a psychiatrist is stressful
We need a reliable psychiatrist
To me, he is a man who is difficult to
replace with anybody else
Miyagawa.. Miyagawa's patient suddenly came in
and then with the desk..
Here, would you like?
No
What else?
Miyagawa also,
He tied me by the hands and feet.
I was imprisoned.
well, at least you survived
There's always someone who is such a natural enemy
I don't want to say it anymore,
my heart goes beating like crazy.
Things keep piling up
So, it's definitely useless to say it aloud.
If you say it, you'll remember the harassment
If you let that Prof. to glare at
your weak point, you're stress
will be bloated for many tens of times
You won't want to go over there
You'll become like me
You have and incredible persuasive power
ah senpai, this, I'm done with this.
The swelling is not cooled properly yet.
It hurts hurts hurts ....
Now, the cool just passed
and the pain is growing bigger.
I mean
the pain of this bruise
it's all that Miyagawa's fault.
Have a deep breath and exhale in one go
OK, inspire
now, exhale
inhale
there! Go
Miyagawa damn it!!
suckerfish~!!
Your voice, your face, the way you talk
even the papers you wrote
I really hate you!!
That's it, keep going!
Your sole presence I can't stand!!
Drop dead! you bastard~!
So, how you feel? Refreshing, right?
Yes
I think it's time for cold sake
for Executive Director Kimura
Yes
Koyume
Yes, Yumeno-neesan
Fight.
Yes
Yes, Lindbergh-san
Look, he probably has a large profit in swiss franc
What? It's Hinoharu Commercial
And that Lindbergh-san made a last-minute cancellation!
Hinoharu
Lindbergh
And though he was enthusiastic and
wanted to bring together that big negotiation
Yeah, yes yes yes, See ya
Ah Yumeno-chan, I'm going home now
Eh?
You're needed in the back of the parlor
by director Ennouji
Since the other day it was crowded
and we couldn't keep it calm
Today, I've come to monopolize Yumeno-chan
Ah well, I'm happy
Yes, this is Ennoji.
Yes I'll do it immediately.
I'm sorry, an urgent business just came up.
Eh?
Here, a congratulatory prize.
I really like Enn-sama
yes, the petals
Yes
Ah I'm sorry
Ah, then, I'm going ahead
Yes.
Do not run away
Where is my share of this month?
I heard it.
Recently, the director of the Keinan University Hospital,
has been expending a lot of money on you
With Such a fat client
you must come to great terms at once, right!
Teasing him, pulling the strings, tempting him,
you have to exploit that, right!
What is this??
This is not not enough at all.
That's it, from now on
we'll intrude on the director's room
to receive our part personally
Hey, maybe it's a good idea?
or can you do it? Akira-saaan
I can, since I'm Yumeno.
Then, excuse me.
Well then, since we are in a hurry, see you later.
The statistics show that suicide is the leading cause of death
from ages 15 to 34 and...
Because of the cherry-blossom the view is beautiful.
When asked whether they have seriously thought
on committing suicide, the percentage
that answer that the idea was there, is bigger
among those on the twenties.
Yumeno, quickly get ready, please.
When facing the suicide of the youth,
some people refuse to depend on others
and it will eventually become a matter
that will chase after the bereaved family.
until reaching the point of
denying the existence of the individual..
[T/N]: The lines that she wrote are partially erased,
so Hinoharu Lindbergh became Hino-rin
Hino..
Rin…｡
On that subject, the Dr. Hino Rintaro
the other day
seems to have helped a women
who tried to commit suicide
Oh, well .. yes, but ..
Now, in order to help a women
What kind of words
should be used to reach them?
I think the best way is to have a slow talk,
just the two of us.
Please looking at the camera, tell us about that.
Well.. that..
If there's something I want to talk to her,
then meeting her and talking directly,
I think that's the best.
Since we don't have people in school broadcasting
the talk between friends is important
The doctor that came here the other day
is recently coming out on TV really well.
Oh.. he's also a nice looking man, right?
Really.
Hino Rintaro ....
The word that we do not say enough is..
"Please do not work hard.", that's it.
Hi
Good morning.
Dr.
As long as the patient does not request it,
the contact outside the hospital is prohibited.
Look, she has been properly coming to work.
It is all right now.
It's because she has been properly coming
that I'm worry about.
Dr.
Dr.!
Thank you very much.
Welcome
Your bill will be 3024 yen.
Yes?
Yumeno? Where are you now?
I'm coming now.
Yumeno-san!
Yumeno-san
Are you okay?
Please hang on.
The customer wanted to drink a lot of sake
I can't walk anymore.
sake?
Yes.
Hino-rin.
Hino-rin?
May I call the Dr. like that?
Hino-rin, your chest is warm
I want to stay like this forever.
Yumeno-san
Why do I get such a lie?
When I first met you in the tatami room,
you just pretended to be drunk,
you also drop the drink
Also tonight ....
I
I fell in love with you, Dr.
Since having this client for our cherry blossom viewing
in such a vicinity
I found myself walking towards the hospital,
by all means I wanted to see you, Dr.
And then, when I saw your figure
I couldn't bear my feelings anymore..
I'm sorry
But..
Just now,
you were really worry about me, right?
Yumeno-san
Please, don't try too hard
I don't know the reasons,
but, you are trying really hard.
Am I wrong?
I've been alone for too long..
I really feel lonely..
Dr....
Will you fell with me?
Eh?
Dr.?
Ri..Rino-rin it's fine.
Can I meet you again?
why..
Why!
Why the Dr. hasn't come!
Just...a little longer.
Ah...!
Dr.?
Somei Medical School's acquisition maneuver
is progressing well.
Ennoji, that's you..what's it.
About the meeting for the necessary arrangements
with the Secretary of regulatory authorities ....
I want to drink hot tea!
Huh?
He just hung it.
Huh?..
Somei Medical University Hospital is available.
OK
No, No!
No, unless it's Dr. Hino, it's not god
He's your family doctor?
Please
Please, to the Dr. Hino's hospital..
He started hyperventilating during work
and then lost consciousness
lacerating her the left side of her head
Although consciousness has recovered
she seems to be excited.
Stop it!
It's ok, we'll disinfected it
No, not anymore!
We will proceed in line
Yes
It's OK
Don't touch me!
I've told you to call Dr. Hino!
It's ok, calm down.
It's not OK!
Stop it!
The Dr. has arrived
What happened? Mayuko-san
Dr.... I can't anymore.
Even though she was administrated 1
intravenous diazepam,
she's not calming down.
Should we try with the thiopental?
It's ok now, I won't let anyone else
to hurt you.
Dr.
Then, please.
Are you the person from Agawa Mayuko-san's company?
Yes
Could you please explain me in detail
the situation when she started hyperventilating?
I'm sorry,
but I wasn't at the same place.
Mayuko.
Mayuko
Mayuko..
Dr.
Just earlier we were contacted by
the manager from
Mayuko-san's company.
And?
It seems that there was bullying at her workplace.
Mayuko-san was capable at work and
had a strong sense of responsibility
More than anyone
she was good at providing a nice atmosphere
She was a popular person at work.
Because of her strength, six months ago,
the manager promoted her as the leader of a new project
And from that day,
Mayuko-san was isolated.
Purposely delaying the time of the meeting,
and informing the changes
by mail to everyone, except her.
And because this miss was not typical of her
for the next meetings
All her colleagues seem to have
criticize her at once.
"Even though,
we're seriously trying really hard,
the person that has been appointed as a leader
is not capable. It's a mistake.", they said.
By means of SNS,
malicious messages started to reach her.
Dr. Hino.
I've just talked to her mother.
It seems she wasn't aware of the hyperventilating event.
It seems that until reaching this state,
she used to be a cheerful person.
Can I touch you just a little?
Mayuko-san...
this wound is
the proof that you were trying really hard.
If I cut my wrist
I don't know what the people around me would say
Even though you knew perfectly,
that it was a wrong thing,
to do to yourself.
Yet, it's impossible to stop.
But Mayuko-san
This wound is
a testimony, that you had a hard time
and you had to desperately fight.
I wonder how he knew..
Someone,
Could you bring some ice?
Yes.
I'll go.
Dr. sorry, I'm coming through.
Is there anything else you need?
Thank you
OK
Even though I'm a doctor,
I am a person,
with the same feelings as you.
Mayuko-san,
the sorrow that you have been fighting,
it feels like this.
Dr....
It hurts.
When you slashed your wrist, it probably hurt, right?
Please feel the ice until it melts
in your own body temperature.
It hurts ...
So, keep feeling
Keep feeling, please
It hurts ...
Feel it a little longer
It hurts!
Feel it, please
Like this ice
The pain will go away without failing
And also, it will wound your heart ....
Please tell me, ...someone tell me
Why was I hated by everyone?
Did I do something wrong?
What was I hated for?
so.. I can fix it.
Dr., please tell me.
I want to fix what I did wrong
I'll try hard to fix it.
Why ..?
Why did they all hate me? Why?
Mayuko-san, please stop trying so hard.
Even if you look really hard for
your mistake
you won't find it.
Because originally,
such thing it's not there.
The colleagues that hurt you
were just unbearable jealous
of you, just that.
My favorite comedian
has a saying
"Jealousy always comes wearing clothes of justice"
Jealousy?
of someone like me?
Dr. Mizushima
It's the first time it turns out this way, right?
Yes.
He's a wonderful doctor.
Please, come again any time.
I'm your ally.
Dr.
Since that door is always open
Yes.
Professor,  did you see the cherry blossom?
I'm really busy right now.
If it is not tough the psychiatrist
won't be fit for the task
If there's no kindness,
they won't be able to save the wounded patient
I, by no means, will not be broken
I believed that
Can I meet you again?
She already came
Yumeno-san
Why?
Subs by Kitty-nyan