A FRITZ LANG FILM
THE 1 000 EYES OF DR. MABUSE
SCREENPLAY BY FRITZ LANG
AND HEINZ OSKAR WUTTIG
BASED ON AN IDEA
BY JAN FETHGE
EXECUTIVE PRODUCER
DIRECTED BY
HOMICIDE EMERGENCY SQUAD
Homicide squad,
Neuber speaking.
"Criminal Psychology"
For you, boss. Mr. Cornelius.
Oh, my gosh!
The clairvoyant character.
Get rid of him.
Think about it. He helped us solve
that prostitute murder case.
Inspector Kras.
This is Cornelius.
You may still be in time to prevent
something terrible from happening.
I had a vision.
And?
Two cars right next to each other
in the middle of traffic.
A street sign: " Hansaring."
I don't know the people involved,
I don't know the circumstances...
but I sense an impending disaster.
A crime.
Murder!
"Television Station"
Where on earth is Barter?
The broadcast begins
in 30 seconds.
He should be here any minute. He called
about 1 5 minutes ago, all excited.
- He has some big scoop.
- Broadcast time is still the same.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Silence in the studio!
In two seconds.
Ladies and gentlemen...
unfortunately we must cancel
our news report.
We just received the horrible news
that our reporter Peter Barter...
died on his way to the studio
behind the wheel of his car...
presumably of heart failure.
Doctor!
Mission accomplished.
Good. Change the license plate
on the car.
Remove the transmitter.
Have the car painted immediately
and disposed of in Holland.
Have you ever seen
the doctor?
What concern is that of yours?
Aren't you satisfied with your salary?
I'm just asking.
I'd like to know
what he looks like.
Then you might as well order
a coffin for yourself.
Do you remember
the American?
He too wanted to speak
to the doctor in person.
They found him
a few hours later.
His throat had been cut.
But I really want to know
what the doctor looks like.
That I don't know.
Don't expect me to explain
clairvoyance to you, Inspector.
Magic powers
defy rational thought.
I feel the disaster looming.
I see it as if in horrible daydreams.
I myself suffer terribly from it,
for I can't stop it...
because, like a dark cloud,
some hostile force of black magic...
obscures my view
at the decisive moment.
Thus leaving a little bit of work
for the police.
By the way, did you know
the reporter, this Barter?
About a year ago,
shortly after I settled here...
he visited me once or twice.
He was always looking
for the sensational...
and he was a skeptic, like you.
That's a professional proclivity,
my dear Cornelius.
Unfortunately, a policeman can't afford
to mess around with magical powers...
and I rarely have anything to do
with dark clouds.
lf, like me, you had grown up
in Ireland...
where people still believe
in the elementary powers of nature...
you might think differently.
But perhaps the blind see more
than those who have sight.
Possibly, but in the Barter case
this vision has failed you.
Maybe you were also thrown off
by your dark cloud.
This was no murder,
my dear Cornelius.
It was a simple heart attack.
For you, Inspector.
Take it to the lab right away!
I'll be back in an hour.
You were right.
The autopsy revealed that
Barter didn't die of a heart attack...
but of a steel needle
in his brain.
Material: the finest iridium steel.
Length: 1 .5 1 inches.
The steel needle smoothly penetrated
the victim's skull bone...
and entered the brain without leaving
any visible trace on the outside.
We're not going to find
anything here either.
"To my dearest Peter,
with much love...
on the occasion
of our first Christmas together.
Corinna."
His girlfriend.
Poor guy.
"TV Journal - Peter Barter"
Not a shred of paper left.
They even took the blotter.
- The audiotapes were also taken.
- Of course.
They were searching for evidence
of Barter's sensational scoop.
And if there was anything here,
I'm sure they found it.
You won't find any fingerprints.
These were no beginners.
All we have is
a small, deadly steel needle.
An incredible weapon, gentlemen.
An air gun that shoots steel needles
absolutely silently.
It's a new infantry weapon...
tested at Fort Benning
in the United States.
But here's something strange:
Before the weapon could go
into full-scale production...
the blueprints disappeared.
They were stolen.
U.S. military intelligence
found the thief--
a U.S. soldier in Germany--
in a deserted bunker
with his throat cut.
He had been gruesomely mutilated
and apparently tortured.
The blueprints were, of course,
nowhere to be found.
- When did this happen?
- About a year ago.
There's no doubt that it was this steel
needle gun that caused Barter's death.
I don't know.
This Barter murder case reminds me
of something that happened long ago.
Gentlemen...
does the name Dr. Mabuse
mean anything to you?
- Never heard of him.
- No.
A criminal genius.
He wanted to shock the world
with terrorist acts...
undermining governments...
and establishing
a fantastic reign of crime.
He ended up in an insane asylum,
where he wrote a kind of last will...
instructions for the crimes
he was planning.
In 1 932 he died, insane.
But if you talk
to old-time criminals...
they all say
that Dr. Mabuse isn't dead.
He can't die.
Cock-and-bull stories!
How could you even think of this--
What was the name again?
Dr. Mabuse.
In those days, I was a young assistant
on the homicide squad...
and we had a similar case there.
A man was shot behind the wheel
of his car from another vehicle.
The Barter case strikes me as
an exact copy of Dr. Mabuse's methods.
You said he was
no longer alive.
Well...
I have seen his dead body
with my own eyes, but--
Why haven't we heard anything
about this case?
The case never made
criminal history...
because Hitler appeared on the scene,
and the whole Nazi nightmare.
But there must be files
on the Mabuse case.
This is number eight.
Switch it on.
Decoding is active.
Write it down.
This is Dr. Mabuse speaking.
Four days ago...
the American Henry W. Taylor
arrived in town.
The British foreign office
just agreed.
Good.
- Gentlemen?
- We accept.
Just a question of principle:
When you take over the entire stock
holdings of Taran Nuclear Works...
is this happening under the auspices
of the United States...
or are you signing
as a private citizen?
In practice, it's irrelevant.
When I evaluate the secret models
of your rockets...
on my U.S. testing grounds...
I will be under government supervision
anyway.
And how do you envision
the financial transaction?
As soon as my lawyers
have examined the contract...
you will receive
the full amount by check.
The name Taylor is an alias.
Departments B and C are to follow
Taylor's each and every step...
and give a detailed report
every 1 2 hours.
Taylor is staying
in a luxury suite...
on the 14th floor
of the Luxor Hotel.
A radio message
from Inspector Kras.
"Before he was murdered
on his way to the TV studio...
the reporter Peter Barter
had been at the Luxor Hotel...
according to a statement
by the vehicle maintenance man."
Please call a short staff meeting
for 20 minutes from now.
In the meantime, I will notify
the president of Interpol.
We have been struggling
for a while...
with a series
of strange, unsolved crimes.
It all began two years ago.
On May 1 5, 1 958...
a passenger airplane crashed
at the Dutch airport of Schiphol...
following an act of sabotage.
The perpetrators
are still unknown.
Among the dead was
the French bank president Luchard.
His death caused a significant drop
on the Paris stock exchange.
During his trip to Germany...
Luchard had stayed
at the Luxor Hotel.
On November 2, 1958...
Mr. Delano, an attorney
for the steel corporation PCA...
was murdered in a sleeping car
on a train traveling from Oslo to Paris.
Two weeks before the murder...
Mr. Delano spent three evenings
in the casino of the Luxor Hotel.
On May 1 2, 1 959...
the Algerian-born arms dealer
Hussein fell victim to a bomb blast...
in his car shortly after crossing
the Belgian border.
Previously, Hussein had once met
with a well-known call girl...
at the Luxor Hotel.
And the list goes on.
Serious capital offenses,
murder, stock fraud, kidnapping.
Each case is different,
and each remains unsolved.
But they all have
one thing in common.
The victims in all these cases were
at some point guests at the Luxor Hotel.
That's why we have set up
one of our best special agents there.
His identity is known only...
to the chief of the Federal Crime Bureau
and myself...
to avoid any kind of leak
to subordinate organizations.
He has been staying at the Luxor
for some time now.
His sole mission is to find out
what's going on at the Luxor Hotel.
I can't watch this!
The firefighters should be
spreading out their sheet by now!
She's about to jump!
Come back inside!
Madam, please don't cause any trouble.
We don't want a scandal.
Should you have financial difficulties,
the hotel will help, of course.
Ladies and gentlemen, you can't possibly
enter here. Please be reasonable.
- After all, a human life is at stake.
- Our jobs are on the line!
Don't give us a hard time.
We need pictures.
I'm afraid that's impossible.
- Is it someone from the 14th floor?
- What's her name?
- I'm sorry.
- Menil is her name.
Marion Menil.
She is staying here at the hotel. I was
going to insure her only yesterday.
Sometimes you get lucky, huh?
Don't be alarmed.
Why would you want to do
something so futile...
from which there is no return?
You are young and your whole life
lies ahead of you.
It might just be wonderful.
Think it over.
You might not die right away.
You may suffer horrible pain
before it's all over.
Or you might survive-- as a cripple.
Think about it.
I'm scared. So very scared.
Give me your hand.
Trust me.
I'll hold on to you.
- She moved!
- He took her hand.
Thank God!
I wouldn't have enjoyed my dinner.
Drink this.
It'll do you good.
This is the hotel manager.
Open the door.
- Please don't let anybody in.
- No, no.
Open the door!
This is the police!
Please!
Perhaps you should go in the other room.
I'll talk to these people.
Come in, gentlemen--
just the two of you.
No, no, please.
Don't push, gentlemen.
- We want to see the woman.
- We've got a right to see her.
Please, don't cause trouble. Mr. Taylor
is a guest from the United States.
What did he say?
What's his name?
Nonsense! Wait, it's--
Of course. I've seen him
in the newspapers. He did look familiar.
Get to the office right away so your
picture makes the evening edition.
In the meantime, I'm going to file
my report by phone.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Who do you think
the noble rescuer is?
Mistelzweig.
Hieronymus B. Mistelzweig.
The " B" stands for "belly."
General insurance: life, accident,
baggage loss, health...
fire, hail, theft, and burglary.
Only lovesickness and a chronic shortage
of cash are excluded.
Well, if you insure that guy,
you can retire.
Why?
Is he that well-off?
Billions. Mr. Travers is one
of the richest men from overseas.
And a bachelor.
Mrs. Menil is apparently wealthy.
She owns fabulous jewelry
and expensive furs.
She flew here from Paris
five days ago.
But our house detective
may know more about her.
- Then please ask him to come here.
- With pleasure.
Are you sure the woman won't do
anything else foolish?
My secretary is with her.
Gentlemen, please visit the bar--
on the house, of course.
I promise I'll give you
all the information you need later.
Mrs. Menil has lived very quietly
in this establishment.
She most certainly does not belong
to the demimonde.
I suspect the whole thing
has to do with a telegram...
that she received
about three hours ago.
- Do you know what it said?
- No...
but according to the receptionist...
Mrs. Menil grew visibly nervous
while reading the telegram...
and she retired
to her room immediately.
Then I will question her
personally.
Above all, I must insist that the lady
leave the hotel at once.
- And I must insist--
- This won't work, gentlemen.
You can't save a person
from committing suicide...
only to leave her
to her own devices.
Give her time
to get over this shock.
Who will guarantee she won't
attempt suicide again?
I believe I can accept
that responsibility.
Perhaps Mr.--
What was the name again?
Berg.
- Mr. Berg can keep an eye on her.
- Of course.
The gentlemen are all gone.
For the moment,
no one is going to bother you.
If I can help you in any way--
No one can help me.
Why didn't you let me--
Everything would have been
over now.
Death is such a finite thing.
People often think they are facing
a catastrophe...
and despair descends
like a dark cloud.
In every situation
there is a way out.
Not for me.
Do you have financial worries?
Romantic troubles?
You trusted me when you were
standing out there on the ledge.
I should probably
be grateful to you.
But I'm not.
Do you have any family
I can notify?
I don't want to see anyone.
I want to go to my room.
I don't want you
to be alone now.
Yes, I understand.
Then please notify
my doctor, Dr.Jordan.
- Where is he? In the lobby?
- No, in the other room.
Forgive me. I was told that
Mrs. Menil was in your suite.
Sister Agnes heard a radio broadcast at
my clinic about this terrible incident.
Mrs. Menil is my patient.
May I see her?
I was just about
to send for you.
Marion!
How could you do such a thing?
You've got to pull yourself together.
I'm going to take you to your room
and give you a little shot...
and then you'll have
a nice sleep.
I'll leave you
in Sister Agnes's care overnight.
She's a familiar face, right?
Please don't think
I'm ungrateful, but--
I think complete rest
is the best remedy now.
If you don't mind, I will take
the lady to her room now.
Professor, is Mrs. Menil
permanently in your care?
No, absolutely not.
But she had a nervous breakdown
once before, about a year ago.
She was a patient at my clinic
for almost two months.
And she's got no husband,
no boyfriend?
As a doctor, I can't make statements
about Mrs. Menil's private life.
Certainly. But I am of course interested
in this woman's situation now.
She is a very lonely person,
very guarded.
It's not easy to win her trust.
You--
You must exert
a strong influence on her.
I mean, on her subconscious...
in that you succeeded
in saving her from suicide.
I'm somewhat surprised...
but very happy about it.
Good-bye now.
" Multimillionaire Thwarts Suicide
at Luxor Hotel"
Not exactly a pleasant advertisement
for our hotel.
- Good evening, Inspector. The usual?
- Yes, the usual.
A lot of action around here.
Are your rates so high that your guests
must jump out the window?
It may be a joke to you, Inspector,
but unfortunately the joke is on me...
as if I were everybody's baby-sitter.
These disgusting reporters.
May they go to hell.
Yes, these reporters
with their scribbling--
To think what my friend Barter
would have done with a thing like this.
Oh, well. Since his death
I haven't been watching TV anymore.
Was he the one who died
of a heart attack in his car?
Yes. A great guy, Inspector.
Generous in every way.
- Mr. Berg?
- Yes.
Mr. Travers' secretary would like
to speak to you on the phone.
Excuse me for a moment, please.
Did you know this Barter well?
He always asked me for tips
on special guests.
Especially the female ones,
I bet.
You will laugh, Inspector, but I had
pointed out Mrs. Menil to Mr. Barter.
Actually, it was
the day she arrived.
She sat over there, while Barter
drank his whiskey over there.
Things must have worked out...
because a little later
they went upstairs together.
Interesting.
Would you kindly let Mrs. Menil
know that I'd like to see her?
I'm afraid that's impossible.
She just took a sleeping pill.
- Is she asleep yet?
- No, but--
- Then I'd like to see her.
- Can't it wait until tomorrow?
Unfortunately, it can't.
My name is Kras.
Inspector Kras.
A man by the name of Inspector Kras
insists he must see you.
Is this necessary?
Why do people torture me so?
Please...
but take the lady's health
into consideration.
Please forgive the late visit,
but I'm afraid it's quite urgent.
Please make it quick.
I feel faint.
Do you remember a man
by the name of Barter?
Barter? No.
A TV reporter.
This is the first time
I've heard his name.
Perhaps this will refresh
your memory.
Oh, that guy!
Yes, I know him.
He introduced himself
downstairs in the bar.
I hadn't quite caught his name.
He wanted an interview.
I refused. After all,
I'm not some movie star.
He was awfully pushy.
And yet you brought him upstairs
to your room.
I didn't want to make
a scene in the bar.
I brought him here upstairs,
but he got quite aggressive.
It got so bad that I had to ask him
to stop bothering me.
He's not going to bother you
anymore.
Shortly after visiting you,
Mr. Barter...
died.
But that's awful!
And when a person wants to die,
they won't let her!
" Return immediately or you must bear
the consequences of your actions.
I have proof
of your guilt."
Mrs. Menil, three hours after receiving
this telegram from Paris...
you attempted suicide.
How did you get
that telegram?
My personal life
is nobody's business.
When the police are interested
in something, there is no personal life.
Why are you torturing me
like this?
Leave me alone!
That's enough.
Can't you see?
But I must talk to you again
about Barter.
I received
a very strange phone call.
For the time being,
please don't leave town.
Good night.
" H. B. Mistelzweig
Insurance"
Tough times, tough business.
Mars has entered the house of death
of too many people.
- Who has entered what?
- Mars is in the house of death.
As a modern businessman, I work
solely on the basis of astrology.
There is no point in insuring people
if you know that they won't live long.
Imagine if I had insured
your friend Barter.
He looked as chipper
as life itself.
He would have just paid
his first premium, and then-- wham!
A heart attack!
What an awful loss that would have been.
No, no. One must look at the stars
of these insurance candidates.
- Very interesting.
- What do you mean?
- Did you have Barter's horoscope?
- This is Inspector Kras.
Please, allow me:
Hieronymus B. Mistelzweig.
" B" stands for "belly."
General insurance:
Life, accident, baggage loss...
health, fire, hail, theft, burglary.
Only lovesickness and a chronic shortage
of cash are excluded.
Impressive.
What companies do you work for?
Lloyd's of London,
Assurance la Paix Paris...
Seguros de Madrid,
Kontor Hamburg National and Overseas.
Mistelzweig has
worldwide connections.
A lucrative business, isn't it?
One doesn't talk about that.
One gets by.
Allow me, gentlemen.
Another round.
A little schnapps with your beer
can't hurt, Inspector.
Besides, it's all tax-deductible.
Karl, one more.
The hotel engineer is,
of course, included.
I'm sorry, Mr. Mistelzweig.
Perhaps later, though.
The freezer for the kitchen
downstairs is on the blink.
Most likely it's a short. Do you have
the key to the machine room?
No, but there must be
a spare downstairs.
I can't find it.
Please come with me.
Go ahead and pour my drink.
I'll be right back.
Do you have an office
here at the hotel?
My office? No, no.
My office is here--
in my head.
I do my business at the Luxor...
but I wouldn't take a permanent office
here if they gave it to me for free.
What don't you like
about the hotel?
Just between you and me:
It's not under a lucky star...
like anything the Nazis started
near the end of the war.
What does that have to do
with the Luxor?
People aren't the only ones influenced
by the constellations upon their birth.
- A building is too.
- Come on now!
- A building isn't born!
- Oh, yes, it is, Inspector.
The placement of its cornerstone
is its birth hour...
and the cornerstone for the Luxor
was laid by the Nazis in May '44...
when they still believed
in final victory.
The bigwigs in the SS wanted
to build a few grand hotels...
for politicians and diplomats...
all in one huge cluster,
so they could spy on everybody.
No, the Luxor has a negative aura.
But your business is thriving here
nevertheless.
Well, in a hotel like this there are
always people with a lot of money.
There's jewelry or baggage to insure,
or travel insurance to write.
My wife has always wanted me
to buy life insurance.
It all depends on the stars,
Inspector.
It's all in the stars.
Considering your profession...
you could be dead tomorrow,
right?
I mean, since you're always
in dangerous situations.
Criminals never sleep,
do they?
But perhaps we could
work something out.
Call me at the office
in the morning.
It's pretty quiet there
these days.
I'd also like to talk
about Mr. Barter.
He wanted insurance too.
I received
a very strange phone call.
To your health,
Mr. Mistelzweig.
Cheers, Inspector.
- It was nice to meet you.
- The pleasure was all mine.
I'll be sure to call you.
No harm done...
but if you could take me to the other
side, I'd appreciate that very much.
May I give you
a lift somewhere?
That's very kind of you.
If you can find room
for my dog too--
Of course.
In Ireland we also have
this cold, wet weather.
I can feel it on my skin
like damp wool.
I don't know.
Careful!
Don't take the turn so fast!
Danger!
Damn! That was close.
- Thanks for the warning.
- How did you know that?
Sometimes I can see
things coming.
You don't believe me.
This morning at the hotel...
you dropped a glass
while brushing your teeth.
In picking up the shards, you cut
the middle finger of your right hand.
But that's--
No one was there to see it
when it happened.
This morning, around 1 1:00...
you signed a check
drawn on an English bank...
but the business transaction
you're planning will not materialize.
The part about the check is true too,
but how do you know the rest?
I told you before:
Sometimes I can see things coming.
If you can predict
future events...
how come you didn't see that
we would almost run you over?
The hour of my death
has not yet come.
- Who are you?
- My name is Cornelius.
Good evening...
Inspector.
Why did you turn on the light?
So that you may see better,
Inspector.
I could have been a burglar.
No, my dog growled and barked.
This means that there's someone
in the room whom he knows.
He would have behaved differently
with a stranger.
And then...
I also smelled
your pipe tobacco.
The odor clings
to your clothing.
Then I knew it was you
waiting for me in the dark.
The blind have keener senses
than people who see.
But how did you get in?
My attendant has the night off.
I was so bold as to let myself in,
Mr. Cornelius.
Please accept my apologies,
but I must talk to you.
There's a new twist
in the Barter case.
Did they find something
in his car?
No.
In his head.
A small, unfriendly thing
Let me be frank,
Mr. Cornelius.
I'm not making much progress
in this matter.
You know I'm a skeptic...
but when you're stuck,
beggars can't be choosers.
If you concentrate
on this object...
what do you see...
that might help me?
A man.
His face is a blur.
Now, nothing!
The cloud again.
The dark cloud.
It covers everything.
It's stronger than I am.
It threatens me personally.
I can feel it.
That's why I would be
grateful to you...
if you kept me informed
about the Barter case.
We have maintained absolute silence
with the press...
regarding the fact that Barter
met a violent death.
Nevertheless, this afternoon I received
a very strange phone call.
A man was willing...
in exchange for immunity
from prosecution and a reward...
to give me information
about this steel needle.
We immediately determined the call
originated from a public phone.
But the guy
was much too smart.
When the patrol car arrived,
he was long gone.
But before he hung up,
he said I should think about it.
He would call me again
tomorrow.
What are we doing here?
The bunker
where they found the American.
You know, the American!
- And why are we here?
- To make a phone call.
- You're so fond of making phone calls.
- Me? What do you mean?
You know. I warned you.
- The doctor doesn't like it.
- What doesn't he like?
- That you make phone calls.
- But I didn't--
I didn't!
- Good morning, Inspector.
- Morning.
It got pretty late last night.
Any news?
Nothing at all.
Everything was quiet.
The telephone didn't work,
but it's been fixed.
- A man from the phone company--
- Don't pick up!
I'd be willing
to purchase it.
Would you accept
45,000 marks?
- But it's worth much more!
- Let's say 50,000.
- All right.
- Would you like a check or cash?
Cash. I may need to leave today,
and the banks are already closed.
Nexit.
You were lucky, Inspector.
If it weren't for that cabinet,
you'd be dead as a rat now.
It would serve me right.
His wife is expecting
their first child.
You slowly get used to the fact that
people bite the dust in our profession.
It's all business as usual.
And it's my fault.
Your fault? Why?
Yesterday I set out
three pieces of bait...
but the response
came faster than I expected.
But from whom?
The psychic?
The insurance agent?
Or the woman?
Why aren't you honest
with me?
I don't know
what you mean.
You sold this piece
of jewelry today.
- You had me followed?
- I feel responsible for you.
You booked flights today
with four different airlines...
for four consecutive dates...
to four different cities...
under four different names...
none of them your real one.
- Why?
- Please, don't ask!
What is threatening you,
Marion?
What were you so afraid of
that you wanted to end your life?
Please don't ask.
Please, please, don't ask!
I don't want to cause you pain, Marion,
but why don't you let me help you?
I don't want to owe
anybody anything.
- I won't accept any money from you.
- Then at least take this back.
I know what it means to a woman
to give up her jewelry.
Then I have no other choice
but to keep it.
Perhaps chance will unite us
once again.
In the meantime,
this piece will remind me of you.
My plane is leaving tomorrow.
Tomorrow, already?
Will you do me a big favor
before we part?
If I can, gladly, of course.
Then spend our last evening
with me.
You must distract yourself
to regain your zest for life.
You need to get out
and see happy people.
You need to hear laughter
and music.
To the next lucky coincidence
that will bring us together.
Everyday worries and concerns
must be checked in with your coat.
All right.
To the next lucky coincidence.
Terrific music, isn't it?
It gets in your blood.
I'm a Scorpio.
They burn with passion.
What are you, madam?
A Libra?
No, I'm a Sagittarius.
Straight to the heart!
- Would you like to dance?
- Oh, yes!
Do you like to dance?
I used to love to dance,
a long time ago.
You know, I believe you are
a cheerful person by nature.
I used to be
very happy and cheerful.
- I loved to laugh.
- Why don't you try it again?
See? Much better.
Come and dance with me.
Wasn't I right to drag you out
of your end-of-the-world mood?
Yes, perhaps.
You dance beautifully.
See? You are
a different person now.
Marion, come to Paris
with me tomorrow.
To Paris?
I can't go to Paris.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not a prude.
I would love to do it.
But I can't leave now.
Why not?
I'm not free.
I'm married.
Do you love your husband?
I hate him.
When the lady
who just stepped out returns...
please tell her
I'll be right back.
He carries a gun
in a shoulder holster.
- Are you sure?
- Absolutely.
I'm all black and blue
from pressing against it.
Have you never considered
divorce?
Yes, often, but my husband
will never let me go.
Money can overcome
many obstacles.
Not in my case.
Money can't help me.
But let's not talk about me.
Tell me about yourself,
about your life.
It's not very interesting.
Business, conferences.
-And women?
- Yes.
But only in passing.
You know, when someone lives
for his work as much as I do--
board meetings, staff meetings,
business meetings--
I practically live in planes
and conference halls.
There's only room
for brief pleasures...
and not much more.
- That's very sad.
- One can't have everything.
Mr. Travers? Excuse me.
We just received this.
- What about the check?
- The lawyers still have it.
- Cancel it right away.
- Yes, sir.
You see?
You can't relax either.
A few minutes ago,
when we were dancing...
I believed that I could
run away from myself.
But I can't.
No one can.
We've all got to follow
our path.
No, I would only bring you
bad luck.
If only all this had happened
three years ago, fine.
But now it's only self-deception.
I'm sorry to spoil
this lovely evening for you.
Please forgive me and forget me.
It's better that way.
Do you really want me
to forget you?
Yes.
"Radio London announces
nuclear power plant...
run by the Taran Plutonium
Corporation was blown up today.
Plant completely destroyed by fire.
Many casualties.
Population within 1 0-mile radius
evacuated for safety reasons."
The catastrophe itself
I did not foresee.
I only felt there was a dark shadow
hovering over your plans.
First, the broken glass
in the bathroom...
then the truck
we nearly collided with...
and now this
Taran Corporation matter.
What's the rational explanation
for all this?
F ate allowed me
to cross your path.
Perhaps I'm to protect you
from future harm.
The explosion in the Taran plant
is hardly harmful to me.
A business transaction
that didn't materialize.
That's all.
I mean your personal life.
Although I'm blind,
light that's too bright is bothersome.
It scatters your thoughts.
You must now focus on me.
You should go away.
Leave this town.
Something has crossed
your path...
and a dark cloud
hangs over you.
I see a figure.
It's very blurred.
An animal.
And a woman?
Perhaps.
I can't quite penetrate
the darkness.
But one thing I do see.
You saved a life...
and it is precisely this life
that threatens you with danger...
and death.
She can't just be making up the fact
she reserved four airplane tickets...
even if she did it
under false names.
I don't get it.
Take a note:
Interpol inquiry.
Does this insurance agent Mistelzweig
really work for Lloyd's of London...
and Assurance la Paix Paris
and all the other companies?
Inspector, Mrs. Menil just canceled
all four flight reservations.
Interesting.
She goes out
with the American...
and the next morning
she cancels her flights.
Yet she didn't look too happy
when she went upstairs.
Interesting.
I have something else for you.
Get hold of this Cornelius character's
latest tax return. Be discreet about it.
Hello, Mr. Cornelius?
This is Kras.
No. No news, really.
Did the man who wanted to give you
the confidential information call you?
He couldn't call me,
Mr. Cornelius.
You see, my phone
exploded yesterday.
A little assassination attempt
against me.
A man from the phone company
supposedly repaired it earlier.
What did the man look like?
Can you please describe him for me?
The only person who could do that
is my assistant...
but, unfortunately, he's dead.
Why didn't you warn me
before it happened?
What is that supposed to mean?
Are you saying you wanted me
to predict your death? You're alive!
- But in the Barter case you did!
- Well, he's truly dead.
Inspector, I sense your mistrust.
You are skeptical.
That's why I would like
to convince you.
Please attend a telepathic sance
at my house tonight.
Choose for yourself
the people you want to witness it.
Bring whomever you wish.
Do you really believe
in this humbug?
Michael, you know I'm a skeptical man.
Always have been.
Now, for the first time
in my life...
I wish I were able
to believe in someone.
The psychic or the woman?
You should know me better,
Michael.
I do what I think is right.
No psychic can change that.
- So you are staying here?
- Yes. You fly to London alone today.
Get information on all the repercussions
of the catastrophe...
especially whether the secret plans
for the rockets were saved.
And something else, Michael.
This you can do right away.
Pick out fifty roses
in the flower shop downstairs...
and have them sent to Mrs. Menil,
with this note.
Certainly.
Excuse me, Mr. Travers.
May I perhaps have a word
with you in private?
What is this about?
It's about Mrs. Menil.
It's not my custom to intrude
in the private affairs of our guests...
but I know you are interested
in anything that concerns Mrs. Menil.
Our access to her
for surveillance purposes...
is unfortunately very restricted.
She spends most of the day
in her suite.
She speaks on the phone a great deal
and receives visitors too.
But I may be able
to reveal something...
of great interest to you.
How much do you want?
That's entirely up to you,
of course.
But it must be absolutely confidential.
I could lose my job.
Well, then?
Forgive me, but it's something
that I can only show you...
if I may trouble you
to come with me.
It won't take long.
It's right here.
This suite is adjacent to the rooms
occupied by Mrs. Menil.
This room was once occupied
by a very jealous husband...
whose wife was staying
right next door.
He was never sure whether
she was faithful to him or not...
so I helped him out
with this little setup.
One fine day,
he caught her in the act.
Here you can see and hear everything,
but from the other side, you can't.
I'm going to turn on
the loudspeaker.
Unbelievable, no? On the other side,
it's just a normal mirror.
Please help me get dressed.
Please see who it is.
These roses are for the lady.
Beautiful roses.
I'll get a vase right away.
Well, did I promise
too much, Mr. Travers?
Turn it off! It's despicable
to eavesdrop on people like that.
Turn it off!
Don't worry, Mr. Berg.
I will pay you for this secret.
So that no one else may misuse it,
reserve this suite for me.
Tell the receptionist that it's for some
business partners I'm expecting.
Of course, Mr. Travers.
Yes?
May I remind you that
we still have an appointment?
I would like you to attend
a telepathic sance with me.
Yes, ma'am.
With a psychic, at 8:30 p.m.
I would very much appreciate
seeing you there.
Hello, Inspector. Is this a bad time?
Shall l--
Don't leave the hotel.
I'll call you later.
Is this place all right?
It looks so-- so dilapidated.
You were right the other day,
Mr. Mistelzweig.
Someone planned to dispatch me
to heaven.
- Maybe I should--
- No, no, no.
You couldn't have come
at a better time. Have a seat.
You are interested in astrology
and such, aren't you?
Yes, as a business principle.
You know--
- Is this your wife?
- Yes, yes.
Would you like to attend
an interesting sance with a psychic?
I'm flattered! When?
Tonight at 8:30.
Perhaps we can talk business too.
I'll bring my wife.
May I introduce my wife?
Mr. Cornelius.
Very pleased to meet you,
madam.
This is my assistant, Mr. Kaiser,
and Mr. Mistelzweig.
Hieronymus B. Mistelzweig.
The " B" stands for "belly."
He's very much interested
in the occult, especially astrology.
Only in a very amateurish way.
I'm an absolute dilettante.
But, in fact, today the sun is
in conjunction with Neptune.
That means water,
so we're due for a thunderstorm.
I should have brought
an umbrella, right?
That's a splendid animal
you've got there.
Come on, doggie.
Uncle has got something for you.
Quiet, Ferro. Be quiet.
He's not interested.
He won't take anything from a stranger.
This is Mr. Cornelius,
my wife...
Mr. Kaiser, and you already know
Mr. Mistelzweig.
- I hope I'm not late.
- Not at all, madam.
Please, let's all take a seat.
It's very informal.
Please...
concentrate on me now.
I'm having difficulty
concentrating.
Something is interfering
with me.
It's not the thunderstorm.
- Inspector.
- Yes?
Would you mind
if we traded places?
Not at all.
- Excuse me!
- No problem.
I hope my cigars
survived intact.
I suspected as much:
Saturn in the 11th house--
a small accident among friends.
Excuse me.
Let us begin.
Someone among us has come here
with the intent to deceive.
I see a woman's hand
and a ring.
A ring that doesn't belong
on that hand.
A tragic fate tore from this woman
the man she loved.
A dark cloud
hangs over the man.
The image is blurring.
A car, with the man
at the wheel.
He is dead.
Peter Barter.
One person here saw him
before he died...
and one person here
will avenge his death.
It won't be an easy task.
The dark cloud
is all-powerful.
It gathers and approaches...
ever closer!
No, it's not a cloud.
It's a face.
The face of a dead man.
No, he's alive.
Mabuse. Dr. Mabuse.
Now it's gone.
The dark cloud has returned.
Close, very close.
It is here!
It is hanging over--
Kras!
Get away from the window!
Turn the lights off!
The shot came from either
the roof or the attic of that house.
Kaiser, maybe we can still
catch the guy!
I'm not staying here
any longer.
Would you please take me
back to the hotel?
Please don't leave me
here alone.
The danger has passed.
I regret this turn of events.
Perhaps some refreshments
will help you recover from the shock.
Mr. Cornelius...
I admire your psychic gift.
Really, it was fabulous!
Amazing!
By the way, what was that strange name
you mentioned?
I don't remember.
I have no control in this state.
It doesn't really matter.
By the way--
just between you and me--
does this Inspector Kras
have a chance of living much longer?
I'm not omniscient,
Mr. Mistelzweig.
Well, he wants to buy
life insurance from me...
and I would appreciate
certain tips.
I don't do business
with the lives of other people.
Of course not.
Please forgive me.
It was just a thought.
By the way, did you notice
that the shot rang out...
just as your grandfather clock
struck for the first time.
- Is it accurate?
- I would assume it is.
No, the clock is exactly
one minute fast.
Here, you see?
Please forgive me.
I forgot.
You are blind.
But don't you think
that this delay of one minute...
may have saved
the inspector's life?
Well, Inspector?
What did you find?
Nothing.
My assistant is still looking
for clues...
but the man is long gone,
of course.
Cornelius, I haven't had a chance
to thank you.
But for your warning,
I would be dead now.
The bullet hit the chair
exactly in the spot...
where my head had been.
Strange.
This is the second assassination attempt
directed at me in the last 48 hours.
You are mistaken, Inspector.
Why is that?
You forget that I had been sitting
in that chair earlier.
This murder attempt
was directed at me.
I loved your roses
so very much.
- How did you get--
- I felt so alone in my room.
Perhaps it's childish, but I'm always
so scared of thunderstorms.
I hope you don't mind
that I simply came by.
- Your door was open.
- Please, come in.
Am I really the reason
you extended your stay?
I wanted to ask you one more thing
before I dive back into my work.
Yes?
Do you prefer
whiskey or cognac?
Whiskey, please.
Straight up.
- Was that the question?
- No.
- Cheers.
And the question?
If you were available,
would you marry me?
I want to tell you
the truth now, Henry.
The whole truth.
In reality,
my marriage is sheer hell.
My husband has always been driven
by an almost pathological jealousy.
He has a physical disability.
It's just a problem with his foot.
It never bothered me.
But it seems to be
the main reason for his jealousy.
He is convinced
that I'm cheating on him.
Sometimes he would beat me
to extract a confession...
but there was nothing
to confess.
That's grounds for divorce!
I have often suggested
separation to him. Very often.
He said he would rather kill me
than set me free.
Last year, I simply ran away.
I was a nervous wreck.
That's when I ended up
at Dr. Jordan's clinic.
An old friend of our family.
When I recovered somewhat,
my husband took me back home...
and the torture, threats and abuse
began all over again.
Ten days ago,
I completely lost control.
I didn't care about anything.
I obtained some poison
and intended to kill him...
but he found out
and nearly beat me to death.
I didn't know what to do,
so I ran away again.
Just to get away from him.
That's how I ended up at the Luxor.
But he tracked me down again.
He sent a telegram saying
if I didn't return immediately...
he would report me.
So that's the story
behind it all.
I saw no other way out
but to kill myself.
So now you know
the whole story.
Do you still want
to marry me...
a woman who tried
to poison her husband?
Is Mrs. Menil there, Mr. Travers?
There's no answer in her room.
It's for you.
Professor Jordan.
The professor?
Yes? This is Marion.
What? When?
Oh, my God!
Ten minutes ago?
You'll stay at the clinic.
Yes, okay. Thank you.
What's going on?
My husband is on his way
to the hotel.
He'll be here any minute.
He mustn't find me in your room.
Stay here.
You are safe with me.
I can't drag you into this.
You don't know Roberto.
Please let me go!
If I don't call you in half an hour,
come to my room.
- Is it still raining?
- I'll call a bellboy--
No, thanks.
I'll take care of it myself.
What is it?
I've already gone to bed.
Open the door
if you don't want a scandal.
Come back tomorrow.
If you don't open up,
I'll kick in the door.
That's it, darling.
Why resist?
I'm sorry
if my sudden appearance...
rattles your tender nerves.
A woman who loves her husband
should welcome him more joyfully.
More tenderly.
What do you want from me?
I'm not sure yet myself.
We'll see.
It was quite stupid of you
to run away again...
and to believe
I wouldn't find you.
Just as stupid as your attempt
to poison me.
You thought no one would miss me
if you succeeded.
Now, one word from me
and you'll land in jail.
But this time you won't
get off the hook so easily.
Beautiful roses.
From him, right?
Since your dramatic
suicide attempt...
you've been
in all the newspapers...
you and your new lover.
You must be grateful
to your savior.
That's best expressed...
with a few tender caresses,
right?
You animal!
There!
Does this pain your little heart?
You love him, don't you?
Yes, I love him!
I love him as much as I hate you.
You hear me?
I don't regret for a second
that I wanted to kill you.
You're not human.
You're a beast!
No so fast, my sweetheart.
Not so fast.
Let's see if the gentleman
from America...
will still want you in bed
with your face cut up.
Shoot him!
- How did you get in here?
- Through the mirror.
The detective--
I'll explain everything.
Do you think anyone
heard the shooting?
Wait.
- There's nobody outside.
- I'm going to call Dr.Jordan.
He must come right away.
Perhaps he can still save Roberto.
This is Marion, Professor.
Please come over right away.
Something terrible
has happened.
Perhaps you can still help him.
Thank you.
He's on his way.
- Where is my cognac?
- Here. I didn't know if you'd be back.
An insurance agent
always comes back.
It's raining cats and dogs.
You wouldn't kick a dog out
in this weather.
Dr.Jordan.
Thank God you're here.
- I shot him.
- I must tell you, Professor--
Believe me,
it was self-defense.
The knife is still lying there
on the ground.
He's dead.
I didn't mean to kill him!
Please help me, Professor.
You've got to help me
out of this mess!
Please, Marion, calm down.
Let me think.
Professor, I'm partially
to blame--
I too am to blame,
Mr. Travers.
I knew how dangerous
this man was.
Perhaps if I had come
right away--
The most important thing now is that
the police don't find out about this.
I had the ambulance park on a side
street, to avoid drawing attention.
If we could just get the corpse
out of the hotel--
A massive heart attack must be treated
in the hospital immediately.
Later, I could fill out the death
certificate to read "heart attack."
But how do we get him
out of the hotel?
The hotel detective will do anything
for money. Besides, he owes me one.
And now it's time to go sleep
in my empty bed.
Would you have an extra raincoat?
I forgot mine.
I have an old one over there.
I'll get it for you.
- Here. Will this do?
- Yes, thank you.
- I'll bring it back tomorrow.
- That's okay.
- Good night.
- Good night, Mr. Mistelzweig.
It's just a minor heart attack,
madam.
Please don't be alarmed.
A few days of rest in my clinic
and he'll recover.
Initially he will need
to take it easy, of course.
Nothing upsetting.
No business.
He'll need to put himself
first now.
$5,000 in cash if you help us,
Mr. Berg.
We don't want any commotion
in the newspapers.
Naturally, Mr. Travers.
It's not in the interest
of the hotel...
to create a stir
in case of sudden illness.
How can we get Mr. Menil
to the ambulance without being seen?
That's easy.
We use the freight elevator.
And the broken mirror?
I'll have that fixed within the hour.
I'll wake up the maintenance man.
He lives in the hotel.
He's my closest friend.
No sirens, no flashing lights.
We don't want any attention.
I'll follow in the car.
I've known Professor Jordan
since I was a child.
I knew he would do
anything for me.
But if we had said
that you fired the gun--
To think that I'm hiding
behind a woman--
I always took responsibility
for my actions.
If he hadn't been so quick,
I would have fired the shots.
But isn't this all beside the point?
You saved my life for the second time.
Even so.
Two hours ago, in this room...
you asked me whether
I would marry you if I were free.
And now I am free.
This worked out fine once again,
just as the doctor predicted.
Precisely.
No!
What? What is it?
Patrol car 8
has detected a fire...
on the top floor
of a bombed-out house.
There's a dead body
in one of the rooms.
You wake me up for that?
Franke is on night duty now.
Let me sleep.
What's that?
A secret transmitter?
Police files on Dr. Mabuse?
Strange place. No sign on the door.
Nothing.
When we saw the fire
from the street...
my partner said,
" No one lives there."
Then we found the body.
Shot in the chest, apparently
straight through the heart.
First they killed him, and then
they tried to burn the place down.
We pulled down the curtains
and doused the sofa with water.
We were able
to stomp out the rest.
- Any ID? Any papers?
- Nothing.
Nice of you
to make time for me...
so early in the morning,
Mr. Cornelius.
I was in the neighborhood
and thought I'd just drop by.
Isn't the little doggie
here today?
A routine checkup at the veterinarian.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
What can I do for you,
Mr. Mistelzweig?
Well, I thought, " Maybe you can
do business with Mr. Cornelius."
With me? Business?
Don't worry.
I don't want to insure you.
I just want--
- Mind if I smoke?
- Please.
I know it's
a bad habit of mine, but--
Did I startle you?
I unseated you, so to speak,
in this charade.
You know, this blind-man ploy
is really great.
Yes, really.
When you take off the sunglasses
and stare into the distance--
Very attractive.
Really stylish.
And the contact lenses--
like in an American horror film.
Come now!
Don't do anything stupid.
The phone is going to ring soon.
A friend of mine.
I took the liberty of giving him
your phone number...
just as a precaution
so that nothing happens.
What do you want from me?
I want to go into business with you.
Fifty-fifty.
During the sance the day before
yesterday, I had this idea.
You know, people are so scared
when it comes to insurance.
If you, with your clairvoyance,
advise them to protect their families...
then they'll all come running
to me, you see?
That's him.
Yes, I'm still here.
No, not much longer.
A few more minutes.
I'll be in touch, yes.
No police-- don't worry.
By the way,
this Kras character--
Didn't you wonder why he would
drag me to your sance?
He wants to keep an eye on me.
I've done time.
Five years.
Insurance fraud.
I've learned a lot since then.
And the two of us will come out
on top of that Kras guy, right?
Think it over, Cornelius.
Fifty-fifty.
The projectile that hit
the psychic's chair...
and the bullet in the corpse...
are of the same caliber
and have the same rifling marks.
They clearly come
from the same gun.
Very interesting.
Thank you very much.
- Any word from Mistelzweig?
- No, he was asked to come at 1 1:00 p.m.
But Interpol's answer
just came in.
Mistelzweig, Hieronymus Balthazar.
Insurance agent
with many years of experience.
Best references from Lloyd's of London.
No prior convictions.
I still don't like his mug.
The embodiment of promptness,
right?
What happened
to your right hand?
A small scuffle
ending in death, perhaps?
Inspector!
A peace-loving man like me?
- Have you ever been bitten by a dog?
- No.
Good for you. It hurts terribly,
let me tell you.
Last night I was going home
when a huge dog jumped at me...
and wouldn't let go.
And this should happen to me,
a real dog lover!
You left me a message, Inspector.
You wanted to talk to me.
Was it because of
the sance last night?
No.
But I want
to show you something.
Well, that's life.
"Yesterday on a steed abreast,
today a bullet in the chest."
- How did you know that?
- What?
That the man was shot in the heart.
You couldn't see that.
Inspector, I was just quoting
an old song...
and right away
you're suspicious again.
Shot through the heart.
Awful.
One moment a man is running around
alive and well...
and twelve hours later
he's dead.
- Stone-dead.
- So you know him then.
That would be pushing it.
I saw him last night at the Luxor.
I noticed him because of his clubfoot.
He has one, doesn't he?
Just what I thought.
He went up to the third floor
where Mrs. Menil is staying.
By the way, it's strange.
Did you know that she checked out?
She's leaving
with the American today.
Let's say good-bye to the professor
and then we'll go.
What's the number?
4-2-5...
5-2-7.
Say...
last night when you called him,
you only dialed three digits.
- Three?
- Yes.
You must be mistaken.
I've known Jordan's number for years.
It's 425-527.
And there's something else.
How could the professor get here
so quickly last night...
just five minutes
after your call...
and with an ambulance?
For God's sake, don't say anything now.
They can hear and see everything.
- Who can hear and see everything?
- Later, later!
We must leave this hotel as soon
as possible, or it's all over!
What are you talking about?
What are you afraid of?
There! Look!
And there are more over there!
And over there!
Everywhere in this hotel.
In the bar, in every room,
in the nightclub.
They can observe everything.
- We must leave immediately.
- But--
Please!
Please believe me!
Listen, Henry. I lied to you.
I was lying the whole time!
But now you have to believe me,
just this once.
- Please! Before it's too late.
- Why?
For God's sake, don't ask
any more questions now.
Come on, before it's too late.
Come on!
Twelve...
eleven...
ten, nine.
I'd like to know if Mrs. Menil
is still staying at the hotel...
or if she and Mr. Travers
have already left.
They must still be here,
probably in Mr. Travers suite.
- I can call to check for you.
- Thanks, but no need. I'll go up.
- But tell me--
- Don't speak.
They can hear us here too.
First we have to get out of here.
You slut.
Go on!
No, no. You know this place.
You've been here often enough.
Mrs. Menil?
Let him search all he likes.
The woman will bleed to death
without a doctor.
Don't worry.
The doctor will be here shortly.
But if she's lucky,
she'll croak before he gets here.
Let's go.
We're in deep trouble,
thanks to this bitch.
She would have jumped ship
in America anyway.
She loves him.
A blind man could see it.
A blind man.
Do you realize
we're the last ones...
to know
about this control room?
Aside from him, of course.
Doesn't that make you a bit uneasy?
I don't know.
I have a strange feeling.
When that reporter Barter
surprised you...
as you were replacing
the defective camera in her room...
he was stone-dead
within the hour.
Number 11 -- dead.
Last night, when the clubfoot
had completed his mission...
and was no longer needed--
gone.
And now that this thing with
the American has failed completely...
do you think
we're still useful to him?
Who built this whole system
for him? I did.
Who obtained the old Gestapo plans
and switched it all over to TV? I did.
He made millions
with this thing.
- He won't just get rid of me.
- He's capable of anything.
From here he saw and heard
everything...
and could play
the role of the psychic.
Then he blackmailed
his victims.
My suicide attempt--
The clubfoot and l--
It was all a sham.
There was nothing but blanks
in my revolver.
You didn't kill anyone.
But why? Why all this?
To create a bond
between us.
In America, after our wedding,
they would have killed you.
I would have inherited everything--
your fortune, your industrial plants--
and then he would have come.
His desire for power
knows no limits.
I had to do
what he wanted...
but I would have told you everything
once we boarded the plane.
But now it's too late.
I love you.
I know you can't
believe me anymore.
It's too late now.
Too late.
They simply disappeared,
Inspector.
Mr. Berg believes they must have
sneaked out of the hotel...
but neither the concierge
nor the two bellboys saw them.
Also, they haven't yet
settled their bill...
and some of Travers' belongings
are still in his room.
Don't call an alarm just yet.
I'll come over myself.
- What's new?
- The autopsy report.
The clubfoot that came in last night.
No internal bleeding.
When he was shot in the heart,
he had already been dead for a while.
The true cause of death
was a steel needle in his brain.
Open up.
Close the door behind me.
Send the elevator upstairs.
I'm terribly sorry,
Mr. Travers...
that you found out
about my plans.
You and I have both lost.
I lost a big game
and you lost your life.
Do you want
to push your infamy...
to the point of letting
this woman bleed to death?
A painless death, Mr. Travers...
and faster than the death
she could have expected from me.
This woman
brought both of us down:
You, because you believed
in her love...
and me,
because I didn't believe...
this love could break
my hypnotic control.
Marion was hypnotized?
Do you think she could have pulled off
that little suicide farce otherwise...
without falling?
Do you believe, even if you had
indeed gained control...
of my enterprises
through Marion...
you would have become the sole owner
of all my financial assets?
Who said anything
about money?
Having gained control
of your nuclear plant...
I would have thrown
the world into chaos...
with the rockets
from your experimental plant.
The famous push of a button.
I would have done it.
- You are insane.
- Maybe.
But where's the line?
Insane.
That's what they said
about Dr. Mabuse...
who died 25 years ago
and whose name and plans I used.
His arrogant contemporaries
considered him a criminal.
But to me he was a genius...
who wanted to throw this rotten world
into a reign of chaos...
that could only be controlled
by the one man...
who knows how to harness
it for his own gain-- me!
All your plans end
with my death.
What can I offer you to at least save
the life of this woman?
Name your price.
I'm not speaking on my own behalf.
I know you can't let me live.
I admire your keen intelligence,
Mr. Travers.
- Then name your price.
- Police officers!
Act rationally, now that your plans
have fallen through.
You underestimate me,
Mr. Travers.
A check signed by you
would be my undoing...
and that's what you're hoping
to achieve, isn't it?
Their things
are still sitting here.
- Did you touch anything?
- Of course not.
Everything's empty next door.
They are searching for you already,
but they won't find you...
or at least not until it's too late--
for you.
I have no more time
to chat with you.
Here...
just in case
you want to act logically...
to escape a slow death
from starvation.
By the way...
this room is soundproof.
- Wait here for further instructions.
- Yes, sir.
We must systematically search
the entire hotel...
from the basement
to the top floor.
The exits are being watched.
Kaiser, you stay here.
The hotel is surrounded. Two officers
in front, a patrol car in back.
There's the main entrance and the
hallway, back there on the right.
Professor Jordan!
Cornelius!
Go get him!
The blond man there
is Dr. Mabuse!
Freeze!
Three men come with me. The rest of you,
don't let anyone through!
Get away from the wheel!
Cuff him!
It was about time.
He almost killed me.
- Goddamn it, who are you really?
- Interpol.
- But why?
- Later!
I know where Mrs. Menil
and the American are.
- Send them after the car!
- Get the patrol car!
A large gray sedan...
an American car...
GX 737.
Kras, homicide squad.
Start search immediately.
A large gray sedan, American-made,
license number GX 737.
Turn on the police radio.
All patrol cars and road blocks
are instructed...
to stop the suspect vehicle...
and arrest the passengers.
Exercise caution.
The suspects have machine guns.
I repeat.: a large gray sedan,
license GX 737--
Change the license plate.
A large American car,
license plate unknown...
exceeding the posted speed limit...
has just left Mhlendamm Street
and is now heading south.
This is Kras. Close all southbound
roads, if it's not too late.
He most likely wants
to get on the freeway.
Then send a coded message
that Route 1 6 will be closed.
In case those guys are listening,
send a false, unencoded message...
saying that we expect them
to break through at Neustadt.
Send four motor cycles
for backup.
- We'll meet at Sdstern.
- Understood.
And ask them at the Luxor
whether the damn Interpol guy...
found the American
and that darn female.
Come on, get in.
The key!
The key for down below!
Open up!
Police!
Double K, EKZ 302.
Reached square sequence. Over.
Good nose! Freeway southeast.
Come on, let's go!
A large American car,
license plate unknown...
has just passed a checkpoint,
apparently bound for Neustadt.
All roads to Neustadt
have been closed.
Let 'em look for us!
That's 35 miles away.
It could be a ruse.
We've been on the freeway too long.
Hold on!
Double K, FKA 7 is running.
Over.
Damn! The freeway reports no contact,
but they should have passed it.
They must have broken through
between mile 1 35 and mile 140.
At the next crossing,
get off onto the old highway.
There they are! F aster!
Get ready.
A patrol car and four motor cycles
are following us.
- Distance?
- About 300 yards.
Don't shoot yet.
Let them get closer.
I'm slowing down.
1 50.
1 00.
Now!
Shoot at the tires!
Damn! I need to put in
a new magazine.
Leave him there!
Let's go!