THE CABINET OF DR. CALIGARI
A film in six acts
written by Carl Mayer
and Hans Janowitz.
Directed by Robert Wiene.
Art direction:
Cast:
Photographed by:
THE CABINET OF DR. CALIGARI
Act I.
"There are spirits...
They are all around us...
They have driven me from hearth
and home, from wife and child..."
"That is my fiancee..."
"What she and I have lived through
is stranger still than
what you have lived through..."
"I will tell you about it."
"The little town where
I was born..."
"A fair."
"Him..."
"Alan, my friend."
SPECIAL EDITION
Fair in Holstenwall
! For the first time!
Entertainments of every variety.
"Come, Franzis,
let's go to the fair!"
"Don't go inside... The town clerk
is in a vile temper today!"
Dr. Caligari.
"Wait!"
"I wish to apply for a permit to
present my spectacle at the fair..."
"What kind of spectacle?"
"A somnambulist."
"Step rrrrright up!
Presenting here for the first time.
Cesare the somnambulist!"
End of Act I.
Act II.
That night the first in a series
of mysterious crimes took place.
"Murder!
The town clerk has been killed."
"Stabbed in the side with
a strange pointed instrument."
"Step rrrrright in!
Presenting here for the first time..."
Cesare the somnambulist!
The miraculous Cesare...
twenty-three years old...
he has slept for twenty-three years...
Continuously... Day and night!
Right before your eyes.
Cesare will awaken from
his death-like trance.
"Step right in!"
THE CABINET OF DR. CALIGARI
"Cesare... Can you hear me?"
Cesare... I am calling you... I...
Dr. Caligari... your master...
"Awaken for a moment
from your dark night..."
"Ladies and gentlemen!"
Cesare the somnambulist will
answer all your questions...
Cesare know every secret...
Cesare knows the past
and sees the future...
Judge for yourselves.
Don't hold back...
"Ask away!"
"How long will I live?"
"Till the break of dawn."
MURDER in Holstenwall
1000 Marks Reward.
The way home.
"Alan, we both love her."
"We'll leave the choice up to her..."
But whomever she chooses,
"we shall remain friends."
Night.
End of Act II.
Act III.
"Mr. Franzis, Mr. Franzis...
Mr. Alan is dead... murdered!"
"The somnambulist's prophecy...?!"
"I won't rest until I get to
the bottom of these dreadful deeds."
"I will obtain police authorization
to examine the somnambulist."
"Murderer! Help! Murderer!"
"Wake him up."
EXTRA EDITION
Holstenwall mystery solved!
Two-time murderer caught
in third attempt!
End of Act III.
Act IV.
Worried because her father
has been away so long...
"I had nothing to do with
the two murders...
so help me God..."
"The old woman... It's true...
I tried to kill her..."
by stabbing her in the side
with a similar knife...
"to throw suspicion
on the mysterious murderer."
"Is my father... Dr. Olsen here?"
After the funeral.
Night.
"Cesare...!"
"It couldn't have been Cesare..."
He was asleep at the time...
"I've watched him for hours..."
End of Act IV.
Act V.
"Is the prisoner secure in his cell?"
"I must see him!"
INSANE ASYLUM
"Do you have a patient
by the name of Caligari?"
"The director returned earlier today...
Perhaps you should speak
to him personally..."
"He... himself...
and none other... is Caligari..."
While the director, now placed under
observation, is sleeping in his villa...
"He's asleep."
SOMNAMBULISM
A Collection from Uppsala University.
Published in 1726.
"His specialty."
The Cabinet of Dr. Caligari.
In the year of 1703, a mystic
by the name of Caligari
toured the fairs of numerous villages
in northern Italy,
accompanied by a somnambulist
named Cesare...
For month he sowed panic amongst
village folks through a series
of foul murders committed under
almost identical circumstances.
He had entirely subjugated to his mill
a somnambulist named Cesare,
whom he did compel to carry out
his nefarious schemes.
A puppet, the exact likeness of Cesare,
and which took his place in a cabinet,
allowed him to divert any suspicion
that might fall on the somnambulist.
My Diary
12 March.
Finally... finally!
A somnambulist has been brought
to the asylum for admission...
Afternoon.
My desire... I shall be able
to satisfy my life's unwavering wish!
Now I shall unravel the psychiatric
secrets of this Caligari!
Now I shall discover if it is true
that a somnambulist can be compelled
to perform acts that in a waking state
he would never commit
and would be repugnant to him.
Whether it is true that a sleepwalker
can be led to commit... even murder!
An obsession.
"I must know everything...
I must penetrate his secrets...
I must become Caligari!"
You must become Caligari.
End of Act V.
Act VI.
"We found the sleepwalker
out in the fields..."
"Mr. Director... Unmask yourself...
You are Dr. Caligari!"
"... and from that day on,
the madman never again left his cell."
"Look! There's Cesare...
Never allow him to tell your fortune
...or you're dead..."
"Jane, I love you...
won't you be my wife at last?"
"We queens are not free to
answer the call of our heart..."
"You all think that I'm insane!
It isn't true...
It's the director who's insane!!"
"He is Caligari...
Caligari... Caligari!"
"At last I understand his delusion."
He thinks I am that mystic Caligari!
"Now I know exactly how
to cure him..."
END
English translation by
Robert Gray (Kinograph)
Adapted for subtitles by
7ime 7raveller