The 1000 Eyes of Dr. Mabuse
Screenplay: Fritz Lang and Heinz Oskar Wuttig
Based on an idea by Jan Fethge
Cinematography: Karl Löb
Production Design:
Erich Kettelhut and Johannes Ott
Music: Gerhard Becker
"Schau ich zum Himmelszelt"
composed by Werner Müller
Assistant Director: Walter Wischniewsky
Film Editors: Walter and Waltraut Wischniewsky
Sound: Eduard Kessel
Sound Recording Directors:
Richard Oehlers, Joseph Thuis
Costumes: Ina Stein
Made at: CCC-Studios Berlin
World Distribution: Omnia
Executive Producer: Alfred Bittins
Directed by Fritz Lang
Homicide Emergency Squad
Homicide squad, Neuber speaking.
"Criminal Psychology"
For you, boss. Mr. Cornelius.
Oh, my gosh!
The clairvoyant character. Get rid of him.
Think about it. He helped us solve
that prostitute murder case.
Inspector Kras.
This is Cornelius.
You may still be in time to prevent something
terrible from happening.
I had a vision.
And?
Two cars right next to each other
in the middle of traffic.
A street sign: "Hansaring."
I don't know the people involved,
I don't know the circumstances...
but I sense an impending disaster.
A crime.
Murder!
"Television Station"
Where on earth is Barter?
The broadcast begins in 30 seconds.
He should be here any minute. He called
about 15 minutes ago, all excited.
- He has some big scoop.
- Broadcast time is still the same.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Silence in the studio!
In two seconds.
Ladies and gentlemen...
unfortunately we must cancel our news report.
We just received the horrible news
that our reporter Peter Barter...
died on his way to the studio
behind the wheel of his car...
presumably of heart failure.
Doctor!
Mission accomplished.
Good. Change the license plate on the car.
Remove the transmitter.
Have the car painted immediately
and disposed of in Holland.
Have you ever seen the doctor?
What concern is that of yours?
Aren't you satisfied with your salary?
I'm just asking.
I'd like to know what he looks like.
Then you might as well order
a coffin for yourself.
Do you remember the American?
He too wanted to speak to the doctor in person.
They found him a few hours later.
His throat had been cut.
But I really want to know what
the doctor looks like.
That I don't know.
Don't expect me to explain
clairvoyance to you, Inspector.
Magic powers defy rational thought.
I feel the disaster looming.
I see it as if in horrible daydreams.
I myself suffer terribly from it,
for I can't stop it...
because, like a dark cloud,
some hostile force of black magic...
obscures my view at the decisive moment.
Thus leaving a little bit of
work for the police.
By the way, did you know
the reporter, this Barter?
About a year ago, shortly
after I settled here...
he visited me once or twice.
He was always looking for the sensational...
and he was a skeptic, like you.
That's a professional proclivity,
my dear Cornelius.
Unfortunately, a policeman can't afford
to mess around with magical powers...
and I rarely have anything
to do with dark clouds.
lf, like me, you had grown up in Ireland...
where people still believe in the
elementary powers of nature...
you might think differently.
But perhaps the blind see more
than those who have sight.
Possibly, but in the Barter case
this vision has failed you.
Maybe you were also thrown
off by your dark cloud.
This was no murder, my dear Cornelius.
It was a simple heart attack.
For you, Inspector.
Take it to the lab right away!
I'll be back in an hour.
You were right.
The autopsy revealed that Barter
didn't die of a heart attack...
but of a steel needle in his brain.
Material: the finest iridium steel.
Length: 38.4 millimeters.
The steel needle smoothly penetrated
the victim's skull bone...
and entered the brain without leaving
any visible trace on the outside.
We're not going to find anything here either.
"To my dearest Peter, with much love...
on the occasion of our first Christmas together.
Corinna."
His girlfriend.
Poor guy.
"TV Journal - Peter Barter"
Not a shred of paper left.
They even took the blotter.
- The audiotapes were also taken.
- Of course.
They were searching for evidence
of Barter's sensational scoop.
And if there was anything here,
I'm sure they found it.
You won't find any fingerprints.
These were no beginners.
All we have is a small, deadly steel needle.
An incredible weapon, gentlemen.
An air gun that shoots steel
needles absolutely silently.
It's a new infantry weapon...
tested at Fort Benning in the United States.
But here's something strange:
Before the weapon could go
into full-scale production...
the blueprints disappeared.
They were stolen.
U.S. military intelligence found the thief--
a U.S. soldier in Germany--
in a deserted bunker with his throat cut.
He had been gruesomely mutilated
and apparently tortured.
The blueprints were, of course,
nowhere to be found.
- When did this happen?
- About a year ago.
There's no doubt that it was this steel needle
gun that caused Barter's death.
I don't know.
This Barter murder case reminds me of
something that happened long ago.
Gentlemen...
does the name Dr. Mabuse mean anything to you?
- Never heard of him.
- No.
A criminal genius.
He wanted to shock the world
with terrorist acts...
undermining governments...
and establishing a fantastic reign of crime.
He ended up in an insane asylum,
where he wrote a kind of last will...
instructions for the crimes he was planning.
In 1932 he died, insane.
But if you talk to old-time criminals...
they all say that Dr. Mabuse isn't dead.
He can't die.
Cock-and-bull stories!
How could you even think of this--
What was the name again?
Dr. Mabuse.
In those days, I was a young assistant
on the homicide squad...
and we had a similar case there.
A man was shot behind the wheel
of his car from another vehicle.
The Barter case strikes me as an exact
copy of Dr. Mabuse's methods.
You said he was no longer alive.
Well...
I have seen his dead body
with my own eyes, but--
Why haven't we heard anything about this case?
The case never made criminal history...
because Hitler appeared on the scene,
and the whole Nazi nightmare.
But there must be files on the Mabuse case.
This is number eight.
Switch it on.
Decoding is active. Write it down.
This is Dr. Mabuse speaking.
Four days ago...
the American Henry W. Taylor arrived in town.
The British foreign office just agreed.
Good.
- Gentlemen?
- We accept.
Just a question of principle:
When you take over the entire stock
holdings of Taran Nuclear Works...
is this happening under the auspices
of the United States...
or are you signing as a private citizen?
In practice, it's irrelevant.
When I evaluate the secret
models of your rockets...
on my U.S. testing grounds...
I will be under government supervision anyway.
And how do you envision the
financial transaction?
As soon as my lawyers have
examined the contract...
you will receive the full amount by check.
The name Taylor is an alias.
Departments B and C are to follow
Taylor's each and every step...
and give a detailed report every 12 hours.
Taylor is staying in a luxury suite...
on the 14th floor of the Luxor Hotel.
A radio message from Inspector Kras.
"Before he was murdered on
his way to the TV studio...
the reporter Peter Barter had
been at the Luxor Hotel...
according to a statement by the
vehicle maintenance man."
Please call a short staff meeting
for 20 minutes from now.
In the meantime, I will notify
the president of Interpol.
We have been struggling for a while...
with a series of strange, unsolved crimes.
It all began two years ago.
On May 15, 1958...
a passenger airplane crashed at
the Dutch airport of Schiphol...
following an act of sabotage.
The perpetrators are still unknown.
Among the dead was the French
bank president Luchard.
His death caused a significant drop
on the Paris stock exchange.
During his trip to Germany...
Luchard had stayed at the Luxor Hotel.
On November 2, 1958...
Mr. Delano, an attorney for the
steel corporation PCA...
was murdered in a sleeping car on a
train traveling from Oslo to Paris.
Two weeks before the murder...
Mr. Delano spent three evenings
in the casino of the Luxor Hotel.
On May 12, 1959...
the Algerian-born arms dealer Hussein
fell victim to a bomb blast...
in his car shortly after crossing
the Belgian border.
Previously, Hussein had once met
with a well-known call girl...
at the Luxor Hotel.
And the list goes on.
Serious capital offenses, murder,
stock fraud, kidnapping.
Each case is different, and
each remains unsolved.
But they all have one thing in common.
The victims in all these cases were at some
point guests at the Luxor Hotel.
That's why we have set up one of
our best special agents there.
His identity is known only...
to the chief of the Federal Crime
Bureau and myself...
to avoid any kind of leak to
subordinate organizations.
He has been staying at the
Luxor for some time now.
His sole mission is to find out what's
going on at the Luxor Hotel.
I can't watch this!
The firefighters should be spreading
out their sheet by now!
She's about to jump!
Come back inside!
Madam, please don't cause any trouble.
We don't want a scandal.
Should you have financial difficulties,
the hotel will help, of course.
Ladies and gentlemen, you can't possibly
enter here. Please be reasonable.
- After all, a human life is at stake.
- Our jobs are on the line!
Don't give us a hard time. We need pictures.
I'm afraid that's impossible.
- Is it someone from the 14th floor?
- What's her name?
- I'm sorry.
- Menil is her name.
Marion Menil.
She is staying here at the hotel. I was
going to insure her only yesterday.
Sometimes you get lucky, huh?
Don't be alarmed.
Why would you want to do something so futile...
from which there is no return?
You are young and your whole
life lies ahead of you.
It might just be wonderful.
Think it over.
You might not die right away.
You may suffer horrible pain
before it's all over.
Or you might survive-- as a cripple.
Think about it.
I'm scared. So very scared.
Give me your hand.
Trust me. I'll hold on to you.
- She moved!
- He took her hand.
Thank God! I wouldn't have enjoyed my dinner.
Drink this. It'll do you good.
This is the hotel manager. Open the door.
- Please don't let anybody in.
- No, no.
Open the door! This is the police!
Please!
Perhaps you should go in the other room.
I'll talk to these people.
Come in, gentlemen-- just the two of you.
No, no, please. Don't push, gentlemen.
- We want to see the woman.
- We've got a right to see her.
Please, don't cause trouble. Mr. Taylor
is a guest from the United States.
What did he say? What's his name?
Nonsense! Wait, it's--
Of course. I've seen him in the newspapers.
He did look familiar.
Get to the office right away so your
picture makes the evening edition.
In the meantime, I'm going to
file my report by phone.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Who do you think the noble rescuer is?
Mistelzweig. Hieronymus B. Mistelzweig.
The "B" stands for "belly."
General insurance: life, accident,
baggage loss, health...
fire, hail, theft, and burglary.
Only lovesickness and a chronic
shortage of cash are excluded.
Well, if you insure that guy, you can retire.
Why? Is he that well-off?
Billions. Mr. Travers is one of the
richest men from overseas.
And a bachelor.
Mrs. Menil is apparently wealthy.
She owns fabulous jewelry and expensive furs.
She flew here from Paris five days ago.
But our house detective may
know more about her.
- Then please ask him to come here.
- With pleasure.
Are you sure the woman won't do
anything else foolish?
My secretary is with her.
Gentlemen, please visit the bar--
on the house, of course.
I promise I'll give you all the
information you need later.
Mrs. Menil has lived very quietly
in this establishment.
She most certainly does not
belong to the demimonde.
I suspect the whole thing has
to do with a telegram...
that she received about three hours ago.
- Do you know what it said?
- No...
but according to the receptionist...
Mrs. Menil grew visibly nervous
while reading the telegram...
and she retired to her room immediately.
Then I will question her personally.
Above all, I must insist that the
lady leave the hotel at once.
- And I must insist--
- This won't work, gentlemen.
You can't save a person from
committing suicide...
only to leave her to her own devices.
Give her time to get over this shock.
Who will guarantee she won't
attempt suicide again?
I believe I can accept that responsibility.
Perhaps Mr.-- What was the name again?
Berg.
- Mr. Berg can keep an eye on her.
- Of course.
The gentlemen are all gone.
For the moment, no one is going to bother you.
If I can help you in any way--
No one can help me.
Why didn't you let me--
Everything would have been over now.
Death is such a finite thing.
People often think they are
facing a catastrophe...
and despair descends like a dark cloud.
In every situation there is a way out.
Not for me.
Do you have financial worries?
Romantic troubles?
You trusted me when you were standing
out there on the ledge.
I should probably be grateful to you.
But I'm not.
Do you have any family I can notify?
I don't want to see anyone.
I want to go to my room.
I don't want you to be alone now.
Yes, I understand.
Then please notify my doctor, Dr. Jordan.
- Where is he? In the lobby?
- No, in the other room.
Forgive me. I was told that Mrs. Menil
was in your suite.
Sister Agnes heard a radio broadcast at
my clinic about this terrible incident.
Mrs. Menil is my patient. May I see her?
I was just about to send for you.
Marion!
How could you do such a thing?
You've got to pull yourself together.
I'm going to take you to your room
and give you a little shot...
and then you'll have a nice sleep.
I'll leave you in Sister Agnes's care overnight.
She's a familiar face, right?
Please don't think I'm ungrateful, but--
I think complete rest is the best remedy now.
If you don't mind, I will take
the lady to her room now.
Professor, is Mrs. Menil permanently
in your care?
No, absolutely not.
But she had a nervous breakdown
once before, about a year ago.
She was a patient at my clinic
for almost two months.
And she's got no husband, no boyfriend?
As a doctor, I can't make statements
about Mrs. Menil's private life.
Certainly. But I am of course interested
in this woman's situation now.
She is a very lonely person, very guarded.
It's not easy to win her trust.
You--
You must exert a strong influence on her.
I mean, on her subconscious...
in that you succeeded in
saving her from suicide.
I'm somewhat surprised...
but very happy about it.
Good-bye now.
"Multimillionaire Thwarts
Suicide at Luxor Hotel"
Not exactly a pleasant advertisement
for our hotel.
- Good evening, Inspector. The usual?
- Yes, the usual.
A lot of action around here.
Are your rates so high that your guests
must jump out the window?
It may be a joke to you, Inspector, but
unfortunately the joke is on me...
as if I were everybody's baby-sitter.
These disgusting reporters. May they go to hell.
Yes, these reporters with their scribbling--
To think what my friend Barter would
have done with a thing like this.
Oh, well. Since his death I haven't
been watching TV anymore.
Was he the one who died of
a heart attack in his car?
Yes. A great guy, Inspector.
Generous in every way.
- Mr. Berg?
- Yes.
Mr. Travers' secretary would like
to speak to you on the phone.
Excuse me for a moment, please.
Did you know this Barter well?
He always asked me for tips on special guests.
Especially the female ones, I bet.
You will laugh, Inspector, but I had pointed
out Mrs. Menil to Mr. Barter.
Actually, it was the day she arrived.
She sat over there, while Barter
drank his whiskey over there.
Things must have worked out...
because a little later they
went upstairs together.
Interesting.
Would you kindly let Mrs. Menil
know that I'd like to see her?
I'm afraid that's impossible.
She just took a sleeping pill.
- Is she asleep yet?
- No, but--
- Then I'd like to see her.
- Can't it wait until tomorrow?
Unfortunately, it can't.
My name is Kras.
Inspector Kras.
A man by the name of Inspector Kras
insists he must see you.
Is this necessary? Why do people torture me so?
Please...
but take the lady's health into consideration.
Please forgive the late visit,
but I'm afraid it's quite urgent.
Please make it quick. I feel faint.
Do you remember a man by the name of Barter?
Barter? No.
A TV reporter.
This is the first time I've heard his name.
Perhaps this will refresh your memory.
Oh, that guy! Yes, I know him.
He introduced himself downstairs in the bar.
I hadn't quite caught his name.
He wanted an interview.
I refused. After all, I'm not some movie star.
He was awfully pushy.
And yet you brought him upstairs to your room.
I didn't want to make a scene in the bar.
I brought him here upstairs,
but he got quite aggressive.
It got so bad that I had to ask
him to stop bothering me.
He's not going to bother you anymore.
Shortly after visiting you, Mr. Barter...
died.
But that's awful!
And when a person wants to die,
they won't let her!
"Return immediately or you must bear
the consequences of your actions.
I have proof of your guilt."
Mrs. Menil, three hours after receiving
this telegram from Paris...
you attempted suicide.
How did you get that telegram?
My personal life is nobody's business.
When the police are interested in something,
there is no personal life.
Why are you torturing me like this?
Leave me alone!
That's enough. Can't you see?
But I must talk to you again about Barter.
I received a very strange phone call.
For the time being, please don't leave town.
Good night.
"H. B. Mistelzweig Insurance"
Tough times, tough business.
Mars has entered the house of
death of too many people.
- Who has entered what?
- Mars is in the house of death.
As a modern businessman, I work
solely on the basis of astrology.
There is no point in insuring people if
you know that they won't live long.
Imagine if I had insured your friend Barter.
He looked as chipper as life itself.
He would have just paid his first
premium, and then-- wham!
A heart attack! What an awful
loss that would have been.
No, no. One must look at the stars
of these insurance candidates.
- Very interesting.
- What do you mean?
- Did you have Barter's horoscope?
- This is Inspector Kras.
Please, allow me: Hieronymus B. Mistelzweig.
"B" stands for "belly."
General insurance:
Life, accident, baggage loss...
health, fire, hail, theft, burglary.
Only lovesickness and a chronic
shortage of cash are excluded.
Impressive. What companies do you work for?
Lloyd's of London, Assurance la Paix Paris...
Seguros de Madrid, Kontor Hamburg
National and Overseas.
Mistelzweig has worldwide connections.
A lucrative business, isn't it?
One doesn't talk about that. One gets by.
Allow me, gentlemen. Another round.
A little schnapps with your beer
can't hurt, Inspector.
Besides, it's all tax-deductible.
Karl, one more.
The hotel engineer is, of course, included.
I'm sorry, Mr. Mistelzweig.
Perhaps later, though.
The freezer for the kitchen
downstairs is on the blink.
Most likely it's a short. Do you have
the key to the machine room?
No, but there must be a spare downstairs.
I can't find it. Please come with me.
Go ahead and pour my drink. I'll be right back.
Do you have an office here at the hotel?
My office? No, no.
My office is here-- in my head.
I do my business at the Luxor...
but I wouldn't take a permanent office
here if they gave it to me for free.
What don't you like about the hotel?
Just between you and me:
It's not under a lucky star...
like anything the Nazis started
near the end of the war.
What does that have to do with the Luxor?
People aren't the only ones influenced
by the constellations upon their birth.
- A building is too.
- Come on now!
- A building isn't born!
- Oh, yes, it is, Inspector.
The placement of its cornerstone
is its birth hour...
and the cornerstone for the Luxor
was laid by the Nazis in May '44...
when they still believed in final victory.
The bigwigs in the SS wanted
to build a few grand hotels...
for politicians and diplomats...
all in one huge cluster, so they
could spy on everybody.
No, the Luxor has a negative aura.
But your business is thriving here nevertheless.
Well, in a hotel like this there are always
people with a lot of money.
There's jewelry or baggage to insure,
or travel insurance to write.
My wife has always wanted
me to buy life insurance.
It all depends on the stars, Inspector.
It's all in the stars.
Considering your profession...
you could be dead tomorrow, right?
I mean, since you're always
in dangerous situations.
Criminals never sleep, do they?
But perhaps we could work something out.
Call me at the office in the morning.
It's pretty quiet there these days.
I'd also like to talk about Mr. Barter.
He wanted insurance too.
I received a very strange phone call.
To your health, Mr. Mistelzweig.
Cheers, Inspector.
- It was nice to meet you.
- The pleasure was all mine.
I'll be sure to call you.
No harm done...
but if you could take me to the other
side, I'd appreciate that very much.
May I give you a lift somewhere?
That's very kind of you.
If you can find room for my dog too--
Of course.
In Ireland we also have this cold, wet weather.
I can feel it on my skin like damp wool.
I don't know.
Careful! Don't take the turn so fast!
Danger!
Damn! That was close.
- Thanks for the warning.
- How did you know that?
Sometimes I can see things coming.
You don't believe me.
This morning at the hotel...
you dropped a glass while brushing your teeth.
In picking up the shards, you cut the
middle finger of your right hand.
But that's--
No one was there to see it when it happened.
This morning, around 11:00...
you signed a check drawn on an English bank...
but the business transaction you're
planning will not materialize.
The part about the check is true too,
but how do you know the rest?
I told you before: Sometimes
I can see things coming.
If you can predict future events...
how come you didn't see that we
would almost run you over?
The hour of my death has not yet come.
- Who are you?
- My name is Cornelius.
Good evening...
Inspector.
Why did you turn on the light?
So that you may see better, Inspector.
I could have been a burglar.
No, my dog growled and barked.
This means that there's someone
in the room whom he knows.
He would have behaved differently
with a stranger.
And then...
I also smelled your pipe tobacco.
The odor clings to your clothing.
Then I knew it was you waiting
for me in the dark.
The blind have keener senses
than people who see.
But how did you get in?
My attendant has the night off.
I was so bold as to let myself
in, Mr. Cornelius.
Please accept my apologies,
but I must talk to you.
There's a new twist in the Barter case.
Did they find something in his car?
No.
In his head.
A small, unfriendly thing
Let me be frank, Mr. Cornelius.
I'm not making much progress in this matter.
You know I'm a skeptic...
but when you're stuck, beggars
can't be choosers.
If you concentrate on this object...
what do you see...
that might help me?
A man.
His face is a blur.
Now, nothing!
The cloud again. The dark cloud.
It covers everything. It's stronger than I am.
It threatens me personally. I can feel it.
That's why I would be grateful to you...
if you kept me informed about the Barter case.
We have maintained absolute
silence with the press...
regarding the fact that Barter
met a violent death.
Nevertheless, this afternoon I received
a very strange phone call.
A man was willing...
in exchange for immunity from
prosecution and a reward...
to give me information about this steel needle.
We immediately determined the call
originated from a public phone.
But the guy
was much too smart.
When the patrol car arrived, he was long gone.
But before he hung up, he said
I should think about it.
He would call me again tomorrow.
What are we doing here?
The bunker where they found the American.
You know, the American!
- And why are we here?
- To make a phone call.
- You're so fond of making phone calls.
- Me? What do you mean?
You know. I warned you.
- The doctor doesn't like it.
- What doesn't he like?
- That you make phone calls.
- But I didn't--
I didn't!
- Good morning, Inspector.
- Morning.
It got pretty late last night. Any news?
Nothing at all. Everything was quiet.
The telephone didn't work, but it's been fixed.
- A man from the phone company--
- Don't pick up!
I'd be willing to purchase it.
Would you accept 45,000 marks?
- But it's worth much more!
- Let's say 50,000.
- All right.
- Would you like a check or cash?
Cash. I may need to leave today,
and the banks are already closed.
Nexit.
You were lucky, Inspector.
If it weren't for that cabinet,
you'd be dead as a rat now.
It would serve me right.
His wife is expecting their first child.
You slowly get used to the fact that people
bite the dust in our profession.
It's all business as usual.
And it's my fault.
Your fault? Why?
Yesterday I set out three pieces of bait...
but the response came faster than I expected.
But from whom?
The psychic?
The insurance agent?
Or the woman?
Why aren't you honest with me?
I don't know what you mean.
You sold this piece of jewelry today.
- You had me followed?
- I feel responsible for you.
You booked flights today with
four different airlines...
for four consecutive dates...
to four different cities...
under four different names...
none of them your real one.
- Why?
- Please, don't ask!
What is threatening you, Marion?
What were you so afraid of that
you wanted to end your life?
Please don't ask. Please, please, don't ask!
I don't want to cause you pain, Marion,
but why don't you let me help you?
I don't want to owe anybody anything.
- I won't accept any money from you.
- Then at least take this back.
I know what it means to a woman
to give up her jewelry.
Then I have no other choice but to keep it.
Perhaps chance will unite us once again.
In the meantime, this piece
will remind me of you.
My plane is leaving tomorrow.
Tomorrow, already?
Will you do me a big favor before we part?
If I can, gladly, of course.
Then spend our last evening with me.
You must distract yourself
to regain your zest for life.
You need to get out and see happy people.
You need to hear laughter and music.
To the next lucky coincidence
that will bring us together.
Everyday worries and concerns must
be checked in with your coat.
All right. To the next lucky coincidence.
Terrific music, isn't it? It gets in your blood.
I'm a Scorpio. They burn with passion.
What are you, madam? A Libra?
No, I'm a Sagittarius.
Straight to the heart!
- Would you like to dance?
- Oh, yes!
Do you like to dance?
I used to love to dance, a long time ago.
You know, I believe you are a
cheerful person by nature.
I used to be very happy and cheerful.
- I loved to laugh.
- Why don't you try it again?
See? Much better. Come and dance with me.
Wasn't I right to drag you out of
your end-of-the-world mood?
Yes, perhaps.
You dance beautifully.
See? You are a different person now.
Marion, come to Paris with me tomorrow.
To Paris? I can't go to Paris.
Don't get me wrong. I'm not a prude.
I would love to do it.
But I can't leave now.
Why not?
I'm not free.
I'm married.
Do you love your husband?
I hate him.
When the lady who just stepped out returns...
please tell her I'll be right back.
He carries a gun in a shoulder holster.
- Are you sure?
- Absolutely.
I'm all black and blue from pressing against it.
Have you never considered divorce?
Yes, often, but my husband will never let me go.
Money can overcome many obstacles.
Not in my case.
Money can't help me.
But let's not talk about me.
Tell me about yourself, about your life.
It's not very interesting.
Business, conferences.
-And women?
- Yes.
But only in passing.
You know, when someone lives
for his work as much as I do--
board meetings, staff meetings,
business meetings--
I practically live in planes
and conference halls.
There's only room for brief pleasures...
and not much more.
- That's very sad.
- One can't have everything.
Mr. Travers? Excuse me. We just received this.
- What about the check?
- The lawyers still have it.
- Cancel it right away.
- Yes, sir.
You see? You can't relax either.
A few minutes ago, when we were dancing...
I believed that I could run away from myself.
But I can't. No one can.
We've all got to follow our path.
No, I would only bring you bad luck.
If only all this had happened
three years ago, fine.
But now it's only self-deception.
I'm sorry to spoil this lovely evening for you.
Please forgive me and forget me.
It's better that way.
Do you really want me to forget you?
Yes.
"Radio London announces nuclear power plant...
run by the Taran Plutonium Corporation
was blown up today.
Plant completely destroyed by fire.
Many casualties.
Population within 10-mile radius
evacuated for safety reasons."
The catastrophe itself I did not foresee.
I only felt there was a dark shadow
hovering over your plans.
First, the broken glass in the bathroom...
then the truck we nearly collided with...
and now this Taran Corporation matter.
What's the rational explanation for all this?
Fate allowed me to cross your path.
Perhaps I'm to protect you from future harm.
The explosion in the Taran plant
is hardly harmful to me.
A business transaction that didn't materialize.
That's all.
I mean your personal life.
Although I'm blind, light that's
too bright is bothersome.
It scatters your thoughts.
You must now focus on me.
You should go away. Leave this town.
Something has crossed your path...
and a dark cloud hangs over you.
I see a figure.
It's very blurred.
An animal.
And a woman?
Perhaps.
I can't quite penetrate the darkness.
But one thing I do see.
You saved a life...
and it is precisely this life that
threatens you with danger...
and death.
She can't just be making up the fact
she reserved four airplane tickets...
even if she did it under false names.
I don't get it.
Take a note: Interpol inquiry.
Does this insurance agent Mistelzweig
really work for Lloyd's of London...
and Assurance la Paix Paris and
all the other companies?
Inspector, Mrs. Menil just canceled
all four flight reservations.
Interesting.
She goes out with the American...
and the next morning she cancels her flights.
Yet she didn't look too happy
when she went upstairs.
Interesting.
I have something else for you.
Get hold of this Cornelius character's latest
tax return. Be discreet about it.
Hello, Mr. Cornelius? This is Kras.
No. No news, really.
Did the man who wanted to give you
the confidential information call you?
He couldn't call me, Mr. Cornelius.
You see, my phone exploded yesterday.
A little assassination attempt against me.
A man from the phone company
supposedly repaired it earlier.
What did the man look like?
Can you please describe him for me?
The only person who could
do that is my assistant...
but, unfortunately, he's dead.
Why didn't you warn me before it happened?
What is that supposed to mean?
Are you saying you wanted me to
predict your death? You're alive!
- But in the Barter case you did!
- Well, he's truly dead.
Inspector, I sense your mistrust.
You are skeptical.
That's why I would like to convince you.
Please attend a telepathic séance
at my house tonight.
Choose for yourself the people
you want to witness it.
Bring whomever you wish.
Do you really believe in this humbug?
Michael, you know I'm a skeptical man.
Always have been.
Now, for the first time in my life...
I wish I were able to believe in someone.
The psychic or the woman?
You should know me better, Michael.
I do what I think is right.
No psychic can change that.
- So you are staying here?
- Yes. You fly to London alone today.
Get information on all the repercussions
of the catastrophe...
especially whether the secret plans
for the rockets were saved.
And something else, Michael.
This you can do right away.
Pick out fifty roses in the flower
shop downstairs...
and have them sent to Mrs. Menil,
with this note.
Certainly.
Excuse me, Mr. Travers.
May I perhaps have a word with you in private?
What is this about?
It's about Mrs. Menil.
It's not my custom to intrude in the
private affairs of our guests...
but I know you are interested in anything
that concerns Mrs. Menil.
Our access to her for surveillance purposes...
is unfortunately very restricted.
She spends most of the day in her suite.
She speaks on the phone a great
deal and receives visitors too.
But I may be able to reveal something...
of great interest to you.
How much do you want?
That's entirely up to you, of course.
But it must be absolutely confidential.
I could lose my job.
Well, then?
Forgive me, but it's something
that I can only show you...
if I may trouble you to come with me.
It won't take long.
It's right here.
This suite is adjacent to the rooms
occupied by Mrs. Menil.
This room was once occupied
by a very jealous husband...
whose wife was staying right next door.
He was never sure whether she
was faithful to him or not...
so I helped him out with this little setup.
One fine day, he caught her in the act.
Here you can see and hear everything,
but from the other side, you can't.
I'm going to turn on the loudspeaker.
Unbelievable, no? On the other side,
it's just a normal mirror.
Please help me get dressed.
Please see who it is.
These roses are for the lady.
Beautiful roses.
I'll get a vase right away.
Well, did I promise too much, Mr. Travers?
Turn it off! It's despicable to eavesdrop
on people like that.
Turn it off!
Don't worry, Mr. Berg.
I will pay you for this secret.
So that no one else may misuse it,
reserve this suite for me.
Tell the receptionist that it's for some
business partners I'm expecting.
Of course, Mr. Travers.
Yes?
May I remind you that we still
have an appointment?
I would like you to attend a
telepathic séance with me.
Yes, ma'am.
With a psychic, at 8:30 p.m.
I would very much appreciate seeing you there.
Hello, Inspector. Is this a bad time?
Shall l--
Don't leave the hotel. I'll call you later.
Is this place all right?
It looks so-- so dilapidated.
You were right the other day, Mr. Mistelzweig.
Someone planned to dispatch me to heaven.
- Maybe I should--
- No, no, no.
You couldn't have come at a
better time. Have a seat.
You are interested in astrology
and such, aren't you?
Yes, as a business principle. You know--
- Is this your wife?
- Yes, yes.
Would you like to attend an interesting
séance with a psychic?
I'm flattered! When?
Tonight at 8:30.
Perhaps we can talk business too.
I'll bring my wife.
May I introduce my wife? Mr. Cornelius.
Very pleased to meet you, madam.
This is my assistant, Mr. Kaiser,
and Mr. Mistelzweig.
Hieronymus B. Mistelzweig.
The "B" stands for "belly."
General insurance: life, accident,
baggage loss, health...
fire, hail, theft, and burglary.
Only lovesickness and a chronic
shortage of cash are excluded.
He's very much interested in the
occult, especially astrology.
Only in a very amateurish way.
I'm an absolute dilettante.
But, in fact, today the sun is in
conjunction with Neptune.
That means water, so we're
due for a thunderstorm.
I should have brought an umbrella, right?
That's a splendid animal you've got there.
Come on, doggie. Uncle has
got something for you.
Quiet, Ferro. Be quiet.
He's not interested. He won't take
anything from a stranger.
This is Mr. Cornelius, my wife...
Mr. Kaiser, and you already
know Mr. Mistelzweig.
- I hope I'm not late.
- Not at all, madam.
Please, let's all take a seat.
It's very informal.
Please...
concentrate on me now.
I'm having difficulty concentrating.
Something is interfering with me.
It's not the thunderstorm.
- Inspector.
- Yes?
Would you mind if we traded places?
Not at all.
- Excuse me!
- No problem.
I hope my cigars survived intact.
I suspected as much:
Saturn in the 11th house-- a small
accident among friends.
Excuse me.
Let us begin.
Someone among us has come here
with the intent to deceive.
I see a woman's hand and a ring.
A ring that doesn't belong on that hand.
A tragic fate tore from this woman
the man she loved.
A dark cloud hangs over the man.
The image is blurring.
A car, with the man at the wheel.
He is dead.
Peter Barter.
One person here saw him before he died...
and one person here will avenge his death.
It won't be an easy task.
The dark cloud is all-powerful.
It gathers and approaches...
ever closer!
No, it's not a cloud.
It's a face.
The face of a dead man.
No, he's alive.
Mabuse. Dr. Mabuse.
Now it's gone. The dark cloud has returned.
Close, very close.
It is here! It is hanging over--
Kras!
Get away from the window!
Turn the lights off!
The shot came from either the roof
or the attic of that house.
Kaiser, maybe we can still catch the guy!
I'm not staying here any longer.
Would you please take me back to the hotel?
Please don't leave me here alone.
The danger has passed.
I regret this turn of events.
Perhaps some refreshments will help
you recover from the shock.
Mr. Cornelius...
I admire your psychic gift.
Really, it was fabulous! Amazing!
By the way, what was that strange
name you mentioned?
I don't remember.
I have no control in this state.
It doesn't really matter.
By the way-- just between you and me--
does this Inspector Kras have a
chance of living much longer?
I'm not omniscient, Mr. Mistelzweig.
Well, he wants to buy life insurance from me...
and I would appreciate certain tips.
I don't do business with the
lives of other people.
Of course not. Please forgive me.
It was just a thought.
By the way, did you notice
that the shot rang out...
just as your grandfather clock
struck for the first time.
- Is it accurate?
- I would assume it is.
No, the clock is exactly one minute fast.
Here, you see?
Please forgive me. I forgot.
You are blind.
But don't you think that this
delay of one minute...
may have saved the inspector's life?
Well, Inspector? What did you find?
Nothing.
My assistant is still looking for clues...
but the man is long gone, of course.
Cornelius, I haven't had a chance to thank you.
But for your warning, I would be dead now.
The bullet hit the chair exactly in the spot...
where my head had been.
Strange.
This is the second assassination attempt
directed at me in the last 48 hours.
You are mistaken, Inspector.
Why is that?
You forget that I had been sitting
in that chair earlier.
This murder attempt was directed at me.
I loved your roses so very much.
- How did you get--
- I felt so alone in my room.
Perhaps it's childish, but I'm always
so scared of thunderstorms.
I hope you don't mind that I simply came by.
- Your door was open.
- Please, come in.
Am I really the reason you extended your stay?
I wanted to ask you one more thing
before I dive back into my work.
Yes?
Do you prefer whiskey or cognac?
Whiskey, please. Straight up.
- Was that the question?
- No.
- Cheers.
And the question?
If you were available, would you marry me?
I want to tell you the truth now, Henry.
The whole truth.
In reality, my marriage is sheer hell.
My husband has always been driven
by an almost pathological jealousy.
He has a physical disability.
It's just a problem with his foot.
It never bothered me.
But it seems to be the main
reason for his jealousy.
He is convinced that I'm cheating on him.
Sometimes he would beat me
to extract a confession...
but there was nothing to confess.
That's grounds for divorce!
I have often suggested separation
to him. Very often.
He said he would rather kill
me than set me free.
Last year, I simply ran away.
I was a nervous wreck.
That's when I ended up at Dr. Jordan's clinic.
An old friend of our family.
When I recovered somewhat,
my husband took me back home...
and the torture, threats and abuse
began all over again.
Ten days ago, I completely lost control.
I didn't care about anything.
I obtained some poison and
intended to kill him...
but he found out and nearly beat me to death.
I didn't know what to do, so I ran away again.
Just to get away from him.
That's how I ended up at the Luxor.
But he tracked me down again.
He sent a telegram saying if I
didn't return immediately...
he would report me.
So that's the story behind it all.
I saw no other way out but to kill myself.
So now you know the whole story.
Do you still want to marry me...
a woman who tried to poison her husband?
Is Mrs. Menil there, Mr. Travers?
There's no answer in her room.
It's for you. Professor Jordan.
The professor?
Yes? This is Marion.
What? When?
Oh, my God! Ten minutes ago?
You'll stay at the clinic.
Yes, okay. Thank you.
What's going on?
My husband is on his way to the hotel.
He'll be here any minute.
He mustn't find me in your room.
Stay here. You are safe with me.
I can't drag you into this.
You don't know Roberto.
Please let me go!
If I don't call you in half an hour,
come to my room.
- Is it still raining?
- I'll call a bellboy--
No, thanks. I'll take care of it myself.
What is it? I've already gone to bed.
Open the door if you don't want a scandal.
Come back tomorrow.
If you don't open up, I'll kick in the door.
That's it, darling. Why resist?
I'm sorry if my sudden appearance...
rattles your tender nerves.
A woman who loves her husband should
welcome him more joyfully.
More tenderly.
What do you want from me?
I'm not sure yet myself.
We'll see.
It was quite stupid of you to run away again...
and to believe I wouldn't find you.
Just as stupid as your attempt to poison me.
You thought no one would miss
me if you succeeded.
Now, one word from me and you'll land in jail.
But this time you won't get
off the hook so easily.
Beautiful roses.
From him, right?
Since your dramatic suicide attempt...
you've been in all the newspapers...
you and your new lover.
You must be grateful to your savior.
That's best expressed...
with a few tender caresses, right?
You animal!
There!
Does this pain your little heart?
You love him, don't you?
Yes, I love him!
I love him as much as I hate you. You hear me?
I don't regret for a second
that I wanted to kill you.
You're not human. You're a beast!
No so fast, my sweetheart. Not so fast.
Let's see if the gentleman from America...
will still want you in bed
with your face cut up.
Shoot him!
- How did you get in here?
- Through the mirror.
The detective-- I'll explain everything.
Do you think anyone heard the shooting?
Wait.
- There's nobody outside.
- I'm going to call Dr.Jordan.
He must come right away.
Perhaps he can still save Roberto.
This is Marion, Professor.
Please come over right away.
Something terrible has happened.
Perhaps you can still help him. Thank you.
He's on his way.
- Where is my cognac?
- Here. I didn't know if you'd be back.
An insurance agent always comes back.
It's raining cats and dogs.
You wouldn't kick a dog out in this weather.
Dr. Jordan. Thank God you're here.
- I shot him.
- I must tell you, Professor--
Believe me, it was self-defense.
The knife is still lying there on the ground.
He's dead.
I didn't mean to kill him!
Please help me, Professor.
You've got to help me out of this mess!
Please, Marion, calm down. Let me think.
Professor, I'm partially to blame--
I too am to blame, Mr. Travers.
I knew how dangerous this man was.
Perhaps if I had come right away--
The most important thing now is that
the police don't find out about this.
I had the ambulance park on a side
street, to avoid drawing attention.
If we could just get the corpse
out of the hotel--
A massive heart attack must be treated
in the hospital immediately.
Later, I could fill out the death certificate
to read "heart attack."
But how do we get him out of the hotel?
The hotel detective will do anything for money.
Besides, he owes me one.
And now it's time to go sleep in my empty bed.
Would you have an extra raincoat? I forgot mine.
I have an old one over there.
I'll get it for you.
- Here. Will this do?
- Yes, thank you.
- I'll bring it back tomorrow.
- That's okay.
- Good night.
- Good night, Mr. Mistelzweig.
It's just a minor heart attack, madam.
Please don't be alarmed.
A few days of rest in my clinic
and he'll recover.
Initially he will need to take
it easy, of course.
Nothing upsetting. No business.
He'll need to put himself first now.
$5,000 in cash if you help us, Mr. Berg.
We don't want any commotion in the newspapers.
Naturally, Mr. Travers.
It's not in the interest of the hotel...
to create a stir in case of sudden illness.
How can we get Mr. Menil to the
ambulance without being seen?
That's easy. We use the freight elevator.
And the broken mirror?
I'll have that fixed within the hour.
I'll wake up the maintenance man.
He lives in the hotel. He's my closest friend.
No sirens, no flashing lights.
We don't want any attention.
I'll follow in the car.
I've known Professor Jordan since I was a child.
I knew he would do anything for me.
But if we had said that you fired the gun--
To think that I'm hiding behind a woman--
I always took responsibility for my actions.
If he hadn't been so quick,
I would have fired the shots.
But isn't this all beside the point?
You saved my life for the second time.
Even so.
Two hours ago, in this room...
you asked me whether I would
marry you if I were free.
And now I am free.
This worked out fine once again,
just as the doctor predicted.
Precisely.
No!
What? What is it?
Patrol car 8 has detected a fire...
on the top floor of a bombed-out house.
There's a dead body in one of the rooms.
You wake me up for that?
Franke is on night duty now. Let me sleep.
What's that?
A secret transmitter?
Police files on Dr. Mabuse?
Strange place. No sign on the door. Nothing.
When we saw the fire from the street...
my partner said, "No one lives there."
Then we found the body.
Shot in the chest, apparently
straight through the heart.
First they killed him, and then they
tried to burn the place down.
We pulled down the curtains and
doused the sofa with water.
We were able to stomp out the rest.
- Any ID? Any papers?
- Nothing.
Nice of you to make time for me...
so early in the morning, Mr. Cornelius.
I was in the neighborhood and
thought I'd just drop by.
Isn't the little doggie here today?
A routine checkup at the veterinarian.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
What can I do for you, Mr. Mistelzweig?
Well, I thought, "Maybe you can
do business with Mr. Cornelius."
With me? Business?
Don't worry. I don't want to insure you.
I just want--
- Mind if I smoke?
- Please.
I know it's a bad habit of mine, but--
Did I startle you?
I unseated you, so to speak, in this charade.
You know, this blind-man ploy is really great.
Yes, really.
When you take off the sunglasses
and stare into the distance--
Very attractive.
Really stylish.
And the contact lenses-- like
in an American horror film.
Come now!
Don't do anything stupid.
The phone is going to ring soon.
A friend of mine.
I took the liberty of giving him
your phone number...
just as a precaution so that nothing happens.
What do you want from me?
I want to go into business
with you. Fifty-fifty.
During the séance the day before
yesterday, I had this idea.
You know, people are so scared
when it comes to insurance.
If you, with your clairvoyance, advise
them to protect their families...
then they'll all come running to me, you see?
That's him.
Yes, I'm still here.
No, not much longer. A few more minutes.
I'll be in touch, yes.
No police-- don't worry.
By the way, this Kras character--
Didn't you wonder why he would
drag me to your séance?
He wants to keep an eye on me.
I've done time. Five years.
Insurance fraud. I've learned a lot since then.
And the two of us will come out
on top of that Kras guy, right?
Think it over, Cornelius. Fifty-fifty.
The projectile that hit the psychic's chair...
and the bullet in the corpse...
are of the same caliber and have
the same rifling marks.
They clearly come from the same gun.
Very interesting.
Thank you very much.
- Any word from Mistelzweig?
- No, he was asked to come at 11:00 p.m.
But Interpol's answer just came in.
Mistelzweig, Hieronymus Balthazar.
Insurance agent with many years of experience.
Best references from Lloyd's of London.
No prior convictions.
I still don't like his mug.
The embodiment of promptness, right?
What happened to your right hand?
A small scuffle ending in death, perhaps?
Inspector! A peace-loving man like me?
- Have you ever been bitten by a dog?
- No.
Good for you. It hurts terribly,
let me tell you.
Last night I was going home when
a huge dog jumped at me...
and wouldn't let go.
And this should happen to me, a real dog lover!
You left me a message, Inspector.
You wanted to talk to me.
Was it because of the séance last night?
No.
But I want to show you something.
Well, that's life.
"Yesterday on a steed abreast,
today a bullet in the chest."
- How did you know that?
- What?
That the man was shot in the heart.
You couldn't see that.
Inspector, I was just quoting an old song...
and right away you're suspicious again.
Shot through the heart. Awful.
One moment a man is running
around alive and well...
and twelve hours later he's dead.
- Stone-dead.
- So you know him then.
That would be pushing it.
I saw him last night at the Luxor.
I noticed him because of his clubfoot.
He has one, doesn't he?
Just what I thought.
He went up to the third floor
where Mrs. Menil is staying.
By the way, it's strange.
Did you know that she checked out?
She's leaving with the American today.
Let's say good-bye to the professor
and then we'll go.
What's the number?
4-2-5...
5-2-7.
Say...
last night when you called him,
you only dialed three digits.
- Three?
- Yes.
You must be mistaken.
I've known Jordan's number for years.
It's 425-527.
And there's something else.
How could the professor get
here so quickly last night...
just five minutes after your call...
and with an ambulance?
For God's sake, don't say anything now.
They can hear and see everything.
- Who can hear and see everything?
- Later, later!
We must leave this hotel as soon
as possible, or it's all over!
What are you talking about?
What are you afraid of?
There! Look!
And there are more over there! And over there!
Everywhere in this hotel.
In the bar, in every room, in the nightclub.
They can observe everything.
- We must leave immediately.
- But--
Please! Please believe me!
Listen, Henry. I lied to you.
I was lying the whole time!
But now you have to believe me, just this once.
- Please! Before it's too late.
- Why?
For God's sake, don't ask any
more questions now.
Come on, before it's too late. Come on!
Twelve...
eleven...
ten, nine.
I'd like to know if Mrs. Menil is
still staying at the hotel...
or if she and Mr. Travers have already left.
They must still be here, probably
in Mr. Travers suite.
- I can call to check for you.
- Thanks, but no need. I'll go up.
- But tell me--
- Don't speak.
They can hear us here too.
First we have to get out of here.
You slut.
Go on!
No, no. You know this place.
You've been here often enough.
Mrs. Menil?
Let him search all he likes.
The woman will bleed to death without a doctor.
Don't worry. The doctor will be here shortly.
But if she's lucky, she'll croak
before he gets here.
Let's go.
We're in deep trouble, thanks to this bitch.
She would have jumped ship in America anyway.
She loves him. A blind man could see it.
A blind man.
Do you realize we're the last ones...
to know about this control room?
Aside from him, of course.
Doesn't that make you a bit uneasy?
I don't know. I have a strange feeling.
When that reporter Barter surprised you...
as you were replacing the defective
camera in her room...
he was stone-dead within the hour.
Number 11 -- dead.
Last night, when the clubfoot
had completed his mission...
and was no longer needed-- gone.
And now that this thing with the
American has failed completely...
do you think we're still useful to him?
Who built this whole system for him? I did.
Who obtained the old Gestapo plans
and switched it all over to TV? I did.
He made millions with this thing.
- He won't just get rid of me.
- He's capable of anything.
From here he saw and heard everything...
and could play the role of the psychic.
Then he blackmailed his victims.
My suicide attempt--
The clubfoot and l-- It was all a sham.
There was nothing but blanks in my revolver.
You didn't kill anyone.
But why? Why all this?
To create a bond between us.
In America, after our wedding,
they would have killed you.
I would have inherited everything--
your fortune, your industrial plants--
and then he would have come.
His desire for power knows no limits.
I had to do what he wanted...
but I would have told you everything
once we boarded the plane.
But now it's too late.
I love you.
I know you can't believe me anymore.
It's too late now. Too late.
They simply disappeared, Inspector.
Mr. Berg believes they must have
sneaked out of the hotel...
but neither the concierge nor
the two bellboys saw them.
Also, they haven't yet settled their bill...
and some of Travers' belongings
are still in his room.
Don't call an alarm just yet.
I'll come over myself.
- What's new?
- The autopsy report.
The clubfoot that came in last night.
No internal bleeding.
When he was shot in the heart, he had
already been dead for a while.
The true cause of death was
a steel needle in his brain.
Open up.
Close the door behind me.
Send the elevator upstairs.
I'm terribly sorry, Mr. Travers...
that you found out about my plans.
You and I have both lost.
I lost a big game and you lost your life.
Do you want to push your infamy...
to the point of letting this
woman bleed to death?
A painless death, Mr. Travers...
and faster than the death she
could have expected from me.
This woman brought both of us down:
You, because you believed in her love...
and me, because I didn't believe...
this love could break my hypnotic control.
Marion was hypnotized?
Do you think she could have pulled off
that little suicide farce otherwise...
without falling?
Do you believe, even if you had
indeed gained control...
of my enterprises through Marion...
you would have become the sole owner
of all my financial assets?
Who said anything about money?
Having gained control of your nuclear plant...
I would have thrown the world into chaos...
with the rockets from your experimental plant.
The famous push of a button.
I would have done it.
- You are insane.
- Maybe.
But where's the line?
Insane.
That's what they said about Dr. Mabuse...
who died 25 years ago and whose
name and plans I used.
His arrogant contemporaries
considered him a criminal.
But to me he was a genius...
who wanted to throw this rotten
world into a reign of chaos...
that could only be controlled by the one man...
who knows how to harness
it for his own gain-- me!
All your plans end with my death.
What can I offer you to at least
save the life of this woman?
Name your price.
I'm not speaking on my own behalf.
I know you can't let me live.
I admire your keen intelligence, Mr. Travers.
- Then name your price.
- Police officers!
Act rationally, now that your
plans have fallen through.
You underestimate me, Mr. Travers.
A check signed by you would be my undoing...
and that's what you're hoping
to achieve, isn't it?
Their things are still sitting here.
- Did you touch anything?
- Of course not.
Everything's empty next door.
They are searching for you already,
but they won't find you...
or at least not until it's too late-- for you.
I have no more time to chat with you.
Here...
just in case you want to act logically...
to escape a slow death from starvation.
By the way...
this room is soundproof.
- Wait here for further instructions.
- Yes, sir.
We must systematically search
the entire hotel...
from the basement to the top floor.
The exits are being watched.
Kaiser, you stay here.
The hotel is surrounded. Two officers
in front, a patrol car in back.
There's the main entrance and the
hallway, back there on the right.
Professor Jordan! Cornelius!
Go get him!
The blond man there is Dr. Mabuse!
Freeze!
Three men come with me. The rest of you,
don't let anyone through!
Get away from the wheel!
Cuff him!
It was about time. He almost killed me.
- Goddamn it, who are you really?
- Interpol.
- But why?
- Later!
I know where Mrs. Menil and the American are.
- Send them after the car!
- Get the patrol car!
A large gray sedan...
an American car...
GX 737.
Kras, homicide squad. Start search immediately.
A large gray sedan, American-made,
license number GX 737.
Turn on the police radio.
All patrol cars and road
blocks are instructed...
to stop the suspect vehicle...
and arrest the passengers.
Exercise caution. The suspects
have machine guns.
I repeat: a large gray sedan, license GX 737--
Change the license plate.
A large American car, license plate unknown...
exceeding the posted speed limit...
has just left Mühlendamm Street
and is now heading south.
This is Kras. Close all southbound
roads, if it's not too late.
He most likely wants to get on the freeway.
Then send a coded message that
Route 16 will be closed.
In case those guys are listening, send
a false, unencoded message...
saying that we expect them to
break through at Neustadt.
Send four motor cycles for backup.
- We'll meet at Südstern.
- Understood.
And ask them at the Luxor whether
the damn Interpol guy...
found the American and that darn female.
Come on, get in.
The key!
The key for down below!
Open up!
Police!
Double K, EKZ 302.
Reached square sequence. Over.
Good nose! Freeway southeast. Come on, let's go!
A large American car, license plate unknown...
has just passed a checkpoint,
apparently bound for Neustadt.
All roads to Neustadt have been closed.
Let 'em look for us! That's 35 miles away.
It could be a ruse. We've been
on the freeway too long.
Hold on!
Double K, FKA 7 is running. Over.
Damn! The freeway reports no contact,
but they should have passed it.
They must have broken through
between mile 135 and mile 140.
At the next crossing, get off
onto the old highway.
There they are! Faster! Get ready.
A patrol car and four motor
cycles are following us.
- Distance?
- About 300 yards.
Don't shoot yet. Let them get closer.
I'm slowing down.
150.
100.
Now!
Shoot at the tires!
Damn! I need to put in a new magazine.
Leave him there! Let's go!