Hey, what are you doing!
It's scratched, isn't it!
You made this, right?
There wasn't anyone except you, right?
Honestly, please tell me
what's your name?
Where's your school? the name of your parents?
your address, telephone number?
Shinya!
Shinya, what happened?
Dr. Miyagawa, has my son
caused you some problem?
Kiryu-kun, he's your son?
Yes.
He has, look at this scratch.
Shinya, is that so?
Shinya!
I was watching.
I expect reimbursement.
I'm really sorry.
Dr..
could you hold me tight?
Yes.
Finally, my full-fledged medical examination started with her.
It's the same as the last time.
Does a psychiatrist have an exchange
like that with a patient?
You are Yumeno-san, right?
Hey, Hino-rin,
could you stop?
deceiving Akira.
I'm not deceiving her.
Then, why
were you holding her tight!
In this way, I want to talk to you
looking at your face..
Didn't I tell you!
I don't want a guy like this to hug you.
because a guy like him
will only betray your trust.
It's useless to believe in him! Do not believe in him, at all!
This hypocrite!
What? Are you just going to stand there?
There are times when you want to strike
things or people in that way
Please continue until you're satisfied.
Don't say things as you understood me.
Once you're calm down,
let's drink some tea together.
The truth is that you want to expel
a patient like me.
The other day when we went to the sea,
Akira-san also did it,
she hand over some tea for me,
didn't you?
I'm fed up with you!
Here.
Yumeno-san, Yumeno-san.
Please come out, Yumeno-san.
Then, if you want to stay there it's fine,
let's talk.
I..
Dr., I
did something that caused you trouble.
Hello, Akira-san.
Here.
When the therapist is facing patients
with dissociative identity disorder
he should never take the attitude
of denying neither of the personalities.
Why do I have this disease?
What is the reason?
Let's look together for the cause,
of this strange thing that happened.
Because the other personality might be hearing the conversation.
How?
It'll work if we can talk about it together.
About what?
Well..
then, today, please tell me about
the childhood memories.
I was always painting alone.
Because I was really shy.
What is it?
This..
Shinya! Stop!
Ah, Dr.
I'm sorry, again such a thing..
Don't mention it,
Shinya-kun, hello.
He is my friend.
I'm sorry
for scattering them around.
Shinya-kun, the only son of Kiryu Kaoru-san,
with Savant syndrome, involving disabilities in language,
called an autism spectrum disorder, it's an special case,
having an unique wonderful view of the world.
So, now let's move forward with no fear!
I'm your ally.
This is a story of a doctor that saves
the lost sheep of this modern era.
Sorry for the late introduction,
I'm a psychiatrist, Hino Rintaro
Seppuku Monaka?
Do you want to apologize with a disemboweled belly?
By all means, I beg your pardon.
Then, I'd like to take Yumeno-chan
outing.
Is she available?
Soon, I have to genuinely persuade
Ike, the Press secretary
I have to receive permission
for a new hospital.
I'm sorry..
I've been thinking of
letting her rest for a while.
But why?
Because she was missing at the "Higashi Odori"?
If that's the case, I can
negotiate with the Shinbashi association.
No,
it's not just that.
I'm really sorry.
Yumechiyo.
You can not just refuse to this.
If there are any reasons just say it.
Yumeno is sick.
Sick? Is she hospitalized?
No.
Then, she's sleeping at the Okiya?
Who's the doctor?
Dr. Hino..
Hino?
Yeah.
Our Hino Rintaro?
Yes.
Director!
As usual, it's always like this.
But compared to the early days,
but I've the conviction that
I've come to understand him a little.
Well, I still
can't tell what Shinya
is thinking.
It's okay.
Even if you don't know it now,
he will surely show you a sign or something,
Just a little while ago, with Dr. Miyagawa
Shinya scratched his car with a bicycle
that fell down.
Prof. Miyagawa's?
Thank you, Shinya-kun!
I've always
wanted to do that.
Dr.
Ah, this, this is it!
This is what?
Maybe this is his sign,
to say 'I'm sorry'.
Is that so!
Isn't that amazing.
One step further into connecting
with Shinya-kun's mind, right?
As expected of the mother.
Well, I'd like to think so..
He does this when he's happy, right?
Yeah.
Shinya.
What's going on? Hino-kun,
explain it to me.
We're in a middle of examination
Director.
Ah, he is my son.
Shinya!
Director, excuse me.
Ah, I'm sorry.
Where is Yumeno?
She already left. Can't this wait,
since I'm in a middle of an examination?
What's wrong with Yumeno?
I can not answer that.
I'm the Director, tell me.
Doctors have a duty of confidentiality.
The Director himself is telling me
to break it?
Do you understand what that attitude means,
in this situation?
Situation?
Someone like you can be fired at any time.
Alright, finally!
It's a chance!
Pink elephants are rare, right?
Do you like elephants?
It's fun to see an elephant jumping.
Hello?
Then, sorry?
Mom.
That over there, it's the mother?
Shinya!
I knew that you'd be here!
Let's go home for today.
Ah?
Shinya. Shinya.
You like it here, Shinya. Can you do it?
Okay.
So, this is your secret place, right?
It feels good, here outside.
Dear Dr. Rintaro,
We took a look at your paper.
We can't be more impressed by
the throughout research and study.
What?
If the author, Yoko Kawakami has an interest
in the research done at our school,
please introduce her to me.
We would like to welcome her in our lab.
University of Houston school of medicine, Texas.
Dean Margaret Goldman.
Dr.
It was a very well-made paper,
and as we talked before,
I was allowed to send it to my old school.
Yes
How do you wish to reply?
Since I'm in charge of some patients,
please let me think about it a little.
I understand.
Come in.
Dr. Is it okay now?
You know.. something big has happened
What happened?
It's Shinya..
What happened to Shinya-kun?
He did it
What is it?
The Grand Prix Art Sculpture Exhibition for Children,
He won it!
Isn't that great!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Shinya, you did it!
Ah, Dr., sorry for that.
Let's celebrate together!
Big time!
Yes!
I've been thinking about this for a while,
That child is probably a case of Savant.
Furthermore,
he may also experience Synesthesia.
What about that?
Write a paper about your interpretation of this!
The secrets of this mysterious brain function
is your area of expertise.
I see.
It can be useful,
Let's do it, Machiko-kun!
Thank you.
What? What do you want to show me?
You may not be pleased by this.
It's really irritating that it concerns
such a virtuous gentleman, right?
Excuse me.
Good evening.
Yumeno.
Ah, then, now,
I'll leave first, excuse me.
En-sama, I'm sorry.
For leaving the other day and also about the Azuma Odori.
My condition was poor.
And you didn't tell me that you are
receiving treatment from Hino.
Who said such thing?
I'm the usual healthy me, now.
Then, what is this?
Oh..it was well photographed.
Who took it?
Should i know?
Since when you have this with Hino..?
Hey.. En-sama,
It's useless to get mad at such a thing,
right?
But, I'm glad you're jealous of me.
One more?
Yumeno-chan..
Dr. Hasumi,
thank you.
Then, next is
Prof. Miyagawa, if you please.
Today, I'd like to ask everyone
for your cooperation
regarding my research.
For some time now,
I've been studying the
connection between mental disorders and the brain.
Among them,
I'm proud of calling myself an expert
regarding Autism and brain function.
Is that so?
Yes.
This time, the patient I'd like to study this time is this person,
he's also Dr. Hino's patient,
Kiryuu Shinya-san.
eh? Is it okay?
Shinya-kun while being a case of autism spectrum disorder,
he also has a rare talent for sculpting.
Recently, he has been awarded with the
Grand Prix Art Sculpture Exhibition for Children.
I dare say, he was
diagnosed as one of the cases
referred as Savant syndrome.
Is that so, Dr. Hino?
It is.
People with Savant syndrome
have an ability to recall images,
sounds, or objects in memory
after only a few instances of exposure
After hearing only once
they can reproduce a tune
they have an exceptional memory.
Amazing.
Furthermore, different letters will induce
the experience of particular colors
the sounds will induce the experience
of a particular shape and smell.
I believe it combines synesthesia,
in which the stimulation in one sensory stream
will automatically associate experiences on another.
People with such a special ability are very rare,
and the number of researches in our country are very few.
I'd like to research
using fMRI and SPECT
the activity of the brain in each region,
and its relevance
By all means, I'd like to count with Shinya-kun's cooperation.
It's an unusual case, right?
Yes, it'll be a very interesting research.
Nice, please, do it by all means.
I object.
What's your objection?
Why don't you cooperate?
It's a nice research.
Shinya-kun can't bear the examinations with
of fMRI or SPECT.
Why?
As a doctor, you probably know the
hardship that children with
Autism spectrum have to suffer, right?
What do you mean?
They can't deal with unexpected situations.
Even in their daily life has steps to follow,
they have to live their life with much predictability.
I'm aware of those things.
Forcing the big sound close to his ear,
for a long period of time with the same posture,
inside of the machine.
That is an environment that Shinya can't possible bear.
During SPECT test, we could use a sedative.
Stop making fun of this!
Have you thought, even once, what it feels to be in his body?
How much they have to struggle
to live in this society,
have you thought about that?!
If you don't listen to your patients,
you can't possibly know, but
every minute using the air around,
they desperately trying to stay alive!
You, that don't even try
to understand those hardships,
I won't leave Shinya-kun to your care!
That's a haughty attitude, Hino-kun.
Are you in a position to judge Miyagawa-kun?
Because,
haven't you been obsessed with one patient?
What do you mean?
I mean Yumeno.
You're also been selfish.
She has her own circumstances.
Isn't it a doctor's duty
to match the needs of the patient?
Kiryuu-kun is a part of our staff, right?
Yes.
Isn't it enough to have the approval of the mother?
Please wait a moment!
It's fine if Hino-kun stops being in charge.
If now,
you push to get the permission from the mother,
you'll break the bond between mother and son,
they've been building till now with much effort!
For Shinya-kun, his mother is his lifeline!
Please, stop this!
Miyagawa-kun, just get her permission immediately.
Hino-kun, you're not in charge of him anymore, okay?
I can't accept this.
I'm taking you out of Yumeno's case too.
I can't accept that either.
Well then, there's nothing left but to quit
Hino-kun, cool off that hot head of yours
and then give us an answer.
Okay?
Understood.
Then, what follow is
the communication of the parties.
I have my hopes on this.
Yes, sir.
What was that? Rintaro.
I'm really sorry, but
I refuse.
Why?
By all means, please, I ask for your cooperation.
Is because of Hino?
Is not that.
This is my decision.
I'm really sorry.
If you refuse this,
it will be difficult to stay here, you know?
I know this.
Could you consider this one more time?
No.
Because my feelings won't change.
Shinya!
Excuse me.
Damn it!
Shinya! Wait! What are you doing?
Please put that back, Shinya
Again ... I'm sorry.
Maybe this is causing Shinya-kun
a tough experience, too.
This is my fault for getting
emotional at the meeting.
I'm sorry.
Since I refuse directly to Dr. Miyagawa,
Dr., you don't have to worry anymore,
please.
I see.
Allow me.
Is open, come in.
Am I interrupting you..?
Not at all.
Excuse me.
Have a seat.
What is it? Akira-san.
I..
About Shinya-kun's incident
I wanted to apologize to that child.
Apologize?
Well.. when I met him for the first time here,
the one who messed up the
miniature garden and the animals
it was me, right?
And Shinya-kun put them in order again,
without looking unpleasant.
I wish to convey clearly
a proper apology..
Akira-san,
please don't worry about it.
That wasn't your doing,
but Yumeno-san who did it.
But..
And
Shinya-kun loves setting up
things that have fallen down.
He would virtually pass unnoticed
to adults around him, but
that kid has a great personality.
Dr...
Has something happened?
That's a cute stuffed toy.
Ah..this..
This, could you give this to Shinya-kun,
doctor?
and tell him that I'm sorry for not
apologizing that time.
Shinya-kun will be happy about this.
Akira-san, are you okay?
Instead of worrying about me, are you okay doctor?
Huh?
It seems like you are being forced by something
I'm wonder if something had happened.
Actually, now I was thinking
of apologizing to Shinya-kun, too.
Even though I call myself his friend,
I can't do anything good
for that child,
I'm a failure as a doctor.
There's nothing like that!
About Shinya-kun, it seems like he
wants to say something.
And that..
I think the Dr. is the only one
who can get to understand that.
Akira-san..
Thank you
There's nothing to thank..
A psychiatrist not only treats patients,
they can also be saved
by the words of a patient.
Like me, right now.
Dr...
Then, about Shinya-kun, I'll leave this to you..
About that, Akira-san.
If you could give this directly to
Shinya-kun would be better.
Tomorrow we're doing a party
to celebrate Shinya-kun's award at my place.
Friends from the hospital are also coming.
If you like,
would you come?
But, me, at that kind of place..
Akira-san, you're shy to strangers, right?
My favorite comedian has this saying,
"Being shy is a wonderful talent
received from god"
Talent?
Yes.
If you said this yourself,
the others will think it too.
In that way, if that the first thing
you can led others to think
then that's a great talent.
Since tomorrow is holidays,
so the celebration will be from midday.
It would be great if you come.
Thank you very much.
Then.
I'll be waiting.
I'll be waiting!
I said it twice..
Here, you liked these, right?
Is it eclair?
Yes
But, not so much recently..
ah, but since you troubled,
I'll receive it.
Hino-kun also comes here?
ah.. that has to do with your duty of confidentiality,
so you can't say it.
If the other party is you, then it's
to hell with confidentiality, right?
What's it that you want to hear about him?
No, today, it's about you.
Huh?
Akari-kun, don't you feel like coming back to our hospital?
You surely don't want to end up
listening the complaints
of the patients at
a dumping place like this, right?
Well about that..
Don't you want to aim the top at the The White Tower
once more?
Shinya-kun, let's toast.
Dr., did you prepare all of this?
Yes.
Mash potato curry,
pseudo tandoori chicken,
ponzu garland chrysanthemum, and so on.
Let's start.
Shinya, it's the toast.
It's Shinya's celebration, here, hold it.
So to celebrate the Shinya-kun's
Children's Art Exhibition Grand Prix ..
let's toast!
Sorry..
Shinya-kun seems to really like
that spot, right?
Dr. the ones who should be thankful
are Shinya and I.
About today, I'm really
thankful.
No, I just like to stay friends
with Shinya-kun, it's just that.
Thank you very much.
Someone is still coming?
Ah Madoka-chan?
Madoka is also coming but,
I invited Akira-san.
And then, today, we have another
reason to celebrate.
Kawakami-kun, please.
Yes.
I've decided to accept studying abroad
at the Texas Houston Psychiatrist School.
Ah, Rintaro's study abroad destination?
Yes.
I'll seek to learn the
empathetic treatment in the United States
and become a full-fledged psychiatrist
as Dr. Hino is.
Wow ~ Congratulations!
Good luck.
Do your best.
Thank you.
Kawakami-san,
without trying so hard, do your best.
Thank you.
Everyone, I've been really under your care until now.
Kawakami-san!
From the bottom of my heart I'll be cheering you.
Then, to celebrate Kawakami Yoko's departure,
once more, let's toast.
Then, let's toast.
Cheers!
Wait, Fukuhara-san.
Are you okay? Don't force yourself.
What is that?
I'm completely okay.
Cheers!
Let's let them drink big time today.
Right.
I wonder what kind of talk
Shinya-kun is having with Yasuke.
If I could become Yasuke,
I could get to understand that kid more.
Texas Houston!
Houston, Texas-! right?
Thank you for the other day.
Ah..no
Are you looking for my brother?
If you want to leave a message, I could tell him.
No..
If you have no business with him,
coming to his place on a holiday it's an intrusion
What are your intentions?
Since you're my brother's patient,
I don't want to send you away
coldhearted or something like that, but..
you're not his only patient.
I'm sorry..
Also, my brother
has a girlfriend,
Yuriko-san.
That's how things are..
Excuse me.
Brother,it's not good unless
you properly lock the door, right?
Look Rintaro
Madoka-chan is here.
Madoka, you're late
Hello, sorry to interrupt.
Before being betrayed,
it's better if I betray him.
See you, Hino-rin.
I wonder if Kaoru-san
is intending to leave the hospital?
In order to protect Shinya-kun.
By the way, Yumeno-san
didn't come today.
Yeah..
What is wrong with
psychiatrists  falling in love~!
Fukuhara-kun, are you still here?
If I knew this was going to happen,
I'd have got ridden of the Dr.'s opinion.
I should have confessed my love for her!
Eh!?
The person Fukuhara-kun was in love with is Kawakami-kun?!
You two, what are you talking about now?
♪～  If only I could express to you
♪～ “I love you”
♪～ Even if you don't answer
Even if you look bothered...
Help me,
I'm being chased by debt collectors again.
Are you okay with your mom being killed?
What if you're killed?
Since that damn doctor appeared
you've changed!
Before, you were kinder, didn't you!
Didn't you help mom!
Are you in love with him?
with Hino?
Don't make me laugh.
Then what..
He's deceiving Akira
into trying to erase me.
I won't allow that, absolutely.
Anyway, please I need 10 million yen
somehow really soon..
or I'll be killed...
Then..
how about using this?
It's a interesting picture.
Kiryuu-san.
Won't you think about it one more time?
Dr., my opinion won't change.
Since there is a meeting,
excuse me.
Eh? What happened? Shinya-kun
Today
it's not the day we meet.
The hiragana?
o
o?
Wait a minute,
I'll write on paper.
Go ahead.
D o c
Doc-tor.
Shinya-kun
I've..
got..
to..
Doctor,
I've got to..
live..
longer..
than..
the..
doctors.
And..
if..
I..
ever..
become..
a..
dad,
I..
don't..
want..
our..
children..
our children to..
to..
be..
troubled..
like..
me.
So,
I..
will..
go..
into..
the..
I'll go into..
the machine.
So..
if..
I..
do..
that..
then..
the..
impor-
tant..
doctors..
may..
come..
up..
with..
a..
new..
treat-
ment.
The end!
Shinya-kun,
you are a tough kid, you know?
I've got to live longer than the doctors.
And if I become a dad I don't want our children to be troubled like me.
As mom is doing her best for me, I also want to do my best
So, I'll go into the machine, in that way,
the important doctors may come up with a new treatment.
Shinya..
Shinya-kun has been properly thinking about this,
more than us.
It's okay, right? Dr.
Since it's what Shinya-kun wants.
Hey Shinya,
you don't have to try it too hard.
If it's unpleasant,
it's okay to ask to stop this.
I'll leave him under your care.
Then, let's go.
Let's go.
Shinya..
About the bicycles,
I think they fell down.
Huh?
Ah, when the kid scratched the car
I think Shinya-kun was just picking up
the bikes which have fallen.
He dislikes when the bikes are down.
So, even though he didn't
knock them down,
he was picking them up.
If adults see this
they would get angry at him,
thinking it's his fault.
But it's wrong, Prof. Miyagawa.
The ones who should be scolded, instead of him,
it's us,
for not trying to understand him.
He's always tried really hard
doing his best effort in order
to understand us.
The most painful thing for the person suffering from
Autism spectrum
and their surrounding family
is not being possible to communicate
by means of oral language.
The miracle that has happened now with Shinya-kun,
is a hope for many people.
Hope?
I ask your favor, somehow.
In any way, using your knowledge,
please, decipher his signs.
Understood.
Then, we're starting.
You'll hear a loud sound,
but don't be afraid, okay?
This, it seems to be you, Kaoru-san.
And then,
this must be Shinya-kun.
Before the examination, using these,
he tried to explain
why he wanted to go through the examination.
I..
want..
to..
protect..
Mom.
Me?
Parents who have children with Autism spectrum
unconsciously tend to blame themselves.
Did something happened during breast-feeding?
Did I do something to this child
that shouldn't be done, during pregnancy?
But the mother did nothing wrong.
Shinya-kun knows that,
knows that his mom, for him,
she will do anything, no matter how hard
no matter how much effort it takes.
Shinya-kun knows that perfectly well.
That's why he wants to protect his mother.
Kaoru-san.
Please do not quit the hospital.
Shinya-kun has been growing  up firmly.
From now on, together,
let's us also have some growth.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Even though I respect Dr. Hino
from the bottom of my heart,
there's only one thing I don't agree with him.
What?
I don't think love is like a
temporal mental illness.
Then..
It's a genuine mental disorder.
That's why I think it was good
to be rejected by him.
Do your best.
Fukuhara-san, you do your best too.
Yes.
Well.
I loved you.
I knew it.
.. so you knew.
Thank you, Fukuhara-kun.
Here.
Hasumi, have you forgotten my face?
Araki.
So you haven't forgotten, right?
So, how was the image diagnosis of the child?
When the issue of the language is challenged,
the normal blood flow
not only increases in the left temporal lobe
but also in the parietal lobe,
which performs spatial recognition
What is more, the main
blood flow in the right side is increased.
Such data, with a clear image of Synesthesia in
children is probably
even worldwide, very rare, I think.
Isn't that amazing! You did it.
Hurts!
What ? Is it okay to let Miyagawa get all the credit?
I'm satisfied just with the fact
that I was able to convey Shinya-kun's thoughts
to his mother.
You need to want more!
And, that woman's treatment,
is it going well?
Ah, is she an appointment patient?
She is Akira-san's mother.
Ah.. this person is.
You're also a doctor?
Yes.
What happens when psychiatrists put a hand
on their patients?
Well,
if you actually put a hand on the patient,
that basically
is a violation of Medical Ethics,
but this guy,
is not that kind of person.
How do you know that is true?
No, because this guy is a virtuous gentleman
wearing a white robe.
Then, what is this?
Hey hey!
So the 'rin' in Hino Rintaro is just
the 'rin' in ethics violation.
She's making a play of sounds, ethics violation=[rinri ihan]
If you don't want to be sued for this photo,
wanna buy it?
I refuse, please leave.
Calm down a little.
Then for this picture, how much
are you asking for selling it?
The doctor over here gets what I'm talking about!
How about 50 million? [~420,353 USD]
You said 50 million..
You wanna pay, right?
Dr. Rintaro, the medical ethics transgressor.
Subs by Kitty-nyan
*´¨)
¸.•´¸.•*´¨) ¸.•*¨)
(¸.•´ (¸.•` ¤ (\_(\
¤ (=' :')
¤.. (,('')('') .. ¤
¤ Chuline ¤