If a person catches a cold they will routinely go to the doctor,
but we would like to create an environment
in which more people will, similarly,
go to the psychiatrist's door without any sense of hesitation.
So when your mind gets weary,
please, also do take a rest for the mind.
Dr. Hino,
thank you very much.
Thank you.
Dr., there is something
that it's really worrying me, recently.
If so then I have some question too!
No, I'll go first..
(Announcer) So, today's guest from
Toshiminami Psychiatric University Hospital
was Dr. Hino Rintaro.
That was well said, Hino-kun.
This will also,
raise our popularity,
the number of examinees and the income
will have a sudden increase.
That's wicked, Hasumi-kun
I just think that it can contribute
to the psychiatric development
that's why I recommended him to the TV show.
Miyagawa-kun, don't you have it?
Something as Hino-kun's bestseller
to take out?
Ah, no,
I ..something like this..
Oh ~again ringing.
Would you stay close, from now on?
I'll be by your side from now on.
Where did you go this morning?
For a walk.
I see.
The weather is good.
Did you feel good?
The day after tomorrow is the performance
of "Higashi Odori", you know.
Let's do it stylish.
Yes.
Refreshing and stylish!
Thank you.
We will ask for your appearance again.
Then with your permission.
Excuse me.
Good work.
Dr. Hino!
Dr. Hino, please your autograph!
I'm really sorry.
The doctor
has plans after this.
Excuse us, give him some space.
Dr...
Ah.. Kawakami-kun,
my bag, thanks.
Dr.! Doctor!
And also I have this.
What is that?
These are fan letters.
Eh!
He's gone.
But.. he's really nice.
Yes?
Akira-san, listen..
That psychiatrist that is your friend,
you know what he told me?
That it was better for me not to be here..
That's the same as telling me to die, you know?
He wants to apart us, you know?
Mom...
mom can't live without
seeing you..
Mom?
By the way,
how about the money?
What?
The 10 million I asked you.
If you don't get them soon,
I may be killed for real.
It means that mom is in trouble.
we don't have any relation with the doctor, right?
No..
I know..
I understand that..
I'm back, we've returned.
Great work.
Dr., you forgot your cellphone.
So, it was here.
It's Akira.
I went for a walk early today.
Thank you for your message.
You can send another again.
Please contact at any time you need.
We'll have a talk.
Dr. that..
your phone was ringing non-stop.
Could it be..a stalker?
No, it's not that.
You know, this is..
Kaoru-san..
This is for your son.
Eh!
Look, the drawing that you showed me,
he is really skillful, right?
Thank you so much.
It's so luxurious!
Shinya will be very happy. Thanks.
Has something happened?
No.
Hello.
Didn't I tell you?
Stop meddling with Akira?
Yes.
If you don't keep your promise,
I'll make Hino-rin's life a living hell.
Dr., is everything okay?
It's okay, just fine. I'm really hungry, aren't you?
Thanks for choosing us! Here's Makoto sushi!
Here are the first class 30 servings.
Dr. Hino,
Did you ask it? Sushi.
No, I didn't ask it.
What? We received an order from Kawakami-san.
I did not make such a call!
Oh, we're beaten, a prank call?
Well..since you took the trouble, I'll take it.
Eh.. Thank you very much!
How much is it?
It is ¥ 97,200. (~802.70 USD)
¥ 97,200!??
So, now let's move forward with no fear!
I'm your ally.
This is a story of a doctor that saves
the lost sheep of this modern era.
Sorry for the late introduction,
I'm a psychiatrist, Hino Rintaro
So, they don't know who ask for the sushi?
Who would eat such thing?
Right?
Ah.. please, eat.
Dr.
Dr.!
What! You should knock when entering a room.
I did..
Oh this is Dr. Hino's book.
Well it ....
I think this book is funny
I don't!
"Know your enemy, know thyself,
and you shall not fear a hundred battles"
I don't really get that,
but if you like sushi, here.
It seems it was ordered excessively,
so, we're sharing portions.
Ah.. from whom?
It's from Dr. Hino.
Nevertheless, I wonder why
did they use Kawakami-san's name?
Kawakami-san, do you have any idea?
..you're not listening..
Ah! Could it be that geisha
named Yumeno-san?
It may be!
Since she borrowed Dr. Hino's money.
If there is some kind of trouble ....
There is no evidence of that!
So you were listening..
The doctor told you clearly, right?
that is bad to judge something by guessing.
that means that Kawakami-san, you
also suspects from Yumeno-san, right?
Right now, you definitely were listening..
Hang in there, Daisaku
What are you listening to?
A lecture of Dr. Hino,
when I hear the doctor's voice, feels like healing.
Dr. Hino's voice?
Your mother was a woman like me?
sluttish with men
This mom with such an elegant face
had an affair.
Yes?
Ah..Hello, Araki senpai,
Is it okay if I stop by today?
Ah..It's okay.
And I have a sort of emergency.
Could you buy me the usual
in a hurry and bring it?
Okay, got it.
See ya.
What our Yumeno did was terrible.
Dr. I'm really sorry.
Has Yumeno come back?
Yes.
And then?
Yes, suddenly her condition became worse.
I'm really sorry.
Even so, isn't the recent Yumeno a little strange?
Yes..
Could it be because our Hino-kun, I wonder..
Never such a thing ....
Yumeno is also Minister Ike's favorite.
If Yumeno acts weird it will be a problem.
Yes..
Yumechiyo.
Don't put me to shame.
Yes.
So, right, the tickets left for "Azuma Odori"
I'll buy them all.
Thank you very much.
Come in.
Here's Hoshino Yoshimi-san, please.
Hello, Hoshino Yoshimi-san
Nice to meet you, my name is Hino.
Have a seat.
what seems to be the problem?
All the time, someone is following me.
Someone..follows you?
Yes, it's an unknown man.
I'm absolutely sure he followed me today too.
I'm scare, can't bear this anymore.
That is scary, I'm sure.
Yes
Every day I'm worried about
being killed.
I'm also scared of crowds,
I don't go outside at night either,
I'm scared of watched behind.
I see, have you discussed this with someone?
My parents don't believe my story.
There is no one who can defend me.
Hoshino-san, why don't you take this
to the police?
I don't want to. I don't rely on something as the police.
I see.
Then, in the future, if you feel like
someone is following you,
while talking loudly on your phone,
please move to the place where
there are people who you can ask for help.
At any rate,
just be resolved to escape.
Yes.
Go out with your family and people you can trust on..
There is no such person! That's why
I came to see Dr. Hino!
If something happens, please help me.
Of course.
Dr.
you will not forsake me, right?
That's right.
If you feel some anxiety.
Please contact me at any time.
Yes.
I see, as expected you
when she talked about your mother,
you lose your cool.
Yes.
Oh.. thank you.
Seeing you with an usual average heart
it's rare.
That shows how serious you are about this
What?
I can tell because of that..right?
Those last words you retorted to her..
A mother like you,
should better disappear.
So, you are that serious
about saving that geisha's daughter.
Yes.
If that's the case,
then, just don't care about
how Ennoji thinks anymore!
Only about what you have to do!
Right?
Yes.
Right.
Senpai.
what?
Can I have something salty?
You, don't go and open anything.
That, don't open that, you!
Good luck with your thesis.
Good evening.
Dr...
So, you're able to come, Akira-san.
It's just that..all the Dr.'s contact data is gone.
Is that so.
Would you like to come inside
and talk about it?
Yasuke, I'm back~
Come in.
Excuse me for disturbing.
I'm back..~
Here.
Thank you
Akira-san, there's something I want
to ask you,
May I ask?
If you don't want to answer, it's fine.
Okay.
Similarly as today, that all your cellphone contact data
is gone,
Has this ever happened before?
Yes.
But..not just the contact data..
things like personal belongings
have increased.
How long has this been going on?
For about 8 years.
8 years ago.
At that time, did something important happen to you?
If you don't want to answer..
A little before that,
my mother appeared.
Your mother?
She wanted me to help her,
since she was having financial problems.
She told me to become a geisha.
So, you quit your job.
At that time, mom
told me for the first time,
that once I've made a lot of money,
we'll live together again.
She said, "This time, Akira-chan
will surely be happy"
Yet, I couldn't earn much money at all.
And mom's debts have
rapidly increased,
even though mom was trying her best,
I've been nothing but just a burden.
Akira-san,
you're not at fault.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Around the time
your mobile data disappeared,
anything strange happened?
Somehow I came to know,
that Yumeno, who occasionally speaks
from the back of my head,
was the one doing all those things.
She has been earning the money
in order to help me.
I see.
During her time, my time disappears.
I wonder if I'm going to disappear, too.
No.
Akira-san won't disappear.
On your birthday, we even went to the sea.
Anything you want,
your daily events,
the things you feel or think,
little by little, in this notebook,
why don't you write them?
Akira-san, I will serve you
as to connect the time
between you and Yumeno-san.
to connect both of our times?
Yes.
It's a dangerous thing to lose the reasoning power
to a thing called love.
Even though during the course of the treatment,
feelings similar to those of love arise,
eventually,
the patient is treated to the point when
they love someone else than the therapist.
It's the psychiatrist's job
to lead them to a happier life.
Inhale.
While picturing it.
Breath slowly..
Continue with a long exhalation.
How do you feel?
It has become a lot easier.
It has. I am happy for you.
Yes.
Yes?
The patient Hoshino Yoshimi-sama
wants to talk with Dr. Hino.
I understand.
Dr. Hino?
I'm really sorry, but
the doctor now it's in the middle of a consultation.
you can talk to me instead,
I'm Dr. Kawakami.
Hoshino-san, what is the problem?
Put Dr. Hino on the phone.
I'm being targeted by a stalker
Please quickly!
Please calm down.
Is the stalker nearby you?
I'm calling you because he is.
Is there anyone near
you can ask for help?
There's none,  because there's no one
I'm calling Dr. Hino
The doctor is really busy now,
first, let's call the police...
It's enough!
I can't bear your talk!
Dr., thank you very much.
If you become anxious...remember
Yes.
Dr. Hino! Just now, Hoshino-san called you.
Yup.
Because she said she was being chased by a stalker
I told her
to contact the police,
but she hung up the phone.
Kaoru-san
Yes.
Here.
Please leave your
message after the beep.
Hoshino-san, it's Hino from
the Toshiminami University Hospital, are you okay?
If something happens, please contact me right away.
I'll be waiting.
Sorry, I...
In the future, when a patient issues an SOS
call
please don't absolutely,
serve such answer.
Yes.
Whenever there is a call from Hoshino-san,
pass it on
Please communicated this to the doctor of the night shift.
I'm really sorry.
Huh ... I am still not there yet..
But, it's great, isn't it?
This thesis, finish it.
That's right.
I regularly
listen to Dr. Hino's recordings,
in order not to miss one word.
I've also read his book
and memorize it all,
it took me one year to complete it.
It looks like you are in love with Dr. Rintaro.
Yes, I really like him.
What?
The one called Yumeno,
mainly the face of the geisha,
owns the main personality.
The one called Akira,
the one who is in the process of opening her heart,
the original personality,
in other words, that means she is the one born into the body.
Yes.
So, how do you intend to treat her?
In her case, to make the two personalities,
recognize and align mutually
it's a good way to achieve
the integration process.
While respecting both personalities,
the treatment must advance
with a consistent attitude.
But, to achieve this,
The presence of the mother is a problem.
A gambling-dependent mother, right?
Yes.
the relationship of codependency formed with the daughter,
that's a burden.
Excuse me!
sorry to bother you so late at night,
Sorry.
Ruriko!
Good evening, Ikumi-sa ~n.
What do you want at this hour!
Excuse me for disturbing.
Go home!
Just leave!
I'll call the police!
Call them if you want..
Akira-san!
Get out!
Akira-san..
I'm really calling the police.
You're treating me like a stalker,
I'm her mother, you know?
You often say so, but..
Ah, that's right!
Yumeno is your biggest earner.
what a good money-spinner, right?
You've always tormented that child!
That child has become like this because of you!
Don't give that scary face.
I was bad ....
you know, I ..
I want to start again for real..
this time….
from the heart...
changing from the heart..
to start over with her, as a parent and child..
These are Akira-san's favorite candy.
could you..
could you do me the favor
of giving this to her..
You do not change at all.
When the circumstances get bad
you suddenly shed meek tears,
as looking sad..
You won't fool me anymore!
What are you doing!
Leave!
Do not show your face again!
Stop it!
do you... you
do you think you're protecting that child?
Akira-san..
you're here, right?
you're listening, right?
next time, both of us,
we are going to start over~
Leave!!
Akira-san, I'll come back again!
Mother...
LEAVE!!
But..
I know..
I know, but..
I've told you, the same as always, I'll gain the money
to help you.
Just forget already about that psychiatrist.
I'll be leaving to the conference.
Yes.
Excuse me,
Is Dr. Hino in here?
Could you knock before coming in?
I'm sorry, when
will he be back?
Where should I wait?
I'm sorry but the doctor
is in his day off.
It is a difficult case,
however, for Dr. Hasumi..
Tonight, the director has invited me, for The Azuma Odori
at Shinbashi, if you want to come..
Dr. Hasumi!
Are you okay?
Ah.. Rintaro.
Yes.
Look..
Ah.. right, I heard that last night you all went to drink, but..
Was there something unusual about Kawakami-kun?
Why?
No, it's just that a while ago,
she was acting strange
mm..maybe something is bothering her..
having received a warning from her beloved Rintaro.
Brother?
This is bad, Yasuke has disappeared.
Yasuke is not there?
There's more, the house is a mess!
All right...well..
I'll return immediately after I've finished
afternoon examination.
What happened to Yasuke?
Yasuke
seems to have disappeared.
What!
Could it be?
the same person that order the sushi...
Hey, I'll go look for Yasuke.
No, but...
Since, I'm done here for today, okay?
Madoka-chan.
Yuriko-san
Whoa..it's terrible.
I'm sure that geisha did this.
Mother, we should start preparing.
Where could Yumeno go?
In such an important day.
It's not around here.
Yeah.
good grief..
Hey, let's try asking that person there.
Okay.
Excuse me but, have you seen around here..
a white and of this size..
I'm sorry, to make you come.
No
I'll go look on that way.
Okay, I'll go this way.
Kawakami-san! Why are you here?
I wanted to apologize to Dr. Hino.
Now it's a bad time.
Wait.. Fukuhara-san
Rintaro!
Ah.. sorry Mizushima. How was it?
Bad, he's nowhere.
Brother!
Yasuke!
Yasuke.
thank goodness.
Yumeno-san
What were you trying to gain,
by doing such thing.
What is your grudge?
The rubbish scattered at home, that
was also you, right?
Madoka, calm down.
What are you trying to do!
Madoka.
But!
Could you take care of Yasuke?
Okay.
Let's go.
Akira-san, are you okay?
Ah.. I'm sorry.
Was it Yumeno, right? Yumeno was angry,
and did that to Yasuke..
It's okay, please calm down.
Yumeno-san is not the perpetrator.
Today she came to the hospital.
She wanted to see the doctor,
but the fact is that I sent her away.
I'm sorry.
So, that was what happened.
Akira-san, why did you go to the examining room?
Here.
Your hand..
If the perpetrator
isn't Yumeno-san, then..
Kawakami-san?
I'm coming in.
The doctor
borrowed this diary.
The doctor's laughing face.. is difficult
The sky is blue and the leaves are green..
now is the season I like the best.
[T/N]: she has the word "TRAITOR" written all over her body
I heard the sound of the sea with the doctor.
it still remains in my ears even now.
I found a four-leaf clover.
I want to make him laugh.
I want the doctor to laugh.
Is that Dr. Rintaro's mother?
eh?
Right.
She seems nice.
Yes, she was really nice.
Dr. Rintaro, even now, is trying to cure..
his mother's mind disease.
I feel sorry for Dr. Rintaro.
Please, don't worry,
Yumechiyo-san.
Yes. She's fine.
Okay, then.
Rintaro, since I've finished, I'll be going then.
Really?
Now, I'm doing some tea..
It was necessary for you, to tell her
even about your mother,
That's also treatment, I see.
Then, l'll let you talk
carefully with Akira-san.
Well then.
Mizushima
Thanks.
I must apologize to Akira-san.
As a result, Yumeno-san got angry
and you were the one that got hurt.
I'm sorry.
Yumeno-san, said she wanted to see
me, right?
Akira-san, from next week on,
why don't you come with Yumechiyo-san
to the examining room?
Am I that much bad?
That is something that I'm still not able to answer.
All I can say now, is that inside of you
there are two different persons, Akira-san and Yumeno-san.
Then through medical examination,
talking not just with you,
but also with Yumeno-san,
inquiring more and more
about you two.
So, that means
that we can't meet again like this?
We can still have a good talk at the examining room.
I'll take you to the Okiya today.
It's okay, I'll return alone.
But..
Because who I am now..
I want to say goodbye to the doctor as Akira.
Dr..
Could you hold me tight?
Akira-san, please remember one thing.
I'll keep my promise.
A~lways
I'll be by your side.
Dr. Hino, I have something to talk with you.
I'd like you to hear this.
Yes.
Dr., it's about Yumeno-san
Is that medical treatment?
or is it... love?
It's medical treatment.
Dr., aren't you in love with her?
I..
I'm in love with you.
Thank you, Kawakami-kun.
But, now it's not possible
for me to accept your feelings.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad I told you.
With this refreshing feeling
I'll be able to do the examination.
examination?
Dr., here is Hoshino Yoshimi-san.
Come in.
Have a seat.
I'll be in charge,
my name is Kawakami.
Wait, what?
Dr. Hino is the one on charge, isn't he?
Why are you in charge?
Hurry up and call the Dr.
I'll go home if you don't call him!
It's you who vandalized Dr. Hino's house, right?
Sorry.
These, I've read these.
Why do you have them?
Hoshino-san,
please listen to this!
I also,
have fallen in love with people I admire.
Huh? Don't make us even!
I also fell deeply in love,
I listened to his voice hundreds of times.
And even though I knew I shouldn't do it..
I also stood in front of his house many times.
Since I was a child, I was really selfish,
didn't have friends,
I really hated myself.
"I want to be different", that was always in my mind.
That's why I'm the same with you.
I also, after meeting Dr. Hino,
felt as if I was reborn.
"January 14
I read Dr. Hino's book,
and now, I also want to change."
Since I was little,
I was clueless and bad at reading situations,
and became hated by everyone."
"February 3
Today I saw Dr. Hino on TV."
"There is not such thing as perfection.
a passing mark without a perfect score is fine."
To think like this is fine."
Although I was worried about a thing at work,
I was really saved by the doctor's words. "
"March 6. Today too,
I watched Dr. Hino on TV"
"When you lose your confidence ... "
each day,
"please, try to find one positive thing about yourself."
"By doing so after a month, you will become self-confident."
Hoshino-san, you in this way, always
have been receiving important things from the doctor,
Isn't it because you want to
properly start over that you came?
However, if you continue this way,
the important words taught by the Dr.,
and lots of warm words,
don't you feel like you'll lose all of them?
Falling in love with someone
who doesn't return your feelings
is painful.
But losing the important things you received from
the person you love,
I think it's even more painful.
Hoshino-san,
the feelings when falling in love with someone,
are in no way something bad.
Won't you make a fresh start in life,
again, together with me?
If so then,
please call Dr. Hino.
please, let me hear his voice just once more.
Dr. Hino..
Hoshino-san
Is it okay if I talk first?
I was looking for my dog desperately.
For you it might be only another person's pet, but
but for me, he is an irreplaceable
important family member.
In the same way as that house.
I inherited that house from my parents,
I treasure being able to use it.
It may be old, but it's full of family memories
from my childhood.
it's a precious house for me.
Such house,
you have dishonored.
I'm very hurt by that.
Hoshino-san, do you have something to tell me?
I see.
Then, excuse me.
I suspect that Hoshino-san has a mild form of
borderline personality disorder
and factitious disorder.
If the healer wants to reach the patient
with his words, in this case
it's important to convey that by stalking the other party,
she has personally hurt the victim,
and to communicate this very clearly
but in a polite way.
If she is allowed to calmly understand the situation,
the patient can be discouraged from continuing such behavior.
Then, surely, Hoshino-san,
will be able to make a new step forward.
I'm really sorry for doing something
arbitrary today.
Is that so.
But, to reach the patient with the attitude
instead of making them
remained cornered,
I think it was really good.
I think that approach shook
Hoshino-san's feelings, isn't it?
As a party of the stalking incident, I
can't carry out Hoshino-san's treatment.
Dr. Kawakami.
I'm leaving Hoshino-san under your care.
Please, continue to get closer
to her heart.
Yes.
There are no final answers in medical treatment.
When doubting or when troubled,
continue to listen to the voice of the patient's heart.
I think that's the most important thing.
From now on, I have my hopes on you.
Thank you very much.
Dr.,
Could you have a look at this?
Yes.
Of course.
Dr.
Please, I'll leave her under your care.
Yumechiyo-san,
please wait at the waiting room.
Yes.
Hi, Akira-san.
You were able to come back.
Dr..
could you hold me tight?
Yes.
Subs by Kitty-nyan
*´¨)
¸.•´¸.•*´¨) ¸.•*¨)
(¸.•´ (¸.•` ¤ (\_(\
¤ (=' :')
¤.. (,('')('') .. ¤
¤ Chuline ¤