Last week, the chief secretary was issued illegal donations
This week, it'll be the rant on that minister.
Why it's only me
the one that have to face those reporters that
want to tear me apart?
You're right.
There are particularly two nasty reporters
Those guys when I have a troubled face
they grin..
That's bullying!
More..
Those guys, are space aliens!
Because space aliens don't understand
the human feelings.
They hurt me cold blooded
Ah.. I wish there was a sort of a barrier
to protect me from those guys
Let's make it.
eh?
To repel any nasty alien attack
let's create a barrier.
The button is here.
May I? If you press this button,
you'll become the strongest.
There will be no fear to any alien.
Is that so?
It is time.
Dr. Hino, for this sudden request,
Thank you very much.
It's good, just wait outside a bit more!
Dr., there is still a lot
of things I want you to hear,
if you could prolong this.
How about having lunch? I'll treat you
Thank you.
But I already have plans.
Huh?
Ike-san, the button for the barrier.
Please don't forget it.
It looks good!
Then, if you excuse me.
Ah Dr.
Dr.!
"Why don't you come at least once to my examining room?"
"examining room?"
"At lunch break, we'll have a cup of tea together."
Dr. Hino, what would you like to do for lunch?
After all,
you want the daily meal, isn't it?
Again?
Yeah, because in the daily meal
you have something for each day.
I brought it today.
It's unusual.
Ah, that means you're economizing?
Because you're cheated by the geisha
with 3 million yen.
What's that story?
The money has been properly returned.
I'm happy for you.
You're happy for what?
But..
That might be the trick, right?
Huh?
Once she returns the money, you trust her
next time, she'll demand a lot of money.
Well, that's the common trick.
Is that so?
Thank you very much for the advice.
If you don't hurry
the daily will be sold out soon.
Huh?
Ah, I'll hurry!
Hey, what were you talking about?
Ask Yumeno to come.
Okay.
Hey, those bad manners!
Here, it's done.
do this properly.
Sister.
Lunch's ready
All right, I'll go just now
The soba will grow stale.
Please come soon.
She's not coming today, right?
Dr. Rintaro, are you coming
to the afternoon conference, right?
Coming.
"Yumeno-san"
The 7 million yen, 7 million.
I KNOW!
She hung up..
Reach!
Long!
Almost reach.
Enough..
Ah bring your brains!
It's always the same with you!
What? What's the matter?
It's too persistent.
Who?
That Dr. Hino
that psychiatry Dr.?
Report to the police..
What do you mean?
I thought about asking the decision
from the professors of psychiatry first.
About Kobayashi Yumiko-san,
35 years old
She fell from the stairs and hit his left side of the abdomen
the results of the MRI revealed
a traumatic spleen injury
By means of an emergency laparotomy, we've removed the spleen
However, it's unlikely that because of the fall,
she would have multiple bruises..
She also came half a month ago for chest bruises.
The cause was the same as this time,
falling from the stairs.
So?
DV.
There is a possibility that she is suffering
Domestic Violence.
That's why the police.
Let's quit this.
The Dir. dislikes this kind of cases the most.
Did you say something?
I didn't say a thing.
Certainly, it's because it was troublesome last year,
it was a false accusation.
False accusation?
The nurses
without authorization from above,
reported the suspicion of DV.
It was just an act performed by the wife.
She just wanted to break up with him, and made the bruises by herself.
Thanks to that, the director has been struggling
with the husband's nearly lawsuit
But, this time is clear by the marks
that she has been beaten by someone.
I've seen these type of injuries for years.
If we do not protect the victim early from the DV problem,
There is also a possibility that the risk extends to life.
I know about that.
Quit the report.
Why?
Because it's troublesome?
Excuse me! She is also my patient.
Even in adults, because they are afraid of the DV perpetrator
they don't want to recognize..
Residents stay in silence.
well..
Yes??
May I ask to talk with Kobayashi Yumiko-san?
That's a face that will likely judge without permission.
Be sure to ask permission from Prof. Hasumi
if you by any chance want to report the case.
Understood.
These are very beautiful flowers!
They are called "preserved flowers".
My husband brought them.
Really?
That's a nice husband.
Yes.
This one, what flower is it?
Gerbera. (African daisy)
It's a gerbera!
haha
What?
Ah, it's just that the Dr.
doesn't know a gerbera..
Sorry
Ah, well, you're Dr...
Sorry about the late introduction,
I'm a psychiatrist, my name is Hino.
psychiatrist ..
I heard that you fell down the stairs.
What is it that you would like to know?
May I ask you one question?
This is something we ask everyone
with the similar injuries you have.
Did someone exert some sort of violence over you?
No one.
Did you suspect it was DV?
My husband is a member of the Tokyo Metropolitan Police Department.
He holds his work proudly and diligently,
with a strong sense of justice.
He is also very respected by many
of his subordinates.
It's not the type of person that would use violence.
I see.
I see,
it's nice that you could clarify it.
If there's anything that is troubling you,
please feel free to say it.
I want to give Yumiko-san
the strength
so you can recover immediately.
Thank you for being so gently.
My wife is under your care,
I'm Kobayashi
I'm a psychiatrist, my name is Hino.
I came to talk a little about the symptoms.
So, take care.
Excuse me.
Thank you, we'll be under your care.
I brought you a change of clothes｡
Thank you.
Dr. Hino, why didn't you ask her
more deeply about the situation?
My favorite comedian has this saying,
"To hear too much is useless when the person is not talking"
But
don't you think she's lying?
Yeah, but Kawakami-kun
The person in question has denied the DV.
Did you drop the ballpoint pen on purpose, right?
Yes.
Did you?
DV victims would overreact to even minor sounds.
But Yumiko-san did not react.
But, police officers usually suffer
from stress and
there is a theory that they often become DV perpetrators.
If it's DV and we don't grasp evidence,
before she leaves the hospital,
it may be serious..
First, let's get close to the patient's heart.
It's dangerous to judge based on preconceptions.
So, now let's move forward with no fear!
I'm your ally.
This is a story of a doctor that saves
the lost sheep of this modern era.
Sorry for the late introduction,
I'm a psychiatrist, Hino Rintaro
How about 500,000 yen?
Huh?
Isn't it Crocodile?
Moreover, with no use.
500 000 is too cheap, isn't it?
But you see, in the market..
Please, I'm in trouble.
Help me.
¥ 505,000.
Please, 510 000!
Oh, Dr.
Haven't you eat yet?
Ah yes.
I wonder if it's okay to bring your lunch to the examination room.
People who are traumatized
there are many times when they aren't able
to come on time.
I want to wait for them.
Dr., there's no meaning in that
if your health is damaged.
Thank you.
Not at all.
By the way, Kaoru-san
Yes.
Do you like gerberas?
I like them, they are cute.
Gerbera has a lot of meaning
in the language of flowers.
Language of flowers? eh..
Then, Dr.
please eat properly, okay?
I'll be leaving first.
So, see you tomorrow
See you tomorrow
the language of flowers..
Yes.
Yumechiyo-san.
Good evening.
Is there anything wrong?
It's a rare match.
If there's something wrong?
What did you intend by calling Yumeno to come here?
It's about that..
The fact is that..
I wanted to have an opportunity to talk to Yumeno-san,
it was an invitation.
to have a talk? Yumechiyo, that's an outing?
Yeah, that will be outing,
not a medical examination.
The charging will be ten times the cost.
Plea..Please wait a minute!
It's a joke.
It's just that Yumeno it's an important geisha at our house.
Either if you meet at the house,
or if you go outside,
please you should not extend your words so much.
I'm sorry.
Yumeno found your invitation
a little too frequent, let's say.
Eh?
In short you're too nagging.
You should go moderate on this too.
From Yumeno's point of view,
you're just a father.
About the DV matter..
The husband seems to be a member
of the Metropolitan Police Department, right?
draw back from this
and leave it to the surgery department.
Okay?
Sorry to disturb you.
En-sama, my stomach is making noise already..
You,
having the Dir. and the Okiya's mother..
Those two are a little tough.
They ARE, and more I
was treated as if I was a person obsessed with sex,
It's ultra upsetting!
to say that for real
you're not obsessed with it, are you?
I'm not.
It's a strange women.
inviting you so excitedly,
then abruptly refusing you
The service is becoming exceedingly crazy
That's why I'm worried.
Stop getting involved
Okay?
So, what is it that you have been eating,
that..
It's a Pork shogayaki sandwich
eh, did you make it?
Yes, although
it's just inserting it between bread, but
It's good, right?
nah, as expected this is better.
Oh, really?
I heard it,
that you have been recommended to become a professor
Who told you that?
I have many connections.
If you're able to properly ascend the stairs
that are in front of you,
you're going to be able to save as many patients as possible, right?
If you penetrate such policy
it's convenient, it'll give you influence.
Listen
Do not get involved with that strange woman.
Okay?
Today too, you've stayed in the hos..
Eh?
Today too, you've stayed in the hospital?
Yes.
Kawakami-san just, just a moment!
eh..what?
That's bad Kawakami-san
to be watching at the patients?
Then, who will defend them?
You're going to far.
I..
it's the first time I'm not able
to save the patient I'm in charge of.
The DV victims
need the help of a third party!
Good morning.
Yes, regarding the matter of
the consultation with head detective Shimada
I'll immediately extend to you the report.
Yes, I'm sorry
Thank you very much.
Kobayashi-san
Good morning.
Ah good morning.
This time I'll introduce myself properly,
I'll be under your care.
I will received it.
Dr. Hino, you are a psychiatric doctor, right?
Yes.
Did you hear it from my wife?
The reason that she fell from the stairs.
Yes.
What was it?
Just to have been half asleep.
Just that?
Yes.
Is that so..
You're concerned right? about no knowing the cause.
Well yeah.
It's just that it seems to me like your wife
is hiding something
eh?
Just a minute.
Yes
I'm sorry I've kept you waiting.
No, no.
You think she is hiding something?
Just, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Oh ... I didn't say such a thing.
What are you thinking!!
Whose instructions are those?
It's okay, just follow my instructions!!
It's not possible for him to suppress the anger,
also has very intense emotional ups and downs
As it's commonly seen in DV perpetrators.
Sorry
It's okay.
It's has been a little busy at work lately.
I see
You're very busy, right?
Then, shouldn't you be relaxing at home for a couple of hours..
Ah, I really can't.
Unfortunately, we don't have any children,
at this moment, my wife situation
will just give me lonely thoughts.
I see..
Here, take it
Oh, I'm sorry
Thank you.
But, I think that your wife has become
someone you want to cherish
with great care, right? Kobayashi-san?
I recall have seen the preserved flowers
in her hospital bedroom.
Oh No, no, that's embarrassing.
In this room..
will you be able to properly rest?
Well, even though it's a bit of poor sleep,
it's still a little better than having to return home..
I see.
And what about your wife?
Has she been lately in a stressful situation?
Huh? Well, I couldn't say..
If one of us is full of stress,
is more likely to be me.
That would be all?
Since I have to stay.
Ah, that's right.
Thank you very much for your time.
Dr. Mizushima
Your wound looks good.
Why did you send me that psychiatric Dr.?
Eh?
It's because you suspected of DV from my husband?
That is a complete insult to my husband
What on earth are you going with that?
About that..
On no account,
we are being affected by that at all.
Please tell Dr. Hino that
I understand.
Yuriko, I'm leaving now
Ah..have a nice day.
Ah, hello En-sama?
Again, I have another consultation...
I'm willing to hear anything from the cute Yumeno
It's just that tomorrow I have a meeting.
Eh..again an adult reunion
I can't go?
I'll go for sure next week.
You promise?
Okay, okay.
I understand.
Yumeno, we have inquired
Dr. Hino very sharply, we've told him,
If you continue being so insistent,
don't come to the geisha house.
I'm leaving.
we want to know about the 7 million quickly
[T/N: written many times]
Irresponsible Akira-chan,
answer me!
It's enough, you're drinking too much.
Even I..you know.
I'm irresponsible at wanting to wash my feet..
such a thing..
We don't get to do only what we
like to do..you know?
Thanks..
Jun-chan, you're a kind guy...
Hurry, bring me some sake, hurry
It's enough..
Pay those 7 million.
What are you looking at?
Stop it.
Dr.
Thank you very much.
Please take care in your way home.
We've done for today.
Dr. your phone is ringing.
It's true.
Here you have.
Yes.
You two, it's okay if I'll leave
ahead of you today?
Yes.
See you tomorrow.
Dr.
Yes!
You're forgetting your jacket.
Ah, thank you.
Until tomorrow then.
Until tomorrow.
Yasuke
Yumeno-san
Ah, welcome home
I wanted to see you.
Hino-rin, I'm sorry
When I told mom that you
had invited me to tea,
for some reason it become a big deal.
No, no.
Let's have a pleasant talk.
I'm really sorry.
eh?
It's okay.
Aren't you going to invite me in?
Please.
Wait, if you get in,
then it becomes an outing?
No, wait wait, at this point,
is it already outing?
It's okay if it's a secret.
I see, then come in.
I'm going to put some tea.
Please have a seat.
eh.. then this is Hino-rin's house.
There are a lot of books
So, what is that you wanted to talk about?
Please, without asking anything
lend me 7 million yen, please!
7 million?
I don't have anyone else to depend on,
please!
Wait, but,
Why so much money?
It's absolutely necessary.
Of course, I don't intend to get it for free,
I..came with the intention.
What's that intention?
I won't go home tonight.
You won't return home!
I'll
become yours, take me Hino-rin.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute, Yumeno-san!
Hino-rin..
Fall in love with me..
Yumeno-san, please let's calm down.
I understood the part about the money,
if there's anything I can do,
I'll do anything that it's at my reach.
Rintaro
Mizushima!
Hey, what are you doing!
This has nothing to do with you!
Even so, I'm stopping it,
because it's strange.
You're trying to get money
from Rintaro
What is your purpose?
Mizushima, you see..
Explain it!
Excuse me,
may I borrow your washroom?
Where is it?
The washroom, it's..
Over there..
Over there!
Rintaro, you too,
that's the lowest thing for a man to do.
You're wrong.
In what I'm wrong?
What is going on? with that girl,
she's weird.
That's why..
that's why I wanted to hear her story.
Because I want to know her true face.
Huh?
She's hiding her true face in a shadow of lies.
She said it,
"Always by myself,
always so lonely."
Always by myself..
Always so lonely..
Yumeno-san?
Yumeno-san!
When the SOS sign is out,
It can not be something that you pretend not to notice.
Rintaro
Have a nice day
I do not want to regret anymore.
You told her, if there was something you
could do to help her, right?
You probably want to help Yumeno-san with your strength.
the Dr. Rintaro.
About that, I was clearly told by
Kobayashi Yumiko-san
On no account,
she wants to have something with you.
I think there's something awkward with that couple.
What!?
Hino-kun,
do you know the reason why I called you?
No.
You has been selling that you hear people's stories
But, the truth is that you don't listen them at all.
Eh?
The patients suspected of DV violence
came to say that they're changing to the police hospital
as soon as possible.
Yumiko-san?
Our hospital is that much hated.
Even though they are surgical patients,
psychiatrists have been persistently hearing and watching them,
for being suspected as a case of domestic violence.
Isn't it true that you have been persistently monitoring
husband and wife?
No,
to say that I persistently listen to them..
That is something that the other party decides,
that's why I told you,
It's in the pointless talk with the patient,
that the unnecessary problems begin.
It's not something pointless,
it's a necessary talk.
Anyway,
We are within a few days from the scratch of the state.
In the meantime,
do not speak at all with the patient or their family.
No, just one time more
I need to speak with them.
Hear the story of the patients in one talk.
Your answer?
Yes..
It's a big mess.
The virtuoso of psychotherapy
is not getting sympathetic to the patient.
So, the ones that have been monitoring were you guys.
Yes.
Sorry about doing something on our own.
But, I was worried about Yumiko-san.
I see.
So then, what do you know?
From the husband's room, very early in the morning,
there were a loud voice and a sound.
Voice and sound?
Yes.
But, later this morning, without any other incident,
he just went to work in 7:00.
A loud voice and a sound..
Ah, good evening.
Well, even though it's a bit of poor sleep,
Chronic lack of sleep
What are you thinking!
irritating moodiness
If one of us is full of stress,
is more likely to be me.
carrying stress everyday
I have no choice but to try
It's okay for today.
Okay.
Alright.
ah.. since also today, I'm going to stay here,
If you need something..
Good night.
Yeah, good night.
Sorry, sorry
here we go...
Yes, come in.
Excuse me..
I'm really sorry for the intrusion,
but you see, I had a sleepless night,
I know it's shameless, but I ask you this favor.
since there isn't any other duty room empty,
excuse me.
I'll ask your help in sharing the room only tonight.
Then, good night.
I wonder what is Dr. Hino thinking to do..
I don't think he can do this
for many nights, right?
Hi, excuse me,
yes.. I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
Sorry..
I'm not sorry!! Stupid!
Hey!
Kobayashi-san?
It hurts, hurts, hurts
hurts, hurts, hurts!
Dr.!
Here.
Ah.. excuse me.
That wound? how?
I've heard that recently,
you can't sleep well,
you have lack of sleep?
Ah, yes.
Have you experienced something different
while sleeping?
When having a relatively light REM sleep
the things that happen in the dream,
would in fact trigger real actions.
For example, if while dreaming you're shouting,
you would be really shouting.
If in the dream you're hitting,
you would be really hitting.
Such condition is called
REM sleep behavior disorder.
So it was me after all..
That's why she couldn't look me in the eyes.
I'm really sorry.
To do such a thing even to the Dr..
Don't worry.
For a long time, vaguely,
I've been having this strange feeling.
But I couldn't remember.
But, if I think about it,
I wasn't conscious of this doing.
You're right.
But, whys is it
that my wife didn't tell me about it?
If I was the one causing the injuries.
If it was me and my head what was acting strange.
I don't see why
my wife is not hating it.
If I consider it myself,
I no longer understand myself.
But, she is like,
this time, even the previous time, just said
"I'm fine,
it was only that I feel down the stairs,
don't worry, just go to work" she said.
That's all, she didn't say anything else.
I see.
Maybe your wife was also puzzled,
and thinking about her usual kind husband,
didn't want to say
to you the truth about this matter.
Here.
yeah, that might be the case.
If you have seen my wife,
that was all,
we no longer speak about anything.
while I was doing such a horrible thing..
So scared she couldn't say anything.
I'm a pathetic men.
You're not pathetic.
I can see it very well.
Kobayashi-san has a strong sense of responsibility.
So I think that in order to seek for a perfect resolution,
you would do your best.
Your own weaknesses and also
your own mistakes,
you won't just accept them.
And because you love your wife,
and because you don't want to disappoint your wife
Aiming for extra perfection,
I'm sure you are working really hard.
I can see that very clear.
Accepting yourself is a very difficult thing.
Because there aren't just good things,
there are also a lot of defects
But she has accept you,
all of you with the good and the bad.
I think it's a great thing.
Dr...
What should I do?
First,
let's consider your disease.
Yes.
Let's seat.
Kobayashi-san
This is a disease that is said to develop if there is a problem
with the function of the brain.
If it's treat it it can improve in most cases.
It's a disease that develops well.
In this case,
by adding extreme stress,
it seems that it made the symptoms
not easy to appear
Stress?
Any sort of big anxiety
You don't have to burden it by yourself, right?
for your wife's sake too
First,
why don't we start with an examination?
I understand.
I'll consider it.
"You're not alone."
"Let's drink tea together."
The legislator of the government political party,
has received the illegal donation of 20 million yen
from the security company,
of the Tokyo Metropolitan Police Department OB chaired officers.
Today's daily special looks good, right?
Yes.
Then, let's eat.
Let's eat.
Furthermore, the incumbent of the Metropolitan Police Dept. incumbent,
is also going to be prosecuted for this issue.
Also the Superintendent Kobayashi Tsukasa..
Eh?
The facts of this illegal donations had been concealed for a long time..
Superintendent Kobayashi?
Kobayashi-san, please calm down!
Let
please, calm down!
Let go!
Where did that psychiatrist go!?
Let me go!!
Minister,
this is another fraud from the government allied party, right?
Ugh ... no ....
so.. that ....
those are space aliens..
I would like to closely explained the circumstances,
of the incident of the previous question
today, and openly ....
Today's Ike-san is stirring..
Do you also want to ask soba?
Yumiko-san
Dr. Hino, you're an awful person.
What I was trying to protect,
you crushed it all..
Hey, now that the politician fraud has been accused,
What's going to happen to him?
It wasn't just my husband,
he wasn't the only one being used!
And though he did anything wrong..
Yet, this thing happened!
It's all the doctor's fault!
Yumiko-san.
To that person,
I wasn't able to give him a child,
and he cherishes me without blaming me even once.
Even though he was really busy,
he found a Gerbera and bought it for me.
Being just the two of us at home,
he always protects me as a treasure.
So this time,
it was my turn to protect him!
Dr., you have the tendency to misunderstand everything..
Why did you break us!?
These were 'preserved flowers', right?
Its moment of beauty is confined
by immersing them in a special fluid.
eh.. what is that?
Yumiko-san, what you were trying to protect
the thing you didn't want to be destroyed,
isn't something similar to the 'preserved flowers'?
Aren't you trying to lock up the shape of happiness inside of yourself
confining it inside?
confine?
I was glad to remain in that way!
Only if I could put up with it..
I was..
I was okay anyhow!
It isn't the case to be okay anyhow.
Yumiko-san you're not fine anyhow.
Your husband,
as you mentioned,
is a respectable person with a strong sense of justice.
That's why this time,
for the sake of heading towards to your happiness,
I think he took a new step forward.
Isn't that a wonderful thing? Don't you think?
Your husband has placed here,
a white Gerbera.
Are you familiar with the flower language?
It means 'hope'
Yes.
You are the hope for your husband.
You are an important person for your husband.
You're not fine anyhow.
Yumiko-san, for your husband's sake,
for your own sake too,
please, how about searching for happiness?
If there's something that troubles you,
I'll be willing to listen to you at any time.
I'm your and your husband's ally
The door of my examination room is always open.
Then, I'll be leaving for today.
Take care.
Here, please.
Yes.
Yumeno-san?
Yes, excuse me.
About the issue of Kobayashi Yumiko-san changing hospital
she has withdrawn the request.
Was Hino-kun the one that uncovered
the illegal donations of politicians?
Just like a detective, right?
It's an interesting candidate for professor.
Yes.
I think he will return immediately.
Please take a seat and wait here.
Yes.
Since Yumeno-san came,
I've asked her to wait in the examination room.
Okay, thank you.
Yumeno-san, sorry to keep you waiting..
Hello,
I see you were able to come.
why..
Always by yourself..
always you're so lonely, right?
It's okay now, I'm here.
Why?
Because..
I'm a psychiatrist.
A doctor of the heart.
We were facing as two people
who meet for the first time.
Subs by Kitty-nyan
*´¨)
¸.•´¸.•*´¨) ¸.•*¨)
(¸.•´ (¸.•` ¤ (\_(\
¤ (=' :')
¤.. (,('')('') .. ¤
¤ Chuline ¤