Always alone,
always lonely..
Hino-kun
How are you going to take responsibility on this?
As expected, it's embarrassing,
having this kind of picture
seen by so many people.
Is there even time for that?
The question is
if this is an ethical issue as a doctor
This will cost the hospital's reputation!
As a doctor,
I'm prepared to take all the responsibilities
if there are complains
related to the treatment.
But, before that, at least,
I'd like to discuss it with the person herself.
You've no chance of convincing the other party,
this will surely become a lawsuit.
I think this is the result
of a sort of misunderstanding,
misunderstanding?
During the sakura's full boom,
isn't it a nice atmosphere?
Did she need rescue breathing
during the flower viewing?
The kiss certainly happened.
But, it's close to an accident.
If we could have a talk..
Hino! that much is enough.
Director, do you know the origin of the picture,
in order to understand this?
Miyagawa, what about that?
I got the picture from
an acquaintance, just that.
An acquaintance?
Did you sell it to the magazine?
It..it wasn't me.
Then,
say it, who sold it!
Hino-kun
Yes.
For the time being, you'll remain in house confinement.
Please wait.
Today, I have to examine many other patients.
Your patients will be delegated to another doctor.
Ask him to enter.
Hello.
Senpai..
Everyone, it's been a while.
Senpai, what does it mean?
Dir. Ennoji asked me to do this.
Help me with Hino's problem.
What about senpai's patients?
Well, for the time being, until your issue
has calmed down, I'll examine them here.
What, wait... what's this, you!
You have emotional sweating, senpai,
you are hiding something!
It's because you're holding it.
I did not lie.
So, what do you mean by that?
I also have my own circumstances.
However, I can't tell it to you.
Anyway, until everything cools down,
here, leave it to me.
I got it, then,
since I'm properly transferring the control here,
please take care of my patients.
What?, are you really okay with this?
Since I wouldn't entrust people to anyone else but you.
Please let us see Dr. Hino.
We want to receive a comment for this article.
This is an inconvenience for the patients.
Please remain quiet.
Is this also part of the emphatic treatment
that Dr. Hino specializes in?
How could that be the case!
Fukuhara-kun!
Wait, Dr. Fukuhara, it's useless!
Do you want to say something about the geisha Yumeno-san?
Please be quiet! Here is a hospital!
Please leave this to me.
Dr. Hino, what does it mean?
Didn't you tell me if I wanted to be
a good psychiatrist, I should refrain from love?
And even
you said such a thing,
isn't this the complete opposite?
I'm really sorry
it ended up in such a commotion
Are you admitting it?
But that was
something like an accidental encounter,
it isn't love.
And what kind of kiss was that?
That is the kiss as shown in the picture.
So then, during my house confinement
Dr. Araki will take my place
and he's willing to do the examination,
Fukuhara-kun, please give him support.
That was without doubts a love kiss..!
Mizushima, I have a request.
I'd like you to observe closely to Araki senpai.
What do you mean?
Even though senpai is an excellent psychiatrist,
the truth is he is under a treatment for an eating disorder.
Today, he didn't bring any food on his bag.
Probably, he intends to get it somewhere.
He's quite bad?
Recently, it looks like it's rapidly deteriorating,
that's worrying.
I'm feeling bad, move away.
Look, do you think it's the time
to worry about others?
It's because I'm fine.
I'll entrust him to you.
I understand.
Miyagawa lacks the guts, even for the small things,
more than expected.
Hasumi is not likely
to succeed as a surgeon beyond this point.
Hino can't answer to my expectations,
he's now escaping from this commotion with the geisha.
The new hospital, on the views of an extra-aged society,
will be aimed to develop a leading medical care
,including psychiatry.
What do you think about being entrusted
the position of director in this new hospital?
I wish I could live up to your expectations.
Really..
What on earth happened to the doctors in here?
So, now let's move forward with no fear!
I'm your ally.
This is a story of a doctor that saves
the lost sheep of this modern era.
Sorry for the late introduction,
I'm a psychiatrist, Hino Rintaro
Madoka?
Hey Madoka,
what's going on?
Is not like you,
to do such a thing.
Eh?
When mom died, remember?
you said this..
"Don't worry, I'm here", you said.
"I'll protect you"
I knew that, even without you saying it.
while I was crying alone here.
But, since then,
I haven't cry like that again, right?
You had to work part time for my good,
study a lot, a lot
you were also the one bringing the money,
always making dinner,
at sports day, also parents' day,
you were there.
Even if mom was not there,
because my brother was there,
I didn't need to cry.
For that kind of brother,
I have nothing but respect.
No matter what, I trust
in my brother!
Madoka..
Hello.
Dr.?
I'm sorry.
I will no longer meet you,Dr.
There's no need for something like that,
please contact me anytime.
But..
Didn't I promise you?
To remain by your side always.
Dr...
Yumeno-san!
You are at home, right?
Wouldn't you let us hear your story?
Yumeno-san!
Please, let us see Yumeno-san!
She is in here, right?
Yumeno-san! Yumeno-san!
Yumeno is not here,
please leave.
You are to noisy.
Yumeno-san!
Yumeno..
You were the one selling that article, right?
To the weekly magazine?
Of course not, I couldn't do such a stingy thing.
Are you suing Dr. Hino?
Who do you think I am?
I'm Shinbashi's dream.
If you want to hear the story of a geisha
properly pay the fees.
Please come to the parlor, okay?
Now, leave, leave!
Mother, spread some salt
Yumeno..
Please return.
You're intruding!
I've something important to talk to the Director!
En-sama, it's been a while.
Excuse me..
Could it be that you forgot this face?
Kikuchiyo?
My daughter seems to have been under your care.
Daughter?
Yumeno is my daughter.
Yumeno is yours?
That girl had to experience such a thing,
so I couldn't keep it quiet.
I wanted to discuss it with you personally.
In other words, money?
That Kikuchiyo who competed against Yumechiyo,
to become Shinbashi's number one,
has now come to ruin.
The visitor is leaving.
Here is not the place to come
with extortions. Leave
Do not say such a vile thing!
If that's the case
I'm leaving a place like this!
Be ready!
Yumeno is my daughter after all!
What about it!
I apologize for causing you any worry.
How did you end up like this, doctor?
I'm troubled, by such a thing.
You are a doctor, right?
My attending doctor, right?
Are you trying to quit as a doctor?
Minister, national politics are the same as examination.
The most important thing to save in a person
is not a credential.
I wonder about that..
Actually, I'm in trouble.
What's the problem?
The problem has become a dilemma.
A dilemma?
I can't tell you the details, but
I'm caught between the interests of two sides.
As a politician?
Of course.
Which one should be discarded.
Once discarded, it puts me at a risky situation.
A dilemma..
This is..
Is this the situation?
What are you doing?
That means that it has caught your finger
and it's causing you pain
Hurts, hurts, hurts.
There's no other way but to break one of the chopsticks.
No, that's..
Ike-san, please think this carefully.
What's the most important thing to save?
That is, Ike-san's finger, right?
If that's the case,
there's no other way but to cut down
one of the sides, right?
Yeah.
Eh, this much? Why?
Perhaps the reporters will come here too, right?
if that's so, I thought you wouldn't be able to buy anything.
Thank you.
Maybe I bought a little too much.
Dr. Araki
didn't do anything unusual today.
I see.
Yeah.
So, should I prepare karaage?
That photo with the full cherry blossom,
it's from about two months, right?
Yup
Rintaro, you were kissed by Yumeno-san?
Or was it Akira-san?
I don't know that.
In those days I wasn't aware of her illness yet.
Though you said it's an accident,
it's actually that she did it suddenly?
Yeah, but
it became an opportunity to know
she was unstable
that could meant step one
on her diagnosis and treatment.
The first step on her treatment?
Are you being serious?
Of course.
What you are doing is really cruel, you know?
Why?
You can't see anything but her illness.
It's 'cause I'm her doctor.
You are an excellent psychiatrist,
everyone knows that, I also respect you.
But if I were her,
I'd like you to really look at me,
and not just the disease.
Wait a minute,
didn't you say it?
to cross over the patient-doctor's boundary?
Having a relation between doctor and patient
and when a thing like that happened
are two different things.
The one afraid of crossing that line
is probably Rintaro, right?
What do you mean?
Rintaro,
in order to be a good psychiatrist
you've always kept love at a distance.
But, that
wasn't just because you didn't want to get hurt?
Sorry..
Even if you apologize now,
I got awfully hurt.
Rintaro, I'll let you know a good thing.
There are two types of kiss for a woman.
An unforgettable kiss even till death.
And the kiss you deadly want to forget.
Thanks for the food.
What about the karaage?
Mm.
Tomorrow, I'm also replacing Dr. Hasumi's
operations very early.
I see.
Is it that I just don't want to get hurt?
Hello.
Good evening Dr. Hino.
Dr., it looks like you'll be fired
from the hospital, right?
It must be hard.
Aizawa Ruriko-san,
please tell me what you want.
Can we meet at the Okiya tomorrow?
I want you to bring the 50 million
I requested the other day.
Otherwise, the commotion
at the weekly magazine won't finish.
It was you the one who sell that article,
isn't it?
Then, until tomorrow.
The money, is it ready?
No
Then, why did you come?
You've lost,
you don't have other choice.
I won't give you any money.
Well the, I'll see in court.
We'll sue you and the hospital.
You are in need for treatment
for your gambling addiction problem.
If I give you money,
you'll spend it all on gambling,
and the disease will get worse.
Not only Akira,
but you're saying I'm also sick,
that's how you deceived her,
it won't work on me!
It was you who sell that photo
for money, isn't it?
Yeah, if it something is profitable
I'll sell it.
Even if you are her mother..
Why? Tell me!
Do you want me to say
that I'd even sell Akira?
You don't get it, right?
That girl
it's living because of me, you know.
Me and Akira we're mother and daughter,
We're connected by a strong bond.
Someone like you,
how much are you
willing to carelessly hurt her?
You took Ennoji from me!
Huh?
It's the revenge!
Ikumi, you had everything.
You had beauty and intelligence,
and you dance was good. Everything!
But Akira,
she won't lose against your talent.
So I'll annoy you!
That girl is my substitute!
You're just seeking for money, right?
Do not say such unreasonable words!
How much that girl was waiting
for you to return,
you don't know, right?
To come out in front of people was really difficult for her.
But she became a geisha because you have debts.
she learned to dance because of you,
working hard, really hard, doing her best.
Up to a point she got sick..
you, that don't know any oh her hardships
don't come and call yourself her mother
when it's convenient to you!
The mother..
The mother is me, only me.
This time, I'll win.
Yumeno..
Since that photo went out,
I've really wanted to see you.
Just kidding!
Come for a moment.
Akira is a fool, for wanting to be love
by such a crazy mother, right?
I don't think so.
Oh, that's right.
You have a big Oedipus complex, too, right?
You're still dragging along
your mother's suicide, right?
It might be so.
I, just now, step on a sensitive topic, is it?
Hey, Hino-rin, tell me,
are you willing to forgive anything I do?
Because, when I went to your house
searching for money,
you should have quickly called the police.
It's not something you would do naturally.
It may become impossible to control your emotions
during the course of treatment.
Mm you have pity because I'm sick.
That's wrong.
What's right then?
I want to become your strength.
Don't just say kind things.
You only want to save your patient Akira.
I know I'm just a nuisance.
Yumeno-san,
Believe me please.
Yumeno-san and Akira-san,
both are important for me.
Both are important personalities.
Then, you'll forgive anything that I do?
I'll forgive you.
Can you love, even a person like me?
You're a fool.
Because Akira is also a fool,
she always ends up being betrayed.
But that's not me, I'm the one who betrays.
I'm ready to do even more awful things.
He did it this time.. that guy!
Director! It's very bad!
What is this?
I just got it from Yabe-kun.
What?
But, if we don't protect Hino..
Professor.
Isn't it okay? Step aside
he'll get fired.
But, Director!
No, I don't think there was really
an ethical violation..
I can always find a replace for him.
Even for you.
Dr. Hino~!
Can you say some comment regarding
Yumeno's words?
Dr. Hino! A comment!
Yumeno-san and her mother will open
a conference about the matter of the article.
By all means, pleas give us a comment!
Dr.! Gives us a comment!
You are in here, right?
Then, you'll forgive anything that I do?
In order to seduce me,
the doctor Hino Rintaro
His method to approach me was to say
he suspected I had dissociative identity disorder.
My daughter was deceived,
she was damaged ..
Everyone, please listen.
My daughter has not mental illness to start with.
The so called Dr. Hino Rintaro hurt her..
and now, she is really ill.
Will you permit this shameless doctor to examine
patients, wearing a white robe at this University Hospital?
My daughter
has become a misanthrope,
she isn't able to perform in the parlor anymore.
My daughter now..is pitiful.
How did Dr. Hino end up involved
with such terrible mother and daughter.
This is just too much.
If that is true..
That's rude!
It's true, isn't it obvious!
Rather than from the mother
from Yumeno-san, Yumeno-san
please tell us your feelings now.
Are you planing to sue Hino-san?
Of course!
We'll suing Hino Rintaro and Keinan University Hospital!
I'm the responsible of the psychiatry department
at the Hospital,
my name is Miyagawa.
I'll like to ask some questions to Yumeno-san.
I'd like to inquire about your dissociative identity disorder
At the moment this photo was taken,
is that the same personality  that is here now?
or was another?
I don't understand the meaning of the question.
If you have the illness you mentioned a moment ago,
at the moment this photo was taken,
I was wondering if there is a chance
that it was another personality on the photo.
Are you saying that she was lying?
You!
The question is the possibility.
If you were a different personality,
the memory is ambiguous or nonexistent.
Is possible such a thing?
Which was it?
How was that?
Please say it clearly!
Please answer clearly!
Are you not answering?
It's Hino Rintaro!
Oh, it's Hino.
If you enter now, you'll ruin this.
It's fine, let me pass, please.
Prof. Miyagawa made the question
in order to defend you,
of course, also the Hospital.
Yumeno-san,
it's fine not to answer.
Hino? Why did you come?
Dr. Miyagawa, thank you very much.
But it's enough.
It's just right,
We'll listen both of your opinions.
Please answer!
Did you deceive Yumeno-san, right!
She is not lying.
Dissociative identity disorder means
she has multiple personalities?
Please explain with more details
Yumeno-san's medical condition.
I can not answer about that.
That means it's pretty severe?
Those issues shouldn't be discussed here.
Then, you admit
Yumeno-san's accusation?
Yes.
Please explain yourself,
explain in detail!
Give as more information.
Please, speak in detail!
I, as her psychiatrist,
will take all the responsibility.
She doesn't have any responsibility.
How are you taking the responsibility?
Do you think that by saying those nice words
you'll be forgotten?
As a psychiatrist that wouldn't be correct, right?
Hey ..at this rate
you'll be able to asks a lot for damages.
Now, you too,
say something.
Are you going to answer?
Please answer clearly!
What do you mean by that?
Doctor!
In order...
I'll answer the questions in order.
Wait, Akira, what's going on?
Yumeno-san.
Akira Wait!
Please, wait!
Speak! Please speak a little more!
Hey, please!
Please let your story be heard!
Ah, doctor!
Please, a comment!
Please continue your talk!
A word, please!
One of the parties left her seat in the middle of the conference,
the truth is not clear yet.
However, this psychiatrist has also appeared
several times on this program.
Like this..
It's too awkward.
It's over, for Hino.
It's what he wanted,
there's nothing to do.
Welcome back.
Sorry, to make you worry.
Really.
Now, the hospital or no one can protect you
from your problem
I know.
Did you speak with Yumeno-san?
I see..
I made dinner, but as I thought you
wouldn't have many appetite, it's not much.
Thank you, Mizushima.
After looking at that conference,
I thought there must be some circumstances,
in trying to protect that patient's situation.
Dr. Hino,
is an ally for us, the patients.
Yes.
Ah, Dr. is here today?
Today, the examining doctor is Dr. Araki.
Dr. Hino isn't attending?
I'm leaving.
We're also leaving.
What.. wait..
Dr. Araki will examine you, please.
Dr. Hino is good.
Dr. Fukuhara, what should we do?
Hasumi.
How is your eyes' condition?
Ah, I've recovered a lot.
I see.
Hey, Araki.
Do not involve Hino
in your ill feelings.
Ill feelings?
Satonaka Midzuki-san
the surgery I made because you asked me..
Leave.
It's all my responsibility.
Although it's something that can't be solved with an apology.
As you see,
I'm really sorry.
No..
It's my fault.
She believed me.
It was me who took the decision.
That's why, it's my fault.
Didn't her mother tell you?
The one who should come
it's not you!
Isn't it Dr. Araki?!
It would have been better
if ten years ago, you would have killed
my daughter and I..
I was also there, at the funeral.
But didn't enter.
I see..
Say
Why did you suddenly come back here?
Hino won't come back anymore.
It's his end.
Are you really trying to go along with Ennoji's desires?
Yeah.
I misjudged you.
Araki..
Araki-senpai?
He vomited blood, they're examining him now.
I'm sorry, even though
you told me to watch over the doctor.
I understand.
I'll be there soon.
Ah.. Hino-kun.
Don't say "Hino-kun" senpai,
even though I told you.
What's the state?
Due to overeating the stomach ulcer caused a bleeding artery.
For now, we stopped the bleeding with an endoscopy,
but if the hole in the stomach
opens more,
he must have a laparotomy.
Please control properly Dr. Araki's issues,
Dr. Hino.
You caused this, senpai?
You got angry, right?
I have enough pain, you know, with the stomach ulcer.
Rintaro, he shouldn't be talking,
his clip was just applied.
Hey, sorry, but could you
just let us the two of us talk?
Just 5 minutes.
Yes, yes.
Excuse me.
Hey, raise the bed.
oh oh painnn.
Going right to the point,
what's your reason?
You too,
you shouldn't be in this place, right?
What happened with Yumeno-san?
I couldn't contact her.
The wicked things,
all of them, I'll eat them for you.
Wicked things?
Like the politics inside the hospital, or the money,
things like that.
The medical corporation that Ennoji wants to buy,
is intended to become a psychiatry oriented hospital.
The director there,
will be set in a very good position,
that's what it means.
I did not know at all.
I'll take over all that muddy business.
That's why, without worrying about anything,
just focus on her.
It is stupid to fight in the hospital for my sake.
And to even risk reducing your life,
I'm not pleased at all.
I don't want you to have the same regrets.
The same regrets?
You see, I..
I myself, experienced counter transference with a patient,
I couldn't save her.
Counter transference?
That patient..
she committed suicide half a year ago.
It was also possible to do the operation at other hospitals.
But, I didn't choose to do that.
She believed in me.
I was in love with her.
That was entirely my responsibility.
Even if it was your responsibility,
do you think she would wish for you to be in this condition?
Yumeno-san,
By all means, save her.
And that
will save yourself.
No one else can save
Yumeno-san.
I understand.
You mean she hasn't contacted
here since that?
And even though I thought
whatever the personality,
she would come back here at night.
Where could she be?
I think that she surely will come back here.
As a psychiatrist, you might not be able
to do anything.
There.
Ike-chan, come here.
follow the applause
Where?
Ike-chan, come here.
follow the applause.
Caught you!
It's me.
What! Idiot!
Koyume-chan..
Koyume-chan, what's your little dream?
(Her name literally means little dream)
Do you want me to tell you?
Ah..If you tell me,
I might be able to grant it.
Really?
What a problem! Number one?
Alright! Leave it to me! Yeah!
Eh! Ike-chan is cool.
Ennoji..
Yes.
I'm sorry, but forget about what we talked before.
What talk?
The think about the acquisition.
You have to keep your promise.
The Minister is resigning due to tax evasion.
If we're careless,
they'll come to investigate us too.
Now, it's a bad time.
Huh..
Sorry.
You idiot!!
Are  you going to give up so easily!!
The point here,
is that you have to keep your promise, okay?
This is not a joke, hey, Hey Ike!!
Why do you think I let you do
as you pleased until now?!
Do something!
You can't take it back now!
Waa..wait!
Ike!!
Chill out!
You, all of you,
you're taking me as a fool!
Are you fooling with me!!
Mother, as expected,
I'm no good as a psychiatrist.
Hello.
It's an emergency. Come immediately to the hospital.
I'm in confinement,
I can't do any examination.
The patient says that if it can't be
any other than you.
Do you mean.. Yumeno-san?
Just come soon, now.
Ah, doctor.
Thank you.
Sorry I made you wait.
I'm glad you're able to come.
Please, sit down.
I was worried,
where did you go?
Hino-rin, why did you show up nonchalantly
at a place like that?
You wanted to see
what kind of awful lies I was going to tell?
You're wrong.
I went because I was worried about you.
Shouldn't you just give up on me?
I cannot do that.
Why not?
No matter what it takes.
Just the fact that you came here,
makes me really happy.
I'm glad to see you again.
Hino-rin, I came to ask you something.
What is it?
I want you to erase
Akira from inside of me.
Why is that?
Because when she's there,
things don't go well.
Even at the conference
Even though I wanted to
completely destroy you
and made you look as a villain.
I received a considerable damage.
And yet,
Akira was a hindrance in my way.
In what way did Akira-san
interfere?
It's a very strange feeling.
It's like I can't recognize
Akira's mind
and my mind anymore.
It's like I'm not myself anymore.
Yumeno-san.
That's a personality integration
That means your treatment
has had a great progression.
Yumeno-san
and Akira-san share the same mind.
If you can continue feeling like that,
the times without memory
will disappear soon.
Didn't I tell you?
I don't need Akira's feelings.
Yumeno-san,
Why do you want to deny Akira-san
so much?
It's okay.
Akira-san's wounded memories,
I'm sure, the person you are now
can easily overcome that.
I'll become your strength..
That's annoying.
Hino-rin,
you already realized this long ago, right?
Akira is in love with you.
For the first time ..
for the first time since birth
she fell in love with a man.
in the morning,day and night
her head is full of you..
I don't know what to do..
It's painful.
So, just erase Akira
please,
erase her.
Yumeno-san,
just like you are,
you're a person worth to be loved.
Please, love both of your selves.
Hino-rin, don't you love me?
I consider you a very important person.
You mean you can't love me as man loves a woman?
I can't do that.
For me,
you're very important for me,
and because you're very important
I want to save you from pain,
and in order to help you
I can't become something else than a doctor.
In order to be your doctor,
I can't afford involving in a love relationship.
Then, why you were so gently?
Didn't I promise you?
To be by your side from now on.
Please stop with the gentle lies.
It's just painful.
Thank you for everything.
Doctor, goodbye.
Yumeno-san, please wait!
Please don't go!
I won't come to examination anymore..
Subs by Kitty-nyan
*´¨)
¸.•´¸.•*´¨) ¸.•*¨)
(¸.•´ (¸.•` ¤ (\_(\
¤ (=' :')
¤.. (,('')('') .. ¤
¤ Chuline ¤
Are you intending to stop being a doctor?
Yes
I've always been looking after Rintaro,
Everyone's fired!
I'm the King!
Is that, being a mother?
I do not have any secrets at all!
Will you marry me?
What?? Watch the last one :P