Hello,
I see you were able to come.
why..
Always by yourself,
always you're so lonely, right?
It's okay now,
I'm here.
Excuse me, an examination?
Please, come again,
I'll be waiting.
Dr. is it ok?
She was the one that place a horse in the sand,
maybe on her own.
In the miniature garden?
Yes.
An unsaddled horse without a rider,
will escape if it's pursued.
For now, let's be gentle.
I understand.
The dizziness and nausea don't lessen,
even though I have been properly taken my medication
And sometimes my knees are trembling
non stop.
I see.
Dr., now, look, my knees are trembling.
I understand.
Let's increase your medication.
And then, for a while,
please look at the situation.
Okay, that would be all.
That would be all.
Eh? Miura-san?
Are you okay?
Stop it!
Dr. Miyagawa, what are you doing?!
Ah!
help me ... please help me!
What is it?
That's Miura Makiko-san,
the ballet prima donna.
Eh?
Dr. Miyagawa intended sexual harassment ...!
That's a lie!
After doing such an indecent thing,
are you trying to run away!?
Coward! Harassing Professor!
Miura-san, it's okay.
Professor, what happened?
It's wrong! A misunderstanding! I did nothing ...!
Ultimatum,
I want the 7 million until tomorrow!
Where's the money?
the money is..
mm you see,
you can't buy without money.
And your mom?
My mom..
I wonder where she went..
Please, I'll take that along with this.
It's 220 yen.
Okay, receiving exact amount.
Thank you.
Here
Were you hungry?
Yes.
What's your name?
Chika.
Chika-chan?
I'm also waiting for my mom.
We're waiting together.
Big sis too?？
Yes.
Since mom will surely come,
until then,
let's eat this while waiting.
Okay, let's go.
So, now let's move forward with no fear!
I'm on your side.
This is a story of a doctor that saves
the lost sheep of this modern era.
Sorry for the late introduction,
I'm a psychiatrist, Hino Rintaro
You know, I really like this.
Then, I'll give you this one too.
Big sis is not eating?
Yeah.
You know, I'm fine because I have these.
It's candy.
What is this, Dr. Miyagawa?
about the sexual harassment.
It wasn't anything like sexual harassment!
ah, you don't believe me?
For this sort of occasion,
with the proper permission of the patients,
I've been recording them.
That would be all.
Eh? Miura-san?
Are you okay?
I'm really sorry, at that moment
to touch the patient was a big mistake.
A doctor that doesn't care
about a patient that fell down
it's not a doctor.
No, the contact is bad.
eh?
I think I saw that face somewhere,
Is she something like a ballerina?
The former prima donna, Miura Makiko-san
former?
Since her husband's dead, two years ago,
she hasn't come out to front stage due to her depressive condition
This is bad.
Even if you told that to the media,
it's something serious.
It'd have been better just to do
diagnosis through image only.
In that way I would never been accused
with this sexual harassment false accusation!
[T/N: he's doing a sort of pun here with his choice of words, that's kind of lost in translation]
Is that attitude that led to this kind of situation.
... What the hell? Hino
I dare you to say that again..
Dr. we have a problem, Miura-san's
daughter is missing.
Why if you were watching,
didn't you stop her!?
Because I didn't know it was
Miura-san's daughter..
My instructions weren't to damage
the child, where's Chika!
She was taken away by being
deceived by that woman, I'm sure!
If something happens to that child,
it'll be your fault!!
Before that, let's look for her quickly
While I was suffering of sexual harassment
by Prof. Miyagawa,
my daughter has disappeared!!
If that child is gone,
I won't be able to keep on living.
If there's any chance of that...
I'll also die!!
Chika.
Doesn't it make you feel in some way uncomfortable?
What?
If I were in her place,
I'll be too worry about the child,
to say those kind of things.
and immediately
I'll go search for the child.
Could you please?
Understood.
Miura-san
What's the commotion about?
Can you stand? Do you wish
to rest a little over there?
Please this way..
It's okay.
Kawakami-kun, about the lady that was with
her daughter..?
It's the geisha who had come to the Dr.'s room
I saw her leaving with the little girl.
Yumeno-san did?
Big sis, your phone is ringing.
Hello, Yumeno-san
Yumeno-san.
Big sis, the clouds are really close.
Are you now together with a girl?
Big sis, we are now at the highest point.
Hello.
Wait, Dr. Hino!!
Please, wait!
I wonder where is mom now..
Can I see her from here?
Chika-chan, and your dad?
Dad has died.
Mom
Don't run down the stairs.
Mom..
Sis, let's try to find mom
together, quickly
It's lonely, right?
You don't want to be alone anymore, right?
Good morning.
Are you Miura Chika-chan?
Yeah.
Chika-chan's mom is really worry.
Where is mom?
She's waiting at the hospital. Let's go.
Big sis, bye bye.
The training was fun today.
That's good
let's do our best, next week too, right?
Yes!
Yumeno-san.
Aizawa Akira-san
Yes.
Wouldn't you like to ride one more time?
if it's possible with me?
You're almost a stranger..
I see.
Please, answer it.
Yes.
Hello? Yumeno?
Where are you?
We're already preparing,
we'll go to the parlor soon.
What are you doing!
quickly, come back home.
I'm sorry, I'll return immediately
I'm sorry, I should get going.
Please hurry Dr.
Something has happened at the hospital.
That child it's my treasure.
More important than life..
Mom!
Chika!
You worried me to death!
Ah, I'm so happy you're safe.
Who did you leave with?
a big sis with candies.
Since I was lonely playing on my own,
she was really friendly
Chika!
Don't leave with people you don't know!
I tell you that all the time!
I'm sorry.
Either way, It's good that your daughter is safe.
You said it's good?
You'll take responsibility on this!
I'll led you to the exit.
This way.
Somehow,
this may not end involving the police, but
Who is this sister?
That was..
My patient.
patient? Give me a break!
With this problem is enough!
I'm sorry.
Hey, mine is not a fail.
Then, I..
You're going to mix the rice and
the ingredients before cooking?
Yeah.
Eh.
egg too?
Yes.
Next it's just to heat it.
It's an unusual omelet.
this too is that person's recipe?
Are you thinking about Yumeno-san's case?
Maybe..,
I think this is a dissociation case.
Yumeno-san is the name of the geisha,
her real name is Aizawa Akira-san
I think she probably suffers of
dissociative identity disorder
Here is an Omurice that when you eat
may have the same taste but..
If we see the entire Omurice as yourself,
Each person, similar to this,
is made with various components.
If there are times with good mood,
there's also times with bad mood.
Usually in a person,
they can be properly
found in the same Omurice, in the same person
However,
when it's the case of dissociation state
the person within oneself can have
a number of states of consciousness
One self is the red ketchup Rice
another self, the yellow omelet.
both of them are the same cooking
but they don't feel
as the same omurice anymore
Then,
will they remember the same things?
Since this state of consciousness
is not connected with this other
memory doesn't remain.
Since the person doesn't remember
what was talking before
he/she will be perceived as a terrible liar
by the surrounding people
The person would become more and more confused.
When it comes to this terrible condition,
for each state of consciousness,
the personality would change.
It can become a child's personality
or sometimes an atrocious personality
can appear.
You mean multiple personalities?
In today's medicine,
It's called Dissociative identity disorder.
Hey brother,
I'm entering~
Madoka-chan, good evening ~.
What happened?
Yuriko-san, you're here.
It's good, listen
What?
Bro
Yes.
Are you going out with a geisha?
I heard it from the lady in front.
She says a geisha
with white makeup and a traditional braid hairstyle
constantly keeps coming here.
It's not constantly..
Just twice.
Twice? I only knew about one..
Well the first time,
she came to return the money,
On the second time..well, Mizushima was here.
Eh what?
Yuriko-san, you met her?
Ah, right, Madoka,
would you like an omurice too?
You won't deceive me
with an omurice.
That geisha is Yumeno-san,
a Rintaro's patient
Patient?
while it's still hot, please.
Is she really a patient?
Nakamura-san, good evening.
Welcome.
Konno-san, how are you?
Fortunately.
Did you wait?
En-sama, you're late.
Sorry, a boring meeting
doen't end easily.
I wanted to hurry and look at Yumeno's face.
I also wanted to meet you.
What is it? You wanted to talk.
You see,
again
there's some favor I need to ask you.
Just say it, I'll give you anything
a bag?, a clock? a ring?
How nice, but even all of that would make me happy,
what I want the most now,
it's the roof for the geisha house
eh?
Since it's old, the leak in the roof is bad,
and mother is worried about it.
The 3 million that I passed you the other day
weren't enough to fix it?
The contractor called
to make an estimation said we need..
just like this more, to do it.
It is said that most of the causes of
dissociative identity disorder occurs,
due to mistreatment and lack of affection
during infancy.
If that kind of painful experience during childhood
is repeated many times,
In order to escape from the pain,
the person would be pushed to another consciousness room.
That is thought to lead to dissociative disorder.
By creating another personality,
the broken heart
becomes detached from their own self.
Yumeno-san too,
suffered of this disconnected heart
because of a painful personal experience?
Though I can't be sure unless I try to talk her
for a longer period of time.
And today also, that kind of situation happened with Prof. Miyagawa..
Just don't summon her to the house again..
since you are doctors and patient.
It's true.
Brother, since you're not immune to women,
you should be really careful.
And Yuriko-san,
keep watching him firmly.
Why do I have to be told
those things by my little sister, even now~
Madoka, what are you doing
since a while ago?
Ah.. this time,
there is a wedding of my husband's relatives,
so I thought of borrowing mom's kimono.
Hey Yuriko-san, this
is too plain, maybe?
Why?
there are a lot of things, you see,
I'm giving this a lot of thought..
Wow! Your mom looks beautiful.
Did you wait?
You're late
Sorry.
Yasuke-kun.
I wonder, if I could
have done something for her.
"You are not alone"
"and the door of the examination room is always open"
It's disgusting.
Dr.,
It is better to eat something and not just the medicine.
I don't have any appetite.
this stabilizer., it's not at all effective
More, give me more, give me.
Yes, Dr.
Oh? Is it..
May I?
Please.
It it safe to drink your medicine
with that desperation?
Someone should stop him.
I don't want to.
It's okay,
what dr. Yabe is passing to him
it's just vitamin.
Eh..
then, no matter how much he drinks,
it won't be effective~
Dr. Yabe, who usually seems so cold,
she's surprisingly gentle.
Only towards Prof. Miyagawa, eh?
why is there no effect?
Excuse me.
Did you call me?
Something really bad just happened.
Miura Makiko-san has informed
that she's suing Prof. Miyagawa for sexual harassment.
So, where is Prof. Miyagawa?
He's become useless.
The elite is weak to punches like this, you know.
That's why I call you.
What?
You, will figure it out somehow.
I understand,
I'll try talking to Prof. Miyagawa.
But, he also has his pride
being a professor, right?
Will he obediently receive an advice
from Hino-kun?
You shouldn't be saying such a thing.
Because I'll have to entrust this
sexual harassment problem,
to a capable strong lawyer.
Miyagawa-kun should hurry and get back on his own feet
and fight back, he's causing trouble.
It is as you say.
Excuse me.
Wha..what do you need?
I heard that stabilizers aren't effective.
What? Did you come to call me a fool?
That? This is ....
Makiko Miura brought these to each examination.
In order to call my attention.
Really...
what is in this thing?
Dr. Miyagawa
My favorite comedian has this saying.
Comedian?
That doesn't suit the level of your education.
This is the person I respect the most in this world.
This is what he says,
"Life is the one thing we go through in order to regret it."
In short, what do you mean?
If you want to know the truth,
I don't like you at all.
Leave me alone.
ah.. hurts..
oh..hurts...
Feels good?
Didn't I say it hurts?
I got it, got it.
It feels good, right?
You don't get it at all.
Oh they are really effective.
And here you don't have to worry about your story being leaked.
Please talk with confidence Oh ....
Originally she ..
came to the hospital to be treated for depressive symptoms.
Ah .. she was really talkative..
I couldn't tell what was real and what was a lie,
she was merely bragging.
My previous boyfriend was an Arabian millionaire!
but I broke up with him because he was vulgar.
vulgar?
There are people that think that the antonym
for luxury is poverty
but that's a mistake.
The antonym for luxury is vulgar
It's not just about how much money has the person.
Ho~o It is indeed the word of a prima donna
Brilliant!
Ah! That was a full big time compliment
Ah.. perhaps that's when she made a..
positive transference with her doctor,
I think that was the starting point.
Eh? Is that possible?
In a therapy context, transference refers to
redirection of a patient's feelings
and desires
for a significant person in the past,
such as parents or lover,
to the therapist, unconsciously.
I know such a thing!
But, at that occasion I thought it was better to exaggerate
my reaction
to please the patient..
After that, what happened?
My medicine prescription worked well..
and I thought she was  recovering steadily,
but one day..
There was this day, when I met,
this person I really respect, Coco Chanel
In 1980, in Paris
That's impossible.
Because Coco Chanel died in 1971, right?
You are not supposed to lie, right?
In the first place,
you weren't still born.
Oh! I see, that might not have been good.
I think she suffers from the histrionic personality disorder.
That's why her disguise of lies,
you can't peel it off carelessly.
Let's think of this as her heart, right?
She was feeling some strong stress
Then she had to protect her heart,
if you say and do whatever to protect it,
then you have to protect the lie.
The lie protected her heart?
Yes. If we're talking of lychee, this is the peel.
So, uncovering her lie is the same as to peel the skin.
It was her bared heart
what she has been protecting in that lie.
And that lie has been exposed by
Dr. Miyagawa who Makiko-san thought was a friend.
With her bare heart wounded,
she started
to think of her doctor as the worst of human beings.
But at the same time she wants to become her friend,
so thinking in this way
she undergoes a sexual harassment commotion,
to go back once again.
What should I do?
Well, this time her conduct is mostly
that of someone that is considering to obtain
affection and interest.
Hurts! With a lot of understanding,
with perseverance, make contact with her,
without making fun of her lies,
Please listen to the loneliness behind the lies!
I can't understand something like a loneliness behind!
Feel empathy.
I'm not good at feeling empathy
Stronger?
Hurts..!
Should go stronger?
Ah Hurts, hurts hurts!
Yumeno..
Certainly.
I knew it, the director
of the Toshiminami gave it to you, right?
You have became close already?
Here, a souvenir,
your favorite candies.
Thanks
I had a narrow escape from death~
You are really a good child.
Ruriko, we should get going.
Akira, see you.
I'll contact you..
En-sama, is there's something wrong?
It's unusual for you to take a day off.
And Yumeno-chan?
She just went out a little,
but she'll return very soon.
Mother,
I'll start preparing for the tea.
If you please.
En-sama, what?, did you come to outing Yumeno
instead of me?
Please enter.
It's not that, not.
Since you're replacing the roof,
I thought of introducing you an acquaintance contractor.
I've heard you had a terrible roof leak,
but it doesn't look that bad.
What is that you're talking about?
So, for the cost of the replacement of the roof
I handed in to Yumeno-chan.
Construction cost? How much did you hand in?
Initially 3 million, but later
she told me another 7 million were needed.
A total of 10 million!?
Yumeno told you so?
Yeah,
she said mom was in trouble.
Wasn't the case?
No..
It's that so..
so it's a lie.
I am so sorry.
Once she's back I'll have a severe talk to her,
I'll ask her to return the money at once.
Has Yumeno-chan,
a bad guy to support?
I don't think that's the case..but..
Could it be..
No, nothing.
Sis Yumeno
Sis Yumeno!
Nutcracker "pas de deux"
Mom..
It's impossible, even if I tried to feel empathy
no matter what, the empathy is not coming.
Because, the biggest victim here is me!
being falsely accused of sexual harassment,
I haven't even told my family yet.
I'll leave the rest to you, Hino-kun.
This is a directive request, solve it somehow.
That's all.
Hello?
Dr. Hino, here it is.
Makiko Miura-san's "Nutcracker",
at the forth place I finally found it.
Fukuhara-kun, despite being Sunday, I'm sorry!
Miura Makiko-san was such a great ballerina.
Miura Makiko, former name Sugawara Makiko.
Her mother was also a ballerina
that represented Japan,
Sugawara Etsuko-san.
Since she was 3 years old
she began with ballet under the strict guidance of her mom.
In 1998 she won the All-Japan Dance Competition.
In 2001 she was the first Japanese person to join the Les Halles Ballet company.
5 years later, in 2006,
she was promoted to the highest position of importance.
The following year she married Takumi, her now late husband.
After becoming a mother,
even though she has continued being inactive
as Miura Makiko
she has obtain lots of recognition.
The dance with his husband Takumi-san,
the "Dance of the Sugar Plum Fairy and the Prince",
it's certainly a legend.
Fukuhara-kun, what? Did you dance Ballet?
As a child I was forced by my mother
to go to a ballet school.
Isn't that amazing!
It became fun while I was doing it.
I even entered the medical school
ballet circle.
Really!
So, then, Fukuhara-kun,
what is this pas de deux?
Recently,
what you heard about the Australian dollar?
Didn't you learn your lesson with the FX?
Just now, I'm recovering.
Even after being on the run,
from the blue face debt collectors,
your throat may have pass through,
Oh, that's a nice hand.
This time I'm after a large profit,
I want to go even to Macau.
Macao, eh..
Being called by the superiors, the Okama from Macao
Being called from the lowers..too
The Okama from Macao
What are you talking about?
someone known?
I thought you're a ghost.
weren't you dead?
Who said that I was dead?
Yumeno.
Akira killed me.
You are again exploiting that girl, aren't you?
Do not say bad things of my reputation.
From a guest,
she deceived him with 10 million yen.
The truth is that I don't think
someone with such a weak spirit could do.
She had that director stretching
under her nose,
it was the money to finance her, anyway.
I knew it, it was you.
If so, what about that?
I'm the mother of that child.
What's wrong with extort from my daughter.
That child will be unhappy every time you appear.
You're being irresponsible,
let that child be free!
Why do you have to meddle
with other people's business!
I'm the one who understands Akira the best.
That girl, you see,
if I'm gone, she'll be lonely, she's gonna die.
Afterall,
Mothers are the most important.
Leave, old woman!
Ah.. sorry
Chika-chan
Chika-chan, what happened?
I wanted to meet with that big sis again.
The big sis with candies?
And your mother?
My mom..
Dr. Hino.
It's "The Nutcracker".
Does mom listen to this occasionally?
Ah, this song..
Was the one your mom
danced with your dad, right?
But,
ever since dad died,
mom,
didn't want to dance it with anyone else.
Is that so.
Chika-chan dances?
I dance, but..
Will you dance with this big brother? right?
If it's only a little.
Really?
Mom.
Ah, sorry, for doing something without your permission.
You were..
We came in behalf of Prof. Miyagawa
from the Toshiminami University Hospital
I'm Hino Rintaro, a psychiatrist.
Entering without permission,
what are you doing?
That matter was left in the hands of the lawyer,
please leave.
"Grand Pas de Deux for the Sugar Plum Fairy
and her Prince in Confiturembourg"
The pas de deux is a dance
with dancing steps for two people, isn't it?
Yes?
Miura-san, you..
Have you been trying to dance
the pas de deux by yourself?
What are you saying?
Please, have a look at Chika-chan's dance.
Children can't keep on living
without her mother's affection.
So, could you give a closer look
to Chika-chan?
Mother!
I'm sorry
I won't dance anymore, please don't cry
It's not that..
I'm sorry
No.. It's not because of that.
It's fine, I's okay now.
Chika-chan
didn't do anything wrong.
You know, people that have lost their loved ones,
there are times when a big gaping hole
appears in their heart,
even if they are already adults,
even if she is a mother,
at those moments, they have to cry
like this.
Miura-san,
in trying to protect in some way their broken hearts,
people resort to lies, and fallacies,
to escape from tension.
That
may not be a good thing.
However, even that,
it's a means of keep on living, that's what I think
please stop
trying to work so hard by yourself.
For Chika-chan's sake too
why don't you start the treatment one more time?
Allow me to be in charge of it, please.
Did you practice by yourself?
Yasuke, I'm home
Rain is falling quite hard, you'll catch a cold,
let's enter, come in .
I see.
Did you come from the examination room?
But, since it's Sunday, nobody is there
Sorry, about that.
I'm placing here a change of clothes.
Thank you very much.
You must be hungry, right?
Would you like a sandwich?
Yeah
I'll make you one now,
please, change your clothes.
Mom's smell
alright..
Mom..
Ah, stop!
You'll get wet.
Hey
So, let's enter
Thank you~
Enter, come in, come in
Sorry for the intrusion
Come in, welcome.
Mom, welcome back
I didn't know you had to take care
of a child, Yuri-chan
I told you, go over there, Akira
Akira? Sounds like a boy's name,
coming in
You don't need to say that kind of things,
just come in..
nay..
don't, don't, hahaha
That child,
it would have been better if I didn't give birth
Don't say such a thing
Hey, say you love me
me too,
see you
Akira,
you have a lot of candies
don't waste them,
and lick them slowly
you got a poor person's mentality,
who did you take it from?
Mom! When are you coming back?
I kept you waiting
Mom!
Let's go
Mom, where are you?
It's ready.
Mom... Where are you?
Akira-san
What did happen to you
during your childhood?
I'm on your side.
Dr...
Please tell me what happened.
I..
Don't come out now.. Stop it!
What's happening?
Hino-rin.
Good evening, Yumeno-san
I'm happy you're so fixedly staring at me..
I want to know your real self.
Then, come over here.
Look at me.
Come closer.
You're not doing anything, what a coward.
Yumeno-san
You are guarding the wounded Akira-san, right?
You always do this, to protect
your own wounded heart, right?
..what a boring man.
Do not come inside of me ever again!
Stop messing with Akira!
Subs by Kitty-nyan
*´¨)
¸.•´¸.•*´¨) ¸.•*¨)
(¸.•´ (¸.•` ¤ (\_(\
¤ (=' :')
¤.. (,('')('') .. ¤
¤ Chuline ¤