I can barely sleep these days,
and I can't concentrate at work.
When was that you become unable to sleep?
It's because of a women with a strong awareness
Ah, Dr. Mizushima
What are you doing?
Here.
Please look.
Huh?
Dr. Fukuhara asked Dr.Hino
to show him the role-playing of
interactive psychotherapy.
But, from the middle it has just become
a love counseling.
Ah.
Although I think I shouldn't wait
even 1 day and confess to her,
the courage doesn't come out.
Confession ... You don't think you have to do that?
No
It's not like that.
She is usually humming AKB48 songs.
If only I could express to you
“I love you”
Even if you don't answer
Even if you look bothered
I would be happy
When I heard the lyrics
I understood the supremacy of confession
If I love and not convey my feelings
I'll come to be a pessimistic and useless man.
I see.
But...
But?
But, even if you confess
it doesn't necessarily mean that you'll get a good answer!
That's it, if I get rejected..
your current relationship
will become awkward
And there is more risk that your state of mind
will fall more and more into insecurity.
It's that what you feel?
That's why, I'm in a trouble.
Let's calm.
Let exhale slowly our breath.
Fukuhara-kun, listen,
As I said in the lecture,
love is something transitory.
It is a state, such as a mental illness.
Dr....
Will you fell with me?
Eh?
Dr.?
Hi..Hino-rin it's fine.
Can I meet you again?
Yumeno-san
Why?..
Dr.?
what's wrong?
It's nothing.
So in other words,
the conclusion is that it is very dangerous
to lose the reason for love.
Let's talk about the hormone balance.
When in love, the male hormone in men
and in women, the female hormone,
each will increase.
For men, it increases the aggressive behavior,
and while they will be able to work
the gentleness is reduced.
If we talk about our work
We'd no longer hear
the story of patients.
To attend the patient with empathy,
becomes really hard.
Those are the possible
consequences that may occur.
Is that so?
Fukuhara kun,
What kind of doctor do you want to be?
that is..
I want to be one that can draw close to the mind
of each person as Dr. Hino.
I want to be a psychiatrist that
could be able to help any patient.
Then, you should refrain from love.
Regarding a psychiatrist,falling in love
is more hassle than what it's worth.
My favorite comedian also has this saying
comedian?
"Falling in love it's the first step for the transformation"
Let's have a cup of tea.
Yes.
This is why Dr. Hino is still single until now
Though, he is great as a psychiatrist
As a man ....
He is problematic, right?
Huh ..that also is there.
So, now let's move forward with no fear!
I'm you our ally.
This is a story of a doctor that saves
the lost sheep of this modern era.
Sorry for the late introduction,
I'm a psychiatrist, Hino Rintaro
The major best-selling author, the novelist
Mr. Kazama Shinnosuke?
Even the fact to be considered,
it is an honor to be designated as
his attending physician.
His latest work, received bad reviews,
he has fallen into a slump
His mood is fairly blocking him.
Please leave it to me.
So, contact Hino-kun.
Yes.
Why Hino?
I can solve this on my own.
Because it's really important that the psychiatrist
has affinity with the patient.
Your contender is much better on this.
I have Dr. Hino.
Hello.
Yes, I'm Hino.
After hospital today, come without fail,
I have a patient that I want you
to be in charged of, Hino-kun.
I understand.
Well then, come to the Kinosa at 7 o'clock.
Is that the Ryōtei (traditional restaurant)
from the other day?
That's it, Is there something
wrong about the place?
No.
You've became quite a photographer, right?
You want to broadcast it on the Internet?
No, until the time comes.
Let's wait.
These are the most excellent psychiatric doctors
in the house.
I'm the Head of the department of Psychiatry,
Prof. Miyagawa.
My name is Hino,
I look forward working with you.
You guys probably have read some of
Mr Kazama novels, right?
Certainly, whatever you write, has become
one best-seller after another.
Also my wife,
started reading it with pleasure.
Could I get your autograph?
That's a total failure.
Not at all, my wife found it
extremely interesting.
Critics gave a harsh time to Mr. Kazama.
Let's leave it there.
It's because they don't know
the suffering of creating something.
That's right.
Now, let's have a nice time.
Good evening.
Mr. Kazama, director Naito,
Welcome, Welcome.
Good evening, I'm Yumeno.
I'm Koyume.
So, let's have some sake.
Because tonight, it's Director Ennoji's treat
So, let's have some party!
No, no.
It's on director Naito.
Ha ha ha! Leave it to me.
Hino-rin, we meet again
Hino-rin?
Huh? What?
Please, have one.
I don't want sake!
I'm sorry to be late.
Who are you?
Mr. Kazama, it's a joke?
She's Hosaka-kun, your secretary, right?
That person is an impostor! You are not Mutsumi!
Mr. Kazama
What are you saying?
It's just like that, it's a different person!
Who instigated this?
Who brought such a fake!
Mr. ..
I see
You are using my name without permission
and wrote this boring book!?
This is why I was criticized so badly
by the critics
Who called you? Ey Was it Naito?
Mr. Kazama, Hosaka-kun and I, neither of us
would do such a thing..
This is your conspiracy!
I'm being wiped out from the literary world
because of you both!
Dr. Kazama, let's calm down.
Don't touch me!
I'll take care of this as your doctor.
This is bad, call an ambulance.
Right now.
Mr., Are you ok?
Don't touch me!
Ouch!
Are you Ok?
Mr.
Mr. Are you OK?
Ah, Stop it!!
Get off me! What are you doing!
Director's special case?
Hold firmly his body.
Yes.
We'll go with 1 ampoule of Diazepam by IV
You put poison in that syringe!
When he becomes quiet
administrate haloperidol
And take a head CT and MRI
Stop that injections!
Oh Hey!
It's good I got injured
Huh?
Hino-rin will take care
of this, right?
Let's ask a surgery dr.
Mizushima, Mizushima
Huh? What?
Sorry, it's just that..
There's a person who injured a finger ..
Ok, yeah.
Later, later
Later?
You're close to Dr. Hino, right?
Eh?
Ah.. well, we live close to each other.
Where does Dr. Hino live?
What?
And, do you know when is his birthday?
Why do you want to know so much
about Dr. Hino?
Could it be?
Are you Dr. Hino's girlfriend?
You're wrong.
Then, why do you have
such a scary face?
Dr. Hasumi
About Mr. Kazama..
I won't know until I see his scans.
Eh-!
With this..we will be connected.
Here.
Sorry, but
you'll have to wait a little more.
Mr. Kazama Shinnosuke
is a metaphor genius.
In other words, a prodigy at metaphors
That transcendent literary style,
surpasses by far the imagination of ordinary people
I'm a big fan.
Hey, he is said to be a treasure
of Japan literary world
You also know that?, Rintaro
Yup.
Around the main character,
odd characters constantly
appear
and it's particularly distinctive,
this flying squirrel.
A flying Squirrel!
Yeah.
But the work he published recently,
has received bad critics.
But, it's weird that those things affected
so much at such a great writer
People are fragile.
People who are believed to be strong
are more fragile
Now, let's eat.
What's this?
It's delicious
I made it using a recipe
from my favorite comedian
Fried curry and bean sprouts.
Bean sprouts and fried ...
eh? Isn't it a salad?
Since the 70% of a salad it's air
to eat it, is similiar to eat air.
Isn't that also a conclusion
from your favorite comedian?
Ah, I forgot the mashed potatoes.
Yup?
I wonder from who.
It's a patient?
Yeah.
Let's meet on your day off
Yumeno
The patient fell in a sudden excitement state
when that happened, he hit on the head,
and that caused a mild brain contusion into
the right temporal lobe.
For the excited condition,
haloperidol was used to calm him.
With the exception of the brain contusion,
no other organic abnormalities were found.
For now, there are none
surgically points to be addressed.
Because of the circumstances and his behaviour before the falling down,
and judging from the diagnosis
of the images of the SPECT scan
It's seems this is paranoid schizophrenia.
The first thing is to prescribe risperidone.
It would be an established tactic to expect the symptoms to improve.
I see..
as expected it's paranoid schizophrenia?
Isn't it too early to judge so?
Is that so? Hino-kun.
No, not from the image of the SPECT,
also it was obserbed a blood flow decrease
in the parietal lobe
which is frequently to find in schizophrenia.
Dr. Miyagawa have you talked to the patient?
I have been in direct contact with the patient.
You understand that I said it many times.
The misdiagnosis is born from being misled
by the patient's story.
Then, what can you conclude about him mistaken a person?
Who are you?
Mr. Kazama, it's a joke?
She's Hosaka-kun, your secretary, right?
That person is an impostor!
That is the Capgras syndrome.
Capgras syndrome?
Can you describe it so as to we can understand?
Capgras delusion syndrome,
also called "the illusion of look-alikes",
is a disorder in which a person holds a delusion
and they're convinced that a familiar person
has been replaced
by an identical-looking impostor.
So, paranoid schizophrenia it's a safe bet.
But..can't we just
get one interview anyway?
What are the basis for Hino-kun to say that even now?
Dr., say it heavily please.
The basis..
Just.. for some reason.
I think we want to listen carefully to the patient's story.
What are you saying? You want.
You can't restrain Paranoid schizophrenia
just with psychotherapy.
In other words, Hino-kun,
what you're saying about this patient, is useless.
What do you think? Hasumi-kun
It is like a fight of judo and karate.
The clothes may resemble
but the way of fighting is completely different.
Well.
Such a place would do, right?
I see.
I made a decision.
About the attending physician ...
Let's ask Dr. Miyagawa.
Thank you very much.
Dr. "just for some reason"
was weak
Get out! You're not Mutsumi!
It's your favorite flower.
Get out! you! Get out!
I do not want to see something like your face!
Get out! - Get out!
Mr..
Kazama-san.
Get out.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
I don't need a doctor! Get out!
The fact is that..
my friend is Kazama-san's fan.
If you could,
would you give me your autograph?
No way!
I see.
Because of my friend's recommendation
I was allowed to also read it.
It was quite interesting.
What was quite interesting?
I don't understand anything of that!
This is why I hate doctors!
Sorry about that.
If you get it, get out!
Kazama-san.
May I ask you one question as a reader?
What?
The protagonist of this novel is in love with the flying squirrel?
Mr., Is the flying squirrel near you, even now?
It's a good question.
But..
It can not be seen anymore.
How is that?
It had already disappeared.
When did it disappear?
Think about it by yourself.
Sorry.
That figure while flying..
it's beautiful.
Hino ...what are you doing?
No, this is an examination.
Mr. Kazama is my patient.
Leave
Excuse me.
I'm relly sorry Mr.
We have your medicine.
I became Mr. Kazama's secretary 15 years ago.
I see
Ah, so, his first novel since you started as his secretary,
was this 'Illusion'?
That's it.
I see.
And his writing, where did he do it?
He confined himself at a Karuizawa hotel.
Heh.
But ... at that time did something change
in his behavior?
No
Mr. Kazama has an amazing ability to concentrate.
He was able to write it in two weeks.
Really!
But, from "Illusion" onwards,
in Mr. Kazama's novels,
a strange and rather interesting character
has appeared.
since that moment, Mr. Kazama created a new style
that earned him high appreciation.
You're really well informed.
Well, actually..
I've just read it last night.
Ah..
My first intention was to study this
as to read his thoughts.
But then this cute flying squirrel
appeared...yes
and finally I became absorbed in reading
I see
Here, please
Ah, sorry.
Like, when it (the squirrel) makes him feel rejuvenated,
when it clings to his back
or when it makes terrible mischiefs and interferes with his work
I like that part, too.
It hates the peanuts in the Kaki-peanuts.
A squirrel that eats Kaki-peanuts without peanuts,
does it even exist?
Does it? I wouldn't know..
From about when does Mr. have this sort of behaviour?
Since about three months.
Demons outside! Good fortune come!
Dr. stop it please!
You! Are you a demon?
Eh? or a god of wealth?
Which one? Answer!
What happened?
I didn't hear about such deadline for the manuscript!
Mr. I have told you properly.
I was also present at that time.
You two are conspiring against me
to make me lose my manuscript!
Demons! After all, you are demons!
"Demons outside"?
Dr. Hino, as soon as possible come with
Prof. Miyagawa to the directors' office.
I'll go later,
So, three months ago..
It is urgent!
Excuse me.
Hino-kun has been interfering with the treatment.
What do you mean?
If Mr. Kazama's delusions
aren't due to Capgras syndrome,
it may not be good administering medicine
that will suppress the delusion
Could you stop meddling with my patient's treatment!
Before deciding the name of the disease,
wouldn't it be better to hear the patient's story?
I'd be a time loss
Loss?
Isn't the time facing the patients, the most important one?
Whenever the treatment is up to Hino-kun,
you can spend talking
dozens of hours.
The publisher director is begging us,
books are not been sold in this era,
only his books will sell when put out.
They want him to write as soon as possible his new work,
or the company will collapse.
I'll issue an inmediate result.
Dr.
Please, leave Mr. Kazama to me.
Hino-kun
Yes.
In the future I forbid any contact with the patient,
also do not meet with the patient's staff.
Ok?
What's with that "Ok"!
Miyagawa, you're messing around!
Because a psychiatrist like you was present
the patient got annoyed!
Don't rely only on medicine!
That's all?
You're saving something.
Also, Ennoji, it's Ennoji.
That's it, go!
What's with "In the future I forbid any contact"
Stop messing around!
acting so refined, when your belly is showing!
You're thinking something evil
Your brains are black!
Well, certainly,
that person is black-hearted haha
feeling refreshed?
Yes
Here, take some sugar and
the fatigue in your head will come off.
Then, only one.
Yeah.
Let's eat.
Life..what's it about, right?
Life?
Well Yeah, life
is full of regrets
This is too sweet
I'll make some tea
Sorry, go ahead
To send such a mail to the busy Hino-rin
was an annoyance, right?
From Yumeno..?
It's a patient.
Heh, it seems..
Let's meet on your day off.
Yumeno
The spring has finally come for you.
It's nothing like that.
hahaha
hahaha..you have spilled some.
It was not a annoyance,
not at all!
All day long, I've been thinking..
Hey! What are you doing?!
Hey!
..of you.
Hey stop, stop it.
Yes, send it.
It has been sent!!
Here, here, she answered!
Huh? I'm Happy!
Then, tomorrow at one p.m.
come to meet me at the geisha house, please.
Geisha house? Hey you, a geisha house..
a geisha?
I'm just going because it's rude
to neglect a promise,
This is not a date.
Because to be good psychiatrist,
I should refrain from falling in love.
Well, then Yasuke-san
I'm leaving!
Excuse me.
Yes!
Ah!
Dr. Hino, welcome.
Thank you for the other day.
The other day, the doctor also wasn't cornered, right?
Please, come in.
Today you're going out with Yumeno, right?
Sorry, but what do you mean by
'going out'?
Oh, don't you know?
A day like today, is to play with a geisha
outside the parlor.
Is that so?
This is the fee. (for a geisha's companionship)
Hino-rin!
Let's go
As the fee, 100 000 yen
will be charge to Hino Rintaro-sama
I see you brought a lot of sweets
whenever you want, please
3 months ago..
Yes?
Nothing!
Just now, you were problably thinking
of your patients, right?
Sorry.
Mr. Kazama?
Yes
Mr. Kazama was always drunk when coming to the parlor,
and it was the frist time he was troubled by
that lady who is his secretary,
that never happened before.
Is that so..
Hino-rin.
In the middle of our date
please forget about the patients.
Just put your attention on me.
Yes.
So, I have one question.
The other day, when you passed through the cherry trees,
why didn't you notice me?
Althought I think you heard my voice
you just followed ahead.
I was wondering, why was that..
Ah, that was my twin sister.
Huh?
I'm often mistaken with
my sister, since we look much alike.
So you have a twin..
Huh ~.
Right!, go go!
will you keep us forever waiting?
Akira-san
If you can't prepare it after two days,
by the beginning of next week,
I'll go to the parlor,
Is that right?
You'll not be in Shinbashi
anymore.
Then please, come to pick me up, please
I'll be waiting for you.
No, that's enough!
Yes, that came up fine!
Huh? Does she have it?
Yumeno-san, here
What happened?
I'm sorry
I.. lied to you just before.
It was a lie that I have a twin sister.
That was a lie..
I didn't notice Hino-rin because,
I was really upset that day.
You're finally here
After all, 10 million is impossible
What's impossible?
What's FX?
You're not Akira-san,
aren't you Yumeno-san?
Could you pay within few days just 1/3?
with your important relatives,
that would be fine
That's good, right?
In fact, that night,
there was a phone call from the hospital my father is in.
Your father,
is his health delicate?
Yumeno-san, please tell me if there's
something I can do to help you.
My father has a lung cancer,
and it has merged with bronchitis,
I've been told that surgery is not possible anymore.
At last, I was able to find a doctor that will take care of him.
But according to that doctor,
the latest treatment
will cost 3 million yen.
3 million ...
I'm sorry
In the middle of a fun date,
I end up with such a story.
Yumeno-san, it's gonna be OK.
Please, don't cry anymore
I will help with the money.
Then..
Please make a deposit here.
"Aizawa Akira"
It's my account.
Okay, but
Why don't you come at least once to my examining room?
examining room?
Ah, I'm sorry if I surprised you
with such a phrase
But, please
it'll help you to have brighter feelings.
At lunch break,
we'll have a cup of tea together.
Let's eat this over there
Right?
Good morning.
Aizawa-sama, here.
Please confirm the amount.
Here is the cash
Please confirm it.
Thank you very much.
What yah doing, hurry, enough!
We'll meet next week, right? Akira..
-san.. that's not,
Yumeno-san
Ah hello
with the director Ennoji, please.
It's Yumeno
Hello, Ennoji, yes
Hello,
What are you doing?
The special patient, Kazama-san
has been complaining of strong abdominal pain.
What about Dr. Miyagawa?
Since the Prof. is busy with meetings
since the beginning of the week,
can you see him instead?
This foreign body was found
in the x-ray of his stomach
What do you think?
Flying squirrel.
Dr., what are you saying?
You've been reading too much of Mr. Kazama's novel?
Look carefully, here.
What's that?
with this, you'll know.
Isn't it a ring?
It's a ring!
He should have swallowed it by mistake.
It's penetrating the stomach wall,
it may not come off without an operation.
Demons outside! Good fortune come!
Mr. Please, stop!
"Taking only seeds of kaki from the kaki-peanuts
while eating them deliciously..."
A squirrel that eats Kaki-peanuts without peanuts,
does it even exist?
Does it? I wouldn't know..
Its flying figure
it's beautiful
Who are you?!
Why did you bring such a fake!
Could it be?
Wait, Rintaro?
There is no need for you to prove
whether you are or not
the real Mutsumi
The answer should be provided
by Mr. Kazama himself.
That is..
It is a symbol of Kazama-san's anguish.
That is incorrect.
I see.
Kazama-san,
now, Mutsumi-san,
she is about to enter this room.
What?
Go ahead.
This way
Well then, eat them in order.
It's enough already
It's not over yet.
Please, eat it.
Don't be so irresponsible!
Please, one more time,
eat them
Don't eat!
Don't you eat it!
please..
Mr., are you ok?
In reality, you are aware that she is the real Mutsumi,
aren't you Mr.?
Mutsumi has peanuts allergy.
And you were aware of that.
That's why you desperately try
to stop her from eating it.
The fact that she is Mutsumi,
you have that awareness somewhere, right?
Kazama-san, your delusions and hallucinations,
I think they aren't due
to paranoid schizophrenia.
The flying squirrel for you
is someone irreplaceable?
isn't it?
The illusion that if you reach for it, disappears.
But the flying squirrel that comes out
in your novel..
that has spent 15 years by your side,
weren't you suppose to continue supporting
your literary creation?
Shut up, quack doctor!
You love Mutsumi-san
Isn't it?
Mr., you've been sitting there
from this morning, right?
Please rest a little
Isn't it cold?
Ah, maybe it's a bit cold
Yes!
Don't catch a cold!
Mutsumi
Yes
This
This is from me, to thank you
Thank you!
Ah It's beautiful! Mr.
Look at it!
got it, got it
It's really beautiful Mr.
I can't make
Mutsumi happy
Why is that?
Isn't it obvious..
60..
Once comfortably in something
like a warm happy family,
I couldn't continue to write novels.
Marry that man
Demons outside!
Mr.! Mr.!
Please,
stop throwing peanuts
to Mutsumi!
There are plenty replacements for you
Do not come here anymore
Go
You released your flying squirrel.
Even though, that illusion was the source of your inspiration.
So when you lost it, you became insecure.
Who are you?!
Perhaps those feelings,
were showing Mutsumi
to you as another person or a demon.
The ring became for you,
another form of the flying squirrel,
wasn't it?
Do you want to remove it with a surgery?
No.
It's fine in this way.
Kazama-san
My favorite comedian has a saying,
"Life is an illusion, we're a bunch of illusions"
What the hell are you saying?
Kazama-san is a genius of illusions
and that is your uniqueness.
So, what about that?
Short-term psychotic disorder.
This is my diagnosis.
Do I need any treatment?
No.
In your case, Kazama-san
it's something temporary.
I think there's no need for help,
if you don't need help in social life.
so self-important..
You'll have many fans waiting for your next novel.
so noisy,
quack doctor, I know that,
you don't need to say it.
Since this is the end,
don't interfere with my work.
Your friend...
what's her name?
Eh?
Your friend who is my fan.
Yuriko
It's Yuri as in Lily (he's explaining the kanji)
Thank you so much!
It'll maker her really happy!
Mr.
I..
Mutsumi
I'm fine on my own.
In the future, I won't
hire another secretary.
Be happy.
Thanks for taking care of me!
The happiness for a woman, what is that?
The happiness of a woman..
I envy her.
What?
Kazama-san won't need a treatment.
So, it isn't paranoid schizophrenia?
Right, it's a short-term psychotic disorder.
Its symptoms have ceased.
They have ceased?
Yes, Kazama-san is a genius of illusion,
he has a great personality.
There is no need for medication,
it'll be fine if he's discharged soon from hospital.
Director, this is a simplistic and biased
diagnosis from Hino
I do not accept it.
So, which one is correct?
I don't know.
You don't know?
But..
What?
When there is no need of treatment
There will be no need of hospital charges
and the fee for the differential bed.
The doctor's fee can't be removed.
That would be a problem.
Anyway, it was good!
Then, excuse me.
Hino-kun
is excellent as an attraction panda, but
If all the symptoms of the patients
are caused due to their personalities
then as a psychiatric you won't
have even one patient left.
maybe it's impossible for him to become a Prof...
Director, there's something I want to show you.
yes?
It's a call from director Naito.
Okay.
Yes, it's Ennoji
Mr. Kazama has started writing a new novel!
Thank you very much!
That's great,
our psychiatry dep. is excellent after all.
We'll show our gratitude the next time..
We are looking forward to it.
Hasumi-kun
Take hold of your weakness.
"In my belly dwells a small ring"
"One day, I swallowed and tried to digested it"
"but, my body rejected it."
"In that garden
you could see it right through"
"between the singing of the frogs at the tree frog"
"it's an eviable thing"
"when you swallowed something that can't be digested"
"It washes everytime you drink water from the mouth to the stomach."
"I would also like to wash the beaten parts of my brain,"
"in that way, at least just once."
Cheers for good work, Dr. Rintaro
Yeah
Although it's the time to say that,
why is there a red line drawn on the book I lent you!
I'm sorry Mizushima
Eh, I've received a bonus from Dir. Ennoji,
So, everyone, without refraining,
please eat all you want.
Sorry,
two servings of kalbi (Korean-food), please
A beer please.
I also want a beer, please.
The bonus, it's a lot of money?
Let's see.
Ah
mm?
Dr. Hino, yesterday morning,
you were sending
a lot of money somewhere, right?
At the Hospital ATM,
not at one transaction
But 30 times.
30 times, so you mean 3 million!?
Where did you remit such big amount?
Could it be? Dr. Hino
only could send it to support that woman, right?
mm?
did you do it? to that geisha,
Yumeno-san, was it?
mm?
she was quite suspicious,
trying to know your address.
As expected, isn't it?
Hot!
To paid for his father's treatment?
You're caught by a classic move.
classic? Is it so?
It's an awfully classic one
Well, and I thought I was paying high tuition fees.
You better give up.
Ah, and there was also the price for going outside..
going... outside, a price?
That was also high.
You were eating yakiniku (roasted meat)?
I ate it.
C'mon, I don't want my Taiyaki (fish-shaped pancak),
with your yakiniku smell
Yumeno-san
Ah welcome back
Because of your help
my father's treatment was a success
Really?
So, what are you doing here
this late?
I.. here ..
I thought of trying to return this.
The medical fees were covered by
the kindness of some relatives.
I see..
Hino-rin, thank you
Really, Thank you very much.
Ah ... cute!
What's its name?
It's Yasuke
Yasuke  Yasuke
If you want to be a good psychiatrist
you should avoid things like love
Love is transient,
similar to a mental disorder
By no means, do not ever
fall in such a thing
That's what I thought.