Yumeno-san, please wait!
Please do not go!
I won't come to examination anymore..
Like this?
Yes.
It wasn't like this,
but like this, right?
Right.
I see..
he might have crossed the line.
Right?
Yeah.
Have you finished with this?
Ah..sorry
This means he is in love, right?
with Yumeno-san.
Counter-transference.. What just happened
might be it.
Even though he had the habit of saying
he'd return.
This time is for real?
It sounds real, like he usually is.
You mean is it treatment? Is it love?
I wonder which one is?
I'm the one asking the question.
By the time when the first symptoms appear
you can't stop it.
Then, which one is it?
Dr. Mizushima
have never spoken clear to him.
You mean it's my fault?
He..
might intend to quit as a doctor.
I guess that's how strong
his resolution is.
Is this, what Akira-san
wanted to do the most?
I shouldn't?
It's not that.
Yasuke!
Dr. I really like this.
Thank you.
It really looks well on you.
Yasuke, let's go.
Aren't you hungry?
I'm hungry
Yasuke, are you hungry?
Even though I didn't expect her condition
to have this sudden improvement,
now, it looks like I was wrong.
Because, at this moment,
Akira-san and Yumeno-san
seem to have become one.
Come, come come..
Ah, running again?
Are you running again?
I'll do it, I'll do it!
Since I'm the one who can!
He's kicking the wall.
After a long time, the tic disorder seems to have reappeared.
If I'll say 'do it', you do it!
Listen you guys,
the acquisition will be an absolute success, okay?
Dr. about that..
I'll..!
I can take the whole country,
I have what it takes, right?
Yeah, I think you're right.
You fool, don't sympathize with such a thing.
There was a phone call this morning, from Minister Ike,
it was about...
What? Hasumi
The acquisition issue is not longer possible, he said.
You'll be my horse.
eh?
I'm saying you'll be my horse!
Wa..wait..!
Wait,
please calm down, Director!
Miyagawa, lead my horse Miyagawa!
Where to?
Isn't that obvious? To the top.
To the top.
Delicious.
It's the first time I eat such a delicious omurice.
Which omurice do you like the best?
Mm..that one, I prefer the jumble one.
Me too, let's prepare them again.
Wait! Granny!
Wait ~!
Aa!
Ah my stomach aches!
Maybe this is the right time.
Bye bye, Ruriko-san~
So, now let's move forward with no fear!
I'm your ally.
This is a story of a doctor that saves
the lost sheep of this modern era.
Sorry for the late introduction,
I'm a psychiatrist, Hino Rintaro
The last time~!
Dr. Rintaro
Is it okay if I come tomorrow as well?
Of course.
Then, I'm leaving for today.
Or else, Okiya's mom will get worry.
Then, I'll take you home.
It's okay.
Since I'm not alone anymore.
Even if we're not together all the time..
Yes
That's it!
I'll give you a copy of the key.
It's a phone call from Yumechiyo.
Yes, it's Hino.
Her mother?
It's okay, calm down.
Sorry I made you wait.
Aizawa Akira-san, is it?
Yes.
Aizawa Ruriko-san is your mother, right?
Your mother has been arrested for eating and drinking
without money at a restaurant in Ningyouchou.
Will you become her identity's guarantor?
What happens when there's no guarantor?
Until the punishment is determined,
she'll remained in detention.
Can't I be instead?
You are?
It's okay.
I'll be her guarantor.
Please, bring her here.
If it's too hard, it's okay to stop.
It's okay, since I want to do this.
You!
Akira-saaan.
I'm sorry, ..sorry
Mom had no money,
so I had a free eating..
You see I was really hungry
and didn't know what to do.
Why did you bring me to this place?
Says a 'dine and dash' woman
who then clings to her daughter in tears.
Someone who even sold her picture to gain money,
what a disgrace!
Such an arrogance!
what's up with the 50 million? The 50 million!
what's up with "I'll get the money somehow,
so don't meet Akira anymore"
with that admirable begging attitude,
you're a liar!
Hey Akira,
let's leave this place quickly
and live the two of us together,
like we used to,
it'll be fun, both of us again!
Until when are you going to continue with that lie.
Please, stop.
What's wrong? Akira.
I only had you, mother, back then, remember?
You were always drunk when coming back.
Is that, being a mother?
I had no alternative, Akira.
Going at school where everyone had their food for lunch,
and for many, many days, you didn't come back.
I was lonely.
I was lonely, so, so lonely.
I'm sorry..
Just keep silent and listen!
And because you didn't come back,
and there was no money,
not even confetti,
and I had no one to go for help,
I was so hungry..
I was so hungry,
that I even finished the ketchup.
And when you finally came back, you brought a man,
and ask me to wait outside.
and said, it'd have been better not to have that child.
Although I was expecting to be hug..
I'd have been happy just to be with you,
I had no only else, but you mom,
That's why I worked and worked and worked,
in the hope for you to say
'you can stay with me'..
I loved to dance.
Because you said my dancing was good.
If I could dance well, I though that would please mom.
Money was really important.
Because if I had money,
mom would hug me.
'You're a good child'
and she'd pat my head.
If I could please the customers,
I could please mom.
She would be proud of me and praised me.
I just loved to see mother's happy face.
For a long time,
I continue living like that.
But, now I want to stop.
I..
Since I became who I am now.
Thank you, mother.
Yumeno..
Goodbye, mom.
Akira.. No! No!
Nooo..
Now, I'm the one
who's giving you a hug.
Noo..
Mom, you were also lonely, right?
Now, I can get that.
Mother,
you have to put up with a lot of things
because of me, right?
I'm really thankful.
But, from now on, you don't have
to endure that for me, okay?
From now on,
Every minute until now,
I'll properly return them to you.
Yumeno..
Noo
Don't want..
Nooo!
Don't want! No!
I became a horse.
A horse?
That Ennoji guy had a breakdown
and told me to become his horse.
He was shouting while riding me.
He said, "Go for the top"
Dr. Hasumi,
what do you consider to be the cause for this?
Haven't you heard?
Not at all.
The acquisition business didn't work out.
The business?
In exchange for the Minister's son's surgery
there was a promise
to receive a large quantity of subsidiary aids.
But that ended once was leaked
that this Minister was doing tax evasion
I see,
that's probably a shock, right?
There's something strange about that,
Minister of Communications, Ike,
contact me directly by phone, and..
and he was concern about a dilemma.
Ike-san?
The dilemma was the hospital.
And the director ended up in such a condition,
we're also troubled now.
Does he have any other symptoms?
His face moved in this way,
when he was in rage.
Do something, Hino!
But, I'm under house confinement.
You can't just say that.
Are you laughing? About my condition.
Is it, Hino?
I'm not laughing.
Aren't you laughing!
Even with this face.
You stole Yumeno from me,
you are also trying to steal the future of the hospital.
Because of you,
the hospital acquisition business has failed.
I don't have the power or authority to do such a thing.
Do you have a grudge against me?!
What are you plotting, Hino-kun?
Director, I
don't want to become your horse..
Be careful with your language, Hino-kun!
Wouldn't you come just once to my examination room?
Fool!
Are you saying that I'm sick?
Who you are now,
and who you've been until now,
don't resemble the same degree of rationality.
Aren't you carrying a big amount
of stress in your heart?
That stress it's because of you!
Because of you!
Didn't you suggest something to Minister Ike, Hino?
If it weren't for you, our acquisition business
wouldn't have failed so quickly.
That was 60 billion, 60 billion!!
What?
You guys also have Hino's opinion?
Are you saying that I'm sick?
There's no such thing.
But, the current you
is similar to the Emperor's new clothes.
You, to say that,
it's rude!
Sorry.
It's just that no one around you
is giving you an honest opinion
about your present condition..
Hino, do not describe the Naked Emperor.
Everything is your fault!
Minister Ike betrayed me!
Hasumi also changed sides!
Miyagawa is a traitor!
Everyone's fired!
I'm the King!
That sharp condition is not usual,
what kind of symptoms are those?
Perhaps it's an acute stress disorder,
that's causing a mild confusion.
And the medical treatment?
It could be good if he could listen to me..
That's impossible.
Dr. Hino, has been somehow
contributing with the hospital until now,
Professor,
he shouldn't be fired, right.
Why are you all relying on Hino..
I want to be loved too.
Professor, I'm here, isn't it?
That's not what I meant.
I..
want to be loved by my patients.
Anyway,
think in a sort of solution.
I leave it to you.
Understood.
So, how did it go?
Mm.. not well.
I we don't do something immediately
his condition certainty..
Not that! With Yumeno-san, what happened?
Sorry.
Yes, it's Hino.
Sorry, but come as soon as possible.
What's wrong?
Oh, I can't by the phone!
I understand, then, could you wait
for about a hour?
That much time.. I can't wait!
I'm on a verge of panic!
Come quickly!
I see, then I'll go immediately.
Ike-san, take a deep breath
and please calm down.
Then, until soon.
Sorry, I have to go.
Because you told me to break it,
I broke it!
But, it became this messy,
what on earth should I do now?
Please, calm down, Ike-san.
What exactly is going on?
Here, look at this!
Is this a fact?
No, it's a misunderstanding.
I knew that Ennoji had requested
Soumei
Medical Corporation under suspicion for acquisition
Press
Minister
Ike
also
involved..
exorbitant subsidies to the Minister.
But, before that happened, the Minister
was under suspicion for tax evasion.
That's why, I decided to break
Ennoji's chopstick.
I was just drawing together two people.
But I didn't do something
to violate the law!
Then, why
are you this much scared?
Could it be you because you took bribes?
I didn't get any money!
Ike-san, are you hiding anything else?
Haven't you been doing the same?
About Yumeno.
I didn't intend to particularly hide it.
Are you still insisting that it's just
a doctor-patient relationship?
About that..
What?
Is it for her sake?
or for your own?
Is there an answer, or you don't want to answer?
which one is it?
Minister..
There are things
that is better if they remain unclear
in this society.
But, you are suffering now of the
consequences of doing so.
The fate of a politician.
Isn't it the same as the psychiatrists'?
If you can explain it in the conference
won't they understand you?
Then, what should I say?
Ike-san, prepare your stomach for the worst?
stomach?
In times like this, if there is a secret people will notice.
Yeah.
In order to win an opponent trust
no matter what kind of punishment you may receive
on this occasion,
shouldn't you expose everything to the daily light?
Ah, welcome back.
I'm sorry.
I've just remembered the day when mom died.
When I returned that day
all the dishes were washed.
That's why I thought mom
was trying really hard.
Then the phone rang
and I knew she had jumped
in front of the train.
It wasn't your fault.
Shouldn't you forgive?
You mean my mom?
I mean yourself.
Regarding this deal
I was absolutely not involved
Isn't that a lie?..
Isn't it true that Minister Kusunoki
has testified that you introduced
Director Ennoji to the Minister?
Certainly, I was the one who introduced them.
However, about the matter of the acquisition
I had no participation at all.
There's also certain
information of a secret meeting you had
with the Director at Yoshino restaurant.
Was it there where the money
was delivered, right?
That's wrong!
We were just having a nice talk.
Stop telling irresponsible lies,
talk with the truth!
I'm not telling you lies!
Minister, What are you hiding?
That's right!
What are you hiding?
This is the truth.
Other than this
I do not have any secrets at all!
Please believe me!
Even after this, can't you believe me?
Even after this, are you still going to torment me?
Somehow I feel sorry for the Minister.
Ah, there goes my dream
it's definitely not coming true now.
If the Dir. is also involved,
he might not come here anymore.
Don't say bad things about the Dir.
Even if he did something bad,
he has been always
supporting us.
Okay?
Koyume?
Thank you, Yumechiyo.
En-sama!
En-sama..
Ah this,
I have this strange twitching
It looks good, right?
Dr. will you taste it?
Is it okay?
Yes.
Here I go.
It's delicious.
Ah.. great.
It's Yumechiyo-san.
Hello.
It's Yumechiyo.
I have an earnest request to ask you, doctor.
Did you tell the Minister to remove his wig?
Eh?
He said he wasn't hiding a secret
and remove it in front of the audience.
Haven't you watch it?
I didn't know.
You are a terrible guy, you too.
Dir. why are you so obsessed
about the acquisition of the hospital?
Are you trying to remove my wig too?
I don't have that intention.
The Soumei medical corporation is my father's hospital.
Father? The Dir.'s father?
Right.
That's why I wanted to buy it no matter what.
Why is it?
Do you have any brothers?
Just one younger sister.
I see.
I have two older brothers.
Both of them are doctors.
They are excellent.
I think the Dir. is also excellent enough.
He never asked me to become his partner.
I couldn't study enough
and couldn't enter medical school.
I knew it myself.
Ah..I was a person who didn't raise any expectations.
not when I married or when his grandson was born.
I was hiding
when I divorced,
but he didn't show up not even once.
I wanted a cheesy revenge.
I wanted to buy my father's important thing,
dismantling it
and to put it on sale,
that's what I thought.
I wonder why..
Regarding Yumeno,
Hasumi and even Miyagawa
everyone, have been influenced by you.
I was dumbfounded,
I'm not at all interesting, right?
Not at all sparkling.
Is that so.
Everything ends up being robbed from me.
Now, there's nothing left.
Tell me, am I sick?
Here I have a twitch,
it doesn't stop
Is it psychosomatic?
Director, surely
you were working too hard alone.
You've been, until now,
exchanging your sorrow and pain
with an energy of anger
to stay alive, aren't you?
It is a tremendous energy.
You could climb up to this place
because
you had that energy, right?
But the energy of anger is like a fire.
In order to burn, it'll use
anything it can lay its hands on,
And then, unnoticed, this flame
will burn your own self, isn't it?
You mean I'm burning out?
ah I'm moved to tears
That's why, it's good,
even if you couldn't do the acquisition.
I'm penniless.
I had invested all my money
in that acquisition
I've nothing left but a twitch.
What should I do?
I think it's fine
not to do anything.
Huh?
Director,
why are you here today?
Because I'd no other place to go.
Isn't it obvious?
Because it is in here, isn't it?
What?
The thing that is important to you, in here.
Now what you need is to
ask for help.
Sometimes, it's good to rely on people.
Human beings are not as bad as
you consider, you know?
Yumechiyo.
Something is in here, right?
Yumechiyo?
Hey? Where did she go?
Yumechiyo!
Yes, just now, I'm going.
You said if there is something here?
Whatever it is, it looks like it's here.
Do you know?
Well, what could that be?
Hino-kun
Yes
Heal me.
It's the condition for you to return to the hospital.
I understand.
You want to entrust me Ennoji's treatment,
I'm already fired, you know.
It's probably better if you do it.
I'll ask your favor.
Are you intending to stop being a doctor?
Have you already decided that?
Yes.
I see
Then, I guess there's nothing left to say.
Just go, quickly.
Ennoji, and also Yumeno's mother,
I'll take care of them.
I'm sorry.
It's the first time
you open your heart.
There's something really special about Yumeno-san.
Mother!
What are you doing here?
Did you listen to our talk just now?
Talk? I don't want to hear your talk never again!
Ruri-chan! It's not that,
he's also my patient.
Ruri-chan?
Patient?
No wonder why you only say strange things!
It's just she said she had no place to go.
So, I ask her to come and help me here.
It also serves as therapy.
You too, listen
carefully to Dr. Akari words,
and heal properly
Yes.
Okay?
Just leave quick, now it's my turn!
What are you looking at?
Senpai.
What?
You, don't imagine something strange.
It's not that.
I'll take care of Ruri-chan.
You, just do what you want to do.
Okay?
Yes.
Huh?
I've told you it's not that.
If I'm not mistaken, it's going up here..
Huh?
It's my first time coming here, too.
Today, it's my mother's 28th dead anniversary.
Is that so?
Dr., you said it's your first time..
I did not come for 27 years.
Why not?
I didn't tell you this yet,
My father
worked overseas and he used to
leave the house for long periods.
At that time, I think my mother was having
an affair with another man.
I was at high school,
and I never had the courage to ask her
about that,
I never talked to her about it. Just in my heart,
I blamed her so much.
I think my mom perceived that.
That made her fall in depression
and drove her to suicide
It was me.
So, I didn't forgive me
and didn't allow myself to come here all this time.
Mother, I'm sorry.
I'm glad you're able to come
and properly visit her grave.
It's thanks to you.
In spite of being a psychiatrist, I've always
being trying to escape from facing myself.
The truth is
I was scared of facing myself.
But I cease to escape when I met with you.
Because you filled
the emptiness within my heart.
Akira-san.
I fell in love with you.
Rather than as a healer,
I love you as a man.
I want to spend my life
making you happy.
Will you marry me?
I'm sorry, it's unexpected for a place like this.
But, I really wanted to convey
my feelings towards you, here
in front of my mother.
Since, I'm behaving so arbitrary,
you don't have to answer right now.
I will answer now.
Dr., thank you.
But I
can't marry you.
Is that so.
You can't?
When a psychiatrist falls in love
with his patient,
that's called Counter-transference, right?
Eh?
It was written in your book.
"Love is like a temporal mental illness."
But, my feelings for you, Akira-san are..
I fell in love with the psychiatrist Hino Rintaro.
And to hear those passionate words
of wanting to spend your life trying to make a patient happy,
that makes you untrustworthy.
Mother, I'm sorry.
To say such a terrible thing
about your son, here.
Dr.
Yes.
As a patient,
could you answer me one thing?
Yes.
It's about my illness,
haven't I healed yet?
No, I think
you are a lot better now.
But, if something
troubles you again
please come for examination at any time.
Thank you very much.
Well then.
You got rejected?
What are you saying, brother?
She was your patient, right?
Yes.
So then, isn't that an ethical violation?
That's why I wanted to marry her,
I properly propose..
You mean she rejected your proposal?
How many times will you say that.
Madoka-chan.
Please prepare for Rintaro his favorite food.
What?
I just.. remember something I have to do.
Wait..Mizushima.
Yuriko-san
had to leave because of the shock.
Ah, speaking of that..
There were beautiful lilies at the grave, so
that was you, right, Madoka-chan?
Thanks
You're wrong.
Those were from Yuriko-san.
She had been leaving flower offerings every anniversary.
Mizushima?
Brother, how could you let such thing passed unnoticed?
That's why
you got rejected even at this age!
Wait, those are different..
You don't get a woman's heart at all!
Sis Yumeno.
You've a visitor.
Yumeno-san,
are you really okay like this?
You really like Rintaro, right?
And if you, Dr. Mizushima
didn't like Dr. Rintaro,
you wouldn't have specially come
to see me, right?
I've always been looking after Rintaro,
I want him to be happy.
Besides me, Dr. Hino
has a lot of patients
that need to be saved by him.
I think it's wrong to become the only one he helps.
So..
Dr. Mizushima,
about Dr. Hino,
please take care of him.
Yumeno-san.
So, I'm
far from getting married now.
I'll work hard as a geisha,
I would like to repay the mother I have here.
Is it enough?
We have to get ready soon.
Please, if you could leave now.
Do you have any appetite?
I have appetite
Do you sleep well?
Almost all night.
Eh? Fukuhara-kun, why?
When just been dumped
now, you might have a hole
in your heart, this big.
About this.
But, Dr. Hino's favorite comedian
has this saying.
"To equal things like love and finding happiness is wrong.
Happiness is a different thing."
When did I say that I got dumped?
I know it just by looking at you.
Is that so?
Fukuhara-kun!
You can't help patients with an examination
based on guessing!
It's not a way of having empathy either.
So..Sorry.
Shinya-kun, hello.
You..
got..
dum-
ped!
Eh?
Dr., it's time for your lecture.
Well yes.
Physician guidelines:
Empathy as the starting point
Psychoanalysis is the science of empathy.
Not all mental disorders are diseases.
My conclusion is that it's has to do with the personality of the mind.
Even without gambling,
I'll be fine.
Even without gambling..
I'm hungry~
A little longer, a bit more, here.
Just another 100 times until noon break.
What?
I want to eat tendon
(fried fish served over a bowl of rice)
If that's not possible,
I want to eat katsudon (pork cutlet on rice).
at least I want bowl of rice with eggs.
Please...
Please~
Okay, what about unadon (bowl of eel and rice)
Thank you~!
Being terrible wounded at heart,
many people fell into a mental illness
due to lack of affection,
for them, the treatment only consists
on something like pharmaceuticals
or changing their mindset.
For those cases, if the physician gets closer
with empathy
it's not unusual that the patient's condition
starts to get better
little by little.
Yumechiyo, how do I look?
En-sama, you look good.
Yes.
Did you call me?
Regarding the medical treatment of the mind
is it enough to only improved
the symptoms?
Not only that, shouldn't it be our goal
also to guide the patient
to a happier life?
Isn't it to do whatever the therapist can
in order to diminish the
patient's loneliness and sorrow, even a little?
In order to become an umbrella for rainy days,
a blanket to wrap in
on days of thunder
what is necessary for us to do?
Not only as a therapist,
but as people who love,
For people who want to give happiness to others,
it's common to all.
It might be the most difficult challenge
in life.
Because love means to support the other person.
Holding someone tight
only to content your own heart,
can be a painful thing.
Some people say love is an obsession.
A couple in love, as well as a family in love
don't share just beautiful times,
there are also times when
it becomes really uncertain.
It's the same for us, as psychiatrists
even while having doubts,
we face the patient day after day.
But if there is no genuine love
for the people we want to save,
we can't do something so overambitious.
To heal those we want to save
there's no other choice but to love,
we should genuinely love people.
This is what I believe.
Everyone, what do you think about this?
Please, let me hear your opinions
concerning today's topic.
Subs by Kitty-nyan
*´¨)
¸.•´¸.•*´¨) ¸.•*¨)
(¸.•´ (¸.•` ¤ (\_(\
¤ (=' :')
¤.. (,('')('') .. ¤
¤ Chuline ¤
Bye bye Dr. Rintaro :D