Do not come inside of me ever again!
Stop messing with Akira!!
I understand.
I won't do anymore what you dislike.
But please, just remember this one thing.
I'm on your side,
Akira and yours.
Then, will you be by my side?
Yes.
I'll be by your side always.
You're lying.
I'm absolutely not buying that.
You too, one day,
will abandon Akira.
Please, wait.
Leave me alone!
Until you appear,
Akira and I were doing just fine.
It's concerning a romance between psychiatrist and patient, right?
Yes.
Patients have
feelings and attitudes
towards important people for them,
and when those feelings
are transferred to the therapist, that
it's called transference.
When the feelings are transferred, is it?
So transference is,
the projection of feelings onto the therapist,
who has come to represent
some important person from the patient's past.
That transference may be
a positive transition or
a negative transition.
Positive transition ..
In circumstances where the patient
feels like in love with the therapist,
generally on that case,
the patient works cooperatively,
and the treatment is often effective.
But, this time it's the opposite,
it's the therapist the one
who responds to those transference feelings
In the patient's mind,
who is falling in love
that important person
would be replaced.
Huh? And the patient would be considered
as something as a lover,
is it?
In Psychology,
that is
called counter-transference.
counter-transference..
Love..
Love is
only a transitory mental disorder,
although you told us that,
even if I keep telling myself that,
and keep stepping on the brake,
I'm on my limit!
If this continues, the break
will break and I'll be running wildly.
Let's settle down a little.
May I?
Running wildly can lead to accidents.
Just look,
let's take some distance between vehicle-to-vehicle
He gets
too obsessed when it comes to patients
until he can't see anything else,
even though it's not the first time.
Who are you talking about? Rintaro?
But, to go beyond the boundaries of doctors and patients
it's absolutely not allowed, right?
Yeah, well, that is right.
Moreover, the other party is a geisha.
A geisha? You mean Yumeno?
Dr. Araki,
why do you know about that?
No, just that when at Shinbashi,
I happened to overhear that there was a popular geisha
there called like that.
So, Rintaro..
Regarding a psychiatrist, falling in love
is more hassle than what it's worth.
that's what you told us.
When in love, the male hormone in men will increase,
and will no longer hear
the story of patients.
Fukuhara-kun, Is countertransference
happening to you?
Is that possible?
What?
Are you in love with the other party,
precisely with a patient?
No,
there's no female patient.
A male patient?
Dr., are you listening to my story?
Huh?
I'm sure, doctor's male hormones
have increased too, right?
No, that should not be the case.
Fukuhara-san, what should we do!
Are you okay? Fukuhara kun!
It's okay, my male hormones..
Sorry, to interrupt your role-playing.
No, no. What's happening? Kawakami-kun.
It's about my friend Otaki Nami.
Otaki Nami-san is under Fukuhara-kun's care, right?
Yes.
Dr. please, do something.
It looks like Nami's disease has relapsed.
Ah, she came.
Nami.
Oh, Yoko!
Just in time...
you know, please, lend me 200,000!
I'll return you soon, with interests.
Nami please, I'm asking you
open your eyes.
You know how much your mother is worried about you, right?
If I get the ten thousand betting ticket,
I'll repay immediately all my debts.
It went up again.
Yes!
Buy more, buy more.
Invest all the 7 million
It's gonna be bad if you don't return those 7 million..
Put these too!
Told you, the cash won't do.
Hurry, move out, enough..
How do I do it? How?
All?!
All, all!
Come on, do it, hurry!
Enter, got it, enter
Buy it, buy it! I'm going for real now!
It's a sure bet!
It went up!
Didn't it go up! See!
It's going up, isn't it?
Is moving!
So, now let's move forward with no fear!
I'm on your side.
This is a story of a doctor that saves
the lost sheep of this modern era.
Sorry for the late introduction,
I'm a psychiatrist, Hino Rintaro
She is
a typical case of gambling addiction.
She has spent 3 months hospitalized,
with Fukuhara-kun being in charge
of her treatment, but
it seems like she has relapsed into her old habits.
Otaki-san .
Dr. Fukuhara
Wouldn't you have a little talk with me?
Dr...
I'm sorry for breaking my promise.
Otaki-san, please wait!
Please, it's enough... Leave me alone.
No, I won't leave you alone.
It doesn't matter what I do with my life,
it's my own choice!
Kawakami-san is seriously worried about you.
And I am your doctor.
I won't leave you alone.
Otaki-san, please recall
those 3 painful months
in rehabilitation.
Didn't we persevere together?
You just can't throw out
all of that in this way.
Dr...
"Positive transference ..."
Since you contacted with your house
Today you'll be staying here, please
that was Fukuhara told us.
I'm sorry,
we'll put this under custody for you.
Wait..
Otaki Nami-san has devoted to gambling
since two years ago, right?
Yes, she was engaged with a colleague
from the company in which she worked.
And even though the wedding date has been decided,
she broke off the engagement when she discovered he was cheating.
It became hard to stay in the company,
and when she change her job,
her mood became unstable..
And from that time, she began to get into gambling.
Her savings for her marriage, she spent them all
and at the end,
the debts started to pile up.
For the repayment she even involved
her mother.
Unable to be indifferent to such Nami-san,
at the request of Kawakami-kun
Fukuhara-kun started the treatment six months ago.
That's right.
"I'm okay..
even without gambling"
"I'm okay even without..
Dr. Hino, please do something.
As expected, Fukuhara-san
can't do anything to help her..
I think Fukuhara-kun is doing well.
Then, why
after 3 months of the medical treatment
does she relapse?
Kawakami-kun,
Gambling addiction is not a disease that will heal so easily.
Although it seems painful your friend's suffering,
we should proceed carefully at this moment.
I understand.
Welcome.
Hey
One more time, I need you to get 10 million somehow.
Please!
The other day, didn't I pass it to you?
Can I help you?
Those..
those have disappeared
It's already impossible.
Don't say that ...
I'm really in trouble.
This will be the last time..
Help your mother..
Even if I beg, won't you help me?
Enough! It would have been better not to have you.
I'm sorry.
What? I didn't listen.
I'm sorry. I'll do something
Akira..
After all, you are mom's child.
Akira..Akira..Akira
200,000?
Does Nami have debts again?
Aunt, as I'm also attending her,
I'm really sorry.
It's that so..
Don't give up!, Fukuhara-san
Ah.. yeah.
Let's go gambling with Nami-san, tonight.
What?
Please, invite Nami-san.
Are you saying that for real?
Fukuhara-kun,
this treatment will be gambling.
So now, you
absolutely can't lose.
Dr. Hino, what's that?
Please tell her come at exactly 6:00 to the examination room.
Otaki-san, excuse me.
Otaki-san, Dr. Hino wants
you to come to the examination room at 6 o'clock.
Dr. Hino wants?
What he wants is to gamble with Otaki-san.
What is Dr. Hino thinking to do,
the inexperienced me, has no idea.
But..
I'm your attending doctor.
I want to do what it's at my hand and
continue to treat you.
You wrote this note while struggling against
your desire in order to get back on your own feet.
At 6 o'clock..
I'd like you not to go to the examination room.
"Chō" is even, "Han" is odd
Fukuhara-kun you'll be losing against Nami-san if you don't practice .
Yes.
Dr. I'll be leaving first.
You're picking him up?
I'm really sorry.
Please tell the boy to come and play
once in a while.
Yes, I will.
Even without gambling, I'm okay.
Even without gambling..
Here I go.
Dr., one dice didn't get in.
Really.
Fukuhara-kun, could you pick it up?
Ah yes.
Okay, Dr., once more, from the beginning.
Here I go!
Enough, doctor!
Sorry.
Okay, one more time.
Yes.
Even without gambling, I'm okay.
Here I go.
Now, get hyped, get hyped
Chō!
Fukuhara-san.
get hyped, get hyped.
Then, Chō.
Isn't it Han?
ah.. Han.
Chō-han, the pieces are equal.
I'm okay, even without gambling.
I'm okay..
Game!
Double ace.
Otaki-san, don't come.
Please move away.
The results if you continue gambling,
Otaki-san should be the one who knows that the best.
It's not just money what you lose.
How about your mother taken over
your debts to help you?
This..
This.
Nami-san.
Unfortunately
the gambling parlor is now closed.
what?
The time now is 6:00 past 1 minute.
But, that is because Nami-san and Dr. Fukuhara joined forces
you were able to endure from gambling for one minute.
From now on, let's extend the time of the endurance a little more.
We were able to cross the first hurdle of the re-start.
Congratulations.
One more time, together, let's recover.
Dr...Dr. Fukuhara..
Hello.
Don't worry.
These are people who had the same trouble than Nami-san.
Nami.
Hello.
Mother, even if these words are tough,
it is not an exaggeration to say,
that the treatment of this disease last a lifetime.
To feel at safe is forbidden.
Is that so?
To start again in gambling is a new awake of something,
in the blink of an eye the symptoms will relapse.
So far, the one that had come to return the debts made by Nami-san,
was you, right?
Yes..
I have no more savings.
I see, I'm sure it's hard.
But from now on, I'd like you
to absolutely not help Nami-san.
But my daughter is sick, right?
Shouldn't I give her anything she needs..
To do that would just worsen Nami-san's condition.
You mean if I pay her debts?
That's it.
Nami-san will also understand.
So, her mother too, needs to be prepared.
Prepared?
In the worst case..
please be prepare to stop living together.
Do I have to go that far?
I hope that this does not happen.
But, if we think about Nami-san's sake,
that resolution is required.
I understand.
To think that somehow the other day
I went to a pachinko shop
although I thought it was dangerous,
I was embezzled by ¥ 40,000
And that time, I was also thinking
about going to the pachinko shop the next day.
Fukuhara-kun, good work.
You were able to proceed with the treatment,
at the same time you attended Nami-san's heart.
Thank you very much.
By the way Fukuhara-kun, did you notice
that Nami-san is falling in love with you?
What?
Fukuhara-kun,
calmly grasp the relationship between doctor and patient.
If there were other person but both of them, the treatment wouldn't advance well.
So, what about Fukuhara-kun?
Unconsciously, will you
fall in love with Nami-san?
That is absolutely impossible!!
He needn't such a big negative..
Right?
Ah, Rintaro, listen..
Yumeno-san.
You came.
I'll be waiting at the examination room.
If you lend me 10 million,
I'll be pleased to go to the examination room.
Hino-rin.
Rintaro, as expected she's weird.
Stop your consultation with her already.
If something happened, you're slow..
Something?
I'm talking about not going beyond the boundaries as a doctor.
It is all right.
Even if I go beyond,
I come back at any time.
Even beyond?
Rintaro, have you fall in love with Yumeno-san?
It's not about if I love her or hate her,
this is about empathy.
What is the difference between empathy and love?
I want to match
in attending her mind.
Isn't that love?!
You two, stop it.
It's not a conversation to be having in the hospital.
Sorry.
I'm sorry about lying you the other day,
I absolutely needed those 10 million.
Why did you need so much money?
Please!
Again lend me 10 million, please.
That is the answer to the question?
Tell me why do you need the money.
The truth is that you have a man, right?
There is no man, it's the truth!
Please, En-sama, believe me.
Okay, however, I have conditions.
Tonight, you'll have to convince someone at the parlor.
And enliven him with your charm.
If that goes well,
I'll give you 10 million.
Come on, just sit here.
What is this?
Though this is the first time I've been called by the senpai.
It was asked by Dr. Mizushima.
Eh?!
Who is the one that occupies your heart now?
Isn't that the geisha called Yumeno?
You mean Yumeno-san..
or you mean Akira-san..
Akira?
I don't know which is the primary personality.
Ta-sama
okay okay what what ...?
Soon, it's my birthday.
Mm then a present..
What do you want?
I'd love to receive a ring from Ta-sama.
Then a ring..
How much will it be?
Since it's in May, my birthstone is Emerald,
so it's expensive
okay..I see..
okay..
In the treatment of dissociative identity disorder,
among the plurality of personalities,
who should be the target of the treatment
you would think about it, right?
Because her real name is Akira,
I'm sure Akira-san
is the original personality.
And I'm trying to somehow help her.
However, I think frail Akira-san
would find difficult to overcome the present circumstances.
On the other hand, Yumeno-san, has been playing an active role
as a geisha at Shinbashi
Although she may cause trouble,
she is full of vitality and
overflows a mysterious charm.
That being the case,
rather than Akira-san, with the idea of
supporting the personality of Yumeno-san
she might have a happy life!
Yup
..that's what I think at the moment, but
senpai, what do you think?
In my opinion,
I've reached to an explanation for your mental condition
at the moment, in one word.
One word?
Right.
It's love!
Love!
I wonder if this fit in countertransference? You..
That's wrong. That's impossible.
While involving with her,
you've fallen for her, right?
Well then, conversely, I'll ask you a question.
Senpai,
What do you think it's the difference
between love and empathy?
Love and empathy?
Yes.
Well Yeah ..
well, empathy is until a handshake,
to embrace each other, that's love.
I agree with you.
When embracing each other, they can't see each other's faces.
how the other party feels
is secondary
your own emotions
go first, that's love.
Facing face to face,
with reciprocal connection, that's empathy.
I want, sincerely,
an empathic medical examination with her.
Once there is something like love,
I can't help her.
I get you.
About that, you know,
you're way too serious,
and that makes anyone worry.
But, you know that sometimes the hunter becomes the hunted.
That geisha called Yumeno,
seems to be the woman Dir. Ennoji
is lavish money on.
You're lying!
We were waiting.
My name is Yumeno, I'll serve you one more.
Yumeno-chan, how nice!
Ike-chan, you're the best!
When looking at your smile,
even the trivial things, by all means, get better
the pounding that has been a bother
is gone.
Okay, drink
That's good.
Yumeno!
Here.
Oh.. great, great!
Together we'll mend the hospital!
Let's mend it!
We'll make money!
Thank you for tonight.
It was for En-sama's sake.
you're kidding..
wasn't for the 10 million's sake?
I'd like to take you out.
Sounds good.
So..this weekend.
we'll go?
Good morning.
Hello? Yumeno-chan?
As promised,
I made a reservation at the restaurant at 12 o'clock.
Hurry, I'll have you picked up.
So, we'll talk about the money there.
Yes.
Excuse me.
What do you want to drink first?
Yeah..
No, I prefer to make a toast,
I'll wait.
Yes, sir.
Yumeno.
So, this is a gift from Mom and Dad.
Really? Thank you
(Ennoji) Prepare your champagne.
Thanks, it's cute.
Ah, she's here.
Congratulations.
It's great, right?, blow them.
That child,
it would have been better not to have her.
Don't say such a thing
Eh? Yumeno-chan?
Eh! Yumeno disappeared?
I wonder if  she didn't like this restaurant.
Even though she told me,
she wanted to see the sea in our outing.
I am so sorry.
I'll locate her at once, and ask her.
It's okay, I'm also leaving already.
I'm really, really
sorry for this.
After I finish with the drying, we'll go for a walk.
Coming~
Ah.. hello.
Yumeno, is she here?
What?
I'm coming in, for a moment.
wait..
Yumeno.
Yumeno!
Just now, for disturbing you like that,
I'm truly sorry. I apologize
No, no. Here.
Thank you.
Excuse my abrupt question, but
has Yumeno, even to Dr. Hino,
did she innocently ask you money?
Yes.
Just as I thought.
Dr., you're also a victim,
I'm really sorry.
Why is that Yumeno-san
would need so much money?
That child is..
a pitiful child.
Even though now,
I'm like a mother for her,
the real mother of that child was also a geisha.
Despite being a geisha, her mother
gave birth to that child alone.
But, since the beginning she liked gambling..
and she didn't do anything that a mother would do.
That child grew up
by herself, all alone.
Having debts everywhere,
at the end,
she took money from the geisha house.
And ran away leaving the girl behind.
The previous mother of the Okiya,
couldn't just be indifferent,
and made her go until high school.
For a while she was steadily
working as an office lady.
But her mother appeared again,
and made that child to pay for her
debts of gambling
That mother, even now,
has a big influence over Yumeno-san
even to the born of the so called Yumeno personality..
Yes?
Yumechiyo-san,
you are her mother figure, right?
That should be the case, I think.
From now on, our talk is
becoming an ethics violation,
as a psychiatrist.
But I want you to know,
about Akira-san and the other personality,
Yumeno-san.
She suffers from Dissociative identity disorder (DID)
Why don't you listen to your mom!
Why didn't you bring the 10 million today!
Can she be cured from that?
Dissociating, in the form of becoming another personality,
If you accustom the mind to avoid
running away from the real world
the circumstances of that extra personality
coming out are few, I think.
The understanding of the person it's indispensable.
Sorry.
It's from Yumeno-san.
Hello.
Dr.!
I.. don't know why I'm here!
Why am I here?
I want to disappear...
I see. Please, stay there,
I'll be there soon.
I'm going to meet her.
So, don't worry.
Dr. Hino, about that child's problem,
please take care of her.
In this day..
to be alone, and get lost;
it's pitiful.
this day?
That mound is a symbol of a mother,
looking as the breasts
that sand mound she is doing now,
it's roundish, smooth and beautiful.
Around the mound it's irregular and dirty,
this division alone is intense,
Maybe she has suffered some kind of abuse from her mother.
Even now she is seeking for a mother, but
ultimately she has repeatedly been betrayed
and disillusioned..
Mom, where are you?
Dr..
Dr.
Why did you come?
You sound like being troubled,
somehow, I wanted to lend you some strength.
Has something similar to this time, happened at times, before?
It's okay not to answer,
if you don't want to.
Here.
Dr., why did you become a mind's doctor?
Eh?
Because..
My mother committed suicide when I was in junior high school.
My mother had been suffering from depression.
But, I
didn't pay attention to her mind's illness,
to my continuously depressed mother
I kept saying "try your best".
I've cornered my mother.
Even that morning..
Here
I won't have tea.
I'm leaving.
Rintaro
Mom too, try your best.
That day,
my mother jumped in front of the train.
If at that time
I had drunk the tea that my mother offered me..
I had properly listened
to what my mother wanted to tell me..
Even now I think of it.
But, the "If"s of the past
no matter how much I consider them,
I can't regain them.
Thank you.
If I'd had a talent for making people laugh,
I would have liked to become a comedian.
When my mother died,
I became unable to feel anything.
the tears didn't come out anymore..
I didn't even know whether I was sad or what.
I thought I was done for.
I wouldn't be laughing or crying anymore,
that was what I thought,
But, after about half a year, there was a day,
when on the TV, I heard a story
almost ridiculous
and when I realized I was laughing.
At that moment,
from inside of my chest, for a long time, from inside
feelings that couldn't be explain with words
suddenly overflowed..
I thought it was an amazing thing to laugh.
Since then I've been supporting heartily that comedian.
But unfortunately to me,
I had no talent for making people laugh.
So, I went with my second choice,
and I became a psychiatrist.
After talking about such a thing
I lose completely the reliance as a psychiatrist
Thank you,
for telling me your story.
I should be the one saying thank you.
At last,
we could drink tea together in this way.
So, you were also alone.
Akira-san,
you're not the only one who feels lonely.
At that time, when he made me laugh,
my favorite comedian, said this,
"Everyone is basically lonely.
Because they're lonely,
they do such things as work desperately,
they make friends,
they fall in love,
in order not to be lonely."
Dr...
would..
Would you stay close, from now on?
Yes.
I'll be by your side from now on.
Sorry, even on a holiday.
It's okay, even at home,
I'd only feel irritated
irritated..
Psychiatrists are troublesome.
About that, I think it's a good thing to be a surgeon.
When there's something bad,
you just take it off at once, that's good.
I might also have a drink.
Is it okay?
It's not herbal tea.
Cheers for god work.
Thanks.
Prof., have you ever fallen in love with patients?
No way.
That wasn't a mistake, right?
Could it be?
that you fall in love with me
No..sorry..
I wonder if I got drunk with one cup..
Sorry for being late,
I returned with Yumeno-san.
what's wrong?
Mother.
Yumeno, congratulations!
Sis Yumeno,
Happy birthday!
Congratulations!
Every year, since you dislike it,
we can't celebrate it,
But as it's such an important day, from now on,
we will properly celebrate it.
Then, sit down, sit down
Happy birthday to you...
Happy birthday to you..
Happy birthday..
Yumeno, Yumeno!
Sister!
Akira-san
Happy birthday.
I'm handing over,
what you left behind the other time.
I..
I wonder if it was a good thing to be born..
Akira-san
Well, I'm sure it's good.
isn't it?
What kind of dog was
Yasuke's mom?
Who could it be?
Yes.
I'm Yumeno's mother,
and I have something to talk with you.
You..what did you do to Yumeno?
That girl suddenly started to act strange.
Isn't it your fault?
You were together today also, right?
What did you do to Yumeno!
Dr...
I wonder if you could help..
10 million is fine
to save that girl from trouble.
Mother.
eh?
Today, do you what day is it?
What day?
Today, it's Akira-san's birthday.
Birthday?
It's just that I don't celebrate
such dates.
Mother, you might have it hard too,
but, you go further and want to cause pain to Akira-san
No matter how many cruel things
you did to her,
No matter how many awful things you said to her,
Akira-san
is willing to forgive you
she wants to be loved by you.
I feel sorry for Akira-san.
You, in some way,
resemble Akira.
I mean the smell..
Could it be that you too,
still miss the breasts
of your mom?
to begin with, why don't you have the scent of a woman?
Although you have money and prestige
Have you already sleep with Akira?
so uncool
Your mother was a woman like me?
sluttish with men
because of that, you became sort of scared of
going out with women?
Lucky guess!
Really!
You and my Akira are really alike.
This mom with such an elegant face
had an affair.
With someone like you as a mother,
it would have been better not to have one.
Subs by Kitty-nyan
*´¨)
¸.•´¸.•*´¨) ¸.•*¨)
(¸.•´ (¸.•` ¤ (\_(\
¤ (=' :')
¤.. (,('')('') .. ¤
¤ Chuline ¤
Yasuke??? Noooo