So the 'rin' in Hino Rintaro is just
the 'rin' in ethics violation.
If you don't want to be sued for this photo,
wanna buy it?
I refuse, please leave.
Calm down a little.
Then for this picture, how much
are you asking to sell it?
The doctor over here gets what I'm talking about!
How about 50 million?
You said 50 million..
You wanna pay, right?
Dr. Rintaro, the medical ethics transgressor.
Ah!
What..
Eh! No way!
er...you..
Ki..Kiku..
Kikuchiyo-san?
Ah Kikuchiyo-san Kikuchiyo-san!
I knew it.
No.. you haven't change!
What? Are you an old customer?
Yes.. I was brought by my senpai,
And though I only met you twice,
I remember you served me sake.
I can see you haven't change..still beautiful.
Stop it, what are you saying..
I mean,
you give off this impressive aura,
is it called a mature sex appeal?
I just..
Nah..
Something that when stare at, you
can't help but get sucked in.
That's too pretentious!
Isn't the detective coming any time now?
That's right, the police is coming.
A detective?
You see, he's a psychiatrist, right?
Occasionally, a patient like that comes here,
with a dangerous entangled incident.
If that's the case...I'll just be a bother.
Hino-rin.
Next, I'll give you a call.
Keep the 50 million prepared.
I'll leave it to you.
Senpai,
thank you for using your wit quickly.
So that person is the mother
who is causing problems to the geisha?
Yes.
You know, a face like that..
is from someone who has been extorting
and deceiving people many times.
You want to apologize to Yumeno?
The truth is that the other day
I had a party with my colleagues
and I invited her there.
So that was the case.
Yes.
And even though she told me she's shy,
I'm afraid that my forced invitation,
was an inconvenience.
Actually, there's no such a shy girl here,
at the parlor.
I want to apologize to her,
about that.
Yumeno-chan, wait.
Now, they are discussing an important matter.
So, the Dir. Ennoji will call you later.
O-kay.
The one who should be apologizing is me.
Because I didn't notice that child was sick
until you told me.
Yumechiyo-san,
even living together,
there are many times when it passes unnoticed.
I think that it's because the contact with her mother
increased, her symptoms appeared stronger.
with her mother?
Yumeno-san, good evening.
Good evening.
The acquisition negotiations of
Soumei medical corporation,
have almost reach to an agreement on the amount.
Wow .. that's a huge hospital.
How much?
An unprecedented amount of 60 billion.
60 billion!!
That's pretty big, for a hospital.
Considering it's with the land,
it's cheap.
Ah, is that so?
So, regarding the matter of subsidies.
Ah.. about that..
I wonder if I can ask something first.
what would be that?
I'd like you to treat one patient.
A patient?
Yeah, I think it's brain tumor.
Well, that's Hasumi-kun's specialized field.
Yes, of what kind is it?
No, I don't know much more than the illness, but
do you know someone called Kusunoki Shozo?
The minister.
It's his only son.
The fact is that the minister Kusunoki is the authority
for the approval of the subsidiary aid.
That's right.
That means, whether we can
receive the 5 billion subsidy or not,
depends on Prof. Hasumi's hands, so to speak.
You're really straightforward.
But you're right.
Ah..that was a slip of the tongue.
Is it okay? Hasumi-kun.
This.. depends on my part.
Don't say such negative words here.
Dr. Hasumi,
don't you want to do something to help?
If you succeed, everyone here will be happy.
Please rest assured.
Hasumi-kun is one of the best brain surgeons in Japan.
I'm relying on you.
I understand.
Then, let's toast, right?
Just before that..
Excuse me.
Press Secretary Ike,
nice to meet you, my name is Araki.
Here
Hasumi, did you forget my face?
Hello.
Araki-kun and Hasumi-kun
are our contemporaries.
Since he is a psychiatrist,
I'm thinking of letting him in
the place of Hino-kun.
If so, what is going to happen
to Hino-kun?
He's brilliant, but
he doesn't listen to people.
He's under consideration from now on.
Is that so.
Excuse me.
Good evening, I'm Yumeno.
Yumeno-chan.
Ike-chan, I wanted to see you.
Me too.
Hey, what were you talking about?
No, just another talk fun for adults.
So, today
let's drink a good sake.
Get it ready.
Yes.
Hey, how are you doing?
It's been a while.
Ah..we met a while ago.
Hino
What does it mean?
Is it true that Araki is returning to psychiatry?
What are you..
Are you okay?!
What happened?
I just felt a little dizzy.
You haven't been informed?
I wasn't inform of anything.
That bastard, what is he thinking.
Dr. Hasumi.
What?
Can you see my face?
Don't ask stupid things.
You need to have an eyesight test.
I don't need.
I don't need it.
Dr. Hasumi.
So, now let's move forward with no fear!
I'm your ally.
This is a story of a doctor that saves
the lost sheep of this modern era.
Sorry for the late introduction,
I'm a psychiatrist, Hino Rintaro
Next it's Aizawa Akira-san.
Come in.
Huh?
Do you mean that the surgery is gonna be impossible?
Yes, surgery is off-label
Prof. Hasumi, what do you mean with
the surgery being off-label?
Until now, you have been performing
any sort of risky tumor removal surgeries
with a successful result, isn't it?
Explain your reasons
Looking at the MRI image ....
the tumor in the left temporal lobe
has infiltrated the vicinity of the hippocampus.
It involves a considerable risk to remove the tumor.
But there isn't a risk of death, right?
There is a risk of damaging the hippocampus with the scalpel.
One mistake and
he may have a loss of memories.
You can't refuse this surgery.
What, what do you need?
Have you also noticed it?
Where's Dr. Rintaro?
He's examining a patient now.
I see.
Let's talk in my room until he finishes.
In your room?
If Prof. Hasumi is not able to perform properly,
it'll be a problem.
What?
I.. I also
have something I'd like to tell you about.
Can I have a minute?
May I?
Okay.
Akira-san, do you like to dance?
I like to dance.
Even though I don't remember
much about the parlor,
but I know when I dance.
Is that so.
When did you start dancing?
Maybe, since I was around 21 years old.
Even since I was little
I couldn't do anything right,
but with dancing, it was the first time
mom gave me compliments.
"As expected from my daughter", she said.
It's a memory of your mom that you want to cherish, right?
When I went to the parlor for the first, I was also
impressed with your dancing.
Please come again.
I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you very much.
Please take care in your way home.
Dr. Hino, could you come for a moment?
What?
Hino, come.
What happened?
Look at this.
Confirm the tumor's depths
Micro cooper
Yes.
Dr. Hasumi, are you okay?
I knew it, he can't see.
Also Prof. Hasumi rejected
a special patient's operation today.
He has succeeded brilliantly operating
in similar cases in the past.
It's not like he can't do it.
A while ago too, at Dr. Hino's examining room
he stumbled in a strange way.
It didn't seem like a
simple dizziness.
Perhaps, back then that was what happened.
That wasn't just a mistake, right?
That was a mistake.
It was a mistake, that?
When did that happen?
At the beginning of this year.
This year?
Since the beginning of this year,
the number of his operations has decreased.
Come to think of it, Dr. Hasumi
refused to take the eyesight test.
The Prof. doesn't wear glasses.
In other words, his visual impairment can't be corrected
with glasses
The Prof. is a brain surgeon.
If there's a problem in the brain,
he should be able to deal with it on his own.
What do you mean?
A visual impairment that can't be corrected with glasses.
It might be a psychogenic visual impairment.
Excuse me.
Have you decided to schedule the surgery yet?
It's under consideration.
There are the risks I mentioned this morning
and more..
It looks like you don't understand this.
Eh?
If we can solve this time's case
with Kusunoki Minister,
the talk about the new Hospital
will go smoothly.
You'll become a lifesaver
hard to replace, for both parent and son.
If that happens,
nobody will complain when you become
the new hospital's director.
Huh..
You said it, right?
"I want to help,
no matter whether it's one or many patients,
at the finally established cutting-edge
Toshiminami International Medical Center."
This dream will come true!
Yes..
What are you hesitating about?
You don't have the right to say 'no'
Do not say he may
lose his memory.
I'm the one that saved you
from medical lawsuit.
Do not forget it!
Until tomorrow,
without exceptions, start scheduling the operation.
Is it okay?
Understood.
Mom,
I'm going to the lesson.
Have a nice day. Be careful on your way there.
Yes.
Ah, sis, welcome home.
Ah mother,
I'm sorry, I'll get ready really fast.
It's okay, if you're tired.
Why don't you take a day off?
From the lessons and also the parlor.
No, but..
It's fine, once in a while.
I'm sorry,
I'm always causing you inconveniences.
No, I also
I'm sorry, until now
I didn't realize anything.
You know, the Akira in you,
and the Yumeno in you,
I like both of you.
Mother...
Yeah?
Isn't that strange!
Even you, mother,
have been brainwashed by Hino-rin.
Mother, if I leave the parlor,
it'll be bad for you, right?
who's earning with this.
Yumeno..?
If it's psychogenic,
I wonder what's the cause.
The director is going to do a new hospital
You knew it, right?
Yeah.
The rumor is about who will be the
new director there? Dr. Hasumi
Eh_ Who gave that information?
Nurse station.
They are well informed.
That's scary in some way.
So, I wonder if the friction of such hospital politics
aren't accumulating.
If he is that much cornered
isn't it better to refuse?
They have different sense of values than you.
Even though we're all doctors?
To say that is really foolish, right?
Those people in order to climb the stairs
of the White Tower University Hospital,
and because of that they are sacrificing a lot of things.
Sacrificing..
I wonder if there's a need to pay such a price
in order to climb.
Is it not the same for you, Rintaro?
Huh?
Because you, aren't you doing this for you mom
even at the expense of yourself?
It's the same for all.
Fighting and doing their best for that.
Sorry..
for suddenly starting to say weird things.
Mizushima, I have something to ask you.
What?
Dr. Hasumi. Good morning.
Good morning.
Professor, please.
What is it?
Dr. Hino wants to have a talk with you.
Hino? But we have a meeting now.
Since we can contact with the brain surgery department, do not worry.
Huh?
You will excuse us.
Excuse me.
What's going on! Hey!
Sorry.
Excuse us.
I'm really sorry, Dr. Hasumi.
I see.
You're known for pushing things this far.
Sorry, but I can't adjust
in a good way to your approach.
It seems you have a problem with your vision?
What can you do about it?
I can hear you.
So it does not solve anything.
A clue for a solution might be grasped.
Your face is blurred.
I can' read this.
I've constriction of the visual field. The acuity is 0.01.
The cephalic MRI found no abnormalities.
No abnormalities in the optic nerve.
The cause is unknown.
I do not see any solution.
Dr. Hasumi,
Will you receive my examination?
You want to say it's psychogenic visual impairment?
I don't know that yet.
I dislike your field.
Dr., I'm also a doctor.
I understand those current painful feelings.
I don't care if you're willing to feel sympathy!
At this point there's nothing to do.
Hello.
Ah, hi.
I was just thinking about calling you.
Is it about the Minister's son, right?
Of course it is!
The Minister is waiting for reply as soon as possible.
What are you hesitating about.
Or is it that you want to miss this opportunity?
Absolutely not!
I've already invested hundreds of millions on this.
Then, do not put me to shame!
You fool!
Even without that,
my stomach constantly hurts.
Ah.. I want to drink tea.
Dr. Hino's tea..
Minister Ike is angry.
I won't accept any other answer but a 'Yes'!
Give an answer Hasumi! An answer!
I'm your lifesaver, you bastard!
I understand.
Then, it's good.
Eh? Hasumi?
I really hate that guy.
That's all. The end.
Senpai, let's reduce this a little.
Why are you talking like a doctor?
Please hear what I have to say.
Okay, okay.
But, even we used to be contemporaries,
it's been already 10 years since
I quit that Hospital.
Dr. Hasumi suffers a visual impairment.
Certainly, that was odd.
Something must have happened in the past.
I'll make some tea.
You ran out of tea again, don't you?
What's that?
A medical malpractice"?
Yeah.
She was also an Ennoji's special patient.
"The victim is Satonaka Mizuki-san, 31-year-old,
daughter of a certain famous confectionery maker's director.
Yeah.
She was also my patient.
What?
Everyone
speaks bad things about me.
I'm being observed, all the time.
Even now..
No ... Stop it!
Satonaka-san
Let's calm down.
Satonaka-san, let's calm down.
It's okay, okay.
Let's calm down, it's fine.
It's okay.
Let's take a deep breath, slowly.
Yes, exhale.
Yes, like that.
Okay, one more time.
"Paranoia and short-term memory disorder
were observed at Satonaka-san's first medical
examination, and she
was suspected to suffer from schizophrenia."
"But, her attending physician, Mr. Araki,
from symptoms such as seizures,
after carrying out a re-examination,
diagnosed a temporal lobe epilepsy.
Even, Mr. Hasumi, a brain surgeon from the same hospital,
determined the same diagnosis.
And Satonaka-san's diagnosis was confirmed."
Yeah.
Even at that time, he..
Wait a moment.
That surgical procedure,
will left a memory disorder, right?
But, in this case
the high stability of
the selective amygdalohippocampectomy, is the best alternative.
If so, the outside of the brain tissue
almost won't require a resection.
What are you nervous about?
With your skills
you can preserve the hippocampus with the latest
multiple subpial transections surgery,
and you can also preserve the memories, right?
I'm counting on you, Hasumi.
Please.
I refuse
You, since when
you've become that self-protective
The latest surgery procedure that you mention,
hasn't yet been settled in the country.
Listen up!
The memories..
are the equivalent of life for a patient!
Hey!
"It resulted in the Hospital accepting Mr. Hasumi's opinion.
Although surgery was successful,
Satonaka-san developed the feared sequela,
she lost her memory."
It's enough already about that talk.
Take that and leave,
I'm feeling bad, move.
"The cause of this, was seen as a medical error
for the patient and her family,
and they urged the Hospital
and sued both doctors, Araki and Hasumi.
However, 2 months later, both sides
unexpectedly settled on an indefinite figure.
What happened behind that settlement
is unknown."
Senpai, are you okay?
I told you to leave, right?
Dir. Ennoji was involved with the settlement, right?
Don't know.
Satonaka-san, after that..
Ask it to Hasumi
Yumeno, I'm coming in.
Oh ... you fall asleep.
Right?
Mother, thank you
Yumeno, thank you too.
But do not come out anymore.
Ruriko,
Eh what is it?
Jun-chan, just
can you go and buy cigarettes?
What?
How much do you want?
Huh? what? Is that kind of talk?
I really like it.
The money,
I'll get it somehow,
Please, just don't meet Yumeno again.
Please!
Oh isn't that interesting?
Yeah
I want 100 million,
I'll leave it in 50 million.
I came up with a nice idea, right?
I will certainly prepare for you the 50 million.
So, about Yumeno..
Promise not to meet Yumeno anymore.
On this street.
Eh!?
You're really giving me the 50 million?
Hey, hey!
you're giving me the 50 million? Hey!
I get it.
Okay.
I promise.
I am sorry to have asked you to come.
I'm listening.
I heard from Akari senpai,
the fact about the medical accident, 10 years ago.
Satonak-san developed the feared sequela
she lost her memory.
Also about she's dead?
What?
That patient died six months ago.
Is that so?
Somehow I couldn't just leave it like that.
I went to the funeral.
Why did you come?
Why?
All I could do was to apologize.
During 10 years..
Since the operation
Satonaka-san lived for 10 years.
I did not expect that outcome.
But, her mother,
every single day, had to listened from her own daughter.
"Are you really my mother?"
Are you really my mother?
She continued to ask that.
The day of the funeral,
she faced to me and said,
It'd have been better..
if my daughter and I
ten years ago
if you had killed both of us.
"Memories are the equivalent to life for the patient"
The words that Araki told me at that time
were true.
What is important as a doctor,
is not just to keep them alive,
but to save that person's life.
From the moment I become aware
of the meaning of those words
my vision began to decline.
Dr. Hansumi,
The more you try to
forget and deny the feeling,
all the more stronger that feeling will grow.
To break this vicious circle,
first, you have to accept that memory.
you may not be able to really
forget that memory.
For me,
there's also an unforgettable memory.
I haven't overcome that memory yet.
Rintaro
Mom, you try your best too.
However, I
I've learned from a lot of patients,
Those patients visiting the doctor's office,
everyone,
has to face a painful memory that is piercing their hearts,
and to reach to an agreement somehow.
That has become my support.
For Dr. Hasumi too,
from now on,
I think that you should slowly start to accept it.
It's okay.
You have already started to accept it.
That's why,
a sign appeared on your body.
If you were me, what would you do?
More than the fact that I can't see by now
I no longer worth as a surgeon anymore.
I would
slowly take a rest in order to heal.
What are you doing in here, Hasumi-kun?
What?
The condition of the Minister's son suddenly changed.
He's arriving soon,
move quickly towards the operation room.
Ha..
Hurry!
No matter what, the operation must be successful!
Director, please wait.
This isn't your business.
Hasumi-kun, just go!
I understand.
Dr., you should know!
What would happen now,
if you operate with that body.
I'm a doctor
I can't afford doing nothing.
Dr. Hasumi
What about the patient?
He just entered the operation room, please hurry.
Let's look for another hospital.
We won't make it on time.
Mitsushima-kun, help me.
Yes.
He was in a state of confusion.
An enlargement of the lateral ventricle is observed in the CT.
What do you think?
I think it's an obstructive hydrocephalus.
I've the same opinion, the vitals?
Blood pressure 100,
the heart rate has improved to 80.
What would you do?
I'd do a craniotomy, performing a tumor removal.
The sub-temporal
or the inferior corner approach ..
There are chances of leaving the hippocampus?
I think there're possibilities of cutting it.
Everybody, without resting a hand, listen to me.
I can't operate today.
In fact, this last half a year
my eyesight has continued to deteriorate.
Mizushima-kun will be the surgeon instead.
It should be fine.
I'll give all the instructions.
Secure firmly the surgical field,
the base of the temporal,
so as not to damage the choroidal artery.
Hurry up.
Yes.
Ah, sorry, about the surgery..
Dr. Mizushima will be the surgeon.
Mizushima will?
Yumeno's memories are also my memories
That's why it's okay.
So it's okay if you don't come out anymore.
Akira-san
Yes.
Come out a little.
Hey, how many hours will it take?
Do you want me to show on the monitor
how is the surgery?
No, it's okay.
My blood is weak.
The fusiform gyrus is in sight.
Slide a little the brain spatula.
Expand the base of the temporal.
Understood
Fixation off.
Yes.
On.
Bipolar.
Yumechiyo will give me
50 million.
Mother will give you?
Yeah.
That's why I don't longer need you to do it.
Take care, okay?
Byyy~e!
When are you coming back?
Mom!
What does it mean that you don't need me?
please ....
Please! Please!
Do not leave me! I beg you!
Mom..
Ah, I forgot, right, right.
Here, I forgot
I brought your candy.
Here.
Here
No..
I don't want it, don't want..
Take it!
I don't need you anymore!
I don't need you..
Goodbye.
Dr. Hino,
a phone call from Yumeno-san.
Please hurry, she's quite upset.
Okay.
Hello, what is it?
Dr., you said it, right, doctor..
Did something happen? Akira-san
My mother's memories
also Yumeno's memories,
you said that I should cherish them..
But, my mother is gone.
Why..?
Why..
I no longer need you, she said.
Akira-san, where are you now?
We have complete exposure of the
hippocampus and amygdala
How does it look?
There's a severe adhesion of the tumor.
Micro Cooper.
Yes.
Make sure not to hurt the hippocampus.
I understand.
Dr. Hino?
Is Akira-san there?
She went out, but
did something happen?
Yuriko-san
seems to have said to Akira-san
that she doesn't need her anymore.
Actually, I ....
The money,
I'll get it somehow,
just don't meet Yumeno again.
Please!
Is that so.. I understand.
Did I do something I shouldn't?
No, there is no such thing.
Please, if she returns, let me know.
I'd like to talk with Akira-san.
I understand.
Director.
Kusunoki Yūji-sama's surgery
has been successful.
Really! That's good, good.
Ah, contact Minister Ike on the phone.
Okay.
Yea, that's good.
Yea, that's good, good.
Dr. Hino.
That was a success thanks to Mizushima-kun.
Is that so!
That was truly a great work.
By not looking, it's the first time I can see.
What is it?
Memories are stored in the brain.
It's not the brain what we are dealing with.
It's memories, it's minds. It's life.
The heart of the humans is located in the brain.
You may not agree with me.
No, I agree with you.
I don't know the location for the heart.
And because I don't know,
I've continued with this work.
Once again,
I want to face the patient.
Is see.
In order to do that,
let's recover, taking a rest, slowly.
Good evening.
Yumeno-san.
I'm in need of money.
I am in need of money.
Please, calm down.
Haven't your mother said
that she doesn't
need more money anymore?
That's why I need the money, isn't it!
But, why?
Because Akira
will be discarded, isn't she!
By such a mother!
do you get it?
Akira wants to be loved
by that mother!
That's why I need the money!
I understand.
You
want to erase me away, right?
Akira too,
she said she didn't need me anymore.
Since you instigate her,
to believe she doesn't need me anymore!
I
sell flattery to men I don't even like.
every night, all types of men..
I charm and entertain
every night all kind of men.
Deceiving, stealing their money..
Then, what is that I am!
What is that you understand!
Why do you want me to disappear!
Yumeno-san.
I never thought about wanting
to erase you.
I just
want to connect both of your times,
Akira-san and yours.
To have part of your life, part of your time,
missing or left out,
doesn't it cause you anxiety?
Yumeno-san's time
and Akira-san's time, both are important.
Fun memories, painful memories,
all of them included are part of you!
Hino-rin, you're really stupid, right?
Those memories are really painful.
Then, I'll show you some painful memories.
A call from the Minister Kusunoki.
It's Ennoji.
No, no..!
It's because our neurosurgery team is excellent.
Yeah.
Ah.. thank you very much.
We'll be talking about that matter again soon.
Well, until then.
Yes, goodbye.
Good morning.
Morning!
well, thanks to you,
the talk about the new hospital
is progressing really well.
Your director's office
should be at the top floor facing south? eh?
You'll have a view to the courtyard.
Director.
And, since next time, I'll reserve a seat for
Minister Kusonoki
you should also greet him.
About that matter,
in fact,...
Dir.! Big problems!
At least knock first, you.
Sorry.
Have you seen this already?
What?
what is this?
What's this!
What's this,
what's this!!
Good morning.
What's wrong?
Dr. Hino.
This..
Subs by Kitty-nyan
*´¨)
¸.•´¸.•*´¨) ¸.•*¨)
(¸.•´ (¸.•` ¤ (\_(\
¤ (=' :')
¤.. (,('')('') .. ¤
¤ Chuline ¤