I knew Harvey Dent.
I was his friend.
And it will be a very long time before
someone inspires us the way he did.
I believed in Harvey Dent.
Dr. Pavel, I'm CIA.
He wasn't alone.
- Uh, you don't get to bring friends.
- They are not my friends.
Don't worry, no charge for them.
And why would I want them?
They were trying to grab your prize.
They work for the mercenary.
The masked man.
- Bane?
- Aye.
Get them onboard. I'll call it in.
The flight plan I just
filed with the agency
lists me, my men, Dr. Pavel here
but only one of you!
First one to talk gets
to stay on my aircraft!
Who paid you to grab Dr. Pavel?
He didn't fly so good!
Who wants to try next?
Tell me about Bane!
Why does he wear the mask?
A lot of loyalty for a hired gun!
Well, perhaps he's wondering
why someone would shoot a man
before throwing him out of a plane.
At least you can talk.
Who are you?
It doesn't matter who we are.
What matters is our plan.
No one cared who I was
till I put on the mask.
If I pull that off, will you die?
It would be extremely painful.
You're a big guy.
For you.
Was getting caught part of your plan?
Of course.
Dr. Pavel refused our
offer in favor of yours.
We had to find out what he told you...
Nothing. I said nothing.
Well, congratulations,
you got yourself caught!
- Sir?
- Now what's the next step of your master plan?
Crashing this plane
with no survivors.
Mayday, Mayday!
Aah! What you doing to me? Let me out!
No!
No, no, no! No!
No! They expect one of us
in the wreckage, brother.
Have we started the fire?
Yes, the fire rises.
Calm down, doctor. Now
is not the time for fear.
That comes later.
Harvey Dent Day may not be
our oldest public holiday
but we're here tonight because
it's one of the most important.
Harvey Dent's uncompromising
stand against organized crime
had made Gotham a safer place
than it was at the time of
his death, eight years ago.
This city has seen a
historic turnaround.
No city is without crime,
but this city is without organized crime
because the Dent Act
gave law enforcement teeth
in its fight against the mob.
Now people are talking
about repealing the Dent Act
and to them I say, "Not on my watch."
I want to thank the Wayne
Foundation for hosting this event.
I'm told Mr. Wayne
couldn't be here tonight.
I'm sure he's with us in spirit.
And now I'm gonna give
way to an important voice
You ever lay eyes on Wayne
at one of these things?
No one has. Not in years.
people put their faith
in a murderous thug
in a mask and a cape.
A thug who showed his true nature
when he betrayed the
trust of this great man
and murdered him in cold blood.
Sweetheart, not so fast with the chow.
- Shrimp balls?
- Thank you.
Jim Gordon can tell you
the truth about Harvey Dent.
I'll let him tell you himself.
Commissioner Gordon.
The truth?
I have
written a speech
telling the truth about Harvey Dent.
Maybe the time isn't right.
Maybe right now
all you need to know is that
there are 1000 inmates
in Blackgate Prison
as a direct result of the Dent Act.
These are violent criminals,
essential cogs in the
organized- crime machine.
Maybe, for now, all I should say
about the death of Harvey Dent is this:
It has not been for nothing.
You see the guy who owns the house?
No. I heard he never
leaves the east wing.
I heard he had an accident.
- Yeah, that he's disfigured. He has to wear a...
- Mr. Till?
Why are your people
using the main staircase?
And where's Mrs. Bolton?
Uh, she's at the bar, sir. Can I help?
The east drawing room.
Unlock the door, put
the tray on the table,
lock the door again. Nothing more.
I'm sorry, Miss Tate. I
tried, but he won't see you.
And you mustn't take it personally.
Everyone knows that
Wayne's holed up in there
with 8- inch nails
peeing into Mason jars.
It's very good of you
to let me on the grounds.
Why are you wasting your
time trying to talk to a man
who threw away your
investment on some
save- the- world vanity project?
He can't get your money back. I can.
I could try explaining
that a save- the- world
project,
vain or not is worth
investing in, Mr. Daggett.
But you understand only money
and the power you think it buys
so why waste my time indeed?
Second shift reports in?
You should spend more
time with the mayor.
Well, that's your department.
Anyone shown him the crime stats?
He goes by his gut and it bothers him,
no matter what the numbers.
Must be popular with his wife.
Not really. She took
the kids to Cleveland.
He'll have plenty of time for visits.
The mayor's gonna
dump him in the spring.
Really?
- But he's a hero.
- A war hero. This is peacetime.
Oh, sorry, sorry. I'm so
terribly sorry, Mr. Wayne.
It is Mr. Wayne, isn't it?
Although you don't
have the long nails or,
heh, the facial scars, sir.
Is that what they say about me?
It's just that no one ever sees you.
That's a beautiful necklace.
Reminds me of one that
belonged to my mother.
It can't be the same one
because her pearls are in this safe
the manufacturer clearly
explained is uncrackable.
Nobody told me it was uncrackable.
I'm afraid I can't let you take those.
Look, you wouldn't
beat up a woman any more
than I would beat up a cripple.
Of course, sometimes
exceptions have to be made.
Good night, Mr. Wayne.
Can I have a ride?
You read my mind.
Let's go.
Miss Tate was asking to see you again.
She's very persistent.
And quite lovely, in
case you were wondering.
- I wasn't.
- What are you doing?
Examining print dust. We've been robbed.
And this is your idea of,
uh, sounding the alarm, is it?
She took the pearls,
tracking device and all.
- She?
- One of the maids.
Perhaps you should stop letting
them in this side of the house.
Perhaps you should start
learning to make your own bed.
- Why were you dusting for prints?
- I wasn't.
She was.
Sir. Congressman Gilly's
wife has been calling in.
The congressman never made it home
after the Wayne Foundation event.
That's a job for the police?
When you and Dent cleaned the
streets, you cleaned them good.
Pretty soon we'll be chasing
down, uh, overdue library books.
And yet here you are,
like we're still at war.
- What's your name, son?
- Blake, sir.
You have something you want to ask me?
It's about that night.
This night, eight years
ago. The night Dent died.
The last confirmed
sighting of the Batman.
He murders those people,
takes down two SWAT teams
breaks Dent's neck
and then just vanishes?
I'm not hearing a question, son.
Don't you want to know who he was?
I know exactly who he was.
He was the Batman.
Let's go see about
the congressman's wife.
Master Wayne?
You haven't been down
here in a long time.
Trying to find out more about
our jewel thief. I ran her prints.
Unless she's lost a lot of weight
she was wearing someone
else's fingerprints.
She's good.
She may be, but we have
a trace on the necklace.
We do. I cross- referenced
the address she went back
to with police data on
high- end B- and- E's, and, um
Selina Kyle.
The databases are full of
close- calls, tips from fences.
She's good, but the ground
is shrinking beneath her feet.
We should send the police
before she fences the pearls.
She won't. She likes them too much.
And they weren't what she was after.
- What was she after?
- My fingerprints.
It was printer toner mixed
with graphite on the safe.
It gives a good pull
and it's untraceable.
Fascinating. You two should
exchange notes over coffee.
You're trying to set me
up with a jewel thief?
At this point, I'd set
you up with a chimpanzee,
if it brought you back to the world.
There's nothing out there for me.
And that's the problem.
You hung up your cape and your
cowl but you didn't move on.
You never went to find
a life. To find someone.
Alfred
I did find someone.
I know, and you lost them.
But that's all part of living, sir.
But you're not living,
you're just waiting,
hoping for things to go bad again.
Remember when you left Gotham?
Before all this, before Batman?
You were gone seven years.
Seven years I waited, hoping
that you wouldn't come back.
Every year, I took a
holiday. I went to Florence.
There's this cafe on
the banks of the Arno.
Every fine evening I'd sit
there and order a Fernet Branca.
I had this fantasy
that I would look across the tables
and I'd see you there, with a wife.
Maybe a couple of kids.
You wouldn't say anything
to me, nor me to you.
But we'd both know that you'd made it.
That you were happy.
I never wanted you to
come back to Gotham.
I always knew there was
nothing here for you,
except pain and tragedy.
And I wanted something
more for you than that.
I still do.
They wash up here a
couple of times a month.
More when it gets colder.
Homeless, sheltering in the tunnels.
We pulled him from the basin,
but other than that we didn't touch him.
- What?
- Name's Jimmy.
He's from St. Swithin's.
It's the boys' home
where I coach some ball.
Jimmy hadn't been around for months.
- No? Why?
- Blake, you know why.
He aged out. We don't
have the resources to
keep boys on after 16.
I thought the Wayne
Foundation gave money for that.
Not for the past couple of years.
- He has a brother here, doesn't he?
- Mark. I'll tell him.
I'd like to, if that's all right.
You know what he was
doing in the tunnels?
Lot of guys been going down
the tunnels when they age out.
Say you can live down there.
Say there's work down there.
Work?
What kind of work are you
gonna find in the sewers?
More than you can find up here, I guess.
So you know about him?
Of course.
Do you think he's coming back?
I don't know.
You brought a date?
I like having someone
around to open doors for me.
Right hand. No partials.
Very nice.
Not so fast, handsome.
You got something for me?
Ah, yes.
I don't know what you're planning
to do with Mr. Wayne's prints,
but I'm guessing you'll need his thumb.
You don't count so good, huh?
I count fine.
In fact, I'm counting to 10 right now.
Okay.
My friend's outside. Just hit "Send."
This place is a little dead.
It'll liven up in a minute. Trust me.
Is everything okay?
Great. Catch you later.
It would have been a lot easier
to just give me what we agreed.
We can't have loose ends.
And even in that dress,
no one's gonna miss you.
No.
But my friend over there?
Every cop in the city's missing him.
That's cute.
But they're not gonna be
looking in a place like this.
I don't know. You did
just use his cell phone.
- Go!
Police! Get down now!
Help me! Help me!
Help me, please! Please help me!
Keep some pressure on that, sweetheart.
Call me?
- You okay, miss?
- He's bleeding. You gotta help him.
I got the congressman.
Clear!
Manhole! Get this up!
Get the DWP down here!
You three, down with me.
You two, you go down,
cover the next exit!
What, they went down there?
We're gonna go down there, right?
That was a gas explosion, kid.
Wasn't gas. It's a sewer.
No one goes in till
we know what's there.
We know, sir. The police commissioner.
Someone get this hothead out of here?
And where's that DWP guy?
Why are you here?
Answer him.
I was asking you.
It's the police commissioner.
And you brought him down here?
- We didn't know what to do.
- You panicked.
And your weakness has cost
the lives of three others.
No, he's alone.
Search him.
Then I will kill you.
- He's dead.
- So show me his body.
The water runs to any one of the
outflows. We'd never find him.
- Follow him!
- Follow him?
You okay? You okay?
Hey, hey, you awake?
I need to see Bruce Wayne.
I'm sorry, Mr. Wayne doesn't
take unscheduled calls.
Even from a police officer.
And if I go get a warrant
for the investigation
of Harvey Dent's murder?
That still count as unscheduled?
What can I do for you, officer?
Commissioner Gordon's been shot.
He chased a gunman down into the sewers.
When I pulled him out, he was
babbling about an underground army.
A masked man called Bane.
Shouldn't you be telling
your superior officers?
They asked me if he saw
any giant alligators.
He needs you.
He needs the Batman.
If Commissioner Gordon thinks...
he doesn't know or care who you are.
But we've met before.
It was a long time ago. I
was a kid. Uh, St. Swithin's.
It used to be funded by the Wayne
Foundation. It's an orphanage.
My mom died when I was small.
It was a car accident, I
don't really remember it.
But my dad got shot a couple
years later over a gambling debt
and I remember that one just fine.
Not a lot of people know
what it feels like, do they?
To be angry in your bones.
I mean, they understand.
Foster parents.
Everybody understands
for a while.
And then they want the angry little kid
to do something he knows he can't do.
Move on.
So after a while, they
stop understanding.
They send the angry kid to a boys' home.
I figured it out too late. You
gotta learn to hide the anger.
Practice smiling in a mirror.
It's like putting on a mask.
So you showed up this
one day, in a cool car.
Pretty girl on your arm.
We were so excited.
Bruce Wayne, billionaire orphan.
I mean, we used to make up
stories about you, man. Legends.
And, you know, with the other kids,
that's all it was, just stories, but
Right when I saw you, I
knew who you really were.
I'd seen that look on your face before.
It's the same one I taught myself.
I don't know why you took
the fall for Dent's murder
but I'm still a believer in the Batman
even if you're not.
Why did you say that your boys'
home used to be funded
by the Wayne Foundation?
Because the money stopped.
Might be time to get some fresh air.
Start paying attention to the details.
Some of those details
might need your help.
You check that name? Bane?
He's a mercenary. No other known names.
Him and his men were
behind a coup in West Africa
that secured mining operations
for our friend John Daggett.
- Now Daggett's brought them here.
- Or so it seems.
- I'll keep digging.
- Yeah.
Alfred, why did the Wayne
Foundation stop funding
boys' homes in the city?
The foundation is funded by the
profits of Wayne Enterprises.
There have to be some.
- Time to talk to Mr. Fox, I think.
- I'll get him on the phone.
No, no, no. Do we still have
any cars around the place?
Yes. One or two.
I need an appointment at
the hospital for my leg.
- Which hospital?
- Whichever one Jim Gordon's in.
- I have seen worse cartilage in knees.
- That's good.
No. That's because there is
no cartilage in your knee.
And not much of any use in
your elbows or your shoulders.
Between that and the scar
tissue on your kidneys
the residual concussive
damage to your brain tissue
and the general scarred- over
quality of your body
- I cannot recommend that
you go heli- skiing. - Right.
We were in this together
then you were gone.
The Batman wasn't needed anymore.
- We won.
- Based on a lie.
And now there's evil rising
from where we tried to bury it.
The Batman has to come back.
What if he doesn't exist anymore?
He must.
You took my goddamn wallet, didn't you?
- You f... You took my wallet!
- No, I
- Get out.
- She took my... Ah!
- Now.
- Creep!
I don't know what he's so upset about.
There's only 60 bucks in here.
Probably the watch.
Who's that?
A stiff can barely climb
out of his sports car.
- No, that's Bruce Wayne!
- Mr. Wayne, over here!
I'm not sure if my assistant...
- Right through here.
Thank you so much.
Bruce Wayne at a charity ball.
Miss Tate, isn't it?
Even before you became a recluse,
you never came to these things.
The proceeds go to the big fat
spread. It's not about charity.
It's about feeding the ego of
whichever society hag laid this on.
Actually, this is my party, Mr. Wayne.
And the proceeds will
go where they should,
because I paid for the
big fat spread myself.
That's very generous of you.
You have to invest if you want
to restore balance to the world.
Take our clean- energy project.
Sometimes the investment
doesn't pay off.
- I'm sorry.
- You have a practiced apathy, Mr. Wayne.
But a man who doesn't care about
the world doesn't spend
half his fortune to save it.
And isn't so wounded when it fails
that he goes into hiding.
Have a good evening, Mr. Wayne.
Mind if I cut in?
Thank you.
You don't seem happy to see me.
You were supposed to be a shut- in.
I felt like some fresh air.
Why didn't you call the police?
I have a powerful friend who
deals with things like this.
That's a brazen costume
for a cat burglar.
Yeah? Who are you pretending to be?
Bruce Wayne, eccentric billionaire.
- Who's your date?
- His wife's in Ibiza.
She left her diamonds behind,
though. Worried they might get stolen.
It's pronounced "Ibiza."
You wouldn't want these folks
realizing you're a crook,
not a social climber.
You think I care what anyone
in this room thinks of me?
I doubt you care what anyone
in any room thinks of you.
Don't condescend, Mr. Wayne.
You don't know a thing about me.
Well, Selina Kyle, I know you came
here from your walk- up in Old Town.
A modest place for a master jewel thief.
Which means that either
you're saving for retirement
or you're in deep with the wrong people.
You don't get to judge me because
you were born in the master
bedroom of Wayne Manor.
Actually, I was born
in the Regency Room.
I started out doing what I had to.
Once you've done what you had to,
they never let you do what you want to.
Start fresh.
Ugh. There's no fresh
start in today's world.
Any 12- year- old with a cell
phone could find out what you did.
Everything we do is collated and
quantified. Everything sticks.
Is that how you justify stealing?
I take what I need from those
who have more than enough.
I don't stand on the
shoulders of people with less.
Robin Hood?
I think I'd do more to help someone
than most of the people
in this room. Than you.
You think maybe you're
assuming a little too much?
Maybe you're being unrealistic about
what's really in your pants
other than your wallet.
Ouch.
You think all this can last?
There's a storm coming, Mr. Wayne.
You and your friends better
batten down the hatches,
because when it hits you're all
gonna wonder how you ever thought
you could live so large
and leave so little for the rest of us.
You sound like you're
looking forward to it.
I'm adaptable.
Those pearls do look better on
you than they did in my safe.
But I still can't let you keep them.
You... You scared her off!
Not likely.
Must have lost my ticket.
- Your wife said you were taking a cab home.
- My wife?
Just you, sir?
Don't worry, Master Wayne.
Takes a little time to get
back in the swing of things.
Bruce Wayne, as I live and breathe.
What brings you out of
cryo- sleep, Mr. Wayne?
You haven't lost your sense of humor.
Even if you have lost most of my money.
Actually, you did that.
If you funnel your entire R and D budget
into a fusion project
that you then mothball
your company is unlikely to thrive.
What are my options?
Well, if you're unwilling
to turn on the machine
I can't. I can't, Lucius.
Well, then sit tight.
Your majority keeps Daggett at bay while
we figure out a future
for the energy program
with Miranda Tate.
She has supported the
project all the way.
She's smart. And quite lovely.
We all just want what's
best for you, Bruce.
Show her the machine.
I'll think it over.
Anything else?
Nope. Why?
These conversations used to
end with an unusual request.
I retired.
Mm- hm. Well, let me show
you some stuff anyway.
Just for old times' sake.
I figured you'd have
shut this place down.
Oh, it was always shut down, officially.
All this new stuff.
After your father died, Wayne
Enterprises set up 14
different defense subsidiaries.
For years, I've been
shuttering and consolidating
all the different
prototypes under one roof.
- My roof.
- Why?
Keep them from falling
into the wrong hands.
Oh, now you're just showing off.
Defense Department projects
for tight geometry urban pacification.
Rotors are configured to
maneuver between buildings
without recirculation.
What's it called?
Oh, it has a long, uninteresting
Wayne Enterprises designation.
I just took to calling it the Bat.
And, yes, Mr. Wayne,
it does come in black.
Works fine, except for the autopilot.
Takes a better mind than mine to fix it.
Better mind?
Well, I was trying to be modest.
A less busy mind.
Yours.
- Is it really painful?
- You're very welcome to try it, Alfred.
Happy watching. Thank you, sir.
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
If you're seriously
considering going back out there
you should hear the
rumors surrounding Bane.
I'm all ears.
There is a prison in a more
ancient part of the world.
A pit where men are
thrown to suffer and die.
But sometimes a man
rises from the darkness.
Sometimes the pit sends something back.
- Bane.
Born and raised in hell on earth.
- Born in a prison?
- No one knows why, or how he escaped.
But they do know that once he did
he was trained by Ra's
Al Ghul, your mentor.
Bane was a member of
the League of Shadows?
And then he was excommunicated.
And any man who is too extreme
for Ra's Al Ghul is
not to be trifled with.
I didn't realize I was known
for trifling with criminals.
That was then.
And you can strap up your
leg and put your mask back on
but that doesn't make you what you were.
If this man is everything
that you say he is,
then the city needs me.
The city needs Bruce Wayne.
Your resources. Your knowledge.
It doesn't need your body, or your life.
That time's past.
You're afraid that if I go
back out there, I'll fail.
No.
I'm afraid that you want to.
You can't short the stock because
Bruce Wayne goes to a party.
Wayne coming back is change.
- Change is either good or bad.
- I vote bad.
On what basis?
I flipped a coin.
It says rye... I said no rye, man.
Hey, rookie, lose the helmet.
We need faces for camera.
Come on. Let's go scalping.
Come on.
Everybody down, now!
This is a stock exchange.
There's no money you can steal.
Really? Then why are you people here?
Everybody,
stay back! Go down to
the end of the block!
We have an emergency situation!
You gotta get in there!
This is a hostage situation.
No, this is a robbery.
They have direct access
to the online trading desk.
I'm not risking my men for your money.
We have to ask you to
move. We have a situation.
It's not our money, it's everybody's.
Really? Mine's in my mattress.
You don't put these guys down,
that stuffing in your mattress
might be worth a whole lot less.
Cut the fiber cable and
take out that cell tower.
- Thank you.
- That'll slow them down.
Move back!
All the way! Go! Sir, get back, please!
They cut the fiber.
Cell's working.
For now.
Get all these barriers
up. All of them up.
No one gets in or out
of any of these streets.
Where am I supposed to move it?
Back it up.
All right, just stay
in your vehicle, okay?
How much longer does the program need?
Eight minutes.
Time to go mobile.
Everybody, up!
You two, move!
Thank you.
Steady.
I've got something.
Hold your fire, they've got hostages.
Hold your fire!
Go, go!
Please! Just let me go!
Hey, please! Hey!
Shoot the tires.
There's no shot.
Now back off. Back off,
they've got hostages.
P.D. Are pursuing the four suspects through
downtown in response to a hostage situation.
What's going on with the lights?
It can't be.
What the hell was that?
Oh, boy, you are in
for a show tonight, son.
Please! Help, help, help!
Sorry.
Put that thing away before
you hurt yourself. Get in!
Let's go. You, get in the car.
They've spotted the Batman.
Call everyone in. Every car
patrol, beat cop, off- duty too.
Pull them in now. I'm gonna
do what Jim Gordon never could.
- What's that?
- I'm gonna take down the Batman.
four suspects are carrying two hostages
kidnapped from the
Gotham Stock Exchange.
Reports from the eyewitnesses...
Scott, dead center of your screen.
- What do you see?
- I see Batman.
Hard to believe,
but the suspects are now
being pursued by what appears
to be the Batman.
Well, what do you know?
Sir, what about the armed robbers?
Please! Just let me go! Please!
One bike's pulled off. No
hostage. Should we pursue?
Negative. Stay on the Batman.
- He's getting away.
- Who do you wanna catch?
Some robber, or the son of a
bitch who killed Harvey Dent?
...the entire upper west hill...
Central Heights and
East Park Side areas.
Eight years, and he has to pick tonight.
He's drawing the cops off Bane.
Please! Just let me go!
Please!
We lost him.
How could you lose him?
He's got a lot of firepower.
What, and you don't?
He's heading back downtown.
Then he's as dumb as he dresses.
Close it off, gentlemen.
Like a rat in a trap, gentlemen.
You might have the
wrong animal there, sir.
You sure it was him?
Bane says the Batman interfered,
but the task was accomplished.
What about the men they arrested?
He said, and I quote, "They
would die before talking."
Where does he find these guys?
Open the champagne.
And can we get some girls in here?
Careful what you wish for.
Cat got your tongue?
You dumb bitch.
Nobody ever accused me of being dumb.
You're dumb for coming here tonight.
I want what you owe me.
Want doesn't get.
Nice outfit. Those heels
make it tough to walk?
I don't know.
Do they?
- So where is it?
- Where's what?
The program. The "Clean slate."
The ultimate tool for a
master thief with a record.
Hold it right there!
Where is it?
The clean slate?
Where you type in someone's
name, date of birth
in a few minutes they're gone
from every database on earth?
- Sound a little too good to be true?
- You're lying!
Rykin Data took it to prototype stage.
That's why I bought them.
But they had nothing.
It was a gangland myth.
Stay back!
I'm not bluffing!
They know.
They just don't care.
You've gotta be kidding me.
- No guns. No killing.
- Where's the fun in that?
My mother warned me about getting
into cars with strange men.
This isn't a car.
See you around.
You're welcome.
I had it under control.
Those weren't street thugs.
They were trained killers.
I saved your life.
In return, I need to know
what you did with Bruce
Wayne's fingerprints.
Wayne wasn't kidding
about a powerful friend.
I sold his prints to
Daggett for something
that doesn't even exist.
I doubt many people
get the better of you.
Hey, when a girl's desperate
- What's he gonna do with them?
- I don't know
but Daggett seemed pretty
interested in that mess
at the stock market.
Miss Kyle?
So that's what that feels like.
I see from the television coverage
that you got your taste
for wanton destruction back.
I retrieved this.
Aren't the police supposed
to be investigating, then?
They don't have the tools to analyze it.
They would if you gave them to them.
One man's tool is another man's weapon.
In your mind, perhaps.
But there aren't many things
you can't turn into a weapon.
Alfred, enough. The police
weren't getting it done.
Perhaps they might have
if you hadn't made a
sideshow of yourself.
You thought I didn't have it in me.
You led a bloated
police force on a chase
with a load of fancy new toys from Fox.
What about when you come
up against him? What then?
I'll fight harder. I always have.
Look. His speed, his
ferocity, his training.
I see the power of belief.
I see the League of Shadows resurgent.
You said he was excommunicated.
By Ra's Al Ghul.
Who leads them now?
Ra's Al Ghul was the League
of Shadows and I beat him.
Bane is a mercenary. We need
to find out what he's up to.
Trades of some kind. Coded.
And my fingerprint,
courtesy of Selina Kyle.
Get this to Fox.
He can crack the code
and tell us what trades
they were executing.
I'll get this to Mr. Fox, but no more.
I've sewn you up, I've set your
bones, but I won't bury you.
I've buried enough members
of the Wayne family.
- You'll leave me?
- You see only one end to your journey.
Leaving is all I have
to make you understand.
You're not Batman anymore.
You have to find another way.
You used to talk about finishing,
about a life beyond that awful cave.
Alfred, Rachel died knowing that
we had decided to be together.
That was my life beyond the
cave. I can't just move on.
She... She didn't. She couldn't.
What if she had?
She... I can't change that.
What if before she
died she wrote a letter
saying she chose Harvey Dent over you?
And what if to spare you pain,
I burnt that letter?
How dare you use Rachel
to try to stop me?
I am using the truth, Master Wayne.
Maybe it's time we all stopped
trying to outsmart the truth
and let it have its day.
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
You expect to destroy my world
and then think that
we're gonna shake hands?
No, no, no.
I know what this means.
What does it mean?
It means your hatred.
And it also means losing
someone that I have cared
for since I first heard his
cries echo through this house.
But it might also mean saving your life.
And that is more important.
Goodbye, Alfred.
Alfred?
- Answering your own door?
- Yeah.
Page three.
Seems you made a series of
large put options on
the futures exchange
verified by thumbprint.
Those options expired
at midnight last night.
Long- term, we may be
able to prove fraud.
But for now, you're completely broke
and Wayne Enterprises is
about to fall into the
hands of John Daggett.
The weapons.
We can't let Daggett get his
hands on Applied Sciences.
Applied Sciences is all
locked up and off the books.
The energy project, however,
is a different story.
Miranda Tate.
Let's convince the
board to get behind her.
Let's show her the reactor.
We're meeting her there in 35
minutes, so you better get dressed.
You brought me out here
to show me this, Mr. Fox?
Bear with me, Miss Tate.
Please keep hands and feet
inside the car at all times.
This is it, isn't it?
The reactor is beneath the river
so it can be instantly
flooded in the event
of a security breach.
Is Bruce Wayne really that paranoid?
I'm gonna plead the fifth on that one.
I thought you might like to
see what your investment built.
No fossil fuels.
Free clean energy for an entire city.
Three years ago, a Russian
scientist published a paper
on weaponized fusion reactions.
One week later, your reactor
started developing problems.
I think this machine works.
Miranda, if it were operational,
the danger to Gotham would be too great.
Would it make you feel better to know
that the Russian scientist died
in a plane crash six months ago?
Someone will work out
what Dr. Pavel did.
Someone will figure out a way
to make this power source
into a nuclear weapon.
I need you to take control of
Wayne Enterprises and this reactor.
To do what with it?
Nothing.
Until we can guarantee its safety.
And if we can't?
Decommission it. Flood it.
Destroy the world's best
chance for a sustainable future?
If the world's not ready, yes.
Bruce, if you want to save the world,
you have to start trusting it.
I'm trusting you.
Doesn't count. You have no choice.
I could have flooded
this chamber at any time.
I'm choosing to trust you.
Please.
All right, ladies and gentlemen.
This meeting will now come to order.
I'd like to point out that we
have a non- board member here
which is highly irregular,
even if his family
name is above the door.
Bruce Wayne's family built this company.
And he himself has run it.
Into the ground, sir!
Does anybody disagree?
Check the share price this morning.
Crazy gambling on futures has
not only cost Mr. Wayne his seat
it's cost us all a lot of money.
And he has to go.
I'm afraid he has a point, Mr. Wayne.
Now, back to business.
Mr. Wayne, over here!
How's it feel to be one of the people?
Mr. Wayne, they're towing your car!
I didn't know what to
do, they had paperwork.
Looks like you need a ride, huh?
Wayne, we'll give you a ride!
How the hell did Miranda Tate
get the inside track on the Wayne board?
She been meeting with
him? Sleeping with him?
- Not that we know of.
- You don't know much of anything, do you?
- Where's Bane?
- We told him it was urgent.
- Where is that masked...?
- Speak of the devil
and he shall appear.
What the hell is going on?
- The plan is proceeding as expected.
- Oh, really?
Do I look like I'm running
Wayne Enterprises right now?
Your hit on the stock exchange,
it didn't work, my friend.
And now you have my construction crews
going around the city at 24 hours a day.
How exactly is that supposed to
help my company absorb Wayne's?
- Leave us.
- No. You stay here.
I'm in charge.
Do you feel in charge?
I've paid you a small fortune.
And this gives you power over me?
What is this?
Your money and infrastructure
have been important
till now.
What are you?
I'm Gotham's reckoning.
Here to end the borrowed time
you've all been living on.
You're pure evil.
I'm necessary evil.
No. No, no, no!
When you started, why the mask?
To protect the people closest to me.
But you were a loner, right?
You didn't have any family?
There are always people you care about.
You just don't realize how
much until they're gone.
The idea was to be a symbol.
Batman could be anybody.
That was the point.
- Well, it was damn good to see him back.
- Not everybody agrees.
They'll figure that out in the end.
You got anything on Bane's whereabouts?
Yeah. I got 500 pages of
tunnel records and a flashlight.
I could use some help, actually.
You know what? Drop me in Old Town.
Hey, hey, hey. I don't think so!
- That's the way this works!
- I don't think so!
- That is the way...
- He's not a mark.
And he doesn't have a
cent to his name, anyway.
Yeah, it's not much. But it's
more than you've got right now.
Actually, they're
letting me keep the house.
The rich don't even go broke
the same as the rest of us, huh?
My powerful friend might hope to
change your mind about leaving.
- And how would he do that?
- By giving you what you want.
- It doesn't exist.
- He says it does.
He wants to meet tonight.
Why?
He needs to find Bane.
Says you'd know how.
- Tell him I'll think about it.
- Okay.
I like your place.
Mr. Wayne?
I'm sorry they took all your money.
No, you're not.
- Can we help you, officer?
- Uh, yeah.
John Daggett's body was
just found in a Dumpster
about an hour ago.
- Thought you might want to know.
- Why?
His name's all over these
permits I just pulled to,
uh, map the tunnels under Gotham.
That's MTA maintenance, uh,
sewer construction,
couple of other things.
Where did you get to
with the tunnel searches?
Remind me to tell detail
to keep hotheads out.
We've had teams down
there. It's a huge network.
Well, get more men. Work
a grid. I want him found.
Yeah, the, uh, masked man. We're on it.
Lose the uniform, you're
working for me now.
We could use some
hotter heads around here.
Sir, that could also be a coincidence.
You're a detective now, son.
You're not allowed to believe
in coincidence anymore.
Nobody's answering.
No.
I'm on my own now.
Do you have keys?
Never needed them.
Hope you didn't like me for my money.
Suffering builds character.
I'll take care of your
parents' legacy, Bruce.
Who's this?
Where's Alfred?
He left
taking everything.
What's that?
My power's been shut off.
You're good at that.
When I was a child,
we had almost nothing.
But on the nights when we had a
fire, we felt very rich indeed.
I assumed your family was wealthy.
Not always.
Not when I was young.
An old mistake.
I've made a few myself.
More than a few.
We could leave.
Tonight.
Take my plane, go anywhere we wanted.
Someday, perhaps.
Not tonight.
Don't be shy.
Wayne says you can
get me the clean slate.
- That depends.
- On what?
On what you want it for.
I acquired it to keep it
out of the wrong hands.
Still don't trust me, huh?
How can we change that?
Start by taking me to Bane.
You asked.
From here, Bane's men
patrol the tunnels.
And they're not your average brawlers.
Neither am I.
- He's behind you.
- Who?
Me.
What do you think you're...?
Just a little further.
I had to find a way to
stop them trying to kill me.
You made a serious mistake.
Not as serious as yours, I fear.
Bane.
Let's not stand on ceremony here
Mr. Wayne.
Peace has cost you your strength.
Victory has defeated you.
Theatricality and deception,
powerful agents to the uninitiated.
But we are initiated, aren't we, Bruce?
Members of the League of Shadows.
And you betrayed us.
"Us"? You were excommunicated
by a gang of psychopaths.
I am the League of Shadows.
And I'm here to fulfill
Ra's Al Ghul's destiny.
You fight like a younger man.
Nothing held back.
Admirable, but mistaken.
Oh, you think darkness is your ally?
But you merely adopted the dark.
I was born in it.
Molded by it.
I didn't see the light
until I was already a man.
By then, it was nothing
to me but blinding!
The shadows betray you
because they belong to me!
I will show you where
I have made my home
whilst preparing to bring justice.
Then I will break you.
Your precious armory.
Gratefully accepted. We will need it.
Ah, yes. I was wondering
what would break first.
Your spirit
or your body.
Get me Commissioner Gordon.
I got a line on the
congressman's kidnapping.
- Excuse me, miss.
- Uh, yes?
I'm gonna need to see your
ticket and identification, please.
Oh. Do you mind?
I showed your picture to
the congressman. Guess what.
Don't tell me. Still in love?
Oh, head over heels.
Pressing charges, though.
You've made some mistakes, Ms. Kyle.
- Girl's gotta eat.
- And you have an appetite.
Why would you run? You can't
hide with a record like this.
Maybe it's not you I'm running from.
Who then? Bane?
What do you know about him?
That you should be as
afraid of him as I am.
We can offer you protection.
Okay.
When I spotted you, I was
looking for a friend
of mine. Bruce Wayne.
Did they kill him?
I'm not sure.
Why didn't you just
kill me?
You don't fear death, you welcome it.
Your punishment must be more severe.
Torture?
Yes.
But not of your body.
Of your soul.
Where am I?
Home.
Where I learned the truth about despair.
As will you.
There is a reason why this
prison is the worst hell on earth:
Hope.
Every man who has rotted
here over the centuries
has looked up to the light and
imagined climbing to freedom.
So easy. So simple.
And like shipwrecked men
turning to seawater from
uncontrollable thirst
many have died trying.
I learned here there can be
no true despair without hope.
So as I terrorize Gotham
I will feed its people
hope to poison their souls.
I will let them believe
that they can survive
so that you can watch them
clambering over each
other to stay in the sun.
You can watch me torture an entire city.
And then when you have truly
understood the depth of your failure
we will fulfill Ra's Al Ghul's destiny.
We will destroy Gotham.
And then, when it is done
and Gotham is ashes
then you have my permission to die.
You're locking her up in here?
The Dent Act allows non- segregation
based on extraordinary need.
First time she broke out of
women's correctional, she was 16.
Little closer, baby.
Why, honey? You wanna hold my hand?
She's gonna be fine.
I still don't see the need
of a board meeting
for the energy project.
Bruce got a lot of things right.
Keeping the board in the
dark was not one of them.
How good of you to join us.
Chair. President.
All I need now is one
more ordinary board member.
Mr. Fox, would you like to nominate?
No.
I will volunteer.
Where are you taking us?
You were right, commissioner.
Will you excuse us, please?
What happened?
Your masked man kidnapped
the Wayne Enterprises board.
He let most of them go, but
he took three into the sewers.
No more patrols. No more hide and seek.
Get every available cop
down there and smoke him out!
The mayor won't want panic.
So it's a training exercise.
I'm sorry I didn't take you seriously.
Not you.
You're telling me the Batman's gone
so you chase up the Daggett
leads any way you can.
Yes, sir.
He asks how much you would
pay us to let you die.
I told him. I told him you have nothing.
Do it for the pleasure.
They pay me more than
that to keep you alive.
He will try the climb.
Has anyone ever made it?
Of course not.
He says there is one who did.
A child.
A child born in this hell.
Bane.
An old legend. Nothing more.
Don't.
Whatever it is they want you
to see, it's happening soon.
Fire in the hole!
Turn it on.
I only need one other board member.
There are eight others waiting.
I won't do it.
All right, stop.
Lucius, you'll kill
this man, and yourself
and you'll barely slow them down.
Go on, then. Do your work.
Take them up to the surface.
People of their status
deserve to experience the next
era of western civilization.
I've been to half of Daggett's
cement plants and locations
they poured underground.
Anything strange about the pourings?
Honestly, commissioner,
I don't know anything
about civil engineering.
But you know about
patterns. Keep looking.
It's done.
This is now a 4- megaton nuclear bomb.
Pull the core out of the reactor.
No, you cannot.
This is the only power source
capable of sustaining it.
If you move it, the core will
decay in a matter of months.
Five, by my calculations.
And then it will go off!
And for the sake of your children,
Dr. Pavel indeed I hope it does.
That was you in front of the
stock exchange, wasn't it?
- When?
When cops were trying to
pull onto Castle Street
and your truck was shutting them out.
- Oh, yeah. You're the cop.
- Detective now.
And, uh, as a detective,
we're not allowed to
believe in coincidence.
What were you doing here?
What are you working on?
Commissioner, it's Blake.
I got two dead witnesses and a
lot of questions. Call me whenev
Wait a minute. I'm looking at
four barrels of polyisobutylene.
That looks like motor
oil right next to it.
Jesus, they're not making
cement. They're making explosives.
Patch me in to Foley.
Foley's overseeing the operation.
They're heading into a trap!
We're seeing thousands of
police heading into the sewers.
Mr. Mayor? Literally thousands.
It's a training exercise, that's all.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I've got tickets to watch
our boys thrash Rapid City.
- Foley.
- It's a trap! Pull everyone out!
Bane has been pouring
concrete laced with explosives!
Where?
Oh, say, can you see By
the dawn's early light
What so proudly we
hailed At the twilight's
There's a ring around the tunnels!
They'll blow it and trap
the cops underground!
Pull them out. Pull them out now!
Through the perilous fight
O'er the ramparts we watched
Were so gallantly streaming
And the rockets' red glare
The bombs bursting in air
Gave proof through
That's a lovely, lovely voice.
that our flag was still there
Oh, say does that
star- spangled banner Yet wave
O'er the land of the free
And the home of the brave
Let the games begin.
Everybody okay?
- Let's move! Move, move!
- Go, go!
Gotham
take control.
Take control of your city.
- Foley.
- Jesus, Blake.
Every cop in the
city's in those tunnels.
Not every cop.
Sir, are you okay? I'm a police officer.
I need your car right now.
Clear the corners, rookie.
Get my coat, son.
This
This is the instrument
of your liberation.
Satellite shows a radiation spike.
Whatever it is, it's nuclear.
Identify yourself to the world.
Dr. Leonid Pavel, nuclear physicist.
Pavel was confirmed dead.
Plane crash on an agency
pull out of Uzbekistan, but
It looks like it's him.
And what...? What is this?
It's a fully primed neutron bomb
with a blast radius of six miles.
And who is capable of
disarming such a device?
Only me.
Only you.
Thank you, good doctor!
Now, this bomb is armed!
And this bomb is mobile!
And the identity of the
triggerman is a mystery.
For one of you holds the detonator!
Now, we come here not as conquerors
but as liberators,
to return control of
this city to the people.
And at the first sign of
interference from the outside world
or from those people attempting to flee
this anonymous Gothamite, this
unsung hero, will trigger the bomb.
For now, martial law is in effect.
Return to your homes,
hold your families close
and wait.
Tomorrow, you claim
what is rightfully yours.
Pull back the fighters.
Start high- level
reconnaissance flights.
Get the president on the line.
Tanks and
planes cannot stop us
from detonating our device.
Send an emissary to discuss
terms of access for
supplies and communication.
How many of you are there, son?
You don't have enough men to
stop 12 million people
from leaving this island.
No. No, we don't.
But you do.
Now, why the hell would I try
to help you keep your hostages?
If one person crosses this bridge
Gotham gets blown to hell.
The people of our greatest
city are resilient.
They have proven this before,
and they will prove it again.
We do not negotiate with terrorists
but we do recognize realities.
As this situation develops
one thing must be
understood above all others.
People of Gotham, we
have not abandoned you.
What does that mean?
It means we're on our own.
I have to get in front of a camera.
They will kill you the
second you show your face.
Bane says he's giving
Gotham back to the people.
They need to know I could lead.
Bane's not gonna let that happen.
Then he'll show his true colors.
And you'll be dead.
Behind you stands a
symbol of oppression.
Blackgate Prison
where a thousand men have languished
under the name of this man:
Harvey Dent.
Who has been held up to you as
the shining example of justice!
We're just gonna keep moving
you till we can get you
in front of the camera.
You have been supplied with
a false idol to stop you
tearing down this corrupt city!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Let me tell you the
truth about Harvey Dent.
From the words of Gotham's
police commissioner
James Gordon:
"The Batman didn't murder Harvey Dent.
He saved my boy
then took the blame for
Harvey's appalling crimes
so that I could, to my shame
build a lie around this fallen idol.
I praised the madman who
tried to murder my own child.
Well, I can no longer live with my lie.
It is time to trust the
people of Gotham with the truth
and it is time for me to resign."
And do you accept
this man's resignation?
And do you accept the
resignation of all of these liars?
Of all the corrupt?
Those men locked up for
eight years in Blackgate
and denied parole under the
Dent Act, it was based on a lie.
Gotham needed a hero.
Well, it needs it now more than ever,
but you betrayed
everything you stood for.
There's a point
far out there when
the structures fail you
when the rules aren't weapons anymore
they're shackles, letting
the bad guy get ahead.
One day, you may face
such a moment of crisis.
And in that moment, I hope
you have a friend like I did
to plunge their hands into the filth,
so that you can keep yours clean!
Your hands look plenty
filthy to me, commissioner.
We take Gotham from the corrupt!
The rich!
The oppressors of generations
who have kept you down
with myths of opportunity.
And we give it back to you
the people.
Gotham is yours!
None shall interfere. Do as you please.
But start by storming Blackgate
and freeing the oppressed!
Open it!
Step forward, those who would serve
for an army will be raised.
The powerful will be ripped
from their decadent nests
and cast out into the cold
world that we know and endure!
Courts will be convened.
Spoils will be enjoyed.
Blood will be shed!
The police will survive
as they learn to serve true justice.
This great city
it will endure.
Gotham will survive!
He says you must first fix your back.
How does he know?
He was the prison doctor.
He's a morphine addict who incurred
the displeasure of powerful people,
including your masked friend.
How?
Many years ago, it was a time of plague.
Some of the other
prisoners attacked Bane.
The doctor's fumbling
attempts to repair the damage
left him in perpetual agony.
The mask holds the pain at bay.
Bane was the child you spoke of?
He was born here?
The legend is that there was a mercenary
who worked for a local warlord.
He fell in love with
the warlord's daughter.
They were married in secret.
When the warlord found out
the mercenary was condemned to this pit.
But then he exiled him instead.
The mercenary understood that
it was the daughter who
had secured his release.
But what he could not know was
the true price of his freedom.
She took his place in the pit.
And she was with child,
the mercenary's child.
lnnocence cannot flower underground.
It has to be stamped out.
One day, the doctor
forgot to lock the cell.
But the child had a friend.
A protector who showed the
others that this innocence
was their redemption.
It was to be prized.
The mother was not so lucky.
This is Bane's prison now. He
wouldn't want this story told.
There's a vertebra
protruding from your back.
It has to be put back.
Stay like this until you stand.
Did you not think I
would return, Bruce? Hmm?
I told you I was immortal.
I watched... I watched you die.
Oh, there are many forms of immortality.
Once, I had a wife
my great love.
- She was taken from me.
- You were the mercenary.
Bane is your child.
Your heir.
An heir to ensure the League
of Shadows fulfills its duty
to restore balance to civilization.
No.
You yourself fought the
decadence of Gotham for years
with all your strength,
all your resources,
all your moral authority.
And the only victory you
could achieve was a lie.
Now you understand.
Gotham is beyond saving.
No.
- And must be allowed to die.
- No!
Yeah, just lift your head.
Oh, that's good.
No, no!
- What's that?
- This was someone's home.
And now it's everyone's home.
There's a storm coming,
remember? This is what you wanted.
It's for the bus, in case
there's a chance to evacuate.
Any news? Is the commissioner...?
The less you know, Father.
How are the boys doing?
Well, we've had more power
on, so they've got some TV.
It's good to see you.
Blake, you be careful out there.
They're hunting down cops like dogs.
Why build yourself?
I'm not meant to die in here.
Here, there. What's the difference?
I told you it could not be done.
You told me a child did it.
But no ordinary child.
A child born in hell.
Forged from suffering.
Hardened by pain.
Not a man from privilege.
We got boots on the ground, sir.
Just waiting on intel.
You have ID?
Of course not.
- Well, how can we trust you?
- We don't have any choice.
Commissioner Gordon. Captain
Jones, Special Forces.
Captain. Glad to have you here.
It's our job, sir. Now, uh,
how many of you are there?
Well, there's dozens. I'd
rather not say exactly.
But the men trapped
underground number almost 3000.
- Condition?
- Getting food and water.
- Can we break them out?
- Yes, sir.
Take out the mercenaries
south of Ackerman Park.
Blow the rubble, make a hole
big enough for 10 at a time.
I'm in contact with my
partner who's down there.
They're just waiting.
Men who haven't seen daylight in months?
Officers who haven't
seen daylight in months.
What about the bomb? Satellite
can't pick up radiation hot spots.
They keep it on a truck. It
must have a lead- lined roof.
- They move it constantly.
- Good. So you know the truck?
Well, it's one of three.
We've been tracking it.
Decoy.
You don't really think he's coming back?
Doesn't matter what I think.
Actually, it does.
You should put your faith in
something a little more real.
The routes don't vary much.
Okay. What about the triggerman?
No leads. It's a bluff.
Bane wouldn't give control
of that bomb to someone else.
We can't take that chance.
Until we have the triggerman,
we just track the device.
And meanwhile, Gotham
lives under a warlord,
like some failed state?
Dial it back, officer. This
situation is unprecedented.
We can't do anything to
risk millions of lives.
You gonna tell him
what's really going on?
Captain, the situation is more
complicated than you think.
There's someone you need to meet.
Came upstairs looking
for a vantage point.
Found the people who
run the corporation.
What corporation?
Wayne Enterprises. You good?
Mr. Fox, would you like
to brief the captain?
Miss Tate's fully
aware of the situation.
And as CEO of Wayne Enterprises,
I have to take responsibility for it.
- Why?
- We built it.
You built the bomb?
It was built as a fusion
reactor. First of its kind.
Bane turned the core into a bomb
and removed it from the reactor.
Here's the important part.
As the device's fuel cells deteriorate
it becomes increasingly unstable
to the point of detonation.
This bomb is a time bomb.
And it will go off in 23 days, regardless
of Bane's revolution or what we,
or the outside world, choose to do.
So your plan might not be
as practical as you thought.
Could you disarm it?
I could reconnect it to
the reactor. Stabilize it.
- Let's move from this location and call it in.
- Right. Let's go.
No, no, we'll take it from here.
You stay and look after these folks.
Someone sold us out.
Go, go, go!
I'll die before I talk.
I'm on your schedule, captain.
There were people living upstairs.
Round them up for judgment
and hang them where the world can see.
He says the leap to freedom
is not about strength.
My body makes the jump.
Survival is the spirit. The soul.
My soul is as ready
to escape as my body.
Fear is why you fail.
No, I'm not afraid.
I'm angry.
Bruce.
Why do we fall?
You do not fear death.
You think this makes you
strong. It makes you weak.
Why?
How can you move faster than possible
fight longer than possible
without the most powerful
impulse of the spirit?
The fear of death.
I do fear death.
I fear dying in here
while my city burns.
There's no one there to save it.
Then make the climb.
How?
As the child did
without the rope.
Then fear will find you again.
Ah, supplies for your journey?
Oh, that's wonderful.
That's What does that mean?
Rise.
No.
No, there's been a mistake!
Take me to Bane!
I want to see Bane!
Order!
This is a mistake! Where is Bane?
There's been no mistake, Mr. Stryver.
You are Philip Stryver
executive vice president
of Daggett lndustries
who for years has been
living off the blood and sweat
of people less powerful than him.
Call Bane. I am one of you.
Bane has no authority here. This
is merely a sentencing hearing.
Now, the choice is yours.
Exile or death!
Order!
Exi... Exile.
Sold.
To the man in the cold sweat.
You follow the thick ice.
You try to swim, you're dead in minutes.
Has anyone made it?
Where are they? It's not
like we have a lot of time.
How long?
The bomb goes off tomorrow.
We have about 18 hours to do something.
To do what?
To mark the truck. Get a GPS on it
so we can start to figure
out how to bring it down.
That's it?
Foley.
Where's Foley, damn it?
You shouldn't be out on the streets.
Jim, he's not here.
You let your wife come to the door?
- When the city's under occupation?
- Wait in the kitchen, honey.
What did you do, bury your
uniform in the backyard?
You saw what they did
to those Special Forces.
Have you forgotten all the
years we were out on patrol?
When every gangbanger wanted
to plant one as soon as
our backs were turned?
That was different. And you know it.
These guys run the city.
The government's done a deal with them.
Bane's got their balls in
a vice. That's not a deal.
You move on Bane, the triggerman
is gonna hit the button.
You think he's given control of
that bomb to one of the people?
You think this is part
of some revolution?
There's one man with his finger
on the button. That's Bane.
Look, we've all got to keep our
heads down till they can fix this.
If you still had a family here...
This only gets fixed
from inside the city!
Look, Peter.
I'm not asking you to walk
down Grand in your dress blues,
but something has to be done.
Sorry, Jim. I gotta...
Keep your head down?
What good's that gonna
do when that thing blows?
You don't know that's gonna happen.
I hear you're looking
for men, commissioner.
How about me instead?
Miss Tate, I, uh, can't
ask you to do that.
Please.
You little punk! What'd you take?
Nothing! I didn't take anything!
You steal from us, you little bastard?
Now, you boys know you can't
come into my neighborhood
without asking politely.
Never steal anything from
someone you can't outrun, kid.
You're pretty generous for a thief.
- I thought they killed you.
- Not yet.
If you're expecting an apology, I...
It wouldn't suit you.
I need your help.
And why would I help you?
For this. Clean slate.
You'd trust me with that?
After what I did to you?
I'll admit, I was a little let down.
But I still think there's more to you.
In fact, I think that for you
this isn't just a tool.
It's an escape route. You
want to disappear. Start fresh.
I can't even get off this island.
I can give you a way off
once you get me to Lucius Fox.
Find out where they're
holding him and take me in.
Why do you need Fox?
- To save the city.
- Who says it needs saving?
Maybe I like it this way.
Maybe you do
but tomorrow that bomb's going off.
Got your powerful friend on the case?
I'm trying
but I need Fox.
As it approaches
flip the switch.
The needle hits 200,
you give me the signal,
I'll mark the truck. Okay?
Heads up, heads up.
- I got it.
- Mercenaries on your 6.
Stand still! Keep your
hands where we can see them!
Commissioner Gordon,
you are under arrest.
On whose authority?
The people of Gotham.
No lawyer? No witnesses?
What sort of due process is this?
Your guilt has been determined,
this is merely a sentencing hearing.
Now, what will it be?
Death or exile?
Crane,
if you think we're going
out onto that ice willingly
you have another thing coming.
Death, then.
- Looks that way.
- Very well.
Death
by exile.
Bring her to me.
Hey, we're going now. Blake says
they're ready! Get your gear on!
Hey, you hear me? We're
going now. Let's do it.
Find this one a spot,
got a big day tomorrow.
We all do.
It's not every day you bag Bruce Wayne.
- Bruce.
- You okay?
Picked a hell of a time to
go on vacation, Mr. Wayne.
How long until that core ignites?
That bomb goes off in 12 hours.
- Unless we can reconnect
it to the reactor.
Can you get Miranda out of here?
Not tonight. I'm sorry.
- Do what's necessary.
- Tonight I need you.
- What for?
- To get me back in the game.
Sorry to spoil things, boys,
but Bane wants these guys to himself.
- I won't forget about you, Miranda.
- I know.
I like your girlfriend, Mr. Wayne.
He should be so lucky.
Any move I make on Bane or the bomb
the triggerman sets it off.
Well, they won't use radio or
cell. Too much interference.
lnfrared doesn't have the range.
It'll have to be a microburst. Longwave.
- Could you block it?
- Yes.
But I'll need the EMP cannon
guidance mount from the Bat.
Remember where you parked?
She fly okay?
Yeah, even without the autopilot.
Thanks.
Autopilot? That's what you're there for.
Okay. It's clear. Come
on, quick. One at a time.
Wait, wait!
Ross!
Ross?
Lock it up.
Get down!
Who are you?
Light it up.
- Dad, check it out.
- Honey, come take a look.
Impossible.
Keep her close.
He'll come for her.
Where's Miranda Tate?
Bane took her.
He's holed up at city hall,
surrounded by his army.
This blocks the remote
detonator signal to the bomb.
Get it onto it before sunrise.
They might hit the
button when it starts.
When what starts?
War.
You missed a spot.
If you're working alone, wear a mask.
I'm not afraid to be
seen standing up to them.
The mask is not for you.
It's to protect the
people you care about.
Count to five, then throw.
No offense, but you got
something bigger in that belt?
- What now? - All- out
assault on Bane.
But you need to get
people across the bridge.
Why?
In case we fail.
Lead an exodus. Save as
many lives as you can.
You don't need me here?
You've given me an army.
Now go.
Hey, thanks.
Don't thank me yet.
Well, I might not get a chance later.
You shouldn't have.
The midtown tunnel's blocked by debris
but the cannons have enough
firepower to make a path for people.
Wait until the fighting begins.
You're gonna wage a war to
save your stuck- up girlfriend?
To start it, throttle
I got it.
We have 45 minutes to save this city.
No, I've got 45 minutes to
get clear of the blast radius.
You don't stand a chance
against these guys.
With your help, I might.
I'll open that tunnel, then I'm gone.
There's more to you than that.
Sorry to keep letting you down.
Come with me. Save yourself.
You don't owe these people any more.
You've given them everything.
Not everything.
Not yet.
Disperse!
Disperse or be fired upon!
There's only one police in this town.
Open fire.
- Here it comes!
- Get ready!
So you came back to die with your city.
No. I came back to stop you.
Now!
That's impossible.
Cut over to Fifth!
Here you go. Get on the bus. Go ahead.
You, come with me. You too.
Hey, you, you, and you,
come here, come here.
Everyone else get on the bus, okay?
You guys, you go knock on
doors and spread the word, okay?
The bomb is gonna go off.
Get out by the South Street
tunnel or over the bridge.
You do two blocks and you get
back to the bus, all right?
Go, go, go!
Is he back?
Keep your eyes open. Go, go.
Cover the doors!
Where's your trigger?!
Where is it?!
You'd never give it
to an ordinary citizen!
Where is it? Where's your trigger?
Where is it?! Where is it?!
Tell me where the trigger is.
Then you have my permission to die.
I broke you.
How have you come back?
You think you're the only
one who could learn
the strength to escape?
Where's the trigger?
But I never escaped.
But the child.
The child of Ra's Al
Ghul made the climb.
But he's not the child of Ra's Al Ghul.
I am.
And though I'm not ordinary
I am a citizen.
Miranda?
Why?
Thalia.
My mother named me Talia,
before she was killed
the way I would have been killed,
if not for my protector, Bane.
Goodbye.
I climbed out of the pit.
I found my father
and brought him back to
exact terrible vengeance.
But by that time
the prisoners and doctor had
done their work to my friend.
My protector.
The League took us in. Trained us.
But my father could not accept Bane.
He saw only a monster.
His very existence
was a reminder of the hell
he'd left his wife to die in.
He excommunicated Bane
from the League of Shadows.
His only crime was that he loved me.
I could not forgive my father.
Until you murdered him.
He was trying to kill
millions of innocent people.
Innocent is a strong word to
throw around Gotham, Bruce.
I honor my father by finishing his work.
Vengeance against the man who killed him
is simply a reward for my patience.
You see
it's the slow knife the
knife that takes its time.
The knife that waits
years without forgetting
then slips quietly between the bones.
That's the knife that cuts deepest.
Please.
Maybe your knife was too slow.
The truck is under attack.
Gordon. You gave him a
way to block my signal.
No matter.
He's bought Gotham 11 minutes.
Come on!
This way!
Stay there! What are you doing?
Blake, MCU!
I'm getting these boys to safety!
You'll get us all killed!
If anyone crosses this bridge,
they'll blow the city!
It's gonna blow anyway! We
need to open this bridge, now!
Detective, if you take one
step forward we will shoot you!
If you take two steps forward,
we will blow the bridge!
Okay, go back by the bus
and wait for me, all right?
Go back and wait.
Prepare a convoy.
We must secure the
bomb until it detonates.
Don't kill him, I want
him to feel the heat.
Feel the fire of 12
million souls you failed.
Goodbye, my friend.
Goodbye.
Keep moving forward!
Flank them at the stairs!
Shoot them.
Shoot them all.
We both know that I
have to kill you now.
You'll just have to imagine the fire.
About the whole no- guns thing
I'm not sure I feel as
strongly about it as you do.
Pull up.
Stay level.
We have to force that convoy east
to the entrance to the reactor.
I need you on the ground,
I'll be in the air. Go.
The situation has changed.
Your orders are out of date.
I'm a cop, like you, and
I'm walking out there.
Please do not shoot me!
Shoot at his feet.
Nothing like a little air superiority.
Detective! Please stop!
Please, detective! Stop!
Stop walking! Blow it! Do it!
You have to get that bomb
here. You've got 10 minutes.
They're pushing us to the
entrance of the reactor.
They're gonna try to reconnect the core.
You idiots!
You sons of bitches! You're killing us!
Yeah, follow your orders!
All right, boys. Get in
a circle. Bow your heads.
It's on my side.
Hey, Father! Let's get
everyone back on the bus, okay?
Go, go, go! Back on the bus!
There's nowhere to go.
On the bus!
You've got to turn the truck east!
Stay straight!
Give me a hand! We
can get a cable on it!
Fox showed me how to
override the reactor.
Oh, dear.
lncluding the emergency flood.
There's no way this
bomb will be stopped.
What are you doing?
Protection from the blast.
We're gonna be all right!
It's an atom bomb!
Think they need to hear that?
Let them die without hope? Come on!
Prepare yourselves.
My father's work is done.
- What are you doing?
- I can get it out over the bay!
Set it to fly out over
the water, then eject?
No autopilot.
You could've gone anywhere,
been anything. But you came back here.
So did you.
I guess we're both suckers.
- I never cared who you were.
- And you were right.
Shouldn't the people know
the hero who saved them?
A hero can be anyone.
Even a man doing something
as simple and reassuring as
putting a coat around
a young boy's shoulders
to let him know the world hadn't ended.
Bruce Wayne?
Come on! There you go! Okay, you too.
Come on, Father.
Hey, heads down! This is it!
- No.
- No, that's Batman!
That's detonation!
It's out over the
bay! Clear of the city!
"I see a beautiful city
and a brilliant people
rising from this abyss.
I see the lives for
which I lay down my life
peaceful useful, prosperous and happy.
I see that I hold a
sanctuary in their hearts
and in the hearts of their descendants
generations hence.
It is a far, far better thing that I do
than I have ever done.
It is a far, far
better rest that I go to
than I have ever known."
I'm so sorry.
I failed you.
You trusted me
and I failed you.
Can I change your mind
about quitting the force?
You know what you said about
structures becoming shackles?
You were right, and I can't
take it. The injustice.
I mean, no one's ever gonna
know who saved an entire city.
They know.
It was the Batman.
Mr. Wayne's will was not amended
to reflect his more modest estate.
Nonetheless, there are
considerable assets to dispose of.
The contents of the house are to be sold
to settle the estate's accounts
and the remainder is left
in its entirety to Alfred J. Pennyworth.
The house and grounds are
left to the city of Gotham
on condition that they
never be demolished, altered
or otherwise interfered with
and that they shall be used for
one purpose, and one purpose only:
The housing and care of the city's
at- risk and orphaned children.
My clerk can help with
the smaller correspondences
and instructions.
Blake, John.
- Nothing here.
- Uh, try my legal name.
You should use your full
name. I like that name.
- Robin.
- Thanks.
Why worry about the
stabilization software?
This entire autopilot
system's completely obsolete.
Please, I just need to know
what I could've done to fix it.
But, Mr. Fox,
it's already been fixed. Software patch.
Six months ago.
Check the ID on the patch.
Bruce Wayne.
- Any news on the missing item?
- Not yet.
They better leave no stone unturned.
We can't leave a string of
pearls on the manifest as lost.