Oh, my.
Can we discuss that?
Because I'm like very upset.
Is there like a writer's guide
to horror films that says,
"bitch must fall down!"
Because that is the
most unprovoked,
unrealistic fucking
tumble I've ever seen.
And I've seen a lot
of fucking horror films.
And then, she just stays there.
It's like, she's waiting for
clown face to catch up to her.
I think I need to write
a manifesto for how to
make good horror films.
Cause this genre
has just gone to shit!
What are you talking about?
We got the scream movies.
Nothing beats the original.
Man, those shits came out
like 20 years ago!
Okay, well, we got the conjuring
and the insidious movies.
That's not the point.
That is the point.
You just said that there
were no good horror movies.
Okay, fine, there's some good
horror movies that have came out.
But, the shitty one's
outnumber the good one's.
That's the problem.
All right, so,
according to Parker,
what makes a good horror movie?
I don't know, the essentials,
good dialog,
characters that I
actually care about.
Characters that are able
to use their better judgment.
Like, if you are home alone
and you hear weird noises,
don't just yell,
"hello?"
Get the fuck out of there, man.
I see you're very
serious about this.
Yes, you gotta be.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, pause that.
Why?
Pause it!
Am I going crazy
or do you hear that?
You're going crazy.
I'm being serious!
I don't hear anything.
Cause you're not listening.
Can you stop? Cause
you're not funny.
I'm not trying to be
funny, I hear noises.
Yeah, right, we're sitting
here watching a horror movie,
talking about horror
movies and all of a sudden
you start hearing weird noises.
Stop playing, miles. I agree
that this is bad timing, but,
I... really do hear
something, I'm not joking.
It sounds like it's
coming from downstairs.
If you tell me
you didn't hear that,
I will bop you.
Okay, fine, I heard that.
But, your mom's working
the night shift right?
So, we're the only one's here.
Park, I don't think
that's my mom down there.
So, what do you wanna do?
What? Check it out, I guess.
Are you...? Didn't we just have
a conversation about that?
And now you wanna go do
the same thing that those
dumb motherfuckers
do in the movies.
First off, it's two of us,
therefore, we're
more of a threat.
And b, this isn't a horror
movie, this is life!
In life, motherfuckers run away.
What are you talking about?
Besides, how do you know
there's not a group
of intruders down there.
Intruders equipped with guns,
or equally harmful sharp ass
objects or an assortment of both.
I'm not running out
of my own house.
It's about the principles.
Fuck principles, principles
don't keep you alive.
Look, I'll grab the bat,
you grab the broom.
The broom?
What you want me to do?
Swoop the shit out of them?
Come on.
Nah, nah, nah.
I'm not going down there, man.
I don't care what you
say, or how you say it,
I'm not going down there.
I'm not doing it.
One, two, three.
Aah!
What the fuck are
you doing here?
You're ready?
I know that, Kenan. I live here.
But, I thought that you
were at Nia's house.
We were, and now we're here.
Y'all sounding like
some fucking pussies.
You know what, I
think you're voices
might be a little
higher than mine.
And you were like...
Yeah, it's funny now.
But, you almost got fucked up.
By who? Me and Parker, bitch!
Oh, I mean, not, not quite.
Not quite.
If those were really intruders,
they would've got fucked
up with our quickness.
No doubt.
Can we take a little break
from the horror movies?
I mean, I'm just saying.
No, come on.
I'm just saying.
Okay, so, aside from
the other components,
good dialogs, smart
characters, that kinda thing,
what is the one ingredient
needed to make
a solid horror film?
The 'o.S.' Factor. I don't know.
The "oh, shit" factor. The what?
'O.S.'
and what's the
'o.S.' Factor?
I was thinking about
the movies you named.
Scream, insidious,
the conjuring,
they all have
that 'o.S.' Factor.
You know, something fresh,
something that throws you off
and makes you say,
"oh, shit"
hence, the 'o.S.' Factor.
I just feel like nowadays,
horror movies abide by the same
formulate blueprint.
And in my opinion, it really
belittles us as
audience members.
I shouldn't have
to turn my brain off
to enjoy a horror movie.
You see what I'm saying?
I wanna be surprised.
I wanna care about
what's going on.
I want an experience.
Yo, one more week.
To what?
To, to what?
To your fucking
birthday, you dum-dum.
Yeah. Being legal
and shit like me.
Yo, I was thinking about this.
We should go to a strip club.
Are you for real? Yeah, man!
Please, don't toy
with my emotions.
I'm serious, man. Let's
hit that shit up.
How am I the only
one here again?
It's just pitiful, man!
Mr. Roland?
Mr. Roland!
Notice me!
What does the board say, miles?
Sorry.
I'm not asking for an apology, I'm
asking to tell me what the board says.
"If you have a question,
raise your hand"
"exclamation point."
He can read.
I had my doubts.
But, you came through.
Why I gotta raise my hand, now?
I'm the only one here.
It's not like you have
hands to choose from.
The rules don't change.
Rules are for the majority.
I'm above the law, Mr. Roland.
If you were above the law,
you wouldn't be in
detention now, would you?
Mr. Roland coming
with the fire!
Miles, I'm losing
my Patience with you.
Is it okay if I go
to the bathroom?
Didn't you have 10 free
minutes before you got here?
Yeah, but, I didn't
have to go then.
As much as I'd like to,
I can't control the actions
of my bladder, Mr. Roland.
You have three
minutes, starting now.
Say I never came back,
what would you do?
Now, you have
two and a half minutes.
You wanna continue?
I could make it
go down to 30 seconds.
I leave now.
Fuck!
Shit!
What happened here?
Aidan hit me in the face
with a fucking rock!
It was an accident,
Dudeski, I said I was sorry.
I was trying to hit
chase with the rock,
but Kurt got in the way.
Oh, okay.
Why the fuck you trying to hit
me in the face with a rock?
It wasn't a big rock.
You would've been fine.
Kurt's fine.
No, I'm not.
Aidan, you're clearly missing
the larger issue at hand,
you don't throw rocks at people.
Dudeski, you totally
had it coming,
you were being an asshole.
How's that being an asshole?
Nic, give me one
example of assholery
that would work in smash
in the face of fucking rock.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Smash,
is a bit excessive.
I didn't wanna smash you.
I just chucked it in the air
with the hopes that it would
hit you in the temple.
I didn't wanna hit you hard
enough to do any serious damage.
But, I did wanna
hit you hard enough
to get my point across
that you can't keep being
an asshole to people.
Ah, well, you still haven't
told me what I did.
You know what you do, chase.
Okay, yeah, sure I do.
See?
Still in pain, Kurt?
Well, seeing as how I got hit
like two seconds ago,
yeah, Aidan, I'm still
in pain, but thanks.
Yeah, that's what
I'm here for, Dudeski.
Not to throw rocks at you,
but to ask if you're okay in the
event you do get hit by a rock.
Okay.
So, there's kitty's coalition
and Sloan's salon.
Which kinda sounds
like a brothel.
Both place are downtown,
so, that's like a 15
minute walk from here.
Sigh.
I think you gotta be
21 and over for Sloan's
because they serve alcohol.
Kitty's coalition is...
18 and over.
Listen, yo!
Today, I was washing my
hands in the bathroom,
and this urinal
flushed by itself.
I was the only one
in the bathroom.
And the urinal that flushed
wasn't the one I was using.
And I wasn't even close to it.
Parker, I'm serious.
And this actually happened?
Yeah, it actually happened, man.
I can't tell if you're
messing with me.
I'm not.
Weird shit is happening.
Ah, don't touch it, man.
Does, does it hurt?
Yeah, this shit hurts.
And I know it wasn't
here last night.
What do you think it is?
I don't know man, I mean,
maybe you scratched
yourself in the sleep?
No. How can you say no for sure?
If you did in your sleep,
you wouldn't know.
I didn't do it in my
fucking sleep, park.
This falls into the
category of 'weird shit'
and I need you
to acknowledge that.
Okay.
What do you know
about your house?
Were there any crimes
committed here?
Not that I know of, why?
I'm just thinking about how
it goes in the movies, man,
you know, weird stuff
starts happening.
And then you find out
the house that you living in
contains a secret
portal to hell.
Or I don't know, the last family
that lived here was all murdered
under mysterious circumstances,
that kinda thing.
Or,
you remember
nightmare on elm street?
What if you're mom
killed someone
and now their evil ghost
has come back to haunt you
as a form of retribution
for her sins?
You wanna turn the TV back on?
The fuck?
Kenan, I need to know what you
know about this house.
What? Miles?
What do you think
I'd know that you don't?
I don't know, do you
know anything about
any secret portals or
or vengeful spirits?
Give me something.
Look, before you
mock my suffering,
look at this shit.
How did you get that?
I don't know.
Looks like you scratched
yourself or something.
My nails are not that sharp.
I'm telling you this has
something to do with the house.
Kenan, has anything weird
been happening to you?
Nope, not to my knowledge.
Seems like you're
the prime target, miles.
Why is that?
And the mocking continues.
I had to.
Yeah, okay.
It's all fun and games until
a motherfucker gets possessed.
Boy has lost his fucking mind.
You remember, when we
went into the kitchen,
because we thought someone
had broken into the house,
but it was really,
just Kenan and Nia?
Yeah.
Sigh.
Well,
for a split second,
not even,
I thought...
I saw something
else in the kitchen.
What do you mean something else?
It was so quick,
I don't even know how to,
I just,
I felt like I caught glimpse
of something that was...
I thought I was going crazy,
that's why I didn't say
anything about it.
But, now...
Hey, ma?
Question.
Hey, miles?
Answer.
What do you know
about this house?
Like, did you get
one of those deals,
that was too good to be true,
cause something really
bad happened here?
Oh, boy!
No, I don't know what you're
expecting to hear, miles.
The house is fairly new.
It's in a good neighborhood.
The crimes rates
are lower than low.
That's why we moved
here, doohickey.
Bop, leave a message please,
I promise I won't
get back to you.
No, I know that...
Since we've been here,
things have been kosher,
but what about before?
The worst thing that happened
here that I know of,
believe it or not, it's Mr.
Huntly's cat going missing.
And they found it the same day.
So, I...
Why are you asking
me this, miles?
You ever kill
anybody before, ma?
No, why would you
even ask me that?
- No.
- Cause he's mental.
Cause I think I'm being haunted
by something in this house.
I'm sorry,
did you say haunted?
Don't listen to him, ma.
I'm telling the truth.
Things have been happening
to me at school,
then I woke up with this.
It looks like you
scratched yourself.
That's what I said.
No, you know what it could be?
An allergic reaction.
I used a different detergent
to wash your clothes.
Why you still doing
this boy's laundry, ma?
He's about to be 18.
And you're about to be 23
yet you still live at home
with your mom.
Explain that to me.
You graduated from college,
you have a job,
why are you still here?
Go home, Roger?
Nia and I are in a process
of getting our own spot.
And you...
Know this.
So, leap off my testicle.
So, apparently,
I'm not sitting here.
Sorry, ma.
Well, back to what matters.
Ma, I don't think this
is an allergic reaction.
I'm gonna give you something
to put on it after dinner.
It really doesn't look that bad.
Er, this is just...
I gotta say this is delightful.
I'm being neglected
by my own family.
I just want the both
of you to know,
if anything happens to me,
you're gonna be like,
"oh, man, maybe we should've
taken miles's concerns
more seriously.
If only we
can go back."
Well, by then it
will be too late,
and you have to live
with your mistake.
Pass the gravy, Kenan.
Two words, here it is,
over-dramatic.
Um... actually
that's one word.
But, thanks for playing.
Yo!
My bad.
You can't be doing
stuff like that, man.
My bad, I thought you heard me.
Pop tart?
No, I'm not really hungry.
Um.
Ah.
Yo?
What?
What are you doing?
Eating my pop tart.
Yeah, but, why are you
chewing like that?
Like what?
You sound like
a fucking giraffe.
I didn't realize I was
chewing that loud.
Well, if you don't
know, now you know.
I'm over here in my zone and
you messing up the flow.
Damn, my bad.
I'm mad you called
me a giraffe though.
Anyway,
you find anything yet?
Nope, there hasn't been a
murder here in over 30 years.
30 years?
30 years.
And even then, it
wasn't really a murder.
It was a vehicular
manslaughter case.
Shit!
So, we got nothing to work with?
Nope.
I just asked...
There's no reason this shit
should be happening to me.
Okay, don't get mad.
I know that I said
before about possibly
seeing something in the kitchen.
But, I was thinking,
what if this was just my
mind playing tricks on me?
You a flip flopping
motherfucker, you just said...
I know, I know.
But, what am I supposed
to make of everything?
I mean this is a good house.
This is a good neighborhood.
I don't know
what's going on, miles.
Me either.
Okay, so...
Why don't you try and enjoy
the next couple of days?
You got your birthday coming up,
the strip club,
fun shit!
Look,
maybe there is no haunting.
I don't get you at all, park.
Now, every thing's
a hallucination?
I just want you
to enjoy your birthday.
You wanna make
some more pop tarts?
I know you want to.
Miles.
Miles?
Mi...
Happy birthday, baby.
Make a wish.
Dang!
He still here.
When you have time
to make me a cake?
Don't worry about it.
This looks good.
Eat it.
For breakfast?
Youthful mother of mine,
embrace me.
Yo!
I love it!
Imma wear on my GQ tee.
You the "ma", ma.
Yes, miles. You
got me something?
You never give me
anything for my birthday.
How cheap was it?
Just open it.
I do enjoy Dunkin' donuts.
But, 10 dollars, that's it?
That's it?
Man, that's a good deal.
You get a dozen donuts.
You get a box of munchkins.
You got possibilities, man.
High value.
Fine, thanks Kenan.
You're not welcome.
Oh, I forgot to ask you, um...
Any supernatural
occurrences last night?
Nope.
That's surprising, I expected
a full on possession by now.
Kenan, stop.
Argh...
Mi-miles.
Asshole!
Argh! No!
Sorry, ma.
Not even subtle about it.
All right, let's take
a trip downstairs.
There's lots of cards, you
know what that means.
A lot of mullah, baby.
So, any more weird stuff?
Nope, for the last
two days, nothing.
See?
Happy day of birth,
we got tobacco, scratch
offs and titties.
And boom.
What the fuck is this?
Strong, strong shit, Miley.
All I did was sniff the
stuff and I'm buzzed.
I had you doing
the Harlem shake.
Come on, Dudeski,
glug, glug, glug.
Don't be a little
whore, chug that shit.
Oh, man, uh!
Whoa!
Shit.
Now, whose ready
for some Booty's
on some Booty's on some Booty?
What you asking again?
Would you rather drink
pee flavored lemonade
or lemonade flavored pee?
I mean either way I lose.
Exactly, but it's
about how you lose.
I don't know man, I
mean, all right, so,
if I drink
pee flavored lemonade,
yeah, it's lemonade,
but it still tastes
like pee, so,
there's really no difference
from drinking actual pee.
But, if I drink
lemonade flavored pee,
yeah, it tastes like lemonade,
but it's still pee.
You gotta make a choice.
Either way, you look at it,
urine is gonna be involved.
That's just a given.
But, it's up to you to do decide
whether or not you
actually want to taste it.
I guess, I'll do it with
the lemonade flavored pee.
Ah, good, man.
Wha...
What's this?
Did you get this
from the strip club?
Whoa, whoa, but how?
Don't question my ways, Brosiff.
That's kind of insanitary.
Mm, smells like
fucking butterflies.
What do butterflies smell like?
Wait, wait.
So,
fuck bitches get money.
Does that mean,
fuck bitches like
have sex with bitches
and get money?
Or is it like
forget bitches,
we don't need 'em,
and get money.
I, I see, I always
thought it was like,
fuck bitches, like
we don't want 'em,
just focus on the cash flow.
Um.
What, what, what?
Wait, wait.
What I think,
it's deliberately ambiguous.
It's like,
I hit a baby
with a chair.
Did you hear the baby using
the chair as a weapon?
Or, did you hear the baby,
that just so happen
to have a chair.
I saw a woman with binoculars.
Did you see the woman
with your binoculars?
Or did you see that the
woman had binoculars?
That's good, that's good.
Mind fuck, Dudeski.
Yo, you know what
I could go for right now?
A Patti LaBelle,
sweet potato pie.
Yeah.
Yo, nobody's sleeping
too late tomorrow
cause we're all going
out to lunch for little
post birthday repast.
Say, uh, 12:30 in
front of the park?
Plan? Plan.
Nighty-night,
hoe-bags.
Yo, tonight was dope.
Thanks.
Yeah, yep.
My son is legal now.
But, you know what,
I still don't get why'd it
all just stop like that.
Miles, let it go.
I can't. Oh, Parker, can you
please tell me how the fuck
you go from being just
as convinced as I am
to now downplaying
the whole situation?
I don't wanna keep talking
about this, all right?
Look, the weird shit is over,
if there was ever any
weird shit to begin with.
You're fine, you
had a good night,
it's Donzo, man.
Yo, all t he horror
movies you watch
and you still not into the game.
Er, you tryna
brush everything off
and that's when
shit gets serious.
Parker, come on.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Hopefully.
But, you gotta let me
borrow 10 dollars.
I don't gotta do
anything, Aidan,
you already owe me 10 dollars.
I'll pay you back.
Yeah, you can't ask
me for more money
when you haven't paid
me back from before.
No, look at it like this,
if I borrow another 10
dollars, I'll owe 20 dollars.
So, you'll get
back even more money.
No, I'll loose more money
because you're not
gonna pay me back.
Aidan, you still owe
me five dollars.
Well, loan me another 5 and
then you'll be even with Kurt.
Man, chase is on some bullshit.
No! Still not picking up?
This was his idea, how he gonna
invite somebody somewhere
and then not answer his phone?
You think he overslept?
Probably. Yo, what
is this guy doing?
I was waiting in that
park for two hours,
cold as shit, my boy.
Shit.
Man, I give up!
One of y'all call him.
Not it.
Look at this.
Oh, shit!
Yeah.
Yeah, but nothing's real, right?
A fucking brand.
And listen to this.
I got this last night.
Happy birthday, miles.
Who is this?
I don't know.
But, I know it
wasn't any of them.
I got the voice
mail at 10:42 P.M.
We were all walking at
kitty's at that time.
I would've seen them do it.
Okay, look,
I believe you all right.
I'm sorry.
I believe you.
She's at work. Did
you tell your mom?
Kenan? He's at Nia's place.
Okay.
Let's get some food
in our systems
and then back
to the drawing board.
I'm done with this shit!
Let's just go kick down
Dudeski's door.
This is simply unacceptable!
Okay.
I gotta tell y'all something.
- No, seriously.
- Here we go.
Ay, yeah, no...
Hold on, wait a minute.
Isn't that chase's house?
We were just with him, bro.
Did you catch what those
detectives were saying?
What? They said he
was ripped open.
From what I heard,
his parents came home
and they found him
stuffed in the closet.
No sign of a break in,
nothing like that, so,
they're calling
it a freak accident,
which makes absolutely no sense.
This is crazy.
I don't like this, Parker.
I got that weird-ass voice mail,
I don't know who it's from.
I got this...
Whatever this is on
the back of my neck
and now chase is...
I knew this wasn't fucking done,
we've got to figure this out.
Yeah.
But, we can't do
shit by ourselves.
Here, listen to it now.
What's this?
The thing that's
been following you,
is not human.
It disguised as voice
to send you that message.
You see, those look like regular
headphones, but they're not.
They were designed to
identify demonic pitch.
That is what it sounds
like in its real form.
Some scary shit, right?
So, we're dealing with a demon?
That's right.
You say you have a mark
on your neck, right?
Yeah.
That's the mark of the Gorenos.
Yes. The "Gorenos"?
Nothing but evil.
It's a demon from the unseen.
The unseen?
See there's heaven
and there's hell
and in between
there is purgatory.
But, just above purgatory,
is the world of the unseen.
These evil entities,
they have their own sort of
agency if you will.
We're talking about evil
that has separated itself
from the constraints
of hell and purgatory.
What does it want with me?
You're 18 now.
Your soul is in its prime.
Its ready.
Ready for what?
And a lot of people turn 18,
why does it want me?
Unlike other evil
forces, the Gorenos
needs to be summoned.
But, I didn't summon it.
Yes, you didn't.
But, somebody did.
Somebody made a deal
with this thing.
And the reward was your
soul when you turn 18.
Now, what's so appealing
about the Gorenos?
It can Grant you one wish,
in return...
For a soul.
So, why hasn't it
already taken it?
Cause it needs you.
This is a process.
The Gorenos has it's own
way of doing things.
First,
it stalks you.
You won't even know it's there.
That's probably what it did
for those weeks leading
up to your birthday.
And then it makes
its presence known,
it haunts you.
That would explain the strange
stuff that's been going down.
And finally,
it leaves a mark on you.
It owns you.
But, it's already left
its mark on me.
So, what does that mean?
The good news,
well not good news.
But, the upside, if you
wanna call it a upside,
is that its gonna let
you live for a while.
So, it can feed off your soul.
Why?
Did the Gorenos kill chase?
Almost definitely.
But, how?
It uses your body as a host.
And it feeds on your
soul at night,
which gives it strength
to go out and kill.
This thing gets off on carnage.
That's what the people who
call for it don't realize.
The only reason
that it needs a soul,
is to have something to feed on.
When it kills,
it uses so much of its energy,
that it has to replenish.
And that's where you come in.
Basically, you are
a nutritious meal.
And it's gonna keep on
doing what its doing
until it has nothing
left to feed on.
And by that point...
I'll be dead.
How is it choosing its victims?
It has dibs on anyone that
miles come in contact with.
Me? Even you?
Not so much, it prefer
the younger flesh.
But,
if you're virgin,
you will live, unless,
you have been offered directly
to the Gorenos. Whoa,
whoa, whoa, wait.
Virgins are really spared?
That's like an actual thing?
So, I'm good then.
Sorry, uh, that was
really inappropriate.
So, how do we stop it?
Give me some time.
A pact with the
Gorenos is strong,
but I'm going to see
what I can find out.
What am I supposed
to do in the mean time?
Here's a suggestion,
find out who fucked
you over and why.
We'll be in touch.
You guys got my information,
thanks for reaching out.
Thank you for being
who you said you were.
I really do wanna
help you, all right?
And listen,
you still have time.
That's the part you
cannot lose sight of.
The Gorenos feeds at night,
when you are sleeping.
That's when you're
at your weakest.
So, don't go to sleep.
Yo,
the voice mail is gone.
It was on here and now
it's not on here!
Fuck, man!
Yo, who would give me
up to a fucking demon?
Ugh, that's the golden question!
I'm a nice guy, right?
I don't have beef with nobody.
You don't.
Was it you?
Yes, miles,
it was me.
Motherfucker, I didn't
summon no demon!
Are you fucking cross faded?
Oh, shit!
What?
No, "oh, shit!",
the 'o.S.' Factor.
What?
Remember, the 'o.S.' Factor?
That's what separates
the good horror movies
from the shitty ones.
That moment, that makes
you go, "oh, shit"?
And what about
the 'o.S.' Factor?
This is the real life case
of the 'o.S.' Factor.
I think I know who set you up.
Who?
Kenan!
What makes you say Kenan?
Now, I could be totally off,
but if my observational skills
are as good as I think they are,
all signs point to Kenan.
I mean, when he is not
minimizing your turmoil,
he is blatantly ignoring it.
And he refuses to let anyone
else to believe you either.
Guilt disguised as contempt!
Who is it?
Open the fucking door, Kenan.
Yo, you got a fucking problem?
Did you summon the Gorenos?
I'm gonna take that
long pause as a yes.
What do you know
about the Gorenos?
How'd you find out?
You're good actor, Kenan.
You're good at shit.
Why would you make
a deal with that?
It's complex, man.
Nah, it seems pretty
cut and dry to me.
Look,
I know we've had our
discrepancies, but,
goddamn, Kenan, I'm
still your brother.
Why'd you do it?
I didn't think it would work.
That's not what I asked you.
Why did you do it?
I'm sorry, miles.
Sorry is not gonna protect
my fucking soul, Kenan.
I was 16, man.
You remember when Nia and I
got in that accident?
One of my biking got
hit by the pickup truck.
Nia was a fucking vegetable.
I just messed up my wrist and...
She slammed her head
in the sidewalk.
They declared her brain dead.
I got to go home
that night, man.
She didn't.
Her parent's wanted to
keep her on life support,
but there is no
recovering from that.
I had to bring her back.
I remember, they did all
those stories on her.
She just woke up one day,
and she was fine, right?
Yeah.
I always wondered about that.
Now, you know what happened.
But, Kenan,
here's the part that
you overlooked,
death is inevitable.
Everyone has their time to die,
and Nia's time was
at that hospital!
You fucked with that
and you shouldn't have.
You don't have
the right to decide
who lives and who doesn't.
I was 16...
Exactly!
You were 16!
You were old enough to
understand what you were doing.
How did you even know how
to summon the Gorenos?
I found everything online.
That's just disturbing.
It came into our room one night.
It was this...
I can't even describe it.
But, I asked it to bring
Nia back to life.
All the friends you have,
all the people you know,
I didn't choose you per Se.
And you choose me?
The Gorenos saw you
sleeping and it...
Implied that
it would be interested
in you when you got older.
And I said okay.
All right, cause that
makes it so much better!
Also, why would you bring
it in to our room?
Why would you put
me at risk like that?
Obviously, I wasn't concerned
with logistics, okay,
I wanted to act fast.
Anyway, the next day,
Nia was fine.
And everyone was saying
it was a medical miracle.
I... I'm sorry, miles.
You sacrificed me
in order to bring
back your girlfriend?
And then you didn't even
give me a heads up,
even after I told you
what was going on.
You trivialized
the entire thing.
You think I wasn't
gonna catch on?
Look, I don't expect
you to help me.
Actually, even if you
offered to help,
I'd tell you to go
fuck yourself.
Just so you know,
the Gorenos has big plans.
You know why it wants me?
It wants to feed on me
because my soul is a
source of nourishment.
This thing is a killer.
And after it kills, it needs
me to refill itself back up.
It already killed chase,
it's gonna kill again.
And I don't even
know how to stop it.
Are you gonna tell
mom about this?
So, did you tell your mom?
She's working late tonight.
Did you call her?
I've been trying,
but her phone's off.
And honestly, she's not
gonna believe me anyway.
What about the mark?
What about chase?
Kenan has her convinced
that I'm crazy, man.
He knows how to absorb himself.
Just like the
fucking movies, yo.
Either the adults are Mia,
or they refuse the accept the
existence of supernatural.
Preach.
So, no news on how
to break the pact?
We can't just have an exorcism?
Nope, this isn't
really a possession,
it's more of a bodily draining.
So, what do we do?
I know what we don't do,
we don't go to sleep.
What's that shit Nas said?
"I never sleep coz sleep
is the cousin of death."
If I'm asleep, I'm weak.
And if I'm weak,
it's snack time.
So, we just gotta stay up.
Well, technically
I could go to sleep.
But, I won't.
Thank you.
And actually speaking
of snack time,
I think we need
a little incentive
for pulling an all nighter.
Parker?
Parker!
Exactly. Oh, shit.
What time is it?
1:32. In the morning?
Yeah.
Guess that sugar
overload was a bit much.
I don't even know.
How do you feel?
Wait,
I was sleeping, it got me.
It fed? What
it feels like.
And if it fed,
then it's out there again.
And you remember
what Haywood said,
anyone who comes in contact
with me is up for grabs.
It already got chase.
Whose next?
I'm assuming it's going
after our friend group.
I know Kurt's still a virgin.
But, reg isn't.
And I'm pretty sure
Aidan isn't either.
Since you're more
positive about reg,
let's start with him.
Reg, what up, miles?
Where are you right now?
I went on a walk.
I'm at the park.
What are you going
on a walk for?
It's almost two in the morning.
I ain't been sleeping, man.
I try to block it out, but,
I keep thinking about chase.
I just been going on these walks
trying to clear my
head, then I go home.
Reg, I tried to tell
you guys sooner,
but you gotta come
over my house.
Listen, I know
what killed chase.
And I know that it's after you
and potentially Aidan.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the Gorenos.
That's what it's called.
It's a demon from the
world of the unseen.
Look, it's a really long story,
but, the shorter version
is that it's feeding on my
soul and going out
and killing my friends
cause that's what it does
and it's fucking evil!
Sounds like you haven't been
getting no sleep either.
Reg, I'm serious.
Miles, my boy,
there's no demon trying
to kill me, all right?
And even if there was
a demon out here,
why would it be after me?
I ain't do nothing.
Cause that's what demons do.
They got an appetite
for mutilation.
They'll kill anybody,
fuck the motive.
Look,
try to get some rest, all right?
I think you need it
more than I do.
Regs, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Well, where is he? Fuck!
He thinks I'm crazy.
Let's go. He's at the park.
Oh, no! What's going on?
Miles, wake up!
What the hell are you doing?
You passed out. What happened?
I feel weak. Want me
to get you some water?
No, we gotta save regs.
Stay here, take
it easy, I'll go.
Parker. Parker, what?
It's not gonna do
anything to me.
You said you feel weak,
just stay here and relax.
Don't go to sleep, but relax.
If he is not at the
park, check his house.
That's the imprint.
Listen, I don't care what the
news report say, it's all wrong.
Chase didn't die
in a freak accident,
and reg wasn't killed
in an animal attack.
I believe you, okay.
Every thing is just
too close together
to be written off
as tragic coincidence.
No, Kurt,
you should be safe
since you're a virgin.
Aidan, I knew you had
a little thing with Nicky,
but I didn't know if you
guys actually did it or not.
Yeah, we did.
I'm not a virgin either, miles.
What?
Since when?
Since I got together
with Malerey.
Are you...
Kurt, I asked you about that,
you said you guys
didn't do anything.
First time you asked, we didn't.
But, we got together
again and it happened.
And you're both targets now.
Why is it only after
people who had sex?
Because, sex out of
wedlock is a sin.
Therefore, your
souls are impure,
which is very appealing
to a murderous demon.
So, what now?
Now, we stick together.
Yeah, you guys should stay
at my place tonight.
By the way,
I'm sure you know this already,
but that was a really
really sick thing...
What your brother did.
Bringing the Gorenos
here and everything.
Yeah, that...
Yeah, what a dick move.
Are y'all gonna cook?
For real?
Hmm mm.
Hey baby, you want some lasagna?
Kenan and Nia are cooking.
No, thanks, but I would like
to talk to you about something.
Sure.
I want you to know,
your elder son,
your first born child,
Kenan Lamar Grant
is a demon worshiper.
Oh, boy! He's a what?
Yeah, oh, boy!
When Kenan and Nia
got into that accident,
Nia, was brain dead.
Do you know the odds
of regaining brain
function after that?
They're not very high.
Which means,
Nia was basically dead.
But, what happened?
She came back to life
and you know why?
It wasn't some miraculous event,
Kenan summoned the demon
called the Gorenos.
And it gave him Nia back
in return for my soul.
What is he talking about?
You're not supposed
to be here, Nia.
Miles. That's what
I'm talking about.
No, it's true.
Ma, didn't I tell you
he was gonna do this?
Anything to make it believable.
This is real!
It left its symbol on me.
It's right there!
You think I'm making this up?
It's all online.
The stuff about
the Gorenos is fake.
Just like slender man.
Just some stuff to scare kids.
Miles, you're taking
this too far.
No, I'm not, Kenan. You need
to own up to what you did.
Nia should be dead!
Okay, look that is the
second time you said that,
you don't even
stop it! Wanna believe!
Cause listen to you, demons?
Demon!
Okay.
In what world am I supposed
to believe any of that?
No! You need to stop.
You need to wake up.
Things are happening
that defy logic, all right?
Every thing I'm
telling you is true.
But, if you're still gonna
take Kenan's side,
you're fucking stupid!
Don't you ever in your life
talk to me like that!
Unclench your jaw.
Ma, I'm sorry
for cursing at you,
I'm sorry for yelling.
But I'm not sorry
for what I said.
Oh, really?
Look, everything happens
for a reason.
We might not have
all the answers.
But, we don't need them
and that's the part
you need to remember.
Kenan and Nia were
hurt real bad.
But, by the grace of god,
they are both here.
They're both well and we're not
gonna talk about this any more.
Miles,
I'm sorry about chase and reg,
I am. I don't even know
what to say, it's terrible.
You are angry and
rightfully so, all right?
But, you do not have a right
to take that out on all of us,
especially Nia!
You owe her an apology.
I knew this was gonna happen.
To be clear this
is not optional.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry Kenan did this.
Cursing at me like that.
Nia, I'm sorry. You
didn't do anything.
I can't fall asleep.
If I go to sleep,
we're all at risk.
Um, not all of us.
Yes, Parker, your virginity
has made you untouchable, yes.
I'm all in for the
group bonding sesh,
really, I'm truly,
I'm lovin' it, but,
you do realize we
can't stay attached
to wieners forever, right?
Whoa, obviously, but,
for right now, it's united we
stay and divided we die.
If anything happens, at least
we got each other's backs.
Kurt?
Aidan?
Yo, miles,
you wanna get something
to eat from downstairs?
We should stay here.
It's just going downstairs.
We'd be right back.
You know you're hungry.
What's up?
You were in the bathroom
this whole time?
Oh, no. Yeah, why?
It's locked.
Aidan? Kurt?
If you can hear me,
say something.
Help!
Parker, where you going?
Really?
Aidan? Kurt?
Help!
You all right, man?
Whoa, what happened?
You passed out, man.
Again?
Where's Kurt?
He's down the hallway,
he's about to call 911.
Kurt, we're good, he's awake.
I feel like nobody's parents
are ever home for this shit.
Right? What the fuck?
This is gotta be child neglect.
No! I still feel weak, man.
Then, that thing is
probably getting stronger.
Yo,
can you dream when
you're unconscious?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
Cause when you pass out,
it shuts off the part of
your brain needed for sleep.
What?
I'm educated.
Did you have a dream?
I don't even want
to get into it, okay.
But, just know, it was
very unpleasant.
And Parker, you
were fucking pussy.
I'm sorry?
I'm just glad
that shit wasn't real.
You know, excluding
my being a pussy,
this dream can mean
one or two things.
Either you just had a
a final destination moment,
where you envisioned
the inevitable,
or,
the Gorenos is on that
Freddy Krueger shit.
Invading your thoughts,
using your nightmares
to fuck with you, man.
It can't do that, can it?
I don't know.
All right, it's...
2:45.
You guys gotta make your exit
before my mom gets here.
Which gives us until
6:30.
And by then the sun will be up,
and the Gorenos can't do
shit during the day time.
So, for these next few hours,
we gotta tough it out.
And please...
Don't let me fall
asleep or faint.
I don't think we can
stop you from fainting, miles.
Yeah!
We'll just be alert.
And if you can't prevent
the act itself,
try and wake me up
as soon as possible.
Uh, you see, it's still
not that easy.
Kurt! Just go with it.
When a person...
Yes and okay.
Connect four tournament?
I know what you're trying to do.
But, you and I both know
I'm not your type, all right.
You can't touch this.
So, personally, I think you're
wasting your time and mine.
You know what I mean?
Cut this shit.
You ain't finished
scaring me off?
And I hate to let you down,
but you ain't the first demon
that's been after me,
you old fuckface.
This weather is bipolar.
I know how to stop the Gorenos.
Are you serious?
How?
What do I have to do?
It is easier said than done.
But, you have to kill the person
that summoned it
in the first place
and you have to re-kill the
soul that was brought to life.
They don't tell you this online.
But, it took seven trips
to seven different libraries
to find this book.
So, I have to kill
Kenan and Nia?
Well, it's a little more
intense than that.
You have to use a knife
and you have to stab
them in the heart.
That's the only way
this would work.
Why does it have
to be in the heart?
The only way to guarantee
that Kenan and Nia
can't be brought back,
it has to be in the heart.
I kinda feel bad though.
Nia didn't even do anything.
Well,
you didn't do anything,
neither did your friends.
But, y'all had to
suffer, am I right?
Look,
I am acutely aware of that.
This is a shitty situation.
But, at the same time,
I don't know if I'm capable
of killing someone.
Even if it's the person who had
no regard for my own life.
Miles, I understand where
you're coming from completely.
This is some heavy stuff.
But, killing those two is
the only way to end this.
If there's no Kenan,
there's no Gorenos.
He's the only reason
why it's here.
And you're sure this
is the way to do it?
It says it right here,
doesn't it?
I can't do it.
I can't do something like that.
That's my brother.
"Violence begets violence."
That was Dr. king.
And some times,
"you have to pick the gun up
to put the gun down."
That was Malcolm X.
Haywood, look,
I'm beyond grateful
for all your help.
But, I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
Uh, maybe there is
another way to stop it.
And if not?
I don't know.
But, I'm not a murderer.
Miles, I'm going to give
it to you straight.
This is not the right time
to become morally
afflicted, all right?
That thing is feeding
on your soul.
You understand what I'm saying?
You are getting weaker,
but it's getting stronger.
You said you've
been fainting, right?
And that's only the tip
of the pencil, believe me.
Miles,
your friends are dying.
You are dying.
It's not gonna stop unless
you do something about it.
Hey.
Miles, look.
I know I'm not your
favorite person right now.
I get it, but...
Have you tried to empathize?
Nia is my fucking everything!
I've been in love with
that girl since I was 10.
Why would I let her die
when there's an opportunity,
a clear opportunity
for me to prevent it?
You gonna sit there
and tell me you
wouldn't have done
the same thing
if it happened to
someone that you loved.
I don't think you realize this,
but the more you
defend yourself,
the more fucked up you sound.
What more can I say?
I'm sorry
that your friends are...
Yeah.
I'm sorry
the Gorenos wanted you.
It is what it is.
Just try not to think about it.
Try not to...
Yo,
you're a fucking dick, man!
Are you gonna be home tonight?
Why?
Wait. No.
Nia's coming over.
I know what's done is done.
But, if I could go back...
If you could go back,
you'd do the same shit.
Yeah.
Not really sure where I
was going with that.
Where the fuck have you been?
I've been calling you all day.
My phone was acting up,
what's wrong?
Kurt's dead.
What?
You hear about it?
It was on the news.
Kurt's neighbors said they found
a scalp in his backyard.
Turns out the scalp was Kurt's
and that's all they found.
But... That thing is
getting stronger.
It can kill in the daytime now.
People on the news
so fucking retarded.
They're saying a wild animal
is roaming the streets.
Why can't they
understand the fact
that this is not
a worldly matter?
Where's Aidan?
He's fine, I called him
like 10 minutes ago.
But, who knows how long
that's gonna last?
I saw Haywood today.
What happened?
I know how to stop the Gorenos.
Kenan?
What happened?
There's some stuff that hasn't
been sitting well with me.
And what stuff would that be?
This whole thing with miles.
Babe, I told you, he's in a bad
place right now, he just needs,
needs some time to get
it together, yeah,
that's what you said before
and I went along with it.
But, in the back of my head,
I couldn't help but think
that maybe there's more to it.
And what does that mean?
It means, I did some
research, okay, and I think
miles is telling the truth.
No, he's not.
Kenan, I was brain dead.
Do you know what that means?
The complete and irreversible
loss of brain function.
Now, for years I
thought I was this
I don't know, wonder woman
because I was able to recover
from something like that.
And no one knew how I did
it, not even the doctors.
Everyone just
it called a miracle.
And I mean the
publicity was awesome.
Yeah, it was, but then
I guess you could...
Say that I became...
Contemplative.
How is that in a matter of days,
not even, I'm back to normal?
It was like you said,
it was a miracle.
It was bullshit, okay?
It was a lie.
And you know it was a lie.
No one can recover
from something like that.
And if they can, they were never
brain dead to begin with.
Kenan, you're caught.
The Gorenos grants people one
wish in return for a soul.
I'm back to life and
everything is all good.
And then miles turns 18
and it all goes downhill, why?
You sacrificed your own
brother, for what?
For you, Nia, I love you.
Did you think I could
function without you?
Maybe not at first, but
you'd have to, all right?
You don't have a choice.
That's how it goes, we die.
Some of us die
sooner than others.
But, it happens.
Of course, it's sad, of course,
it sucks, but, you find
ways to deal with it.
This was the only way
that I could deal with it.
And no one seems to understand
that, not even you.
Kenan, this was,
not only was this selfish,
but it was just really fucked up
thing to do, I mean honestly,
who does that
and thinks it's okay?
And you continued
to lie about it.
Look at how you're acting!
Nia, yeah, I was selfish,
but that is the point.
You're such a big
part of my life.
That I...
Miles was right.
Fuck miles! I shouldn't be here.
Don't open the door.
Why? Cause you
know who it is?
Let me go, Kenan.
I'm sure, we all know
what this is about.
What the fuck is that?
It's called a knife.
See,
this was not how I wanted
things to play out.
But, then I saw how...
Remorseless you are.
Just, empty.
And I guess that prompted
a change of heart.
So, you gonna stab us?
I have to.
Miles, I want you to know that
I believe you about the Gorenos.
Did Kenan finally admit it?
About fucking time!
So, I now know how
to stop the Gorenos.
I have to kill you.
And I have to kill Nia.
Which I feel terrible
about, cause
this wasn't even
your fault, Nia.
But, I gotta stab
you guys in the heart.
So, you think we're just
gonna let you stab us?
Are you fucking retarded?
What you balling up
your fist for, Kenan?
I mean, let's use
our heads here.
Fist...
Versus knife.
Not really a fair fight.
Kenan! Kenan, stop!
Kenan!
Nia,
Nia, let's go.
- Nia, let's go.
- I'm not going.
Kenan, I love you, okay?
Nia, I love you too,
but we need to leave.
Why? I think we should stay.
Because I'm not
supposed to be here.
Yet, here you are.
Yes, here I am.
And as long as I'm here,
people are gonna die.
Miles is gonna die.
Kenan, I love you so much.
But, you brought some
really evil shit here.
And I cannot get behind it.
I know a way that we can rid
of it and still be together.
Look, I can't force
you to do anything.
But, I know what I'm doing.
Nia, please listen to me,
I don't wanna be without you.
Then don't.
No, no...!
No!
The CSI folks
found both Kenan and Nia's
fingerprints on the knife.
So, they inferred that it was
either a joint suicide
or murder suicide.
And as far as I was concerned,
I was at Parker's
when it happened.
So, I don't know shit.
My mom thought the easiest
thing to do was move out,
and I don't really blame her.
We got an apartment downtown.
That worked out better
for my mom anyway
since it was closer
to the hospital.
And with me going
to college soon,
it didn't make sense
for her to live
in a big house like that
by herself especially
after what happened.