"My dear love."
"You reside in my heart."
"I get these thoughts
sometimes in my mind."
"Sometimes in my mind--"
POLICE RESIDENCE
Hello!
Sir, the car has come
and is waiting downstairs.
Okay.
Hey, pass the towel.
I'm asking you for the towel.
Hey!
There is hardly any sugar in this.
There is no sugar.
What can be done?
Who are you? Damn it!
Are you looking for your gun?
Are you trying to call the police?
I will help you.
Hello, police darling!
CI Sharma got kidnapped
from his apartment.
Hey, what do you
think of the police?
Pack up!
- What happened, brother?
- We forgot the keys upstairs.
- What a silly thing!
- I will go and get it.
If one gets to do the final action,
it gives great joy.
Thanks, darling.
Hey Laxman, not that side,
go to the fifth floor.
- Come on, hurry up!
- Okay, sir.
- Something happened here.
- Some sound is coming from inside.
- Crap! Krishna, check up over here.
- Okay, sir.
Crap!
This morning some unidentified miscreants
kidnapped Bowenpalli CI Sharma.
The kidnappers wore masks
of famous Telugu film heroes.
Are the kidnappings that happened fourteen
years ago repeating again?
Are you conducting some special
training courses for the kidnappers?
How are they managing it in such
a planned and organized manner?
- How much did they demand?
- One crore, sir.
One crore?!
He is our man.
Give whatever they ask
and settle the matter.
- Where are you?
- We came to buy pizzas.
- Do it fast.
- Okay, sir.
- There is a cellar next to the stairs.
- There is one, sir.
Put the money in the pizza bag next to it
and tell me the number of the vehicle.
Okay, sir.
AP09 AS 1234, sir.
AP09 AS 1234.
Stop the pizza bike immediately.
Breaking up is normal
and quite common these days.
It takes some time.
AP09 AS 1234.
A person started driving the bike
that you mentioned, sir.
Keep following him
without missing out.
Just keep following him.
Okay, sir.
He has taken a left turn
at the journalist colony.
- He's going towards the lake.
- Keep following him.
He parked the bike and is going towards
the garbage heap with the money bag.
I'll be on the phone.
You catch him and recover the money.
It seems that he realized
that I am following him.
He is unloading himself.
Hands up!
Turn this side.
Did you catch him?
Sir, the matter is..
It may not be nice if we catch him.
- What is the matter?
- It is--
Stop! Stop right there!
Sir, if you want a pizza,
you must order over the phone.
- You must not snatch like this.
- This too is an order.. law and order!
Stop!
This is the number
that sir mentioned.
- Sir!
- Hello!
We found the vehicle
with number 1234.
1234.
Hello!
We caught the pizza bike
with number 1234.
1234 again!
Sir, tell me.
He gave the same number
to all the bikes and fooled us.
Here the signal is a bit week, sir.
Don't let any vehicle off till I come.
Hello!
- Hello. Hey, wait.
- I'm speaking to you.
Get lost.
Bhadram,
don't let any vehicle go till I come.
I should not let any vehicle go?!
Okay, sir.
1234.
Sir!
He won't come on time at all!
Will he come...
...or not?
- "It's a mad world!"
- Tell me.
Your marriage is to happen
in 10 minutes.. where are you?
Any problem if I arrive there in 9 mins?
All the guests have come
and are waiting for you.. come quickly.
I must increase the speed in that case.
Here he comes.. hey, wait.
Where is the ring?
I am asking you where the ring is.
Here it is.
C'mon, everybody inside..
C'mon.
You brought it at the right time..
superb!
The marriage isn't cancelled because
he brought the ring in time.
Alas!
- Where is he?
- Hey, come on.
No!
She broke up with me...
...and the foolish girl got me
to buy the ring for her marriage!
- Drop the both of them.
- What?!
Sorry, I left them.
Raja Harishchandra Prasad.
How come you have breakups
with so many girls?
"I am an emperor who
does not make compromises."
"Oh God, no girl falls for me."
"I never lie to my girlfriends."
"That is my virtue,
what is wrong with it."
"Oh girl, I always speak the truth
and this nature has brought me doom."
"You told the facts to your girlfriend...
your friendship stands broken."
"I am an emperor who
does not make compromises."
"Oh God, no girl falls for me."
I saw her.
I love you, dad.
It is a blank check.
Hey, how is the birthday party
that I arranged?
Forget the party.. whose dress
between the both of us is better?
Your dress is crap and
your friend's one is superb!
What happened?
She slapped me since
I told the truth.
Oh... so sweet!
"I told the truth that her face,
looks, shoes and nails are not good."
"When the lover's father inquired,
I gave proof that I am jobless."
"On learning the truth, the girl
got angry and changed her address."
"In that manner I lost my lover."
"You told the facts to your girlfriend."
"Your friendship stands broken."
- Thank you, papa!
- Hey, careful!
"Things work out well
if you praise anyone."
"The beautiful girl is approaching."
"When I create my magic
all girls fall for me."
"When my eyes meet hers
I get the feeling of floating in the air."
"Why should I tell the truth
and cause my love to fail."
"You didn't tell lies to your girlfriend."
"What if your friendship is broken."
Cousin! Cousin!
Please open the window.
Wait!
Go and enjoy.
Thanks, cousin. I wish that you
get a lovely figure like me.
- Get lost!
- Good morning, sir.
- Tell me what the matter is.
- It is about an insurance policy.
I will call you later.
Brother! Brother!
- Do you have sugar complaint?
- How do you know that?
Because you cannot
control going to the loo.
- Hey!
- Get lost!
These people must be bashed.
Do you all in the city
have sugar complaint?
- You will all have a hard time.
- Hey!
Drive the car fast.
- They are coming, go fast.
- Madam!
You must have mistaken this
to be an auto. It is a Nano car.
That is an auto and this a Nano.
This is a Nano and that is an auto.
Please get down from the car.
Please!
The traffic is jammed. Hello!
Oh my God!
My Nano car! Who the hell was that?
Do you think that this road
belongs to your dad.
Why did you park the car in the middle!
Who are you to tell me to get lost?
How dare you hit my car?!
What do you think of yourselves?
Where are you taking my car?
Take your leg off the accelerator.
- I am removing my leg.
- Do it soon!
Why are they chasing you?
If they catch me
I will be forced to marry.
It seems that I am the one
who is going to suffer.
Can we escape in
this rat-sized car?
Cats cannot enter
the holes that rats can!
That's my baby Nano!
Oh crap!
- Go back quickly!
- Don't shout!
Hey, stay in your seat
or you will die.
They are coming close.
Her dress is flying
out of the car. See it.
Hold the steering.
- Hold the steering.
- Okay.
Take this and cut it.
- What should I cut?
- Cut it!
Cut the dress that
is flying out of the car.
Go fast!
Hey! Why did you put the tanker
in the middle of the road?
Won’t you let people pass?
- How long will it take, bro?
- 10 min.
Hey! Come in.. let us sit
in a jolly way inside the car.
Why do you say jolly when we are
in trouble? First get out of the car.
Get out. Out now.
My girl, did you escape
from your marriage ceremony?
What is it my boy?
Yes, we just saw a love movie
and decided to elope!
Go and mind your business.
- Go on now.
- Take good care of the girl.
Who should I take good care of?
Your daughter or this girl?
Who are you in the first place
and why did you enter my car?
Clarify it to me.
It seems that I did not cry
when I was born.
My father wrapped me in
a blue towel and held me close.
Stop your nonsense.
I did not say that to you. Go on.
What are you talking about?
You were the one who asked me
to clarify everything.
That is why I am saying the entire story!
You are a legend.
Just tell me why you
entered my car in this dress.
- Tell me quickly!
- So strange!
Whenever I fall in love with someone
they get married before I could propose.
The same thing happened with Yusuf.
It got repeated again
with Jaswinder Singh.
It fits you.
- At the same time--
- What happened?
I met Joseph.
Why did I fall in love with Joseph when
there are so many others in the world?
He was my English professor.
Everyone used to bunk going to college.
But I used to bunk going home
and go around him.
One day I thought of proposing to him
and sought the blessings of all gods.
In the world--
Why did you fall in love
only with Joseph...
...when there are so many
others in the world?
Is that all? It would be better
if you ask this to him instead of me.
I have an idea.
If the wedding dress goes missing,
the marriage is postponed.
That's why I stole the wedding dress,
escaped from them and got into your car.
When there are so many love stories
in the world, why is only yours so bad?
- Is that so?
- Yes!
Give me your phone.
- Give me your phone.
- I am giving it. Will you kill me?
What is she going to do?
- Hello!
- Tell me, Priya!
- Did the marriage get cancelled?
- What actually happened was--
- Just wait a minute.
Tell me now.
Mad girl, would the marriage get cancelled
just because you stole the wedding dress?
The marriage was over long ago.
It is my turn.
- But still--
- Alas! Please check whom you are hitting.
You get lost!
Did you not find one
telugu boy to fall in love?
How is that possible when
everyone maintains 2-3 girls?
- What about your love story?
- Love?!
When Soundarya entered my life,
my heart beat fast...
...and my phone got busy too!
- What are all these gifts?
- They are all for Soundarya.
I am going there now.
"Wherever I am I always
feel like being beside you."
Isn't that so?
I see Soundarya everywhere.
There.. There.. And here!
Oh God.. Soundarya!
Alas! My Soundarya!
She is my Soundarya! Soundarya!
Who is he?
All the jewelry set that I gave you!
Soundarya... it is me Raja!
Soundarya!
Hello... Please wait, Soundarya!
- Okay.
- There... Here.
Where is your Soundarya?
Having faith in girls is
like keeping a bomb in the pocket.
It can blast any time.
My love did not get set because
I did not find the right girl.
Otherwise I too would
have been happy like them.
What type of girl
does the Master prefer?
It is enough if it is a girl...
Why need more options?
What type of boy do you want?
His body should be strong
and his heart should be soft.
He should be a software engineer.
But I am 10th fail!
All newspapers
and news channels say that...
...how can those who cannot save
themselves, save the people!
We need to do something
before the issue becomes serious.
Sir, I believe that Dilip is
the correct person for this case.
Dilip means--
Do you remember that...
...a few years ago kidnappings by masked
men happened in the same manner.
At that time they didn't stop at one
or two and even kidnapped MLA Govindaraju.
When the entire government
was feeling the heat...
...Dilip Kumar was the person
who easily solved that case.
He is the correct
person for this case.
Call him right now.
- Hello!
- Sir has come to the old police station.
What?!
The commissioner has come there?
What is he doing?
He is making a list from old files...
...assuming that the kidnapper
must be an old criminal.
"It is all clear so beat it."
"Just beat it."
"You better do it when you can."
"Don't want to see you idle, macho man."
"You wanna be there better do it."
"So beat it."
Come along!
Dasanna, listen to me once!
Hey, tell us the truth!
Sir... what I mean is.--
They are not the kidnappers.
It is a waste of energy bashing them.
Hey, mind your business!
- Tell me the truth!
- I don't know anything.
Tell me who did it!
We have checked all of them.
Only Basavayya remains.
Where will he go?
We will catch him for sure.
Basavayya!
- 9!
- 6!
- I say 9.
- Make it 6 rupees.
You don't bargain for condoms
but do so for vegetables!
Hey! Why do you speak and dress like that?
It is not just appearance
but a necessity.
How many days should
we run this market?
I want to enter the software
field and try my luck.
Who threw the stone?!
Hit and miss!
Luck is not enough..
you need brains too for it.
It means that the boy
has all the qualities.
He is a strong person
with a soft heart...
...we only need to find whether
he is a software engineer or not.
You didn't tell me why
you dressed up like this.
It is...
I found the girl of my heart.
Is that all?
She is not a part-time affair
but more like a life-time thing.
Father will like him.
Once you see him for yourself...
...you too will appreciate him.
Let's check it out.
"This is a bottle gourd!"
How much is the bottle gourd for?
- 9!
- 6!
I am saying that is costs 9!
Raja!
His brains are bust!
What a fantastic guy!
- A wasteful life!
- What happened?
I would have hanged myself
had this tie been a little longer.
You won't gain anything
if you feel sorry like this.
I feel like crying.
This time I will give you a great idea.
- What is it?
- Love!
That is a useless thing.
Enough of the depression that
he suffered due to the ideas you gave him.
I will give the idea now.
Uncle, this is not of the old generation.
This is the age of the new generation.
Be it old generation or the new one,
the ramp walk is still the same.
Who is the fool that
gave you the software idea?
Yeah! It is me of course.
Tell me once again!
What does it matter
if he is not a software engineer?
It seems that they have
4 to 5 shops in the market.
His daddy must surely be very rich.
He can start a software
company with that money.
And I can convince
my father easily.
Raja!
When you speak to girls,
only your honesty must be visible.
If you try to show something else,
there won't be a second meeting.
Oh!
What should I do now, daddy?
You should go
and meet that girl immediately.
Is he like some movie hero
to appear immediately before me?
- Where is chicken?
- Over here!
Hi girls... greetings!
- Raja sir.
- No!
- Raja.
- I'm coming.
- Excuse me, biryani.
- You want biryani.. Just a second.
I like this since childhood.
- Please take this and enjoy.
- Thanks.
Sambar.
I love social service.
- Here.
- Over there.
Look over there.
What is that?
Oh!
You too eat here?
Oh.. so you work over here.. Okay!
Hey, Sunny!
This is the dress my dad brought
from Singapore.
It is oversized for me. You wear it,
girls will fall over for you.
Hey!
Stop your recollection.
Every dialog that you
speak should impress the girl.
Okay, I'll handle it.
My heart has a liking for you.
And I like your heart too.
"This heart of mine."
"Don't melt it and leave."
What magic did you do, darling?
I didn't do any magic.
You are the one who
is imagining things.
Why don't you have
some more pieces?
They may charge extra for it.
This is an unlimited buffet...
you can eat as much as you want.
You are already fat..
eat in a limited way now.
When I look at you,
I get intoxicated as if drunk.
My eyes start to wink
and legs shudder.
I feel like I fell in love at last.
Your poetry is better than
that of the great poet Kalidas.
- I write poems... do you read poems?
- No!
He is acting over-smart.
I shall set him right.
- Ladyfingers 20 rupees a kilo!
- No... it is only 9... 9! 9!
This is not a market, Mr. Raja!
It is a restaurant.
It is indeed.
I'm always busy in making market software.
I do it as a hobby for my dad.
Actually,
the entire market belongs to us.
What is the name of
your software company?
Dull.. Dull Private Limited.
Where is it?
In high-tech city..
Very far from the city.
Where is it located in high-tech city?
Why is she asking so many questions?
Do you know the place called Silpa Ramam?
- Is it located there?
- Not there.
Do you know the KFC next to it?
I know that. Is it there?
Not there. Do you know
the Cream Stone next to it?
- I don't know that.
- That is exactly where it is located.
The ice cream there is very good.
Do you want to
order some ice cream?
You must be able to guess her taste
before she tells you. Go ahead!
I will have a blast.
Let me guess your taste.
Vanilla delight with
extra sauce and extra nuts.
Now let me guess yours.
Strawberry delight with
extra nuts and chocolate sauce?
Good for nothing!
How is my costume?
Doesn't it look great?
It looks fantastic.
Go and manage that fatso.
My work will become easier.
You go on. I will handle her.
I will tell it concisely
and accurately.
There is a flower and the bee.
Why does the bee go around the flower?
Let me ask one more thing.
There is a balloon and there is air.
Why does air go inside the balloon?
There is this plate
and there is your head.
What will happen
if I bash your head with this plate?
What would happen?
It seems that your friend is very busy.
Shall we go?
Okay!
Man, these are your car keys.
Bye!
Idea.
- What you should now do is--
- I got it.
If I remove the air from my bike tires,
I can go with her in her car.
Is that so? I understood it.
Hey, you have grown smart.
Go away and stop your comments.
Raja!
My car is not starting. If you don't
mind will you drop me on your bike?
One second!
Sir, she is your daughter.
Do you want me to stop the car?
Drive on!
Sir.
The kidnapper Basavayya is not revealing
the truth even after we bashed him.
Good morning, sir.
Sir, please don't do anything to me.
- Sit down.
- Please, sir.
Don't worry and sit down.
Laxman, bring me that file
- Tea?
- No need, sir.
- Would you prefer coffee?
- No, sir.
There is no link between
those kidnappings and me.
I stopped all such things
and am managing my business.
I too am thinking the same.
Sign here.
As you say, sir.
Sir.
Get one cup of milk.
Sir, please don't beat me.
You just signed on the paper confessing
that you did the kidnappings.
Now you want milk!
He is the only one
remaining in the list.
If he is kicked hard,
he will confess the truth.
Okay, I take your leave.
Sir, he is innocent.
There is no connection
between him and the kidnappings.
I know that.
I know how to connect
and correct things.
- Sir, What I mean is--
- Call for the press.
Okay.
Hey man..
Switch on the TV.
The new police commissioner is about to
speak about the kidnappings in the city.
The case of the kidnapping
of Bowenpalli CI Sharma...
...and in the case of the kidnapping
of the PA of Minister Govindaraj...
...we captured the main
kidnapper of those cases.
Now people will get
to hear about kidnappings...
...only in movies and in dictionaries.
People won’t see them in real life.
- Sir!
- What is it?
We got news that another
MLA Munuswamy has been kidnapped.
Why don't you speak loudly?
Sir, It seems that they kidnapped
MLA Munuswamy.
Oh God!
News we just received.
The city has been put on red alert
after the kidnapping of MLA Munuswamy.
Is the officer Dilip who solved
many kidnapping cases earlier...
...checkmated this time?
Had that kidnapper
kidnapped you and me...
...the torture from above
could have been avoided.
Sir, please listen to me.
The kidnappings which started with the
police are now targeting politicians.
Hey! Put the phone down.
Hey, release Basavayya.
I told him earlier that
this person is not the kidnapper.
But no one cared to listen to me.
What are you mumbling to yourself?
Come here.
Nothing, sir.
I was just saying that I mentioned
earlier that he is not the kidnapper.
In that case tell me about
the kidnappers and I will listen.
Sir, they are not
some ordinary kidnappers.
It seems that they are not
doing it for cash or such things.
There seems to be a police
point of view in their deeds.
What do you suggest that we do now?
Please give me a minute.
Dasanna, I have a dry throat.
Get me a cup of tea.
Sir, we should not think
like policeman for some time.
We must think like the
kidnappers do to catch them.
- Interesting!
- Thanks.
Sir I have a plan. Can I say it?
- First listen to my plan.
- Tell me, sir.
Take an auto from here
and go to RTC crossroads.
Eat a biryani in
hotel Bawarchi there...
...it seems that they are selling tickets
in black in the movie hall opposite to it.
Go and take care of them.
He wants tea!
Father, check!
What do you want it for?
To propose to someone?
She put her hand on me here.
- Is that so?
- Oh boy, do you have snake gourd?
I want some big sized ones.
- You want only big ones?
- Yes.
Get lost from here!
Just because she put her hand on you, do
you think that she's ready to marry you?
I'm not just thinking.
It is a fact!
When I put my hand on his shoulder
I got a positive reaction.
- She may have got used to it!
- What did you say?
If so many girls deserted him,
it means that...
...there is some
problem with the boy.
The must observe him closely
and do the correct analysis.
Do you suggest that
I should buy a good calculator?
I love you Geeta.
I love you so much.
Bye!
- Who are you talking to over the phone?
- Geeta!
- Who is she?
- My mother.
- Your mom?
- Yes, my mother.
Dad, I asked you for some idea
but you are watching a movie.
I think--
Every time that you are with that girl
I shall call you using the name Bujji.
- Okay.
- You should talk to me.
- Talk to you?!
- I mean you should talk to Bujji.
In a close and romantic manner.
If she feels jealous like the heroine of
the movie then you must use that reaction.
What should I do with that reaction?
Put up a romantic expression on your face.
- Who are you scaring?
- It is a romantic expression.
It feels like violence
and not romance.
Okay, one more important thing.
You must use all your experience.
But don't repeat any of those things.
- All the...
- Best!
Yes!
"Bad boys bad boys. Whatcha gonna do."
"Whatcha gonna do when they come for you?"
Bujji!
"Whatcha gonna do."
Oh! Is he his girlfriend?
Why is she calling so many times?
It seems that this plan might work out.
- It's very hot here.
- You got a phone call.
Must be some useless fellow.
Someone by the name Bujji.
Bujji called?! Oh my dear Bujji!
- I shall call her back.. hello!
- Who is this Bujji?
Oh God!
Don't you know who Bujji is?
Come on I will tell you.
"Once upon a time there was a girl."
"She became my friend unexpectedly."
"She has a slim waist
and is like a golden doll."
"She has got piercing looks."
"She dresses up well
and looks very cute."
"That is my dear Bujji."
"That is my cute Bujji."
"That is the Bujji of my heart."
"That is my little beauty Bujji."
Bujji! Bujji! Bujji!
Bujji!
I am not Bujji... It is his Bujji.
This is superb!
"She is like a clever bird."
"You may want to have some cool drink."
"Bujji is a lively young girl."
"She is like a cute little puppy."
"She is like a teddy
bear with soft cheeks."
"She is like a cute
baby saying cute words."
"She is the one that
I made friends with."
"She called me to meet in
the evening and I shall meet her."
"She is my cute Bujji."
"She is my Bujji
who drives me mad."
"She is the Bujji of my heart."
"She is my dear little Bujji."
"She is lovely like an angel
but her anger is real danger."
"She is short tempered and
speaks straight from the heart."
"She is a hummingbird who sings sweetly
and is also explosive like a bomb."
"She always wins whenever she fights
and has always the upper hand."
"She is my cute Bujji."
"She is the Bujji who drives me mad."
"Once upon a time there was a girl."
"She became my friend unexpectedly."
"She is my cute Bujji."
- "She is the Bujji who drives me mad'
- Bujji!."
Bujji! Bujji!
"She is the Bujji of my heart."
What happened?
My heart is burning.
- What is the reason?
- Bujji!
The heart is burning! It is not!
I don't understand this, dad.
Even if your heart is burning
stay calm like a cucumber.
In that case,
we should not stop with words.
We should do something more.
You go now.
They started a game.
Let us hit back now.
Bujji and victory shall
always be with you.
- Are you Bujji?
- My name is Masala Manga.
Hey!
Are you Bujji?
I am not Bujji.
This is the dress for Bujji.
You spoke about some surprise but are
asking for the prices of these clothes.
Bujji.
"She is my dear Bujji."
- "She is my cute Bujji."
- Bujji!
- Yeah!
- "My dear Bujji."
My Bujji!
- My dear.
- Bujji!
Enough of it. Don't over do it.
- Okay!
- Priya.
- She is my Bujji.
- Priya!
Hello!
We can exchange greetings later.
There is a discount sale going on.
- Let us go and clean up the shop.
- Let's do it.
This is what happens
when ladies go shopping.
Come on!
Please come!
Why do you address me like that.
See my dear,
how he is addressing me.
I am seeing her.
Damn it!
I am asking you to
see here and not there.
- Oh, you want me to see here!
- Please come!
- I shall--
- Please don't do that.
- Welcome, Madam!
- Lead the way.
My dear, is this fine?
- It looks great.
- Indeed!
- What about this?
- Superb!
- And this one?
- Great!
Madam, why don't you go to
the trial room and take a trial?
- What did you say?
- Why don't you take a trial?
- A trial?
- Yes!
You mean that after
I go into the trial room...
...you want to capture
my video secretly, you scoundrel!
Pack them!
After I go home, I shall try
them on in front of my dear one.
Are you shocked?
- I am shaken!
- One and the same.
Pack all of these too!
She is mad after shopping.
That is why she bought
the entire shop.
"Bad boys."
Phone call for me.
Tell me, father.
It seems that the drama
artist I arranged got fever.
She says that she cannot come.
Postpone your program
till tomorrow.
It means--
Our plan worked out. He thought
the man that we set up as Bujji.
I shall wait outside.
Pay the bill and come.
Hey! The bill!
- How much is it?
- Only 1,99,999.
- Did it cost that much?
- Yeah!
Is it a bill or the rent
for this building?
- It is the bill indeed.
- It is indeed dead cheap.
Yeah!
- Take this.
- Why did you give your identity card?
- What is written here?
- All cards are accepted.
That is why I gave that.
Hey! All cards does
not include identity cards.
Where are you escaping to?
You didn't buy even a single saree,
you cheap faced woman!
Make her work for days on end--
Never mind the load.
Don't spare her at all.
My dear!
Priya! Priya!
Forget about Bujji.
There is no other woman in my life.
None other than you.
As if I don't know.
Uncle! Uncle!
They beat me black
and blue in there.
Uncle, please give me a hundred.
I can't wear this dress and live.
Sister, please give me some money.
When your brother-in-law is there,
why do you ask me?
A hundred, brother-in-law.
Why just a hundred?
Take the entire purse.
- Go and enjoy!
- Uncle, you are great.
"The heart shines resplendently."
"The heart brims with joy."
"Like an unexpected
shower of jasmines."
"My heart got a new experience."
"Love has come to me
with pleasant greetings."
"My sweet dreams have come true."
"The heart shines resplendently."
"Like an unexpected
shower of jasmines."
THE MLA MUNUSWAMY
WHO WAS KIDNAPPED
Hey, who are you all?
How dare you play
with MLA Munuswamy?!
Choose one of these five fingers.
One, two, three, four, five.
Tell your people to
get 5 crore cash ready.
- Give me one more chance.
- Okay!
One, two, three, four, five.
- Tell them to ready five crores!
- Alas!
Hey, give me one last chance.
Tell them to keep
3 crores cash ready!
This is utter injustice.
Who are you guys?
Hey, don't do it!
It is more than 10 days that
MLA Munuswamy has been kidnapped.
People are surprised that the police
still doesn't have any clue in this case.
- Those people might harm him.
- The case of these kidnappings.
You must get him freed somehow.
Don't cry like that...
I can't bear it. Who is Munuswamy?
This throat pain is bothering me.
Who is Munuswamy?
He is like my younger brother.
He is my own brother.
Madam, I am giving you my word.
Your husband shall eat the
food you cook for dinner tonight.
This is my word.
- What happened to sir's voice?
- The matter is--
Some years ago a
policeman fired at him.
The bullet remained in his throat.
- If that is taken out.
- He may lose his voice or even his life.
- PA!
- I'm coming, Sir.
We must find the whereabouts of
Munuswamy anyhow by today evening.
I will take care of that.
Greetings.
"Just beat it!"
Hello!
We have put the three crores
in a bag as they said...
...and put it in the middle of the road.
We will recover the money
as soon as they release the MLA.
- How many of our guys are there?
- We have 10 men incognito.
We should not miss Mumuswamy
or the cash in the bag.
Okay, sir.
What are you looking at?
Nothing, brother.
As per my calculation it appears that
they are observing every move of ours.
How do you know that?
Das, we get a salary of 10 thousand
and make plans at our level.
The are doing kidnaps
and making away with crores.
How deep do you feel they shall think?
By the way,
how did they kidnap Munuswamy?
When some students were pinning
the national flag on his shirt...
...the pin pricked him.
The MLA could not bear that
and put his hand on his heart.
Everyone thought that he got a heart
attack and took him to the ambulance.
Only after it crossed some signals,
the truth dawned on everyone.
That he did not get a heart
attack but it was a planned move.
It looks like the
climax of a great movie.
If they took him in the
ambulance when they kidnapped...
...how will they bring
him at the time of his release?
The MLA is somewhere
in the vicinity.
Check all the vehicles
in the area without sparing any.
Come, let's go!
Hey, stop it.
- Come! Come!
- Hey!
Mental fellow!
What happened?
It seems that Munuswamy
is somewhere in the vicinity.
He's creating a scene unnecessarily.
Munuswamy!
Some madman is running away
with the cash bag into Indira Nagar.
Please come quickly.
Crap!
Come on quickly.
Stop, I said.
- That is a lot of money. Give it back!
- Money?!
Yes, give it back.
Why would I need any money?
- I'll throw it away.
- Don't throw it! Don't throw it!
I threw it away.. I threw it!
I threw it away!
Stop!
Get the entire area searched and...
...find out what happened to
that cash bag. I need a report.
- What happened?
- Sir!
- Hey!
- Don't run away with the money.
Can't you see, you bastards?
Are you blind?
Hey, stop!
Start it quickly!
- You wait, brother!
- Drive on quickly.
There are always two steps
ahead of us in everything.
The bullet missed by a whisker. Crap!
If you wish to consider,
I have a plan to catch them.
Wait... hold on one second.
- "Got to beat it!"
- This DGP is bothering me.
They are making calls every
moment and building the pressure.
You said that you want
to discuss some plan.
When the attacks happened in Mumbai on
26/11, since we manage to capture Kasab...
...the pressure on
the government eased.
The anger of the public shifted to Kasab.
If we have to capture the kidnappers
we must first reduce the pressure on us.
- What do you mean?
- I mean that...
...this time it will be us and
not they who will make the plan.
Let us get a big shot kidnapped
by an officer of Department.
After that we shall call
the press and say that...
...the same person did this kidnap
also and that we are investigating...
...and take two months time.
The person who is doing
this will attempt it again.
But while he attempts this
time our bullet will not miss him.
Since the bullet already hit him...
...he may stay quiet for some time.
These plans are good to hear but
getting permission is difficult.
It is called permission
if we ask for it.
If we do it without asking,
Then it becomes a mission.
The interval of Mahesh babu's movie
Pokiri was shot in this location.
Is that so?
They may have done that...
what do we care?
Hot groundnuts and tasty nuts!
Everyone is enjoying well.
Tasty nuts... fresh nuts.
Madam, instead of biting your nails,
please buy some nuts and eat.
There are doing match fixing for my
marriage at home without my consent...
...and you advise me
to eat these lousy nuts!
- I will break your teeth!
- Priya, calm down!
You go away.
You didn't tell me about the match
fixing but you told that to him.
What is the actual matter?
Hey girl, do you want
to say anything to my son?
Do you want to speak to the girl?
I wish to speak... tell me.
Stop shaking your head like that.
What do you mean
that you don't like him?
Are you in love with someone?
- That is what dad is asking.
- Hey, get lost.
Enough of the nodding.
Bring him home.
I know that you are there for me.
Please make my father
also realize that.
What does your father do?
He is the police commissioner.
- What did you say?
- He is the police commissioner.
'The basic things
that we need to live.'
'That's right...
Food, water and air.'
'Let's start with air.'
- How are you doing, my boy.
- I'm doing fine.
- Please take this.
- What is the need for all these?
You have come here
for the first time.
- This will be the last time also.
- Hey, Bunty!
What happens when
we start working out?
- Naughty boy!
- Which is farther, the Moon or Mumbai?
- Of course it is Mumbai!
- Is that so?
We can see the moon
but we cannot see Mumbai.
- Keshav.
- Oh God, daddy is here.
Bring those files here.
Hello, uncle.
- Tell me.
- Priya must have told you about me.
What do you do normally?
I mostly participate
in extracurricular activities.
What do you mean?
Like Ganpati festival, 10k Run,
party rallies and whatnot... all!
What do you do in you are free?
I do all these when I am free.
I'm very busy at other times.
I watch movies.
- Movies?!
- Only Hollywood films, uncle.
I mean the Telugu version is
released by the local distributor.
Deyyyala kota, Rakshasa bali...
movies like that.
I watched that movie 10 times.
You came to ask for my daughter even
after knowing that I am the commissioner?
Do you think I will backtrack hearing
that you are the commissioner's daughter?
Can't we fall in love
with commissioner's daughter?
Won't commissioner's
daughters have husbands?
"Beat it! Just beat it!"
Hello!
Tell that I will kill him.
If he disappoints me I will finish him
in an encounter like I did to his brother.
Would you prefer jam
or butter in your bread?
Butter!
Take these.
I never denied anything
to my daughter since childhood.
I like her a lot.
Me too.
So much that I can
even kill for her sake.
I like her so much that
I'm ready to die for her sake.
Raja! Raja!
Raja, what happened?
Did it fail?
See this, uncle?
I like your daughter a lot.
She likes you a lot.
So it means that you like me a lot.
That is why when
I was about to cut my finger...
...you thrust your hand in between.
"Beat it! Just beat it!"
You too are--
- A fan of Michael Jackson!
- Wow!
I like you.
I know that, uncle.
Hey!
Song, uncle!
"This love is a great thing."
"Love has burst open
from the heart, my love."
"This thrill has send
the mind in a tizzy."
"The world has turned upside down."
"This is a lucky
and lovely chance."
"I wish to perform
the Gangnam dance."
"Boom boom it's crazy time...
boom boom its cosy time."
"Boom boom hits jolly time...
One more time."
"Boom boom it's party time...
Boom boom it's freaking time."
"Boom boom it's jolly time...
One more time."
"I don't remember the alphabet and
numbers... I became like a toddler."
"I don't remember any ATM pin code.
My memory is gone."
"When I saw you I froze
like a statue and fell in love."
"You are like a high tension
wire who blew out my fuse."
"Boom boom it's crazy time...
Boom boom its party time."
"Boom boom it's jolly time...
One more time."
"Boom boom it's party time...
Boom boom its freaking time."
"Boom boom its jolly time...
One more time."
"I get the feeling of doing
scuba diving in a sea of perfume."
"I feel like having the rainbow
as wings and flying to the sky."
"I realize the thrill of
surfing on the waves of Moonlight."
"Oh girl, when you hug me."
"I feel that the thirst for
love inside me is being quenched."
"This is the coma of love."
"Love has burst out
from within the heart."
"This thrill has send
the mind in a tizzy."
"My mind has gone
spinning in a tizzy."
"Let us enjoy with one and all."
"I feel like dancing
the Gangnam style."
"Boom boom gets crazy time...
Boom boom its cosy time."
"Boom boom its jolly time...
one more time."
"Boom boom its party time...
Boom boom it's freaking time."
"Boom boom it's jolly time...
One more time."
"Boom boom."
- I told it.
- Rayudu!
- My name is Atama Rayudu.
- Whatever!
- Take this and put this in the car.
- Okay.
I am the great Atama Rayudu.
- Why don't you shave and go?
- I will do it in the evening.
The mind is very peaceful now.
I got very tense thinking that you will
get Priya married to that minister's son.
The boy who came here the day before
yesterday... you and I both like him.
Just wait a minute...
I will return shortly.
I performed the
worship as you said.
But the marriage will
happen as per my wish.
Go inside now.
Hey, tell Raja to come
to the farmhouse tomorrow.
Okay, sir.
Why did he call me to the
farmhouse early in the morning?
Will he make the plant some trees?
Hey Raja!
Lord Buddha advised
us to plant trees ages ago.
- I'm seeing that in action today.
- Yes.
You planted them well in a line.
- Give it to me, I will do it.
- No, Raja!
I participated in that when I was young.
Don't remember the name.
- What is that called?
- Janmabhoomi, sir.
That is the name, Janmabhoomi.
I was number one in that.
Hey!
This is the result
if you disappoint me!
This is the result.
Raja, Go and wait inside.
I will return shortly.
Your father asked me to
come to the farmhouse alone.
- Is that so?
- What do you think could be the reason?
Even if my father shouts, tell him
that you love me and won't leave me.
Don't be scared. I won't keep
quiet if anything happens to you.
- Do you expect something to happen to me?
- Bury that corpse!
I'm sharing my address with you.
If you don't get my call after
10 min, send in the ambulance.
If I am not found,
tell them to dig up the place.
My boy, you seem to have set aside
some important work to meet me.
I don't have anything more
important than you, father in law!
Father in law?!
When you address me like that
I feel the vibration all over my body.
Father in law!
You address me like that again!
I like you very much.
Smart, daring, dashing, intelligent!
I have no objection
to perform your marriage.
But there is a small problem.
Let us postpone the marriage
till that problem is solved.
What do you say?
Your problem is indeed my problem.
Don't say that. If Priya learns about it,
it will become a big problem.
If you don't tell that to me,
I swear by my life.
I'm telling you since
you ask me repeatedly.
You know that there are
kidnappings happening in the city.
I too don't understand that.
How is it that they can't be captured
when a strict officer like you is around?
Because I'm the one who is doing
all the kidnappings in the city.
Inspector Sharma, the MLA...
I am doing all that according to a plan.
Now it has reached the final stage.
If this plan is to succeed...
...we can easily catch
a big terrorist group.
What plan are you talking about?
It is--
Let us get a big-shot kidnapped
by an officer of our department.
The person who has done this earlier
will attempt it this time also.
But on this attempt,
our bullet will not miss him.
But we need a very
dependable person to do this.
We need someone very close.
Do you consider me an outsider,
father-in-law?
I'm there.
- You can't handle it.
- If it is okay with you...
...I'm ready this very moment.
I'm ready this moment.
Do we need to take
any permissions for this?
It is called permission
if we say before doing it.
If we do it without saying,
it becomes a mission.
I'm there... I'm there.
- You are there.
- I'm there that's all.
Sir, when you told him that we're
doing the kidnaps to catch terrorists...
...how did he believe it
without even sparing a thought?
One needs a brain to think.
I don't understand
your plan at all.
Did you hear the story
of one bullet two birds?
No!
When I learned that Raja
is in love with my daughter...
...I got so angry as to kill him.
But what can I do? My daughter
also fell in love with him.
And there is continuous torture from
above and below to catch the kidnappers.
You mean that you will make him do the
kidnapping, catch him in the act...
...and finish him before
you finish your cup of tea.
You are like a god, sir!
Do you think that
he might have overheard us?
I don't know, sir.
Father in law, a thought flashed
my mind as I crossed the gate.
What if someone else
catches me other than you?
Oh God, I can't do this.
Please find someone else for this.
Sorry!
Hey, call up my number.
"Beat it! Just beat it!"
Hello... cancel this mission.
Cancel the order that I gave
about the undercover officer.
Let my job be gone if it comes to that.
Father-in-law, let's do it!
Let's do it, sir!
Hope no more thoughts
will flash across your mind.
I don't sleep when
I'm on a mission!
How will I get any dreams?
- Raja!
- Yes, sir!
You must remember three
rules regarding this.
The first one is that the person
you shall kidnap must be a big shot.
The second one.
For one week after that you should
not get caught by anyone including me.
All one needs is 2 min
to catch this fool!
- The third one?
- You should not disappoint me.
This is what happens
if anyone disappoints me!
- This will be the result!
- Okay, sir.
From this moment your
name shall not be Raja.
Run Raja!
Run Raja?!
Run!
Tell me, brother. The engagement
will be on the ninth, isn't it?
Okay, brother.
Sacrificial lamb!
I noted, brother.
Hey Raja! Sorry, Run Raja!
- When are you starting your mission?
- I already did the kidnapping.
Is that so?
Superb! Who is the person?
Rather than choosing someone else,
I kidnapped the Commissioner's daughter.
Who can be a bigger shot
than the Commissioner's daughter?
Which Commissioner
are you talking about?
I kidnapped Priya since it is very easy.
Priya! No!
Hello! Seems like
the phone got discharged.
- Are you mad? Why did you kidnap me?
- Quiet!
I cannot tell you that.
It is a top-secret.
It is not wrong for us
to stay together before marriage.
I even took your
father's permission.
I never loved you.
Why do you say that?
My plan was to go off
to Australia after my exams.
But at the same time my father got
me engaged to the minister's son.
I just said off the hook
that I have a boyfriend.
If my father knows that I don't
have one, he is sure to kill me.
Hey, I have a super idea.
You must trap someone and
make him believe that you love him.
After that he will come
to convince your father.
Priya, what are you thinking about?
Wondering where I can
find such a sacrificial lamb!
His name is Raja.
He is the dumbest person in the world.
He ends up breaking with
his girlfriends in a trice.
- That is the matter.
- Yes!
She broke up with me
and is getting married.
We got our sacrificial lamb.
If you set him up,
he will set your father up.
It means that I must change my getup.
Drive fast!
3 2 1... hit him!
Chase him!
You would not get
hurt even if we broke up.
And it is not new to you.
So I acted as if I was in love with you.
You believed it as it is your habit
and became a sacrificial lamb.
Sacrificial lamb!
Yes.
I'm used to being a sacrificial lamb.
But not this time round.
- Hello! Father in law!
- Raja, tell me where my daughter is.
Your daughter disappointed me a lot.
But I won't disappoint you.
I know what will happen
if I disappoint you.
Do you remember, father-in-law?
My name is Raja.
Run Raja!
My legs are faster than wheels
and mind costlier than a diamond.
- Don't play with me!
- Forget catching me...
...it is a waste even to
think of catching me.
- Raja, I am telling you not to do it.
- Because you can't catch me.
Raja, don't do it!
This is a punch dialogue
used in most movies after a kidnap.
If kidnappers talk more than this,
the call will be traced.
You know it better.
On duty, this is Run Raja...
Reporting, Sir!
Raja, I am telling you not to do it.
Hey, stop!
Where are your pants?
They did not even give me the time
to wear them and brought me here.
What is the work for me here?
- Hello, Doctor!
- Hello!
Can't he see?
Hello!
Go there!
- Hello, sir. How are you?
- No!
- Not fine.
- Sir!
I am Dr Subramaniam.
FRCS... Returned from London.
I'm specialist in
public and private parts.
- Which part?
- Any part.
How did this happen?
Reporting, Sir!
I slipped and fell
down on the bathroom.
Why don't you take precaution even
after it is shown in many movies?
I will tell you a love story.
Doctor, why are you doing
entertainment instead of treatment?
Hey, come here.
Did you call me or your man?
He is calling you.
Come here.
This is the correct position.
That is very good, sir. Fantastic!
The tablet name is
'Tinnevaru Karyam Light Kuma'.
- What is that?
- 'Tinnevaru Karyam Light Kuma'.
Okay? Go and get it.
- Sir!
- You speak, doctor.
Once upon a time in
a place called Pithapuram...
...there used to be a powerful police
officer who suffered from neck pain.
He used to have a daughter
who drove him mad.
- Every house has the same problem.
- Well said!
There used to be a hero
who made her mad in love.
The father devised a special
plan to get them separated.
There used to be Chandramukhi Mahal
on the outskirts of the village.
They used to say in the village that
people who entered it never came out.
As per the plan, if the hero stayed
in that place for one week...
...the father committed to give
his daughter in marriage to him.
Our hero entered
the mansion as expected.
Since he won't have time
pass if he went alone...
...he took the police
officer’s daughter also inside.
- After going in--
- This seems like it is my story.
On learning about it the
police officer got startled.
Since he did not have the courage to go
inside, he managed to go in after a week.
Meanwhile another
man followed him...
...caught him from behind
and twisted his neck like this.
- Alas!
- Don't move! Don't move! Yeah!
It is very tender..
Don't move it till it becomes strong.
- What are you talking about?
- Your neck.
- Okay, see you.
- Doctor!
What happened next in the story?
Only recently my grandma
told me the story.
The hero raped the
heroine and killed her.
Doctor!
- You said that it is a love story.
- It is indeed one!
It is a romantic rape story.
Understood?
Go away!
What is that sound again?
Pizza, sir.
A pizza!
Take this hot pizza and eat it.
You will calm down.
Hey, who ordered for this?
Who is this quack of a doctor?
He doesn't know anything.
- Sir, bomb! In this box.
- Damn!
Take this...
Take it that side and check.
But sir.
I'm telling you to go.
Go that side and check.
- What is there in that?
- The pizza, sir.
- What did you say?
- I speak the truth. Come and see.
Let me see.
- A cellphone!
- What is this?!
Since I knew you would tap a cellphone,
I made this arrangement, father-in-law.
Sir, he is not a normal person.
Get lost!
- Hello, father in law!
- Hello!
- Hello father-in-law, over.
- You are finished!
Father-in-law, say 'over'
after you complete your message.
You are overdoing it.
You must say 'over' at the end
of the message and not during it.
- Over!
I said ‘over’!
You mean that your message is over!
Father-in-law, I heard that you
have a broken neck. Please take care.
I can do anything for the
happiness of my father-in-law.
I forgot to tell you that there is
a famous psychiatrist in our area.
Come here!
Sir?
This cannot cover
an area beyond 1 km range.
Don't spare the railway
station in the vicinity.
Search everywhere! Go now!
Where are you now, Raja?
- I am... I am.
- Yes!
I am right in your home!
- Hey!
- Over!
You are finished!
Father-in-law is done and so am I!
How dare you tell stories
that you are in my home?!
I love you!
Wait, my boy...
Take this lemon juice.
It is sweet like sugar.
You pamper me a lot.
- Drink some more of it.
- Drink, brother-in-law.
Brother-in-law?! Naughty boy!
Aunty... I take your leave. Bye!
Bye!
What are you doing?
These mosquitoes
are bothering us a lot!
Did it hurt badly?
Take this band aid.
Priya, wait! Go away if you like.
Go directly to your father and
tell him that your love is a drama.
He will call the Minister and tell him to
get ready for his son's marriage with you.
Only then will
your itch be reduced.
Who asked you to kidnap me?
It was your father.
Your father told
me to kidnap a big shot.
Rather than spending time with an
unknown big shot for an entire week...
...I thought it would be better to
make romance with a big shot I know.
After coming here I realized
that it is only violence.
If you stay with me you need
not disappoint me...
...and I won't disappoint your father.
I need to land a police job.
What do you say?
Okay.
Keshav, what is the update?
I assembled a team
as per your order.
Good!
If we put the city on high alert
we can trace Priya madam very quickly.
People will say that a man
who can't protect his daughter...
...how he will
be able to capture the kidnappers.
Search very silently
without anyone knowing it.
Okay, sir. Let's go!
I forgot to ask you.
Where are we spending this one week?
It is... Just a minute.
Hello!
- Where are you?
- First listen to what I say.
Take your tablets without fail.
And put some cash in my bank account.
- Bye!
Where are we going to stay?
I made all the
arrangements except wine.
Let's go in.
- Nice house!
- Feel free as if it were your house.
Come! Come!
This fatso leads a lavish life!
Oh... So much has happened.
"Twirl your mustache round."
"Wear Goggles like the boss."
"Mix lassi in coconut water."
"Make up your mood and come."
"Twirl your mustache round."
"Wear Goggles like the boss."
"Mix lassi in coconut water."
"Make up your mood and come."
- "All the Rajni fans!
- Great leader."
- "Don't miss the chance!
- Great leader!"
"Do the lungi dance!"
How is my performance?
Is there any other way to go out?
There are steps leading to
the terrace next to the kitchen.
Uncle, is it you?
What brings you so suddenly?
I came just like that.
The doctor gave me medicine
for my headache. But not cured.
My friends gave this
medicine which cured me.
When checking, people don't spare
even a square inch inside the house.
But they don't guess that...
...the house can have
a terrace where one can hide.
What happened, uncle?
My father is not a constable
but the commissioner.
He might even come to the terrace.
- See who has come!
- Uncle!
That is why we are hiding on
the terrace of the next building.
Hi Maggi!
Mosquitoes!
"Beat it! Just beat it!"
One sec!
"You better run,
you better do what you can."
"Don't wanna see no blood,
don't be a macho man."
Cut the call! Cut the call!
Sir, your phone.
"So beat it, but you wanna be bad."
Cut it!
- Hello... Tell me, sir.
- Dilip, what is happening?
I'm searching for some
clue regarding the kidnappers.
We will definitely catch him, sir.
Bye, sir.
Maggi, It is very cold outside.
Close the door and sleep.
Okay, uncle.
This police and thief play is thrilling.
Let's play everyday.
I don't like it at all.
I can't live in fear like this.
I have exams from
the day after tomorrow.
Who asked you to live in fear?
You will go to the dance class
and beauty parlor as usual.
You will go to the college
and take your exam also.
Hey, give it.
That is your hall ticket.
You are free as of now.
Can we try something?
There are mosquitoes here.
Light the coil so that she can study.
Okay!
Priya! Priya!
Where are you? Come out.
- Let me go.
- Come with me!
No!
How dare you take Priya?
Priya! What happened?
I got a feeling that
the minister's son came.
Does that stupid
man come to your dreams?
Don't feel tense and
prepare for the exam instead.
I'm not able to do it.
I'm not good with words.
But when I see you in a dull mood--
Shall we go out?
Why do you take the Ameerpet bus but
ask ticket for a different place?
You fool! Throw him out of the bus!
I never got into
a bus in my entire life.
And today you made
me to board a running bus.
The bus was running...
How did they get in?
Where do you want to go?
Where are we going now?
Where are we going?
I'm coming across more such idiots.
Tell me where you want to go
and I will give you the ticket.
No one knows where bus will go.
Don't know where it will stop.
But I know that the destination
will be a surprising location.
I decided to enjoy
that surprise tonight.
"Will you come along
as my companion."
"Will you extend your
hand of friendship."
"Will you see this world through my eyes."
"Will you set aside
your tensions and problems."
"Will you get ready to
enjoy the taste of happiness."
"Will you set yourself free
and enjoy the romantic moments."
"Shake your bridles away and welcome
to see the beauty of this world."
"Life is full of anxiety and tears."
"Even this moment can
slip away very quickly."
"You are the smile that
makes this moment precious."
"Live for the day."
"Laughter effuses from you and this world
is like a mirror reflecting your nature."
"The secret of happiness
is in your hands."
"Shake your bridles away and welcome
to see the beauty of this life."
"We are carefree and just
going where life takes us."
"You have seen the white
light and the dark shades."
"Come close to me and lets
enjoy this moment together."
"Shake your bridles away and welcome
to see the beauty of this life."
Hey, eat this.
I don't want it. Eat it and sleep.
- No, father.
- You must eat.
I don't feel hungry.
I don't know how many days you went
without food when I was not with you.
You must not do that
when I'm with you.
You must never go to
sleep on an empty stomach.
I'm there to feed you to your fill.
Eat well and sleep.
- Do you like it?
- Don't ever leave me and go.
Why would I do that? Eat now.
When someone used to ask me about
mother, I would show them her photo.
But when they asked
me about mothers love.
I used to show you to them.
Did you have any
fight with that girl?
Tell me what happened.
I like Priya very much.
Everything happens
for the good eventually.
It is very late, go to bed now.
- Hello, Commissioner!
- Hello, brother.
My son wants to speak your daughter.
Please send her across once.
- Someone kidnapped Priya.
- What kidnap?!
I mean that she went
for the college excursion.
The engagement is within a week and
you have sent her on an excursion!
She will return tomorrow.
- I wanted to tell you that.
- Okay.
- Remember that we have only one week.
- Okay, brother.
What happened, Sir?
People normally are happy
when they have a son.
But this mad son of
mine is driving me crazy.
- Papa!
- Here he comes!
You did not wish
me happy birthday today.
But you celebrated
your birthday last month.
Today is my birthday.
"Happy birthday to you."
Where is my gift?
- The gift.
- You forgot it again.
That is why I brought it myself.
- What is that?
- My gift!
- Where is it?
- There!
Greetings, Sir.
A policeman as a gift?! Who is he?
Why did you do that?
Just wait a minute!
Oh girl, come here.
- What is it now?
- Just wait.
- Come here.
- What is it?
Oh girl, did you tell him
that I slapped you on your behind?
Did you slapped my behind?
I didn't even know.
It seems she did not
even know that I did it.
Why are you beating me?
Did you inform him before beating?
Brother, is it okay?
You are my real brother.
That is what happened.
- Don't pull hard at my throat!
- Papa, do you love me?
- You spoke English?
- Yeah!
Shut up and put the phone down.
The chairman is acting over smart.
I will stab him!
Don't shout so loud.
My son is here.
The bald uncle is a bad man.
- Hey, what are you doing here?
- Are you doing fine, Sir?
Brother, he's the one who saved me.
He's a very sharp guy.
- He should be here always.
- The bullet in my throat!
- Okay?
- Okay!
- Papa, where is Priya?
- Priya... she is--
I caught you!
Come on! Quick!
The photo should go to all the police
stations in the State in 10 min.
Okay, come on. Send it fast.
Come on, quick! Send it fast.
The photo will go to all
stations in the next 5 min.
We will surely find him.
- Is that so?
- Yes!
Do one thing in that case.
- What is it, sir?
- Bring sweets for everyone.
Okay, sir.
I'm the one who is doing
the kidnappings in the city.
Inspector Sharma, the MLA..
I'm doing it all in a planned manner.
Hello, father-in-law. You always cut
the call before I complete my sentence.
The matter is that if you
try to target me or my people.
I will make an MMS of this video
and send it to all news channels.
I saw that in a movie.
I should take my precautions.
One more thing.
Run Raja reporting, Sir!
Stop it! Stop sending the photo!
Stop it immediately!
There are many systems, Sir.
It is very difficult to stop them all.
- Where is the main switch?
- It is on the outside.
Move aside. Make way for me!
Why is he behaving
in a strange manner?
- Hey, come here.
- What is it?
Do you think it is safe
for Priya to come to the temple?
It is not safe in the first place
to kidnap and keep her in the city.
Sir, what should I do
about the sweets? I understood!
Do you want us to search the homes
of all your daughter's friends?
Where did Mahesh babu and Aarti Agarwal
go when their parents opposed them?
They went to Jaipur.
Where did Pawan Kalyan
go in the movie Balu?
He went to Agra via Taj Mahal.
So forget the city and split the
team and send them all over India.
Since they will think like that...
...we will think differently
and keep her in the city.
Hey, if you both get
caught the girl will be safe.
But you will be finished
in an encounter. You want that?
Why should we worry
about what happens tomorrow?
She's happy at this moment.
I can do anything for that.
Why are you being emotional?
Let's go.
Hey, see front ways.
Hey!
"I came close to you even
though I did not intend to."
"I liked you as my life even
though I wanted to reject you."
"This is the real truth."
"This is what my heart says."
"My heart is anxious
to reach you with love."
"I was not aware of this turbulence
growing inside my heart."
"The love is my heart
swelled and flowed towards you."
"This heart is out of control
and does things on its own."
"It has liked you a lot and
has decided to reach you today."
"I became yours without
knowing it myself."
"I am floating in the
waves of joyous moonlight."
"I am in love, baby...
I am in love, baby."
"My lips blossomed like
a flower taking your name."
"There is something in
you that has taken over me."
"The world around me has changed."
"The steps I take in your
company make me float in joy."
"The more I know you and the more I
move with you, my love for you increases."
"I find solace in your shadow and have
a desire to spend my life with you."
"Shall I become your life
partner who shall never leave you."
Why didn't you get ready yet?
What is that?
The hall ticket?!
What about your higher
studies in Australia?
Raja won't be there.
"Beat it, just beat it!"
- Sir?
- Dilip, will you come home once?
Yes, sir.
What is the status
of the kidnappers case?
We got entire north India searched.
We send the force
now to South India.
We will catch Raja somehow.
Who is this Raja?
I refer to the kidnapper
who thinks he's the king.
- That's all!
- Sir!
Why is the minister calling all the time?
- Phone?
- I'm in a meeting. Go away now.
Some lady is on the line.
Sir, You have an offer
for a free SIM. Do you want it?
No!
Listen! Don't disturb me
even if the prime minister calls.
You will never get a call from him.
Sir, what if it is very urgent?
Oh God, sorry!
Tell them that I went into a coma.
Coma!
- Hello!
- Is father there?
He went into a coma.
- When?
- Just a second back.
I am collecting the proofs.
- Okay... okay.
- I take your leave.
Close the kidnap
case soon as possible.
Did you ever go into coma?
- No, I went to Goa.
- But sir went.
- When?
- Just a second back.
Hey baboon. I am talking to you.
Why are you going away?
Why are you laughing?
If you tell me I too will laugh.
They believed when I said
that you went into a coma.
- Who was that?
- It was your daughter Priya.
Give me the phone!
I am giving it, sir.
Hello... Priya!
Do one thing.
Come out of there immediately.
Take an auto and go to the nearest
police station and call me from there.
What is the need for us to
take an auto? We have a Nano car!
Don't worry about Priya.
She's eating biryani
and enjoying herself.
One more thing, father-in-law.
It was I who called with Priya's voice.
It seems that you went into a coma!
He is torturing me!
He always disappears
without informing.
Sir! Sir!
- Tell me.
- The engagement date is getting close.
Please inform the Minister
that the girl got kidnapped.
Why did you not inform
me even after all this happened?
You have so much power but
are unable to catch a small fish!
He's definitely not alone, sir.
Hello!
- Sir, phone call for you.
- For me?!
Yes, sir.
Hello!
Why did you switch off the phone?
The battery got low?
- He is the boy!
- Put the speaker on.
I had to make a call
to your stooge's phone!
Kidnappers always speak like this.
There are three stages
in a kidnap as you mentioned.
The first is to kidnap a big shot.
The second is to hide for
a week without getting caught.
And the third?
If you want your daughter back single,
get 5 crores cash ready.
Your daughter will
reach you even otherwise.
But not single but
with a family pack.
My name is Raja! Run Raja!
- Legs are faster than wheels!
- Mind is costlier than a diamond!
Forget catching me... even thinking
about that is a waste of time.
Because... he can't be caught!
Why can't he be caught?
He'll surely be caught!
Raja, till now you only
saw what a policeman can do.
Now you will see the
power of a politician.
You are superb!
That's fine...
how will you collect the money?
The kidnappings in the city.
I understood.
Let's go.
Brother, as you say.
Hey, get down.
- Get up and move.
- Cut it!
Are you saying that about me?
Not you, brother.
The entire money is here.
We just have to handover when he says.
We want both the
money and the girl.
Okay, brother.
He won't pay but will
always demand everything.
Get up.
Brother!
They all are our men.
No one can harm us.
Take the bag and
put it on the table in front of you.
Give me the pen.
He should add one more letter
and it means... 'dog'.
How dare he call me a dog?!
He calls me a dog?!
Let him say so. Where is the table?
Go and put it on the table.
I put the bag there.
Why did you put the bag?
Did someone come?
- "Oh God!"
- Hello!
Brother, I cannot hear you.
First check if the
bag is there or not.
Brother!
Actor Rajni is here!
He has come to take the bag.
What is this nonsense about Rajnikant?
He is the superstar who said that his
saying once is as good as a hundred times!
Did you get drunk early
in the morning, useless fellow?
Do you get the smell?
First check where the bag is.
- "Oh lord of Tirumala!"
- He is taking the bag away.
"Jumma! Jumma!"
It is not Rajnikant!
It is Amitabh Bachan!
Why would he come here?
"Give me a kiss!"
- "Give me a kiss!"
- Enough of the dancing... let's go.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
- Who is he behind the saree?
- Hey, come out.
I'm coming.
It is actor Brahmanandam.
- Babu Mohan is also here.
- Catch whoever is there.
- Bye!
Is this an airport to see them off?
Let's go.
What is the problem?
I need to go to the loo.
You drink so much beer
that your bladder is full! Idiot!
Why did Mumbai and
Delhi shift to Hyderabad?
Even Sonia madam has come.
The politicians all are
going for lunch, brother!
I will catch them before
they finish their lunch.
Catch at least one of them.
Now see what I'll do, brother.
Who are you, bastards? Are you
thieves who came to steal something?
I am getting bashed up.
Bro, the bag is over here.
We found the bag, boss.
- Bring it here.
- What do you think about our mettle?
- Brother!
- What?
We have been deceived thoroughly!
What?!
- Good morning, sir.
- Why did you call me urgently?
- Please come with me for 2 min.
- Good morning!
This is the voice of the kidnapper...
...who called when Inspector
Sharma was kidnapped.
One second, Sir.
Now please listen to this.
This is the voice
of Munuswamy's kidnapper
They both are the same. So what?
Brother, we found the cash.
Did you get it? I'm coming.
Now listen to this voice.
This is the voice that I recorded
when Raja called up my cell.
It is Raja who did
all the kidnappings.
Oh my God!
Super shot!
Rajni style it is!
This is how kidnappers speak.
You cannot catch me.
I must catch him somehow.
I must catch him.
Hello, uncle.
Is it true that you kidnapped
me for the sake of money?
What is it that you
showed me all these days?
I'm speaking to you, Raja.
- We found the girl.
- They found her it seems.
What is the delay? Make all
arrangements for the engagement.
Okay, I take your leave.
I did not rest even for
a second when I beat you.
But you still smile like a groom.
I should have got the doubt
when I couldn't catch you.
This is the pistol that
I use when doing encounters.
Tell me where you put
the cash before I count three.
- Three.
- I like your daughter a lot.
- She too likes me very much.
- Two.
But there is no resemblance
between you and her.
- One.
- You want to know about the money?
I retained it as dowry.
The only thing remaining is for you
to get your daughter married to me.
I will never disappoint
you as a son-in-law!
I will kill you!
I will give it right away.
Sir, the minister is on the line.
What happened, brother?
Tommy! Tommy!
Tommy!
What is Tommy's belt doing here?
Alas!
You are the next target,
Govinda Raju!
- What is that crap?
- Please don't tear it, brother.
I too got a similar letter.
It means that the next target is you!
Who is there behind him?
Sir, he is definitely not alone.
We must find out his
relation with the kidnappers.
Let us go about as per your plan.
If you kill him in an encounter
you will be a hero with the masses.
And your daughter will
consider him useless.
Father-in-law!
Let the Minister take precaution!
Sir, don't mind him.
Let the marriage happen first.
We will take care of him after that.
Sir, the plan that I gave now.
I hope it will help in my promotion!
We wanted to fix the marriage
towards the month end.
Send in the plumber.
There is no water in the house.
Priest, make it fast
without any delay.
Why did you put your hand
suddenly without calling me first?
He is already in the station...
why worry now?
Is it enough if he alone is captured?
You said that there
are many others in his team.
- It is better we take precautions.
- Hey!
Do it fast.
We came to fix the water tank.
- Where is the terrace?
- Take the stairs and go up there.
Please send them.
How long will it take?
It is almost done.
We just need to put the tank up.
Okay, do it fast.
- Sir! What is happening?
- Mukund!
- Sir!
What happened, Sir?
Sir! Sir!
We searched the entire
house but cannot find Mukund.
Nonsense!
Are you not ashamed to say that?
Mukund Is nowhere to be seen.
He has been kidnapped.
But he said that he will kidnap me.
Why did he do it to my son?
Who is he?
He said he'd target the minister, and
not that the minister would be kidnapped.
What is the use?
What are you doing?
Don't unnecessarily abuse us.
We're doing our duty!
Naeem, calm down.
Listen, put up check
posts all over the city.
Get all the hotels in the city and
the resorts on the outskirts checked.
Don't give any room
for their ideas to succeed.
- Go!
- Yes, sir.
Fast!
Take a left turn.
Why towards the left?
Our house is on the right.
Ramu, take a left turn.
- Priya, where are you going?
- Uncle!
Is it not enough that you
kidnapped me and took the money?
Why did you kidnap the minister's son?
How many more kidnaps will you do?
How many more will
you fleece and torture?
Priya! What do you know
for you to speak like that?
I will tell you many more
things that you don't know.
- Why reveal all that now?
- This is the right time to reveal that.
She must know about it.
You shouted and called
him a kidnapper.
Do you know that he
was once a police officer?
Your father and Prakash uncle
were good friends once upon a time.
- Please keep this.
- Don't do it... I don't want.
- Please keep it, sir.
- No... I don't want.
- I'm telling you I don't want it.
- Don't you understand?
- Please go and mind your business.
Whoever worked sincerely
in the station...
...Prakash uncle used
to treat them as his kin.
- Get out!
- Give the cash!
Take it!
At that time many kidnappings
happened in the city.
It became a bother
for the police force.
- Sir!
- Giri, what happened?
It seems that the
MLA was kidnapped.
The MLA Govindaraju was kidnapped.
Our leader must be freed!
Our leader Govindaraju
must be released!
We have been searching
in the city the past three days.
We will find him.
Why are you doing
duty on your birthday?
- There is no option!
- Happy birthday!
Thank you!
We brought the driver who was
present when the MLA was kidnapped.
Tell me the truth.
Tell me who kidnapped him.
I will tell you. The person
who kidnapped is none other than--
How can we give you...
It is government money.
What should we do then?
He should be freed somehow.
What is that man saying?
What is this meeting?
First our leaders should be freed.
Please sit down.
I'm talking to him.
Please request them somehow.
They wanted the money to be given
at the farmhouse outside the city.
Why do you say that you
want to go to the MLA guesthouse?
The one doing kidnaps
in the city is none other than...
It is MLA Govindaraju himself.
He's doing all this to stash the
money sanctioned by the government.
Bring the press and police along.
- And come to the MLA's house soon.
- Prakash, your gun.
Sir! SI Prakash is beating
our men and entering the house.
Keep quiet!
all of you wear your masks.
Police officer!
Please give the bag to them.
Otherwise these
people might kill me.
There are only files
in this bag and no money.
These are the proofs
for your criminal history.
These are the files pending
in the court for long.
It is better that politicians
like you should not live.
We can explain it away saying
that the kidnappers killed you.
That gun won't fire, Prakash.
Prakash, your gun!
Instead of doing
small-time kidnappings...
...it is I who advised him to kidnap
big-time politicians to get more money.
- Yeah!
- We managed the kidnaps.
But to escape from that we need
someone to own up doing the kidnappings.
You must confess that it
is you who did the kidnappings!
Traitor!
Khalid!
Hey! Hey!
Hey, capture and
take him from here.
- Khalid!
- Hey!
Hey, take him away quickly
- Khalid!
- Sharma, take this gun.
Shoot him!
My dear!
Khalid! Get up!
Happy birthday, Sir!
Khalid!
After crosschecking the
witnesses and evidences...
...the court has come to the
conclusion that Prakash is guilty...
...and the court sentences him to
14 years of rigorous imprisonment.
He was a sincere officer on duty.
But he was falsely
Implicated and imprisoned.
His son Raja could not
live alone without his father.
They made him an orphan.
I will bear the
Expenses to raise him.
Please take good care of Raja.
As you wish, Madam.
Take this, sir.
Sir, this chain belongs
to master Mukund.
Get 15 crores ready.
You take care of the Minister
and I will handle this one.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Sir.
- Yeah?
- You asked for the kidnappers sketch.
- Okay.
Sir, greetings.
- I brought the CCTV camera tapes.
- Load them.
Hey, wait.
Rewind it.
Play now!
Pause it!
Raja is here... who is it there then?
This is a pre-recorded tape.
Someone has put them in a loop.
He escaped long ago.
I stayed here without
even going to the loo.
- Did anyone come here?
- No one came, Sir.
I did not even go to the loo.
First go and relieve yourself!
Sir, Naeem came here
a little while ago.
We all went to have
some tea at that time.
Naeem was attending the minister's
son's engagement. How can he come here?
This is the picture of the
character in the movie Chatrapati.
Is some film shooting happening here?
- He is that character for sure!
- Hey, give.
He told a movie
story and cheated me.
I see a police point
of view in every step.
He is definitely not alone.
Find out who is on the phone.
- Don't give the money to Naeem.
- Okay.
Who was on the phone?
He wanted the money
to be brought immediately.
He will ask for the
money to be sent quickly.
The one who lost 15 crores
knows the pain.
Don't worry, brother.
We still have 500 crores up there.
Why should you reveal that to all?
Naeem, I spoke in haste.
Don't mind that.
- I won't mind, Sir.
- Oh police man.
I handed 15 crores cash
to you due to faith in you.
Get my son released quickly.
Don't worry, brother.
There is God above...
And our man here.
- We can trust them!
- Oh great lord.
It's gone for good!
- Greetings, Sir. What will you take?
- A cup of tea.
Make it two!
Come and sit.
Come here.
Super!
People may have changed...
But not the taste of tea!
The kidnaps happening in the city.
Ineffectiveness of the police!
Is this an ad?
Could you not find
some sacrificial lamb?
You are used to it.
You selected someone
to do the kidnaps.
He is none other than my own son.
Raja... Raja Harischandra Prasad!
You must be wondering what went wrong
when everything happened as per your plan.
It is actually
we who made the plan.
Hope you remember the plan.
We will get some big-shot kidnapped
by an officer of our department.
The person who told you the plan...
...Is the son of Khalid Pasha
whom you shot dead.
Naeem Pasha!
- I put the money here for my tea.
- Okay, sir.
I don't like being in debt.
Goodbye!
I was told to hand
you over this box.
You look very good on TV,
father-in-law.
I hope you will appreciate me
for shooting you so well. Run Raja!
The one responsible for the kidnaps
in the city is none other than...
...the Police Commissioner Dilip Kumar
who was appointed for the case.
Inspector Sharma, the MLA...
I'm doing all that as per plan.
Not just that. He killed
the people who knew the truth...
...and buried them
in his farmhouse.
The locals revealed that and it
made a strong case against him.
The police are exhuming
those dead bodies.
Please open the door!
Open the door, please.
Please stop it.
This is not a sin that will
be washed away by a single bullet.
You must get proper punishment.
Sir, the plumber has come.
Sorry for the delay.
But you already sent your assistant.
I don't have any assistant.
Who is the person who came
in the morning and went up?
- Papa!
- Ah!
What are you doing here?
You did not tell me about this.
It is all your plan, isn't it.
Earlier you got yourself
kidnapped and grabbed the money.
Now since your health is not well,
you wanted me to be kidnapped.
Who told you all this?
My brother Naeem told me all this.
What about the money
in the bathroom in that case?
Hey, there must be
a lot of money here.
But it is not there now.
As per the plan, all of this money
should be stored safely somewhere.
- That's why--
- The entire money?
- This is all!
- That's what happened, Papa.
Your son has done a great job.
Right, papa!
Why do you stand here
and watch the movie?
Go up and check the tank.
Papa... Check!
You idiot!
Sir, please answer the questions.
The person who supported
me in this is minister Govindaraju.
- And the MLA Munuswamy.
- Brother!
We are doomed. The Commissioner
has revealed our names also.
Sir, the 500 crores stashed
in the tank upstairs...
...it is entirely gone!
Brother!
Sir!
Why the delay? Start it!
Hey... wait Naeem!
If you hit with a stone,
the pain will be temporary.
But we should hit them in such
a way that the pain stays lifelong.
- We managed it well.
- Why not?
- Where is the tape?
- Does it hurt a lot?
Won't it hurt if you beat?
Who are you guys?
Some strangers donated
around 500 crores...
...to all the
orphanages in the city.
This is a superb thing. To find
such good Samaritans these days!
- Tell me.
- What I'm thinking is--
This Nano car is a bit cramped.
I'm asking you about the both of us.
One moment!
I--
- Shall we go to a movie?
- Which one?
A girl who wears a
lot of golden ornaments...
...and the boy who
claims he can be trusted...
...such people never
do well in life.
- What are you saying?
- What about you?
Bangaram... calm down.
She is Priya--
She might be your ex-girlfriend.
But would you address
her like that before me.
Her name is Bangaram.
- She's not my ex-girlfriend.
- No?
- Yes!
- Yes?!
I mean that I'm saying no.
Don't confuse me
and tell me clearly.
- Brother!
- Yes?
If I start here I can go to her father.
The girl looks good.
You must trap someone and make
him believe that you love him.
After that he will make
your father believe it.
Where can I find such
a sacrificial lamb now?
I must do a lot for her it seems.
My dear,
you must understand all this.
One second.
Bujji, I love you.
Hey, why do you take
the name of Bujji?!
- Why do you take her name again?
- Yes!
What about me?
"She is my dear little Bujji."
"She is my cute little Bujji."
"My Bujji Is the
darling of my heart."