ln pursuit of dreams,
l run even today
My desires remain far, far away
ln search ofdreams we run on and on
Do we see them?
Do we perceive?
ln pursuit of dreams,
l run even today
My desires remain far, far away
ln search ofdreams we run on and on
Do we see them?
Do we perceive?
ln pursuit of dreams,
l run even today
My desires remain far, far away
ln search of dreams we run on and on
Do we see them?
Do we perceive?
Christ's Grace
Jesus protects this house
Oh Lord!
Has she returned so quickly?
Chey!
Alleluia!
Good morning sir
Yes?
l am from Murdoch marketing company
with some products for the kitchen
- Look here
- Sir?
The only 'product' of my kitchen
has gone for her driving lessons
lfshe sees me here with you
l may as well join a meditation camp
You can go
- Sir?
- Aiyo! Sh...!
What is it, dear?
lchaya(hubby), Lucy speaking
5 minutes more and l am done
What are you up to?
l...er...am watching
Shalom (Christian) channel on TV
By the way, l'll be back after
shopping at the supermarket
Jesus! Does that mean
you'll be here only after 2 hours?
-Yes, lchaya
- Chey!
Listen! Wait till l return
before you go out, okay?
Come quickly, okay?
- Heard me?
- Okay, lchaya
- So, you are from home appliances, eh?
-Yes sir
Well, come in
Let me have a look
- Sir, casserole?
- No
Sir, ifyou are really interested
l have a small side business too
CDs ofsome new movies
Only Rs 100
- ls that so?
-Yes
Where? Let me see
Sir, are you a businessman?
No, in the police force
Deputy Superintendent of Police
Benny Tharakan
Selling pirated movie CDs
is your business, eh?
Sir?!
Be quiet! So convenient
coming in with evidence, like this
Non-bailable offence, understood?
Please don't betray me, sir
l desperately need the money
Please sir
l'll do anything you ask me to
Do have only movie CDs?
lsn't there any other kind?
Other kind?
Don't you have adult movies?
Yes or no?
Take it out
Wait here
Let me find out first
whetherto send you off or not
Aiyo! lsn't that me?
Christ! lt's me!
You!!!
Reporter, Bharath vision
Jesus!
My dear sister,
don't get me into trouble
l've just got back into service
After 2 suspensions and 2 meditations
Please, l'll do
what ever you want me to
Sir, answerthat call
Must be from the Tv channel
Hello?
venu, that's my name
A well known camera man
ofa well known TV channel
l know you, sir
l've met you
- So, further introductions not needed
- Not at all
lf prime time
news today decides to air...
...your antics with that chick
what will be your opinion?
Aiyo! l no longer will exist
Tell me sir, what should l do?
Rs 3 lakhs, in notes of 1000
Send it with that girl
Okay, sir
Okay
Why has no one taken this?
We don't want any lOUs, sir
Just give us our salary
This is not an lOU
Just a security
Look, only 2 minutes left
Go and begin the news telecast
By then the money will be here
Money that's not come since 4 months
do you think will come in half an hour?
On its way
Then l'll read the news
after it arrives
Or you do it yourself, after all
you were a lion in Bharath vision, right?
Yes dude, l was indeed, a lion
When l started my own channel
l became a cat
Okay, don't read, you pig
l'll do it, give me that coat
No need to remove the coat
l got the money
Here, Rs 3 lakhs
Did you see how we got the money?
Here's Rs 3 lakhs, take your dues
lf anything's left, leave it there itself
Bro, l have to go read news
Please keep my 40 aside
Brother, where's mine?
A Bharath vision lD card?
Are you back with that channel?
l went for an 'operation', dear
My old card came of use, that's all
Stop your chatter
Come with me
Were you going to explain
all that happened, to them?
You can as well air it on news time!
Let everybody here be aware!
Great! Remember the way
you followed ethics so strictly?
When it didn't work, you quit
Bharath vision to start a new channel
As the head, you are resorting
to 3rd rate tactics, to pay the salaries...
...and that too mimicking
a decent guy, like venu sir
Go and tell venu everything!
You can get married to my dead body
He'll kill me!
l've not made it a habit, right?
This was only the first time
Sir?
What is it?
Minister Kunjumoideen will land at 1:00 PM
None of us will be there to coverthe event
Select some good channel
and just reproduce their content
lsn't that what we do every time!
Hey! Also include an 'it seems'
in every other sentence
What's that sir?
Like...the Minister is involved in
the sex racket case 'it seems'
Or...there is a chance
he'll resign 'it seems'
Like this, we include 'it seems'
in all matters, we are not sure of
Understood?
-Yes, now l do
- Then go
What a big media staryou were
Rs 1.5 lakh salary and...
...post of chief operating officer
What went wrong at Bharath vision?
Conceit! l have only myselfto blame
A kind ofsmugness, dying to be pricked!
Oh Lord!
lt's venu!
Would he have somehow
come to know what l did?
Aiyo! Would Benny Tharakan
have talked to him, about it?
Will the Town Hall
be free tomorrow?
Why?
To keep my dead body
for public viewing
Hello?
What's up dude?
ls it?
He doesn't know!
Aren't you ashamed
to go cover a silly 'lathi charge'?
Oh, you call itjust time pass, eh?
Definitely not! You are itching for kudos!
Returning from Delhi after 5 years
just a cheap trick to say you are back
Ow!
He's swearing!!
He can't be idle even for a day
without taking up some work
Probably needs the money
He?
The money he earns for
each assignment of Reuters and CNN...
...no camera man would get
even after 3 or4 years oftoil
When sensitive issues crop up
channels in Delhi bid for his services
4 lnternational awards
including the Rory Peck Award
This is not for money
Just to show off, that's all!
Forwhich channel could it be?
Certainly not, for Bharath vision
Look here Suraj
Renuka Ma'am has come
lfyou confront her,
you'll need to look out for anotherjob
Her attitude is
'Just take a leap ifyou cannot'
l will take it up, not with her
but with CEO vijayakumar sir
She separated me and my wife allotting
different shifts without a word to us
My shift is from 6:00 AM to 6:00 PM
and hers, from 6:00 PM to 6:00 AM
l have been gazing at stars
the whole of last month
- Be quiet, dude
- Get lost, buddy
When she joined as junior reporter
l was already here, as sub-editor
Now she claims
to be executive editor!
Arun, come here
On the run down, first item should be
Minister Kunjumoideen and sex racket
The women's activist Sharada
and the retired old DySP Ramarajan
l want both ofthem on phone
connected to me, right time
lfyou come up with stories like unable
to connect, and so on, l'll blast you!
- Revathi?
- Ma'am
Greetings, l am Renuka
The news, headlines
Minister Kunjumoideen has also been
implicated in Vadakara sex racket case...
...says retired DySP Ramarajan
ln Kuttikanam adivasi zone,
Land mafia faked 420 documents
The news in detail
Minister Kunjumoideen's part in the case
is now a topic ofcontroversy
The girl who'd been harassed had named
the minister too in her original statement
This claim by DySP Ramarajan, the officer
who was investigating the case then...
...has sparked off
these fresh controversies
Arun, didn't you get connection?
l am trying, but not getting through
You'll get it from me
ifyou don't get it, right now
Get lost from here
ifyou can't, dude!
The ministerwho was in Delhi
since the last 4 days, will be here...
...in Nedumbashery airport
by afternoon...is the latest report
Sir may l?
Yes
What's it, dude?
l have a complaint
You oryourwife?
So this game was
with your approval, eh?
Dude, l'll know even
if a leaf moves in this place
Sir, it's been a month
since anything moved at all!
Sorry, she takes the decisions
She can, but she'll have
to bear my mother's curse
What's your mother's role in this?
Motherwants to die, only after
she sees her grand child
That's being greedy, isn't it?
Didn't she get to see you, as a baby?
- Look here sir
- lfyou want to change shifts, go ask her
ls she Goddess of Chottanikkara
to bow and beg favors from?
Go and ask her directly, useless!
Why use me to test
your sharp tongue?
- Sir, can you help?
- No!
Oh, there she is!
The she-devil!
We don't pay a salary for
couples to coochy-coo during work
There's no question
ofchanging the shift time
May be, on humanitarian
considerations...?
l don't see such considerations
when you force TAM rating on me
Do you think l am a machine?
l've lost out an entire life!
Don't forget that!
Hello?
ls it?
Did you see?
No, l will come
Sir
The minister is in the guest house,
women activists and party members too
We can expect something hot
You take overthe news, l'll come 'live'
Did you see that enthusiasm?
Focus channel got venu to shoot for them
You mean Reuter's venu?
Here?
He's come from Delhi and is here
since a week, to testify on some old case
Must have accepted this job
having free time on his hands
Oh Lord! ln today's lathi charge
once, just one beating...
...may this queen ofJhansi
receive on her head, please God!
- What's it, dude?
- Nothing, sir
- Preetha, did you see venu sir?
- ls Reuters venu covering this?
- Why is he here, for this lifeless story?
- Ourvice President requested him, come
Where the heck is this man?!
Must be hanging around somewhere
The Ministerwill soon be here
Nothing will happen
till l get out of here
We cannot be too sure, sir
Your own party members
will stir up problems
That's also part of politics
Creating and solving problems
You guys need your guns and lathis
l need to use my tongue, just watch
Don't get excited
Stop your slogans
Stop!
Stop, l say
Don't you understand?
l have only respect
forthe women folk ofthis land
Listen to what l have to say...
...afterwhich you can shout
dissent or block my way! Please!
Please...please...please!
Okay, stop
Let him say his piece
Don't bother asking me
l will tell you everything
All this hullaballoo is simply because of
the statement ofa retd DySP, 6 years later
Let the police investigate
l am prepared to co operate
Do you want me to step down
during the period of investigation?
Let my party or chief minister demand
l am prepared for that also
To counter a false accusation
What more should l do?
How is it?
Enough?
Mohammed, what is
the schedule for this evening?
Renu, don't try to barge in
He subdued everyone with just 4 sentences
Don't think you can play around
with this news, the whole day today
Chey! l came because l heard
venu was covering this for Focus TV
You can expect
fireworks when he's around
Move aside all ofyou
Move!
See you later
Move
Come on finish off
all these sons of guns!!!
Charge!
Get lost you!
Start the car
See that shoe
and that bare foot
- Shoot both, dude!
- Okay
Da!
You are totally useless
Get lost, you...!
Sorry, ma'am
venu sir?
There won't be any more
further issues, will there?
What?
l mean the other one?
Did he see me throwing my shoe?
Well, if he did, let him!
- Here, go and serve it
- Thank you, sir
Talking diplomatically and calmly
the event passed off uneventfully
But someone threw a shoe at him
and party members turned violent
Chey! Who could it be?
Did you see the rhythm
in those shots?
Oh!
One second, turning on a single leg
a180degree pan, a shot with amazing impact!
Wouldn't you have got it
using both legs for 2 seconds?
Sure you will
But it can be shown only in your cheap,
crappy, sub standard channel
All good channels
will cut them, edit them
Whatever l shoot, will not
give them a chance to edit
- Oh! Forsure
- Look there, my boy
Chey! They chopped
the scenes, those vagabonds!
Smart boys don't
need an excuse to edit
Yes, venu here
l came, created an issue
and shot those scenes foryou
Now, using my footage, you are
teaching your boys editing, eh?
Rascals! With no sense
about rules of continuity!
What? Sorry?
You can stuffyour sorry
under your leg...arms...
...l'll take it when l need it!
What is it, dude?
Giggling away to glory,eh?
Twin screen play writers
What the heck do you know?
venu, they are my friends
They have 5 super hit films to their credit
They've come here for my sake
To discuss a program for my NBl Channel
lfyou have anything to say
direct it at me, not them
l will tell this not only
to you, but to them also
l didn'tjump up from the middle
of my dinner, to wield a camera
As a gold medalist from film institute
l refused to step into the film world...why?
My ambition was to shoot visuals
that were authentic, not manipulated
Understood?
Humph!
Cinema my foot!
Looks like, a gas bag
sprouted hands and legs!
Like army stories narrated by
tea shop owners with big moustaches
Sure! Army stories indeed
Kargil war! Who covered it
forthe Defense Ministry?
Him
The terrorist attack
at the Taj hotel, Mumbai
Who covered the commando
operation for CNN channel?
Was it Azhagappan?
Not azhag-appan
Your appan (dad)!
very good
Oh, it was you, sir?
ls he in?
Sure, come in
venu, look who's here
Hey, Somarajan sir?
When l called
Rishi said you were here
Don't worry, l won't
stay for long and trouble you
So my perjury,
led to something good
Yes, l got the fax today
My lPS is confirmed
lt was only foryou
l've surfaced here after 5 years
Just to change
my earlier statement
Thanks
Thank you
When l packed up and left
l swore l wouldn't return
But my return has resulted
in something good!
Don't you know him?
Superintendent of Police
Somarajan sir ofSpecial branch
- Was suspended for a brief period
- Along with a criminal case
He was the defendant
and l was the petitioner
News continues
Head lines
Minister Kunjumoideen is also
implicated in Vadakara sex racket case...
...says retired DySP Ramarajan
ln Kuttikanam Adivasi zone
Land mafia fakes 420 documents
The news in detail
Did the vehicle, for a second
slip into reverse gear?
This vehicle does not have a reverse gear
lt can only take an U-turn, ifyou want
venu
Come on, take an U-turn
Anyway these guys
don't know anything
What ifthere's scope for a story?
- Should l?
- Go ahead
Sir
Please, sir
About 5 years ago...
After nearly 7 days offasting
and in very poor health conditions...
...social activist and poetess Radhadevi
has been arrested and admitted in hospital
Demanding immediate solution
to the Chambakara issue...
...Radhadevi announced solidarity with
the citizens protest and started herfast
venu sir has come!
Did you get it, sir?
The police refuse to allow us in
Here's the Commissioner's permission
lfshe's conscious after an hour
and cooperates, take her interview also
- Let's go to the casualty
- Me?
You want me to shoot
this lifeless interview?
Tojust focus on her mug
watch it and die of boredom?
Get lost, dude!
Go do it yourself
Sir, the permission
is in your name, Reuters venu
lfyou are not there
the police will block our entry
You can go after it begins
You are just harassing me
Come!
lmpossible!
lt's not for an interview
We must tell the public about her condition
Didn't l tell you
that you can't meet her?
Why not?
Not possible, that's all
Let me see if l can
Who is this fiery maiden?
Renuka, junior reporter of Bharath vision
A beginner's enthusiasm
- l must see how you will
- Let me go
You useless, behaving atrociously, eh?
You...!
Hey, that was great
You arrogant girl!
You! You dare lay
hands on a policewoman
You fool! Aren't lady-police
assigned to deal with women?
Why do you interfere?
Throw him into the police van, the dog
You dare to lay hands
on media persons, you pig?!
Let me go
Kill him, this son ofa gun
- That's venu sir
-You mean, Reuters venu?
Sir
And then?
What?
You saw DySP Somarajan
pushing away the reporter Renuka
And then?
very calmly and
full of respect, l asked him
Sir, is it right to do such things
to a girl, that too, to a media person
He said who are you
to ask me such...come here
And gave me a slap
And a kick here...here on my chest
l don't remember anything else
Note it down
The certificate is ready
You go and take that
How are you?
Are you in pain?
Sure, l'm covered by insurance
He asked, if you are in pain
- What?
- Pain
Pain, yes it is paining
This thing blocks and l'm unable to hear
Removing that is not going to help
He'll never be able to hear again
l hope there is nothing
seriously wrong, doctor
Ear drum is totally damaged
He'll have to use a hearing aid
Explain it to him gently
Okay?
Look here, just take it easy
What?
Don't get agitated
You'll be a little upset on hearing this
But how can l tell you this,
in any otherway...?
Doctorjust said...
What's this, dude?
Like some melodrama in cinema
With broken words, it is cancer
lts blood cancer, brother...
Tell me whatever it is
you dumb fellow!
l'm not dumb
You are the one now, deaf
Your ear is gone forever, dude
Hereafter, we must fix that thingy
A hearing aid, that's what l meant
So, this is a goner!
Once, the artist van Gogh
chopped his ear off, for his lady love
My dear girl, l'vejust lost it for you
without love or any such moonshine
Be grateful, okay?
Gratitude
- That thing which you said...
- Gratitude?
No, this love
lt can happen even now and
everything will fall in place
- Will that happen?
- lt's already too late
- Then go get a taxi
- Okay
Get lost, dude and
stop weaving stories
venu!
My God! You should have
seen them after that incident
lt wasn't love,
theyjust took off on a high!
l, was the reason for that love to begin
Since l am not there in the rest ofthe story
l'll say, okay good night
Good night
And then?
And then...
Where were you?
The press meet is about
to begin, l'll call you back
Hey, it's urgent
lt's an exclusive
Needs to be
shot immediately
What is it about?
l'll explain
Come quickly
l am waiting outside
Monacha, l've got
an exclusive, l'm leaving
Shouldn't l come
to cover the event?
This is being covered by venu sir
Reuters venu, accompanied by, Renuka
Come, get in
- What is so exclusive?
- l'll tell you everything
Which is this place?
Guest house of Kelvin Joseph
He is the guy who is
funding Rishi's new channel
Didn't you say
we have something exclusive?
Yes, there is no one else here
Only 2 of us, exclusive literally, come
- Come on, l say
-venu
Let me go
Come
What are your intentions?
Dishonorable ones, of course!
Sure! Go climb a wall!
Oh! That!
No! Please no...not before marriage
lsn't that what you mean?
Well, l have no such inclinations
Then?
Why that disappointed
expression, when l said that?
Aiyada! Disappointment!
Do you know to cook?
- Sure, to an extent
- Okay
- Where's the kitchen?
- Over there
What do you prefer?
Tea or coffee?
Before that, by the way
have you heard my song?
Song?
Music track, karaoke
ln our future lives, very frequently
we have to face 2 gigantic issues
Your cooking and my music!
Let's begin our interaction
from that point
As rays ofthe fading evening sun,
lay sprawled on the shores unrestrained
Swinging your little tender arms, dear
on a little boat you rowed, my baby dear
Tear drops neverfell but brimmed
Eyes that glistened with tears unshed
Memories, like a wick of lamp burning
not feeling the heat of the flame brightening
oh, why did you leave me and go
My sweet little chirpy red sparrow
l wait on these shores foryou on and on
My desires like roots spread far and yon
As rays ofthe fading evening sun,
lay sprawled on the shores unshackled
Swinging yourtender little arms, dear
in a boat you rowed away, my baby dear
As the wheels oftime and age
Turned around on earth's heritage
As flowering trees and young Laurel
grew and changed beyond recall
As before my eyes this little stream
faded out of sight, never to be seen
l turned into a golden sand boat
that didn't have water to go afloat
As rays ofthe fading evening sun,
lay sprawled on the shores uncontrolled
Swinging yourtender little arms, dear
in a boatyou rowed away, my baby dear
Adorned in anklets on feet so pretty
Bangles aplenty on hands so dainty
A garland, you once gave me
with blossoms of Mimusop's Elengi
Festivities, dance ofwarfares
Long over are the temple fairs
A sentinel l stand in a temple forsaken
Like a burnt out black stone lamp alone
As rays ofthe fading evening sun,
lay sprawled on the shores unrestrained
Swinging yourtender little arms, dear
in a boat you rowed away, my baby dear
As rays offading evening sun,
sprawled upon the shores unrestrained
Swinging yourtender little arms, dear
in a boatyou rowed away, my baby dear
As rays of fading evening sun,
lay sprawled upon the shores unrestrained
Swinging your tender little arms, dear
in a boat you rowed away, my baby dear
Go climb the wall!
Cruel fellow!
And then?
Why mood off, sir?
A kind of sadness?
He's sad that
he can't have a baby
Haven't you heard?
Sorrow of being childless
What do the doctors say?
No use!
No use at all!
How can a baby be born
when we didn't have a chance?
Cruel she-devil
Witch, hellcat!
Cheater!
Da! You don't say anything
l will, she cheated me also
l will tell you, the rest ofthe story
lt was when, l quit Bharath vision
and started my own channel, the NBl
lt was 2 or 3 days
before its launch
The day before these lovers
tired after love making...
...decided to get married
at the registry office
Well known NRl businessman
and Malayalee Rajan Kartha nominated...
...as Rajya Sabha memberfrom Kerala as
decided by Democratic party central powers
State party president and possibly future
Chief Minister, Bharathan Pillai...
...overcoming objections
ofother parties in Kerala...
...vouched for Rajan Kartha's nomination
When Kerala does not have
a single candidate or MP...
Rishi, this is a good omen
Which one?
Our channel is taking off, at a time
when the situation is heating up with news
Our channel won't have
any dearth for news
That's true, but actually it's not
the way you think it is, Jose'aettan
From today, all channels will focus on
Rajan Kartha and Bharathan Pillai
But we will wake up in 2 days with
an exclusive story that'll divert viewers
All other channels are baffled
What's the story?
4 exclusive stories are ready
We'll just decide what to air
We have 2 more days, right?
There is 1 which could be
most exclusive, we can't ignore that
venu!
Ah! Has the bridegroom arrived?
Don't you know him?
venu
Who doesn't?
- Kelvin Joseph's partner
- l know him
Don't splurge all your money on him
although he may convince you
Come
We are getting married tomorrow
But not inviting you,
it's a registered marriage
Rishi did mention it, congrats!
Thanks
Give it to me
Dude, it's only a signature tomorrow
Don't take way Renu, for another month
She is my sub-editor
Come down to earth dude, just beginning
and thinks he's already a channel bigwig
Go, go
Dad wanted a proper wedding
Find someone else then, to stand
well decorated and smiling...shall we?
l just mentioned dad's wish
Let's find someone for dad then
Will your mom allow it?
God! What a thorny tree
Am l a thorny tree?
Am l not a flower, hmmm?
Hey! Can't you wait till tomorrow?
l've reached limits
of my patience, dude!
Rishi come here,
l'm reiterating what l've always said
l'm not investing, to strut around like
a channel owner, it's only for business
l have no allegiance to
any particular religion or party
Ratings, commercial
value of news, that's all
Also, l'm giving you
the freedom you've always wanted
Correct! Even otherwise
who are we indebted to?
A man comes home, freshens up
waits for his kids to sleep, views Tv...
...for 2 hours, the programs and news
forwhich we have toiled and sweated
Ask him to get lost, l say!
Sheer attitude problem
Let's see you like this always, okay?
Sure, if this attitude shifts...
...l swear l'll work for you,
for your channel, for what you pay!
Renu, its Manilal here
A shocking exclusive!
l got this information, just now
Okay, Mani
venu, something important, come
Rishi! Can your channel
go on air today, tonight?
We are on to an exclusive
which nobody may get
Yes or no?
Yes ofcourse!
Listen, we are going on air
tonight itself, get everything set
The promos have to start
by today evening, 6:00 PM
NBl will be launched tonight at 10:00
with news, that's going to shock Kerala
Promos have to start
on internet and FM Radio
Rishi, seeing the promos,
people will wait for the shocking news...
...but what if the info is wrong?
We already have 4 other stories
that will shock, we'll start with any ofthem
Forward this now itself to play up
Okay
What is that?
5m, waterproof USB wire camera
Usually used in surgical procedures
lt will enter any body organ
or even the intestines, to shoot
But why, for our purpose?
62 degree wide vision view
Av details will be, clear
as crystal, high resolution
Have you prepared
your introduction lines?
Let's shoot it here
in the vehicle itself
Do we have to?
lt must be your face before the visuals
You won't get any benefit otherwise
Okay
Ready, rolling
ln lndia, people worm into political and
law making infrastructures ofthis country...
...out ofsheer power of money, one such
shocking scene, we invite you to witness
Candidate for Rajya Sabha, Rajan Kartha and
Bharatha pillai Democratic party president...
...caught in the act with crores
of money changing hands, watch it!
l hope we get to see all
what was just said
- Camera
- Sir
Here, take it
- Pan rights
- Okay, sir
- Okay sir?
- Okay, fine
Sir, this has come back after repair
Where shall we put it?
lt was taken from the office room
Keep it back there
Why does he still have this old fridge?
Can't he buy a new one?
That's our Bharathan Pillai sir
Such humility and modesty
varghese, l am feeling very tired
Shall we meet tomorrow?
Okay, sir
Okay, leader
Okay, we are leaving
Okay, everything
as we'd already planned
He is Kartha sir
Come, come
- Greetings
-varghese, don't allow anyone in
- Okay sir
l didn't have much hope
till the decision was made
Party members
protested so vehemently
They raise a hue and cry
only here, none of it reaches Delhi
lsn't that why l extended
my hand, when you asked?
Now, where is that stuff
which must reach my hand?
Oh that, yes!
That is ready
True, it's the key to your fridge
l took it by telling varghese,
it needed repair
The entire amount
you've asked is here, count it
This will cover only
the Rajya sabha seat
The crown of a central minister
is on its way, don't forget that
l shall continue remembering it
like this, all the time, isn't that enough?
Sure
Sir is returning
Get the camera
Renu, take it
Come
Where?
What is it?
Sign off, it should be with
Pillai's house as a back drop
This is Renuka, with cameraman Venu
from Bharathan Pillai's residence
Come
Police!
Don't drive off immediately!
Go straight ahead, there is
a roundabout, take a right and ask there
Now take off!
Hey! Come here
Who are you?
Why are you
prowling around here?
Nothing
Who was in that vehicle?
They asked for directions
and l told them
Hello?
Chief lnspector, Anthony
What is it?
You wanted to see me?
l am right in front ofyour house
We've caught a man
who looks suspicious
Looks like a journalist
What?
Ajournalist?
Reuters, BBC
Delhi based
Not any local channel eh?
What were you planning?
Look sir, this is wrongful confinement
How can you hold me like a criminal?
l am a media person
with a national rating
Okay! How many policemen know
what Reuters means in our town?
Please wait outside
venu, sit please
No thanks
What was the information?
What did you see and shoot?
Open your mouth
and tell me, you...!
Hey, be quiet!
What you've guessed
was the information we got
Later, we realized it was false
How?
Kartha sir came in
with nothing in his hand
He did not carry any briefcase
or bag which could contain money
- Sir
- What is it?
Police chased and caught the van
We've got a wireless message
And?
The van belongs
to NBl, a new channel
lt is all set to launch tonight
Flash news is appearing on TV right now
Nothing was found from the vehicle
Only the driverwas there
So the van was allowed to go
NBl, News Bureau of lndia
Launching tonight at 10:00 PM
With explosive news
Tonight, at 10:00 PM
Will their news shock us?
Come on, tell us
lf it is something like that
you can demand and we'll fix a deal
l'll lavishly give it all to you
lts only 5 minutes more, tell me
l don't know
l really don't know, sir
varghese, get an ambulance ready
So as to reach here, in just 2 minutes
Hello?
Yes, Bharathan Pillai
Who was it?
- Don't know, got disconnected
- Call him back
Now it is switched off
Greetings, good evening
NBl, News Bureau of lndia
No need for introductions
for news, that's true and authentic
ln the same way NBl
without introductions
From this minute, foryou, from today
As a brand new channel, naturally
we come to you, with exclusive news
Confessions, we have seen them
many times on channel screens
But here is a secret which will
shock Kerala, truth brought by a priest
ln 2003 there was a sensational...
Sorry venu
Sorry forthe inconvenience
varghese, drop him
wherever he needs to go
Sorry
What the heck did you build up to?
Was it only me?
Who asked for an ambulance?
lfthe news was true
we had to shift stufffrom here
What will l do with that cash?
Thatwas the reason
Who is this priest?
Who knows?
A sinnerwho is not penitent
deserves to be punished
Rishi
What happened?
Where is Renu?
You returned
together, didn't you?
We waited for you till the last minute
When you didn't come, we aired another story
Tell me what happened?
l sent her offat 9:00 PM
With the footage we shot
And then?
Do you think she could be hurt?
No! Don't panic!
Nothing will happen to her
Why don'twe air
this issue now itself?
Rishi look!
Candidate for Rajya Sabha, Rajan Kartha and
Bharathan pillai Democratic party president...
...caught in the act with crores
of money changing hands, watch it!
How can your program on
confessions have any effect...
...when such explosive news is being aired?
This channel was a dead baby
even before it was born
Even a launch program
couldn't be done confidentially...
...and l've wasted my money
Enough, just wind up now
This is Renuka, with cameraman Venu
from Bharathan Pillai's residence
- Sir
- Where did you drop her?
Sir, at the over-bridge
Another car came and she got into it
Let's go to Bharath vision
Move man
You are finished!!!
You are no more!
Over! l'll just think you died
afterturning insane!
Hello?
venu, you dragged and threw me down
from a very great height
l called to let you
know my happiness
A deep wound and the sharp pain
When it heals, only l'll feel it
But be sure, you also will know it
Democratic party after its meeting...
...decides to strip
Bharathan Pillai's presidential position
They have also requested vigilance...
...to start investigations
against Kartha and Bharathan Pillai
Oh that was a terrible thing to do!
Doesn't matter
Forgiven
lf l was 1 day late, l would've had
to stand in a queue at the family court
l've forgiven!
l will not forgive!
She ruined my NBl
He wasn't referring to you
Bharathan Pillai would have
been a Chief Minister today
Today he'sjust
a state committee member
The rotten corpse!
lts 5 years since we heard
anything about NRl, Rajan Kartha
- Da!
- What is it, da?
They are all his people
Send them away, quickly
l'm hungry, where's your bike?
Da?
Did you pay salary to your staff?
-Yes l did
- How did you manage?
Did you get a windfall?
You refused to loan me
So l sold you
How?
We got incriminating
footage ofthat DySP Benny
Some youngster shot it at some resort
l showed him the footage and
threatened him, mimicking you
Rs 3 lakhs
Stop!
- Stop!
- Don't punch me
Stop the bike!
Aiyo!
l'll kill you
Can't l use your name a bit?
This has a different name
You want to see...?
Will an action do?
- Have you gone away?
- l am here
l will use you also
Don't do that
l am not like that
What's happening?
Police!
Why are you dancing
in the middle ofthe night?
We were just exercising
Exercise? Middle ofthe night?
Put them both in thejeep
Wait!
l will come by myself
Do l have to repeat it to you?
You'll face consequences
ifyou lay your hands on me
Tomorrow, all channels will carry
your stupid face, as its cover story
Beware! You are playing games
with Reuters stinger Venu, got it?
You may be big people, but when you
play such public games, what shall we do?
Oh, so what shall we do?
Sir?
This is his usual drama
Any time police catch him
or gets into any other issue...
...he will immediately say
that he's big-wig of a channel
He's nothing ofthat sort
Does video coverage, ofweddings
Da!
l will come
Walk quickly, man!
Come in
Move aside!
Francis! Get their bikes
to the police station
Put in a liter of petrol also, okay?
Get up, l say
Get up
What's happening?
This man is a nuisance
He brought the bench
from the veranda to sleep here
Lock me up
Or, l will sleep here
l always sleep at ten
after a glass of milk
Go
This is sheer menace and
l already wrote out the FlR!
lf you want to get out
get someone to bail you
We don't have anyone, sir
We are orphans
We are from the public orphanage
Sir?
Please switch on that fan
Do you hear him?
Switch on the fan
Who is it, middle ofthe night?!
lf it is anyone important
ask him to call tomorrow, l'm offto sleep
Hello, who is it?
lsn't this the number of Venu
stinger cameraman, of Reuters?
Who is it, sir?
ls it from the orphanage?
Hello?
l am advocate, Manilal
What is the case?
Counsel, it was a mistake
Please ask him to overlook this
My police pal, see what happens
when you confront me, at midnight?
- Did you see now?
- Heard now?
Thanks a lot
venu?
l've been trying you from
last evening but couldn't get through
Who are you?
l am advocate, Manilal
l have something to tell you
What is it?
lt's about an exclusive
However important it is
l'll see you tomorrow...
...when l am fresh
Come let's go!
So tell me, what is this
exclusive, all about?
An exclusive like this won't ever occur
in the history of news channels again
A story that has
to be shot risking life
l've risked my life many times
Forget that, come to the point
l will, but before that, l want
a firm affirmation from you
This exclusive info was got
from a particular channel
The story has to be
covered, only forthem
Their reporterwill accompany you
Do you have any objections?
Once l disclose information
You can't go back on your word
Mr lawyer, l do follow certain ethics
lf l give my word, it is forever
So you agree?
Agreed
But l'll be the one to decide
what to do and how to do it
Okay, agreed
Now l come to the actual point
What you have to cover, is a murder
The murder planned, is on behalf
ofa well known politician of Kerala
Sorry! l cannot do this
Hey! venu!
Please!
A life is more important
than a piece of news
Since we have info,
we have to try and save him
lt may lessen the news value, but
ratings mustn't depend on blood spilt
venu, let me explain
lt's not my urge to make money
by 'live' coverage ofa man's death
He can't be saved by anyone
even if it's reported to the police
Because, Bharathan Pillai still dictates,
even though, he's not yet Chief Minister
- Bharathan Pillai?
-Yes
This murderwill
take place on his behalf
We can't prevent it, can't we at least
make sure the culprits don't escape?
Okay, so who is the victim?
A man in Bharathan Pillai's group
We don't know who orwhat...
What rubbish is this?
l can only assure you
this information is 100% genuine
Tell me the place, time and date and
who is the reporter, coming with me
Renu?
This woman?!
Find someone else!
Lawyer, drop me back!
venu, listen to me
You can't go, you agreed...
...l disclosed info because
you claimed to have ethics
Did you tell me before hand
this useless creature was coming?
You only said some reporter
Didn't l warn you to disclose info
only after telling him everything, Chey!
Think it's not Renuka, but a stranger
X orY, with a professional approach
l am totally professional! Such a riskyjob,
l need someone who gels with me
Petty personal issues
mustn't come in the way...
...ofthis exclusive with
such strong social impact
We don't have any option, but Renuka
venu, you can insist on
whatever conditions you want
Please
Please venu!
Okay
These are my conditions
l'll be the sole decision maker
Reporter X or Y is not allowed
to make any suggestions
Sure
A DSNG van, without any crew
must be at my disposal
Okay
visuals l 'UP' has to be aired, unedited
With no interference in it, whatsoever
Agreed
My remuneration alone, is Rs 10 lakh
- Here, it's got more than what you've asked
- Let it wait, there are more conditions
visuals must accompany
a scrolling script...
'visuals exclusively covered
by cameraman venu'
No intro or sign out by the reporter
Agreed
You have 12 hours to plan
and prepare, Renu knows the details
Okay
The baton has now
shifted into your hands
venu...Renu?
Shake hands on this
Not necessary!
What's this? You'll be
working together hereafter
Be professional
venu please?
Keep the cash in the car
You have neither an intro nor sign off
Why the hell are you tagging along?
Suppose you run away with the footage
as a revenge forthe old grouse?
There is only 1 creature on earth
who'd do such things, and that's you!
l forgot to tell you, DSNG receives
poor signal at the crime spot
Even if it did, we cannot
go there with the van, right?
Oh, you are right
Okay, now both of you
can chart out a plan
Not 'both' of us
Only me!
- Shall l suggest something?
- No!
- Listen first
- Not necessary
Don't get into a fervor
and try to save the victim
You must be so blood thirsty!
Cruel she-devil!
Murder will occur even if we interfere
and finally we'll become defendants
- Are you sure?
-very sure
Then l will surely interfere, l don't care
if l'm accused, you'll also go to jail
Come on, be serious
You want me
to be serious? Really?
lf l did, you'll be lying
in lCU, very serious
There are arrears
in plenty against you
No need to contribute, be quiet
and just allow me to do my stuff
To hell with you!
Lean back and sit without
touching me, especially your bust!
You dirty...chi!!!
Turn left
This is the club house
Here? ln such an open area?
Disputed property
Government acquired 15 years ago,
not even a watchman will be here
What time is this
crime scheduled for?
Between 8:00 and 9:00 PM
ls it a favorable time?
Like they fix in weddings?
Come here
Are you scared to be alone?
l am going up there
A little
Then wait right here
After some time,
your fear will increase
lfyou make a sound,
l'll kill you with one blow!
Hey!
What is it?
A rat!
Rat?! l'll stuff cloth down your throat!
Not a sound from you!
Don't scare me,
you she-devil!!!
How did you come up?
l too learnt martial art
Kalari, for 6-7 years
Look...a car
Let me go, don't kill me
l begged forgiveness at his feet
Take me to him
You are great man
Sirwill come to meet you here
Don't hurt me, please
Let me go
Leave me
Don't harm me
Leave me, aiyo!
Don't harm me, sir
Didn't l confess everything?
Will your confessions
give me back, all what l lost?
My image, position, the days l spent
idle at home, since last 5 years
Suguna, to you, wasn't it
just an itch on your tongue?
When you betrayed us
to the channel you knew very well...
...it would cost me
and Kartha our political careers
Let me at least have
thejoy of deciding your end
Sir, don't kill me
Take him away and hang him
Hello, venu?
Ready?
l am going to upload
the footage ofthe visuals
You have to 'UP' itwith
the scrolling script and your logo
Okay
When you switch on, l'll go watch TV
in some place, any editing, remember...?!
Okay venu, there won't be
any interference from us
Yes! venu's footage will come now
UP the scrolling script along with it, okay?
Get ready with camera
DSNG crew and everything
We've got to be in front
of Bharathan Pillai's house
l am going to that
restaurant to watch TV
l want to see ifthey have
messed with my visuals
Be right here, till l get back
A true and shocking incident
that occurred a few moments ago
Prompted us to air this special bulletin
Brutal visuals we have never seen before
Democratic party leader Bharathan Pillai's
Cruel revenge against party member Sugunan
Don't harm me, sir
Didn't l confess to everything?
My image, position, the days l spent
idle at home since last 5 years
Suguna, wasn't itto you
just an itch on yourtongue?
Don't kill me
Take him away and hang him
From the place of incident
this is Renuka with camera man, Venu
Get down the way you came up
Sure, give me the bag
l will throw it down
From the place of incident
this is Renuka with cameraman, Venu
You...!
lsn't it them?
The camera man and reporter?
Sir, this is really amazing
Did the 2 ofyou really shoot this?
- ls his body still hanging there?
- May be, let the police enquire
- They must have shot it, hiding
- No dude, he shot it right from the front
They wouldn't be alive
ifthey'd been caught by those thugs
Sir, we are on ourway
to Bharathan Pillai's house
lf Pillai resists arrest
we'll have to use force
We've sent ourforces
to the club house
Once the body is traced and identified
we'll immediately go in and arrest, sir
Look! Bharathan Pillai's house
Police have come to arrest him
Afterwatching visuals of
Bharath Vision's exposure
You are seeing here
the frenzy of people
We also know only
what was shown on Tv
Police have already gone
to the place ofthe incident
Let us trace the body first
afterthat we'll take necessary steps
Will there be any arrests, sir?
We cannot say, at thisjuncture
We'll let you know by and by
Move!
Arrest the murderer
Stop!
What do you want?
Pelt stones till l die?
Go ahead
Do it, kill me
No need for police and courts
You have the right to punish me
Before that, you have
to know certain truths
You don't have
to say any darn thing!
We saw everything on Tv
Just answer the police
when they question you
varghese!
Look! There's the dead man!
Whatever l have to say
is here, for you to see, 'alive'
lt was him, it seems
who l killed and then hanged
What more can l say?!
Ask him whateveryou want
Mr Suguna, what do you have to say?
l don't know anything, l too saw it
on TV, Pillai sirwill tell you the rest
Mr Pillai, what do you have to say?
l don't understand why that girl
and cameraman have enmity to me
l also have no idea
how they created such visuals
l am not a technical expert
You remember, 5 years ago
the same team hunted and...
...pinned Kartha and me down
with a bribe charge, using visuals
l couldn't prove anything then
Break and destroy Bharath vision!
Come, dude!
Damn his hidden camera!!
Wait there! You can't go
after creating controversies
Go, get into the van
without gaping, you idiot
Don't let them go
Come on, climb
Abu! van!
Move
Burn it up!
Turn right, we'll go to
Bharath vision
Turn right
lt's safer there
What?
Turn right
We'll go to the studio
Don't utter a word
What do we do at the studio?
Move aside
Where is he?
Come
l don't know what happened
The original footage...
Enough! Stop
- l wasjust talking to the home secretary
- Later
- Let me discuss this with my legal advisor
- We'll get him to the police station, come
Move aside!
Get down!
Today, some shocking visuals
ofa brutal murderthat stunned...
...the conscience of Kerala
were aired by Bharath Vision
But soon after that, within minutes
the man who was claimed to be killed...
- l am venu
- Where are you?
- Are you in your apartment?
- No, at the studio
l am right beneath
your apartment
Right below my apartment?!
Don't you dare go there!
l'll kill the 2 ofyou
You went to favor Bharath vision
Exclusive it seems!
Go, take her also along
l can't do anything foryou
Tell me where the keys are, vagabond!
Only you can go in, not her
l'll decide that, now tell me
where is the key, useless!
On the window sill
Don't open the door to anyone, l'll be
ruined if anyone knows you are in there
Look, you don't broadcast this, okay?
l'll kill you, ifyou do!
Get inside, you...!
Oh Lord, am l fated to die
without a drop to drink?
Protestors from Bharathan Pillai's house
were uncontrollable by the time...
...they reached the Bharath Vision studios
Police arrived and stopped them while
breaking the glass and trying to barge in...
...and on charges of
telecasting false news
...they arrested CEO
and 1 ofthe directors, Vijaykumar
His granny's information!
He has to be kicked, the pig!
lt was l who got the information
Not vijaykumar, sir
What?
lt was l who was informed
Tell me, who gave the info to you
Come on tell me
Go on
lt was the lawyer, Manilal
So he was the one who betrayed, eh?
He is innocent
l know very well
Not innocent (actor)
ldavela Babu (actor)
How can you trust him?
ls he God, or your dad?
He's my cousin, all exclusive info
l've covered, were based on his tip-offs
His info was always true
including the bribe case
Manilal will not betray
Pillai deserves a bouquet
He retrieved all he'd lost on a single night
At the same time, made us go into hiding
Yes, now l can hear
Mr Bharathan Pillai, the incident at
the club house being proved false...
...are you now claiming that
the bribe case charged on you
...and Kartha 5 years back
was totally baseless?
Didn't the truth
come out by itself?
Now let the central committee
decide what l should do
l've suffered for 5 years, in spite of
not having committed a single crime
The people and party members
who rejected me then, are now with me
l'm sure the central
committee will realize this
Thank you
High hopes! l didn't hang that fellow
to get an award for good behavior
Let them bring it back
All what they took away
The 2 ofthem are in a pathetic state
Must be hiding, not knowing what to do
Renuka along with camera man venu
Dude, this is simple straight math
Anyone with an ounce of brains
can decipher this move, let alone venu
The credibility he'd destroyed
l managed to get back
Now to ruin theirtrust and careers
l'm taking the same route, a silent chase
Sir, but isn't there a risk?
Will he not come after you again?
Of course he will
But not immediately, varghese
They will not get out
until this noise dies down
l too gain time that way,
because by then...
...l'll occupy the chief minister's chair
Let them come after that
- Here, use onions
- l don't want your onions
Don't show your craving
- l never asked
- l won't give, even ifyou ask
Shhhh!
Someone's knocking
Some one's outside
Sure, there is someone
Greedy devil!
Thanks
Ask them to come in
Burn it all up, dude!
Sir, this is venu's l-Pad
All the visuals are in this
So we've got all
the original footage
-Yes sir
- Good!
Settle their accounts
Having been proved
that the visuals were false...
Police have charged a case
against Venu and Renuka
And they are on the lookoutto find them
The sooner they are...
Switch it off, l say!
Says the city police commissioner
What do we do now?
Think! lfyou get
a brainwave, tell me
We need to know
the legal consequences
Shall l call Manilal?
Who am l, to ask permission?
Your husband?
My phone was lost in that DSNG van
lfyou give me your phone, l'll call him
Call him with the speaker phone
switched on
l want to hearwhat he says
Okay
Don't tell him about this place
Stand near me and call
Hello?
Mani, it's me Renu
Where were you?
Couldn't you call?
l was so worried
Don't ever be caught
by the party men or police
All ofthem are in a frenzy
Tell me, what can
happen to us, at the most?
lfyou are caught
it will be a big problem
Once arrested, you won't
get bail for 40 days
l'll tell you a way out, because
l'm concerned about you
The 1st one, who's caught
gets 40 days in lock-up
When the 2nd person surrenders,
it'll be forjust 1or 2 days
You will surely
get bail, being a woman
Why take a risk?
Get him caught somehow
Tell me the place,
l'll take care ofthe rest
Don't glare at me, he likes me
He must've said that, to save me
Your Mani...l'll...!
You and your people
are all ofthe same kind, cheats!
Didn't you move away
from me, to talk in secret?
l've been told the FlR
has not yet been written
Yes
Tell me, you want to be
defendant or a witness?
There's not much time
isn't it, Anthony?
Yes, sir
Let's say, you trusted Renuka
and aired the visuals from Bharath vision
You neither knew anything nor
did you entrustvenu this job, that's all
Bharatha vision can continue
functioning as usual from tomorrow
What do you say?
Where are they?
venu and Renuka?
They are on the run
Don't you know?
We have decided
not to run after them
Sorry sir, but l'm running afterthem
Was it for this show-down
he was brought to the police club?
No sir, the commissioner
wanted to question...
- No!
- Sir!
You never asked me
why l was running afterthem?!
l have my doubts, as to why
they wanted to create a footage...
...ofa man being killed
when he actually was not
So l thought l'll ask them directly
Benny
You must find them, quickly
Time is running out, for me and you!
You heard that?
Today's 10:00 PM news
has to be neutral
But stress on, Renuka's thirst
for exclusivity and popularity
Okay, sir
And venu, just a camera man
who covered, what she asked him to
See that you protect him
lf possible, we'll drop a bombshell
An exclusive interview with venu
ls it to be here, in the studio?
You...! Go get your text
ready for the evening news!
Go, all ofyou
Dumbo! But not when
he doesn't get his pay!
SP Somarajan sir is calling
Sir?
Rishi, Police may raid your studio
Their intention is to catch venu
Come, we have work to do
lfthey begin to shoot
take away the camera
Return it only after
removing the footage
- lndhu, is the sound ready?
- Ready
vCR must be in position
Only the indicator must be seen
Don't allow anyone to enter or exit
What is it, sir?
- Where is venu?
- Which venu?
How many venu-s do you know?
lndhu?
Call venu
What is the problem, sir?
Don't harass him, innocent chap!
Sir, there's venu
What is it sir?
This...!!!
What is it, sir?
Are you making fun of me?
Where is he buddy, the Reuters stinger?
Why would he be here?
He must be at Bharath vision studio
Don't play your games with me
l'll deal with you good and proper
Tell me! You must know
His 1 and only friend, right?
Sir, leave his collar
Look, it's going on 'live'
Live?
Mr Rishikesh, as a responsible channel head
shouldn't you be helping the police?
Get lost, you useless!!!
Sure, l'll help you catch him, you...!!!
How can you behave like this?
Sudhi, cut Rishi's audio
Now onwards it will be
a shower ofswearwords!
Ouch!
Okay, let me know ifyou get info
This is my number, here
Okay, see you then
Sure
Sir, watch out, these rascals might
put a camera even into our innerwear
lndhu, audio on
The competition for exclusive news
may have put Renuka into thisjeopardy
What you saw now, is how,
based on past events...
...police are treating
the entire media community
This is what DySP Benny Tharakan
wrote,just before he left the studio
l'll deal with you outside, you dog!
ln case you don't see me on this channel
you can conclude, l'm in police custody
We are on to fresh info about
the telecasting offalse news issue
The police who are on the look out
for Reuters stinger camera man Venu ...
...in connection with the controversial
murderfootage, will join us on line now
Hello venu?
Sorry, ourtechnicians
will soon connect us
Hello?
Venu?
Can you hear me?
Send me at least
a bottle of brandy, you fool!
Hello?
l'm going insane, there's nothing
to booze, you miserly vagabond
Hello
- Can'tyou hear me?
- Yes, l can, tell me Venu
What actually
happened that night?
What else, itwasjust
a drama by that Pillai
l must be kicked
in the butt for falling for that...!
Hello, Venu?
You vagabond!
ln this situation
what have you got to say?
There are unscrupulous fellows
amongst us, who use personal phone calls ...
...ofeven their closest pals
for exclusivity
lfthat attitude changes
we can be free of such issues
Thank you, MrVenu
A short break before
we move on to othertopics
Sir, Kakkanad, Skyline apartments
Sir, we've traced his hide out
Skyline apartments, at Kakkanad
very good
But we couldn't trace
the floor he occupies
We'll enquire if any media person
resides there and search that first
Da! l've favors saved up, to return to you!
You sold me, on 1st chance you got, right?
Forget it, your phone call
was traced and police have located you
Somaraj sir informed me, they'll be
there right now, so go away from there
Where will l go at this time of the night?
Just move from there for the time being
l'll find another place and call you
Where are you going?
Police have traced us here
They'll be here at any moment
Oh Lord!
One minute, l'll go
to the john and come
l can't bear it any more
What?
Please stop!
What for?
What?
What is it?
l want to pee
Oh! This will be our ruin!
Couldn't you finish it at the apartment?
You locked the door and
took off before l could, didn't you?
Get off
Please
Chey! That was an ambulance
Where is the bike's key, you...!?
Here
You were trying
to get me caught, right?
l did that, so you
wouldn't leave me and go
You cheat! Don't lie
l know...you didn't go to pee
Chey! Get lost da!
You dare say,
'get lost, da' to me?
Didn't you start the bike
to go off and let me get caught?
l thought l'll be ready
by the time you come back
Why did you lock me up in the flat?
So what? Yes l did!!!
To trap you, now what about it?
Sure, l too did the same
One of us must give ourselves up
We can't live like fugitives, under pressure
l am not giving myself up
without finding a solution to this
Then drop me at
the police station and go
Don't start being sentimental, okay?
Sentiments?! Sure l don't have any
Remember? Only popularity mania, right?
Look, no flashbacks, okay?
Pouring oil on troubled waters!
You are a reporter, me, a camera man
That's all, now get on the bike
Unless this is solved
we are not surrendering
A hideout is ready, take the 1st left
afterthe Alpuzha Nedumudi bridge
After about, 1.5 km
you'll see a wooden gate
l'll be there, with Abu
Okay
Who was it?
Rishi
Hi
Come dude, this summer house
belongs to a friend, he's in the USA
Come
l'll come back
tomorrow morning
What?
l'll be here in the morning
with clothes and a hearing aid
Buy all newspapers
you can lay hands on
l have news foryou
Bharath vision has
denounced both ofyou
vijaykumar presented it
on the late night report
Tell this to hertomorrow
- lt's not over
- What else?
News from Delhi, yourjob
at Reuters has been terminated
What else?
Nothing much
Bharathan Pillai is being
considered for CM post
The central committee is meeting
Swearing in may happen soon
- Okay
- See you, dude
Abu
These clothes are for them
Da, give me those newspapers
- These are clothes for both ofyou
- Thank you
Here's your hearing aid
Rishi, the original footage
is missing from the DSNG van
Without that
how can we prove the truth?
That's how they planned it
The screen play was fool-proof
From the time we passed info
to the restaurant drama, a neat script!
Written and directed
by Bharathan Pillai
lfso, Rajan Kartha
must be the producer
He's here in Kochi
since the last few days
Almost from the day
you came from Delhi
Didn't you say, swearing in
ofthe CM will happen shortly?
We have time
only till then, Rishi
Now Sugunan must be
made to talk, isn't it?
Yes
Ouch!
Oh mother!
What happened?
He hit me and took off
Some rascal!
Aw, my hand
Hey! Aren't you Sugunan sir?
Just give me a hand, brother
Let's go to the hospital
- Ouch my hand!
- Gently, take care
- ls it still paining?
- No, it's better now
Siryou are very smartly dressed
Don't you wear Khadi usually?
lt is to avoid Tv
Nuisance!
Look! That's the vehicle that hit me
Really?!
l'll find out right now
Don't step out, you'll be recognized
l'll go find out
- What's all this?
- Exactly what we also want to know!
1st die, then come alive
Are you the Lasser of modern times?
1st let him get over his shock
Then he'll talk, our Sugunan-Lasser
Okay
We saw you being killed
We showed it to the public also
No confusion about this at all!
But after some time
you reappeared alive
- Public became confused
- And so did we
We are not going to clearthat
We are going to increase it
On the same place and rope
you will swing, hanging dead
We'll shoot it very smartly
and show it to the public
The public will go mad
What must they believe?
l swear, l have not done
anything intentionally
l really thought
they were going to kill me
l did tell Manilal, about the bribe
You guys flashed it, as hot news
lt was only recently Pillai sir
came to know it was l who had informed
l fell at his feet, cried begging his pardon
He asked me to pass 1 more info to Manilal
That a murder would happen,
on behalf of Pillai sir
After l did that,
he asked me to leave
But the next day...
Sugana, come with me
Bharathan Pillai sir, is asking foryou
Hello, take this
What is it, sir?
What are you doing?
Leave me
What is it, sir
Stop it!
Don't harm me
Didn't l confess everything, sir?
Confession to the holy person
in a church will do you good
But what's inside my chest
is not a holy heart, Suguna
- Ready, sir
- Lift him now
How is it?
lsn't it okay?
Leave me, l say
Go, hang him!
Afteryou left
they returned
Shibu, this is an antidote
Make him inhale it, he'll wake up
They took me
to Pillai sir's house
When people turned nasty
He asked me to come out
l was only a dupe sir, a dupe of
the person who was to be, actually killed
Dupe?
ln that club house
there will be an actual murder
ln the same place
almost in the same manner
Who?
Who will it be?
l don't know, sir
But l know for sure
it's on the 12th night
How do you know this?
l heard Pillai sir's assistant
varghese, tell my captors...
...that they must leave the club house
as soon as the deed was done
That their tickets have been booked
forthe 2:00 AM train, on13th morning
That they should return, only after
Pillai sir, was sworn in, as Chief Minister
Abu, go drop Suguna
at the nearest hospital
- Do you know who's going to die?
- No
lt's you
Pillai wants to frame us
with that crime
Don't try to run and escape
Even ifyou try, they won't allow you
Remember, we haven't met
We'll be there on the 12th
We want to shoot that event
Go, don't be scared
Nothing will happen to you
- Abu
-Yes, sir
Here, ask that lawyer Manilal
to meet me before noon tomorrow
He started all this, right?
Mani, l have to see you urgently
Come tomorrow afternoon
- What is it?
- l'll tell you
We've found a way out ofthis mess
You have to stand by us
Sure
- What did you think?
- Poor fellow
Yes
He's a great actor, noticed his tears
without a drop of glycerin? Cheat!
We did not get him, dude
Pillai threw him at us, a bait
What are you saying?
lt's the next scene in
Pillai's frivolous drama
Believing his story, Renuka and l will
go on 12th, to shoot the original murder
Pillai, Kartha and their boys will wait
Because it is we who are going to die
Simple
Gosh! This is getting
more and more complicated
lfwe remain free, they are clueless
as to the extent we'd go, to prove the truth
So we have to be
eliminated forever
They will make us, fugitives forever
Police, government and the media
We have no option but to go
to their butcher shop on 12th
This is a trap for us, as well
as our only way to escape
lfwe win, we can regain all we lost
As well as ensure, Pillai's political funeral
- lfyou lose?
- Death
Like your usage, 'it seems'
they committed suicide
On 12th we are shooting
the incident, whatever the risk
Look at the irony of it
However priceless, this exclusive
we shoot now is, no channel will air it!
Except for his NBl
Ours is a small channel...
...ifyou intend giving it to some
gigantic one, please let me know
We don't have to trouble
ourselves unnecessarily
Only l will be going, to shoot this
What if l come?
You want to sign-out, as usual
Just forthat, you needn't come
This is an issue
involving my credibility
l will come!
Whoever objects, l'll come!
Go, let me plan this out
l have been tolerating
innuendos for last 3-4 days
l don't want considerations
Nor do l even expect it
You don't deserve it also
l don't need to
convince you ofthat
The 1 who was supposed to be
convinced, has never come forward
l am not interested
in a reconciliation talk
Me too
Then?
This is a social issue
which involves me too
l cannot stay away
whateveryou say
This is to make you
stay away from death, you...!
After all, he did have you
in his heart, for some time
He is now going
into the arena of death
- What?
- Nothing
Tell me, Rishi
What is happening?
lt's not Sugunan, who will die
lt will be you and venu
Do you really want to go now?
lf l don't go after knowing this
l won't exist anymore, Rishi
l thought we had time, that when
l get a chance, l could explain
l expected such a chance, when
l set out with him on this venture
Since that is no longer a surety...
l'll tell you the truth,
l never betrayed you
That day, fearing the police
when venu sent me off in the van
l was on my way
to our...sorry, yourstudio
But...
Abu make it fast, its already 9:15 PM
lt has to be edited and aired by 10:00 PM
Renu, be assured
l'll reach you there in 15 minutes
Mani! Success! l'm on my way
to the studio with the footage
Renu l know, l was there nearby
lt's all a mess now and venu
has been caught by the police
Now, they'll soon be after you
Aiyo!
Oh God!
l am right behind you, a black lnnova
Stop and get into my car, that will be safer
- Abu, stop here
- Renu, time is...?
Abu, just stop!
Get in, quick!
Mani quickly, it has to be
aired at 10:00 PM
Be on Bharath vision's pay roll
and get the story for NBl Channel, eh?
But l am no longeryourstaff
l resigned 5 days back
We've not got any such resignation
And even if there is, l've not accepted it
Mani, stop! l want to get out
He will not, because if he does
this footage will go to Bharathan Pillai
Drive us to the studio, dude!
He has taken Rs 2 lakhs
from us for this story
How can this become
NBl's launch story?
My mistake sir, l didn't know
she had committed to NBl
l will return that money
today itself...sir, please!
That's all over
Nothing more to discuss
Sir, but...
lt's not money alone
Once you did this story, he'd bargained
and fixed senior editor's post for you
Mani, l don't want any post
Get me that footage back
This will come only in NBl
lt will not
lt can come in any other
channel, but never NBl
l am sitting in the chair
Rishi discarded and left
How can l let this explosive
story, be launched by Rishi?
Mani, for them it's channel war
To me it's a question of trust and my life
Mani please, tomorrow
venu and l are getting married
Sir, please!
You don't talk anymore
l will not air this
without your permission
But l'll use this to
make sure NBl is not born
Simple, l'll just hand this overto Pillai
NBl will remain, a dream to Rishi
And venu is in police custody
l won't be able to even guess
in what state, he will return
You have time till
Pillai attends this call
Sir, no
l beg you
Sir, it's her future
that will be affected
- Hello?
- ls it Bharathan Pillai?
Yes
Sir...
l became 'all alone
in one single night'
With nothing left, l had only
Bharath vision, as an option for survival
Renu, 5 years you have...
Oh God!
-venu must be told...
- Don't, Rishi
He must not know this now
He won't take me along otherwise
l know his concern, for people
he cares for, please don't tell him
Okay, l won't
What is that secret meet there?
Will that she-devil
betray us, in this also?
Da! Don't be so mean
Are you on her side or mine?
This is why we say
you should also be there
Your cousin is risking
her life for this
Convince her not to,
she refuses to listen to me
venu, is there
some other way out?
You tell us
Mani, let venu explain
Today is the 10th
Day after tomorrow, it is12th
Only ifwe convincingly shoot
our act, that we are going to die...
...Pillai and Kartha's
intentions can be proved
But how and who will shoot this?
lt's impossible to shoot in
the club house or surroundings
Then?
Come, l'll explain
500 meters away, that is
halfa kilometer away, on top...
...ofthe pavilion, cameras with
telescopic lenses, will be set up
Rishi's camera crew
will operate them
Pretending to cover Sugunan's murder
we will reach the club house, on 12th night
We'll get surrounded by them
and a little struggle will ensue
A little action sequence by me
And finally, we get caught
lf Kartha comes, we can
expect a cinema style dialog
l'll have a voice recorder in my pocket
After shooting what we want
you and Abu should interfere
Don't delay my friend,
orwe'll never come out alive!
l agree, sir
Can l tell you what l fear?
Those who fear need not come
Didn't l warn you?
Let her tell her opinion
Yes, Renu?
ln case we are not able
to pull this off, Pillai and Kartha...
...will escape for ever
We can't take a chance
That is what l'm also coming to, silly
- This will not be exclusive to NBl
- What?
We will allow 2 more channels
to shoot, without our involvement
That's why l asked,
Manilal also to come
Go climb a wall!!!
lt's impossible!
This is exclusive to NBl
Dude?
Don't say 'no'! l've pinned all my hopes
on this and planned a lot for its success
Does our friendship have
the value of, just an exclusive?
l have not gained anything
with this friendship, l've only lost
- l will do this story alone, if not...
- lf not...?
lf not, don't expect
anything more from me
Then so be it!
You are not doing this story
Abu! Start the vehicle
Rishi!
Didn't you hear me?
You can take it yourself, sir
Rishi? Please!
ls your father dead? Everybody
thinks only oftheir own benefits
This is not the 1st time
Abu can operate my camera
Lawyer Mani, 12th is day after tomorrow
Tomorrow we set up camera at the stadium
Fix up a couple of more
channels and let me know
Park it near the north ofthe stadium
When it gets dark, we'll be there
Abu, don't wait, it'll take time
Come only when l call you
Okay, sir
- What is it?
- A mosquito
Mosquito?!
This is field limit, whatever happens
don't move away from this limit
Find all possibilities and fix the limit
-venu, there's a car!
- l saw it too, you useless!
Bharathan Pillai!
Rishi has cheated us
lt's not what we thought, lets escape
Be quiet, girl!
venu, it will happen today!
The camera is gone
Now what's the point?
Whatever happens
you won't die, enough?
Without getting into trouble
come with me, you shrew!
l was in a hurry to die sir
So, l came here today itself
There lies your camera, how will you
shoot and show it to the public now?
Call that lawyer
Call Manilal
Call that lawyer!
Don't!
Take it away, there mustn't be
even a small scratch on the body
They have to be hanged
Not murdered but as suicide
Why do you need a binocular
camera to shoot such a near event?
Not binoculars, a microscope
is enough for a worm like you
What are you glaring at?
Where are your contraptions
witnesses, 2-3 channels, etc?
People ready tojump to save you
from death, where the hell are they?
When you sent him away
l knew, you'd smelt trouble
Stop lecturing and call that punk
Pillai waves from 1.5 KM away
and now hiding in the kitchen
l'll give you a sound sla-!
Why should l hide, venu?
lt's you who are still in hiding
venu, Manilal is trapped
l heard his phone ringing
He's here somewhere
Lawyer, don't hide
Come into the arena, you pig
Come out! lt'll be awkward only
if have to see them, ever again
Son ofa mongrel!
l don't have any cinema dialog
l will go away after just 1, okay?
This is not revenge, if it was
l'd have had time, only for that in life
This is just a precaution!
Allow me to rule and live peacefully, dude
Taking cameras into people's bedroom,
bathroom and calling it media activism!
This is the only medicine
for all that, okay?
2 media persons who've lost
credibility and life, commit suicide
Shall l hang them, sir?
Do you have anything to say?
l don't, but she has...a sign-off
After all we are going to die, right?
Go ahead!
Look somewhere and say it
From the place ofevents
this is Renuka with cameraman venu
More cameras?
lfthere are cameras here
ask your people to bash them up
Don't panic, these are
last minute tactics to escape
Hang them both!
Freeze!
- Are we on time?
- Perfectly on time!
What other contraptions
do you want to see?
Open your eyes wide and look!
Lights on!
See, how many cameras!
No other channel
Only NBl
Because, this is
an exclusive for his channel
Arrest them
Lawyer, when Rishi stormed off
angrily, what did you think?
Thatwe had parted ways?
He had ajob here
which needed 24 hrs
When l learnt that itwas you
who had fixed up a story for her...
...at Bharath vision, l knew
it was you, who was their pimp
You want to give him a couple?
You can't, once we are out of here
That's not myjob
But l want to!
Excellent!
Thatwas personal
Come on, get going
Come, my girl
With 7- 8 cameras around, you signed-off
looking, where there was no camera!
Smart girl!
Come
Come on, say it now
This is Renuka
with camera man venu
- With camera man venu?
- This is Renuka, forever!
Encoded by ViZNU.
Support us by visiting www.P2PDL.com.