(ALI_MG)
My girlfriend’s bitchin’ 'cause I always sleep in
She’s always screamin’ when she’s calling her friend
She’s kinda hot though
Yeah, she’s kinda hot though (Just an itty bitty little bit hot)
My shrink is telling me I got crazy dreams
She’s also saying I got low self-esteem
She’s kinda hot though
Yeah, she’s kinda hot though (Just a little bit a little bit hot)
She put me on meds, she won’t get out of my head
She’s kinda hot though
(One, two, three, go!)
My friend left college 'cause it felt like a job
His mom and dad both think he’s a slob
He’s got a shot though (No, not really)
Yeah, he’s got a shot though (No, no, not really)
When you’ve got bigger plans that no one else understands
You’ve got a shot though
(Oh my, that’s a big plan you’ve got there)
They say we’re losers and we’re alright with that
We are the leaders of the not-coming-back’s
But we’re alright though
Yeah, we’re alright though
We are the kings and the queens of the new broken scene
(Uno, dos, tres, cuatro)
Sometimes I’m feeling like I’m going insane
My neighbour told me that I got bad brains
But I’m alright though (We’re alright though)
Yeah, we’ll be alright though (We’re alright though)
'Cause we’re the kings and the queens of the new broken scene
And we’re alright though
(One, two, three, four)
They say we’re losers and we’re alright with that
We are the leaders of the not-coming-back’s
But we’re alright though (We’re alright though)
Yeah, we’re alright though (We’re alright though)
We are the kings and the queens of the new broken scene
Yeah, we’re alright though (We're gonna be OK)
Na na na na na na na na na na na
But we’re alright though
Yeah, we’re alright though
Na na na na na na na na na na na
We are the kings and the queens of the new broken scene
Yeah, we’re alright though