Go, swim away! You're free now.
The two snake spirits
White snake is the elder, green snake
is younger.
They are always caring for
and helping each other.
It's so boring here as celestial beings.
And so lonely too.
Everday just drags on.
Everything remains the same here.
To be joyful one should go to
the mortal world.
It's certainly warmer there.
Seek fun in the mortal world.
Romance is sweet in the world of humans.
If you know the mortal world is fun,
...why not go there to live?
I'd sure like to.
But I fear the heavenly rules
and punishments.
Well, I've had enough here,
I'll take my chances.
I've decided to take a trip there.
Please take care of our home.
You treat me like your younger sister,
we go through everything together.
I will worry if you go alone.
Of course I too would like to go with you.
After Xu Xian paid his respects to
his ancestors,
...he took his time on the way home.
Gazing tirelessly West Lake's
picture-perfect scener.
There, unexpectedly, he'd meet
a beauty by the shore.
Dear sister.
He's neither kith nor kin,
why are you so lost in thought over him?
We have just got here to the mortal world,
and you seem to be like, totally besotted!
It's true that we don't know him, but...
I remember him saving my life once
perhaps eons ago.
That's in his past life,
of course you wouldn't know.
Oh, so then he's your benefactor.
I have to pay my debt of gratitude.
I need to get to know him first,
...and I'll need your help.
Hey, look.
Boatman, would you go to Qingbo Gate?
Yes.
Hop on.
Please come closer.
Be careful.
Boatman.
Where are you heading to?
We're going to Qingbo Gate.
Could you take us?
Of course, this master is going that way.
Come on, you two.
Watch out!
It's slippery.
Mister.
My lady invites you to sit inside.
There's no room.
I don't want to cause you
any inconvenience.
Mister, since we are travelling together,
there's no such thing as inconvenience.
Please come in.
- Come on.
- Please stop pulling.
- It's fine.
- I'll come in.
- Sure.
Let me hold the umbrella.
That's alright, thank you.
Please sit down.
Please.
Just sit down,
or my boat will rock over.
May we know your name, mister?
Xu Xian.
So it's Mr. Xu.
Yes.
Sorry to bother you.
Don't be so modest.
Boatman.
You can't take their money.
- I should pay.
- It's the same.
Give her money back, I'll pay you.
Let me pay...
It's the same.
You shouldn't have.
You're most welcome.
Qingqing.
We ought to move on,
looks like it might rain.
Is that so?
It's raining again.
It's quite heavy, what should we do?
Please take this umbrella, miss.
We can't... what about you?
It's fine, I live close by.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Let's go, it's getting heavier.
Where do you live, mister?
I'll return the umbrella to you tomorrow.
Don't worry.
I'll pick it up from your residence
tomorrow.
Good idea.
Outside Qingbo Gate,
there's Qianwang Temple.
Beside it is a red door;
with character "Bai" on it.
That's my home.
I'll pay you a visit tomorrow.
Mister, you can get off too.
Alright.
Playing in the woods a thousand years ago,
I was held hostage by a naughty child.
Luckily my benefactor was there to help,
...or else I'd be beaten to death.
I must repay this favour,
I'd like to marry him.
"Bai Residence"
Mr. Xu.
Mr. Xu, why are you leaving?
My lady worried that you can't find us,
she sent me here to welcome you.
Please come inside.
My lady has been expecting you.
Please have a seat, Mr. Xu.
Mr. Xu.
Please sit down, Mr. Xu.
After you, miss.
Are you busy at work?
Yes, I work in a shop.
We're busy all the year round.
The dishes are getting cold,
I'll check in the kitchen.
Please have another drink.
Please.
The wine's getting cold,
I'll fill this up.
Be seated, please.
No, I can't drink too much.
Don't worry, you won't get drunk.
Sister. Should I send him off?
Qingqing.
I must remind you,
although you're in love with Mr. Xu,
and we've checked his background out.
But still, you never know.
I request you to think it over.
Qingqing, I appreciate your concern.
But about Mr. Xu,
he's honest and sincere.
There's not a lie coming from him,
he's not like the others.
If you love him that much,
I'll talk to him.
You're dashing and polite,
young and good looking.
Your wife must be ver lucky, I'd say
She's fortunate to have a husband
like you.
My parents died when I was ver young,
I work & live at my brother-in-law's
pharmacy.
I'm not married yet,
so how would there be a wife as you say?
One should get married on coming of age.
Say, even if not married
you should be engaged.
I have no assets and no abilities,
...how could I get engaged?
Okay, so you're not engaged now,
you don't plan to stay single forever,
do you?
No matter what,
you don't have to worry about me.
I don't think it's a good idea
to be single.
Let me be your matchmaker.
There's a young spinster I know of;
She's prettier than the fairies.
Even if she is,
she certainly won't marry a poor man,
right?
But this young lady that I speak of...
she's marrying for love, not for money.
To fall in love it's got to be
predestined.
Otherwise it won't work.
If it's not meant to be,
how could she fall in love
at first sight?
She'd have to meet me first,
before she could fall in love.
You've met her, and you've talked to her.
Please don't pretend to be a fool.
I've met and talked to her?
Are you teasing me?
Whom are you referring to?
My lady Miss Bai Suzhen.
I'm a junior worker in a pharmacy,
I am no match for your lady.
I'm from a poor family, I've no assets,
...how could I get married?
Haven't I told you?
She's not interested in betrothal money.
There's no need to worry.
I appreciate your kindness. I however,
must talk to my elder sister and
brother-in-law first.
Then I'll give you an answer.
What if your sister says no?
She would of course consider.
Wait a minute, I'll ask my lady
to come here,
...and you can have a talk.
Shoulder to shoulder, side by side.
In a pair, under the full moon.
Like a fish in the sea,
husband and wife will be together forever.
Ver much in love,
the couple is thrilled.
The hills and the willow trees
on the side,
...the little boat sails on.
My dear wife...
You're a rare gem, such a romantic.
You are willing to marry a poor man
like me.
I'm ashamed that I haven't achieved
my goals yet,
I feel bad not being able to
provide you a good life.
We're husband and wife now,
don't be so modest.
I'm not marrying for money;
As long as our love can last forever,
...I can live a simple and poor life.
Even if you put vanity aside,
one would still need money to live
a simple life.
My income is limited,
I reckon it will be difficult for us.
Don't worry,
I have it all planned out.
I have many relatives in Suzhou city.
They'd all be willing to lend
a helping hand.
I've been practising medicine
since I was young, &...
I've been handed down a
'cure-all' prescription.
Let's move to Suzhou.
We'll open a clinic.
Xu Xian bid his sister goodbye
and moved away.
"Baohe Clinic"
Business at the new clinic is going well.
Bai Suzhen is a good doctor.
She can cure all.
She can even cure all kinds of
hopeless cases.
One dose of her prescription
will do the trick.
Their reputation has spread far and wide.
The clinic is often packed.
"Luzu Temple"
Incense sticks for sale...
I'll burn incense sticks under
my master's order.
I'm passing by, and it happens to be
Luzu's birthday.
That's why I'm here to meet and
greet new friends.
Charms, amulets for sale.
Guaranteed to keep off all troubles
and evil spirits.
Work like magic they do.
My name is Guo Wei,
I can summon wind and rain.
I know how to ward off evil spirits.
You are here to pay your respects to Luzu,
don't miss the chance to buy my charms.
Strange, I can feel some evil spirit.
It's you to flush the spookiness around!
Nonsense! We all know Mr. Xu.
Mr. Xu and his wife are life-savers;
Evil spirits? That's ridiculous.
Everone.
What evil spirits?
No one believes you.
He indeed has evil force around him.
And it's from someone close to him.
What rubbish!
Your wife is a monster.
That's sheer nonsense.
Tell me then, what kind of a monster
is she?
Speak up.
Where? Monster?
If you can't tell,
...I'll wreck your booth.
Wreck it!
I couldn't say what kind of
a monster she is,
but I'm certain that she's the one.
If you don't get rid of her,
your life is in grave danger.
Taoist priest, you are much older than me,
I'll let you get away this time.
I'd be a conman if I take your money.
Now, I'm giving you three charms for free.
Come here to thank me tomorrow.
He makes sense.
- What if she isn't?
- If she isn't...
What do you say?
Wreck his booth.
Fine! It's a deal.
Alright.
Here you go.
Hide the first one in your hair,
then the devil wouldn't hurt you.
Place the second one above your door,
then she couldn't escape.
Burn the third one in front of her,
and her true identity...
will be revealed!
What a silly Taoist priest.
A third grade fortune-teller he is.
I've been a snake spirit for
a thousand years,
do you think I'll be scared of
your charms?
But my husband is confused,
I must try to lift his suspicion.
I must solve this puzzle for him.
Are you alright, dear?
What do you want to tell me?
I met a Taoist priest at Luzu Temple.
He just kept insisting that
you're a monster;
Moreover, he has even given me 3 charms.
This is ridiculous!
Go on then, try it out!
See if it works.
What if it doesn't?
If it doesn't,
I'm going to wreck his booth tomorrow.
Go on then, try it out!
Go on.
I'm worried that you couldn't handle it...
So you believe what the
Taoist priest said?
You think that I'm some evil spirit.
If I burn this you will...
my true identity will be revealed.
Dear, it's just a scam,
You shouldn't listen to such gossip
from now on.
Especially not those conmen.
I won't listen to such nonsense anymore.
I'll go wreck his booth right now.
Dear.
Where do you think you're going,
Taoist priest?
Do you think you can bully people
...with your voodoo?
Are you scared of me?
Taoist priest.
Miss Qing...
Please spare me...
Sister.
Are you alright?
Congratulations!
What is it, dear?
Dear.
Should I congratulate you or myself?
Congratulations!
Mr. Xu...
What is it?
Miss Qing, where is Mr. Xu?
There's a monk outside
who wants to meet the master.
A monk.
What is it?
There's a monk here to see you.
Give him a donation and send him off.
He's not here for money or
for consultation.
He wants to see you;
Um... it seems rather important.
What does he want from me?
Strange.
Do you know who that monk is?
Monk Fahai of Golden Mountain Temple.
Master, are you looking for me?
You don't know me, but I know
you are Xu Xian.
Do you have advice for me, master?
This is not such a good place to talk;
There's an open space over the bridge,
...let's walk over there.
Only my family's here,
we can talk at ease.
This is kinda private,
we better talk over there.
After you.
Don't let anyone disturb us.
Yes.
I don't collect alms nor am I
connected to medicine.
But this is important,
I must warn you.
Please, master.
Listen well:
Your wife is a white snake spirit.
A white snake spirit?
Also,
her maid is a green snake spirit.
Both snakes could be tring to harm you.
I don't believe any of this!
I'm just a poor man,
why do they want to harm me?
They've done nothing but good deeds.
In fact people call my wife "Empress Bai".
Well, that's her bewitching charm.
The white snake spirit is ver powerful.
If you don't leave her,
...you might die.
You see, it was fate that brought us
together.
Follow me to Golden Mountain Temple
to become a monk.
That way, you can stay alive.
I don't aspire to be a monk.
Don't be so stubborn!
Trouble is upon you.
Thanks for your concern, master.
I don't believe they are snake spirits.
And I don't think they are tring to
harm me.
Most of all, I don't want to
become a monk.
Thank you.
So you still don't believe me.
No, last time I got tricked by
...some Taoist monk.
Guess I won't believe any of this again.
That Taoist monk must be incompetent.
Fine, if you don't believe me,
wait till the Dragon Boat Festival;
And you'll know it's all true.
Amitabha Buddha.
High noon sun on Dragon Boat Festival
is unbearable,
Snakes and insects are in panic.
The realgar wine being naturally
ver potent,
Snakes & insects will keep at bay
or suffer from it.
Over here it's the festival preparations,
others are in panic.
The red sun shines brightly,
the scorching heat is unbearable.
It's almost noon;
you better hide, Qingqing!
We'll go through...
bliss and misfortune together.
I can't leave you on your own.
I can't let you suffer all by yourself.
I'm more powerful,
I think I can handle it.
You better go,
don't waste anymore time.
I want to be here with you.
Qingqing.
Dear.
It's been so busy at work these days,
at least we have a day off today.
Have a cup of realgar wine,
let's celebrate the Dragon Boat Festival.
But I can't drink,
not at all.
Just have a sip,
you'll be fine.
I'm pregnant,
I can't take realgar.
That's actually good for you,
...you will be fine.
You should have a few drinks too,
it's refreshing and it detoxicates.
I... I can't drink.
Qingqing, watch out.
Yes.
Dear.
I told you I can't drink.
Just smell it.
No.
It smells so good.
Very well then, just one sip.
- Okay.
- No more.
No more.
Come on.
Are you alright, dear?
What's wrong?
I... I need to lie down.
Dear.
You look terrible.
Is it nausea?
I'm fine.
Don't come in,
I just need to lie down for a while.
My dear, I'm bringing you medicine.
Qingqing, my wife needs help.
Hurry!
Dear.
Take some medicine,
you'll feel better.
Sister.
Master Xu was frightened to death by you.
Where is he?
My dear.
I wanted to repay you.
But I scared you to death
It's all because of Monk Fahai.
It's his fault.
He tried to alienate us.
I didn't want you to suspect,
that's why I drank the wine unwillingly.
This is terrible.
Stop cring, don't be sad.
We must try to save him.
But he's dead.
What can bring him back to life?
Only the glossy ganoderma,
yet it's on the summit of Kunlun Mountain.
Thank you for reminding me,
I'll go right away.
I know the danger I'll face,
but for my husband, I must go.
After I've got the ganoderma,
I'll come back right away.
If I'm not back within three days,
...it means that I'm dead.
In that case, you must leave after
buring my husband.
Master Xu, my sister did this for you.
She might not live.
Qingqing.
Sister.
I'll be off then. Take care of him.
Don't worry. You... just go.
Riding the clouds to Mount Kunlun.
All for the sake of her beloved.
Desperate to bring him back to life,
She'll beg for the venerable old man's
mercy.
How dare you pick-up the ganoderma?
Celestial spirits.
Please wait, let me explain.
You're a thief!
What more do you want to say?
Stop it...
Step back...
It's you, White Snake!
Please spare me, venerable old man.
I'm Bai Suzhen, the sinful.
I tried to steal the ganoderma to save
my husband.
I just hoped to repay him
for saving me in past life,
and now he's dead because of me.
After some thought,
I decided to risk by coming here.
Please have mercy on me;
Allow me to bring this
to the mortal world.
Trust me, I'm not tring to escape,
I don't expect to be spared.
I just want to bring my husband to life.
Then I'll return for my punishment.
I'm willing to die for this.
If you want to save your husband,
you should have told us first.
You've committed a theft,
it's hard to talk your way out.
She's pregnant,
and she didn't mean bad.
I'll let her go this time,
but this won't be let off again.
Give the ganoderma to her,
White Crane, Yellow Deer.
Thank you!
After Bai Suzhen thanked the
venerable old man,
she left in gratitude.
Heading back to the mortal world,
she is hurrying home.
My dear.
You...
My dear...
My dear.
What have you seen?
When I brought you the medicine,
I saw a big white snake on the bed,
...it was so scar.
I've killed the snake,
it's hanging on the tree.
Do you want to take a look?
No.
You better go,
I don't want you to conjure up
crazy stories, go on.
Are you still scared?
Don't worry,
I'll go with you.
Alright then, I'll go.
There, it's hanging on the tree.
Master Xu, look.
It's dead.
Master Xu.
Go back to the room to rest.
You're no monster,
that monk is full of nonsense.
Say, if I was really a monster,
will you stop loving me?
What are you talking about?
We love each other.
I don't care if you were a monster.
Without affection, human is not
as good as a monster.
I'm glad to hear that.
So you are true to me.
Let me tell you the truth now.
I'm indeed a snake spirit.
You've saved me in your past life,
I'm here to repay you.
I hoped we can grow old together.
That we'll forever live happily.
Then came the cold hearted monk Fahai;
he just wouldn't give up.
I don't want anyone to come between us.
I don't want anyone to be in the way.
Telling you the truth is my only option.
Don't worry.
We've been a couple for quite a while,
our love is real.
We don't need to worry.
It doesn't matter whether
you're human or a spirit,
nothing can come between us.
Master Xu.
Good day, master.
It's fate! Here we meet again.
Master.
You can't go back,
you will only be hurt by the monster.
Follow me to Golden Mountain Temple
to become a monk.
That's your only chance to be saved.
Even if my wife is a monster,
I'm not scared of her. She's nice to me.
She revealed her true form
on Dragon Boat Festival,
...and you were scared to death.
I'm here to save you.
Okay, so I was scared to death on
Dragon Boat Festival
...where were you?
You weren't there to save me.
Instead, my wife risked her life
and brought the ganoderma
in order to restore my life.
That's because I knew it wasn't
your time to go yet,
...that's why I wasn't there.
Let's not talk about this.
Follow me to Golden Mountain Temple
to become a monk.
I don't want to be a monk.
Please let me go home.
I've no business with the Buddhist Temple.
Please leave me alone.
Master...
You're so stubborn. Where's Fashan?
- Here, master.
- Master.
Bring him back.
I don't want to go.
I don't want to be a monk.
My dear wife, help me!
Help me!
Did you hear, sister?
Qingqing, he kidnapped my husband.
Hateful monk Fahai!
We haven't done anything wrong
to deserve this.
Qingqing, we must hurry to
the Golden Mountain Temple.
Be careful, Qingqing.
Monk Fahai is ver powerful.
I know.
"Golden Mountain Temple"
Master, please let my husband go.
You're a snake spirit yet
It's an offence on your part
coming to mortal world.
You better turn around while you can,
...or you will be punished.
Xu Xian was once my savior,
I made it up to him by marrying.
Please be kind,
and let my husband go.
How dare you talk about
your personal life?
This is a Buddhist temple.
If I hand Xu Xian over,
you will turn him into a monster too.
We haven't harmed anyone,
what's wrong with me looking for
my husband here?
And tell me what's your grudge,
why are you separating me from my husband?
You're a high rank Buddhist monk,
you should be kind to
all living creatures.
Please don't go over the top,
you should be more forgiving.
I won't be duped by you,
there's no use for the pretty speech.
Unless you move Yangtze River up here
on the mountain,
...you won't see your husband.
He is unreasonable,
mean and arrogant.
Fine, let's do what he wants.
We'll move Yangtze River here.
Then he'll let Xu Xian go.
Amitabha Buddha.
Let me go!
Sister.
Are you alright?
It hurts.
I think it's time to give birth.
What should we do?
We're so close to winning.
Qingqing, I can't hold up anymore.
Sister.
We can't stop now,
or the water will flow back down,
...and we'll drown.
The water!
Let's go!
Come on.
Hurry.
Sister.
My dear.
Xu Xian.
And you are?
Venerable old man.
Please help me.
Save my wife.
Bai Suzhen has failed in her attempt.
Where's my wife?
She's hidden in the woods.
I'll show you the way.
I'll let you two see each other.
Thank you, master.
Close your eyes.
Yes.
Qingqing.
Sister.
My dear...
Listen, Qingqing.
My dear.
My husband is here.
Dear wife...
My dear.
My beloved!
Dear wife...
My dear husband.
My dear husband...
Dear wife...
- My beloved!
- Dear wife... you...
How did you escape?
The venerable old man saved me.
Sweetheart.
Thank you, venerable old man.
Hurry, sister.
You better hurry.
Are you alright?
It's all because of you.
Qingqing.
I cannot believe you.
My sister has suffered all because of you.
Think it over, Xu Xian.
We've risked everything for you.
Sister.
Dear wife...
Move away.
Sister...
Qingqing...
Dear wife...
Don't come any closer.
A bit further.
A little bit more.
Turn your head.
Qingqing.
Sister...
Sister.
Dear...
My dear wife...
Dear.
Sister, you have a bonny boy!
My dear, you've borne enough hardships...
I want to look at my son.
Fahai is here, take the baby.
Honey.
Hurry and leave.
We'll go through this together,
Let's go!
You better leave, dear.
No.
I don't think I can go anywhere.
Qingqing, you...
Take him to Hangzhou,
ask my aunt to take care of him.
And I'll have an heir,
also someone to revenge for me.
Listen to me, go now!
Or you won't be able to make it.
Sister.
Leave, Qingqing.
Qingqing.
For your own personal grudge
you stirred up trouble.
By drowning Golden Mountain
you tried to harm others.
You've done the worst crime,
what do you have to say now?
Why did I do that for?
Who's really behind this?
I've done serious damage,
but you should share the punishment
with me.
You're a real snake spirit.
Still tring to bite at your time
of death.
I'm generous enough to let you live,
so you can live the rest of life
in an earthen bowl.
She's just given birth.
Have mercy on her.
Let her go!
We'll forever be grateful.
She's nothing but a pest.
Why won't you give up?
You refuse to come to your senses,
...do you really wish to die?
You have no conscience.
You're the pest.
I'm not scared of death.
I'll fight you.
Dear...
Snake Spirit, you aren't going anywhere.
Amitabha Buddha.
My dear...
Dear wife...
Leaping out from a foggy cloud of
miserable gloom...
They soared into a sunny day
with gentle breeze.
In a different world of emotions.
We'll never be apart.
Never again shall we be apart.