www.youtube.com/watch?v=omLgJe9cnCw
What more can I do, there's nothing I haven't tried
Still it's so hard for her to notice
I've tried hard to be straight
There's nothing left I can say
If only she would look my way
She don't know me (she don't know)
She don't see me (she don't care)
She can't hear me (she can't hear)
Can not help me (she don't want)
She don't want me like I want her ( like I want her)
I've got to tell her ( got to tell her)
That I love her ( that I love her)
She doesn't even know my name
I dream of when she'll be mine
I dream of crossing that line
And holding her so tender
Dreaming it could come true
So many things I would do
If only you'd give me a chance
She don't know me (she don't know)
She don't see me (she don't care)
She can't hear me (she can't hear)
Can not help me (she don't want)
She don't want me like I want her (like I want her)
I've got to tell her ( got to tell her)
That I love her
She doesn't even know my name
She don't know me ( she don't know)
She don't see me ( she don't care)
She can't hear me ( she can't hear)
Can not help me ( she don't want)
She don't want me ( like I want her) like I want her
I've got to tell her ( got to tell her)
That I love her
She don't know me ( she don't know)
She don't see me ( she don' know)
She can't hear me