Okay.
One picture and we're history.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Come on.
Man, do we have to do this?
You want everyone in school
to think we're chicken?
I could live with that.
You wuss. Come on.
I don't see anything. Do you?
No, I don't see anything.
Let's just take the picture
and get out of here.
Fine. Here, take the picture.
Wait, I should bein the picture, too,
or no one will believe I was here.
Shut up and take the picture!
You take the picture.
You take it! You!
Guys, don't fight.
I'll take the picture.
Say "cheese."
A ghost!
"...and to the Save the Dolphins Foundation
$11 million.
"To the Save the Pumas
Foundation, $1.2 million.
"To the Patagonian
Wasp Salvation Fund,
"$1.4 million.
"To the Dyslexic
Dalmatians Foundation..."
To hell with the livestock.
What did the old stiff leave me?
I believe that what the bereaved
is trying to express
is that the sudden death
of her only father
has left a great gaping void
in her bank... in her life.
And Carrigan wonders what he has left her
to fill it up with.
Let's see.
"Bobcats, owls,
"snakes,
"daughter Carrigan,
"Whipstaff Manor in Maine."
And?
And I'm late for lunch,
so if you'll excuse me...
Are you telling me that I just spent the
last two daysholding his clammy hand
waiting for him to kick it,and all
I get is one lousy piece of property?
No, it was lousy 50 years ago.
Now it's condemned. Enjoy.
Wait a minute.
This is not fair!
I'll contest, and then I'll drag you and
all of those damned dolphins into court.
Knock yourself out.
Dibs, this is all your fault.
As usual. If you would have
just forged the damn will.
This is condemned
seafront property.
Dibs, don't you get it?
Flipper got more money than me.
Carrigan! The deed's in there!
My God.
"Buccaneers and buried gold,
"Whipstaff doth
a treasure hold."
Treasure?
Dibs, you idiot! Get it out.
I knew that place was worth something.
There's treasure in that house
and finally, I'm going to
get what I deserve.
Carrigan,
I think I need a doctor.
There's plenty in Maine.
So, what do you think?
I think
you're going to get wet.
Wait! Carrigan!
Dibs, light!
What a dump.
This place is fabulous.
You could just
do so much with it.
I know it's a bit spooky. Dibs.
Hello.
Who is it?
Afraid I can't answer that.
Why not?
It's kind of hard to explain.
Is he the caretaker?
Are you the caretaker?
No.
Is he a drug dealer?
Is he... Are you a transient?
No, not exactly.
Then tell him to show himself.
Show yourself!
Here's the thing. If I do, don't scream, okay?
I get that a lot.
Are you a burglar?
I must warn you
that I am armed.
Hello?
Cut the crap. If you don't show yourself,
I'll have you arrested for trespassing.
Okay, calm down, lady.
Here I come!
Hi! I'm Casper.
No, you shouldn't do that,
or you'll wake the...
Too late.
So tell me.
You have experience?
I have quite a bit of experience. Not,
you know, like, exactly doing it,
but I've studied it,and I've talked to
people who have done it.
I've seen the videos, and I feel very
confident that with my knowledge
I could do it, no problem.
Then you can handle this?
It's like no problem whatsoever.
Piece of cake. Piece of crumb cake.
Well? How did it go?
It was fine. Was no problem.
Piece of cake.
Who you gonna call?
Someone else.
What do we do now?
What do I usually do when something
stands in my way?
Are you sure we're not going
a tad overboard here?
Dibs, I have huffed and puffed. Now I
want to rip this place down.
I want my treasure. They can't haunt a
pile of rubble, for Christ's sake.
People, please!
You're sweaty male construction types,
for Christ's sake!
Dibs, do something!
Come on, get out of there!
Charlie, quick, keep running and don't
look back! Run, Charlie!
Wait! They were just kidding!
Honest!
Every time.
All I want is a friend.
Did you ever feel the way
Priscilla Cow felt
that you'd like to be
completely different?
Almost everybody feels like
that once in a while.
But most of the time
I hope you can be glad
to be yourself.
That's really
something to celebrate.
A ghost!
More on the Pentagon playboys
as the story unfolds.
But, now...
step aside, Sigmund Freud.
Jump back, Joyce Brothers.
It's Dr. James Harvey,
therapist to the dead?
Are you depressed? Are you anxious?
Are you lonely?
Do you need someone to talk to?
No problem, if you're a ghost!
You can call them ghosts if you like
or as I prefer, the living impaired.
But the bottom line is,
they need help sometimes
just like the rest of us.
After the sudden unexpected death
of his wife, Amelia,
Dr. Harvey gave up
conventional psychiatry
and some say
conventional sanity.
Now, along with his loner daughter, Kat,
short for Kathy
Doc Harvey travels from town to town,
searching for paranoid poltergeists,
scared specters,
the depressed and the dead.
How do you feel about your father's
livelihood?
Please don't ask me
any questions.
- Do you believe in ghosts?
- Ever seen one?
Does your father hurt you
in any way?
He's my father.
Could you just talk to us?
Look, it's the first day
of school
and I'm sure I'll have homework,
so could you please...
Carrigan.
What part don't you understand?
No, not "I ate fish."
I hate fish.
Don't you people have
cows here?
Listen, I have had
a long and trying day.
Do you think that you could bring me a pint
of Häagen-Dazs ice cream, rum raisin
and a Diet Pepsi?
Think you can handle that?
Now you want me to hold. Fine.
And with therapy they can begin to
process this pain.
They can pack up their emotional baggage,
and they can move on.
My Harry passed away five years ago,
but he was so miserable.
His spirit would not
leave the apartment.
So I called Dr. Harvey.
He came over
and in a few weeks Harry left
smiling.
The living-impaired
are known for haunting us.
My question is,
what's haunting them?
It's a lack of resolution.
Ghosts are simply spirits
without resolution.
With unfinished business.
And it's my job to find out what that is.
And so Dr. James Harvey
continues his work
dragging his daughter along for the ride.
This week they're in Santa Fe,
but next week, "boo" knows?
Now, from the ghost shrink
to shrinking...
Yes, I'm still here.
Get me Santa Fe.
That's life!
That's what all the people say
You're ridin' high in April
Shot down in
I'm sorry about
your Cactus Spooners.
Crooners.
I don't care what they said,
you are not demented.
You're a picture
of mental health.
They were talking about you.
Try explaining afterlife therapy to
a bunch of junior high kids.
Some people go through life
never questioning the norm.
But you and I, we're doing something
extraordinary with our lives.
No, we aren't doing anything.
You're the one who's been packing up my stuff
and moving me around the country.
I mean, in two years,
I have been to nine different schools.
I've eaten
in nine different cafeterias.
I mean, I can't even remember
anyone's name.
For once,
I would just like to be
in one place long enough
to make a friend.
Honey, you will.
Right.
I mean, come on, we're moving to
Friendship, Maine.
Even I might make one.
You better, Dad,
'cause a single guy your age
is more likely to become a bank hostage
than to make new friends.
You sound like your mother.
You're not gonna find her.
Mom's not a ghost, Dad.
Yes, she is.
She has unfinished business.
There's no such thing
as ghosts.
I'll tell you what
you go with me
this one last time.
If I don't find whati I'm looking for
then it's over.
No more moving,
no more ghost mining.
You promise?
I promise.
Deal.
It's not so bad.
If you're Stephen King.
Dr. Harvey, hello.
I'm Carrigan Crittenden.
And this is Dibs.
Hello.
I'm a close personal friend.
And this is my daughter, Kat.
His close personal daughter.
How nice to meet you, Kat.
Very nice to meet you.
You have a beautiful daughter.
Very beautiful.
We are very happy that you could come
all the way to Whipstaff.
Very happy.
The both of us.
You're kind of hurting my face.
Sorry. Now, Dr. Harvey
exactly what kind of
time frame are you looking at?
Please tell me you'll just go in the house
and spray and that's it.
No. As with a traditional
psychological cure
it can take weeks
or even years...
Excuse me!
Did you just say
the word "years"?
It's conceivable.
No, it isn't.
Days is conceivable.
Weeks, maybe.
Possibly.
Months, no. Years, forget it.
Forget it. Dibs, check.
Get the bouquet.
Now, Dr. Harvey
I will be watching you
very closely.
These are for you.
Have a lovely night.
Wow.
It's her. She's here.
She's in my house. I did it!
What if she likes me?
What if she doesn't?
"Hi, I'm Casper. I'm a ghost."
No, that's total disaster.
"Yo, I'm Casper.
What's up? Give me four."
God, I'd kill for a pinkie.
See? That was easy.
Yeah.
Pennies should hold for now
but we ought to get a box of 20 amps
in the morning.
Right, yeah,
20s should be fine.
All right, I'm gonna
go find a room, Dad.
You gonna be all right alone?
If I'm not back in 10 days,
send a search party.
"Stretch"
"Fatso"
and "Stinkie"?
Man, they had cruel parents.
I wonder where Doc and Dopey sleep.
Dad, I found my room!
There's a girl on my bed.
Yes!
Space master! In here.
It's very scary.
Have you seen
any surprises yet?
Please. This is
the deadest place yet.
This is a nice room.
Right. This place is
a freak's holiday.
Mom belongs over here.
How about if I help you unpack?
Why bother? We'll just be repacking
in two weeks anyway, right?
I'm kidding.
This place is fine.
Good.
Night, bucket.
Night, Dad.
We're gonna be glad we came.
You watch.
Hi.
Man!
Perfect first impression.
What a jerk!
Better?
Honey!
Honey, what?
Dad, I saw a ghost!
It was a real, live ghost! Slow down.
What are you saying?
I saw a ghost.
And it had a head, it was round, it was
white and see-through, and...
Wait a minute. Now maybe...
Dad, please.
Do not think I'm as crazy as I thought
you were. I promise.
No, but remember,
ghosts can't hurt you, okay?
They're simply spirits with unfinished
business, all right?
Let's just see about this
ghost, all right?
Come here. Come on.
Over here. Check here.
See? No ghost there.
And then we can check
over here, all right?
No, there's no ghost in there.
We can even check over here.
There. See?
Pleasure to meet you, sir.
Dad, put me down!
This is insane.
What are you doing?
I can walk, you know.
My God, this is big.
Dad? What?
We're in a closet.
Right now I want you to stay in here
no matter what you hear, okay?
Okay.
Wait! What?
Dad, I'm sorry.
For what?
For not believing you. For thinking
you were a total loser.
Apologize later.
Blew it!
Uh-oh.
It's them.
- Giddyup there!
- Go, horsie!
Man oh, man, them ponies run faster
when we go down to Belmont.
Here, Flicka.
Hey, guys. Have fun?
Look, it's Casper!
Now on a scale of 1 to 10,
10 being fun and 1 being you
yeah, we had fun.
Giddyup there.
Say, Bulbhead, why ain't you inside
doing your chores?
Yeah, where's dinner? I'm starving.
Look at me, I'm wasting away here.
I know. How about you guys relax out here
and tonight we'll eat alfresco?
Sounds great. Who's that?
Short-sheet, you wouldn't be trying to
keep us out of the house, would you?
No!
I can see right through that bulbous
little head of yours.
It's just such a lovely night.
I thought we'd have fun just eating
under the harvest moon.
Shine on, shine on harvest moon
Up in the sky
Bye-bye!
Hold it.
Fatso, you smell something?
Yeah.
No, besides him.
Hello?
No need to be afraid.
Yeah, right, don't be afraid.
I'd like to make contact with you, but just
one little thing, please.
Don't pop out from under a rug or through
a keyhole. No spooking.
Let's get beyond that.
I would like to approach you.
Now I'm coming in the room.
I'm in the room.
Can you deal with that?
Dive!
Dad?
I'm gonna kill you, your mama
and all her
bridge-playing friends.
You think you got it tough?
I got a facelift.
There was one
just like it underneath.
Dad?
Boys,
we got a closet case here!
Smell-o-gram!
Sushi, anyone?
California roll coming up!
All for one and one for all!
Catch your pants
before they fall!
On the runway, we have Dr. James Harvey
wearing smashing underwear.
Marky Mark he's not!
You are good.
Stop. It's you.
Are we scary or what?
And it looks as if we're gonna go into
sudden death overtime.
Anybody for
a little shish ke-doc?
I am.
Who do you think you are
defiling our domicile?
Dr. James Harvey,
your therapist.
Dad!
Are you okay?
Dad.
And he's down for the count.
A winner by a clean stink out!
Get back.
What the hell is that thing?
Not the nose!
I'm being hosed!
No!
This sucks.
Dad? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Why don't we go regroup?
Get your hand out of my mouth!
I found half a Twinkie!
Who let one? Who do you think?
Who's got their
pointy head in my...
That's not my head.
You know, fellas, we're never
this close anymore.
Morning. No, please don't scream.
I promise, I won't hurt you.
I'm a ghost. Yes, I admit it,
but I'm a friendly ghost.
You have to trust me. If you scream,
you'll wake up my uncles
and they get awfully cranky.
I'm gonna let you go now. Okay?
You're so cold.
Yeah, but it saves
in the heating, though.
Come on.
It's okay.
I can see right through you.
It kind of happens
when you don't have any skin.
What are you made of?
You know that tingling feeling
when your foot falls asleep?
I think I'm made of that.
Sunny-side up
kind of makes me yak.
No problem.
So, can you go invisible?
That one's easy.
It's fresh.
Go ahead.
I've never done this before.
Me, neither.
Can you hurt me? No.
Can I hurt you?
No.
Cool.
Morning, Dr. Harvey.
Some breakfast?
You okay?
Good.
How about a paper? The New York Times?
The Journal? Hong Kong Press?
Sure. Coming at you.
Hope you're hungry.
I love the smell of fleshies
in the morning.
I'm melting.
Auntie Phlegm.
What a world!
They're gone. What happened?
They must have crossed over.
Don't think so!
Guess again, Bonebag!
Fellas. Good morning.
Casper.
How dare you serve these air-sucking
intruders before us.
I was just... Give me my
meal!
Okay.
I feel like Oprah on hiatus.
You look like Oprah on hiatus.
Ketchup, please.
You know what the problem is?
Casper's got no respect for us.
After all we've done
for the little glowworm.
What the hell do you think
you're doing, Bulbhead?
This floor used to be
dirty enough to eat off of.
But we have company.
Yeah? Company loves misery.
You guys are disgusting,
obnoxious creeps.
Thank you.
I mean, what's your problem?
He's just cleaning the floor.
Shut up, Skinbag.
Piss off. Take a hike.
- Get a grave.
- Honey!
School thing and you don't
want to be late...
- Drop dead!
- Too late!
You go have a lot of fun.
I know you will.
All right, guys, we've obviously gotten off
on the wrong foot here.
Now, you know and I know that you
really shouldn't be here.
So I'll tell you what.
Why don't you go ahead
and finish your meal
and we can meet in my office
and start the process of
crossing over.
What do you say?
It's your hour.
Watch it!
Amber, wait up!
Had that locker last year.
Thanks.
My name's Vic.
Kat.
Coming, Vic?
Okay, gang, let's settle down!
Put a lid on it!
I got a couple of
announcements to make.
First. The asbestos removal from the
gym is taking a little longer than planned.
So we're gonna have to
push back the Halloween Dance
just by a couple of months.
As most of you know, my parents have
finished the new boathouse.
So I'm sure it'd be no problem
having the party at my place.
Great. That's done.
Secondly, we have
a new student today.
I'd like you all to
meet Harvey Kathleen.
Would you like to come up
and say hi to everyone for me?
Why don't you tell us something special
about yourself, Kathleen?
It's Kat.
I guess I just moved here
with my dad from Santa Fe
and Friendship seems like
a pretty friendly place.
So where are you guys living?
In outer space?
No. Whipstaff.
You've heard of it.
You actually live there?
Yeah, I mean...
I know it looks kind of funky and stuf
from the outside and everything
but, I mean... I don't know,
inside it's kind of cool.
Yeah, if you drink blood.
Mr. Curtis, check this.We're dead for
the Halloween Dance, right?
This girl has a seriously creepy house
with room to spare.
Wait a minute. I thought we were having
the party at my place.
Okay, we'll take a vote.
Whoever wants the party
at my house, raise your hand.
Whipstaff?
"Johns Hopkins University."
Very impressive.
- Very.
- Pull!
Not this one.
Thank you, gentlemen.
What a dish, Doc.
The little missus, perhaps?
Fatso, you animal!
Is she available, Doc?
She's my wife, Amelia.
She's deceased.
Even better.
But we're not here
to talk about me.
See? Now don't you
feel just awful?
I was just goofing.
Don't be goofing on Amelia.
She's as nice a person as they come.
She's always treated you right, Stinkie.
I got no complaints. She's always
been an angel to me.
Wait a minute.
What are you saying?
I'm saying she's
a peach. None better. Why?
You've actually seen her?
What, you think I'm blind?
Of course, I've seen her.
Who hasn't?
What, you're not looking
for her, are you, Doc?
That's not really the focus
of our sessions here, is it?
But as long as you
raise the issue
you wouldn't have a way of contacting
others like yourselves
would you?
I didn't think so.
Now that's not generally
allowed there, Doc.
I mean, you got to
go through channels.
Yeah, paperwork.
Red tape. A holy mess,
you know what I'm saying?
But for you, I don't know, maybe we
could work something out.
You keep that ghoul Crittenden
off our backs
and I'd say we got a deal.
Right, boys?
Deal?
Deal.
Fatso, you know
where Amelia floats. Go.
It's that easy, huh?
We got a ghost-to-ghost
network.
We share haunting stories.
We throw parties.
The parties are always
pretty dead, though.
SharePirate.Com Subs
That was fast.
I think it's for you, Doc.
Go.
Amelia?
My man!
What are you doing...
I mean, hi.
Can I come in?
No. It's so much
nicer out here in the flesh...
Fresh air.
So did you ask your dad
about the party?
Yeah.
He kind of hit the ceiling, but I think
it's gonna be okay.
Cool. So listen
if you're not hooked up with anybody
else, you wanna... I don't know
you wanna hang out
with me at the party?
I'd love to.
All right. Cool.
All right, see you.
Okay.
Did you ask her? Yeah.
And she actually believed you.
This really bites.
No, it's absolutely perfect.
See? I'm a good dancer.
I don't need a costume.
I'm always
the life of the party.
Casper! Listen,
I know you want to go.
Come on, we'd have
a great time together.
Casper, I have a date.
What's this Vic guy
got that I don't?
A pulse.
Big fleshy deal.
A tan.
Very bad for your skin.
How about a reflection?
Okay, but can he do this?
Come with me
if you want to live.
Casper, no. Don't!
Casper, no. Oh, my God.
High, this is very high!
Casper!
Casper, this is beautiful.
I come here every night.
Alone?
What were you like
when you were alive?
I was...
I don't remember.
You don't remember anything
from your life?
No.
So, nothing?
You don't remember
what school you went to?
How old you were?
Your favorite song?
What about your dad?
Not even your mom?
Is that bad?
No. It's just kind of sad.
I wonder why you don't
remember anything.
Guess 'cause
when you're a ghost
life doesn't matter
that much anymore.
So you forget.
Sometimes I worry
that I'm starting to forget.
Forget what?
My mom.
Just certain things.
The sound of her
making breakfast downstairs.
The way she put on
her lipstick, so carefully.
I do remember.
She always used Ivory soap.
And when she'd hug me,
I'd breathe her in so deep
and I remember,
before I'd go to sleep
she'd whisper in my ear,
"Stardust in the eyes,
rosy cheeks,
"and a happy girl
in the morning."
If my mom's a ghost,
did she forget about me?
No. She'd never forget you.
If I were alive
would you go to
the Halloween Dance with me?
Can I keep you?
Casper, close the window.
It's cold.
Hey, Dad.
I found your Visa card.
Where was it?
In your wallet.
I was thinking,
maybe I could use it
to buy this perfect costume
I saw in a store downtown.
You always made your costume.
No, Mom did.
I think I could come up
with something pretty good.
Why don't we just roll you
in aluminum foil and you
could go as a leftover?
Don't worry.
You always look cute.
I don't wanna look cute.
Cute's like when you're
nine years old
and you've got papier-mâché
around your head.
I wanna look
nice.
Like date nice.
Really?
Honey, you know,
I think maybe it's time
that we sat down...
It's a little late
for that, Dad.
How late?
Don't worry, not that late.
Good.
You know that I would
love to buy you
everything that you wanted
but until Miss Crittenden
pays me, that thing is
pretty worthless.
That's okay.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sure I can come up
with something perfect
for the party.
It's my party,
and I'll die if I want to
Die if I want to
Dad, please.
Whatever you do,
don't let those guys crash it.
I think they're actually
getting to be quite
focused now.
You will die, too,
when it happens to you
Big finish.
Scream or sugar?
The patient has
finally arrived.
Late again, I see.
Could this be an expression
of hostility, Doc?
It's your hour, Freud.
What, so silent?
No pearls of wisdom today,
Doc?
Come on, Doc.
Stay tough, don't stop.
Come on, Doc,
hang with us homeboys.
Wait a second.
What? You ain't thinking
about packing it in now,
are you, Doc?
We're just
starting to have fun.
It ain't often we meet
a bonebag as amusing as you.
Boys, this is serious.
I think the doc is having
one of them fleshy breakdowns.
Time for drastic measures.
You think
we should sing a song?
No. I think it's time
we gave the doc
our own prescription.
But what about the party?
The party'll have to wait.
Are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Gentlemen.
Happy hour. Happy hour.
Ninety-nine
bottles of beer on the wall
Ninety-nine bottles of beer
Here's to dead guys!
This is an outrage.
This is appalling.
You pay a man to get ghosts
out of the house
and what does he do?
He gets the ghosts
out of the house.
Exactly.
It's about time.
Look familiar?
I know this!
I had five fingers. I remember.
Hootie!
And wait!
Check it out.
Hands up, Kat!
It was my mom's.
Can I?
Go ahead.
It's perfect.
Do you think I could
wear it to the party tonight?
Casper?
I begged and begged my dad
to get me this sled.
He acted like I couldn't even
have it 'cause I didn't know
how to ride it.
Then one morning I came down
for breakfast and there
it was, just for me.
For no reason at all.
I took it out and went
sledding all day.
My dad said that's enough but
I couldn't stop.
I was having so much fun.
Then it got late, it got dark.
It got cold
and I got sick.
My dad got sad.
What's it like to die?
Like being born.
Only backwards.
I remember, I didn't go
where I was supposed to go.
I just stayed behind
so my dad wouldn't be lonely.
Is that your dad?
"McFadden claimed that
he was haunted by
the ghost of his dead son
"and that he invented
a machine to bring him
back to life...
"The Lazarus."
Sorry. I guess we'll have
to take the long way.
Hurry up! Come on!
My dad hid it
so no one could find it.
But I remember where it is!
Wait till you see it.
Don't you know a shortcut?
You got it.
Casper, no.
Wall! Human! Stop!
Hey, over here.
Go ahead. Sit down.
I would hold on.
Why?
Casper!
Well?
What was that?
The "Up and At 'Em Machine."
My dad was a great inventor
but he had trouble
getting going in the morning.
Didn't he ever
hear of caffeine?
What is all this?
My dad's lab.
Kind of a slob, wasn't he?
Here, he could do
whatever he wanted to.
No matter how busy he was
he would drop everything
to play pirates with me.
Man, we had so much fun!
Aye, matey.
Buccaneers and buried gold.
Whipstaff doth a treasure hold.
Come on.
So where's this Lazarus thing?
You're looking at it.
Down there?
That's useful.
I know there's a way
to get it going.
I just can't... What about that?
That?
That's the vault.
Wait! It's got to be this!
Hey, I did it!
Lazarus.
What is this? Careful!
That's what makes
the whole thing work.
Kind of an instant
primordial soup mix.
It's what brings
ghosts back to life.
Just enough for one.
Pull the lever.
Which one?
I don't know. Try one.
Casper.
I'm gonna be alive.
How am I gonna do this?
I couldn't even
get my Easy Bake oven to work.
Casper?
Am I alive?
Do you have any idea
what this means?
Yes!
No.
You don't have
to be scared of death anymore.
One minute you're a ghost
next you're back on your feet
free to come and go
as you please.
Hell, you could even
fly through...
Walls!
Thick walls.
Thick as steel.
Certainly could get
to whatever's
behind those walls.
Like a treasure, for example?
Then snap, crackle, pop,
you're back alive and on your
way to the Riviera.
If you were a ghost.
If you were.
Damn it, Dibs.
This won't hurt a bit.
Stop being such a weenie!
It's just business. Come on!
If you would just...
So there you are.
Dibs, you're taking this
way too personally.
Wait!
Carrigan?
Are you a ghost yet?
Carrigan!
What a tragic waste.
She had my favorite sunglasses.
Not so fast, little man.
The bitch is back.
Warden threw a party
at the county jail
The prison band was there and
they began to wail
The band was playin' hard
the joint began to swing
You shoulda heard those
knocked out jailbirds sing
Let's rock
This Dr. Harvey's got
a lot of spirit, you know
what I'm saying?
Yeah, but he's got his
whole miserable life
ahead of him.
So we could do him a favor
and put him out of his misery.
Yeah. Good idea.
We've been the ghostly trio
long enough.
Time to make it a quartet.
Can I just say something here?
Get a little personal?
Yeah. Why not?
Well, you know.
I just got to tell you
you guys remind me of
what it's like
to hang out with the boys.
I mean
you are absolutely there
for each other.
I mean
you look life
right in the face.
You say, "I'm a ghost.
I don't need you."
You know what?
I'm gonna tell that
Miss Critten Picken...
Crichton Critten.
I'm gonna tell that lady
you ain't going anywhere.
It's your house.
You're haunting it.
Possession is nine-tenths
of the law...
No. Yes.
No.
Yes.
I didn't think so at first
but you guys are great.
I love you.
No.
What a sweetheart.
I can't croak him now.
Me, neither. No way.
All right, boys.
The night is young.
We are going to clean out
every bar this town has got!
We're gonna booze it
until we lose it.
Come on.
I think my ears just popped.
Come to mama!
My treasure!
You mean my treasure.
Miss Crittenden?
In the flesh.
Well, in a couple of minutes.
Dibs! What are you doing?
This is no time to shave!
Helping you. Remember?
Remember what?
This!
You stole that.
That's Casper's.
So sue me!
Dibs! The capsule, now!
Coming. I'm coming, okay?
Keep away from me!
Here!
Jump in!
Perfect.
We're here.
Okay.
Hi. Come on in.
This is the room.
Stay together, you'll be safe,
and I'll be right back.
Amber, do we have to do this?
She wants a Halloween party.
She's gonna get
a Halloween party.
That's my treasure!
Stay back! Keep away from me!
Casper.
Don't come near me,
you spiteful spook.
I'll knock you into
the next world!
Come on. Let's go.
Hey, Poppin Fresh.
It's my turn in the oven!
Dibs! Get this thing cooking,
you flaccid little worm, you!
How kind of you to drop in.
You know, if there's one thing
I've learned from you
it's always kick them
when they're down.
And, baby,
you're six feet under.
Oh, what a shame.
Sorry, sweetheart.
We're through.
I am not gonna forget this,
you ungrateful lousy
little worm, you!
You can haunt me all you want
but it's gonna be
in a great, big,
expensive house
with lovely purple wallpaper
and great big green carpets.
And a little dog
called Carrigan.
A bitch, just like you!
I got the power!
I got the treasure!
And you have a flight to catch.
Any other takers?
No. But aren't you
forgetting something?
What?
Your unfinished business.
My what?
You know unfinished business.
All ghosts have
unfinished business.
That's why
they don't cross over.
Unfinished business?
I have no unfinished business.
I have my treasure, my mansion.
I have everything!
I'm just perfect!
Wait, I lied!
I have unfinished business.
Lots of unfinished business.
I'm not ready to
cross over yet!
Wait! You tricked me,
you rotten little brats!
No!
My treasure!
A ball? That's your treasure?
Are you kidding?
It's autographed by
Duke Snider
of the Brooklyn Dodgers.
My favorite player.
Casper
it's time.
Honey, I'm home!
Dad?
No. What have you done to him?
Nothing.
He's just a little dead.
I'm free!
I've never felt so good
in my life!
I can fly!
Rookie.
Stinkie, work with him.
Dad?
Who's the girl?
Dad, it's me. It's Kat!
Kat?
Kat Ballou?
Katatonic?
Katastrophic?
Kreplach soup?
Flash flood alert.
Don't you remember?
Yeah, I remember!
No, this.
Kat.
Sweetheart.
What have I done?
Kat, don't cry.
Please.
Come on, Dr. Harvey.
You need this more than I do.
Casper.
This is the way it's got to be.
Dad?
Honey.
It felt like
the strangest dream.
I thought we almost
lost each other
for a minute there.
Oh, bucket.
Your party started without you.
Your date's probably waiting.
Maybe we should get going.
Where are we?
Well, go ahead.
What about you?
This is your party.
Go do your thing.
Go hang or chill
or kick it,
or whatever you call it.
I think you got a date
out there.
Thanks, Dad.
I hope no one saw that.
Hold still.
I'm trying.
Could you weigh any more?
Just shut up
and get your head down.
You got to see this.
People are gonna freak.
Let me see.
Cool.
Thank you.
You're... That's right.
Kat's mom?
Are you an angel?
That was a very noble thing
you did tonight, Casper.
I know Kat
will never forget it.
She needs her father.
And I know yours
will never forget it either.
You've fulfilled his
greatest dream, Casper
and I know
he is very proud of you.
And for what you've done
I'm giving you
your dream in return.
But it's just for tonight.
Sort of a Cinderella deal.
So I have until midnight?
Ten.
Hey! Cinderella
got until midnight.
Cinderella wasn't 12 years old.
I told you I was a good dancer.
Can I keep you?
Casper?
Hello, James.
Amelia.
It's all right.
It's just me.
I thought I'd have
a hundred things
to say when I...
How?
Let's just say you know
three crazy ghosts
who kept their word.
James, I know
you've been
searching for me.
But there's something
you have to understand.
You and Kat loved me
so well when I was alive
that I have no
unfinished business.
Please don't let me be yours.
But, Amelia
I don't...
I don't really know
what I'm doing.
What parent does?
James, Kat is growing up
beautifully because of you.
No wonder I miss you so much.
Just a couple of things,
though.
Don't pick up the extension
every time she gets
a phone call.
French fries are not
a breakfast food.
And don't ask her
to wear a T-shirt under...
Under her bathing suit.
I know.
Our daughter is a teenager.
A teenager.
Wait.
Where are you going?
Where I can watch over
both of you
until we're together again.
Good-bye, James.
Casper?
Boo?
Not bad for my first party,
huh?
Couldn't have been better.
It ain't over yet.
Boys?
Casper the friendly ghost
The friendliest ghost you know
Though grown-ups
might look at him in fright
The children all love him so
Casper the friendly ghost
He couldn't be bad or mean
You know, he jump and play
Sing and dance all day
The friendliest ghost
you've ever seen
He always say "Hello"
And he's really glad to meet ya
Wherever he may go
You know, he's kind to
every living creature
Grown-ups don't understand
Why children
all love him the most
But kids all know
that he loves them so
Casper the friendly ghost
Casper, your friendly
Your friendly
He always say "Hello"
He's always glad to meet ya
Wherever he may go
He's kind to
every living creature
Grown-ups don't understand
Why children
all love him the most
But kids all know
he loves them so
Casper the friendly ghost