Puppet, sir? Only 10 piastres.
They're crap, squirrel. They fall apart
before you're out of the door.
Five then, sir. It's handmade!
Please? My sister.
She's very, very sick.
I know your sister.
She's peddling in the next bar over.
Do you know my mother?
- Nope.
- She's very, very sick.
I'll give you two.
That's a bad idea, you know.
Like feeding pigeons.
- Do I know you?
- My name is Semelier.
I work for a private collector of rare
antiquities. I cabled you last week.
Yes.
And I didn't answer.
There's been a discovery in East Africa.
A Christian church, circa 5 A.D.
No, that's not possible.
The Byzantine Empire had adopted
Christianity at that time...
- ...but they never got that far south.
- Nevertheless, there it sits.
The British have financed a dig
to uncover this church.
We believe a rare object waits inside.
We'd like you to find it
and bring it back to us.
So you think I'm a thief?
Now you think I'm a thief
and a whore.
No...
...simply a man who's lost faith
in everything except himself.
You know nothing about me.
An Oxford-educated archeologist,
an expert in religious icons.
You were a priest before the war.
So, what happened?
This is a leather impression
of the artifact we're looking for.
A representation of a mythical demon.
It's Sumerian.
What makes you think
it's in a church in Africa?
Major Granville in Nairobi
is in charge of the dig.
He's been persuaded to let you join it.
You're assuming that I will say yes.
You already have.
March!
Left. Left, right, left.
Left, left. Left, right, left. Left...
Mr. Merrin, sir.
The major will see you now.
Beautiful, aren't they?
It's a hobby from school days.
Works wonders for the nerves.
You should try it sometime.
What can you tell me about the dig?
The location is a remote area
of the Turkana district called Derati.
It was discovered
several months ago...
...by a detachment of my men
on maneuvers there.
When the powers that be realized
its importance, they organized a dig.
So, what have they learned so far?
That it's a church
where no church should be.
This is Father Francis.
He'll be accompanying you to Derati.
It's a pleasure to finally meet you,
Father Merrin.
- I've read all your work at seminary.
- It's Mr. Merrin.
I was especially impressed
with your treatise on the Roman rituals.
I'm no longer a part of that.
But I'm sure you didn't come here
to discuss Catholic rituals.
I was actually headed to Kenya
on missionary work...
...when Rome learned of the find.
They that the site's religious aspect
have proper consideration.
Hm.
How come you've opened
the site to the Vatican?
We haven't...
...officially.
You're both my guests.
Tell me, have you any theories on
who might have built this church?
Well, not until I've seen it.
Surely the Vatican has some record
of its creation?
No, I'm afraid not.
We're as in the dark about it
as you are.
How long have you been
with the dig, Chuma?
Since the beginning.
The British hired me as an interpreter.
What happened here?
Plague. Ravaged the valley 50 years ago.
How many died?
All of them.
I'm Lankester Merrin.
Agent Granville should've contacted you
about my joining the dig.
He did.
Is something bothering you, mate?
No. I'd like to see the dig site
as soon as possible.
- Do you drink, Merrin?
- I shouldn't.
But my will is weak.
Then you might just survive this place.
I understand you've uncovered the church
dome but that progress has slowed down.
You could say that. Right, doctor?
- I'm Sarah Novak. Nice to meet you.
- Lankester... Lankester Merrin.
You still haven't made it
by my room, doctor.
I've been having this swelling...
...in the evening. Thought you might
have something I could put on it.
How about a muzzle?
So how are the interior
excavations coming on?
- They're not.
- No?
Has the structure collapsed?
No, the church is perfect,
but none of the men will enter.
- Those we have left, anyway.
- Why is that?
I shall be leaving for the dig
in five minutes.
Pleasant fellow.
- What's wrong with his face?
- Other than it's attached to his body?
Could be an allergic reaction
or some kind of localized infection.
Do you know why the men
won't enter the church?
- Evil spirits.
- Oh.
If you believe the Turkana.
And do you?
No. I'm a doctor.
But as a priest, surely you must believe
in such things.
- I'm an archeologist. I'm not a priest.
- Now, that's funny.
I met Father Francis outside,
and he told me you were.
Did he? Well, he is mistaken.
Father Merrin.
This is Emekwi.
He's donating the use of a room
in his hotel for the mission school.
Father, we are so glad
that you are here.
These are my sons, James and Joseph.
- Hello, James. Joseph.
- They are learning the Bible.
We are Christians, you know.
Mm.
Emekwi, can you see
to Mr. Merrin's bags?
Oh, of course. James, Joseph?
Very nice meeting you, doctor.
There's your goddamn church.
Is this your first assignment, Father?
Well, before this, I was studying
in the archives in the Holy See.
The Vatican. Impressive. But not really
training for missionary work, is it?
This is strange.
It's 1500 years old.
It should be badly weathered.
It's almost as if it were buried
right after it was built.
Chuma.
Where's Jefferies?
I need to go into the church.
Hyenas.
They've been here ever since
we started digging.
Even at daytime?
- What's the matter with him?
- I don't know.
The heat?
Joseph'?
Are you out here by yourself?
It's dangerous.
- I'm collecting rocks.
- I can see that.
I think you're about ready
for this now.
It's a tool for professional diggers.
Wow.
His seizure's stopped. I wanted to keep
him at the hospital for observation...
...but Turkana have stopped
trusting my medicine.
Well, that must make your job
very hard.
You have no idea.
Thank you.
So, what is it you hope to find here?
The answer to why a church
was built here...
...a thousand years
before Christianity arrived.
You were a priest once, weren't you?
Yes, I was.
Bloody savages!
Can't wipe their own ass
without instruction.
- I have to get back to town.
- Wait. I found this.
And I want you to have it.
It's a St. Joseph, for luck.
Please. For my behavior.
Thank you.
What the hell are you doing?
- Get the fuck out of here, you little scab!
- Don't!
- Joseph, wait.
- Don't do that.
All right, Merrin. I didn't know
you was a fuzzy lover.
It's okay. Come.
These little buggers,
they get in everywhere.
How soon can you have the doors
to the church uncovered?
- A few days.
- And in the meantime, how do we get in?
We don't. Chuma will take you in
through the roof.
Following us, Father?
Is it safe to walk around?
Let's see.
Lucifer. The Lord's favorite angel.
Cast out after the war in heaven.
Can't even trust angels, can you?
- You ever seen anything like it?
- Not this far from Rome.
It's odd.
Churches were built to exalt heaven,
but this...
The weapons are pointing downward.
Look behind you, Father.
Desecration of Christ.
Who would do something like this?
The crucifix was broken off from here.
Chuma, is there an inventory
of what's been found here?
- I wouldn't know.
- Well, who would know?
Because this place
has been vandalized.
Probably the lead archeologist,
Monsieur Bession.
So where can I find him?
I need to talk to him.
- It's not possible.
- Why not?
He's gone mad.
No one's been inside Bession's tent
since he fell ill?
They are superstitious.
- And you?
- Not superstitious. Smart.
Chuma!
Yes?
- Where's Bession now?
- A sanatorium in Nairobi.
How long has he been gone?
A few weeks.
- And he can read and write Aramaic?
- Sorry?
The language spoken in Palestine...
- ...at the time of Christ.
- And what does it say?
"The fallen shall rise
in a river of blood."
- Do you have a moment?
- Of course.
Can I get you some tea?
Or maybe something more substantial?
Yes, that would be very nice.
You dabble in the occult?
I found them here when I arrived.
I wanted to ask you,
did you treat Bession?
You should let me clean that
before it gets infected.
There was nothing I could do
for Monsieur Bession.
He had no medical symptoms.
Nothing to suggest
any kind of disease or infection.
His breakdown was purely mental.
And extremely severe.
That's why the Turkana
fear the church is cursed.
That and the disappearances.
In the past few weeks,
we've lost a dozen men.
Runaways?
- Or is it those evil spirits?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry. I shouldn't have...
- Your curiosity's perfectly natural.
My father was a strong man.
When the Nazis started rounding up
the Jews in our town, he didn't hesitate.
He hid our neighbors
in the crawl space.
But someone turned us in, and we were
all sent to the concentration camps.
I'm sorry.
People can't really understand, can they?
If they weren't there.
If they didn't see.
No.
And my husband turned out
to be one of those people.
I met him after the war, and we
came to Africa together, in love.
One night I realized I...
I had to tell him the truth...
...about the Nazis
and what they did to me.
After that he never touched me again.
So...
What turns a man of the cloth
into an archeologist?
I don't know, I suppose I...
I wanted to work with something real,
something I could touch with my hands.
Do you miss it? Being a priest?
No. There's no point in that.
Sometimes I think the best view of God
is from hell.
I should get to bed.
I'm going to Nairobi tomorrow,
to see Bession.
- Talk to Father Gionetti.
- Gionetti?
He runs the sanitarium.
Well, thank you for the medical care.
And deliver us from evil...
...for thine is the kingdom and the power
and the glory, forever and ever...
Amen.
You, priest, what is your name?
I'm Father Merrin.
God is not here today, priest.
Want some water?
Hey. What's wrong?
It's late. You should go back to bed.
Give it to me! It's mine!
- Oh, is it yours?
- Give it to me!
Mr. Merrin gave it to me.
- Here, take it. Take it!
- Just give it to me, you idiot!
Who are you calling idiot?
Take it, it's right here!
- Give it to me! It's mine!
- Shorty, shorty!
- Just give it to me!
- All right, okay!
Go back to bed, and I'll give you
the stupid thing.
Joseph, look out!
Joseph, get Papa, get Papa!
Joseph, help me!
Joseph, please, get Papa quickly!
Help me! Help me!
Help me! Papa, help me, please!
- What happened?
- Hyenas. They tore James apart.
Did you see that, Lankester?
The hyenas ignored Joseph.
- They were focused on his brother.
- That was a lot more than focused.
They acted as if he wasn't even there.
Can you see? Can you hear?
Monsieur Bession?
Mr. Bession.
You worked on a dig in Derati.
You drew a picture of an idol.
Where did you see it?
Was it in the church?
Monsieur Bession.
- Father Merrin.
- How do you know my name?
I said, how do you know my name?
Are you hurt?
No.
I'm free.
God is not here today, priest.
I hope he finds peace.
I'm Father Gionetti.
I've been waiting for you.
How did he know my name?
Have you drifted so far from God,
Merrin, that you can't see?
Monsieur Bession
was touched by the devil.
Demonic possession?
Forgive me, Father.
I never said he was possessed.
Only touched.
So, touched.
What does that mean?
In 1647, the Ursuline Convent
in Loudun, France...
...was plagued by possession.
Thirty-four nuns had been touched by
the devil, committing unspeakable acts.
Having orgies including goats doesn't
make them possessed, simply horny...
...and inventive.
Four priests were dispatched
to exorcise the demons.
Three of them were possessed
themselves and subsequently died.
The last one was driven insane
by his brush...
...with evil.
That is what happened
to Monsieur Bession.
And that evil remains in Derati.
You must be careful there.
Remember, he is the father of lies.
He will seek to poison your mind.
You will need this against him.
The Roman Rituals.
If you need somebody to perform
an exorcism, I'm not your man.
I'm not a priest anymore.
You will always be a priest,
Father Merrin.
Only your faith can save you.
Well, then, I'm doomed.
Joseph?
What do you have there?
Can I see?
You threw it away.
- What the hell are you doing in here?
- It was in the dirt outside.
You threw it away.
No, I didn't.
- The clasp must have come loose.
- Liar!
Do I repulse you that much?
Maybe if you could cure
my fucking face...
...I might look as good to you
as that archeologist.
- Joseph?
- He's coming for you.
What?
He's coming for you.
- What happened?
- I had a bad dream.
Don't worry.
You'll be fine.
Where is everybody?
Sebituana's baby is coming,
so the village has gathered in welcome.
Joseph.
Hey.
You're back.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, I'm just a little bit tired.
These lesions...
- ...they're not from the shock, are they?
- No.
They're completely asymptomatic.
It just doesn't make sense.
- He should have recovered by now.
- So, what is it?
In this part of the world...
...it could be a dozen things.
But his symptoms don't really
match any of them.
So all I can do is just watch and wait.
I have to do some work up at the dig.
- Will you be all right?
- Mm. Yes.
Come sit with me, Lankester.
I promise I won't bite.
What is it?
- How was Nairobi?
- Oh, fine.
- Did you see Monsieur Bession?
- He's dead.
- How?
- I don't know.
Some accident.
I just don't understand.
Everything that's happening here...
It seems like I can't help
anyone anymore.
Hey.
Easy.
Help me hold him.
Emekwi.
I'm doing everything I can for him.
Joseph?
It's this place, Lankester.
The Turkana are right, it's cursed.
- Sarah.
- You don't understand.
What they did to me in the camp.
They...
There's nothing left to bleed.
There is something here,
something evil.
Sarah, it's so much easier
to believe in evil as an entity...
...but it's not.
It's a purely human condition
inside all of us.
Did Bession talk about what he found
under the church?
There's an ancient temple below,
a pagan place...
...where they used to conduct sacrifices,
human sacrifices.
Why would they build a church
on top of something like that?
Perhaps to purify the site.
But then, why bury it?
Merrin!
You better come with me.
Jefferies didn't show up
for the dig this morning.
He wasn't in his room, so they came
to the bar, and they found...
Chief Sebituana's baby
was stillborn last night.
He blames the whites.
You think the Turkana took Jeffries?
I think this place is on the verge
of an uprising.
I've contacted Major Granville.
A detachment will be here
by this afternoon.
You disagree?
In my experience, bringing soldiers
into a situation is always a bad idea.
Who buried them?
Everybody died.
All right.
Gut!
- Major Granville.
- Hello.
Come on. Out you get.
Move it, Wilkins.
- Any answers on Jefferies?
- I'm afraid not.
Well, you did the right thing
calling me, Father.
I've been in these situations before,
and you have to stay on top of...
On top of these people.
I'm not sure the Turkana are responsible
for what's happening here, major.
Major Granville?
This dig is too important to jeopardize,
and until I'm satisfied...
...the excavation is secure, the British
army will assume complete control.
- The Turkana won't like force.
- I'm not concerned with what they like.
And if they start any more trouble...
...they will have to answer to the might
of His Majesty King George.
You cannot be here.
Please tell Sebituana
I'm sorry for his loss.
You are not welcome here.
I want to know about the plague
that destroyed this village 50 years ago.
It was not a plague.
So, what was it?
The evil in your church,
it has taken Emekwi's youngest son...
...and it is getting stronger.
You must abandon your work,
or we'll be forced to stop you.
So you don't want to tell me?
He says he doesn't have to tell you,
because it's happening again...
...right now.
You don't bury your dead.
You cremate them.
- Yes.
- Then who's buried in that graveyard?
I'm sorry.
What are you...?
Daddy.
I will shoot 10, priest...
...and you will choose.
I can't do that.
No!
Now you choose...
...or I will kill them all.
Are you praying...
...to God?
Shoot me.
God is not here today, priest.
Papa.
- They're empty.
- What?
I dug up three graves.
They were all empty. What happened?
- I don't know.
- Oh, yes, you do.
- You've been lying since we got here.
- Let go of me.
Damn it!
There are crosses on the graves.
There are crosses on the coffins.
The church buried them, didn't they?
Didn't they?
Yes.
Why?
What were they hiding?
That this place is damned.
No! You asked the question!
Now you're gonna listen to the answer!
There was a massacre here...
...1500 years ago.
An army from the West,
led by two priests...
...searching for the origin
of a powerful evil.
When they got here,
that evil consumed them...
...turning the soldiers against each other
in a bloodbath.
Only a single priest survived. When that
priest made it to the Emperor Justinian...
...he ordered that a church be built over the
site and buried to seal the evil inside.
All mention of it was to be stricken
from the history texts forever.
But it wasn't.
No.
In 1893...
...a Vatican researcher found
an ancient letter in the archives.
Four priests came
to examine the site...
...enlisting the help of the people
of this valley in their search...
...and they all disappeared.
Where did they go?
No one knows.
The Vatican ordered a cover-up...
...the false graveyard.
The tale of a plague to...
To scare people away.
And then the British
stumbled across it.
And I was sent here to see
if the legend was real.
What legend?
That after the war in heaven...
...this is the spot where Lucifer fell.
God brought you here, Lankester.
Leave me alone.
No.
The devil is here...
...inside that boy.
The Turkana know it.
They came to drive the devil from him,
and he almost killed them.
You can't run from this.
You must help me.
I can't.
But you've seen what's going on here.
You have to believe.
I believe in nothing.
They've found Jefferies.
Major Granville. Wait.
Get him down.
You all right, major?
Savages.
Major.
Major!
- Bloody savages.
- Why are you here?
- Granville!
- You have no business to be here!
- You must leave.
- Granville!
You people have plundered
our ancestors.
- You must return Turkana to us now.
- Let me through!
It's time to go.
You have already polluted our lives.
You came here with your evil.
- We knew peace before you came.
- Granville!
No!
They think it's inside Joseph.
They believe the evil is upon us.
Chuma!
Merrin?
They believe it is inside Joseph.
They're going to kill him.
Now, please...
...go.
Sir, the Turkana are preparing
to attack.
Leave me.
Sir?
I said, leave me.
Yes, sir.
- We must leave now.
- Why?
- Where's Sarah?
- I don't know.
Take the boy to Nairobi.
Father Gionetti.
Why?
Turkana are coming to kill him.
It's a sandstorm.
It won't let us leave.
We have to hide him.
- The church.
- No.
The Turkana won't go in there.
It's his only chance.
- Aren't you coming?
- I have to find Sarah.
We'll meet you.
Francis.
Now go.
Sarah?
The Lord is coming for you.
Sarah!
Oh, my God.
Bession was Sarah's husband?
Yes.
She went into the church
with him, didn't she?
It's not Joseph.
It's Sarah.
Ready yourselves, men!
Fire!
Chuma.
Francis?
Francis.
O, Lord, forgive my disbelief.
I need you.
These people need you.
This valley needs you.
Hear my cry...
Do not abandon me now.
Forgive my sins.
Joseph.
Come sit with us.
I promise I won't bite.
Joseph, run.
He's mine.
Run.
Leave him alone.
It's me you want.
I am a fallen priest.
Lord, have mercy on us.
Christ, have mercy on us.
God, Father in heaven,
have mercy on us.
God, the Son, redeemer of the world,
God, the Holy Spirit, have mercy on us.
Christ, hear us.
Holy Mary, pray for us.
Lord, have mercy on us.
What's the matter, Merrin?
Don't you wanna fuck me anymore?
All ye holy angels and archangels,
pray for us!
All ye holy orders of blessed spirits,
Why would he listen to you?
You.
You believe in nothing.
You're all alone.
Without hope.
Almighty Lord
and father of Jesus Christ...
...grant me, your unworthy servant,
pardon for my sins...
...and the power to fight this cruel...
Joseph, come on.
- Don't be afraid.
- No! Father!
- Joseph.
- Father Merrin...
Help me.
Joseph!
O, Lord...
...by your name, save me.
By your strength, defend my cause.
Joseph.
Joseph, wait.
- Joseph.
- Father.
I'm coming.
O, God, hear my prayer.
The ruthless seek my life.
They do not keep God before them.
Turn back the evil upon my foes.
In your faithfulness, destroy them.
Where is your God now, Merrin?
Fucking his only son
while you call his name?
He doesn't care about this whore.
But you do...
...because you want to shove
your rotten cock up her juicy ass.
You can't have her, priest.
The whore is mine.
And I'll kill her before I let you
take her from me.
From the souls made to the image
and likeness of God...
...I cast you out!
You're a killer, Merrin.
You looked them in the eye
and pointed your finger and they died.
God is not here today, priest.
Oh, yes, he is.
You're going to watch him die, Merrin.
Fail him like you failed all the others.
God, spare this child,
for he is innocent...
...and deserves your blessing.
God, spare this child...
...for he is innocent
and deserves your blessing.
God, spare this child, for he is innocent
I command you to depart!
It's the power of Christ that compels you!
It is God who commands you.
It is Christ who commands you.
God, the Father, commands you.
God, the Son, commands you.
The Holy Spirit commands you.
The cross commands you.
Unclean spirit, I cast you out!
Lankester.
Sarah, Sarah.
It's over now.
Joseph, Joseph.
Father.
Don't be afraid.
I need your help, Joseph.
Listen, whatever you hear,
whatever you see, it's just his lies.
Don't listen. Don't watch.
You understand?
Don't listen!
It's just lies. You have to be strong
and concentrate.
Can you read this?
I will start there.
And then you will answer.
That's me. That's you. That's me,
and that's you. You understand?
Good.
Let's start.
O, God, by your name, save me.
"Amen."
Save your servant.
"Who places his trust in thee,
my God."
Be unto her, O, Lord, a fortified tower.
"In the face of the enemy."
O, Lord, hear my prayer.
"And let my cry come unto thee."
- The Lord be with you.
- "And also with you."
Begone, evil spirit...
...in the name of the Father
and of the Son...
...and of the Holy Ghost.
By the sign of this Holy Cross...
...by our Lord Jesus Christ...
...God, the Holy Ghost,
commands you!
The blood of the martyrs
In God's name, demon!
I cast you out!
Sarah.
Okay?
Thank you.
Sarah. What is it?
What is it, Sarah?
Help. Help!
- Lankester.
- No.
Help.
- Help.
Sarah.
Father.
She's with God now.
She's with God.
I trust your mission was successful.
I couldn't find
what you were looking for.
But you found something.
Didn't you?
Goodbye, Mr. Semelier.
Au revoir, Mr. Merrin.
It's Father Merrin.