Subtitles by KBS World
Mr. Ko was at Aeji's kindergarten.
One, two, three!
Warm water. It'll warm you up.
I don't know why I feel this way.
I keep having second thoughts.
It's so hard.
You don't look very well.
Why did you go to the river in this cold?
I'm not sure if I'm doing the right thing.
I wanted to be a good mom for Miho,
but I don't feel he's come to me all the way.
Tell him about Miho.
He'll change if he knows Miho is his.
No, I don't want to do that.
He's hesitating and I refuse to tell him about Miho to get him to come to me.
It makes me feel too desperate.
I can't use Miho like that.
What's wrong with doing that?
He has to know she's his child.
I don't want to push his child on him,
as if that's going to divide him in half.
I'm not doing that.
When everything is over, I'll tell him.
Sunjeong, give him some time.
Men can tell good men apart.
I think he's a serious and sincere man.
I know that.
I do,
but I don't know what to do with how I feel.
Trying to be nice is driving me crazy.
Whenever his ex-wife's family bothers me,
I want to pay them back,
but I've been holding it in.
I'm afraid that would make him leave me.
I don't want to lose him again.
Then don't.
If you do, you're a fool.
Your friends are so funny.
Mom!
Where were you?
The market.
Mr. Ko cooked noodles.
He's really great at it.
He is?
You're not busy?
I pulled an all nighter, so I came to take a nap
and Miho was here so we ate some noodles.
Miho has a cold.
It's too cold here.
We should move to the apartment quickly.
It's okay. I'm better now.
Mom, Mr. Ko, I'm going to the academy.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes. I don't have a fever now.
Be safe.
Miho, see you later.
I disappointed you, didn't I?
I'm sorry I made you feel that way.
I should've dropped by last night,
but I was just too busy.
I thought this last night.
Miho was sick and I was conflicted.
Why am I here going through this?
I kept thinking, what am I doing here?
Sunjeong, just hold on a little more.
Just a little more.
I'm going to your father.
Can you go alone?
I'll walk slowly. I can use the workout.
How can you leave your post again?
I went to throw the trash out.
You keep wandering around.
This is too much.
I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
I'm sick of hearing that.
What were you thinking?
If you don't want to work, quit.
You got fired, remember?
You're not a vice principal anymore.
You have to do a better job.
You think making money is easy?
Go clean the bathroom.
What are you doing?
When did you come?
You old hags!
What did you say?
Shut your traps!
Say it again.
Stop it.
Are you all out of you minds?
You think you can mistreat him?
Is owning this building that special?
My parents had a bathroom bigger than this!
It's so dark it looks haunted.
How dare you mistreat my husband!
And what are you?
Aren't you renting here?
Got fired and no longer a vice principal and what?
He is a very well-respected man.
How dare you talk to him like that?
Who knows where you'll be when you get old?
What do you think you're doing?
I'm doing the right thing!
He's quitting so find someone else!
Let's go.
Don't do this.
Let's go. You don't need this job.
I'll get a job. I will!
Don't forget to wire his paycheck.
What the...
Come!
Ouch. My back.
Screaming hurt my bones.
Why did you come?
I'm glad I did.
Those darn women.
I would've beat them up if it weren't for my back.
You've done enough.
What kind of job are you going to get?
- Huh?
- You said you'll get a job.
So I can stay home and do nothing?
Hold on.
When I'm better, I'll look for a job.
I hope people don't say I'm too old.
You worked to provide for me for 40 years
so I should do the same for you to call it even.
I think I married incredibly well.
You were amazing.
You were like Joan of Arc.
I didn't get much education,
but having a teacher as a husband made me proud.
I'm not well educated,
but people respected me because of you.
So I can't see you suffering like that.
You do what you want to do from now on.
You don't have to make money.
You've already done enough of that.
Thanks.
Honey,
let's not be greedy.
I thought about it while lying on my back,
and life isn't all that special.
When you die, it's over,
so there's no need to expose yourself to that kind of abuse.
But we need a house.
Who cares if we don't have one?
It's okay to rent,
as long as we have a roof over our head.
What's the use of buying a house now?
I was once a homeowner.
The experience was enough for me.
Are you sure?
Nothing really bothers me anymore.
Crying about money won't change anything.
What about the doorplate?
I wanted to hang that up again.
Then hang it up on your chest.
That'll do.
Son?
What's that?
Seaweed soup.
But it's not anyone's birthday.
It doesn't have to be someone's birthday.
Sweetheart, can we talk...
I don't want to talk about that.
She wants you to bring her food?
No.
I'm going to teach her a lesson.
Why does she have to treat my precious son like a servant?
Let her come out and eat.
You don't know what you're talking about.
Get up and eat.
Mother's angry, isn't she?
I don't care what she says.
Not when my wife is dying here.
Eat up.
Is it good?
You're better than me.
It's delicious.
Eat up. Eat some rice, too.
Sedal.
About the baby...
Let's have another one.
But I'm not getting drunk this time.
Let's do it right. Plan it.
Father, you're being mean about my family.
I'm very disappointed.
Father,
please stop hating me.
Can you please be more understanding...
I have to take the trash to my...
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Thinking about ways to torture Gwangbak?
Please don't say things like that.
She's the one who's torturing me.
Father, how was your day?
It was good.
Father, I'm really sorry.
I don't know what came over me.
I swear it will never ever happen again.
Please forgive me.
Whatever. Follow me.
Have a seat.
Sit down.
You must sit down first.
I said sit down!
I'll do it.
Just sit there.
Okay.
- Your seat is...
- It's okay.
I have to sit here to drink with you.
Excuse me?
I must get drunk to make us even.
You like being even.
I'm sorry, father.
I was so mad I couldn't sleep.
Father, let's say I lost.
Let's say?
You're letting me win?
No, it's not that.
Let's compete fair and square.
How's that?
Why? You're afraid?
No.
Let's put a wager on this, then.
The winner gets a wish.
What?
Nothing, father. I'm sorry.
Okay.
That's actually a good idea.
You won't regret it later?
I won't. How about you?
Of course not, since I'm going to win.
We don't know that.
You think you can beat me?
I've been drinking with construction workers.
Okay.
Fine. Let's do this.
Okay. Go!
Go!
Okay!
Here.
Bottoms up!
Bottoms up, bottoms up, bottoms up.
Bottoms up.
Gwangbak,
love shot.
Okay, father!
You know?
You shouldn't be that way...
Uh, father!
Father!
Yes! Yes!
I won.
I wo...
Are you asleep?
No.
What are you doing?
It's not working.
What made you get a job as a security guard?
You've always been a teacher.
You've never done any hard labor at all.
After quitting my job,
I felt really lost.
I thought, "Why didn't I prepare for this?"
I felt really empty inside.
People nowadays live to be 100,
but I've done nothing to prepare for that.
I knew it in my head,
but I was hit really hard
because I thought things would work out.
Take a break.
We can live off of your retirement fund.
I should work while I can.
I can't handle staying home.
If I did, I would have to take care of you.
I'd rather work.
I want you to take care of me.
Bathroom.
Huh? Can you make it?
Yes.
Okay, okay.
- Should I come in?
- Don't be silly!
Bong, stay there, okay?
Are you jealous of Yeongdal?
Of course.
I'll be just like her in my next life.
Start being like her now.
Why would you wait until your next life?
Bong, is your bottom freezing?
Oh, laughing makes my bones ache.
Water.
Father.
What's that?
It smells good.
Oh, I made hangover soup.
Father, I won.
What do you mean?
The drinking competition.
What drinking competition?
Don't you remember?
A drinking competition with you?
I can't believe my ears.
I stole your mother's line.
Father, you said the winner gets a wish.
I never said that.
Father, just a minute.
What is it?
If that's true,
why do I have a picture like this?
He looks just like you, right?
You!
Go wash up, father.
I'll set the table.
I tried to make it like Aunt Sunjeong.
I hope it's good.
How is it, father?
It's not bad.
Where did you learn to drink like that?
My father taught me.
You can hold your liquor.
I was told never to get drunk before the elderly.
Father, can I tell you my wish?
No thanks.
How can you and I have a drinking competition to begin with?
Don't ever mention it again.
Take a look inside.
It's a contract for cafe.
Why are you giving this...
I want you to manage it.
Excuse me?
You want to be a writer?
Who was that?
The Harry Potter writer wrote at a cafe?
Don't dawdle at home.
Go write at the cafe.
Father!
You can spend the profit any way you want.
Excuse me?
You can spend it or give it to your parents.
Don't take trash to your parents.
Father!
Hey!
Watch out for the soup.
Father, thank you!
Thank you so much.
And delete that photo.
I will.
Salla.
Please go.
You saw how my son reacted.
But we haven't met formally.
Let me meet him.
It's okay.
I don't want to break his heart.
Why is our dating breaking his heart?
I'll talk to him.
My son is very stubborn.
Please leave.
What we had is over.
It's not over.
Please leave.
Hurry.
Mom.
Mom, what is it?
What's wrong.
It's nothing.
You can tell me.
Ouch! That stung. Ouch...
Oh, this is nuts.
Who is it?
Sedal, it's me.
Didn't you go to work?
What's wrong with you?
You're so selfish.
Why?
Let mom get married.
Did she tell you to say that?
You're married and have 2 kids,
so why won't you let mom get married?
Mom was crying.
She broke up with him because of you.
Good for her.
You are so selfish.
Mom should live her life.
She had a tough life raising us.
I realized something after I got married.
How amazing it is to have a husband.
She's finally found someone nice.
You only care about your own happiness?
Thinking about mom chokes me up.
Imagine how lonely she must have been.
We should be helping her get married.
Say something.
I have nothing to say.
Sedal!
You stay out of this!
Why should I?
I don't want to talk about mom.
Don't you feel sorry for her?
I do!
That's why I'm saying no.
You don't know anything.
You think you're the only one who loves mom?
I love mom, too.
But she doesn't need to get married.
She can live happily ever after with me.
Mom wants to live happily ever after with him, not you!
You stay out.
I'll take care of it.
You...
I'm the eldest son.
I'll take care of mom,
so you stay out.
Look what you made me do!
It's all sewn up!
Then rip it back up.
Watch me!
I'm getting her married!
You better not!
Go home.
I can't stand the sight of you!
I gave it a lot of thought,
and I build up the courage to come see you.
I'm not even sure if this is right.
It must have been very hard for you.
I'm sorry for what my family's done to you.
Minjung
is like a son to me.
He was my daughter's husband,
but I relied on him.
It's very hard for me, so I could only
imagine how my wife or Subak feels.
Please take good care of Minjung.
I know you'll be kind to Aeji and Jungji, too.
Mr. Wang.
I think this is the answer.
Dragging on won't help anyone.
I'll talk to my family,
so don't pay attention to them.
Even if anything happens again,
just ignore it.
Thank you. Thank you.
What could I possibly tell you here?
I'm so sorry about everything.
I'll take good care of the kids and pray for their mom's happiness.
Thank you so much.
He said that?
It broke my heart.
It couldn't have been an easy decision.
It was very gracious of him.
Let's make it work.
If we're happy, everything will work out.
Okay.
What did you say?
Don't go to Minjung from now on.
He's not family anymore.
And give him the kids.
Honey.
This is the right thing to do.
Don't hold on to him anymore.
He won't come back, even if you do.
Send the kids to Minjung, just as you agreed.
I can't.
I'm going to raise them.
Subak...
Then what about Subak?
What about our poor Subak?
She can't drag him back to her life.
Admit it. It's over.
Some things can't be forced.
Setting Minjung free is the right thing.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
First, second, third, fourth. That one.
- Do you like it?
- Yes.
Is it done?
I'm sorry I couldn't help.
It's okay.
We didn't have much stuff.
Thank you.
I'll come straight home after work.
Let's have a party.
Okay, Minjung.
Mom, I'm so happy.
This is my first room.
Miho, let's have a party.
Wear a dress.
Are you going somewhere?
No, but we're celebrating you.
Me? Why is that?
Because you deserve it.
Oh, no...
What is it?
Look.
What do we do?
It's over 39°C.
Take him to the hospital.
Call Minjung.
Tell him to bring his car.
But Bong told us not to!
But he needs to know his son is sick!
Mother, help her.
Okay.
Ouch, my back.
It's okay, it's okay.
Ship these out by the end of the day.
These new products will go out tomorrow.
- Okay.
- Good.
The person you called is unavailable...
Hello?
It's me. Where is he?
Put him on the phone.
He's at work.
What's going on?
Jungji's burning up!
We're at the hospital!
Hospital?
Okay. Hold on.
I'll try calling him.
Minjung!
What's wrong?
Why won't you answer your phone?
I left it at my office.
What's wrong?
Jungji is sick.
He's at the hospital.
You should go.
Why won't you answer your phone?
What did the doctor say?
It's enteritis.
Are they admitting him?
What do I do...
Stay here.
I'll go see his doctor.
I got dressed up for nothing.
You can wear it again next time.
Mr. Ko isn't coming home?
Where did he go?
Jungji's at the hospital, so he went there.
You used to look happy with him before,
but these days, you don't.
Minjung, Minjung.
What is it?
The doctor said he's okay now.
He can go home.
Good. Thank you.
Jungji,
thank you for pulling through.
My baby...
Don't ever get sick again.
Take Jungji.
Oh...
Take him with you.
You'll take good care of him, won't you?
You won't mistreat him.
You'll be good to him, right?
Subak.
I thought long and hard about it.
My father's right.
This is how it should be.
I'm grateful for her sending you right away.
And I'm grateful you stayed by Jungji's side.
You didn't even send each other a text.
You really impressed me.
I'll send Aeji and the kids stuff later.
Jungji, I'm sorry. Mom's sorry.
Be good. Don't get sick.
Be well and healthy.
Oh, my boy...
Goodbye.
Why are you here alone?
Where's Jungji?
He's gone.
And I'm sending Aeji, too.
Subak!
Mom.
I'm going to be successful.
I may not be much now,
but I'll be successful
and bring my kids back.
Aeji, mom's going to make lots of money.
Stay with dad until then.
No, no!
I want to live with you and grandma!
Just wait until I make money.
No!
Take her.
Okay.
Let's go.
Mom!
- Aeji!
- Subak.
Don't look.
Mom...
- Aeji.
- Subak!
Subak!
Subak! Subak!
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
I know.
I'm never going to part with my baby.
Here.
Aeji, you can use this room with Miho.
This is mine.
Okay. You take the bed.
Mom, I can sleep on the floor. It's okay.
Okay.
I'll buy you a nicer one when we move.
No, no, no.
No! You'll die!
You'll die if you do that.
Hey, hey.
You died.
Oh, boy.
No, no! You'll die. You'll die. No.
Should we stop?
No, no.
Dad, I want to play more.
Just once, then.
Dad, you're the best.
Okay.
Mom, can I call Mr. Ko dad?
- Do you want to?
- Yes.
Then go ahead.
Say, "Dad, let's eat."
Dad, let's eat.
Huh?
No! He's not your dad!
He's my dad!
He's my dad. No, no!
Okay, okay. I'm your dad. I'm your dad.
I'm not her dad. I'm your dad.
Have you ever done this kind of work before?
No, I've never done this before.
You have a friendly face, so you'll be good.
There is a two week training period.
Do I have to do that?
Yes.
You must learn about our bags and about haw to deal with customers.
Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
The best shop and the best manager,
Wang Hobak!
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Dad!
Yay!
Mom!
What? Is that true?
Yes. I won 1st place.
You won 1st place?
I can't believe my ears!
My company had a contest,
and the 1st place winner gets a shop.
Good.
Honey, Don's luck is finally changing.
I owe it all to you, mom.
I made a healthy pizza thinking of you.
What did you make?
- You like pumpkin, right?
- Yes.
I used chicken breast and pumpkin.
Oh, that sounds yummy.
I'm getting a shop next week.
Bong, please come.
Anggeum, you too.
You're the best, the best.
Oh, hey, you...
Not here...
I'm so happy.
It's okay. You can fall over.
Let's go to sleep.
How's Aeji? Is she okay?
She just feel asleep.
Being away from her mom must be hard.
She's sleeping in our room?
Miho's not sleeping in the bed because of her.
I'll sleep with her for a while.
Did you tell Miho to do it?
To call me dad?
No, Miho wanted to.
I'm grateful,
but I don't think she should for now.
Aeji keeps crying.
But Miho is...
It's nothing.
Mom.
You weren't sleeping?
I won't call Mr. Ko dad.
Mom, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You shouldn't be sorry.
So don't say you're sorry.
You're not sleeping?
I have to study.
You're not sleepy?
You aunt wants water.
What a nice husband.
I've never seen you study before.
You hated studying when you were a student.
But I have to, if I want to make money.
Don't you feel sorry for her?
She broke up with him.
Mom was crying.
Mom.
Mom, are you asleep?
If you're not, can we talk?
Mom.
Mom...
This is nutty, nutty, nuts.
Daese.
Salla.
I missed you so much.
But this is the last time.
Why is that?
Don't ask too many questions.
I came to tell you this is the last time.
You made me happy.
Thank you for making my heart flutter.
You made me feel like a woman again.
I will never forget that.
I hope you meet someone nice.
Salla!
Thank you for coming to meet me.
I wanted to see you, so I'm glad you called.
Let's cut to the chase.
What do you do?
How come so many are into heavy equipment?
I don't trust business cards.
You can get them made anywhere.
But it's real...
I came to ask you for a favor.
Stop calling my mom out.
Please leave her alone.
I can make Salla happy.
May I ask why you're against me?
If I need to change...
Just break up with her.
If you call my mom again,
I won't let you get away with that.
I feel like I've seen him somewhere.
Where have I seen him?
Be my pony.
Sure.
Get on.
Giddy up, giddy up!
Trot, trot.
Giddy up, giddy up.
Why don't you play with your doll?
Aeji, let's play with your dolls.
No, no!
I want a pony ride.
Giddy up, giddy up. Trot, trot.
I'm done.
Oh, no! Are you hurt?
Why did you make her cry?
Miho, why didn't you take better care of her?
Aeji tripped getting off from Miho's back.
Aeji doesn't like stuff like that.
Aeji, don't cry.
Welcome.
We'll learn about service manners.
Anyone can have a good first impression.
When a customer comes in, smile brightly,
tuck your stomach in and say "Hello, welcome."
Hello, welcome.
Thank you, come again.
Healthy.
Next patient.
- Minjung, dinner's ready.
- Okay.
Dad, I want barbecue.
Barbecue?
Aeji, you want barbecue?
Should we go out and eat?
But dinner's ready.
Okay, sure.
Minjung, there's too much smoke here.
Okay. I'll eat first.
Okay.
Let's go.
Your eyes stung, didn't they?
Oh, my!
Is it a girl?
No, he's a boy.
He looks just like his mom!
He does?
People say he looks like his dad.
Bye.
- Bye.
Oh, good girl.
Dad, I want that!
Can I have it?
Please!
Let me have it, please.
Sure. Pick one.
Miho, you pick one, too.
Thank you, Mr. Ko.
No! It's mine.
No, no! I want to play with that.
But that one's yours.
This is mine.
Mr. Ko bought it for me.
No!
Aeji, what's wrong?
Let me see you.
Are you hurt?
Where?
Are you okay?
It's fine. You're fine.
What is it?
Minjung,
can't you just leave Miho and Aeji alone?
Kids fight all the time growing up.
Your involvement isn't helping.
I know that.
But she's having a hard time.
She's stressed out about losing her mom,
so why can't you let her be?
She can learn later.
Didn't I tell you?
They must be our kids, or it won't work.
I want you to stay out.
Miho and I need to become friends with Aeji.
But you stepping in isn't giving us a chance.
Just trust Miho.
She's a good girl.
She knows what to do.
Miho is a kid, too, you know?
Miho's grown up, but Aeji's still a baby.
Don't you feel sorry for Aeji?
You only feel sorry for Aeji?
Aeji keeps acting out,
and you won't pay attention to Miho.
Look.
You said they would be our kids,
but you're siding with Miho.
I'm not siding with Miho.
I just feel bad for her.
Why should you feel that?
I've never mistreated Miho.
Minjung, I want this to work.
But it feels like you're not really here.
Your heart is somewhere else.
Like where?
Where could my heart go?
Don't over analyze things.
Let Aeji sleep with Miho.
They'll become friends faster.
Let's take things slowly.
- I'll sleep with her...
- For how long?
Sunjeong, why are you acting this way?
We're talking
Can you answer it later...
Uncle.
Yes.
I'm good.
Aeji and Jungji are good, too.
Grand opening?
Congratulations. That's great news.
I'll be there.
Aeji, eat lunch.
I need to take Jungji to see a doctor.
Mom.
Oh!
Sangnam.
Go home.
Huh? Man...
Hello.
Follow that cab. Don't lose him.
- Okay.
- I'll pay you well.
Okay.
Sedal, I found him!
Really?
Okay. I'll be right there.
He's headed for Yeongnam intersection.
Okay. I'm driving, so hold on.
Yes, yes.
Okay. I got it. Don't lose him.
Aeji!
Aeji, where are you?
Aeji! Aeji!
Where? The beltway?
Why didn't you tell me that before?
Minjung, the Naebu Beltway.
Aeji!
Mom!
Oh, my...
What happened to your face?
What happened to your hand?
Oh, no...
Man...
What did she do to her?
Didn't you hear what Aeji said?
She abused her.
Raise her as her own child?
Yeah, right.
She said that to seduce Minjung.
I can't take this.
I should just...
Mom, you stay home.
My heart was bleeding when I sent my kids.
You promised to take good care of them.
Where's Aeji?
Aeji's hurt.
She fell down coming to me and got hurt.
I'm sorry. Is it serious?
She's my child, so stay out.
How dare you act like you care?
You are the worst person in the world.
You used my kids to seduce a man?
You made him bring them and abused them?
I heard you treated her differently than your own.
Why did you abuse them?
What did they ever to do you?
How could you kick my daughter out when she was having a hard time?
You have a very nice place.
You thought you two could be happy?
When you broke my heart like this?
What do you have here?
What are these?
Stop it!
Don't do that to my mom.
I'm stopping because of your kid.
Don't embarrass yourself in front of her.
Mom, why were you just standing there?
Why didn't you fight back? Why?
You should fight back.
Who are you?
Hey? Do you recognize me?
Yes.
This is nuts, you know?
Give my in-law's house back!
I'll kill you if you don't!
Minjung, phone.
- Stay down!
- What is it?
Who do you think you are!
If you're going to abuse them,
why did you take the kids?
I brought Aeji and Jungji home with me!
Minjung, don't look for me.
It was already over between us,
but we forced ourselves to reconnect.
I was happy while it lasted.
Thanks, Minjung.
Goodbye.
The person you're trying to reach...
She left?
What do you mean?
She won't answer her phone.
Why did you let that happen? Why?
Why couldn't you make it work?
Don't you feel sorry for Miho?
You couldn't be there for her all these years.
She went through so much raising her alone.
You should've understood why she did that.
What do you mean...
How can you be so dense?
You didn't know Miho was your daughter?
Subtitles by KBS World