Subtitles by KBS World
You!
Heo Sedal!
Wha... What is it?
What did you do to me?
What do you mean?
You!
I'm going to kill you!
Hey!
Open the door!
Open it, right now!
Open it before I get really man!
What did you do to me?
Calm down, Hobak.
How can I calm down?
Open!
So you can beat me up?
You...
You want me to die from being mad?
Huh?
Don't get mad.
Beat me up, go ahead.
I'm so happy I can go nuts.
They can't act like newlyweds because of us.
Who'd want to live like this?
You're lucky she's your daughter in law.
You should try being nicer to her.
And when you call her, don't say "Hey."
Call her by name with affection.
Your voice is too loud.
Try being a little warm to her.
Gwangbak?
Oh, my baby.
Gwangbak? Darling!
Show me some nice fountain pens.
It's for my darling daughter in law.
Excuse me?
My daughter in law.
You must really love your daughter in law.
She's going to be a writer.
She's going to be really famous.
You must be proud.
Is there anything with hearts?
Ding-dong, a kiss is here for you.
What's up?
I had a  meeting nearby and I missed you.
Really?
Umm... Let's take our time.
Would you like to go for a drive?
Really?
How exciting!
Where would you like to go, princess?
I didn't know I'd get yelled at for not calling you "princess."
Go wherever you want, prince.
I was having trouble writing.
What were you writing about?
It's a secret.
Stop taking so much time.
It's not good to take so much time.
I can't kiss while I'm driving.
How mean.
Gwangbak.
Gwangbak. Are you in there?
I have something to say.
Me too. But go ahead.
Let's have a baby.
I thought we could take our time,
but I think a baby can solve
all the problems we have right now.
If my father had his first grandchild...
Me too.
I thought that, too.
Really?
You're the best.
Hobak.
Is something the matter?
Huh?
No...
You don't look so well.
Are you coming down with something?
I think I'm just tired.
Uncle, what's up?
Do you have time to have coffee with me?
No, you should make time.
How's Goof-off?
Is he behaving himself?
I don't want to talk about him.
Why? He's been acting up?
It's not that.
He's become weird and narrow minded.
He used to be somewhat charming before,
but not anymore.
I thought you didn't like him acting all charming.
A man should be charming!
Don't be so harsh.
What?
I feel bad for Goof-off.
What do you know?
I'm so upset.
Did you hear something from him?
Yes, he came to talk to me.
I told him to keep it a secret.
Why would he tell you that?
Who else could he talk to?
I'm his friend.
It's nothing to brag about...
Keep it to yourself.
Don't tell anyone else.
I won't. It's nothing to brag about.
I know. How embarrassing.
But you're the one who made him do that!
When did I make him do that?
He took advantage of me when I was drunk!
What are you talking about?
Huh?
You turned him into a housewife when you were drunk?
Oh...
That?
What did you think I was talking about?
Well, I...
Right. I was talking about that, too.
He doesn't want to be a housewife?
It's not that.
He feels like he's turned into a real wife.
Now that you're successful,
he's scared you'd leave him someday.
That you'd dump him.
He said that?
Yes.
You've taken him back,
so don't make him feel that way.
Have some pity on him.
I used to be more pathetic than him before,
but now, he's far more pathetic than me.
Don't you think so?
What?
Goodbye.
You can't come because you're sick?
She was just fine a little while ago.
Man...
She caught a cold, out of the blue.
She'll be able to go to work tomorrow.
Thank you.
He sounds so mean.
When you were late to school or absent,
I used to call your homeroom teacher.
Why am I still doing this at your age?
Oh...
She didn't go to work?
She's sick.
She's such a cry baby.
Isn't Jungji's 1st birthday party coming up?
Oh, right.
I almost forgot.
Stay on top of things!
You forgot Bong's birthday, remember?
Call him.
Ask Minjung about Jungji's birthday.
You call him.
I don't want to talk to him.
You still have to.
He doesn't even want to see me!
Yes, mother?
I need to talk to you, so come by the house.
Please tell me over the phone.
I won't bite.
Don't you miss your kids?
Why haven't you visited?
I just missed yesterday.
Your mind is off somewhere else, that's why.
Jungji's first birthday is the day after tomorrow.
You forgot, didn't you?
You're in love, so how could you remember?
I didn't forget.
And you didn't even call?
Come or don't.
Do as you want.
I just called to remind you.
Sunjeong!
Are you okay?
Father, when did you get home?
Father, have you eaten dinner?
What's that?
Did you write that?
Did you?
Yes.
Read it out loud.
Marriage and moving out.
Read that part.
Hurry!
When you get married, you must move out.
Marriage is nice if you lived by yourselves,
but living with others makes life difficult.
Moving into the in laws house is opening the gates of hell.
What was that?
Gates of hell?
- Father, this...
- That's how you feel?
- I was just...
- Don't make excuses.
You wrote it and you meant it.
I was trying to capture the readers eyes,
for those getting married soon...
I don't want to hear anything else.
Just say yes or no.
Is this how you feel or not?
It is.
How do you feel?
Father, this...
Everything a writer writes isn't really...
There might be exaggerations, and...
Don't side with her.
I went to buy a fountain pen today.
I told the salesclerk you'll be a famous writer soon, bragging.
I picked out a fountain pen just for you.
And you stab me in the back like this?
Living with me is hell?
You're the one who said you didn't want to
move out because you like living with me.
That was all fake?
Thanks for trying.
It must have been very hard.
Move out this instant.
Father.
Come with me.
Sangnam, that was...
Wait.
Let me ask you one question.
Is this really how you feel?
Like I said just now,
I used to exaggerate expressions to attract...
Enough.
Just tell me how you feel.
Do you really think so?
You have to ask?
I did exaggerate, but I do think so.
I didn't know it would be this bad at first.
I thought if I did my best, it'll work out.
But after I moved in, you know!
I do, but...
When I saw it in writing, I felt sad.
Was everything you did all fake?
Were you just pretending to be happy?
It wasn't like that.
But explaining it clearly is...
This won't work out.
We should
move out.
No, not like this.
That doesn't matter.
I don't want you hiding your feelings.
Sangnam,
I want you to try to understand me.
Now, it's become a huge mess.
Let's move out after I make up with him.
Now isn't the time.
I'll talk to your father.
I didn't know my writing would have such a bad effect.
Can you separate a writer from her work?
Now I'm scared to write anything.
What if people pick on everything I write?
Put yourself in my shoes.
What if I wrote that living with your parents?
Mommy!
You can't go?
No.
But this is such a great chance!
I'm sorry.
Why? You won't get another chance like this.
I couldn't sleep because I know that.
Oh, I don't know how to say this.
What is it?
I'm expecting a new addition to the family.
Oh, how embarrassing.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're expecting a baby?
Yes.
You are?
Congratulations.
I thought you were thinking of divorcing.
Oh, I can't believe it either.
It's a good thing.
Congratulations.
You can go to Italy another time.
Will there be another chance?
I thought my luck changed this year.
Your luck did change.
Not everyone can get pregnant at your age.
Don't bother me.
I'm about to explode.
Why? Did something bad happen?
I wanted to get presents from Italy
for everyone in the family,
but I can't now.
You're not going to Italy?
It's more like I can't go.
How can I go like this?
Really?
You're the best. Come here.
Ugh!
Oh! Agh!
Are you coming from the academy?
Yes.
Are you hungry?
I got some snacks with my friends.
Do you have any glue?
I have some in my room.
Miho,
how is Daebak doing these days?
Is he studying hard?
I don't know.
Why? You don't see him? Did you fight?
We broke up.
Why? Why did you break up?
Is Daebak seeing that other girl?
No. I'll tell you later.
Hobak,
my heart is still pounding.
Are you sure?
I asked Subak and she said it's true.
How could this happen?
This can't be.
Hobak.
We got lucky, didn't we?
I'm glad we signed the contract.
This is a good sign.
Right.
I felt so badly whenever I saw Gwangbak.
Just hold on for two more weeks.
What would you like?
What's going on here?
Hobak.
Minjung.
Sit. Sit down.
Hobak, let's sit down.
My hands are still shaking,
so I don't know where to even start.
I didn't believe it until now.
I was sure it was a  misunderstanding.
But now, I don't know what to say.
You divorced Subak because of her,
didn't you?
Hobak, let's discuss this next time.
There's no need.
It's all out in the open now.
I thought it was Subak's fault.
I really trusted you.
I trusted you, no matter what others said.
I'm sorry, but don't be so hard on him.
It's not his fault.
Don't you start.
I'm trying so hard not to lose my temper.
If it weren't for Gwangbak, I'd be screaming.
I'm trying to stay calm because of her.
Actually...
Aunt Sunjeong, how could you do this to me?
I respected you and I was grateful for you.
I relied on you after I got married.
I feel like I've been betrayed.
How...
She's my sister.
He's my brother in law.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
Do you know how my sister is doing?
Do you know what happened to my parents?
My parents can't sleep at night.
It's not her fault.
You know nothing, so stop this.
- Let's go.
- You can't go like this.
What's wrong is wrong.
Had I known, I would've done something.
I fell for his lies and blamed my sister.
You're mistaken if you think you'll be happy.
It's not too late yet so end it.
Didn't you feel guilty to see me?
You didn't feel guilty?
You're too brazen. I'm shocked.
I'm shocked you could smile at me every day.
Gwangbak, that's too harsh.
She didn't do anything wrong.
It's not like what you think.
Don't side with her.
What you two did is a sin.
You should have nothing to say!
But what about Miho?
Don't you feel ashamed?
She broke up with Daebak.
How could you break her heart like this?
Gwangbak!
I'm disappointed in you, Minjung.
No, I feel betrayed.
You and I know what happened.
How could you stab me in the back?
You fooled Subak.
You fooled everyone.
I never did anything to deserve this.
Be honest.
I am being honest.
You've been seeing her for a while.
We were friends, but we didn't keep in touch.
She looked after your father.
I had no choice so she did me a favor.
I couldn't hire a caregiver,
and Subak refused to do it.
So I had no other choice.
I never did anything wrong.
Believe me.
How can we?
You divorced Subak and you're marrying her.
I don't want to continue arguing.
I don't know how to explain this,
and I don't feel the need to.
I'm leaving.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry
I put you through that.
What did you do all day?
I've been to places.
Whenever I didn't feel like going to work,
I wished I could sleep all day.
I wished I had nothing to do but hang out.
But having a job is a precious thing.
One never knows unless he loses it.
That's because we're fools.
The media's been talking about how people live to be 100,
but I never paid attention.
I regret not preparing for this.
What am I going to do until I'm 100?
I envy you so much.
How about working as a security guard?
Security guard?
I know someone who owns a small building,
and she needs someone to maintain it.
It'll give you a place to go every day.
You can think about what to do there.
I'm sorry.
I know you've never done anything like it.
I said that out of frustration.
I'm home.
You're home?
- Hello.
- You're home.
Hi.
I wanted to be the first to greet him.
Go ahead, Yeongdal.
You're home?
Did you have a drink?
Yes.
You've been drinking every day.
You should quit drinking.
How can you drink at a time like this?
We must make money and buy a house.
I know.
You're right.
Isn't this too hard for you?
When I'm with Don, everything is fun.
You should join us.
He can't do stuff like this.
Why not?
I can do it.
Don,
doing this on a winder night, eating snacks,
is really fun.
Losing a house is making us do weird things.
I know.
Subak, thanks!
That rude little girl!
I'll have to teach her a lesson.
Where's Bong?
Is he sick?
Honey, aren't you having breakfast?
Why aren't you getting up?
Bong, are you sick? Huh?
No. I just feel sleepy.
Oh, boy.
Why are you sleepy all of a sudden?
You always wake up early.
Bong, if you're sick, let's go see a doctor.
The breadwinner can't be sick.
What's going on?
Why don't you get up?
Everyone's here, worried about you.
If you're sick, say it.
- Oh, boy.
- Leave me alone! Please!
Let me sleep.
I could sleep in.
Whats wrong with that?
I...
Why are you screaming when we're worried?
If I'm sick, I'm sick.
I don't have the right to be sick?
Fine! Be sick if you want to be sick.
I can't believe my ears.
All my life, I lived like clockwork,
so I'm trying to sleep in and be sick.
What's the problem?
Bong, is something wrong?
No. There's nothing wrong.
I'm going to work. I am.
Oh...
[Provisional Attachment of Property Notice]
You'll do it?
I can't say no to anything right now.
I don't know why I hesitated.
I still have a lot to learn, I guess.
Who cares if I was a vice principal?
I care.
You've always been a teacher, so I know!
But you are a bigger man.
Others would be so conflicted.
Men have a hard time after they retire.
Jangbi,
I only want one thing.
Before I die, I want to
put my name up on my own house again.
Will that day come again?
Haebak and Daebak.
I have to take care of those two,
and to think about moving from
one place to another, at my old age...
Isn't he too old?
Don't judge him by his looks.
He's a meticulous man.
He retired from being a vice principal.
I only care if he'll be a good security guard.
Excuse me.
Yes, yes.
Competition in this field is high.
Everyone wants to do this.
I know. Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Please keep the entrance clean at all time,
and you must clean the restrooms, too.
You never said that!
It comes with the job.
Can you start right away?
Yes, yes, I can.
Hello.
I called because I think we must meet.
There's no need.
I answered to tell you not to call again.
I won't answer when you call.
I'm hanging up.
Excuse me,
I'm older than you, so listen to me.
Why can't you see me?
Did you do something wrong?
No, I didn't.
It's not like we'll never see each other.
Because of Gwangbak and Sangnam,
we because in laws, so don't do this.
We have to meet, eventually.
I'm sorry.
I know what you're going to say,
but I have nothing to tell you,
and to be honest, I don't want to see you.
Are you psychic/
How do you know what I'll say?
When an older person asks you to meet...
I'm sorry, but I'm hanging up.
Hey! How dare you!
What's wrong with her?
Excuse me.
I know you're uncomfortable.
Just hold on a few more days.
And I'll tell Sangnam.
They were selling shepherd's purse.
I'll make soy bean paste soup with it.
That sounds delicious.
My mouth is already watering.
Try smiling. We should.
You and I both know what really happened.
Aeji's grandmother called.
Again?
I told her I'm not going to meet her.
Was that a mistake?
No, you did the right thing.
No need to meet her.
If she calls again, don't answer it.
You know what she'll say.
I have nothing to say to her,
outside letting her beat me up.
I feel guilty.
Don't be.
Why should you?
Go, Minjung. Isn't it Jungji's first birthday?
Yes. I'll be back.
One, two, three!
I'm here.
Hi.
Welcome, Minjung.
- Welcome.
- Dad!
Hi, Aeji.
Oh, Jungji.
Happy first birthday.
Now that both parents are here,
let's start Ko Jungji's first birthday party!
I've always been paid to host these events.
Sedal, do it for free, for me. Start.
Let's see him choose his future career.
Let's see what he'll become!
Time to find out what Jungji will become!
Jungji, grab one! Go!
He picked up the spoon!
That means he won't go hungry!
Good, good!
That's not enough. He should be successful.
Not going hungry is the best!
Maybe he'll run a really big restaurant.
- Take some pictures, Don.
- Okay.
Let's start with Subak's family.
Yes, you should.
- Get closer.
- Closer, closer.
One, two, three!
She's moving out?
She doesn't want to run into me,
so she's getting a room or something.
She'll tell Sangnam later.
She'll try to defend herself.
What happens when Sangnam's father finds out?
He'll hate me.
He loves her to death.
Even so,
he wouldn't side with her.
Oh, who knows?
People put their family first.
I was on Minjung's side,
but now I'm on Subak's side.
We thought everything was Subak's fault.
Minjung is a really bad person.
I didn't want to see him when he came in.
Oh, I can't believe I feel this way.
I'll be going.
Why can't you play with the kids more?
I have to go to work.
Aeji, I have to go.
Dad, bye.
- Tell him to come again.
- Come again.
I will.
Jungji, happy birthday.
Daddy has to go.
Can I talk to you?
Bye.
- Bye, Minjung.
- Goodbye.
This is for Jungji's party.
Take it.
Can we go somewhere and talk?
What's there to talk about?
I'm sorry.
For our kids' sake...
Hold on, please.
Let's go somewhere and talk.
It's too late.
I'm leaving.
Subak,
don't even come back again.
If I want to see the kids, I'll come.
So don't come here anymore.
I'll be back.
Why did you let him go?
Why didn't you ask him to talk to you?
Go after him.
Stop it, mom.
If I don't go to work, I'll get fired.
He told me not to be late.
What if you lose Minjung for good?
There's something you don't know.
Now he's visiting to see the kids,
but when he moves in with her, he won't.
He won't want to upset her so he won't see the kids!
What do you want me to do?
I'm sick, so stop pressuring me.
He doesn't want me, so I can't do anything!
Give up. You should give up.
Then what about your kids?
Can you raise them alone?
I will. I can do it.
How can you, when you have no money?
Tell me what you plan to do.
I don't know! I don't!
What's wrong?
Why are you screaming?
How can we help it?
Minjung is awful.
He won't even talk to me now.
How can he change overnight?
He doesn't care about us anymore.
And Subak here is sick.
I can't take this!
He's not family anymore.
Don't expect anything from him.
Father!
Help me.
Please help me.
Oh, when did you get here?
Why didn't you call?
Can we get a drink?
Including me, everyone in the family wants you back.
I'm sorry.
It's over.
I know, I do.
You already submitted the papers.
Why wouldn't we want you back?
My wife keeps calling you because of that,
and I want to hold on to you, too.
But all we can do is wait.
Minjung,
can you reconsider all this?
I'm begging you.
You should think about the kids.
It's better for their mom to raise them.
I'm sure you don't want to see her now,
but it'll pass with time.
That's what being married is like.
Look at Hobak's family.
They are doing okay now.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about many things.
But I can't go back.
I'm having a hard time because of that.
But it's harder for Subak.
You're meeting someone new,
but Subak was dumped.
You saw her.
She looks awful now.
Can I ask you something?
I heard the woman you're seeing now
is Sangnam's aunt. Is that true?
Yes.
And you knew her from before?
I'm not very happy about that.
You said there was no reason when you
divorced my daughter, but that was a lie.
That's not true.
I know.
You're not that kind of man.
I believed that.
You told us she was a caregiver and had her take care of your father.
You knew her before you got married?
Does your father know about her?
No, he doesn't.
I'm disappointed in you.
I feel betrayed.
How could you do this to me?
How could you deceive your father...
Was that why you divorced Subak?
I swear it didn't happen like that.
Subak was...
What did Subak do?
Tell me.
It's nothing.
But I didn't cause the divorce.
You're truly awful!
You're still blaming Subak?
This is fraud.
I didn't know your true colors.
I was mistaken.
Father.
Have a seat.
I just need to mop the floor.
I just saw Minjung.
Have a seat.
Subak.
Yes, father.
I think we need to let him go.
The divorce became official long ago,
but we were all holding onto him.
Let's let him go.
Whatever the reason.
Let's do that, okay?
Father,
I think I was immature.
I regret the way I lived before.
There's no one like Minjung.
I'm so sad,
and I miss him so much.
But...
I was so bad to him, so I can't ask him back.
I'm going crazy.
"I did this for you."
"I was so good to you."
"So you can't leave me."
I can't even say any of that.
I never cooked for him,
and I never did his laundry.
I hate myself for that.
Bringing up the past will only make you sad.
What about the kids?
I'm going to raise them.
All I have left are the kids,
so I can't give them to him.
But you don't have the means to.
Even if you got child support,
will Minjung give them to you?
Didn't you give him sole custody?
I'm going to get it back.
He can have more kids when he remarries,
but it's different for me.
I gave birth to them.
I want to raise them.
Father, help me with that.
How come you're coming home together?
We were talking.
Talking about what?
To let Minjung go.
Are you crazy?
I can't! I won't!
I won't let him go.
Did you marry him?
Let him go.
I know how you feel, but it's too much.
I'm too much?
They say you can never really know someone,
but I never knew Minjung would do this.
How devious of him!
He had an ulterior motive,
and we well for that.
Don't call him names.
It just wasn't meant to be.
Subak's innocent.
How can I just sit here?
Honey, isn't there some law against this?
Ask if we can nullify the divorce.
How can you just sit here, doing nothing?
What's the use of holding onto him?
Watch me!
I'm not letting him do this!
Because this is unfair!
Salla,
I rented this whole place just for you.
Stop.
One, two.
One, two, three.
Oh!
Mommy!
Can you wrap up?
I'm leaving now.
Okay. Have a good evening.
Thanks.
Tada!
What are you doing here?
Hobak, let's do something real naughty.
Don't waste money on stuff like this.
I didn't use the living allowance.
I saved money by clipping coupons.
Tell me what you want to eat.
Let's grab some late-night snacks.
Is there a 24 hour barbecue place?
Of course.
Where else would I use my inheritance?
You got inheritance?
Sell me and use the money.
- Ugh!
- Oh!
Let's go. Let's go.
Make me a wrap.
Okay.
Hold on, my lady.
Here.
Man.
You must have been really hungry.
It's good.
I'm not the one eating.
It's for the baby.
"Crying Out Love, In the Center of the World."
Crying out baby, at a barbecue pork place.
Excuse me,
my wife is having a baby. It's our third kid.
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
Hello,
my wife's pregnant with our third kid.
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
What's wrong with you?
I won't tell my family or your family.
It's all gone?
Huh?
Can we get 2 more portions of pork?
My wife's eating for 2.
Please.
I'm so happy.
I'm so glad you're happy.
We should wait until it warms up, right?
- For what?
- Our wedding.
I'm not interested in getting married.
What did you say?
I don't want to get married.
You fraud!
You were playing with my heart?
Man!
I never did. What did I do?
Why didn't she let me finish?
Salla! Salla! Salla!
Salla! Ouch!
Salla!
So that's why it felt so awkward.
I never expected that from Minjung.
Maybe that's not the whole story.
I have a feeling he didn't.
Maybe he did it to get back at Subak.
Oh... If he just met her, maybe.
But he's known her for a long time.
They fooled the whole family.
And she even took care of his father.
Oh, it's giving me a headache.
That's their family's problem.
You focus on our baby.
How am I going to raise this baby?
I thought things were getting better...
I'll raise the baby.
I've been studying, reading books.
Giving birth is serious business.
You worked all through your pregnancies,
and I feel so sad when I think of that.
So you know it's hard?
Why wouldn't I?
I feel guilty.
When you had Sintong, I ran away, scared.
When you had Bangtong, I wasn't happy.
I thought you ruined my life.
I was so immature.
I thought the kids were a burden.
I didn't know how precious they were.
I never bought you anything yummy to eat.
I only caused misery for you.
Hobak, you should relax and enjoy your life.
I'll make it up to you.
I'm serious.
I heard women want to be treasured when they are pregnant, and I'll treasure you.
If you want anything done, just ask.
Do you mean it?
I do! Why don't you test me out?
Strawberries?
I want strawberries.
Okay, strawberries it is!
Little darling, hold on.
Daddy will be back.
Salla, hold on.
Just listen to me.
Stop following me.
Let's talk.
I have nothing to say.
Why do you always jump to conclusions?
You don't want to marry me?
After proposing?
I was going to say that was how I felt before.
Come with me.
Man...
Yes.
Bong comes out whenever we do this.
Ugh, you should be more careful.
There are other people living here.
We didn't do that, you know?
Oh, Anggeum, stop lying!
Mom, you were in there?
You saw us?
Oh, no!
Of course, I did.
I didn't want to come out and disturb you.
My butt is all frozen now.
Anggeum, you were pretty affectionate.
You dragged Bong into the shed and outside.
When? I never even kissed him.
Then how did you have 5 children?
Anggeum, you're so cheeky.
Bong, did you like kissing Anggeum?
Huh? Well, I...
Answer her.
She's asking if you liked it.
Yes, yes, I liked it.
I actually loved it.
Mother, I'm going to work.
- Yes, see you later.
- Have a nice day.
Hello.
Yes, manager.
Okay. I'll be right there.
What's going on?
We need you at the factory.
Yes, mother.
Minjung, something awful has happened.
Jungji is burning up.
But there's no one home!
Jungji's sick?
Okay, I'll be right there.
I'm sorry, you go first.
I'll come later.
But this is really urgent...
Please take care of it.
Jungji!
You're here already?
Let's go to the hospital.
The car's ready.
Oh, he's fine now.
He was burning up before.
He was burning up?
The fever broke now that you're here.
Minjung, go.
Don't come even if my mom calls.
Why not?
Jungji's better, so take Subak out.
I have to go to the factory.
Take Subak out for a drive.
Mom, what's wrong with you?
Don't beg.
My kids aren't bait.
And don't call him when he's working.
I don't like it when you do this.
You're driving me mad!
I can't believe her!
I'm doing this for you!
Mother, please stop this.
I was needed at the factory, but I came here.
Why did you lie to me?
You lied to me first.
Didn't you fool Subak first?
I can't watch you getting remarried.
You got divorced because of that other woman, didn't you?
What did Subak ever do?
It's over now.
I'm not going to let you push me around.
I'm taking the kids this weekend.
That's that.
You can't take the kids!
How can you do this to me?
I'm taking you to court!
Fine. Do whatever you want.
Do whatever I want?
After ruining my daughter's life?
How can you dump her after cheating?
How dare you have the audacity to walk around with your head held up high?
Please stop this.
I'm taking you to court.
You don't deserve any mercy!
Fine, take me to court!
What?
Okay. Let's go to the police.
You should be in prison!
I won't let you get away with this.
I was good to you!
How could you!
How could you stab us in the back?
Please!
I wasn't going to say this,
but do you know why I got a divorce?
It was because of Subak.
Subak
had an affair with that company's president.
What?
I wasn't going to submit the divorce papers.
For the kids, I didn't want to,
I thought I should let it pass.
But when I found out that she lived with a man in college,
I couldn't handle it anymore.
That's why I got a divorce!
Thank you. Please come back.
Goodbye.
It was you! Wasn't it?
- What?
- You told Minjung, didn't you?
Mom, let's not do this here.
What's going on?
What are you going to do about Subak?
Minjung knew about it all along.
Oh, no.
Subak cheated on him?
Did she?
- Oh...
- Mom!
Where were you?
Minjung took the kids.
He took them all saying he'll raise them.
What?
Oh...
Mom! What was grandmother saying?
Minjung took the kids!
He took the kids!
What?
Mom!
Subtitles by KBS World
Don't touch me.
I've completely lost my mind!
You're scaring the kids.
I'm taking my own kids, so shut up!
They are Minjung's kids, too.
What are you doing?
Bring the kids out.
She wants them back?
Mother's still young.
She should remarry.
Please don't talk about my mom.
If I talk, you're dead.
You want me to beat you up?
What did you do with your New Year's bonus?
You're giving money to your in laws now?
I'll be grateful for the rest of my life.
Please don't come to me again.