Subtitles by KBS World
Please come pick up your drink when it buzzes.
Hello.
I'd like to see you.
Okay. I'll be there.
I ordered a small latte macchiato,
not a tall Americano!
How many times did I say latte macchiato?
I'm sorry.
I'll make you another one.
How can you mess up the order?
Let me make you another one?
Stop making mistakes. Where's your head?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you worked here.
A little during the day, a little at night.
It's just for a few hours a day.
I'm trying to keep myself busy.
This is my first time, so I make mistakes and get yelled at which makes me forget.
No matter how hard you loved,
your business at hand comes first.
It's the same for everyone.
I only heard yesterday that your parents are against the marriage.
I'm sorry.
Sangnam is in a lot of pain.
If it's something my family can solve,
I'd be more than willing to do,
but since it's your family's decision,
there's pretty much nothing either me or Sangnam can do.
I'm sorry.
How is Sangnam?
He never shows his feelings.
But I can imagine how it must be.
He just works all day.
They broke up?
Yes, see?
Sangnam would do anything I say.
But that's not like Sangnam.
It is like Sangnam.
Why don't you introduce someone to him?
But I don't know anyone.
He really broke up because you told him to?
He really did.
My son's a good boy. He sure is.
A good boy?
How?
Having a sick person in the family is hard.
It was really hard when your grandpa was sick.
The Korean War was nothing compared to that.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
It's hard on the caregiver, too.
How's he going to look after him?
My sister from Paju is there for now,
and my other siblings live too far.
Subak will have to take turns with her.
But he's her father in law.
She can't really take care of him.
She can't help him with the chamber pot.
She'll just have to.
Maybe she can't help with the chamber pot,
but she has to help feed him and run errands.
I'll make money and pay for a caregiver.
I can't actually do it.
Why do things like this keep happening to us?
Maybe we should call for a shaman.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
I'm sorry about everything.
Don't be.
How can people steal from farmers?
God will punish them, wherever they go.
Thank goodness you weren't hurt too badly.
I hope you get well soon.
Thank you.
I'm always causing you trouble.
Especially when Minjung's living with you.
Please don't say that.
Taking care of your father must be hard.
I'm sorry, but I have to say something.
My father's had surgery.
Subak should come see him, shouldn't she?
Stop that.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
But my wife is sick today,
so Subak had to take care of her children.
She'll come as soon as she can.
Minsu, what is it?
I have to go home. What should I do?
You should go, then.
How can I leave him all alone?
He can't even move.
What is Subak doing?
She's busy.
Still, how can she not even visit?
I forgot to mention it to her.
Don't even try.
Then how could your father in law know?
You're always on your wife's side,
so she thinks she's better than us.
You should go. I'll be right there.
Hey! Watch where you drive that thing!
- What the heck!
- I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Make soup with this and take it to the hospital.
I don't know how.
Don't say you can't. Just try.
Ask your mom how to do it and learn.
Why didn't you visit your father in law?
I was going to, but mom's sick.
I have to feed Jungji and go to work later.
When your father in law's at the hospital,
you should drop everything and visit him.
You're making me look bad by not going.
What is it?
How can you be such a blabbermouth?
What did I do?
You wanted to keep this a secret!
You wanted this to be a business trip,
but you turn around and tell everyone?
Do you know what your father and uncle tried to do to me today?
How could they bring a baseball bat?
Were they trying to kill me?
Don't you know that's against the law?
I almost called the police.
Tell your family to stay out of this.
I don't want them ganging up on me again.
You're driving me away, remember that.
How dare they?
Mom!
Sedal, what's going on?
I couldn't reach you.
What is it?
I had a problem, but it's okay now.
So you're not on a business trip?
It's like a business trip. I'm getting paid.
Mom, don't worry. It's a good thing.
It's a good thing? Okay.
I moved into your apartment. Isn't it great?
I'm selling my beauty salon,
and I bought a make up shop.
Hobak, this must be a great apartment.
See? Everyone's doing so well.
You got promoted, and I bought a makeup shop.
Everything worked out so well, right?
Yes.
Come to the grand opening, okay?
You have to help me with the party.
Mother, I'm home.
Hi.
- Hello, Bong.
- Hi.
What about dinner?
A meeting ran late, so I ate there.
- Okay.
- Did you have dinner yet?
There's nothing to eat.
Anggeum won't even go into the kitchen.
Mom, but you ate a lot.
You even had scorched rice soup.
Why you little! Why don't you go to work?
I'm done for the day.
Bong, go and rest. You look tired.
And stop worrying about your children.
You might be able to hide from your past,
but you can't hide from your destiny.
Things work out according to your destiny.
Things happen because they're destined to be.
I know.
Don't give in to Anggeum first.
Make sure you put her in her place.
I won't give in to her.
I have nothing to say.
Good.
They really aren't talking to each other.
A woman shouldn't be too stubborn.
Has Anggeum always been like that?
She wasn't.
When she first got married, she was so nice.
Subak got her looks from her mom.
So she changed because the marriage was that hard?
It's not like it was hard just for her!
It was a difficult time for everyone.
Did you turn Anggeum into a witch?
What?
I remember hearing her say
how she used to be a nice woman
but you turned her into a witch.
Why you little!
You believe her? She was lying.
Is Jungji better?
What about?
He was throwing up last night.
Mom, Jungji threw up last night?
I think he had indigestion.
You sound like you don't even care.
What do you mean?
Why did you feed him?
Why did you make him throw up?
Did you give him anything spoiled?
I worked my butt off to take care of your kids and this is the thanks I get?
Babies throw up.
You think I gave him poison?
I didn't mean it like that.
You don't do it for free.
I pay you, and I want my money's worth.
What?
Oh, whatever!
You promised to raise them, so you should do a good job!
Then you raise them.
I'm too busy to raise them!
I have to go to work!
Take the soup!
I made it despite being sick!
Ugh!
Oh, man!
Oh? Oh!
Hey...
Hey!
Man...
Uncle! Look what you did!
Likewise! Look what you did!
Oh, man.
Minsuk.
I'm saying hi here.
How is he?
Can't you see?
I brought soup. Give it to him.
I spilled a big on the way here.
Tell him I was here. I have to go to work.
Hold on.
I don't believe you!
Do you know how long father's been here?
How could you show up this late?
I've been busy.
Minjung hasn't told you?
I know you're busy.
But you're Minjung's wife. Act like it.
Minjung spends every night here.
What if he gets into a car accident at work?
I'm a daughter in law, too,
so I wanted to leave you alone,
but you made me furious.
I'm going to be breathing down your neck.
You've been doing that already.
What?
You always pick on me.
That's breathing down my neck.
You nearly drove me mad with your nonsense.
I never said anything because I put Minjung's happiness first.
Act like a proper daughter in law.
Take care of him by yourself or hire a caregiver.
What? How can you just leave?
I can't do this.
I was in the Miss Korea pageant!
Miss Korea is a person, too!
Even if you were Miss Universe, now that you're someone's wife, you must act like it.
Minsuk,
he's your father, not mine.
Why do I have to take care of him?
Your father's a vice principal.
He should've taught you better than that.
Why do you keep bringing my father up?
What does my father have anything to do with this?
It's not like you helped him get that job.
You're impossible.
If you don't want to make your father look bad, be a good daughter in law.
Wha...
Man!
Parcel service!
Yes, I'm on my way.
I know you're busy.
You didn't have to come.
I am but I thought I'd drop by.
I heard you got a job.
Yes.
That must be hard.
I'm sorry.
Are your kids doing okay?
Yes.
The nurse asked for his urine output.
The urinal's right there.
I can't do stuff like that.
Just leave it.
Minjung can do it when he gets here.
Go get his food and help him eat.
He needs to eat, so he can take his medicine.
Excuse me?
Okay.
Oh, my! Ouch! Ouch!
Oh, man!
She works at the cafe at the intersection.
She needed something to occupy her mind.
When I brought you up, she just cried.
You think it's easy to make money?
Minjung.
How did you know?
I couldn't call you,
so I called your office and they told me.
Your father's hurt?
A little.
His surgery went well.
He'll have to stay here for a while.
Your nose is bleeding?
Huh?
Yes.
How?
It's from exhaustion, I guess.
Who's looking after him?
You're already busy with your work.
My family is trying to work things out.
I never met him before,
but can I come in and say hello?
Oh, good shot.
You just need a little more practice!
Really?
Doesn't my swing look great? Huh?
I'll take you out on your first round soon.
This is nutty, nutty, nuts!
Nutty, nutty, nuts!
Yes!
I'm home.
Mom, how was your day?
Good.
Where's grandmother?
She went out with aunt.
Mom, I'm hungry.
I'm working, but I'm happy.
Mom, you're the CEO. What am I?
You're an employee.
I want to be vice president.
You can be whatever you want.
What about the rice?
It's ready.
Oh! My!
You're good at this.
How did you do it?
It's easy.
The rice cooker does it for you.
There's nothing hard for you, is there?
You're creeping me out.
And the soup?
Kimchi soup. There was nothing else.
Ugh.
This is just great!
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Take these sandwiches.
Don't skip lunch.
Thanks.
And don't get caught working there.
How did you know?
Word travels fast in this neighborhood.
Don't you want to be a writer? Just write.
Mom, I made sandwiches. Try some.
Oh, you're the only one who cares about me.
You did well on the exams, didn't you?
Please become a judge and make mom happy.
Mom, mom, I'm in a hurry.
My boss wants me to come to work right now.
Haebak, can you pick up Aeji?
Mom's too sick to go.
See? This is what my life looks like.
Don't ever get married.
Just live with me.
Ugh.
Yes?
I can't come today.
I have to babysit.
Nobody cares about me.
What?
The beauty salon woman's grand opening?
A makeup shop?
Thank you.
Why did you get a divorce?
Irreconcilable differences.
Kids?
One son.
- How old is he?
- Three.
Who is raising him?
His mom.
Do you see her?
When I pay alimony and when my son wants to eat something special, we go out sometimes.
A three year old boy has cravings?
She's using her son as an excuse to see you.
Are you jealous?
Are you crazy?
Wow, the great Ms. Wang Subak is jealous.
She's no match for you.
Is there someone you're seeing?
What do you want to know?
You're married, so I can't hang my hopes on you.
Yes, it's me.
No, I've been busy.
Don't start whining again.
I'm home.
You're early.
Hey, your mom won't make us lunch,
so we're playing for Chinese food.
- So, what's happening?
- With what?
Oh, you said you'll find a woman for you uncle, so what's happening?
Your uncle can't wait any longer.
I'm asking around, so don't rush me.
If you want just anyone, that's easy.
But a woman who's rich and good looking isn't easy to find.
You sound really annoyed.
Did someone slap you?
Nobody slapped me!
You're making me mad!
Oh, boy.
Don't get mad. Take your son.
- Oh, man.
- Oh.
What happened to him?
Why did he get hurt?
I didn't do it. I don't know.
Hey!
Mom!
Mom, what happened to my son's face?
Kids get hurt all the time playing.
Kids get hurt all the time?
You neglected him, and he got hurt!
What are you doing to my kids?
What do you mean by that?
Kids get hurt all the time growing up.
What if he gets a scar?
Ugh, kids fall down! That's normal.
How could you say that?
It's better not to get hurt!
You feed him god knows what, you make him fall down and get hurt.
I can't believe you!
You think I have nothing else to do?
I took my eyes off for only a second!
How can you yell at your own mother like this?
If my son got hurt, you should've told me.
How could you hide it from me?
Then you raise your own kids.
I don't know why I even bother.
Why did I ever tell you to move in?
Ugh.
You're the one who told them to move in.
I know.
And I'm being punished by having to raise her kids,
and look how she's yelling at me.
You reap what you sow.
You worshiped Subak when you raised her,
so you have to suffer the consequences.
She didn't worship me!
You don't know what you're talking about!
You're just snapping at everyone today!
Now you're turning on me?
Grandma, you should stay out of this!
Ugh, seriously!
How dare she! She has no appreciation!
I knew this would happen.
What do you mean?
You should hide your affection for your kids, not worship them like gods.
I knew Subak would turn on you someday.
Please don't add to my misery.
- Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
- Ugh.
- What are you doing?
- Just come with me.
Yes, it's me.
What is it?
Are you mad?
You left without a word.
You were busy talking on the phone.
Why is Ms. Almighty acting this way?
Being jealous of little girls.
Whatever. Why did you call?
Because I miss you.
Subak, do you want me to give you a chance to make an investment?
Seriously?
If you can get some money, I'll let you in.
How much are you talking about?
More the better.
I'll double it within a month.
Oh, my, really?
But I don't have any money.
You don't have a hundred thousand?
If I did, I wouldn't be living this way.
It'll turn into two hundred thousand?
Of course. Get a loan or something.
Your father's a vice principal, right?
School teachers have the best credit.
I can't ask my father for that.
Isn't there another way?
Oh, there is.
What is it?
Gwangbak.
Hi.
Oh, my!
You work here?
You're a lowly part timer now?
Everyone in your family works part time, huh?
What do you mean?
Your uncle and you.
That's only two people.
Two people in one family is a lot.
You keep getting weirder and weirder.
Even your face looks odd.
Quitting your job made you a nobody.
I used to envy you as a student.
Oh, you're dating a high school dropout?
Who told you that?
Everyone knows it, girl.
I posted it on my blog and everyone went wild.
Hey!
Why would you scream?
There's no secret in this world.
how could you date a high school dropout?
It must be hard to go down to his level.
It's not like that.
You better watch what you say.
Calm down, girl.
Here's my business card.
My mom opened a makeup shop.
She's president and I'm vice president.
Oh, can I order some coffee?
You better say hi.
I'm your brother's friend!
If you do this...
What?
I won't deliver pizza to your place.
Hey, Don!
I don't hang out with part time workers.
[Vice president Heo Yeongdal]
Vice president...
Hey...
You don't have to call me about every little thing.
I'm stuck at the hospital.
Why did you come?
I brought some food.
He needs to eat well to get well.
You didn't have to.
You're making me feel badly.
If you have something to take care of,
I'll stay here, so go and take care of it.
It's okay. You're busy.
I'm not busy. I have time.
So hurry up and go.
I'll tell your father I'm a caregiver.
Well, then,
I'll be back soon. I'm sorry.
Don't say you're sorry.
I won those bottled water at a giveaway,
and I want them all delivered today.
I think we have to deliver them.
If we don't he'll post complaints on our site creating bad publicity.
Oh, it's delicious.
I'm glad you like it.
Have you been doing this for a long time?
Not very long.
I need to make money.
Okay.
How many kids do you have?
I have one daughter.
She must be pretty, if she took after you.
Would you like to see her picture?
Sure.
Oh, she's precious.
She looks smart.
Everyone says that.
Hello?
Sunjeong, I'm sorry.
I had to make some urgent deliveries.
I'll be there as soon as I finish this.
If you're in a hurry, you can leave.
Will you stay a little longer then?
Thanks.
Who is it?
Who are you?
I'm Miho.
Miho?
Oh, you're Sunjeong's daughter.
Open the door. I'm your aunt.
She has a boyfriend?
Yes.
You gave her the perfect name.
Does this feel good?
Yes.
Oh, you're back.
Thank you so much about today.
I shouldn't ask you to do things like this.
It's okay, Minjung.
Call me when you need me.
I'll come.
My house is pretty close.
This will never happen again.
I'm very sorry about today.
I said not to say you're sorry.
What's this?
It's nothing.
What is it?
It's not much.
Hire a caregiver with this.
This is too much for you.
- Don't do this.
- I want to.
This will make me feel better.
You can pay me back, if you want to.
But still, I can't take this.
People are watching.
Bye, Minjung.
Sunjeong, don't do this to me.
You're crossing the line here.
I couldn't handle this.
I'd rather die than take this money.
I know you care and that's enough for me.
Go. And don't ever come back.
Thanks for today.
Father!
Girl!
You still scream "father" when you're scared?
So odd. Everyone else screams "mommy."
Nice house.
How did you get in here?
Your daughter's a smart girl.
Miho!
Mom.
I said don't open the door for strangers.
She said she's my aunt.
Look what you're teaching your kid!
Go up to Sangnam's room.
Get up.
You're crazy.
Look who's talking! How could you do this?
Get out.
This is my husband and my son's house.
I didn't know they were loaded.
That's Daese's chair, so get up!
What the...
Fine, I'm getting up.
Happy?
How did you find this house?
Didn't Sangnam tell you?
He came to see me.
Sangnam did?
We're mother and son.
You can't get between us.
Leave before Daese comes home.
I didn't get a penny when I got divorced.
I should see him at least once.
Daese will never see you.
What did you just say?
You think you can get money from him?
That won't happen as long as I live.
Daese and Sangnam had a hard life.
What about me?
You think my life was peachy?
When they were living in this big house, I was living like a dog.
Now they're living with you.
Why are you living with Daese?
What are you expecting to get?
Watch your mouth.
You screwed up my life,
and I had to flee to Geoje-do Island.
I ran into Daese there by accident,
and I've been living in this house since then.
That's it?
What?
It's as if you were the lady of the house.
You have feelings for Daese, don't you?
How dare you slap me?
You feel guilty, don't you?
Our parents did a great job raising you!
Oh Manjeong, I'm sick and tired of you!
Get out! I'm going to protect Sangnam!
Let go of me!
Are you crazy?
I'm Sangnam's mom!
How dare you!
Get out!
Hey! Let go of me!
- Get out!
- Let go!
Let go! Ugh!
If you ever come back, I'll kill you!
Hey! Oh Sunjeong!
Let me have my shoes!
Hobak!
Oh, uncle.
You're home from work?
I have to go back later.
You're a busy man.
And you're taking classes?
I have to work really hard.
Vice president isn't enough for me.
I'm going to president.
Did you and father meet Sedal?
Yes.
Is father really angry?
I never saw him so angry before.
He took a baseball bat to beat Goof-off up.
And? Did he beat him up?
What do you think?
He just scared him.
Why didn't you talk him out of it?
You're worried about Sedal?
I was worried about your father.
Sedal deserves a beating.
I guess you're on your husband's side,
but I would've beaten the crap out of him.
Why would you break your father's heart?
He cried.
How could you make mom and father fight?
They don't even talk to each other.
This family is a mess right now.
Subak, I'm sorry.
Father says mom favors me,
but father's always on your side.
You don't think I'm upset at father?
You said you wouldn't disappoint father.
So show me.
Either divorce him or learn to control him.
You only have two choices.
Stop dragging your feet like this.
A married couple should be a unit.
Maybe not one unit, but still a unit of sorts.
Whatever.
You two should be as one.
Mom, I'm sorry.
You and father had a fight?
It's my fault.
I wanted to be happy,
but it didn't work out, mom.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
But I don't want to do anything I'll regret.
Please give me some time.
I won't disappoint either of you.
Father.
You're going home?
Yes.
I heard you and mom had a fight.
I heard you don't talk to each other.
What about Sedal?
Did he call?
Don't worry about it, father. I'm okay.
When I can't handle it, I'll tell you.
Okay.
Go home.
Good night.
Oh, Sangnam.
What are you doing here?
I can't believe I ran into you like this!
I'm so happy to see you.
How have you been?
Are you here alone?
Can I sit down?
I'd like to be alone.
I don't know what's going on,
but you shouldn't drink alone like this.
Pour me a drink.
Oh, there's no food.
My treat.
What's good here?
Cheers!
What are you talking about?
I saw them with my own eyes!
They were drinking at the tent bar!
How could he do this to you?
Ugh!
Huh? Now I remember.
I told you about seeing Yeongdal with a man
in front of the movie theater, remember?
That was him! What a bastard!
He broke up with you because of Yeongdal!
Are you serious?
Dead serious!
He chose her over you!
He wouldn't do that.
He's not a two timer!
I saw them with my own eyes!
Gwangbak! Gwangbak!
Should we get another bottle?
No, no more.
Let's get one more bottle.
I'm drunk.
I'm a working man,
so I must get up on time to go to work.
You can skip work just one day.
Oh, I'll help.
I'm fine.
I can walk fine.
You're drunk,
so let's go get some coffee.
Yeongdal,
don't waste your time on me.
I
have someone I'm in love with.
Hey!
Hold on!
Good morning.
Hot chocolate.
Oh, my!
Oh, my! Fire!
You fool!
Look at what's happening to this family!
Why can't you get up and cook?
Is your back broken?
All you do is lie down!
Grandmother, stop it.
Mom's miserable.
Mother,
I'm not coming home tonight.
What?
Why not?
I'm going on a business trip.
How can you work after eating like this?
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Gwangbak, take this medicine.
We need to get the fever down.
Gwangbak!
You haven't eaten in days.
Have some bread, okay?
This just might kill you.
I hope you like the perilla leaves.
Mmm,
it's good.
You're a great cook.
I'm glad you like them.
You're here.
Yes.
I ran over to help him with lunch.
She's taking great care of me.
She even made side dishes for me.
I'll bring some warm water.
What did you say?
Stop coming here.
Minjung.
I appreciate you coming here to help me.
I do, but it's not right.
It makes me uncomfortable and nervous.
I'm okay with this, so don't feel badly.
It's not okay.
You have a family and a husband.
What if he finds out later?
I was your ex-boyfriend for heaven's sake!
Put yourself in your husband's shoes.
If you were my wife, I couldn't understand.
I couldn't forgive you for that.
Why do you make things difficult for me?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I made things difficult for you.
But you shouldn't feel that way.
Just let me do what I can.
You need someone to take care of him,
but you can't afford to hire anyone.
This has nothing to do with you.
It does.
He's your father,
but you won't take my money!
I can't ignore you when things are hard.
I just can't do that.
So let me help you out.
Sunjeong,
I know how you feel.
And I appreciate it.
I have a conscience.
Go. Don't come back.
I don't want to see you like this.
Minjung,
I don't have a husband.
I was afraid you'd feel uncomfortable
and sad if you knew that I'm divorced.
I'm single.
[Grand opening]
What happened to Mrs. Wang?
She never comes to our meetings anymore.
It's because her son in law went bankrupt.
I'm sure she's embarrassed.
She was too much to handle, remember?
You switch sides so easily.
You were as thick as thieves with her!
We just pretended to be on her side.
Did you call your brother?
His phone was off.
I sent him a text, so he'll show up.
He better!
Oh, he's here! My son's here.
Sedal!
Oh, my son!
I'm glad you came.
This is it?
I would've opened a bigger one for you.
Did you get the tree I sent?
Yes.
Is this your car?
It will be.
Where are you staying?
It's top secret. I should go.
Madam Park Salla, I hope you hit the jackpot.
Come in and make everyone jealous.
- Huh?
- Hurry, hurry.
Oh, hold on...
Whoa!
Everyone, my son's here.
Hello.
Thank you for coming to my mother, Madam Park Salla's, grand opening ceremony,
and I'm going to take you out to a hotel buffet in the near future.
Wow!
He said hotel buffet.
Hotel buffet? How amazing!
Oh,
I have an important meeting,
so I have to say goodbye here.
I hope you and my mother remain good friends.
Oh!
Madam Park Salla.
Goodbye, my darling son!
What are you doing?
Step aside.
It's amazing.
What does it sound like?
Amazing.
Sedal!
Let's talk.
I have nothing to say.
Don't rat on me to your father.
Hey, hey!
Oh, the engine sounds amazing!
It's crazy!
Sedal's gotten so awesome, huh?
It's like he has transformed.
Women must fall all over him.
You should keep your guard up.
- What is it?
- Mom, where are you?
You said you'd be back soon!
Jungji won't stop crying!
And I have to go to work.
I don't care. He's your child.
I'm not a nanny!
Mom! Mom!
Oh, man!
You're materialistic.
You're really mean.
You make me feel embarrassed, did you know?
Fine.
I'm a materialistic witch.
So what?
I've been a housewife all my life,
and all I have to show for it is my old body,
and you're embarrassed?
Others run their own businesses,
but all I am is my daughter's nanny.
People respect you because of your job,
but nobody respects me! Not even you!
Do you know how I feel?
Do you?
Subtitles by KBS World
My sister's sick.
A real man must protect the woman he loves!
What am I going to do with you?
Even when your daughter's dying,
all you care about is bragging to others!
I found a woman for Sangnam.
Okay, I'll meet her.
But I told you what to do.
If it goes wrong, my father would kill me.
Let's get a divorce.
You!
Don't push me any further!