Subtitles by KBS World
Where's Gwangbak?
We went out early to do research.
She's not going to debut as a writer this year.
She's all bluff, like someone I know.
Just say she's like me.
Don't beat around the bush.
But you still understood.
Mom, the soy bean stew is extra delicious.
I didn't know it was this good.
That means you're old.
How could you say that?
Do I look old?
Everyone thinks I look younger than I am.
No way.
You're all bluff, too!
I'm not!
You bluffed about finding a woman for him!
I've been asking around, so hold on.
Just forget it!
I'll die before that happens.
You have to be careful setting people up.
It's not like he has anything to offer.
Yes, he does!
You're embarrassing me, mom.
He works part time and makes money,
and he's learning how to make pizza
so he can open a pizza shop.
I'm not expecting much for a daughter in law.
I just want someone who won't cut me off
and drive me crazy whenever I talk.
Don't beat around the bush.
You want someone who's not like me.
You understood, so I'm good.
Grandmother, you're just as bad.
You say whatever you want to say.
I'm a descendant of the six martyrs.
I say what needs to be said, no matter what.
I know.
You must work at a nice place.
You can come and go as you wish.
Of course.
What my mom just said...
I know. I'll find someone.
I don't care about anything else.
I know, money.
I'm not totally crazy about money,
but because of where I am right now,
it would be nicer if she had some money.
I don't care about the looks. You know?
I said I got it!
If she's rich, she could be an old hag.
I'm not that desperate.
Oh, my!
Hello.
Excuse me?
You must be doing really well.
You look better than when you lived at my house.
Who...
You don't remember?
I was your landlady.
Oh...
You don't fight with your husband anymore?
You used to fight with him and cry.
I don't cry anymore.
Bye.
Hey, Mrs. Landlady!
I'm not married!
Don't call me "Mrs."
How annoying.
You said you're single, right?
I am, so?
Goodbye.
Friend!
What brings you here?
I came to see you.
Wow, you must be making lots of money.
Where's Yeongdal?
She went out to meet up with a friend.
You don't want Yeongdal to get married?
I do.
It's difficult to choose from all those men.
What kind of son in law do you want?
Someone rich and handsome with a good job.
And he must be good to me.
My Don is handsome, yes.
But he has no money.
He has no future and he has a part time job.
What kind of daughter in law do you want?
I don't want much.
If Yeongdal says yes, I'll consider her.
What?
You'll consider her?
I don't believe this.
Don't say that!
Loser has nothing to offer!
Goof off's nothing special, but he got Hobak.
If Don marries Yeongdal, we'd be even.
How dare you!
Don't even think about that.
I want you to leave!
And I don't want to be friends with you!
Don't push me.
If you act like that, your daughter's going to get old and die alone!
What? Leave!
Hey!
And don't come back!
The Korean War was nothing compared to this!
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Oh my!
You're full of energy, aren't you?
We're lucky that gate isn't broken.
This is all your fault.
What is?
You treat Don like dirt, so everyone else does!
Anggeum, I fixed the stroller.
Hey, don't say hi to the beauty salon woman.
Don't even talk to her when you see her.
Tell her to keep her stupid daughter!
I should just die!
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo!
She must have asked her for her daughter.
Don, don't even think about it.
I don't want her.
I couldn't, if I wanted.
What?
Nothing. I fixed the stroller.
Hey.
Uncle, are you free tonight?
Really?
Who is it?
Is she pretty?
I thought you didn't care.
Just meet her.
She's a semi real estate tycoon.
Semi real estate tycoon?
Why would she want me?
This isn't working.
This is nutty, nutty, nuts.
Dad!
Boys!
- It's dad!
- Dad! Dad!
What's wrong with you guys?
It's been so long, they're happy to see you.
What are you doing home?
Mom, why are you home?
I had to close the shop for your kids.
Hobak asked me to take care of them.
I'm making spicy rice cakes.
I don't want that!
I want dad's pizza.
Pizza! Pizza!
Dad, have some!
I don't like this kind of food.
I'm more of a rice and kimchi kind of man.
Sintong, Bangtong.
This is just a "what if."
If we were to live without mom...
I can't even talk to you!
I'm not even finished yet!
I miss mom so much!
Why would you say that?
I said "if."
If mom doesn't come back from her trip...
- Mom!
How can you cry at the word "mom"?
Man!
Why are you crying?
Why did you make them cry?
They started crying when I said the word "mom."
It's like they're orphans or something.
At their age, they need their mom.
They don't even want to eat right now.
Who goes on a business trip just like that?
Mom.
Do you have any money?
Money? How much?
$100,000?
What?
I wish I did!
How can I have $100,000?
You can't borrow it?
I don't know anyone who's that rich!
Why? Why do you need it?
I need it for something.
What about your rich director?
Why don't you ask her?
Man!
This isn't working.
I think he gave up.
He didn't.
He's trying to get the money.
Please give him more time.
I'm bored.
Is there anything fun we can do?
Do you want to play go stop?
That's lame.
Do you know how to play cards?
No.
How about chess?
Can you dance the waltz?
Let's just play go stop, okay?
I'll teach you.
Once you get into it, you'll never stop.
A few coins can give you loads of fun when you play go stop.
No thanks.
Oh, this is nuts.
[Only the first place can be Choi Daese's daughter in law]
Four people got eliminated on the way.
I'm so nervous.
Get in one line!
We'll move to the dorms!
Let's go.
Change into the uniforms and gather outside.
Huh? Where did the luggage go?
Mom, what is it?
Where are you?
Why did you take the luggage?
I told you,
I'm going on a trip with my friends.
You never said that!
You're not in that audition, are you?
Assemble!
I got to go, mom!
Listen carefully.
All your personal information will be sealed.
You'll be addressed by your number.
Here are the rules to the audition.
You will take five tests, and for each test,
the two lowest scores will be eliminated.
And in the final round, test number 5,
only one person will be picked.
We don't need 2nd or 3rd places.
We only need the 1st place winner.
There can only be one daughter in law.
The contents of the tests are top secret.
You all must pay close attention.
[Choi Daese's daughter in law audition]
Are you kidding me with this?
They can't be normal.
They probably came for the pay.
I can't believe you're doing this.
Just watch.
I'm going to eliminate that rude girl.
How dare she do this to me?
Let's go! Let's go!
- Hey!
- Let's go! Let's go!
Hey!
Yes! Yes!
Let's go!
Oh, Jangbi!
look at her! Look!
She did this! Whoa!
Look at her!
Let's go!
Let's go, number 1!
Man...
Woohoo!
That was a warm up.
The real audition will start back at the school.
Warm up?
This wasn't part of the test.
You should've told me that!
I thought this was a test so I gave it my all!
That sucks.
I can't believe this!
I'm leaving!
I don't want that!
Jangbi, I like her.
We're not looking for your wife.
She's proud and passionate.
You want a daughter in law like her?
Isn't the rude girl also proud and passionate?
Man.
See? You actually like girls like her.
Don't even joke about it.
I hate rude girls.
Man...
The first test is on basic knowledge.
[Choi Daese's daughter in law audition Crossword Puzzle Test]
I'm too weak, and I lost my appetite.
Anggeum, this is for you.
What is it?
Mother lost her appetite,
so can you make something for her?
Make her some sailfin sandfish stew.
It'll make her appetite return.
I'm hanging up.
What did Bong say?
I don't know.
Oh...
If you were that nice to your wife,
I'd be carrying you around on my back.
Oh no.
What is it?
Oh no!
Oh, my!
Oh, no! What am I going to do?
What's this?
Anggeum! Anggeum!
Oh, no!
What? What's this? What's this?
Man...
Anggeum!
Where did you go?
To the pharmacy.
What's that smell?
You almost set the house on fire!
What were you thinking?
You could've burnt the house down!
Oh, man.
My heart is still pounding.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
It's so cold.
Ms. Lee Anggeum, parcel delivery!
You darn dish!
Mother!
Why do I bother living?
The chores never end...
I must be the only one living like this at this age!
I'm old, my body's not like before,
but there's so much to do around the house.
Now I have to take care of my grandkids.
Subak says she'll pay me,
but I don't care for that anymore.
I can't do this!
Jungji hurt his finger playing with a toy,
and my heart can't take it anymore.
It feels like I committed a crime.
I'm so nervous that I can't breathe.
I'm so sorry... To you...
And to Subak...
She's going to flip out when she comes home.
Oh, why should I bother living?
Mother, don't worry.
I'll come home early tonight.
I brought spicy chicken, your favorite.
I dropped by just to bring you this,
even though I wasn't in the neighborhood.
Have some and feel better.
I don't want any spicy chicken.
I'll clean up here.
Oh...
How did you do?
Did you do well?
I don't know. It was so hard.
What was the point of that?
It was so funny.
But it's kind of fun, isn't it?
I'll get paid even if I get eliminated.
Didn't you see? They pay you.
Right. It's better than working part time.
Why didn't you let me see it?
Cheating would've gotten us eliminated.
The eliminated will be announced after 60 seconds.
Here are the two who've been eliminated!
The first one is
Number 7.
This second one is
Number 8.
Yay! I passed!
This is the cap for the 1st place winner.
The 1st place winner for this test
will be announced in 60 seconds.
Boo!
Number 4!
Passed the 1st test. Won 1st place.
Aunt Sunjeong!
She passed the first test.
Congrats!
Man, I already got eliminated?
- How annoying!
- What was that?
We'll start the second test.
The second test is on entertaining guests.
You're having a housewarming party.
You must get the party going!
You must know how to drink, dance and sing!
The winner will be announced in 60 seconds.
Please step back.
I pick Number 1.
I pick Number 4.
Jangbi, you can't do that.
Number was the best dancer.
- Don't you think?
- I pick Number 4.
She was beyond funny.
The most entertaining by far.
I pick Number 1.
Number 1.
Here they are!
The eliminated are
Numbers 3 and 6!
The 1st place winner of this test is
Number 1!
Man...
You don't have much time left.
This is nuts.
[House deeds]
Give me some breathing room!
I'll call you when I get the money,
so stop calling me and driving me mad!
Both of you have to be here since it's in both names.
And I'll need both of your signatures and IDs.
It's an emergency.
Can you help me out?
Half of it's mine, so can I  get half the loan?
I'm afraid I can't.
Mom!
Sedal!
Sedal! Sedal!
You have to come back! You have to!
If you don't bring the money,
you know what will happen to your wife.
Man!
What's wrong with him?
This is nuts.
The person you have called is unavailable.
Your call will be directed to voicemail.
He turned his phone off.
I don't think...
Hold on.
Please go to him.
He'll get the money.
I can't...
It couldn't be...
[Godfather Payday Loans
Immediate money in your pocket]
You loved taking my money, didn't you?
You said you'd pay it back, so pay it back!
I will! I promise!
Please don't kill me.
Start writing.
Write what?
That you're donating your organs.
- Who's there?
- Who are you?
Hey!
This is nuts.
How's Hobak?
Is she alive?
Would you like to come and see?
No, I'm never going back there again.
Where's the money?
Well, actually...
Let's do this.
Can't I pay it in installments?
What?
I've seen a credit card with $100,000 limit,
but I've never seen that amount in cash.
I went to the bank for a loan, and they said no.
I tried to get a mortgage loan,
but they said both of us must be there.
I never had even $100 in my wallet,
so how can I get $100,000?
So I was thinking,
can I make a monthly payment of $1,000?
Are you kidding me?
Please help me out here!
My boys can't live without their mom.
They start crying if I just utter the word "mom."
You want a monthly plan on ransom?
I'm out of options here.
Or give me a discount!
I could get $10,000, if I tried.
No, $20,000! $30,000!
I can't do anymore than that!
I could get a loan through my mom.
Don't try to negotiate.
It's $100,000 or nothing.
Fine!
Let's cut it down to $50,000!
I can't do anymore than that!
Let's make it $50,000, okay?
Fine. $50,000.
You have until 5:00 p.m.
After that, you'll never see your wife again.
I can't get it by 5:00 p.m.
Give me one week, okay?
No, three days!
No, tomorrow! Can it be tomorrow?
No.
Please! Give me a break.
I didn't even call the police!
So you can't pressure me like this.
Please give me more time.
I've said what I came to say.
This is nuts.
I don't care!
I don't care what happens to Hobak,
so don't call me, okay?
Do whatever you want to her!
I don't care!
I don't care anymore!
I don't care what happens to Hobak,
so don't call me, okay?
I told you I'm divorcing her!
Do whatever you want to her!
I think it's time for you to make your decision.
Mother!
Oh, you're home!
Subak's not home yet, is she?
She called from the fruit shop.
She's getting some tangerines.
She'll start yelling if she finds out.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Let's hide him.
Okay.
- Jungji.
- Where can we hide him?
In the bathroom?
She'll find him right away.
Where? Where?
In the closet?
- Closet?
- Hold on.
He couldn't breathe.
Mother, this way.
Let's leave him in grandmother's room.
She doesn't go in there much.
Okay.
- Here, here.
- Oh, okay.
- This won't work.
- Somewhere else.
- Get a blanket.
- Okay.
Mom!
What's going on?
What do you mean?
Why did you come out from there all panting?
- We were moving something.
- The baby...
What?
We moved some things.
Yes, right.
What were you moving?
Jungji!
Where's Jungji?
Grandmother took him out.
She did?
What if he gets hurt?
She wanted to show him off at the senior
center because he's pretty, like you.
But that's nothing.
We've always been pretty.
Oh!
Why did you come home so early?
I didn't have much to deliver.
What about the hospital?
Sunjeong, I mean the caregiver is there.
I'm going to go soon.
The third test is risk management test!
Your house is on fire!
You must rescue your baby and escape!
Yes! Yes!
Mom! I won 1st place in two tests!
I have the highest marks!
There must be some really dumb girls there for you to win 1st place.
Anyway, I hope you win 1st place.
You should at least do it once in your life.
Again?
That's not good.
What do we do?
I might get eliminated.
You can't.
That's what my father wants.
What are the scores?
It's 2 to 1.
Next test is cooking. What do I do?
Everyone will be bad at it.
You should try your best.
Make it as delicious as you can.
I should've learned to cook.
What are you making?
It's top secret. I'm so nervous.
Look, Mr. Park,
you said you'd take care of it!
I must have some inheritance.
I want it now and you can't do it?
I'm not going to the board meeting.
If you keep this up, I'm taking legal measures.
I drew you a bath.
Dad,
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
I'll go through the lawyer.
Just do what my lawyer, Mr. Park tells you to do.
Your bath..
I don't want anything else.
I just want what's rightfully mine right now.
But that's not yours!
Grandfather left it to me!
I'm not going back to the States.
I said no!
Your bath...
What's wrong with you?
Dad, talk to my lawyer.
Can't you see I'm busy?
Why are you talking about the stupid bath?
How can you hold down a job, being so dense?
Can't you see I'm talking to my dad?
I can't see anything right now...
I'm going out.
Hey, hey...
This is nuts.
- Hey, Sedal!
- Oh, hey.
It's been a while.
What's up?
I heard you were busy.
Let's play some golf, okay?
Let's go next week.
Do you have some time?
Yes. You want coffee?
Or let's get dinner a little later.
I don't have time for that.
I'm in a hurry.
Can you lend me money?
Money?
Yes, can you lend me $100,000?
Oh, I have to finish writing a report.
Hey, Goof off, call me later, okay?
Hey...
Hey, Goof off.
Hi.
Are you busy?
Can we get coffee?
I know why you're here.
What?
These days,
it only takes a minute for word to spread.
It's an amazing world.
Everyone's talking about you needing money.
I was going to ignore you,
but I thought I should give you some advice.
I heard you hooked up with a rich woman.
You abandoned your wife and kids?
We don't think you're worth our time.
For money?
What you did is unspeakable.
Why do you need to borrow money?
She ran out of money?
Why don't you sell that watch?
Wake up!
[Pawn Shop]
How much can you give me?
how much do you want?
I'd like $50,000,
but I'll take whatever you can give me.
It's not an average watch,
so don't put it with other watches.
And don't show it to anyone.
I'll come back for it in a week.
Did you buy this?
I didn't really buy it.
It was a gift?
Yes.
From a woman?
Of course.
Why?
You should keep this instead of selling it.
What?
I can't cook.
Me neither.
No one here can cook well.
Everyone's the same.
I wish the contest was to eat this radish.
Let's start by eating the radish.
Really?
Number 4 won 1st place!
That was warm up.
- Darn it!
- Okay.
This is the fourth test.
The cooking test you've been waiting for!
Your parents in law came to your house,
and you must whip something up in a hurry.
We have some common ingredients up here.
You can take anything you want.
Mr. Choi Daese who's holding this audition will be the judge of this test.
You have 30 minutes.
Things are not going well.
She only did well on the first test.
Other girls are pretty good at cooking,
but Number 4 is not so good.
Can I ask you to do something for me?
I have some.
We brought some for ourselves.
Okay.
Oh, stir fried fish cake.
That looks really good.
Are you sure that's edible?
Oh!
What's this?
Soft tofu stew.
Oh, this smells good.
This looks very edible to me.
Can I have some water?
Of course.
- Here it is.
- Thank you.
Please stand in front of your dish.
Check your rankings.
1st place!
1st place! 1st place! 1st place!
Seven people remain.
Only the final test remains.
But the points given are the highest,
so we don't know who will win.
Oh...
Man...
Since everyone looks finished,
I think we should have a family meeting.
Family meeting?
Why not? Let's do it.
But what would you have to say here?
Why not? He's family.
Actually,
I want everyone to help with the chores.
Oh...
This is a big family,
but we all depend on mother alone.
She does everything for us.
From things like cooking, laundry, cleaning
to taking care of Aeji and Jungji.
I know it's my fault,
but I'm afraid mother will get sick.
People in the past did more!
Grandmother, stop saying that.
You always talk about the past.
Minjung is right.
We should've done this a long time ago.
Mother, she's no spring chicken.
She's old, she's over 60 years old.
Being over 60 years old isn't old!
She's in her prime!
You were born healthy,
so you're healthier than I am right now,
but I'm not like you.
I'm scared of everything I have to do.
Then we should decide what to do.
Mother, what do you think?
What should we do?
Can I tell you what I thought of?
Sure, go ahead.
Mother can continue to cook.
She is the best cook here.
And I think we should divide up the rest.
We can take turns doing the dishes and doing the laundry.
Uncle can clean downstairs,
and I can clean upstairs.
The front yard,
I think the men can clean it on Sundays.
Oh, that would be amazing help for me.
Then make a schedule and post it up there.
Haebak, you do it.
Okay.
The breakfast dishes can be done by
grandmother, uncle and Subak.
Me too?
Of course. You're very healthy.
Father, Daebak and I'll do the dinner dishes.
And Minjung can do them on Sundays, since you get off late.
Father, when should we start?
We should start this evening.
That means you have to go first.
Okay.
I'll start it off.
I don't believe this!
I have to watch him do the dishes now?
You're having a hard time because of your kids!
When my father gets discharged,
I'll come home early and look after Jungji.
You pick the time, too.
She's not doing it for free. I pay her.
It's not about the money.
We should talk about this.
You keep saying you pay me, but how much
have you paid me? $100 twice, $200 once.
I only got $400 from you. $400.
You've been raising your grandkids for money?
If I had to pay more, I'd get a professional.
Why would I have you take care of them?
And you won't stop nagging,
making them sick and hurt.
I can't help it if they get sick!
It's because you don't pay attention!
Come with me.
- Man!
- I don't pay attention?
I'm raising your kids for you and you say that?
I can't believe this!
You're worse than a mother in law!
I worked my butt off raising her kids!
And that's the thanks I get?
Then take your kids and move out!
Don't do that to your mother.
You heard what she said.
Having to live here is miserable enough,
but she tells me to take my kids and move out.
I thought you were upset, too.
Just let it go. You told me that.
Imagine how hard it must be for her.
When the kids get hurt, don't blame mother.
She was so worried that she cried.
Even though they're my kids,
it's hard to take care of them.
You shouldn't just leave them to her.
It's not like I'm doing nothing!
I have a job!
Mom said she'll take care of Jungji,
so I can go out and make money.
So why is she acting like this now?
You should fix your work hours.
You can't keep going to work in the evenings
to come home late or early in the mornings.
You have too many work dinners.
You drink every night.
You're a housewife.
Why does that matter when I have a job?
You work too, so how could you say that?
When I go to work, I'm not a housewife.
Do you hear her?
I could just slap her on the mouth.
Why didn't you follow them upstairs?
I'm not crazy!
She needs that.
Oh, I wish Minjung were our son.
A son like him would be so reliable.
Why are you smiling like that?
No reason.
Wash them clean.
Don't forget the corners.
I don't want to have to do them again.
Don't worry.
I'm meticulous.
Nice going.
Mother, this is actually fun.
I need to do this to be appreciated.
What if your father saw you doing this?
He'd say, "Good job! Good for you."
This isn't right!
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Father.
I'm sorry for all the trouble I caused.
No, don't say that.
We're actually pretty pleased.
Couples need to fight sometimes, too.
- Minjung.
- Yes, father?
It feels like you're really family now.
My wife is so happy with you.
You have to get married.
I want to move out of this house with you.
But nobody wants to marry me.
Who is she?
Semi real estate tycoon.
It means she has lots of land or buildings.
Is that true?
You're in luck, then.
I'll have to meet her to see if I am.
Go inside. It's cold.
You're meeting a woman.
I want to see you off.
Good luck.
I had a really great dream.
Divorce is in my future,
so  I should at least get married.
Of course.
Find someone different from Anggeum.
- Okay?
- Not okay.
Why you little!
Hello, I'm Wang Don.
I'm Ji Hwaja.
Hi.
I think I know why we're still single.
Excuse me?
It's so we can meet.
Have you been on many blind dates?
Just once,
but she asked
about my salary, house, and car,
but I'm unemployed.
So I kept my mouth shut,
and she just left.
I haven't been on any since then.
My god! How crazy!
You shouldn't meet women like that.
I'm forty and you're thirty five, right?
I'm older, right?
Yes.
I heard you were never married.
Every man I've ever met came after my money.
So I got really scared.
Use this.
This is your lucky day.
Excuse me?
I don't care if you have money or not.
I don't care what car you drive.
Why? Because I can buy you one.
All I need is a man with
a sound mind and a sound body.
And someone younger.
Rich women meet younger men, don't they?
Let's go out for dinner.
I'm not hungry.
My treat. Don't worry.
Here.
It's for coffee.
With me, you don't have to worry about money.
I have plenty of money.
Korean food? Chinese? Japanese?
How about Japanese?
Let's go get some Japanese food.
I come here often.
You don't eat food like this often, do you?
Order whatever you want.
My treat.
Okay.
When I get stressed out,
I come here and order whatever I want.
Say ah!
I can eat it myself.
Don't say no.
Ah!
How cute!
I don't think you'd stab a woman in her back.
I like you.
Do you like me?
Well...
I can't tell after just one date.
I agree.
So let's meet every day from now on.
Oh, my!
Stop this!
Man!
Miran!
Eun Miran!
She hasn't come home yet.
This is nuts.
He's at the summer house right now.
His phone is still off.
From what the maids are doing,
it looks like there will be a party.
I think this is enough.
Why don't we give it another day?
No.
What are you going to do?
Should I go get him?
So you can beat him up?
There's no need for that.
I was being stupid.
Now I know for sure,
so I'm over him.
I have no regrets.
Ms. Eun.
What are you doing?
Get out of my house!
I'm sorry. Forgive me.
I'm really sorry.
You weren't home and I was in a hurry.
I have no time to explain anything.
Don't ask me any questions.
Just lend me $50,000.
I know I shouldn't ask for money before we're married,
but please help me out.
Before we're married?
Married?
When did I say I'd marry you?
Wake up.
Are you delusional?
Then, were you toying with me?
We had fun together.
I can't believe you'd steal from me.
You're pathetic, just like others.
You are just like all the others.
You'd do anything for money.
You can call me names and treat me like dirt.
But you're the only rich person I know.
And I wanted that more than anything.
But please.
Someone's life depends on this.
I'm not buying this charade.
Get him out of here!
Hold, hold on!
Please help me out.
My wife is going to die.
What will my sons do if she does?
They cry when I merely mention the word "mom"
How can I let anything happen to them?
Miran, I mean, director!
Please!
A person's life is on the line.
She might die,
no, she might already be dead.
I'll do anything you want.
Please,
please help me.
I'm not asking for it.
Let me borrow it.
I'll give you the deeds to my apartment.
My wife is...
Stop.
You're so boring.
I thought you were different.
But you fell for it pretty easily.
Over a measly $100,000 credit card.
You're pathetic.
You sold your soul for money.
Get him out of here!
Agh!
I had fun.
Thank you for such a valuable lesson.
I wore these here, so I'm keeping them on.
If I hadn't worn these here,
it would've been pretty funny.
I'm leaving.
Oh!
The watch.
leave it there.
What are you doing?
Does that upset you?
We're even.
You destroyed my life just like that.
Like this fake watch.
Wait!
Put this on.
Man.
I knew you'd get kicked out.
There were many men before you.
But you lasted longer than anyone else.
And here.
This was delivered just now.
Goodbye.
It's freezing!
Why is it snowing all of a sudden?
[Divorce agreement]
Remember what I said?
You have no right to say you want a divorce.
And that I would bring it up.
I think it's time.
I'll see you at the court house.
Subtitles by KBS World
You're really going to make Sangnam marry the winner?
If I can break that rude girl, it's worth it.
I have something to tell you.
Congratulate me. I'm getting a divorce.
You must have been in a lot of pain.
What's wrong with you?
I think we're destined to be together.
You were with that woman you met?
We should plan the wedding!
If it weren't for her,
this wouldn't have happened!
Maybe I should just hire someone!
What did you just say?
I told you not to let strangers in!
- Take them out of here?
- What?
This is uncomfortable for both of us!