Subtitles by KBS World
Be careful. Don't get caught.
I'm actually petrified.
Should I just come clean?
There's no need to expose yourself.
Let's put it off as long as we can.
Okay.
[Wang Bong]
I'm never playing Go-Stop again.
Old bats!
Why don't you die already!
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
[Put Yourself in Others' Shoes]
Oh!
What are you doing?
Oh, you startled me.
Why can't you knock?
Knock? Yeah, right.
Come to my room.
Do you know what day it is today?
I don't believe this.
The day of your father's memorial service!
I did mark the calendar...
You're so dim.
What good would marking the calendar do?
You should mark it in your brain!
How come you only have one eyebrow done?
Are you going out?
I have a private fund meeting.
Don't forget to go grocery shopping because of your meeting.
I've been doing it for dozens of years.
You know your late father in law is picky, don't you?
Buy the fifty dollar yellow corvina, and...
Fifty dollars?
That's not much!
It's only once a year.
Make some pancakes and dumplings my son likes.
Why are you making that face?
You don't want to do it?
I'm not loving it.
Blame yourself for not having any daughters in law.
Come to think of it, you're pretty pathetic.
You have no daughter in law to cook for you.
You look awful.
And you look great because I cook for you.
Right. I'm lucky, I know.
You better watch out today.
Your luck is really bad.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
She has a knack for getting on my nerves.
You have bad luck, so you look awful.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
I guess you could call that a gift.
Hello? Yes.
Unemployment what?
Unemployment benefit? What's...
Hello? Yes, I'm Wang Gwangbak.
You didn't go to school?
I'm sorry, but you're not qualified for unemployment benefit.
Couldn't you have called me on my mobile phone?
Your mobile phone was off,
so I called your home.
Why would you be so kind?
Fine. Goodbye.
Why would you ask for that unemployment thing?
It's not for me.
Mom, I'm late.
Mom, your eyebrow,
don't forget the other eyebrow.
Hey,
be honest with me. You're not...
I'm not what?
You're spinning this into something weird again.
I asked because of someone else at school.
You've been acting suspicious lately.
And what's with the dog sounds at night?
I'll tell you someday.
You have a blind date Saturday!
The treatment went well,
but you need to be careful for a while.
Bean sprouts.
Next is meat, meat.
- This, this, this.
- Okay.
Oh, that woman.
She's going to try to crush me again by bragging away.
I can't take that again!
Her bragging days are over.
How so?
Gwangbak.
What about Gwangbak?
Charge, charge!
Crush them! Crush them!
Don't! No!
To the left, left, left!
Yes! Hey! You go in!
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm coming!
Nice!
Get rid of it!
Yes! Hey, it worked!
[Have a nice day!]
Got any money?
Of course not.
This is insane!
Where are we off to?
I don't know. Do you?
Those who give orders,
those who follow them.
That's the societal problem these days.
That's what they say.
I wish I was the one giving the orders.
I know.
What's life?
If you don't own, you rent.
You're either unemployed or have a part time job.
I majored in English lit not knowing what it was.
I majored in law and now I'm a law abiding citizen.
Hey! Madam Park Salla.
Where are you off to?
Hello.
I'm not going to get in trouble.
I'm going to be trouble!
You're not kids anymore!
When did these become kids' shoes?
I don't know.
Wow.
How cool.
Who owns a car like that in our town?
Move closer to them, real close.
Honk at them, too.
Real close, so they can see.
Oh, look at that car!
I don't believe it.
Do you see them?
I Just love this!
Mom, you're funny.
Preparing for the memorial service will be hard.
Should I send my housekeeper later?
It's okay. I have Hobak.
Sorry I'm late.
My daughter wants to say hello.
How have you been?
- How pretty!
- She's so pretty.
Thank you.
I'll pay for your meal, so please enjoy.
How nice of her.
She is so generous.
Your daughter's the only person who drives a car like that around here.
She just bought a car, but replaced it again!
I heard your eldest son in law treats you so well.
They say if you love your wife,
you love her family as well!
So of course he treats me so well.
Of the two son in laws,
which do you like better?
Oh, you have to ask?
My second son in law doesn't even try.
He's an unemployed bum.
She's here, she's here.
Why are you so quiet?
Were you talking about me behind my back?
- No!
- We wouldn't.
If your son is a bum,
don't let him get married.
You'll be ruining the life of someone's daughter.
Mother in laws these days are out to get their son in laws.
The world is coming to an end.
Wait until you get a son in law.
In the past, I used to be proud of myself,
but now, I'm proud of my children.
When your children do well, you look great, don't you?
- Right.
- Yes.
Your third daughter's next in line, isn't she?
So many people are asking me about her.
Doctors, judges and prosecutors.
Teachers are very popular these days.
She's meeting one this Saturday.
He's a successful dermatologist.
How nice!
Your son in law can give you a face lift!
She hasn't even met him.
Don't count your chickens before they hatch.
I'm sure it'll work out great.
Should we start a face lift fund and ask my son in law to give us a discount?
- Yes!
- Let's do that.
I heard lots of doctors are losing their jobs.
Are you planning on opening up an office for him?
What?
My daughter has a great job, so why would I?
To be frank, if your eldest daughter hadn't gotten plastic surgery, she wouldn't be that pretty.
And Gwangbak isn't all that pretty, either, so why would a successful doctor want to marry her
when she was fired from school?
What are you talking about?
She said she was fired from school.
No, no way!
She went to work this morning.
Didn't you know?
She's been hanging out at a cafe down the street,
and everyone knows that already.
And you call yourself a mother?
Right, I saw her yesterday.
She was hanging out there.
Oh, my.
She didn't even tell her mom?
Why would anyone quit a teaching job?
Those are my shoes!
Don't forget your groceries.
Slow down. You'll trip and fall.
Would you like to try that on?
I don't need to.
I know my body very well.
I'll take this.
Ma'am,
do you have another credit card?
Why?
- Yes, mom?
- Where are you?
At school, of course.
At school my butt!
Oh! Oh, no... Oh, no...
Oh! I'm sorry!
Oh no, I'm so sorry.
You!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
- Hello.
- Oh, hi, hi.
Oh, it's the geezer.
Mr. Vice Principal,
the ball...
Ugh...
What is it?
Come home right now.
Why? Did something happen to mother?
No, it's your daughter!
Gwangbak.
Why are you home so early?
Your mom called.
Did she find out?
I'm sorry.
You should've been more careful.
I have to go back to work before lunch.
I'm going to say I didn't know.
That's not fair!
How's that not fair?
I want to live, too!
Let's do rock paper scissors.
Look before you throw.
I'm not having a good day.
Why you little!
Come over here!
Mom,
sorry.
If you're sorry tell me what happened.
Why did you get fired?
I didn't get fired.
You didn't get fired?
Did you quit?
Why?
Why would you quit a teaching job?
She wants to become a writer.
A writer? Bah!
You've gone totally nuts!
How can you become a writer when you can't even write?
But I can!
I've written a few magazine articles.
When did you quit your job?
A month ago.
It's been a month?
So you lied to me every morning and went to that cafe instead of going to work?
I don't believe this!
Oh, go easy on her.
You hit harder than anyone I know.
You stay out of this.
I told you you'd have an awful day.
Mom, I'm going to become a writer.
It's my dream.
I'm going to become world famous, lie Psy.
Mom, you've heard of Harry Potter, right?
Helicopter?
Air plane, air plane!
Why would you take a helicopter when there's the air plane?
Anggeum, she doesn't mean the chopper.
It's Harry Potter.
What's that?
Helicopter or whatever it is, I don't care.
Do it while being a teacher.
How can she write while being a teacher?
Why not?
You can sleep less and write!
That should be easy!
It's not that easy.
Writing is a very difficult process.
Mom, I'm sorry I didn't tell you first,
but I'm not good at teaching.
I became a teacher because dad's a teacher,
and I thought it'd be a nice job for a woman.
Getting up early is really hard,
and I'm not the teaching type.
What am I going to do with you, huh?
Can't you see how everyone in the country is dying to become a teacher?
It's not everyone in the country.
Have you forgotten how everyone became envious when you became a teacher?
It wasn't everyone.
When will you become that writer thing?
You answer her.
I don't know. You'll need luck.
It's kind of impossible.
That's so sad.
I'll make it happen as soon as possible.
Quit!
Oh, man!
Put yourself in Gwangbak's shoes.
Afraid of you finding about it,
she couldn't even eat for the last month and lost so much weight.
Why would you do it if you're so scared!
Wait a minute, you knew about this, didn't you?
Huh?
Uh, no.
Did dad know about it?
Well, actually...
I'm sorry, dad.
Oh, man...
How could you?
When your daughter goes mad and starts talking nonsense,
you should be telling her right from wrong!
Instead, you lead her down the wrong path?
Must you be so cruel?
She says it's her dream!
Stop torturing him.
Why are you torturing my child when it's your child's fault?
I'm not holding the memorial ceremony.
- What?
- She's not doing the ceremony.
How dare you!
Mr. Ko!
The creditors were here.
What do we do?
That hurts!
Ouch.
What are you laughing at?
Why you little...
Let me go! That really hurts.
Then be quiet and follow me.
It hurts, let me go, let me go. Ouch.
Let's talk, man to man.
Why do you walk around during class?
Don't you get tired?
I don't really get tired.
Bring your parents in for a conference.
It'd be better to just talk to me.
I can't have a conversation with you!
I can talk to you just fine.
You're aging your teacher!
He's been old!
He's been old?
I can't believe you said that!
You can't talk to him.
It's impossible to communicate with him!
Go.
Bring one of your parents tomorrow!
Don't get your hopes up.
Mr. Kim,
you shouldn't use physical punishment like pulling the ear or hitting with the attendance book.
It's not easy for him.
You try talking to him for five minutes.
You'll go mad.
A kid like that, the parents are the problem.
We shouldn't blame the kid.
It's the parents' fault.
Wait for me!
Guys!
Guys! Wait for me!
Do you have a death wish or something?
You drink it.
I'm so sorry!
It won't be easy for you to get all of that by next week.
I'm not worried. I have you.
I'm an old man now.
Too bad your dad got hurt at a time like this.
I know. He's being a huge crybaby about it.
There they go again.
They look like a motorcycle gang.
Leave them be. They're pretty violent.
Even calling the police doesn't work.
Go easy on them!
Hey, you!
Stop that!
Hey, I said stop it.
What if I can't stop?
Hey.
What is this?
I got humiliated!
Why are my credit cards suspended?
You can't use them for now.
My company's in trouble.
But I'm going furniture shopping with my friends tomorrow!
But we just got new furniture.
That was two years ago!
Shopping's great for taking your mind off things.
If I can't get a new husband,
I should at least get a new bed...
That's enough!
You don't have to yell.
Grow up, please.
How can you...
What brings you here?
When was the last time you visited father?
Don't beat around the bush.
It's been a year since mom passed away.
If one of them passed away first,
you said you'd take care of the other.
I went to father's house last week,
and he's aged so much in just a year.
He said he should get a dog or something...
He's getting a dog?
He doesn't even like dogs,
so imagine how lonely he must be to say that.
Do they own you?
How can you say that? Own me?
My friend saw you at a barbecue restaurant.
You were laughing and having barbecue with your in laws!
I wasn't laughing.
How can you laugh and eat at the same time?
You went on vacation with your in laws.
Have you ever taken our parents on vacation?
You were always too busy for them.
We think we lost you.
I hate your wife but I hate you even more.
If you'd gotten your bearings straight,
this wouldn't have happened.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
If you know that, fix it.
Take care of father.
I will, but...
But what?
Do you need to get your wife's permission?
Actually, I'm not really...
You're not really what?
You're the richest of all four siblings.
The rest of us gave up everything for you.
When you wanted to sell father's land to expand your business,
we didn't object because you're the eldest.
I'm barely making ends meet, but if it weren't for my in laws, I would've taken father in.
I will take care of father.
You could've called instead of spending money on coming here.
Stop worrying about that and take father in this week.
If you don't, I'm going to bring him to you.
Mom's first memorial service is next week.
You do the ceremony at your house.
I'm so bored, I'm going nuts.
Nutty, nutty, nuts.
I'm going nuts.
Wang Don, come out and play!
Loser, come out and play.
Loser!
Loser's not home!
Loser? Did you call me loser?
Uncle, bring out the dishes...
- Grandmother, I'm here.
- You're late!
I came straight from work.
I can't believe my mother in law.
Why would she say something like that?
Like grandma said, it was worse than the Korean War.
Oh, my back.
Thank god it's grandfather's memorial service.
Why are you just standing there?
You came early.
Why don't you take a day off?
Mom can't do all this alone.
Hobak isn't a daughter in law.
Why would she take the day off to help?
You don't have a job,
so why couldn't you help?
Subak can't help.
She doesn't cook.
She'll just be in the way.
It's her good fortune.
It's all thanks to Minjung.
It was her fortune to have found a husband like him.
So get yourself a good husband.
Why am I talking to you?
I hate you!
Oh, mommy.
Let me go.
Get out of my sight.
Huh? This must be new!
How pretty!
Who bought you this?
Who do you think?
There's only one person who buys me clothes in this family.
I wonder what she does with all the money she makes...
Why would you pull something like that?
You broke mom's heart.
She was humiliated at the private fund meeting.
I'm going to become a writer.
Shut up! I'm not finished with you!
After that's done, clean the fish and steam it.
And season these vegetables. Hurry up.
Stop chatting and get back to work!
Your grandfather is probably starving.
You're all such useless girls!
Why couldn't you be sons?
Grandma!
They're a motorcycle gang.
Why would you follow around gang members?
They don't even want you.
Because I'm bored.
You're bored?
Do your parents know about this?
I don't think so.
Do you have a girlfriend?
You do!
What's your dream?
Dream?
What do you want to do?
What do you want to become?
If you can't answer in 5 seconds,
you don't have one.
You don't want to become a celebrity, do you?
I'm not a child.
What do you take me for?
Lots of kids want to become a star.
I'm not interested in stuff like that.
That's boring.
If you don't want a boring life,
you must have a dream.
When you have a dream, you don't get bored.
You don't get bored?
Then I'll think about it.
Not something your parents want,
but what you want.
Because you own your life.
In other words,
it's okay to make parents cry if it's for the sake of your dream.
Do you understand what I mean?
Start.
Okay.
But my son's missing.
[Rude Ugly Hag]
- Hello?
- I'm going to kill you!
How dare you?
You should come home before the sun goes down!
Do you even know what day today is?
You must be itching to get it!
I have a baseball bat right here!
Where are you?
Tell me before I beat you up.
Are you at an internet cafe again?
No, this is a Chinese restaurant.
Hello?
Isn't this Wang Daebak's mobile phone?
It is, but...
Who was that?
She's a rude, ugly hag.
I'm in the 7th grade, so leave me alone.
As if that's a title!
- Come with me!
- I'm in the 7th grade!
Let's bow.
Honey, this is nothing compared to what I used to make for you,
but what else can we do?
It doesn't look like much,
but it sure was expensive,
so enjoy your meal.
Have a grand feast in your afterlife!
Please make sure no ill fortune comes our way.
The other kids couldn't make it because they live in China and America.
So don't be all upset over it.
Honey, make sure our eldest son is healthy and find a wife for our youngest son.
His sister in law won't stop picking on him.
Honey, you know Bong is the best son in the world, don't you?
He brings me back to life whenever I get sick,
he always does that.
He won't let me come and meet you.
And our youngest son.
I'm so grateful you gave him to me before leaving.
Oh, he plays cards with me.
He's the only one who spends time with me.
If you hadn't given him to me before you died,
I don't know how I could've...
- Grandma.
- Yes?
You should tell us about your pregnancy.
Huh?
You'd never believe it.
I was old and I didn't know I was pregnant,
and my stomach started getting big.
Your grandfather was really sick and he kept asking,
"What's wrong with your stomach?"
So I said,
"I have no idea. I don't know."
We forgot what we did and blamed it on constipation.
It was so much trouble, worse than the Korean War.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Heat up the soup and bring some out!
Coming!
Sis, do the dishes later and come eat with us.
I'll just finish this up.
I'll have to do it sooner or later.
Okay.
Uncle, I need to talk to you.
I get scared whenever you say that.
I mean, why wouldn't you let my husband get a job?
He said that?
He said you told him not to because you'd be bored.
You won't have anyone to hang with.
Heo Sedal! I can't believe he said that.
And you believe him?
You were made for each other.
Eat up. Not leaving scraps is a way to save.
Mother, you eat, too.
I will.
Where are your husbands?
Why aren't they here?
They're all busy.
Even so!
You have to feel sorry for your father.
He has nobody to do this for him.
He has me.
Oh, I forgot all about you!
You're not the only woman who had a son at an old age.
I've suffered, too.
Giving birth at an old age must run in the family.
Why don't you have one, too?
Don't! It's too much trouble.
Just raise the two you have right now well.
Oh, don't worry.
I almost died trying to lose weight after giving birth.
It wasn't you!
Money did it for you.
Why couldn't you get dental implants for your only grandma with that money?
My teeth are so bad I can hardly chew.
You have problems with your dentures?
No.
Why would you ask your granddaughter that?
You have a son right here.
I'll get you new ones.
Tell her that after you actually do it.
Yes, sir.
Uncle, have some beer.
Your face changes every time I see you.
I could hang your pictures and call them the Evolution of Wang Subak, Before and After.
What do you mean?
She's always been pretty!
She was even in the Miss Korea pageant.
- She got eliminated.
- In the preliminaries.
To be frank, Hobak is better looking than Subak.
She's far more useful.
Don't say that.
We owe a lot to Subak.
It's not Subak!
It's all because of my son.
Subak bought us that TV,
bought us a new kimchi fridge last year,
and she got us a bidet.
She's been taking good care of us.
There's someone here who won't even buy us $1 undies.
They sell undies for a dollar?
They even have ones that are 50 cents.
Hobak's husband doesn't make money like Minjung does.
It's the thought that counts, not the money.
What's Sedal been up to?
Is he ever getting a job?
He keeps avoiding me.
He came over earlier, saying,
"Loser, come out and play."
He asked your uncle out without saying hello to me.
How dare he!
How is my son a loser?
He's the loser.
She ruined her own life.
Why was she in such a hurry to get pregnant?
She fell for his looks.
Hobak likes handsome men.
But he's not handsome!
He's all dark, with eyes all bulging out.
If she thinks he's handsome, he is.
The problem is that she's the only one who thinks that.
Why couldn't she get a job and help her family out a bit and let me find a husband for her.
It was so humiliating for me to listen to people talk about
her getting pregnant before getting married.
Nobody respects a girl who gets pregnant before getting married!
That's why she's living such a pathetic life.
That beauty salon woman used to suck up to me before,
but now that we're in laws, she belittles me!
Why would you bring that up now?
It's because I'm so frustrated!
Why can't she be more like her older sister?
Don't mind her.
She's just upset.
She doesn't hate you.
But this happens every time she sees me, every time.
It's already been 10 years.
This is all because I'm poor.
It's all because of money.
Daebak, Haebak.
I'm sorry for being friends with someone like him.
You didn't force him on her!
Don't treat your brother in law so badly.
He might be young, but he's still your brother in law.
You can't say that.
I was too busy taking care of him to take care of my own children.
It's your fault he turned out this way.
What? What did you say?
You cherished him, calling him your "precious son,"
and you spoiled him.
Bong got him jobs, but he couldn't last a month.
It's hard on Bong, too, you know?
That's enough.
Are you drunk?
I'm not drunk!
I only had one beer.
I'm not going to keep this bottled up.
Fine, go ahead.
You think you did a better job at raising your children?
When I fled from North Korea during the war
and started selling pancakes, I did pretty well.
I never lost money.
As for children, one's  a vice principal,
one's unemployed.
That about evens out, don't you think?
When I count Subak and Hobak, that evens out too!
Raising children isn't a business, so stop it.
Your mom started it!
He'll be forty soon!
How will he ever get married?
After mother passes away,
we'll have to take care of him!
You have a young child, too,
so don't be so mean!
Who knows what will happen to Daebak?
That's why I'm not spoiling Daebak.
I'm afraid he'll turn out like his uncle.
What?
Turn out like him?
I said stop it.
Why are you yelling at me?
I'm not making this up, you know!
Grandma, why are you picking on mom?
Mom has every right to say that!
She's worried about uncle.
Oh, you're ganging up on me?
I don't believe this!
This is worse than the Korean War!
Honey, why did you give me Don?
Your daughter in law is being so mean to me!
I can't live like this, honey!
Oh, honey!
Oh, honey...
I should die already!
I have nothing to live for!
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Stop saying that.
What's wrong with her?
Is she sick?
She's not sick.
She's old.
I'll yell at her later.
She'll yell at you!
Be careful.
When you quit your job, she'll come after you.
I won't let her.
She gets scared when I glare at her.
As if she's a cuckoo bird,
she laid her egg in my nest,
and look how she treats me!
She thinks she's old and frail? Yeah right!
And she says she wants to die?
What a joke!
What's wrong with you?
Today's my father's memorial service!
Imagine how my mother feels right now.
Sure! I'm the worst woman in the world, I am.
Oh, you startled me.
You're here!
Why aren't you going in?
I was waiting for you, so I can go in with you.
You're late.
I'll take these in for you.
I'm here.
Oh.
My precious Minjung.
Welcome, welcome.
- Hello.
- You came.
You're late!
Everyone's been waiting for you.
Don't be such a nag.
I'm sure he was busy with work.
The memorial went well, so don't worry.
You must be hungry.
Get him some food.
It's okay. I already ate.
You did?
Oh, then forget about it.
I haven't eaten yet.
Why did you come so late?
It's not like you have a job.
And what are you wearing?
It's so obvious your mom didn't teach you any manners.
Get him some food.
Minjung said he's okay.
Why bother?
- Mother.
- Yes?
Here.
Oh, grandfather will be very happy.
Would you like a drink?
I saved a yellow corvina for you, Minjung.
Oh, I'm so happy.
"My precious Minjung, my precious Minjung."
Whose am I?
Not hers, obviously.
Nutty, nutty, nutty, nutty, nuts!
Oh, man!
I'm never going to your house again.
It's not my house.
It's my parents house.
Right, your parents house.
They don't respect me at all!
You need to act respectable to be respected.
Don't you feel anything when you see Minjung?
What am I supposed to feel?
I feel persecuted.
What else am I supposed to feel?
I put your suit out for you.
Why didn't you wear that?
If you can't make money,
at least be well mannered.
I'm not the type to make money.
What do you want from me?
The become the money making type!
Then you stop going to your parents house.
They treat you so badly!
Why do you bother?
I just don't understand you!
Man.
Man, this is nuts.
You're right. I don't understand myself, either.
Why do I bother going over there?
Were you looking at father's picture?
So I don't forget his face.
I want to say hello to him when I see him in heaven.
Anyway, Bong,
what should I say when I see father?
I think it'd be really awkward.
Father will feel awkward, too, for he's never met you.
Even if it were awkward,
if I said, "Dad, hello.
It's really nice to meet you,"
then, would he recognize me?
I'm sure he will.
Would you like to have a drink with me?
Me?
Yes, you.
Mom, mom.
Oh, mother.
Open your eyes.
Mother, look at me.
What's wrong?
Bong's calling me.
- So?
- What do you mean, so?
He'll yell at me again.
If I don't come back in 10 minutes,
come and rescue me.
Gosh! You're on your own.
I'm so sleepy.
- Sit down.
- Okay.
I feel such sadness whenever I see you.
You were born after father died,
so you were never held by father.
You're like my own son.
You were born after Subak and Hobak were born.
I've raised you like my own.
I know.
Anggeum nursed me because mom couldn't do it.
But is that true?
I've never witnessed it.
Me neither.
I'm sorry, Bong.
Mom and Anggeum fight all the time because of me.
And I'm embarrassed to face my nieces and nephew.
If you're embarrassed, stop acting like a loser.
A man should never act like a loser.
How many years do you think mother has left?
She must see you get married and have children.
If mom dies,
it would be really awkward for me.
Awkward isn't a word you use in that situation.
Open the door.
I know you're not sleeping.
You must be exhausted.
Go to bed.
You've never won any awards at writing not even as a kid!
You'll never be a writer!
Some people are late bloomers!
I've worked for a magazine before.
How dare you! Open it!
Seeing my face now will make you even madder.
You'll wake Haebak.
She's such a hardworking student!
She needs her rest.
You'll wake Haebak.
She's such a hardworking student!
She needs her rest.
You, how dare you...
What are you doing?
Let's go downstairs.
Let me go.
I need to settle this tonight.
You can settle it tomorrow.
Let me go!
Man.
There's no use.
You know how stubborn Gwangbak is.
She really wants this, so let her give it a try.
She's almost thirty and now she's unemployed.
I can't let this happen. I'll kill her.
Hey!
Oh my!
Request to leave school.
I'm going on a search for my dream.
Goodbye.
Hey, Wang Daebak!
What's wrong with your family?
Not a day goes by without trouble.
What if things are the same after I marry you?
You're going to marry me?
Of course.
Anyway, Daebak,
what's going on with you these days?
You won't reply to my text messages.
I've been busy.
Are you seeing another girl?
Give me your phone.
Acting like this will just drive me away.
Fine, I respect myself too much to do this.
I won't dwell on you.
But you have to hang out with me today.
I have to go.
I'm going to kill you!
No.
Miho, would you like me to give you a push?
For real?
Daebak, this is so great!
Are you into me?
I am!
Daebak, you like me, don't you?
- I'm not mad!
- Oh, my!
Daebak, I'm going to kill you!
You just wait till I get a little older!
Sangnam!
Hey.
I did it.
What?
You told me to make my parents cry.
They'll be crying their eyes out.
What did you do?
I'm not going to tell you.
Hold on.
Hold it right there!
Why are you acting like this is you first day?
At this rate, you won't be able to go home tonight.
Finish it up, so you can bring cookies to your kids
tonight and have them welcome you with kisses.
Isn't that what you want?
[Request to leave school]
[Wang Daebak]
Is that the rude, ugly hag?
Yes.
You're not going to check that?
I know what it says.
I'm going to kill you!
My bat is right here.
What am I going to do with you?
Ugh...
Is she your mom?
My older sister.
She's not attractive, is she?
No.
Miho, you look furious.
I'll get him for this.
When he gets old, I'm going to make his life miserable.
Message, ang, ang!
Is it your boyfriend?
No, it's one of my sister in laws.
She wants to see me.
Oh, it's like I'm already married.
I better go.
Do you really like him that much?
Totally.
I think I can make a decent man of him.
You think you can train him to be a good husband?
Yes.
Oh, where's uncle?
I have to act out the TV drama and make money.
Do it tomorrow.
He'll be late.
I'm going to my in law's house.
My teeth are too weak for eating beef,
and my back is too bent for a new suit!
You know that old bat from the rice shop?
Her daughters in law took her to Jeju-do Island.
My sister Punggeum's mother in law left her $100,000 when she passed away.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Grandma, hello.
Welcome, my granddaughter in law!
She's not your granddaughter in law.
She's not even fully grown.
I'll grow up nicely and marry Daebak.
Just listen to you talk.
Daebak isn't home.
I'm here to see Gwangbak.
A strange guy? Who?
I haven't met him.
I asked who he is,
but he won't tell me.
Anyway, after meeting him,
he's gone completely wild.
He even ignores my text messages.
Can you talk to him?
These are the deeds to my factory and my house.
And these are to my car.
I know it's not enough, but it's all I have.
You can't do this to us!
That money was everything to me!
I'm sorry.
If you could give me some time,
I'll pay you back every cent.
Please drop the charges against me.
If I go to prison,
my family...
I don't believe this.
They must be shipped out in 30 minutes.
Let's hurry up.
Okay.
[Distribution Team 1]
[Manager Wang Hobak]
What is it?
Remember Mansang?
Oh Mansang.
The one who looks like this all the time.
- What about him?
- Well...
His wife is having a baby.
I don't know why he keeps making babies when he's broke.
So?
We're collecting $50 each to help with the hospital bill.
Oh Mansang had a son only three months ago.
Oh, that...
Was it three months ago?
I remember reading about it in world news,
but Koreans don't have babies that quickly?
Oh, it's Mansang's second wife.
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
- This is it?
- Give that back!
- What's this?
- You should carry more cash.
Hey!
Honey, I'll see you later.
Hey! Hey! Why that little...
Oh, man! Ugh!
You don't take care of the house one bit!
Why, you won't even say hello to your mother in law?
I know I live next door and see you every day, but still!
Your father's a teacher, but he didn't teach you manners, huh?
Hello.
I heard you give my son $3 a day!
He's unemployed.
He doesn't need money.
$3 is plenty.
Don't be so rude just because you make the money!
Who knows?
He might become really successful!
Don't belittle him just because your mom does.
When Sedal was single,
so many women came after him.
Just look how handsome he is!
He's blinding!
My father doesn't think he's all that handsome.
They say he's dark with eyes that bulge out.
Hey, he's got big eyes and nice big lips.
A man with big everything is a good thing!
If you hadn't gotten pregnant,
you'd have had no chance to have him!
You got yourself a younger man,
so treat him like a king.
You can't talk down at him and treat him like your little brother!
I'm sorry I hooked up with a man,
though only a year younger.
Only a year?
You've eaten a year's worth of meals more!
You're older regardless!
He eats more than I do.
And he has snacks and even late night snacks.
If you counted the serving sizes,
he'd be 10 years older.
And I don't like you going through my kitchen.
Sometimes, I'm too busy to clean up,
and I don't want other people rummaging.
Put yourself in my shoes.
What if I went to your house and started poking around, opening up everything?
But I'm your mother in law!
You can't act like me!
I can't believe this.
You were thinking bad thoughts about me, weren't you?
Dad!
Oh!
Aeji, what are you doing?
Playing with my doll.
But mom won't play with me.
Her nose hurts.
Her nose hurts?
Mr. Ko, have you eaten?
Yes. Can I talk to you later?
Oh, you're home.
I didn't like the way it looked,
so I got it done again.
It's my last time.
I won't touch my nose again.
It'll be dangerous if I do.
Oh! Remember my friend Seo Gija?
She had a big barbecue restaurant in Gangnam.
We went there a few times.
She went bankrupt and had to sell her restaurant and her house,
and now she lives in a basement apartment.
Oh, that's so sad.
I couldn't handle that.
I'd rather die if that happened to me.
Ma'am? Hello? Are you there?
The housekeeper is gone.
She'll come back for her stuff.
What?
You have to run the house from now on.
I can't run the house!
I have two kids!
You must be mad.
Yes, I am mad,
so you should get it together.
Why are you doing this to me?
I can't! I've never even done dishes,
not even once growing up!
You know that!
Oh, my nose.
Go.
Is that him?
Hey! Stop!
It's me, Choi Sangnam.
Really?
Find her.
I said I don't care how much money it takes!
Understand?
Hey! Stop!
Stop right there!
Subtitles by KBS World
Did a war break out?
Subak, Hobak, Gwangbak, Haebak!
What are you good for?
Why are my children always quitting?
Sedal won't help, so I've been trying so hard to save every penny...
I'm not going to think of you as my daughter!
Ugh! How could anyone love you?
I feel really bad, so I can't say hello properly.
Why don't we go to a police station?
You said you wanted to go to a police station.
I think I've seen you before.
That's way too obvious.
I saw something weird today.
Why? What was it?
Isn't that your brother in law?
Do you know what next Saturday is?
I told you, my mom's 60th birthday.
It's my mother's first memorial service.
Can't we do it another day?
What's this?
Tell your father to come and eat.