Subtitles by KBS World
What's this?
Black bean noodles.
I know what it is.
Why did you order this?
It's for father.
What?
Tell your father to come and eat.
It's been a year since his last visit.
It's the first time since mother's death.
How can you just order him noodles?
And it's not even special noodles.
How much was the dinner you just had?
He's my father, my father!
But there's nothing to eat at home!
The housekeeper is gone and I can't cook!
You could at least make an effort!
Have you ever cooked a meal for my father?
Even if you don't know how to cook,
can't you at least feign to make an effort?
Why are you yelling at me?
Why?
Stop it, please.
Why are you doing that?
Don't fight.
All I need is some rice.
I said stop.
It's father's fault, too.
Why couldn't he call us ahead?
How can he just show up out of the blue?
But this is his son's house!
I'm not comfortable!
You're uncomfortable?
Deal with it because we have to live with him.
What did you say?
Live with your father?
Yes, starting right now.
You don't want to live with me?
What is it?
I did everything I could for your family.
Why can't you do this one thing for me?
You might think he's an embarrassment,
an aged country folk, but he's my father.
He's still my father.
He brought me into this world and raised me.
He made me who I am!
I did my best, too.
I sent him money monthly and on holidays.
What more do you want?
I'm your wife.
So how can you bring him without consulting with me first?
Ask anybody.
Who'd welcome such a situation?
You just said that you're my wife, right?
Yes, so what?
This is what being married means?
This is...
- It was a woman before...
- This is Kim Siyeon.
You sound so young.
Living youthfully will do it!
Enjoy life!
She's really funny.
Don't you dare tell anyone!
Oh, I'm going nuts.
What's wrong with you?
Ugh, I should keep my mouth busy.
Isn't there anything to munch on?
Mom, are there any snacks?
Anggeum!
- What is it?
- Fry them some dumplings.
Mom...
It's okay, Anggeum.
Being well-fed is very important.
I shouldn't have to ask you to get snacks for my young son.
I don't believe how dense you are.
To be frank, he's not so young.
I know. Don't bother, Anggeum.
I'm serious, I'm okay.
Sedal, I want to talk to you before you go.
Just fry me two.
Don't fry too many.
Hey, I'm leaving.
- Hey, watch that.
- The mood is...
- I'm home.
- Oh, you're home!
- Daebak, did you eat?
- Yes.
What did you eat?
I grabbed something with my friends.
You should always get a proper meal.
Eating is saving, you know?
Hi, Daebak.
Hello, there.
Uncle, aren't you wasting time?
I have plenty of time, so I'm not wasting it.
It's because you don't have a dream.
Sedal, what's your dream?
Rich man.
No need to ask.
What else could be there?
At least Sedal has a dream, even though it's impossible, so why don't you have one?
Is it becoming a lonely old man?
That's possible.
Why that little...
A lonely old man?
How dare you?
You should grow up!
Don't tell your sister in law I fled.
Tell me what you've been dying to tell me.
You must keep it a secret.
Or your niece will murder me.
Okay.
For real?
Oh, no! This is really bad.
Why didn't they clean up after themselves?
Why do I always have to do it? Man!
Anggeum, I'll do it.
Where's Sedal?
I guess he left.
He didn't even say goodbye.
What are you doing?
- Get out.
- After I do this.
Get out right now!
Go, uncle.
Mother, you shouldn't be like that.
Men these days must help with the chores.
You raise your boy that way, for I won't stand it.
His own nephew doesn't respect him,
and now you want him to do the dishes?
Mom!
It's Subak. How nice!
Anggeum, your favorite daughter is here.
Mom, let's go.
How dare you treat him like this?
He's supposed to become a great man,
so treat him properly, understand?
Supposed to be?
Shouldn't he already be?
Did you have a fight with grandmother?
She didn't even say hi.
I don't want to talk about it.
Why are you here?
Your kids went to bed.
Where's father?
At his class reunion.
- Today?
- Yes.
My sister in law brought him.
I won't live with my father in law.
That old man must be crazy.
Why would he come just because his daughter brought him?
Living with a single father in law is hard!
I know.
Don't tell father.
He'll yell at me.
I was sitting at the playground until now.
Let me give you a tip.
Don't fall for me.
I hate it when women cry.
Nutty, nutty, nuts! Man!
You didn't tell uncle, did you?
It nearly drove me mad holding it in.
Oh, I'm so worried I can't sleep.
You can't be worried about Minjung.
I'm worried he might ask for a loan.
Don't you lend him money.
I don't have any to lend.
He never paid attention when I asked for a loan.
I bet he didn't see this coming!
Life can be mysterious,
interesting, delicious, funny,
lame, crazy, awkward.
You're really enjoying this, huh?
They're family.
How can you be so happy?
I am happy, so what?
To be frank, I'm a pretty handsome man.
But I'm always compared to him.
His eyes are bulging out, too!
So why does your mom always pick on me?
But Minjung's fair skinned and handsome.
He's not dark like you!
Turn the lights off.
This is nuts.
For me, it doesn't matter if they're on.
Leave me alone. I'm tired.
I should look for a husband for Gwangbak.
Someone with eyes bulging out.
That'd be so funny.
Three sons in law with eyes bulging out.
With googly eyes.
Looking here and there.
74, 75.
Hey! Who's there?
To me, my father's the most important.
If we fall into the river,
I'd save him first.
You take care of him!
It's your duty!
Why is Subak sleeping here?
She came to get the kids but decided to stay.
What is it?
Of all my classmates,
I'm the most successful.
They must all be losers.
Middle school vice principal is the most successful?
It's not about the money.
Having a job at my age is really lucky.
The others are all unemployed.
You don't have that many years left.
On top of that,
they're still living with their children.
They call them kangaroos or salmon.
What's that?
Kangaroos are the children who are adults but single and living with their parents.
We have one, too.
A kangaroo inside his sister in law's pouch.
How about the salmon?
Those who are married but have moved back into their parents house.
Salmon return home to spawn.
At least salmon spawn, but children return to take advantage of their old parents.
We're lucky we don't have any salmon.
Don't be so sure.
Look at how Sedal is doing.
I'm afraid of Hobak wanting to move in here.
Of course, I would never let her.
Hobak would never do that.
She's quite capable of making a living.
I hope I have a long life.
At least until Daebak gets on his own two feet.
Subak said she'll take care of Daebak.
But he's my child.
Subak's rich.
She can take care of him.
Besides, he's her little brother.
Then why are you mean to Don?
He's my brother.
Well, that's that and this is this.
You always turn on me like this.
Go to sleep!
Sangnam's not here.
And Mr. Yang's excavator's broken.
Okay. I'll be right over.
Sangnam's not home?
He said it's his friend's birthday.
He probably slept over at a friends after drinking.
Don't worry, Daese.
I'm not worried, but he's never done this before.
Even if he's wasted, he doesn't miss work.
Are you keeping something from me?
No, what would I hide from you?
Do you still keep in touch with her?
No, I haven't been for a while now.
I don't even know where she is now.
Even if you find her, don't tell Sangnam.
I don't care if you see her,
but not Sangnam.
But what if he runs into her somewhere...
I said no.
She's your sister, so you can see her, but not my son.
I don't want to hurt him.
He's only just recovered.
Don't you understand?
I do.
Of course I do.
I feel the same way.
If you mess things up for Sangnam,
I'll never forgive you.
Hello?
Father!
Minjung, I'm going home.
Don't worry about me.
I'm more comfortable at my own home.
I didn't come to burden you.
I just missed you.
That's why I came up with Minsuk.
So don't fight because of me.
Take care of your family.
I can still manage on my own.
If I get really bored, I'll get a dog.
Minjung,
I'll hold your mother's memorial services until the day I die.
I won't let my daughter in law do it.
Goodbye.
You don't look so good.
Whatever's going on, don't skip meals.
Take care, son.
Father...
Anyone home?
Careful. You'll get hurt.
Parcel service.
Yes, I'm on my way.
You're home right now?
Okay.
This is number 102.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, but where's number 103?
It's over there.
Pardon?
Yes.
Yes, I'm on my way.
You're home, right?
Hey, I called go 3 times, right?
I scored.
Oh you poor thing!
Hand over the money.
- No, no!
- Hey! Hey!
Why you little...
Hey! Stop right there!
Why are you running around like kids?
My Minjung, you're not hurt, are you?
- Oh...
- Are you hurt? Oh, no.
Uncle, are you okay?
Why don't you look where you're going?
What if your uncle broke his bone?
I'm sorry.
But that was uncle's fault, not Minjung's.
Oh, what brings you here?
You didn't have to bring anything.
- Come and sit down.
- Okay.
The kids...
Jungji's napping and Aeji's at kindergarten.
Would you like something to drink?
I'm okay.
I heard your father came?
He left.
He did?
Good! Subak couldn't take care of him.
Why not?
Subak's the eldest daughter in law.
She should, eventually.
But right now, the kids are young,
and Subak can't run the house.
You will have a say if you take care of your in laws.
I don't know about that, but she will someday.
But living together would be uncomfortable for both parties.
I'm not at a place where I can bring him in.
Oh, that's great news.
That's not great news.
Well, there's something I must tell you.
What is it?
I don't think you should.
Well...
What's wrong with you?
Just thinking about it is funny.
There was someone who looked just like him.
I went to the market and saw a parcel service man who looks just like Minjung.
That's not Minjung. No way.
Of course not.
You might feel offended, but he looked just like you, from the back and even the voice.
There are many people who look alike.
Looking alike doesn't mean anything.
What if Subak married a man like him?
Don't you agree, my Minjung?
Huh? Yes, well...
Why am I sweating?
Oh, you said you want to tell me something?
I know what that is.
Excuse me?
The parcel service, I know.
If Sedal knows, I know.
I should tell her but I can't.
I understand.
Cheer up.
I've never even had a job,
but you've always run your own business.
What's life?
If you don't own, you rent.
You're either unemployed or have a part time job.
Hey, Madam Park Salla!
How come there's nobody here?
I'm so frustrated.
The new beauty salon stole my customers.
This is not good.
Want me to take my guys there and teach them a lesson?
You can't even teach your wife a lesson.
It's not that I can't but that I won't.
I feel sorry for her ugly face.
She's not just ugly.
She's too stingy.
Worse than Scrooge.
Sedal, why don't you talk to her?
You know she can't be persuaded into anything.
That only worked once for me.
When she got pregnant with Sintong.
You didn't persuade her.
She seduced you!
Thinking about that makes me mad.
There were so many rich girls after you,
but you went and fell for that ugly girl!
I know.
I'm going nuts.
Sis!
I'm here.
This is so nice.
You'll need a few dresses.
Dresses?
They are a must when you go on a cruise.
There'll be parties at night.
I'll buy you a few.
Oh, my!
That'll turn my friends green with envy.
I'll be the only one to go on a cruise in this town.
I need to lose this belly to fit into a dress.
What's up?
She wanted to talk, so I told her to come.
Sit.
Can we go out?
Say it here.
What is it?
Let's go out, Subak.
Why? Talk here. Is it a secret?
It's about mom's birthday.
I'll pay for it, so you don't have to do it.
Why? Why would you do it?
Because I want to.
I've never heard such nonsense in all my life!
Is it because I yelled at you?
I can't throw a huge party like Subak.
We can do that for your 70th birthday.
Let's make this one simple.
What's wrong with you?
Just do what Hobak says.
Mom, let's do that.
We can't do a hotel buffet,
but we can go to a nice Chinese...
No!
Let's do that, Anggeum.
Don't be like this.
Why don't you just pitch in, then?
Listen to Hobak.
You stay out of this!
You don't even know what's going on.
But I do, unfortunately.
Why are you doing this?
Don't ask why.
Just do what Hobak says.
Hobak never spends her money unwisely.
I know.
So I need to know why.
I already made reservations at the hotel.
Cancel them.
Don't lose the down payment.
Listen to Hobak.
Don't blow the money.
You stay out of this!
Right! Why do you keep butting in?
I have good reasons.
When someone says something, listen!
Why do you have to nitpick?
You're not in the situation to do that!
Uncle!
My situation?
What do you mean by that?
Oh, man!
Was it Sedal?
Uncle, let's go.
- Tell me!
- Yes, tell us, uncle.
Uncle...
They'll find out anyway.
Let's tell them.
Your dear Minjung went bankrupt and lost his company.
So how can you afford a hotel or a cruise?
Oh, I can't believe I had to say this.
- Subak.
- Sis.
Be careful.
The doctor says you're healthy for your age.
Okay.
Be careful.
- Only two more trips to the doctor's.
- Okay.
Parcel service.
I left it with the guard like you asked.
Thank you.
- Yes?
- Why is your phone always busy?
Tell me what happened!
Your company went bankrupt?
Come home right now!
Subak, don't yell.
Let's talk tonight.
Why are you so busy?
You don't have a job, so why?
I am very busy.
I'm hanging up.
Let's talk later.
I said let's talk later.
What are you going to do?
I have to use them today!
I'm very sorry.
I'll pay for them.
That's not the problem!
Oh, this is crazy.
I can't believe my luck.
What are you doing?
Let's have another kid.
Sintong and Bangtong went on a camping trip with their taekwondo group,
so it's a great opportunity.
Sit down.
Opportunities like this don't come often.
So don't say no.
Oh, I think it just might work!
Are you getting excited too, honey?
Did mother tell you to convince me?
How did you know?
Oh man!
Ouch, it hurts.
I'm not how I used to be.
My bones are making sounds.
I think I need to get some meat in my diet.
Let's pay for my mom's birthday party.
Feed me meat instead with that money.
We should do this one as a daughter and a son in law.
If you have that kind of money, lend it to my mom.
She's offering to pay interest.
I don't have that much money.
Let's do it, okay?
Mom! Mom!
- What is it?
- Come over.
She won't budge.
Oh! Stop it!
That hurt!
Why do you always beat him up?
I'm just playing with him.
That might actually kill him.
Would you be happy if someone beat your son?
I knew you'd get in trouble.
Yell at her!
You should change your tone first.
The way you talk to him is so rude.
And you always beat him up.
You should know better.
Your father's a teacher!
I'm sure you're the only wife who gives $3 a day to her husband for allowance.
He might be younger,
but he's your husband.
Did you hear that?
I didn't beat him up.
I saw you many times!
I saw it too.
Don't you know how lucky you are?
You're living with a younger husband.
You should get a mean mother in law
and experience hell to know how lucky you are.
She'll never get it.
I know, I'm dense, so I don't get it.
Why did you call me over?
You need to listen to her.
I want to pay for my mom's birthday party.
Subak was going to but something happened.
I heard she went bankrupt.
Serves your mother right for belittling Sedal.
I thought you don't have any money.
How would you throw a party?
It won't be a party, per say.
We're just going to have lunch and send her on a trip to Jeju-do Island.
Nice!
You wouldn't listen when I asked you for a loan, but you'll go all out for your mom.
She's got 4 daughters,
so why are you doing it?
Please let me do this.
I'll do the same for your 60th birthday.
You can't do the same thing for her!
You have to do something even better for her!
Let's see how well you do when you get married!
- Where are you going?
- My mom's house.
Father found out, too.
Hey, I'm coming, too.
I can't miss a show like this one!
Oh, man...
Tell us what happened.
She says she doesn't know anything.
When something like this happens,
he should first tell his wife, but instead,
he let her find out from someone else!
Hobak and Sedal found out first.
Yes, I saw him first.
I have quick eyes.
So that's why they're bulging out.
Oh, what now?
How will you make a living?
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Don't worry mom.
Business owners always have a backup plan.
What do we do about your birthday, mom?
I made reservations and sent invitations already.
That's not what's important here.
Call him.
He won't answer my calls.
You don't have to throw a big party!
60th birthday isn't very special these days.
Grandmother, you stay out of it.
Minjung, it's me.
If you're not too busy will you come over?
Even if he's busy, he should still come!
- Minjung.
You look awful.
He lost weight, so his eyes are bulging out even more than...
Minjung.
Come and have a seat.
You should've told us sooner!
You sure can keep a secret.
Tell us what happened.
I'm sorry.
What happened?
What did you do?
How can you go bankrupt?
What about my mom's birthday party?
How am I supposed to face my friends?
You be quiet!
Why are you yelling at her and not him?
Subak's the one who's going crazy now!
It's Minjung!
He's right.
It's Minjung and then Subak.
Then it's mother, then father, and then...
Tell us.
I got loans and expanded my business,
but things turned bad and I couldn't make the payments.
I had to file for bankruptcy recently.
I had to sell the company and the factory, too.
As long as you don't have debt, you're fine.
I have a bit left to pay back,
and I'm talking to the creditors right now.
We have debt?
What am I going to do?
Oh, my poor daughter!
Sis, get up, get up.
Come with me.
Oh, no... Oh, no...
What do I do...
He'll overcome this so don't worry.
He's not the type to let this get the best of him.
This is crazy!
How did we go bankrupt?
What do I do now?
It's not easy to make a come back after going bankrupt!
And you're not young!
What about Subak?
I raised her like a princess.
Running a business has its ups and downs.
Bring us some drinks.
How can you drink at a time like this?
I can.
I'm too frustrated to make you anything.
Leave us.
Why should I leave?
Don't let this get you down.
Life is long. These things happen.
Losing money is losing little,
but people think they lost everything.
They let themselves be ruined.
But I believe in you.
Thank you, father.
How can you believe in him?
Why didn't you teach him?
What do I know about running a business?
You should because you're a vice principal.
How could you teach students?
You don't even deserve an answer.
What will you do now?
I'm going to try everything.
Minjung,
why didn't you prepare something beforehand?
You have a wife and two kids.
You leave...
When did you all come in?
Leave us.
Don't leave.
We all need to know.
We all need to hear this.
He's down as it is!
Don't be that way!
You should try to comfort him.
He doesn't deserve comforting.
Do you have any plans?
I'm trying something out right now.
What is it?
Parcel service...
Huh?
He's doing parcel service.
When they ring your bell,
you drop everything and answer the door.
That kind of thing.
Parcel service?
So you're the man I saw at the market!
My, I can't believe you!
You didn't say anything when I laughed!
What do we do now?
Anything but that!
It's embarrassing.
Embarrassing isn't the issue.
What do I tell my friends?
How will I face the neighbors?
How can you be delivering parcels?
Lots of people do it.
Subak, what's done is done.
Like your father said, things happen.
I'm still young and healthy.
I just need you by my side.
- Honey...
- Don't.
Let me hold you.
Subak, don't get mad.
Let's work together to...
Stop it! Seriously!
No, no!
I married a businessman,
not a parcel service guy.
I was in the Miss Korea pageant, so how...
How can this be?
Let's sell this house.
Let's sell the house and open a restaurant.
I'll run it.
I can run it, so you stay out of it.
I'm pretty, so I'll attract lots of customers.
I can do that really well.
- This house...
- Let's do that, okay?
Opening a restaurant isn't easy.
Making money isn't easy at all.
Then what do you want me to do?
Don't leave like that!
You always go out without saying a word!
Are you trying to drive me crazy?
Are you really my wife?
How can you be so cruel?
What did I do?
How could the first words out of your mouth be that you're embarrassed?
Can't you be worried for me?
Can't you ask to see if I'm okay first?
Or tell me that you'll be by my side no matter what?
I sold my parents land but I lost it all.
Can you just imagine how I must feel?
I have to hold onto something and start again, but I have nothing to hold on to.
I'm the one who wants to die.
I sat by the river and thought about it.
I thought about jumping in,
but because of you and the girls, I couldn't!
Did you know?
Mom!
Mom...
I'm worried about Subak.
I feel bad for Minjung, too.
What if they get divorced?
Oh, no...
Subak can't live without money.
Women are all the same.
- You, too?
- I'm a woman, too.
Women and money can't be separated.
I don't like women like that.
I like money, but I like you more, for now.
At a time like this, you must study harder.
If you study hard and get a good job...
Okay. Darn it.
Stop hanging out with your friends.
Stop it. You nag too much.
Daebak, I'm not getting a job.
I'm going to be a housewife.
Daebak, grow up fast so I can marry you.
Stop suffocating me.
I'll grow up eventually.
Why can't we grow up fast, huh?
Miho!
Mom!
Daebak, I'm going.
Go home and study, okay?
I'll check on you later.
If you go anywhere else, I'll kill you.
Go ahead and kill me!
People these days all want to become government workers or get high paying jobs.
Even though it's not easy to get them.
There are so many unemployed people,
but they still don't want 3D jobs.
Most people want white collar jobs,
so how did you choose this line of work?
I feel like I'm being interrogated.
I am interrogating you.
First, if you're healthy, there's no cutoff age,
and the job depends on my skills.
You can always find a job in this field.
For a man, this line of work is pretty good.
If everyone went to college and got desk jobs,
what would become of this country?
Us young people must change how we think.
And renew how society views blue collar workers.
You're saying this line of work must become desirable for the future of our country?
I thought you were a party girl, but you're smart.
Same here.
When do you feel most proud about your job?
When I save people at accident sites.
Oh, really?
When there's an accident,
the fire department calls us.
We rush over there...
Wow.
Digging through the debris and saving people,
is both thrilling and rewarding.
That's amazing.
Are you married?
No, not yet.
You just yelled "Yes!" in your head, right?
Pass.
Do you currently have a girlfriend?
Currently?
I haven't found one for fall of 2013.
You answered like a player.
But seriously, I've seen you somewhere.
That's such a lame pick up line.
Which elementary school did you go to?
- Sinsangdo.
- Middle school?
- Guksabong?
- That's odd.
How about high school?
Ask me which hotel I frequent.
Maybe you slept with me.
You're not my type.
Or we passed each other in the hallway.
Here's a realistic question.
How much is your income?
It depends on the job.
I make a decent living, of course.
I know some people who went to good schools,
had good jobs but are learning to drive excavators.
Oh...
What kind of heavy equipment can you drive?
Most people focus on one thing.
It's hard enough to get one license.
But thanks to my father, I learned it early.
So I can operate almost everything here.
As well as I would a woman.
Oh, boy.
Get in.
- Me?
- I'll drive you to the gate.
Okay.
Excuse me...
The stitches have healed.
If you hadn't bumped into anything,
it would've healed faster.
Ugh, I've lost sleep over that.
That's better.
I felt embarrassed seeing a urologist.
And I couldn't tell everyone I met that I got hurt at a construction site.
Be careful.
That's a bad place to get hurt.
I know. It could be lethal.
Maybe I should wear protective gear.
Should I put a bowl over it when I work?
- Just be careful.
- Oh, it's tight.
Oh, my!
Oh, I'm so sorry. Oh, no...
Oh, man...
Why are you so clumsy?
What do you have against me to do this again?
Me?
You don't remember me?
I'm not sure...
Are your eyes for decoration?
I was going to let it go,
but my doctor told me to be careful,
so I was real careful, like this.
I was really, really careful!
This is the third time you did this to me.
I didn't know.
But why are you yelling at me?
How can I help it?
You didn't even apologize properly.
How can you be so rude?
I'm sorry.
- Pay up.
- Excuse me?
I had to see my doctor for one more week,
so you must pay for that.
Says who?
There's no evidence!
That's ridiculous!
Why is it ridiculous?
Then let's go see my doctor
and find out for yourself.
Find out what? Unbelievable.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
I'm sorry. I don't know what you take me for, but I'm not that naive.
There are people who cause accidents on purpose and swindle people for money...
What? Swindle for money?
If you don't want me to think that, stop this.
Try this again, and I'm calling the police.
Sunjeong, get me a cold drink with ice.
Okay.
Wow.
How can I get her?
She's unbelievable.
You ran into that rude person again?
Yes, she must hang out there.
She kept saying she didn't do anything.
She's not careful and has no manners.
I hope you don't marry a girl like her.
It's a woman?
You can't even call her a woman.
Don't you ever bring a girl who talks back to introduce to me.
I'd never meet a girl like that.
Daese, here.
Mark my words.
I'm going to make her pay.
I feel sorry for her.
I know.
Ugh.
Can me. I have a question.
I'll pay you 50 cents.
I'll only answer 50 cent worth.
You said you live with your aunt?
Why do you?
Isn't that uncomfortable?
There's a reason.
I can't comment on that.
When did your mother pass away?
She's not dead.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You said your father's in the same business?
It must be nice to work with your father.
Not really.
He knows everything, so I can't fool him.
But you asking me all these questions makes me feel like I'm being interrogated.
Can I interrogate you now?
No, you can't.
That's not fair!
Your grandmother is amazing.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Our names end with "Bak,"
Subak, Hobak, Gwangbak, Haebak.
And the youngest is Daebak.
Yes.
You know how the third daughter is always the prettiest?
I'm the third daughter.
You can tell, huh?
That means the others are really, really ugly.
No! Subak is extremely pretty.
Hobak's also pretty and so is Haebak.
But of course, I'm the prettiest.
We should hang up!
Oh, my ear feels hot.
This isn't an interrogation.
It's torture.
My arm hurts, too.
We talked for 1 hour and 23 minutes and 40 seconds.
Who called?
Oh, I'm paying for this.
I'll take you to dinner when I get paid.
You have to get up early, don't you?
You're very understanding.
Laborers must sleep well and eat well.
On regular schedule.
Oh, another strength of blue collar jobs.
They're healthy in mind and body.
I won't leave that out.
I had a good laugh thanks to you.
But I shouldn't because something's up.
I heard from Daebak about your eldest sister.
You should try to lighten things up.
Have good dreams.
Good night.
Father, take the rest of the week off.
I can take care of everything.
Mr. Park's excavator's fixed, so he's back.
But we have to fix a few pumps and transmissions, so it'll cost us.
But it only happens every few years.
Yes, I'll come home for lunch later.
Let's start the day with happy thoughts!
Safety first!
We need to weld the excavator booms.
A few of them have cracks in them.
When you weld the buckets, check them.
Okay.
You don't have to worry.
He's good.
You're lucky to have a son like him.
He's still a kid.
Father!
When you first came to my shop,
you were a little boy with a runny nose.
Like this!
Are you dating someone?
Where did you get such weird info?
You have a girlfriend?
No, auntie.
I would've told you if I did.
I saw you talking on the phone really late.
And you were laughing, too.
We were talking about work.
I haven't seen you like that in a long time.
Was it a woman?
I'm not interested in her.
So it was a woman.
I don't care for her.
I wish you'd get yourself a girlfriend!
If she doesn't feel right, stop it.
Don't hurt a woman for no reason.
You know you have player's blood in you.
Because you took after me.
I'm actually a bigger player than you.
I'm always working on it.
I can't take this anymore.
How can you take this every day?
I'm forced to take this.
- Would you like some more soup?
- Yes.
- More.
- It's delicious. You're the best.
Mom.
Why are you here?
I thought Subak would be here.
You're taking care of the girls?
How can Subak take care of them?
Why? Do you even feel bad for her?
About what?
Why didn't you let Minjung tell her?
Why did you have to tell everyone?
I don't understand you sometimes.
There's nothing to understand.
I was just talking about your birthday...
Enough. Stop talking about it.
You don't have to do it, so don't worry.
She can't even eat and I understand why.
Her world is falling apart.
I made some pine nut porridge.
If you knew this,
why didn't you tell me?
You should've warned me.
Minjung said he was going to tell you.
Were you and Minjung in on it together?
How can you say that?
Mom's mad because I told her,
you're mad because I didn't tell you.
Everyone hates me.
I'm sorry, Subak.
You should eat.
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
- Subak.
- Be honest with me.
You're happy to see me like this, right?
- Are you crazy?
- Yes, I'm crazy.
Bring me someone who wouldn't go crazy in this situation!
I know. I know this is hard for you.
So calm down.
Don't think too much.
You have to think about the girls...
Get out.
I don't need this from you!
Who do you think you are?
Get out!
Take this and get out!
Don't do this to me.
What did I ever do to you?
Did I pray for Minjung to go bankrupt?
I'll let this slide because I know how you feel,
but still, it's too much to endure.
What did you have to endure?
I've always been discriminated against!
Ever since I was little, I endured it all!
Mom only loved you!
She was always Subak this, Subak that!
I can't stand it!
I'm so sick of it!
You don't know how hard it was for me, do you?
How could you?
You were so loved!
But do you know how I must have felt growing up, being hated?
What about me?
You think you never hurt me?
You've hurt me too, you know.
Hurt you?
Me?
You did.
How did I ever hurt you?
Tell me. What was it?
Subtitles by KBS World
That. I would never forget that. Never.
- But you!
- I said stop!
You better take that one to the grave.
Do you know how proud and respectful he is about his job?
You don't want to work, do you?
No! Not with you!
This is how we're celebrating my birthday?
Why did you come?
Go deliver your parcels!
Don't you feel bad for father?
Imagine how lonely he must be in his house.
How could you not tell me anything?
How could you betray me like this?