Subtitles by KBS World
I want to be free.
What?
What did you say you want?
Why do I have to repeat myself?
I am free spirited.
I've been locked up in a cage called Hobak,
and I'm dying to get my freedom back.
What do you mean by that?
You don't understand Korean?
Like I said, freedom.
Give me freedom or give me death.
Are you cheating on me?
That's where all women jump to.
When did you meet her? Who is she?
Come clean when you can.
Don't ask me too many questions.
I don't have anything to come clean about.
It's simple. Give me freedom.
You...
Do you want me to beat you up?
Marriage isn't a joke!
How can you say that after having 2 kids?
We didn't get married out of love.
We did because you got pregnant.
Instead of "I woke up one morning and found myself famous,"
I woke up one morning and found myself married.
Let's go back to who we used to be.
Back to being free, before we met.
Crazy bastard.
Don't swear. A man and a woman can...
We're not a man and a woman.
We're husband and wife, crazy bastard.
See how we can't communicate?
Don't try to resolve this by calling us that.
We're actually a man and a woman.
I'm a man, you're a woman. Didn't you know?
She doesn't even know she's a woman.
Enough.
You already decided everything for me and
fed me the food I have never had before,
and now you want to be free?
How dare you!
I'm going to kill you.
A man like you deserves a good beating.
Hey.
You're embarrassing me! Use words!
How can I use words? How?
Come here. Come here!
Don't use violence! This is why I hate you.
Don't just stand there. Stop her!
What? What?
You can't do this here.
Don't grab me. Grab her, her!
Her, her! Her, her!
This is nutty, nutty, nuts!
Bastard!
Daese.
Are you busy?
No, do you want something?
You're not going out, are you?
I'm just going to the market.
Why?
It's because I'm getting a package today.
Who is it?
Please sign here.
Okay.
What about Mr. Ko Minjung?
Oh, something came up.
Okay.
Hello. May I help you find something?
Well, I... Uh...
Is it a present?
Uh...
It's for my wife.
She's lucky. May Ii suggest something?
How about these?
Oh.
Well, I'm looking for a dollar undies.
Excuse me?
Uh, I mean...
Do older women like these?
When you turn around...
Pants, pants...
I'm home, mother.
Hi.
Did you have dinner?
I lost my appetite.
Why didn't you make something special?
What's that behind you?
Oh, I brought some documents from school.
I need to get some work done.
When you come home, I look at your hands.
To see if you brought any food.
I'll bring you something delicious tomorrow.
Okay. Go to your room and rest.
Okay.
When you turn around, pants, pants...
What is it?
Are you going to yell at me about not making mother good food to eat?
If you deserve it, I should.
Here.
What is it?
Open it.
What's this?
Oh, my.
Are these for me?
Do you like them?
I've never seen anything like these before.
Why didn't you just get dollar undies?
These must be expensive.
I was going to get you a box full of dollar undies, but they looked prettier.
You actually went to a women's underwear shop and bought these?
Oh, I was sweating so hard.
I still can't believe I did that. Oh, boy.
Oh, darling old man!
Why...
No one's looking!
But this is poison, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Living with Minjung must be hard.
I can escape to school,
but you have to take care of things.
Don't even get me started.
You're having a hard time,
but Minjung is also having a hard time.
Please be nicer to him.
I'm feeding him and raising his kids.
How much nicer do I have to be?
Do it for Subak.
Just think about it.
When mother's mean to you, how do I look?
- I'd love to beat you up.
- See?
Oh, I must be crazy for accepting this,
knowing this is poison.
Where am I going to go wearing these?
You're going to wear them outside?
But these are too nice to wear at home!
Where are you planning on
flashing your underwear?
You'll ruin people's eyes!
I heard the front door.
I did, too.
You heard the door?
Hello! Welcome home.
- Welcome home.
- How was your day?
- What's...
- Must've had a tough day, huh?
How are you?
Oh, Minjung, did you have a hard day?
Providing for your family is hard, isn't it?
It's not easy delivering packages.
It's hard enough having to live here,
but nobody waits for you when you come home
and you get into trouble with me
trying to make noodles,  making cat noise.
And I make you sleep outside.
I made you cry just the other night.
I know how hard it must have been.
How was that?
Did you go inside Minjung's head?
We all waited up for you.
You did that for me?
Yes, Minjung.
We usually go to sleep early,
but we stayed up for you.
Thank you so much.
You didn't have to do this.
I'm very sorry about the other night.
Are you really?
We were in shock that night.
Don't be. We're sorry.
No.
Can I go to bed now?
Why don't we order some snacks?
Why? You hate ordering food.
Dad, pizza!
- Okay.
- We can ask uncle to
- bring some home.
- Yes, let's do that.
- Call him.
- Okay.
Oh, boy.
It's so nice to sit together like this and to eat pizza late at night.
Yes, I can't stop smiling!
I wish we could eat like this every night.
Why can't you focus on studying?
Don't yell at my precious grandson.
Father, let's do this once a week.
We can also have a family meeting.
Yes, let's do that.
Tonight's topic should be that.
Tell your father to leave your mom alone.
We're the only family whose father is still in power.
What good will destroying his ego do?
You don't know how good you have it.
When your husband is strong, people don't look down on you or your children. Got it?
Don't get it.
Why you little...
You should know how lucky you are.
I lost my husband really early,
and I lived as a widow all those years...
Mother.
Mom.
As you get older, you get more wrinkles and tears.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Grandmother, in other families,
when the wives make noise when doing
the dishes, the husbands get nervous
and try to think about what they did wrong.
I know.
I know this guy from school, and he's now a gangster, but he's afraid of his wife.
While we're afraid of him.
Who cares about how other families are?
I know some husbands even buy underwear for their wives.
I'd like to see what they look like.
Minjung, let's drink.
Thank you for making this happen.
Okay.
What's there to life?
This is happiness, being with family like this.
Of course, of course.
Didn't your father say anything?
He didn't even come in.
What was that?
Minjung's father was here? When?
A few days ago.
He brought chestnuts,
but he turned around and went home.
I forgot to mention it.
How could you?
Come with me!
I can't believe this.
Grandmother, why did you bring that up?
You know how father gets.
Why are you blaming my mom?
You should've told me.
I could've at least called him.
He must be really upset.
Can't you imagine how he must have felt when he left them by the door?
Why are you changing into this weird person?
I don't know.
I don't know why I'm changing like this.
I guess people get rotten when they get old.
What?
Having to take care of a mean mother in law,
a tough husband, and five children turned me into this. So?
What?
There you go with that, "what?" What?
And I don't understand him either.
How can he just drop by without calling?
He didn't want you to go to any trouble preparing for his visit!
Don't you know how important he is?
I can't believe my ears.
Are your children important or not?
Of course they're important.
What a stupid question.
How do you manage to teach?
Aren't they the most important?
They're as important as my own life. So?
You and him have shared with each other children who you value as much as life itself!
That's what in laws are. Understand?
That's how special the relationship is,
so how could you cause conflicts?
You say "that beauty salon woman,"
and you belittle her all the time.
How would Sedal's mother feel about that?
She'll call me annoying vice principal's wife.
At least you know.
Put yourself in their shoes.
You'd know the answer right away.
I don't want these underwear.
Fine. I'll give them to mother.
They won't fit!
They are free size.
They'll fit anyone in any size.
Ugh!
He hasn't called you?
No.
And he won't answer my calls.
Should we call the police?
Don't worry.
He'll come home when he's ready.
How is she doing?
She's running a small beer house.
It looked like she's deep in debt.
I guess people don't change.
She should be doing better.
Why did you go there?
What did you expect from her?
I'm sorry, Daese.
What did she say to Sangnam?
Why is he acting like that?
Be honest with me,
although I can guess.
She broke Sangnam's heart.
How could she be so cold after 20 years?
How could she say those mean things?
She's not human.
I would've found her if she were.
She was into gambling and was cheating on me.
She stole every penny I had and left.
When I was at work,
she invited him to my house and...
She exposed our little boy to that.
It's all my fault.
Don't worry too much, Daese.
Sangnam just needs to clear his head.
If
anything happened to Sangnam,
I couldn't go on living.
That will never happen, Daese.
I'm worried to death about him being somewhere, thinking some stupid thoughts.
You can't grab me there!
Huh?
Hey, Goof-off.
You better come home, or else!
Stop talking nonsense, and come home.
If you don't, you're dead. Understand?
She still has no clue. Oh, boy.
How to get rid of your wife of 10 years.
How can she kick her husband out?
I should go and teach her a lesson.
Leave her alone.
Why isn't Yeongdal home?
Mom.
Hey, you should come home early!
Why are you yelling at my house?
And stop using my things.
You're sleeping here?
You had another fight?
I don't even want to talk about it.
Why are you coming home so late?
I had a blind date.
I thought you were getting married.
You can't just see one man. That's dumb.
It's always better to have options.
- Oh, boy.
- I'm not the only one doing it.
Me do it, too.
Mom, did you ask Sedal?
Ask me what?
Sedal, can you lend me some money?
Money? For what?
I could expand my beauty salon
or try something completely different,
but I need some dough.
Since the director likes you,
maybe you can ask for a loan.
Can he be cheating on you?
He says he's not.
And I believe him.
He doesn't have the guts to cheat on me.
But you never know.
He's kind of charming.
Charming my butt.
If he were a boy, I could beat him up.
Why is he suddenly crying for freedom?
Sedal is kind of immature, don't you think?
Why don't you just talk to him?
I'm too furious to talk to him.
He won't even come home after what he did.
I think you should try dressing up a bit.
You can't ask for freedom because of that!
I'm sure it's not that...
Hobak, don't get me wrong.
He must see beautiful women at the hotel.
And you've been together for a decade.
As a man, he could be getting ideas.
So dress up a little, don't scream at him,
and be more feminine and nicer to him.
Even I think you're too much sometimes.
Don't wear stretched out shirts or Sedal's old boxers.
Talk to him and just humor him.
Don't scream, be more feminine and nicer.
After the beep you will go to voice mail.
Sedal,
I'm sorry I got mad at you.
And I'm sorry about beating you.
I guess we've hit a difficult time, so let's try to work things out.
I won't scream and I won't wear your old boxers or stretched out t-shirts.
I was wrong.
And...
I'll make glass noodles so come and take it.
Is something going on with Sedal?
Why?
He asked Hobak to let him go.
Set him free.
Goof-off, how dare you...
Do you know something?
Tell me. You know something, don't you?
You're home already?
Hobak, it's me.
What are you saying?
He's cheating on me?
Calm down, Hobak.
He can't because he has no money.
Money doesn't affect cheating, it seems.
Oh, I had no idea.
Sintong's way smarter than me!
Who is it?
How long has it been?
Hobak, calm down.
How can I calm down?
Tell me everything.
Hurry up and tell me.
You actually know her.
I know her?
Who?
One of my friends?
The director.
What?
It's the director.
That can't be.
Hobak...
How can that be?
So that means that... That he's...
I had no idea.
Uncle, did you know?
I found out recently, too.
I heard it's a noticeable trait from childhood!
He wasn't like that when he was younger, right?
Can it happen this late?
How sad! And he couldn't tell anyone.
He didn't tell you.
He must have been tormented.
Oh, I thought this only happened in movies.
Oh, what do I do?
Hobak, what are you talking about?
You said he likes men.
What? Why would Sedal like men?
You said he's seeing the director.
That director's a woman.
The director is...
A woman?
You didn't know?
Oh, man!
Oh, hello, Mr. Ko.
I heard you came but I didn't ring the bell.
I'm so sorry.
You could've called me.
I didn't want to trouble you.
I just brought some chestnuts.
You must miss your granddaughters.
I sent Minjung and the girls to your house.
Oh, you didn't have to do that.
Thank you for being so kind.
Yes, Jungji.
You wouldn't answer my calls.
I'm sorry. It was all my fault.
I'll answer my phone before the third ring.
Things are complicated, but I'm sorting them out.
Director, she's made glass noodles.
Glass noodles?
Yes, Koreans' favorite, glass noodles.
I'll go home and get it right away.
Hey, glass noodles, glass noodles.
I'm in a hurry. Get it.
Why didn't you tell me?
What? I asked you to make me some.
That director's a woman?
It's not like you ever asked.
I never lied to you.
I told you where I went with the director,
and I told you about the amusement park.
You never asked me any questions.
I never lied to you.
Crazy bastard.
Did you like sharing the rice rolls I made with her?
Was it nice to hang around with her?
I wasn't going to say this but...
You gave me $3 a day,
but she gave me a $100,000 credit card.
It was like she opened up my world.
I couldn't believe my luck,
so I live everyday in gratitude.
It was just for the money?
Just?
Do you know what money can do?
Do you know the power of money?
Of course you don't.
Do you know what men want these days?
They want some rich women to appear and rescue them from their miserable reality.
I never felt this way before.
Your mother called me "my Sedal,"
and my friends started calling me every day.
When I go out, people respect me.
When I go to a restaurant or a bar, they treat me like a king. Did you know?
You're totally crazy.
Yes, let's say that I am.
I'm not supposed to be poor.
I'm supposed to become the president.
And you were a frog in your previous life.
You're worse than a tadpole.
I didn't know you were this hopeless.
Get a hold of yourself, crazy bastard!
Get out of my house!
I don't need you.
I'm embarrassed to call you my sons' dad.
How can you go completely crazy?
You gold digger!
Hey, Minjung!
Welcome!
Grandpa!
Oh, my darling Aeji.
Thank you for coming, Subak.
- She was fidgeting.
- Oh, no.
You can take her to the bedroom.
I'm trying to catch a chicken for you.
Careful. Don't get hurt doing it.
I used to be good, but not anymore.
They think I'm a joke because I'm old.
What do you mean?
You're not old.
Aeji, let's go and catch a chicken.
Let's go.
Aeji, come here. Grab that one.
Where are you coming from?
The market. You?
A party.
Is your back broken? What's that?
You don't know how comfortable this is.
Your sons haven't gotten you a stroller yet?
My son bought me this.
I have one more from my daughter at home.
Ugh.
Why I should...
I should just die! Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
I'm the one who doesn't have a stroller.
Isn't anyone home?
Come out!
Why you little!
Oh.
Hey, come out.
Why? I'm eating rice cake.
Eat that later.
Get the stroller for me.
You're going to ride it?
No, I'm going to push it.
- Go straight.
- Straight.
And turn right. Turn this way. Yes.
What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
I'm exhausted.
Don't talk to me.
Mom's going to drive this.
What?
I'm the only one without a stroller.
Even the dogs have them.
I can lean on it, so it's very comfortable.
I saw others push this around,
and I didn't know why they were doing it.
You can't.
Do you know how much this was?
Why not?
It's for Jungji.
But I never saw Subak use is.
I can push this around and break it in.
Subak will be furious.
Uncle, take this back home.
And wash the dirt off the wheels.
Okay.
Leave it!
Hurry up.
Uncle.
I said leave it!
Uncle!
Oh, I give up!
Do you need any help, father?
Don't even think about it. I'm an expert.
Aren't you hungry?
It's almost done.
Wow, that looks delicious.
Here you go.
Aeji, eat up.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
Make sure you chew it thoroughly.
Go get Subak.
Jungji must be asleep.
Okay.
Did something happen?
My back hurts.
Your back hurts?
I'll take you to see a doctor tomorrow.
I don't need to see a doctor.
What's wrong with Anggeum?
What is she on?
I don't think she's on anything.
I just came home.
Why do I bother living?
Everyone, even the dogs, push them around,
and I'm the only one without it.
Without what?
A stroller.
About the stroller...
Leave it alone.
I'm going to push it around.
I know how it's done.
But you're healthy.
My back hurts, too.
You push it around later,
and let's give it to mother for now.
Do you know how much it was?
What if she takes it out one day and someone steals it?
Mother doesn't have much time left.
Just humor her.
I've been hearing that for 40 years.
You're pretty good for a first timer.
Oh, this is so comfortable.
You're the best.
Hey, go straight, go straight.
Watch out.
We need to go.
What's taking him so long?
Father, we're leaving!
Hold on.
Hold on a second.
It's the girls.
We should've left earlier.
I should've packed these for you earlier.
- Oh.
- What is all this?
These are what I harvested.
Some sesame oil, perilla oil, beans and sesame seeds. Take them.
I know you can buy these in Seoul,
but I grew them without using pesticides.
Thank you, father.
My mother in law will love them.
Minjung, I forgot the diaper bag.
I'll get it.
Oh...
Subak.
Oh, my darling Jungji.
Subak, hold on.
Let's clean the table and do the dishes.
Right now?
But it's late.
It won't take long.
Just leave them and go.
I've been doing chores for over 10 years.
I'm an expert now.
We can do it really quickly.
We don't have time.
Even if we leave now, we'll get home late.
- The girls must go to bed.
- Yes, just go.
We'll go then, father.
Grandpa, goodbye.
Yes, Aeji, come see grandpa again.
Minjung, drive safely.
Subak, goodbye.
I'll call you. Go in.
Okay. Go.
What's wrong?
Why are you so quiet?
Is it because we didn't do the dishes?
Yes. Why couldn't we just do it?
If you really want to, go back and do it.
You're all pouting.
I just feel badly about it.
Father said he'll do it.
He even caught a chicken for us,
cooked it and made porridge.
He did all of that alone,
so why couldn't we at least do the dishes?
Then why didn't you hurry up?
Why did you waste all that time talking?
You weren't this chatty when you were busy working.
But we haven't visited him in a long time.
And why couldn't you say thank you when he packed us all that food?
You could've at least pretended.
I can't pretend.
What?
I'm not thankful at all.
We could just buy them in Seoul.
I'm not sure why he does it,
but the stuff he gives us aren't very fresh.
They're half eaten by bugs,
or they are all wilted.
I can go to the market and get fresh ones,
so why does he even bother?
I don't like them.
Now my mom has to throw them out.
What's wrong?
You startled me.
What is it now?
What's the problem?
What's wrong with what I said?
I'm tired so don't annoy me.
You know how stressful it was for me?
You don't know because it's your father's,
but I wasn't because of Jungji.
I wanted to leave, but you only got up after dark,
and now you're pouting because we didn't do the dishes and I didn't say thank you!
Do you know how hard farming is?
Farming is the hardest job in the world.
You have to start working in the spring,
take care of the crops all summer long,
and you never get a moment's rest.
Try standing in a field for an hour in the middle of summer.
You couldn't do it if you tried.
Even with the farming equipment, you must take care of most of the things with your hands.
And even after the harvest,
you must shake the trains off by hand,
dry them, peel them and rub them.
They don't grow by themselves.
My father,
he's been a farmer all his life.
He's old, and it's hard for him,
but he still tries and sends whatever he harvests to his children.
He grew them organically.
And that's all you can say about them?
You might think farmers are below you,
but I have nothing but respect for him.
My father who's a farmer.
So?
I can't speak my mind?
Don't eat them.
Don't eat the food my father gave me.
I won't.
Why did you have  to tell me that here?
We're standing in the middle of the road!
You overreact whenever I talk about him.
How lucky you are to have a father like him!
Let's go.
You're not going to get them?
Leave them for my coworkers.
Whatever! How stubborn.
What?
Why is that out here?
Why is the stroller outside, covered in dirt?
Don't ask. I don't want to talk about it.
Why?
Grandmother, do you know how much that is?
It's not something you can just push around.
Didn't you know?
Don't ever take it out again, okay?
What the heck was she saying?
I still have water in my ears.
Oh.
Sangnam.
Good morning.
You should take time off.
Should I take over Mr. Kang's excavator?
Take a break.
I already did.
I'm dying to go back to work.
This was supposed to be finished yesterday.
Oh, things just don't get done without me.
Right. Without you, nothing gets done.
So be nice while you have me.
People are dying to hire me.
Let's grab a drink after work.
I'll buy this time.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
- Have a good day.
- Number 1 at school!
- And Haebak.
- You have a date, okay?
Gwangbak is meeting someone?
Yes.
I don't know what happened,
but she asked me to set her up.
I thought you becoming a writer came first.
Who knows when she'll become one?
Getting married is a hundred times better.
Can I think about it for a few days?
What?
You're totally out of your mind!
Meet him and marry him.
He's from a good family.
She hasn't even met him yet.
He has a good job, his parents are set, and they have some money.
They can even buy them a house.
But money isn't everything in a marriage.
It's the most important thing.
Without money, there's no love.
There are more important things than money.
Become a writer after you're married.
I can't handle two kangaroos at once.
I'm already tired as I am.
I can't have my say because of you!
I can't pick on Don because of you!
I'll meet him.
But let me decide my marriage.
I'm working.
I have to get back soon.
Come home.
How can I when you're beating me up?
Would you if you were me?
I can't take it anymore.
Are you living with her?
How dare you!
I'd never do anything like that.
It's like you don't know me at all!
That's why I can't stand you.
Sedal,
I'm sorry.
You should be.
You have no manners at all.
You beat me up in front of strangers.
I'll change.
I won't do anything you don't like.
And I know I was too much to handle.
And I understand why you chose money.
You do?
Women lose their heads over luxury brand bags,
so of course you lost yours over that credit card.
I'd lose my head, too,
although no man would give me such a thing.
Of course not.
I got in your way, I know.
If I wasn't pregnant with Sintong,
we would've never gotten married.
Of course not.
You're a good man.
You made buying that apartment possible.
You survived on $3 a day,
wore clothes I got from the salvage bin,
and stood by me all those years. Thank you.
Stop that. You're making me cry.
And that's how we got here.
Now that we bought an apartment,
I'll be less frugal.
I won't wear your old boxers and try to be more feminine.
Stop that, please.
That won't help.
I don't want to listen to that sob story.
Sedal.
It's too late. I can't live with you.
I feel nothing for you.
What?
I wasn't going to say this,
but you stopped being a woman to me.
You're just scary.
You're more like a sister, a mother or a witch.
You make me feel little.
How could this work?
Hobak, please set me free. Please.
Ugh...
If you belittle her
and break her heart,
I won't stand it.
She is,
she is my woman and my wife!
I won't see him, even if he came.
I don't mind getting a divorce.
For the first time in my life, I'm happy.
Dad, please leave me alone.
Being your puppet for 30 years was enough!
Hello?
Hello.
Are you director Eun Miran?
Who is this?
I'm Heo Sedal's wife.
So?
I'd like to see you, if you don't mind.
Me? Why?
I'll tell you in person.
I'm at the lobby.
Then come up.
Hello.
I just called...
Sit down.
What's up?
I wasn't sure if I should come.
I thought about how to handle this before coming to see you.
Thank you for being good to my husband,
and paying him a good salary.
Get to the point.
I'm a busy woman.
Okay.
I don't think you started it.
Why would a woman like you want my husband?
He's acting like that because he's immature.
But that's not true.
Oppa may be immature,
but that's very charming.
Oppa?
Of course.
We've had good times.
I heard women call their boyfriends "oppa" in Korea.
Wait, he said his wife is much older.
You're older than him, right?
He said I'm much older?
I think he said by five or six years.
I'm one year older.
By birthdays, it's even less than that.
And by law, he's married with two sons.
What you're doing is against the law.
I'm not sure how it is in the States,
but in Korea, this is a crime.
Oppa and I didn't do anything.
We didn't break any law.
And that's why I came to ask for a favor.
Before you break the law,
stop this, please.
You have everything a woman would want,
so why get involved with a married man?
People will criticize you.
I'm sure you can find handsome men.
But he's fun. Didn't you know?
He's fun?
He almost drove me crazy.
You'd get sick of him in less than a month.
You have no idea how charming he is.
I feel bad for him.
I never felt this way before,
but now I feel like giving it a try.
It was nice meeting you.
I have an appointment.
How much do you want? For oppa?
He's not for sale.
Mom, I'll see you later.
Good luck.
Try not to speak your mind and be demure.
Oh, you're going on that date?
Aunt, you have a date?
Now that even your niece knows,
you have to get married within this year.
Do you understand?
Ask about his salary, buying an apartment,
and where his parents will live.
And check what kind of car he drives.
I have to check his car, too?
But I'm meeting him for the first time!
What else could you talk about?
Your purpose is getting married.
And they are the most important things.
Were you planning on asking about his hobbies or his army stories?
I'm different from you.
What?
Whatever.
Oh, my. Did you hear that?
Even she won't take me seriously.
Gwangbak, where are you going?
Dinner plans.
Get in. I'll give you a ride.
It's okay. It's just around the corner.
Oh, Gwangbak!
I thought we could get coffee or something.
I'll see you at Yeongdal's wedding.
You fell for it,too?
That was a lie.
That was a lie?
Yes. That's what she does.
She always puts on a show like that.
She posted a picture saying he proposed,
and that they had fish stew together!
He never proposed to her.
She hasn't seen him in days.
I met up with Yeongdal yesterday.
It was some fantasy she created.
Don't you remember?
She's done it before.
I'll see you again.
- Gwangbak.
- Later!
Gwangbak!
Hey, munchkin.
What are you doing?
I can't find the answers.
About what?
She got dumped.
Huh?
She was sobbing and I felt so bad for her.
He's marrying some other woman.
He's a real jerk, isn't he?
So she's meeting someone today.
And she's going to get married.
I'm sorry about disappearing without calling.
I'm not the kind of man who'd do that.
Even if we broke up, I'd talk to you.
I won't disappear or send you a text.
I wouldn't do that to you.
I thought you wouldn't do that to me,
but you did, and it was a huge shock.
That night,
I went to see someone.
Who?
The woman who was my mom once.
Remember I told you that growing up,
I never knew mom's love?
She never cared for me and when I turned 9,
when my father was struggling during
the national financial crisis, she left us.
I thought I should meet her at least once.
I believed she had a reason for leaving.
But when I met her,
she had no reason to offer.
She was just a selfish and mean woman.
She didn't care about her son.
You know those bad moms on the news?
She was one of them.
You can stop now.
And you can stop being hurt.
I'm here.
I'll protect you.
You can rely on me and believe in me.
I'm not sure if I can believe in you.
I'm serious.
Where are you going all dressed up?
Are you meeting a man?
No, I'm not meeting a man.
I'm not that desperate.
This is bad.
Just because you couldn't reach me,
you came up with stories in your head
and are now meeting a man.
How can I believe in you?
I am meeting a man, but I'm not desperate.
I was just upset.
And you were going to have an affair?
How can you...
It's not like you're my husband!
Let's get dinner and talk about whether or not we could call it an affair.
I'm hungry.
Me, too. I haven't eaten much in days.
Then why would you meet another man?
One more thing.
Don't ever hug any other man like that.
- I'll get angry.
- When did I do that?
You did just now.
You're such a player.
You didn't ask for permission to hug me.
You didn't even call me.
You even said that I was your destiny.
When did I do that?
That's what it says in your phone.
You showed me when we were fishing.
Call me.
Read it.
You,
are,
my,
sucker?
You are my sucker?
Yes.
Stop! Stop right there!
Subtitles by KBS World
You met her?
You should've beaten her up!
I can't even begin to compete with her.
The human heart has a mind of its own.
I feel like giving it a try.
Let's be friends.
Friends?
Drop by anytime.
I'm always home.
I'll be waiting.
Yeongdal's getting married.
That's a lie.
How can Yeongdal beat you?
Pack me lunch tomorrow.
I'm going hiking.
All together?
Not you. Just me and the director.
It tastes...