Subtitles by KBS World
You know why I asked you here, don't you?
I'll keep it simple.
Keep your hands off my kids' dad.
Was that too hard to understand?
Keep your hands off.
I know why you called,
but seeing you is making me nervous.
That's because you did something wrong.
I never did anything wrong.
Really?
After wrecking my family?
I never wrecked your family.
How dare you?
You pretended to be a caregiver and took care of my father in law.
You're despicable.
I knew something was off when I saw you two.
Did you enjoy making me look like a fool?
I'm sure you did.
It wasn't like that.
Whether or not it was,
stop seeing him from now on.
I know you have no right to say that.
No right?
I'm the mother of his kids and his wife.
You used to be.
Talking to you nicely isn't working.
You seduced my husband and wrecked my family,
so how could you be so brazen?
You made us get a divorce!
I had nothing to do with that.
How much schooling did you get?
What? You don't understand Korean?
We broke up because of you.
I don't want to sit here with you anymore.
So end it.
I won't do that.
What?
Your divorce had nothing to do with me.
You even looked after my father in law!
Who wouldn't fall for his old girlfriend when she does something like that?
You're very tricky.
You hide behind that demure looking face.
Women like you give me the chills.
Miho's your daughter, right?
Does she know, too?
That her mom is doing this?
I guess you're finished.
I'm leaving.
But poor you.
He's not going to marry you.
We're getting back together.
Don't you know him?
He will never abandon his children.
He never will abandon his children,
but can you really get back together?
We'll see about that.
You!
You want me to slap you?
Go ahead.
But I won't just stand here and take it.
What?
Don't waste your energy.
You're wasting your time here.
I've never gotten involved in your marital affairs and I don't plan to.
You two should take care of it.
I'm only going to talk to him.
And don't use the children as ammunition.
I hope we never see each other again.
What did she say?
She's very tough.
My heart is still pounding.
Why should it?
You should be firm.
She looks shy, but she's really tough.
I thought she'd cry and beg for forgiveness,
but she never backed down the whole time.
Why didn't you beat her up, then?
She would've beaten me up if I tried.
She said she's not backing down.
What do I do, mom?
You have to appeal to Minjung.
You have to change his mind.
Go and beg, if you have to.
How can I...
I'm scared to see him.
Why should you be?
You have the kids.
Daebak, what are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
We can't see each other again.
Why is that?
I deserve an explanation.
All I can say is our families are enemies.
I am Romeo and you are Juliet.
I don't want to be Juliet.
I want to live. Dying is sad!
Miho, goodbye.
No! Tell me the reason.
You should ask your mom.
Daebak! Daebak! Daebak!
Miho, why are you crying?
What's wrong?
Mom, did you do something bad?
Did someone say something to you?
Daebak broke up with me,
saying our families are enemies.
No.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I never did.
It came from the board of directors.
You have to resign before the new semester.
You have a month to sort things out.
[Letter of Resignation]
Good job.
Keep it up.
When are you going to China?
Soon, I think.
Don't send him.
You should go, old man.
I think you love picking on me.
I'm not an old man.
But you couldn't.
You can't speak Chinese.
Whatever.
You don't have any plans for dinner, do you?
I'm meeting Mr. Park, so come with me.
But I do have plans.
Can you move it?
Mr. Park wants to see you.
It's important.
I'm sorry, father.
Hello?
Father, are you at school?
Yes.
What time can you come?
Sangnam already made reservations.
Okay. I'll be right over.
It's Sangnam's treat, so please enjoy.
Applause!
Eat up!
She couldn't even visit us over the holidays.
I'm trying hard not to get upset.
I didn't raise Gwangbak to be a cook.
I'm sorry.
When's the housewarming party?
When I learn to cook.
We can order food.
Who cooks at home these days?
Don't you agree, Anggeum?
That's the first correct thing you said.
Bong, is something wrong?
Mother's talking to you.
Huh?
Why aren't you eating?
I'm fine, mother.
I had lunch late.
Do eat, mother.
The meat's burning. Eat up.
Oh, okay.
Eat before they burn.
Thank you, honey.
I never even thought of it.
They hadn't eaten out since what happened.
I think I married well.
Of course, you did.
I'm glad you're happy.
Oh, it's so nice to be out.
I feel like I've been liberated.
Like I escaped from prison.
Prison is a little too harsh.
Being married is harder than I expected.
I agree.
Why is that?
I'm the one who has to adapt,
so why is it hard for you?
Maybe because we hadn't dated for long,
but I feel like I don't know you all that well.
You don't?
You don't know me?
Sometimes I feel that way.
So you regret marrying me?
- Not really.
- Be honest with me.
You're getting ahead of yourself again.
That's why you have to be clear about it.
It sounds like you regret marrying me.
- It's not that.
- Then what is it?
You don't regret marrying me,
but you're disappointed in me?
Not disappointed... But...
It sort of feels like it.
Wait, this isn't it.
Why is this conversation going like...
- Forget it.
- What?
I can't tell you anything.
You're disappointed in me.
End of discussion.
You told me to be honest.
Fine. Be as honest as you want to be.
You think I don't want to be honest here?
Then tell me what you want to say.
That way, I can change.
I want us to be honest with each other,
and help each other fix mistakes we make.
I don't like getting emotional like this
and fight over the expressions we use.
Keep the promise we made on our first night.
Not using harsh words when we fight.
What harsh words did I use?
You did.
Even your tone was rude.
I can't communicate with you.
How frustrating.
What do you mean by that?
I'm frustrated because we can't communicate.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Don't over analyze it.
I'm not talking about schooling.
I'm not educated, so that's expected.
I'm just a high school drop out.
Stop it! I said I didn't mean it like that.
I'm leaving. I don't want to fight.
Don't come here when you two fight.
I don't understand women.
It's like they are from another country.
Aren't we speaking the same language?
Women and men must be different species.
You thought we were the same species?
Have you heard of "Men are from Mars,
Women are from Venus"?
Sangnam,
women take everything emotionally.
Depending on how they feel.
That's so unfair.
You need to know just one thing.
When talking to a women, just listen to her.
And take her side.
If you tell her how you feel after that,
she will be ready to listen to you.
But aunt, I didn't even say much tonight.
I just said I was having a hard time, too,
she got mad, and the rest is pretty foggy.
That was where your mistakes began.
If Gwangbak said it was hard for her,
you should've said she made you happy.
How can you say something that stupid?
You're impossible.
I don't think I was ready to get married.
Don't say that to anyone else but me.
It sounds like you regret getting married.
Aunt, this is difficult.
Of course it is.
You're two now, not one.
Did she go to her parents house?
Bring her home before your father finds out.
He's taking a shower right now.
Leave her alone. She'll come home.
You still don't get it.
Do everything you can and bring her home.
Oh, man.
Whose side are you on?
Mine.
Where are you?
My parents place.
You didn't tell them we fought, did you?
Actually, you attacked me for no reason.
Of course I did. I told them everything.
My father said he'll get you for this.
You...
I have a father, too, you know?
Come home before I count to three.
Forget it.
- One.
- Hah!
Two!
- Two and a half!
- Bah!
Two and a half and a half!
Why don't you come and get me, then?
Wait for me.
Wait till I get my hands on you!
Huh?
Did you fly over here?
I'm not talking to you.
You told me to pick you up, remember?
I came home for father, not for you.
What have you done right so far?
Other people get treated as a princess,
but look at me!
Just because you took my family out,
don't think your job is done.
I couldn't even go home over the holidays.
You think I married you to be your cook?
I should be regretting, not you!
Why won't you say anything?
Aunt Sunjeong told me I must listen when a woman talks.
You only listen to your aunt.
Why won't you listen to me?
Oh, my!
Why that...
Wifey, don't be mad at me.
Please.
Oh, man.
Who wants to?
Why don't you continue that in the house?
- We're home.
You said you had an important engagement.
Was dinner with your in laws good?
Are you their servant?
It wasn't like that.
We didn't have a housewarming party,
and her family is not doing...
And don't dance like that for your wife.
It's degrading.
What are you doing?
- Nothing.
Honey,
if I retired...
When will it be?
You can't retire yet.
You still have a few years left.
Who knows what will happen?
I'll have to, if the board tells me to.
You can't sleep?
No.
Instead of thinking about stuff like that,
you should think about seeing Minjung.
He's doing this because we lost our house.
You should show him who you are.
He already had her waiting for him,
and that's why he went and got a divorce.
Maybe you should meet her and...
That's enough.
You're not a pit bull.
Just let him be.
I am a pit bull.
That's why I survived this long.
Mother, I'm going to work.
You're not having breakfast?
I'm not hungry.
That's because you were up all night pouting.
I'll see you later.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hello.
Drink this.
What is it?
Vegetable juice.
It's great for pregnant women.
- What?
- Huh?
It's great for pregnant women and for everyone else.
Oh, I've been so tired lately. Exhausted.
You are? Exhausted?
Then listen to this kind of music.
- What's that?
- Uh,
prenatal music.
I'm not pregnant!
It's great for pregnant women and for everyone else.
When you're pregnant, you must feel peaceful.
- What's wrong?
- Huh?
Peace of mind's great for pregnant women
and for everyone else.
Stop that.
Pregnant and other women? As if!
Stop talking about pregnant women.
I can't stand you!
This is totally nuts.
The juice.
Oh.
Hobak, how is it going?
He's driving me crazy.
He's so interested and so jealous.
That's when you reel him in!
How?
What are you doing?
Oh.
Oh, I'm glad to see you.
What are you doing?
How can you dump Subak and do this?
You bastard!
Where are you going?
The restaurant.
That's not what's important here.
I couldn't come up with any other solutions.
Will you do as I say?
Do what?
I thought about what you said before.
When you said you'd raise my kids as your own, I was so grateful.
You've taught me a lot.
I should've said that before you did.
I'll think of Miho as my own.
Minjung.
Sunjeong, I'm coming to you.
Hold on, Minjung.
I'm so overwhelmed.
You really are coming to me?
It's been hard for me because of Miho.
She's heard somethings here and there,
and thinks I did something wrong.
She does?
I want to have a clear conscience, as a mother.
Sooner the better.
Okay.
I wonder if Miho will understand us.
She's at a sensitive age.
Miho really liked you from the beginning.
Which was rather weird.
She said she felt connected to you
and that she wished you were her dad.
She did?
Remember the money you gave her?
She even laminated that.
Oh, boy...
I'm glad she likes me.
Let's find a place for us to live first.
I want to move out before Gwangbak finds out.
She doesn't know about us yet.
You couldn't live with her if she did.
Let's find a place quickly.
Really?
Yes.
What do we do about Daebak?
That's that.
If you're happy, I'm happy, too.
You and him were in love a long time ago.
How did you know?
I'm a romance expert.
But don't tell anyone just yet.
I know that.
Miho.
Hello.
How did you come?
You came alone?
Yes.
Let's go in.
I don't have any snacks here.
It's okay.
Did you want to talk to me?
Mom told me everything.
You're going to marry my mom?
Yes.
Will you give me your blessings?
Yes. You're approved.
But I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Be good to my mom.
And don't worry about me.
I know I'm getting a sister and a brother.
I can look after Aeji and Jungji.
I've been babysitting Jungji anyway.
So you just need to be good to my mom.
I will.
My mom had a very difficult life.
She was really popular,
but she never dated anyone.
I think she was waiting for you.
So promise me that you'll make my mom happy.
Dad!
Aeji, it's you!
Dad, did you miss me?
Of course, I missed you.
Mom said no, but I made her come.
You did?
Mom, did I say it right?
What do you mean?
You told me to say that.
I never told you to say anything.
Did you eat?
I ate at work.
What brings you here?
The kids said they missed their dad.
I never said that.
What's wrong with you?
Aeji, what would you like?
Dad, pizza! Pizza!
Okay. Let's get pizza.
Where did you go before?
The academy.
Just the academy?
Yes.
Miho was here just now.
She made me pinky swear that I will make you happy.
Your daughter is really amazing.
Mom, let's go home. I'm sleepy.
Yes. You should go.
Dad, can we sleep here?
Here?
Mom, was that good?
Did I say it like you asked me to?
Why are you saying these things?
You can't sleep here.
It gets really cold.
It's not that cold.
The kids will catch a cold.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
Aeji, good night.
Dad, good night.
Go inside.
I told you to sleep there.
How can I?
Why not?
You had two kids together.
Don't be so self conscious.
Why should you be?
You did nothing wrong.
One thing you did was losing the house.
But it wasn't his house!
Be confident.
You are his first wife.
Men love to see their wives in their aprons,
cooking dinner when they come home.
The next time you go, cook something
and spend the night there.
Yes, yes.
Say, "Spend the night there."
I know! It must be love!
Hobak, let's do something naughty together.
Who the heck is this?
His hobby is buying cars.
He has them lined up and picks from them,
like picking out what shoes to wear.
It'd be nice to have money like that.
I can picture him.
He must be unattractive.
Fat and bald, am I right?
You really have no clue.
Rich people take good care of themselves.
He's 28 or 29 and single.
You're 36 so how much younger is he?
Oh, you're a grandpa.
Grandpa?
You!
I don't look like a grandpa!
You actually do.
Whatever!
You didn't tell him you're married?
Crazy? Why would I say that?
You didn't tell him you have two kids?
It's good manners to pretend to be single.
This is nutty, nutty, nuts!
Have you no conscience at all?
At least I had a conscience!
I told her I was married with two kids.
So why are you acting like you're single?
He never asked, so why should I?
That's not playing fair!
You're a fraud.
It is troublesome.
He sends flowers and sushi.
Sit down.
It hurts my neck to look at you
And?
You ate what he sent?
I did, with my co-workers.
He keeps asking me what I want,
saying he wants to buy me a handbag.
Crazy bastard.
Why bother calling him names?
It's your fault for flirting with him!
I never flirted with him.
I was being a model, smiling.
Oh! This, this.
This, wave dance.
When I did this, he called me cute.
That's flirting!
No one's ever called me cute before.
- Quit!
- Oh, you startled me.
Quit doing that model gig,
and this,
don't do this wave dance.
Don't do it for others.
Just do it for me.
You can only do it in front of me!
You said I looked awkward!
You don't. It's cute!
And d-d-don't believe a word men say.
All they want is to foo-fool around with you,
and you b-b-believe them?
Stop stuttering.
Why would a young, handsome rich man purse you, unless he's crazy?
I'm an expert in that field, and I'm  telling you, your life will be ruined.
Maybe this apartment is bad luck.
Why do we have to be tested like this?
I'm not being tested here.
I'm enjoying it.
Snap out of it.
Or you'll get kicked out in your undies.
Did you get kicked out in your undies?
Of course!
I mean, it could happen.
Don't worry.
I'm not interested in him.
There are many men who are interested in me.
There are many?
Hey, tell me.
Who are they? Who?
That's so funny!
That text was awesome. Perfect timing.
Hobak, let's do something naughty.
This is so much fun.
He must be so jealous.
Totally.
I had a hard time trying not to laugh.
I wish I'd known about this sooner.
You need some tension in your marriage.
He's here.
Hello.
- Oh, hello.
- Hi.
I brought lunch.
I cooked all of it.
Don't eat sushi men buy you.
It's done. All you need to do is reheat it.
And pretend you cooked it.
Leave Aeji home.
Take Jungji and have some beer with him.
Okay.
Here.
Oh, you're home.
You must be tired.
When did you come?
Just now.
Is it a bit bland?
Will you taste this for me?
What's that?
Why are they out there?
They went bad.
Jungji, daddy's home.
Play with daddy while I set the table.
Where's Aeji?
Should I tell her to come?
It's okay.
It's good.
Oh!
Salla, wake up.
It's been a while.
Yes. May I help you stand up?
Yes, please.
Why are you crying?
Did I do something wrong?
No.
I thought you'd never come back.
So I decided to get over you.
Why wouldn't I come back?
Because of your ex-wife.
You never called again.
I thought you spent the holidays with her.
Am I crazy?
Why would I be with her?
Salla, you're a rash person.
How could you get over me so soon?
Please don't do that anymore.
When you decide to get over me,
tell me first.
Everyone told me to get remarried,
but I never did.
Because of my kids.
Now that they are all married,
I thought I had finally met someone good,
but when your ex-wife appeared and went crazy on me,
I thought it wasn't meant to be.
But here you are, proposing to me.
I can't help but cry.
Proposing to you?
Yes.
I can't believe what's happening.
I'm so happy.
Mom, where were you?
Mother, I'm here, too.
What's up Don?
- Did you just call me Don?
- Huh?
Oh, mother!
Let me down. I'm taken.
Mom,
you're taken?
Oh, no.
I misspoke because I was startled.
Where did you get those flowers?
Who gave them to you?
A friend.
Enjoy yourselves. Don, you too.
Thank you, mother.
Mom, is it him?
Shh.
He proposed to me.
- He did?
- Shh!
They'll hear you!
Keep this a secret from Sedal.
Why?
Loser wants to go.
Okay. Mom, I'm leaving.
Okay. Take care.
I'm leaving! Goof-off, bye!
How dare he...
What did you and Yeongdal talk about?
Nothing.
Mom, are you seeing someone?
Of course not.
Mom, please.
Don't go around meeting just anyone.
You've been down that road before.
She totally misunderstood you.
I gave her the flowers to cheer her up,
but she thinks I proposed to her. What do I do?
She's always jumping to conclusions.
Daese, you should get married.
You never remarried because of Sangnam,
but now you should live your life.
I don't know if I can.
I'm afraid of living with a woman.
Will I be able to make her happy?
I'm afraid of failing again.
And it's hard to adjust my lifestyle.
Don't be too scared.
I'm all for you getting remarried.
Could I really pull it off?
Of course.
What do I do?
Jungji fell asleep.
He might catch a cold if I take him home now.
Then spend the night here.
Should I?
I'll sleep at my office.
I...
Yes, director.
We're getting ready to go home.
Please hold.
Hobak, it's the director.
Yes, director?
Really?
Thank you!
Anna, congratulate me!
I'm going to Italy!
Congratulations!
I feel like I'm dreaming!
Wow!
- A month?
- Yes.
My shop's been selected as the best shop,
so I'm going to Italy to see the industry.
I can't believe my luck.
My heart's still pounding.
What about me, then?
You can do what you've been doing.
You're all excited, aren't you?
Do you have to go?
What do you mean?
I've been dying to go!
Everyone wanted to go!
It's not a vacation.
It's for business.
This is nuts.
What's up?
Can you buy me a drink?
In the middle of the day?
Come in. I'm not busy.
Is your life fun?
It must be.
You're living with my baby sister,
so it must be rainbows and butterflies.
Sedal, what's wrong?
Didn't you make my niece's life miserable?
I feel so little.
Your niece is so successful.
She's flying high, soaring, actually.
But I've fallen so low, down to the basement.
Things are even, then.
A couple is one body and mind.
Hobak is flying and you're falling down.
Add them up and you meet at ground level.
I don't understand this feeling.
I'm scared.
About what?
About her leaving me.
What?
Housewives in my neighborhood all worry
if their husbands become successful,
they might one day leave them.
What the...
I heard she's really popular.
Men won't leave her alone.
I wish I could just beat them all up and tell your niece to quit.
"Quit your job and run the household
because I'll be working from now on!"
It's all my fault.
I can't blame anyone else.
I'm so happy.
I wanted to meet you formally.
Thank you for being Sunjeong's guardian.
She's like my own sister.
You were like a father and brother to me, too.
Daese, I want to thank you.
You're embarrassing me.
You ran the household.
You helped me out a lot.
I didn't do that for free. I got paid.
I knew you two would meet again someday.
Aren't you glad you waited for him?
Because of Miho...
Daese, let me poor you a drink.
He thinks raising Miho alone was hard.
Tell him.
Later.
Tell me what?
I'll tell you later.
Oh, I'm getting drunk.
I'll drink some more and go take a nap.
- You should.
- Here.
There are two rooms and three rooms.
How many rooms for 56 square meters?
Two.
-Two rooms.
- Okay.
Let's look for a few more days.
The ones we like are too expensive.
I'm sorry. I should pay for the house.
But I know how things are with you.
Does your ex-wife visit you?
I saw her.
I couldn't sleep last night.
I slept at the office.
Don't think about it.
And don't worry, either.
I still feel the same way.
I'll tell you what's going on right now.
Her parents want me to go back to her,
and she wants that, too.
Thank you for telling me everything.
We're finally by ourselves.
Good. What should we do?
Play the king game?
Let's play the robot cleaner game.
The winner makes the loser clean.
Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors!
I won!
Let's start the robot cleaner game.
Beep!
I'm your Blabbermouth Robot Cleaner.
Master, please choose.
Very clean, kind of clean.
Very clean, start!
Beep!
Very, very, very clean. Start.
When it's done, please kiss me.
Hurry, hurry!  Hey! Hurry up!
I need charging, I need charging.
Stay away! Why do you need charging already?
Go! Very clean, start.
Error, error.
Kind of, kind of, kind of clean, start.
Start cleaning.
Oh!
What are you doing?
Father, you were home?
What's going on here?
You think your husband is a joke?
How could you treat him like a slave?
Is he a vacuum cleaner?
We were just fooling around.
This is fooling around to you?
It was a game.
You're laughing?
No, I'm not.
I'm sorry, father.
We thought you weren't home.
So you've been doing this behind my back?
No, this was the first time.
Have you no dignity?
You're the problem!
This is why she treats you like a fool!
They were just playing a game.
Of all games, they have to play that?
If they were living by themselves,
they'd fool around all they want,
but we're here, so they can't do anything.
They were goofing around, thinking there was
nobody home, so don't be mad, Daese.
How can they do something like that?
She was treating him like he was a servant!
She gets on my nerves all the time.
That must be her special talent.
Hello?
It's me.
Who is this?
Don't pretend you don't know my voice.
I'm Minjung's mother in law.
Oh, okay.
Hello.
Let's cut to the chase.
I want to meet you.
Where can we meet?
I'm sorry, but I don't want to meet you.
What?
I'm older than you, so you should come.
You have no manners.
I have something to say, so come.
No thank you. And I have nothing to hear.
Who said you could decide that?
Are you feeling guilty?
I'm not going to beat you up,
so you should come and meet me.
I'm sorry, but I must hang up.
Hello? Hey!
The person you have called is unavailable...
Ugh...
I'm scared to go home.
Time flew by when I was working,
but now the day goes by so slowly.
Tell your family.
I should, but I can't do it.
I know how sad she'll become.
But you're getting pension.
Pension is not the issue.
I'm still strong, but I can't work anymore.
There's nothing for me to do.
What skills do I have?
I can't farm or do manual labor.
I've always been a teacher,
so what else could I do now?
I feel so lost.
I envy you for being a technician.
Wishing my children to be happy...
I'm home.
You're home?
- You're home?
- Did you have a good day?
Yes, I did.
You had a drink, didn't you?
Yes.
What's all this?
We're making envelopes.
We're making money.
Why don't you join us?
We need money if we want to buy a house.
Mother, you shouldn't do this.
Why should I just sit around, doing nothing?
It's better to make envelopes.
Everyone here wants to make money.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Come in here.
Subak is innocent,
but she can't say anything to Minjung.
How is she innocent?
She lost our house, not his!
Why don't you try talking to him?
What can I say?
What do you mean?
Sweet talk him into changing his mind.
Minjung, it's me.
When are you free?
Did something happen?
Does something have to happen for us to meet?
Make time for me this week.
This week?
Tell him tomorrow, tomorrow.
How about tomorrow?
I'm busy all week with work.
Let's have a drink.
I have something to say.
I'll make time and call you.
Okay. I got it.
What did he say?
He's busy.
He's too busy to even eat?
Why can't you do anything right?
You should've said meet me at so and so.
Why were you so timid?
We're not family, so I couldn't help it.
Not family? Ugh.
What is it?
I have a stomachache.
Maybe I have indigestion from dinner.
You have a stomachache?
How does it feel?
Are you nauseous?
I guess I do.
Don't take that!
What are you doing?
Medicine's bad if you're pregnant.
What?
It's great for pregnant women and for everyone else.
What's wrong with you?
Are you accusing me of something?
What?
You keep talking about pregnant women.
You think I'm cheating on you?
No, I don't think that.
I wouldn't do anything immoral.
How dare you!
If you say that again, I'll!
You'll what? You'll what?
I'll slap my mouth.
Oh, satisfied? Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh.
Mother, what's wrong?
It's my bladder.
I had a lot of cold broth.
Why are you pacing here like a space cadet?
I couldn't fall asleep.
You know what "space cadet" means?
Yes. Yeongdal taught me.
Oh, boy.
Bong.
I'm here.
Why did you drink?
I met a friend.
And why can't you sleep?
I must be going through male menopause.
Whatever it is, don't worry so much.
It'll go away, no matter how hard it is.
Will it go away?
Of course.
I must go on, but it's too hard.
Bong, did you go in?
No, I didn't.
I'll stay here, so you take your time.
Having you there makes feel safe.
Mother, spring will come, won't it?
Of course.
It'll come very soon.
Doctor,
I'm only 37, so I'm scared.
I feel like I've ceased being a woman.
You said you have 2 kids?
Yes.
I don't care if it's menopause,
but to actually face it is...
Look here.
Can you see this?
What's that?
Is that...
Is that like cancer?
Didn't you say you have 2 kids?
See this handsome little thing?
Congratulations.
What did you say?
You're pregnant.
No way.
That can't be.
Nothing happened, so how can I be pregnant?
I'll be out for one hour.
Just one hour.
Not even 10 minutes more.
Okay.
Don't do this.
What?
The plants did nothing wrong!
They're all dead!
I don't want any traces of you in there.
And stop coming here.
What will people say?
You can't go in.
You should go.
- Out of my way!
- No!
I have no time or energy to argue with you.
Sunjeong!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I'm okay.
Why are you here?
I brought some plants for your place.
She wouldn't let me go in.
Subak,
don't ever come here again.
If I want to see the kids, I'll go there.
So you should stop coming here.
Subtitles by KBS World
Living with your in laws is hell?
Thank you for enduring it.
Move out right now!
Let's move out.
I can't, not like this.
What's going on here?
It's not his fault.
How can you break her heart like this?
You should be ashamed of yourself!
The breadwinner can't get sick.
Get up, why don't you?
Leave me alone!
Just leave me alone!
I'm sorry. For our kids' sake...
I'm leaving.
He's not family.
You can't expect anything.
Father, please help me.
I was so good to you!
You're a beast!
I...
I didn't want to say this,
but do you know why I divorced Subak?