Subtitles by KBS World
Oh, my...
What's all this?
I mean,
how could you buy so much?
That's not the $100,000 limit credit card!
Please don't mention the past.
It's nuts.
Then help me not bring it up.
Follow me.
Receipts.
Here.
Household accounting book.
I haven't yet...
Not yet?
I'll do it.
When everyone goes to sleep.
I can focus better when everyone's asleep.
I used to study for exams after everyone...
Fine!
Just look at these.
You don't know anything, do you?
Why? What's wrong?
Everything is wrong.
How can you use a month's budget on one day?
How are we supposed to live?
But I only bought what we need.
Mr. Heo Sedal.
We used to live on $300 a month.
Look here.
I told you to refer to how I spent money!
Stop nagging on him.
That's enough.
Mom, please go to your room.
Stick to the budget.
You'll make us go bankrupt if you don't.
I'm going to check the book once a week.
Okay.
You're being too harsh on him.
Why are you kneeling?
You should relax.
I'm relaxed.
Mom, I'm fine. Go to bed.
You're driving me mad.
You're being too mean.
You should praise him for his efforts.
Were you great from the beginning?
Instead of explaining how to do it,
you make him sit on his knees,
as if he's one of your sons.
Mother.
Mom, go to your room.
Why are you butting in our business?
Your business?
Have your bodies switched or something?
What do you mean?
Hobak, you should get a check up
to make sure you're not a man.
Sedal, you too.
It's like if you switched roles with each other.
That's because we're married.
Idiot.
You have no balls.
I can't believe I gave birth to you.
Why did I even bother?
But we work well together and that's good.
Right, honey?
How can you use violence?
I want a divorce.
I'm moving out.
Don't tell your parents yet.
I'm pregnant.
What's wrong?
Did you have a bad dream?
I wish!
Go back to sleep.
You almost scared a baby out of me!
You too? That can't be.
What?
Don't talk to me about any babies.
Why you little, just go to sleep!
You have no wife or children to support.
Your brother is supporting you,
so why can't you sleep well?
Wife and children.
Mom's words are hitting me really hard.
Hobak.
Yeongdal.
Sintong, Bangtong.
Why are you calling them?
Please don't tell the boys.
I was checking to see if they're asleep.
They are fast asleep.
Yeongdal, be honest with me.
About what?
I've been suspicious of you lately.
You are, aren't you?
No, I'm not even married.
Don't just deny it.
Be honest with me,
so we can figure things out.
What if your stomach starts to grow?
Shh!
Oh, boy...
Hobak.
You shouldn't cry.
You have to pull yourself together.
I have experience in this.
You're scared, aren't you?
How many months?
Have you gone to the doctor's?
No, I'm too scared to.
I only did a home pregnancy test.
Whose is it?
Heo Yeongdal. It's mine.
Not you! The baby's dad.
Oh, tell me, so we can figure things out.
Yeongdal, is it...
Is it what?
That you don't know who the dad is?
Huh?
I mean, did you get drunk and...
Hobak,
I've always had a lot of men around,
but I was never that crazy.
I'm sorry.
Then who is it?
Did you tell him?
And?
He won't take care of you? He won't?
That bastard!
Tell me who he is. I'll kill him.
Please don't.
Who is it? Huh?
We should beat up a bastard like that.
My uncle? Ugh...
Hobak. Shh!
This can't be.
You hate each other.
It just happened.
Hobak, what do we do?
- Mom!
- Mother.
What are you doing?
Why aren't you in bed?
I was asking Yeongdal something.
Mom, let's go.
Now you're yelling at your sister in law, too?
She's not yelling at me.
Mom, let's go.
The stew came out really delicious.
It's perfect for winter.
Yes.
Minjung didn't come home, did he?
Huh?
No.
He didn't even call last night.
He would've come home, if he could.
He must be really busy.
It's because it's the end of the year.
Bring him some clothes.
Okay.
You're really getting a divorce?
What else can I do?
You're getting a divorce over that?
Your husband must be really petty.
Didn't you complain about me being married?
I'm actually glad.
I was really scared when it happened,
but now I feel relieved.
You're not happy I'm getting a divorce?
Fine, I am. Boy...
I got a divorce, but it's not good.
You should try to make things work for the kids.
But I can't.
Is anything up at home?
Nobody has dropped by or called?
No, why do you ask?
It's nothing.
It's just over that hill there.
Right this way.
It's perfect for one person.
Would you like to move in?
Yes, mother.
You didn't come home.
You must be really busy.
I am.
I made ground bean stew for you.
Are you coming home late tonight?
I'm going to make kimchi stew for you.
We made kimchi together,
so we should eat it together.
I got mackerels at the market.
I'm going to boil it with some kimchi,
and it'll be perfect with rice.
Makes your mouth water, huh?
That thing you do,
when you see something delicious.
Drop by for dinner, okay?
And drive carefully.
The streets were so slippery that I almost slipped and fell.
I was carrying Jungji on my back, so if I'd fallen,
I would've made a pancake of your son!
So watch out and don't slip.
You must be busy. I'm hanging up.
Okay.
Goodbye, mother.
So, will you move...
I will.
Yeongdal!
I need to ask you something.
I dropped by on my way to a shop.
Did my uncle call?
He hasn't?
Oh, man.
Yeongdal, let me ask you one thing.
Do you love my uncle?
And you want to marry him?
How can you do that?
How can you make her cry and do nothing as if it's none of your business?
What else could I do?
You have to take responsibility, like a man.
I want to, but...
But what?
Why are you making excuses?
You know how pathetic you look if you ignore the issue and disappear?
She'll remember that forever.
I know that.
But I haven't disappeared on her.
Not texting or calling her after hearing that is disappearing on her.
I wasn't being literal, you know?
You don't get it at all, do you?
I'm furious so imagine how she feels.
What am I supposed to do?
You really don't know?
You have to marry her.
But it's not like I have a job.
Then why did you sleep with her?
I didn't want to do it. I got drunk.
Don't blame the alcohol.
You sound like a loser.
Don't live up to your nickname!
You!
Then don't act like a loser.
Uncle, be honest with me.
Do you love Yeongdal?
Even if I do, it doesn't matter.
She got furious saying she felt dirty.
That's not true!
She said she loves you.
She did?
She loves me?
Yes.
That can't be.
I'm not her type. You know that.
Her ideal man is a rich man.
Who marries their ideal?
The important thing is that she loves you.
Although I don't know why.
From my experience, the man who takes care of me is the best man in the world.
Being poor means nothing, if there's love.
That was how I felt, uncle.
But she's not you.
All women are the same.
Thanks, Hobak.
Yeongdal.
Yes?
Don't let this baby ruin your life.
If you end up with me, your life will become miserable.
You called me to tell me that?
You made me here in silence for 30 minutes,
and that's all you have to say?
Fine.
I'm going to have this baby alone.
Don't even say hi to me from now on.
This wasn't what I planned.
This is crazy.
What do you want?
I...
I can't buy you brand name handbags.
Is that okay with you?
Don!
Oh, hey, hey, hey!
The baby, careful.
You must be busy with your son's wedding.
I am.
Oh, my...
Meet me after the wedding.
I'm on fire, thanks to you.
You're the hottest man.
I can tell just looking at you.
I came to say hi today.
I can't go a day without seeing your face.
Okay.
Is your ex-wife coming to the wedding?
She wants to, but...
My husband died, so I don't know,
but how does it feel to meet your ex-wife?
I don't feel anything.
It's like meeting a robot.
- A robot?
- Yes.
Okay.
You can call me or text me.
My phone is always on.
Okay. Bye.
Who was she?
The makeup store owner.
Whatever.
Father.
No more.
How much is it?
It's not much, but it's the best I could.
What do you take me for?
Excuse me?
You think I'm a beggar?
This is the best you could do?
You take me for an idiot, don't you?
- That's not true.
- Mother.
Mother.
Why do you think Sangnam introduced us?
He wants you to treat me like a mother!
You don't get it, do you?
Did I give you a list of things to buy?
Haven't you heard of what people do?
What kind of wedding gifts they buy?
Then you should at least show some courtesy.
$5,000? That's it?
Is that for my chewing gum?
If I wanted to,
I can cancel this wedding.
Mother,
this isn't a wedding gift.
We're not giving each other wedding gifts,
and I'm going to stick to that.
This is a little gift I'm giving to thank you for bringing Sangnam into this world.
For bringing him into the world?
I told you to act like my daughter in law.
How dare you act this way?
You want a piece of me?
I was infamous when I ran a tea house.
Who do you think I am?
Fine. I'm calling Sangnam.
Look at you!
Do you really want me to call him?
If you want to, go ahead.
What?
I don't think this is right.
I won't answer to any more unjust demands.
I thought you were a reasonable person,
and I wouldn't have come had I known better.
Whatever you want to tell Sangnam,
you can go ahead and tell him.
I brought this for you,
so I'll leave it with you.
I can't believe her!
Hey! You!
I think you should show your father in law
a token of appreciation for raising Sangnam up so well all alone.
But don't tell Sangnam about it.
I like this one,
but would my father in law like it?
You have great taste.
It's a popular gift item for the groom's father.
You can wrap it in the traditional quilt.
Then I'll take the box and wrapping quilt, too.
How about your letter?
My letter?
Brides write letters to their in laws.
What do I say?
Things that are nice to hear.
Thank him for his son, and for bringing you into the family.
And say that you'll be good to the family.
Who wouldn't like that?
They'll be so happy.
Here is a sample letter.
Some people put rice paper over it and trace it, too.
You can decorate it with pressed flowers.
Talk about earning points, right?
Is he here?
Where were you?
We closed a long time ago.
Oh, I met some friends.
Don, come in.
Hello.
It's you, Loser.
How come you came with Yeongdal?
I ran into him outside.
Sedal is in the kitchen.
Your friend is now a housewife.
Hold on.
I'm almost done with the dishes.
Whoa!
You look nice, uncle.
Wow, you look really handsome in that suit.
I heard you're busy these days.
Yes.
You'll be making lots of money soon.
Dad's setting up a pizza shop for you when you get your license, right?
Women will line up for you, uncle.
You went a little too far.
There are so many pizza shops now that they go bankrupt every day.
Mom!
Don't talk about going bankrupt! It's bad luck.
How can you talk like that to your mom?
Sorry, mom.
I can't believe you're listening to Loser.
Don't stand there like that. Sit.
Okay.
Loser, you look different tonight.
It's because you've only seen him delivering pizza.
He's actually tall and stylish.
Oh, here.
Oh! Uncle! You're so kind!
You'll make a great husband!
Right, mother?
Where did you get the money to buy this?
I know you can't afford it.
You should save every penny you make,
if you want to get married some day.
He can afford this.
I won't let you spend money on me.
That's like stealing from the poor.
I know you don't make that much.
I'm saying this as your friend's mom.
Okay.
You don't know how life will turn out.
He might become rich selling pizza.
Words are easy.
Anyway, why are you sitting so closely?
Huh?
Oh, my!
You actually look really good together.
I'm actually offended to hear that.
What do you take Yeongdal for?
Loser,
don't be offended by mom's words.
Just let it pass.
Why should he?
He should pay attention to every word,
so someone will marry him someday.
It'd be so sad if he gets old and dies alone.
See if you can find a widow with kids.
Who knows?
He might get drunk like me and get some poor woman knocked up.
What kind of idiot would get knocked up by someone who's unemployed and penniless?
That's nonsense.
I agree.
Unbelievable.
Wasn't Hobak funny?
She tried to make her uncle look good.
As if I would ever even consider him.
No way!
Don't hang out with Loser, okay?
Don't even say hi when he visits.
You can't get involved with him, okay?
I know.
Hey.
How's your back?
It's much better.
I can get around now.
But the weather must affect it.
I go to the sauna sometimes.
What brings you by?
I just wanted to see you.
Is something wrong?
What is it?
Father...
I...
I'm getting a divorce.
I'm sorry, father.
Is living at her parents house too hard?
It's not that.
I've moved out.
I got a room.
How about the kids?
I'm worried about them.
Whoever raises them,
they'll grow up with only one parent.
Not being able to be there for them really breaks my heart.
I want to be able to provide for them.
When I think of them...
Dad!
My little girl.
Dad, why won't you come home?
Are you busy?
I've been really busy.
I won't be able to come home.
Is that okay?
No! Dad, come home.
I will soon.
Do you want to go on a trip next Sunday?
Really?
Yes, really.
You're really getting married?
Yes.
Out of the frying pan, into the fire.
I married off two daughters before her,
but it's never been this difficult.
It was off and it was on. Off and on.
Like if it's some kind of a light switch.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo!
I've never seen anything like it or heard of any daughter in law audition.
I'll be great to her to make up for that.
Of course you should.
Of course.
If you two are happy, it'll be worth it.
When dating, only the two of you matter,
but in marriage, you share responsibilities.
That's the difference between dating and marriage.
You'll face heartaches and difficulties,
and you'll be disappointed in each other.
You know our family motto?
Read it.
Put yourself in other's shoes.
That will prevent lots of arguments.
I'll remember that.
Me too.
Don't try to take advantage.
Try to give more.
Think of what you can do for each other.
Remember what your father's saying.
We will.
Don't pay attention to each others families.
You won't have time for that.
You'll be busy building your own family.
We're all doing pretty well. so don't worry.
Right.
What do you mean by that?
They shouldn't draw any lines.
There has to be a relationship.
Nothing's changing for his family,
but we're losing a daughter.
Put yourself in our shoes.
I'm losing a daughter I've raised for 30 years.
Are you trying to do business with your kid?
It's okay.
I'll remember that.
Don't take my mom too seriously.
I don't know why she's acting like that.
I thought she was funny.
It won't be funny for so long.
My brother in laws are all tired of it.
You've trained me well, so I'm good.
I'll see you tomorrow.
What are you going to do tonight?
I'm going to spend my last night being single partying all night.
Oh, you will?
Wow...
We'll finally be married tomorrow.
But what is this feeling?
Aren't you really happy?
You know how honest I am, right?
I shouldn't feel this way,
but I'm only human.
What do you mean?
Now that I know you'll be mine,
I don't feel anything when I hold you.
There's no excitement anymore.
What?
How mean!
I'm going to get you for this!
Oh...
I didn't see anything.
So continue on.
I'll see you tomorrow, uncle.
How embarrassing.
Father, how come you're not in bed?
I will, soon.
What are you doing up?
I can't fall asleep.
Father, thank you.
I should thank you.
Gwangbak,
I'm always on your side.
I've never opposed anything you did.
Except for this wedding.
I know.
You've always been on my side,
even when I quit my job to become a writer.
You've always been behind me all the way,
and knowing you were there gave me all the confidence I needed.
Thank you so much, father.
My little girl.
You're leaving me now.
You're not my daughter anymore.
You're a man's wife
and a daughter in law of another family.
Times change, but all parents want one thing.
A happy marriage life for their children.
I'll be happy, father.
I know you will be.
Be wise.
Everyone loves those who are good to their parents.
Respect and love your father in law.
Then Sangnam will treasure you.
That's how you become family.
I will, father.
Don't worry about us.
We have your sisters and Daebak.
It's okay if you're not here.
If you build a happy family,
I will be happy for you.
I'll try my best.
Oh, I knew it.
Why aren't you in bed?
A groom needs his beauty sleep.
I want to have a drink with you.
Come inside, father.
Sangnam.
I only have one thing to say.
Good luck, son.
Father.
Thank you for raising me.
I'm the one who's thankful.
Thank you for growing up to be a good man,
and thank you for being by my side.
To me, you were a friend, brother,
son and wife.
Actually,
I was able to make it because of you.
I don't know where I'd be if it weren't for you.
Father.
Thank you, father.
You grew up without a mom.
Thinking about it breaks my heart.
It's okay.
You were mom and dad to me.
I'm a good man because of you.
Father,
I've always been proud of you.
I gave up education and followed your path because I was proud of you.
You are the greatest man to me.
I want to live like you.
You shouldn't.
You should live happily with your wife.
I will.
So happy that you'll be jealous.
Good.
Father.
Thank you.
Why aren't you asleep?
I want to sleep with you, mom.
Mom, you're sad, aren't you?
This is my third time, so not really.
Compared to Subak and Hobak,
I had bigger hopes for you.
Growing up, you were a stubborn girl.
You never once gave in.
You never once listened to me.
I'm sorry, mom.
I was nothing but trouble for you.
I want you to be happy.
That's all I want.
I will be.
I promised father earlier.
I told you I won't give you allowance,
but I will, secretly.
You will?
Of course.
I'll skim money and give it to you.
And I'll buy you boxes of dollar undies.
Oh, you're the best.
Have lots of children.
It's hard to raise many kids,
but once they're grown up, it's nice.
If one child makes you sad,
another makes up for it, and so on.
I'll have at least five.
You'll raise them for me, right?
No thank you!
Can I get some sleep here?
You weren't asleep?
I couldn't.
You're teaching your daughter to skim money.
So how can I sleep?
Oh, no, Jungji's up.
Oh, no.
Bark for him before you get married.
Oh, boy.
- How pretty.
- Bounce. bounce.
Let me use the toilet.
Where's my necktie?
It's on the dresser.
Okay.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Hey, Gwangbak.
Letter?
Okay.
Put it in and wrap it up?
You go ahead first.
Miho, go with your uncle.
Why?
I have to do something before I go.
Go ahead without me.
You have to greet the guests.
Okay. Let's go, Miho.
Where are you?
I'm about to leave.
Then come to the house.
Why?
Come. We have no time.
- Come.
- Why?
You need to wear hanbok.
I have to wear hanbok?
Were you going to wear that cheap outfit?
Come to my dress room and change.
You have a dress room?
I turned the basement into my dress room.
Girl,
you're enjoying all the luxury I could've.
It's a bit creepy here.
Come in.
It's too dark in here.
Turn the lights on.
Where are the clothes?
Hey! Sunjeong!
Why are you doing this?
Sunjeong!
I'm sorry, but stay there.
I put water and a chamber pot in there.
So stay there until the wedding's over.
You little!
Hey! Sunjeong!
Open this door! Open it!
I'll kill you!
I can't die just yet.
Sangnam invited you because he's naive,
but Daese and I won't let that happen.
I won't let you ruin Sangnam's wedding.
Hey! Sunjeong!
When I get out of here,
I'll kill you!
What took you so long?
We're about to start.
Hello.
Yes, hello.
It's my little sister's wedding.
Try to act like we're a loving couple,
so nobody will suspect anything.
I think everyone's here.
How do we start?
We'll have a simple ceremony and have lunch.
Okay. Go ahead and start.
I'll be the host.
I know how it's done.
This is the wedding style the government
wants us to have,
so there's no preacher or emcee.
It's cozy and nice.
Now, everyone,
focus and clap your hands!
If you don't, you'll be fined a dollar.
I will be the emcee because...
Well, someone has to do it.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm the bride's brother in law, Heo Sedal!
Sedal, keep it short, please.
I spent the last three days planning this,
but due to the groom's protest,
I'll keep it simple.
Today's lunch is Korean cuisine buffet,
so you can eat after the ceremony.
If you're caught eating before everyone else,
there'll be a dollar fine.
First!
We were supposed to sing the national anthem,
but we're going to skip to the blessings of the fathers in honor.
Please go first.
You should go first.
Okay.
Have lots of kids and be happy, no matter what.
Ditto.
Vice Principal, you should give a speech.
Speeches are boring if they're too long.
I've already said everything last night.
You'll get the answer if you put
yourself in other's shoes.
Ditto.
Next is the wedding rings...
But the bride and groom got impatient and already put them on.
Next is the announcement of the marriage.
I, Choi Sangnam.
And I, Wang Gwangbak.
Have become husband and wife!
We'll have lots of kids and live happily.
And when we make mistakes, let us know.
And guide us in the right direction.
That concludes Choi Sangnam...
And Wang Gwangbak's.
Wedding ceremony.
Oh, man.
What the heck!
Aunt,
it's small, but please give it to father.
I will. Thanks.
No. Thank you for your advice.
Aunt where is she?
It's almost over.
Well, I'm not sure.
Gum, gum.
Oh, no, oh, no.
For the bride and groom. Cheers!
Cheers!
Eat up.
You too.
Let me know if you want anything.
I'll get it for you.
Okay.
Hurry up and go.
Drive carefully and call us later.
We will.
You're leaving as two, but come back as three.
- Oh.
- We'll do our best.
We'll see you later.
Aunt, bye bye!
Sunjeong, good job.
It was nothing.
Congratulations on getting a daughter in law.
Oh, I put her gift in your room.
Take a look.
By the way, wasn't their eldest son in law the parcel service guy?
You're right.
I almost didn't recognize him.
He looked pretty handsome today.
How interesting.
Open this door! Open!
What was that?
Who do you think you are?
I missed my son's wedding because of you!
You!
What are you doing?
Sangnam is my only son.
You made me miss my son's wedding!
I won't ever forget this.
That was so mean.
You have no pity for me?
I won't ever see him again.
How could you...
What you did was wrong.
He's my own son.
I know I've done some bad things,
but how could you lock me up in the basement?
I'm addicted to chewing gum,
and I can't go a moment without it...
I'm sorry about locking you up, but your appearance would've been bad for Sangnam.
Fine. I'm the problem here.
Who can I blame?
You can see him tomorrow.
Really? I can do that?
Honey, thanks.
It's so much fun!
Don, run!
Run! Run!
Yeongdal, are you having fun?
Huh? Are you?
Yes!
Ouch.
It hurts.
Hey!
Giddy up! Giddy up!
Yeongdal, are you having fun/
Yes!
Faster! Faster!
Don!
- Are you okay?
- Yes...
What was that?
Hey! Why are you laughing?
I can't breathe.
Sangnam.
Sunjeong, thanks.
But you did all the work.
You raised your son alone, and now he's
all grown up and married. You're amazing.
That's all because of you.
You've been like a mom to Sangnam.
I've always been grateful to you.
Please don't say that.
I'm indebted to you.
I'm going to be nice to Gwangbak.
She's my son's wife, so I shouldn't hate her.
Good for you, Daese.
But why did you tell Manjeong to stay?
Why didn't you just send her away?
Who knows what she might be up to?
I thought she should meet him one last time.
I've always felt badly about Sangnam's scars.
He's finally getting over them,
and I didn't want to get in the way.
We can't go back to the way things were,
but whenever they miss each other,
I think they can meet as mom and son.
And I think she's changed a lot.
Don't worry too much.
She'll only see them after the honeymoon.
What are you doing?
Reading a book on pregnancy.
And your mom?
She's meeting her friends.
Are you craving anything?
I am.
Excuse me,
can I buy a bowl of blood sausage soup?
But we're closed.
Just one bowl, please.
My wife is pregnant,
and she really wants blood sausage soup.
- She's pregnant?
- Yes.
If she doesn't eat it, our baby will be ugly.
Ma'am, you're very pretty.
Ugh...
This is only because you're so nice.
Thank you.
Yeongdal.
Don!
Let's have lots of fun.
I have a favor to ask.
You have to make me breakfast.
I can't work if I don't eat breakfast.
I promise.
I'll cook for you.
And instead of doing something the other likes,
let's not do what the other doesn't like.
Right. That shows how much you care.
Let's tell each other three things we hate.
You go first.
Don't talk badly about my family when we argue.
Don't look at other women.
Don't come home late without letting me know.
No silent treatment, no matter how mad.
No swearing or hitting, no matter how mad.
No spying on each other's phone. Okay?
Promise.
Copy.
Laminate.
Is it good?
Yes.
You carried it inside your jacket, so it's warm.
You'll get indigestion. Slow down.
My beautiful princess.
I'm a beautiful princess?
Yes, that's what I saved you in my phone as.
Then I should call you my handsome prince.
I feel sad for my princess.
Your friend must be having a great time
at a warm hotel room,
but you're eating soup out in the cold,
when you're much prettier.
I am?
To be honest, Gwangbak's not pretty.
She's skinny like a cotton swap.
Look at her eyes.
It's a miracle her eyeballs don't fall out.
I used to envy Gwangbak's good grades.
Why would you envy that?
Oh...
I'm sorry you got knocked up by me.
What's wrong with you?
There are so many rich men.
You're in serious trouble, girl.
That's not true. I'm the luckiest girl.
Thanks, Yeongdal.
Your mother doesn't know, does she?
No.
How do we tell her?
She hates me.
Let's work toward each other's dream.
I hope your China deal goes well.
And I want you to continue writing.
I can have a few hours a day to myself?
Of course.
I'll talk to father and be very supportive.
Shall we work on our parents request?
Oh, no!
Hold on.
Why?
I have a confession.
There's more?
I get scared when you say that.
There's something else I need to know?
Yes.
It's okay, you know?
I'm already yours.
I can't run away now.
I've never told anyone this before.
I've been saving this.
I love you.
Me too.
I love you, too.
Let's see...
Oh!
Sunjeong! Sunjeong!
Look! Look at this!
How can she send this to me?
I am so offended!
This is no gift!
I'm sure she made a mistake.
You can't make a mistake like this!
She's thoughtless!
Completely thoughtless!
She's not careful, has no respect,
and has no manners!
How can she put this in the gift?
This shows she didn't pay any attention!
Daese, calm down.
I can't calm down! I won't!
I was planning on being nice to her!
How can she disappoint me like this?
This is how she's going to act?
- Is it good?
- It's so good.
Slow down.
Say ah.
Is that you, Yeongdal?
Don, wait for me!
Hey!
Stop! You! Loser!
Loser!
Thief!
Subtitles by KBS World
I was so upset I couldn't sleep.
I was so nice to her!
We should make it official.
You're impossible.
You don't want to divorce me?
Shut up.
You have to do everything I say.
I want to divorce now so I can marry you.
You want to marry me?
Bong, please help.
She won't even consider me.
What is wrong with you?
You said you'll be good to me!
Yes.
You're not doing this for the family.
This is your revenge!
This is my revenge.
I can't take Sedal back just like that.