Subtitles by KBS World
I need this for my writing.
I need to know how it feels.
Your teeth.
I know, I've been brushing like crazy.
Hey, hey.
Where are you going?
Research.
Hey, aren't you going to say hi?
Why won't you say hi?
I'm your brother's friend!
Can't you say hi?
No.
You...
But I'm like your brother.
Stop following me. It's embarrassing.
Yes, I'm on my way.
I'll be there in about five minutes.
Yes. I'll be there soon.
Parcel service!
Hello?
Dad!
Yes, Aeji!
Why is your phone always busy?
It's because I'm really busy.
I'm going to forget your face, dad.
But I won't forget your face.
Why did you call?
Tell me why you called.
Dad, I want to learn taekwondo.
You want to learn taekwondo?
Okay. I'll tell mom to send you.
Aeji, I'll talk to you later.
Oh, dad, don't do the cat sound.
Aeji, I'm getting a call.
Aeji, I love you.
Yes, parcel service.
Oh, my! Son!
Make my day.
Madam Park Salla, do whatever you want.
Get in.
Oh, my. Oh, my. Oh, my...
Oh, my. I'm so excited.
A foreign car!
How much does a car like this cost?
You wouldn't know.
Your father never got to enjoy this.
Why did he have to leave us so soon?
His temper was just as short as yours.
That darn old man!
How could he just die leaving behind two little children?
I'm sure he didn't want to die.
And to be honest, he wasn't old.
He was my age when he died.
He probably aged on the other side.
I wonder if he got remarried.
He was like me, so he must be popular.
He better not!
If he did, I'm going to destroy him.
Stop thinking about him and enjoy your life.
You should meet someone.
No, I'm too old for that.
There were many chances,
but I never took them because of you.
Mom, do whatever you want to do today.
I got a credit card.
Really? I can just use it?
Yes. The director gave me permission.
Those darn women.
I'll make them crazy jealous!
Look at her walking.
Honk at her.
Roll down the window.
Anggeum!
What kind of car...
Mother.
This is my son's car.
It's a foreign car.
It's not my car.
I'd ask you to get in, but there's no room.
Hey, roll up the window.
Mom, was that something you wanted to do?
Of course.
Did you see her getting upset?
That was nothing compared to what she put me through.
Hey, park really close.
Park close to the window so they can see.
Closer. Honk.
Oh, my.
- Who's car is that.
- Closer, closer.
A little closer. Closer.
I see Salla in the car.
A little closer.
Subak could do it, so why can't you?
Why did you break the window?
Oh, what do I do?
Don't worry.
I'll replace it with stronger glass.
Call the window repair shop.
Did you hear that?
Okay, everyone.
Don't worry about the cracked window.
A flying bird doesn't look back.
Forget about your husbands or kids
and have a good time here.
Oh, let me introduce myself.
I'm Heo Sedal,
Madam Park Salla's only son
and Madam Lee Anggeum's son in law.
And I have an announcement.
I'll pay for today's lunch.
Oh, please sit.
The window will crack more.
Enjoy two orders each.
I see some who need three orders.
And do take two orders to go.
I'll pay with this.
Add the cost for the new window.
Salla, your son is amazing.
I wish I had a son like him.
I know.
A son in law is someone else's son.
But my son is mine and that's what counts.
Bragging about your son in law is no good.
Don't you agree?
Right.
Your son must be doing great.
He is doing really great.
A few nights ago he bought a bunch of gifts for his wife's family.
Anggeum, I heard you really enjoyed that.
This is why you shouldn't mistreat people.
You never know what will happen.
Oh, Minjung.
You deliver here?
Yes.
Mom, say hello.
This is Minjung.
He's making a delivery here.
Oh, you're Subak's husband!
Oh, it must be so hard on you.
I heard you're living with your in laws.
Yes. Hello.
Things must be really tough.
I feel so bad for you.
Your mother in law is here.
Say hello.
She's not going to get away with this.
She can't do that to me!
Mom, did you boil Jungji's bottles?
That's not my job! You do it.
What's wrong?
Wasn't lunch fun?
I'm furious. That's why.
The beauty salon woman,
she's acting like she owns the world.
Sedal drove her to the restaurant in a foreign car and broke their window trying to park really close.
He broke the window?
She was just trying to imitate you.
Why did Minjung have to make a delivery just then?
I couldn't believe my eyes.
He came to that restaurant?
Unbelievable.
They were laughing at me for having bragged about my son in law, and it was humiliating.
I don't even want to see you.
How can you say that to me?
You enjoyed a lot of things thanks to me.
This is why money is important.
When I gave you money, you loved me and Minjung, but now, you hate us.
How could you change so completely?
Mom, you're really mean!
Daughters are useless.
Where did my knife go?
And the cutting board is missing, too.
Huh?
What happened here?
Uncle! Uncle!
Yes?
Did you empty out the fridge?
Why would I do that?
The vegetables I bought yesterday are gone,
my knife cutting board and pots are gone.
You didn't put them somewhere?
I saw Gwangbak carrying all kinds of stuff.
Huh?
Why did you bring so much stuff?
It's not like you're moving.
It just sort of happened.
I thought we'd need them if we wanted to make stew and cut the fish.
Oh, boy.
They might think we're moving in together.
You like me a lot, huh?
Why do you always tease me?
What are your plans?
Plans?
You lured me to go night fishing with no plans?
I didn't lure you.
You did.
Let's catch some fish and eat them.
- And?
- And make stew.
And?
With stew, we'd need alcohol. Let's drink.
And make noodles.
And?
Reheat the stew and eat it again.
And eat more noodles?
Just be honest. You want to kiss me.
I don't! Stop teasing me!
Did I make you nervous?
Yes.
So I made you nervous.
I was going to do it, if you were honest.
Honesty is in right now.
Giving it to you straight.
So be honest with me.
You want to kiss me, don't you?
Yes.
Did you brush your teeth?
I brushed them really clean.
I brushed them three times today.
I'm impressed,
but there'll be lots of people there.
Hey, aim it right.
You should open your mouth wider.
How would I do that?
My mouth is pretty big as it is. Ah.
There you go!
Who am I?
Honey!
Louder.
My honey!
Oh, good job.
Others might say we're being silly,
but I'd say we're being romantic.
Romantic is different from silly, okay?
I know.
How do you spell it?
I lived in the States since I was young.
That woman at home wouldn't know that.
I'm going.
Just like that?
This looks perfectly fine.
That's enough. Stop.
Sedal!
Oh, it's been a while.
You live here?
Was that the director's car?
Yes.
How long have you been out here? So sneaky!
How much did you see?
See what?
If you didn't see anything, that's fine.
Did the director drive you home?
Of course.
Your director must be a very nice person.
Yes, very nice.
He gave me $100,000 when you gave me $3!
What?
Wait for me, Sedal!
Dad!
Hey! You're wrinkling my suit.
They're just happy to see their dad.
Dad, you smell really nice.
I don't.
It's really nice. It's fantastic.
You do! Are you wearing perfume?
Where did you get such keen sense of smell?
Of course I smell nice.
The director wears expensive perfume.
You smell like a woman.
The director uses women's perfume?
Of course.
Oh, he has lots of different kinds of perfume.
The director likes a wide variety of stuff.
Pack me some rice rolls tomorrow.
Why?
I'm going to an amusement park.
With her?
What?
The woman who calls you "honey."
What is he talking about?
You shouldn't say things like that!
Why an amusement park?
The director wants to go because he's lived in the States all his life.
So he wants to experience Korean amusement parks.
He lived in the States for a long time?
Yes.
Be nice to the director.
It must get lonely.
I'll make really good rice rolls.
What do I have?
I should go grocery shopping.
Mom.
Why aren't you in bed?
I can't fall asleep.
A woman called dad "honey."
It was a spam message.
Don't worry about it and go to bed.
Mom, you don't know anything.
They won't bite.
They must know we're here.
Should we just go home?
Give it more time. We just got here.
Right, since you packed so much stuff, we should stay here for days.
Not for days.
Oh, it's cold.
You're cold?
Yes, it must be because of the water.
I think it's nice and cool.
To catch a fish...
I have coffee in the truck.
Go get some.
I have to keep my eye on that.
They won't bite yet.
I think I have a fever.
You have a fever?
Yes, I'm shivering.
Catching fish isn't very important.
Let's go.
Oh! Oh! What are you doing? Sangnam!
Oh, my.
Did you bring this from home?
Yes. I brought a CD player, too.
You came prepared.
You brought everything but the kitchen sink.
Didn't your mom say anything?
Oh, you snuck out.
Like the movies.
It's research.
Research on night fishing.
How do you want to do it?
It's a bit creepy here.
I'm a bit scared.
You can lean on me.
What?
When you go night fishing, it's scary,
so you tend to lean on each other.
Says who?
Someone. A dating expert.
Are you warm now?
Yes.
Can you stay here?
I'll check on the rod.
Stay. I'm scared.
But you told me to lean on you.
Fishing isn't important.
Here and now.
We are what's important.
Oh!
Us? Here and now?
I don't go night fishing with just anyone.
This is my first time.
Ha! All women say it's their first time.
This is my first time night fishing.
Earlier,
if I remember correctly,
you said you wanted to make fish stew
and have a drink.
But let's switch the order.
Look at me.
Stop that and just look.
Don't change your mind later.
I won't.
Don't call the police.
Never.
Your eyes are very pretty.
They look like puppy eyes.
Puppies have my eyes.
Whatever.
It's biting!
You didn't come here for that, did you?
There's a motel over there.
We're leaving in a while.
Let's finish what we started.
Did you order noodles?
No, we didn't!
Unbelievable!
Why would you bring that?
Someone ordered it for sure.
Give it to us. We'll eat it.
You sure?
Here.
It looks good.
Let's eat.
You're not eating?
I don't feel like it.
Having hot noodles at a quiet place is making me miss one thing.
What do you miss?
Guess what it is.
I wish someone could guess what it is.
Sir! What's wrong with you?
- Do you need...
- No, we don't!
You're really sharp.
I was just thinking of this.
Thank you.
I never knew fishing would be this crazy.
I thought we'd be left alone.
You seem very desperate.
Normally, it's the men.
Sir!
Sunjeong, thanks.
When you're finished, just leave them.
No, I'll clean up.
Why don't you eat with us?
I ate earlier with Miho.
She doesn't look so good.
I feel so bad for her.
Everyone has a sad story.
This is all because of her.
She borrowed so much money
that Sunjeong had to break up with
the man she loved and married an older man.
And she divorced him soon after.
Whenever I see her, I feel guilty.
And heartbroken.
She ruined many lives.
I was bankrupt, her family went bankrupt.
And she ruined her little sister's life.
I guess it's fate.
I wish we could find someone nice for her.
Oh, how old is she?
Thirty-eight.
She's at her prime, but look at her.
I'll ask around.
The problem is that she hasn't gotten over him.
He's probably married by now.
Probably.
When she meets someone, she'll get over him.
I should start asking around tomorrow.
I'm home.
Who is it?
It's me, mother.
Don't be alarmed.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to see my girls.
But what if you wake them up?
They already woke up several times.
What's going on?
It's Minjung.
He surprised me trying to see the girls.
That's enough. He just misses them.
Go to bed.
Yes, father.
I'm sorry, mother.
Good night.
It's like he wants me to hate him more.
You're still up?
I don't go to sleep early.
That's tacky.
Did you sign Aeji up for taekwondo?
No, I signed her up for ballet.
Why?
Mom said a girl shouldn't learn taekwondo.
She said ballet would be better.
I took ballet lessons when I was little.
But Aeji wants to learn taekwondo.
I already enrolled her.
It's nice and cheap.
I didn't go to an expensive one.
Subak,
Aeji's our daughter.
You should talk to me, not your mother.
What's wrong with talking to my mom?
She's raising our girls?
Then why don't you take care of everything?
Why did you have to deliver the package then?
You have no common sense!
Mom got embarrassed and yelled at me!
Sedal drove his mom in a foreign car,
but you had to deliver a package.
Don't you feel anything?
What am I supposed to feel?
What?
Sunjeong.
What do you want from me?
I told you!
I never loved you!
Sunjeong, why are you acting like this?
Don't do this.
This isn't like you.
This is so sudden!
I just want to break up with you!
Let me go. I told you I hate you.
Just tell me the reason.
I'll change.
I'll change everything you don't like.
I'm tired of you.
I hate you.
Is it because of him?
It can't be him.
He can't make you happy.
Why not? He's rich.
Can you make me happy?
Do you have money?
Why? We're going to feed off love?
Dream on.
The 7 years with you have been exhausting.
All we do is go for walks when we're on dates.
I'm sick and tired of it.
I don't want a poor man.
Don't drag this on.
Let me go.
I can't break up with you like this.
I can't let you go to him.
How...
We've been in love for 7 years.
How could you throw that all away?
Can you live without me?
Can you forget me?
I can't forget you.
Do it.
I'm choosing money, so get over me.
Don't ever call me again.
Ever.
Sunjeong! Sunjeong!
Sunjeong!
Who's there?
What are you doing?
Mother.
You were the cat?
I can't believe you did that.
Was it fun to trick me?
You saw Sedal at my get-together, right?
Didn't you feel anything about it?
I guess you'd never know.
What's going on?
He was making the cat noise.
Why would he do that?
Ask him yourself.
You're eating that?
You should eat rice.
There's no rice.
How can there be no rice?
Anyone of us could get hungry.
Make more rice from now on.
Don't give him stress about food.
Being stressed about food is the worst.
It's not because I want him to starve.
I just didn't like him lying to me.
He was being sneaky and lying to me.
I can't seem to like him.
Why can't you just let it slide?
This isn't life or death.
He could look for food if he's hungry.
He's just being careful.
But he's doing whatever he wants.
He steals, fights, lies and makes cat noises.
Don't be like that.
You said it yourself.
That it's like he wants you to hate him.
You're intentionally hating him.
I shouldn't have let them move in with us.
You're the one who begged me to let them.
He's not friendly like other son in laws.
You said you like him because he's quiet.
Other son in laws treat their mother in laws like their own mothers.
But my son in laws are not like that.
Son in laws aren't your real sons.
You said it yourself.
A daughter in law isn't your daughter.
I feel so lonely, so lonely.
How come you never side with me?
Put yourself in my shoes.
Eat, eat. Take your time.
- Eat.
- Okay.
Don't worry about other people.
Eat whatever you want to eat.
Turn the lights on.
And don't make any cat noises.
I won't.
And try to be friendly to my wife.
Joke around with her sometimes.
Do you understand what I mean?
Think of her as your own mother.
She likes that kind of stuff.
Eat. It'll get soggy.
What did you save my name as in your phone?
It's a secret.
What did you save my name as?
I'm not tell you, either.
It's obvious.
Husband?
No way.
My love Sangnam?
Eww.
If you show me yours, I'll tell you.
Call me.
You,
are,
my?
I got it!
What is it?
Isn't it the movie title?
This was a movie?
You are my destiny.
Right?
No?
Dream on.
Then what is it?
Show me.
- It's my sister.
- Answer it.
What is it?
I'm doing research.
Right now?
Man...
Hello?
I'm the manager,
and the fish are biting.
I called because that woman is angry.
I think she has an ulterior motive.
You should hurry up and do whatever it is.
You're a really dense guy.
Don't make her anxious. Just do it.
She's really asking for it.
I'm not asking for it!
I can't believe you!
Let's take care of that later and deal with the fish first.
Grab it, hurry.
Why are you grabbing me?
Huh?
Help! Help!
Help!
Why are you swimming here?
It's not deep. Get out of there.
Hurry up and get out.
Get out!
It's only knee deep.
Oh, I'm sleepy.
You can sleep when your father goes to work.
We have to do what he says.
Mom, this milk is expired.
Throw it out.
A few days is okay.
Leave it. Minjung or uncle can drink it.
Did you sleep well, mother?
I didn't because of a cat.
Oh, mother,
I'm sorry. I won't do that again.
Oh, why are you massaging my shoulders?
I'll try to be more like your own son.
Oh, that hurts.
Stop that.
My mom doesn't like stuff like that.
It's too early for that!
I'm going to work.
Oh, I don't believe you.
Why couldn't you go along with that?
You said you wanted him to act like your son.
Nothing will make you happy.
Only I can deal with your temper.
He's not good at being friendly.
Ugh!
His grip is too strong!
We didn't have any fish stew.
And we didn't kiss.
Let's save it for a special occasion.
Ouch!
Stop drooling and go over there.
I'll give you some later.
Stay far away from me.
How mean.
You're only packing dad's lunch.
Your son is starving here.
You don't even know who that's for!
It's for your dad and the director.
It might be someone else.
Stop that.
How dare you!
Stop drooling over food.
You should be more picky, like other kids.
Even if I gave you dog food, you'd eat it.
Yours is here.
Eat this.
But it isn't pretty!
How can you give this to your son?
Oh, but the ends are more delicious!
Oh...
Okay, okay.
Don't make him cry! It's bad luck.
Why is he crying so early in the morning?
Mom won't give me rice rolls.
Give them some. Don't starve them.
They can eat later.
I hope the director likes them.
You don't look like you're going to work.
You look like you're going to goof off.
My nickname is Goof-off.
Goof-off Heo Sedal. Bye.
You look cool, honey.
Oh, you love it when I go to work.
I do! Work hard for the director, okay?
I hope the rice rolls are good.
I hope the director likes them.
I'll see you later.
Have a good day.
Okay.
Oh, I'm dizzy.
It's me.
How are you?
Can you go out for fish stew?
I made reservations.
I would love to but I'm coughing.
Oh, no.
I can't believe you caught a cold.
You didn't catch a cold?
I never do.
I'm sorry.
Let's meet another time.
I don't want to give this to you.
Okay, then.
Take care of yourself.
I know this sounds lame,
but who cares?
We're apart but our hearts are together.
Bye.
Okay.
You must like this kind of food.
I had made reservations here for today.
And I felt like having fish stew.
Well, are you the type who doesn't like to splurge on food?
- What?
- The restaurants we've been to.
You always eat stuff like this.
I'm not saying this is bad.
I actually love food like this.
Are you asking if I'm stingy comparatively to what I earn?
No, I'm not really asking that.
Actually,
I spend a lot of money on food and clothes.
I make money to spend it.
The same goes for women.
I do whatever the woman asks.
You said okay when I asked you to this restaurant.
Actually, I would've gone to any restaurant.
When I went to China, if you had asked me for a handbag, I would've bought you one.
So don't try to test me.
You should be honest with me.
Okay. I will.
Oh, my!
He said he'll do anything for you?
Yes.
I don't have to explain anything to him.
I didn't say anything but he knew.
He was fighting the urges to do things for me and was wondering about me.
He told me to ask for anything.
I thought he might be stingy.
He might be testing me.
Testing you?
To see if I'm after his money.
But that's for the really rich people.
But why did you come home so early?
He has to go to work.
Right after lunch.
But it's Sunday.
He's busy. He's making money.
Right.
The man makes the money and the woman spends the money.
That's the ideal couple.
Be prepared for him to propose.
Of course.
Excuse me...
Oh?
You came!
I thought I'd drop by.
You can't just drop by.
You must work out.
I don't know how to do this.
I've never worked out before.
I'll teach you. First of all.
Oh, my! Agh!
You've seen MMA on TV, right?
This is the position.
Isn't it a bit too steamy?
This can't be.
Is this how it's done?
That's for those who are good.
It won't be that hard in the beginning.
We'll start with the basics.
I think it might be fun.
Hello.
If you need a parcel service, please call us.
I told you we have someone else.
You're starting to bother me.
I'm sorry.
But if you change your mind, do call us.
We'll give you a good deal.
Have a nice day.
I'll take this out.
Just leave it.
It's okay. I'm on my way out anyway.
Huh?
Mom, did you see the yogurt?
I was going to use it for a facial.
Uncle, did you eat it?
What?
I put yogurt and fruit in the fridge for a facial.
I didn't see it.
Who else would eat that?
You should've asked.
I can't believe you.
I said I didn't eat it.
Why are you all standing here?
It's nothing, mom.
Subak was in the Miss Korea pageant!
But now she can't even go get facials.
So how could you eat the yogurt that she was going to use for a facial?
You eat too much.
It's because you have nothing better to do.
What?
Why didn't he ask if he could eat it?
He took the herbal tea I made for my husband
and ate the snacks I bought for Daebak.
Everything just disappears.
Are you upset about him eating?
It's his brother who's feeding him.
It's not you!
She didn't say that.
Grandmother, why are you yelling?
What?
Wow, you've teamed up against me!
Uncle, you shouldn't have done that.
But it wasn't me!
How can you yell at him over yogurt?
My son's spending money my other son made, so what's your problem?
How dare you yell at my son?
My son has to work really hard to support you two, so shut up!
If he makes a mistake, I can scold him.
I have the right to, don't you think?
I raised him like my own child.
I even nursed him.
You didn't raise him!
He never received proper care because of your children!
Oh, I feel sorry for my hard working son.
You spend money on food to poop and to put on your faces.
You leeched off Minjung, and now you're leeching off my precious son!
Grandmother, what's wrong with you?
I'm not leeching off dad.
How dare you yell at her?
She's my mom.
Your mom yelled at my mom first!
What? Your mom?
Uncle, calm down.
Subak, that's enough.
Oh, I don't believe this.
Just look at what's going on.
Just tell me.
Is your daughter's face more important than my son's stomach?
What's going on?
You don't need to know.
When did you come home?
But I didn't eat it. Man.
I put yogurt in the fridge to use for a facial, but uncle ate it!
But I ate that.
And now my stomach hurts.
What?
Minjung, you ate it?
I'll talk to you later.
Why you little! Subak! Come out!
Grandmother.
I'm sorry.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo...
How was it?
The first day i s hard, right?
Thanks.
But is this really free?
I was going to charge you a lot of money,
but I can't.
You're my teacher's daughter.
How do you feel?
I feel amazing.
You might feel aches and pain tonight.
And tomorrow, you might get muscle pain.
Minjung!
Hobak.
Isn't it hard living there?
It's a big family.
I expected it.
Especially my mom. You know how she's harsh with words.
I can imagine how it must be for you.
She's even hard on me.
But don't let it bother you.
Or it'll become too much to handle.
I can't seem to be able to do it, though.
I didn't know when I was living there,
but now that I am...
I'm sure.
Have you had lunch?
No, I have a stomachache.
Why?
I think it was something I ate.
You should be more careful.
Anyway,
Hobak.
Yes?
There's something I want to ask.
Does Subak have some kind of secret?
Excuse me?
What do you mean...
I mean,
both you and Sedal seem
to know something I don't.
I think you should get out more.
Living with mom and dad isn't easy.
I used to love visiting mom,
but now, I feel really uncomfortable.
How's your cold?
I can't even be sick at home.
Would you like to get coffee?
That's Hobak.
And Minjung's there, too.
Hobak!
What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
I thought you had work.
Yes. I ran into her. Sit.
You did?
But why are you talking to her at a cafe?
We weren't really talking.
We just ran into each other in the street so I asked him to have some coffee.
What were you talking about?
I'm sure you didn't sit here in silence.
We just talked about silly stuff.
How funny.
Why would my husband and my sister meet at a cafe and drink coffee?
Why can't she have coffee with Minjung?
We're all family.
Family?
He became family when he married you.
I just asked her about how she's doing because I haven't seen her in a while.
I'm leaving. You guys talk.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
Subak, coffee?
Anything's fine.
What did you talk about?
We didn't talk about much.
Watch your mouth.
Keep it shut until you die.
I know.
I won't talk even after I'm dead.
How are you doing?
Is everything okay?
Why did you stop visiting mom?
Is it because you bought an apartment and your husband's doing well now?
Like mom said, you never did anything for her so shouldn't you start now?
How could you stop visiting just like that?
I know.
I'm rude.
That's why my life turned out like this.
Are you kidding me?
Subak, I'm too busy with my life to kid anyone.
And I'm not visiting mom because I think we need some time apart.
I'd like you to stay out of this.
Stay out?
I'm the eldest daughter.
I need to be on top of what's going on.
It's between me and mom.
You wouldn't know what it is because you were always her favorite.
You're funny.
Mom didn't like you because you were dumb,
but you always blame me.
Do you know why mom hated you?
Grandmother was mean to her because of you.
She hated her because you were a daughter.
Was that my fault?
How could you just repeat what mom said?
I never asked to be born.
You have children, so how can you say that?
This is why mom doesn't like you.
Subak, that's enough.
Hobak, let's stop this.
I thought we could have a nice chat.
I'm leaving.
Gwangbak, bye.
Your hairband!
Are you doing your homework?
You have to finish your homework.
Or there's no dinner!
- Okay.
- Stepmom!
You want to get off here?
People might see us.
You don't want me to get caught, right?
Are you scared?
I'm not.
I just don't want it to get messy.
I can't handle her crying and going crazy.
And for your sake, baby, I can't get caught.
Go.
Daebak,
isn't that your brother in law?
Subtitles by KBS World
I'm left breathless from running around all day, in search of love, in search of life
Beneath the skies of Seoul I get closer to my dreams
Both love and friendship coexist under the sky
You must get back at her, okay?
- You!
- One more word!
Mom, forgive me. I'm sorry.
I'm going to pretend I never had you.
My father would pass out if he found out.
I'm so happy I'm going nuts.
You must have come to ask for money,
but as you can see, I don't have any.
Is that all you can say?
Why did you come?
Because you're his mom!