Subtitles by KBS World
The deeds to the house.
The deeds, the deeds!
Where are the deeds to the house?
Bong! Oh, Bong! Oh...
Oh, why aren't they here? Huh?
Why aren't the deeds here?
Where were you?
We're a mess here.
Why?
The deeds to the house are gone.
Subak!
Subak! Hey! You!
Uncle, uncle, let me go.
He'll kill me. Father will kill me!
This isn't right!
- Let go!
- Come here.
- Hey!
- Let go!
- Come here!
Come here! Bong! Come!
Come here!
Let go! Let me go!
Bong! Anggeum! Ugh.
She tried to run. It was Subak!
No! I know nothing! I know nothing!
You! It was you!
You sent me to the sauna that time.
You stole it then, didn't you?
Where is it?
Where are the deeds?
What do we do? What do we do?
She stole from you!
Where are the deeds?
Father, father, hold on.
I'll get them back.
It must be a mistake.
This is wrong.
He said he'll double it for me.
He said it'll be just $100,000.
It's not the whole house.
I'll go and get them back.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Father, forgive me.
I'll go and get it right now.
Bong!
Oh, Bong!
My money!
What about my money?
Just wait, I'll get it all back, mom.
You and I should just die!
Ugh! Anggeum! Anggeum!
Oh, this is crazy.
Who is it?
Who did you give it to?
Oh, there you are!
You're in on this together!
- Right!
- Let's beat her up!
Don't do this!
We're victims, too! We are!
Stop it!
Don't you dare touch her!
We look like a family.
We do.
Mom, wake me up early tomorrow.
Get everything ready before you go to bed.
And pick out your clothes, too.
Miho, are you going somewhere?
I'm going to camp.
Mom, I'm going to the bathroom.
She has no siblings,
so I send her to every camp there is.
Good. She is very vibrant and was raised well.
You did a great job raising her.
That's not so. She helped me out a lot.
I made it because of her.
Minjung, thank you.
For what?
For taking your time to be here.
Miho looks very happy.
It's nothing compared to what you've done for me.
Why didn't you get married again?
I'm sure lots of men hit on you.
I'm not that popular.
I know.
How can I, when I have a kid?
But it's not easy for a young woman to be a single mother.
Tell him. He should know Miho's his.
Minjung.
Yeah?
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Minjung, don't go into shock...
I wanted to tell you, but I couldn't.
Why are you hesitating? Just tell me.
Minjung, actually...
Hold on.
Hello?
Minjung.
Where are you?
Can you come here?
Things are crazy here.
What happened?
Your father in law might die!
What?
Okay.
Sunjeong, I have to go to my in law's.
Why? What's wrong?
It must be urgent.
I have to go. I'm sorry.
It's okay. Go.
Quiet down! Quiet!
He was convicted 7 times!
He stole over ten million dollars!
They don't know if they can catch him.
What do I do?
Even if he's caught,
we won't get our money back!
I can't believe I fell for this!
My money! Where's my money!
Please catch that bastard!
Father! Father!
Honey.
Where's Subak?
Mom!
You!
Father.
I'm going to kill you.
Don't stop him!
Don't stop Bong!
She's not his daughter! She's not!
I knew she'd ruin this family someday!
Let Bong do what he wants!
You!
Father, father.
How could you do this?
You know what this house means to us!
You know that!
With your father's paycheck,
I saved every penny I could and even worked
as a street vendor and bought this house.
How could you lose it like this?
How could you do such a thing?
How could you?
What do we do?
We're going to be homeless now.
Oh, where do we go?
Where will everyone go?
What were you doing?
You didn't know she was stealing the deed?
This is all your fault!
You let your daughter run wild!
Like mother, like daughter!
Yes.
Like mother, like daughter.
You and I should die.
- Mom. Mom.
- Die!
Subak, hurry up and go upstairs.
You and I should die!
Let's go and die!
Mother!
- Mother!
- Mom!
- Carry her on your back!
- Me?
Let me.
Hurry.
- Mom.
- Mother!
Mother.
- Oh, Bong!
- Bong!
Oh, Bong.
It's an emergency!
- Here.
- Here, here.
- Please take care of her.
- This way.
Bong!
Bong.
Bong, Bong, take this. Take this.
Here.
Mom, we're in big trouble.
Don't tell your mom just yet.
Okay.
Oh, what am I supposed to do now?
My mind is blank.
Hobak, is there anything we can do?
Is there anything, Minjung?
Oh, so there isn't.
What will we do?
What if they all want to move in with us?
This is nuts.
- Mom.
- Mother.
- Where am I?
- At the hospital.
You passed out, so Minjung carried you.
Let's go.
But you need this fluid.
Mother, you should stay for this.
My insides are burning up,
so how can I just lie down here?
- Get ready for my funeral.
- You can't!
- Mom!
- Mother.
My wife.
I think I married well.
You do?
My mom.
I'd resented her all my life,
but you helped me let it all go.
And because you're good to her,
I'm very happy.
I'm glad you're happy.
But I can't bring myself to call her "mom" yet.
You will, in time.
I hope this happiness lasts a long time.
I've never been this happy before.
Mother, it's me.
Will you please come over?
If you're good to your wife,
your wife will be good to your family.
Jangbi, what do women like?
Designer handbags.
Besides that.
- Money.
- Jangbi!
I'm serious.
They pretend to be happy about flowers.
I'll be back.
How much is it?
It's the best I can do.
Hah!
I must look like a fool to you!
Do I look like a beggar?
I'm your husband's mother.
Your mother in law.
You don't get it?
You think I came all the way here to get a measly $5,000?
You think I'm that easy?
You think you can get away with $5,000?
When I asked you for $50,000?
You think I'm a joke?
You call me mother, mother,
but you have no respect for me.
It's not like that, mother.
I don't understand why you're doing this.
Why can't you understand?
You must be really stupid.
This couldn't be any simpler.
How did you teach your students?
You're a college graduate!
How can you be so dumb?
Mother, you can say anything you want,
but if you want Sangnam and me to be happy,
I don't get why you would do this to me.
I guess you don't want this.
When will you give me the rest?
I can't give you anymore.
What?
Even if I had it, I wouldn't give it to you.
This is the last time.
What?
Sangnam and I promised not to give gifts.
But I gave you $5,000 behind his back.
And I gave you another $5,000.
That's $10,000.
For me, that's a lot of money.
I can't give you anymore.
You're pretty bold.
Which tea house did you work at?
So this is how you want to handle this?
If I put my mind to it...
Please stop.
You can't threaten me.
I'm very disappointed in you.
Sangnam was happy to get you back,
so how can you do this to him?
I'm begging you.
Please think of Sangnam.
I want to respect you as my husband's mother,
but to be honest, I can't do it.
If you keep this up, I'm going to tell
father or aunt and top you from coming here.
What?
This is my son's house!
You don't deserve to be a mother.
Please leave.
I don't deserve to be a mom?
No. You don't.
Please leave.
I never want to see you again.
And I won't call you mother.
Stop it!
Oh, my, Sangnam!
I know I'm not good enough,
but how could she treat me like this?
My heart is pounding and I can't talk.
How can this be?
I won't come here again.
I only wanted to see my daughter in law.
- Mother, that's not true!
- Stop it.
Go upstairs.
- Sangnam, it wasn't...
- Go!
Sangnam, Sangnam.
Sangnam, I'm leaving.
I'm okay.
I guess I deserved that.
I just want you to be happy.
I'll call you.
- Sangnam.
Not another word.
It wasn't like that.
I'm disappointed in you.
Just listen to me.
There's no need. I heard everything.
Sangnam.
I was there. Don't make any excuses.
I thought you'd be different.
I thought you'd understand how my mom hurt me.
And we just started to make up.
Had I known you were like this,
I wouldn't have told you about my mom.
She brought me into this world.
You can't mistreat her like that.
If you couldn't respect her as my mother,
at least you could be polite.
Don't you owe me that?
Denying my birth mother is denying me.
Hobak.
Now?
What happened?
What?
Gwangbak.
What do we do, Hobak?
Mom.
What do we do?
What should we do about this?
Mom.
I'm sure Subak didn't want this.
She was trying to make money.
Ugh...
Don't even bring up Subak.
If it weren't for the others, she'd be dead.
How come she didn't know he was a fraud?
How could she steal the deeds to the house?
She's out of her mind!
She's 38 years old, for goodness sake!
Oh, I can't blame anyone.
I'm the one who raised her.
Mom, mom.
The number you dialed is not in service.
Subak.
I wish I was dead.
What do we do? What do I do?
Hobak, don't tell my mom.
Okay.
I got the pork.
Then make the kimchi stew.
Me?
Should I call Minjung?
No, it's okay.
I'll do it this time.
This is nuts.
I'll make it perfect.
Jungji, yes.
Have some more.
Here, kimchi stew.
Sedal made this. He's become a pretty good cook these days.
There's pork in it. It looks good.
Father, have some.
Hurry up. Father, eat.
Mom, here.
Why should I bother eating?
We have nowhere to go.
But we're all fine and that's a good thing.
What if someone got hurt or sick?
This is better than that.
You can buy another house.
Another house?
But this house is like my life.
Buying a house isn't easy.
It look us our whole lives to buy this house.
So don't just blurt out whatever you think.
This house is like my life.
It can't be as important as your life.
Your life is far more precious.
What Hobak is saying is since we're all...
Be quiet.
You're both useless.
You don't care because you're fine.
Daughters are useless.
Go.
Why did you come here to begin with?
Mom, calm down.
I don't need you either!
You saw what happened to us!
Forget about your dream and study again!
Please.
Please be quiet.
My mind is going wild, so be quiet.
Mother, I'm sorry.
Why should you be?
I did a bad job raising my children.
It's all my fault.
Eat.
Hobak, do you have any money?
No?
Don't they have to move?
They have to hand the house over.
Yes.
Should I talk to my father in law?
To see if he can give us a loan?
Don't.
You shouldn't say things like that.
People who ask for loans are the worst.
But our parents are...
Still, you can't.
He won't lend you money, even if you asked.
And you just got married.
I'd be upset if I were him since he doesn't even like you.
Don't tell anyone about what happened.
They'll think less of us.
What do we do about the house?
We'll figure something out.
You have some money, don't you?
Yes.
I shouldn't have given that $10,000.
Who?
Nobody.
I gave  mom some, and that's gone, too.
Who knew this would happen?
I'll try my best.
But you just bought an apartment.
I'll talk to my boss.
Oh, I shouldn't have bought that apartment.
Let's start searching tomorrow.
Okay.
I shouldn't have quit school.
If I had my job, it wouldn't be this bad.
Let's not dwell on the past.
What are you doing?
I was getting kimchi.
For instant noodles?
Yes.
You didn't have dinner?
I did, but I'm hungry.
Where's your wife?
Why are you making it?
She's not here.
And she didn't tell you?
She's upset at me.
What?
What's the use of sitting here all night?
She's right.
You should go home.
Go.
Oh...
I'm sorry I can't help.
You being here was enough for me.
I'll take Jungji with me.
How will you take care of him?
Minjung, I'll take care of him.
She and I will take care of him.
There are chores, and mother's sick,
so I'll take him for a few days.
Father.
Where were you?
I...
Were you at your parents house?
No, I wasn't.
You told me not to go there.
I had some things to take care...
Things?
How can you just go out without a word?
I'm sorry.
This will never happen again.
You keep doing the same thing over and over.
I feel nervous all day because of you.
I worry about how you'll piss me off again.
And how I'm supposed to deal with it.
It's like I'm at war with you.
Why do I have to go through this?
Especially after that letter you wrote?
You know how hard your husband works?
I do.
Then how could you do this?
He works from 6 am to 6 pm every day.
Even if he eats 3 meals a day,
he still gets hungry at night.
How could you let him eat instant noodles?
I'm sorry.
And you're giving him the silent treatment?
Why are you mad at him?
Don't you know  how stressful it is for a man
if his wife is home, all mad at him?
He wasn't himself today at work, and this was why.
What if there was an accident?
Working with heavy equipment is dangerous!
You're unbelievable!
Is there money in there?
It's empty.
I'm going to talk to my boss.
You were least loved growing up,
but now, you're their greatest hope.
You're acting like their firstborn.
Do your parents know this?
I'm not looking for appreciation.
I'm doing this because it's my duty.
Gwangbak's going to help. too.
I can't believe what Subak did.
I didn't want to stop your father before.
- What's going on?
- Excuse me?
Your parents called you over.
Yeongdal called, but she hung up on me.
We had dinner together.
Is Yeongdal doing okay?
Yes, she looked fine.
She didn't even say hi to me.
She's not being pushed around?
They are treating her like a princess.
She doesn't do a thing.
Her mother in law is spoon feeding her.
She should.
They all should treat her like a princess.
But the good days are over.
- What?
- Huh?
It's nothing.
This is nutty, nutty, nuts.
Nutty, nutty...
Don't wait for me.
I'm pulling an all niter.
Subak, wait.
Meeting you again made me so happy.
This is too worn, so I can't give you much.
And this is a knock off.
A knock off?
It's an imitation.
Mom, here.
I sold my handbag.
I wish I had more things to sell,
but that was the only one I had.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I did a horrible thing.
Mom, try some of this.
I'll make rice for dinner later.
I don't want anything.
You're the only one who can save us now,
so you have to study again, judge.
Subak,
I poured water in, so give it 3 minutes.
I can't eat anymore.
You think you deserve to eat?
You still get hungry?
I don't want to see you, so get out!
Your mom and dad are dying now,
and you're sitting here eating?
You're shameless, aren't you?
- How dare you sit here?
- Grandmother.
If you weren't here, we'd be trouble free!
Everything happened because of you! Get out!
Go somewhere and die or something!
I can't believe her!
What is it, Hobak?
Father, we found a house.
Can you and mom come and have a look?
You did?
Gwangbak and I found one.
It's not that nice, but come anyway.
Okay. I will.
Father.
Is it here?
Yes. Go in.
You can move in right away.
Have a look.
Okay.
It's not the best...
We won't be able to find anything nicer.
They don't have anything available.
If you have money, you could get one.
We'll put new wallpaper up tonight.
I'm sorry, father.
Nothing else was available right away,
and we didn't have that much money.
Thank you.
We're sorry we couldn't find a better house.
Mom, we're sorry.
It's okay.
I was worried about where to live,
but thanks to you two, I'm relieved.
Thank you, really.
Hobak.
Yes, Minjung.
What happened?
We found a place and signed the lease.
They're moving in tomorrow.
Good.
I'm sorry. I wish I could help.
It's okay. Thanks for asking.
But you don't need to do anymore.
I'm really sorry.
I think uncle called because he didn't know what to do.
Goodbye, Minjung.
If you're done with that, make barely tea.
Did you hear me?
Huh? Oh, you said something?
It's okay. I'll do it.
Let's talk.
I heard about last night.
I don't think your father in law slept well.
I'm sorry.
You're smart, so I thought you'd be wise.
I heard you went out without telling anyone.
That's bad manners.
You should say where you're going.
And you made Sangnam eat instant noodles.
His father really hates that.
I'm sorry.
And you're not speaking to each other?
It's just you two here.
So when you fight, you must make up quickly.
Don't let me or your father in law find out.
That's why living with your in laws is hard.
If you couldn't do it, you shouldn't have moved in.
And you shouldn't make mistakes.
I won't.
How can you be fighting already?
Sangnam didn't come home last night, right?
He had to work.
Sangnam has always slept at home.
I wanted to make things easier for you,
so I scolded Daese and Sangnam,
but I don't think I should've done that.
Sangnam is a very considerate person.
He's never done this before.
I don't know what you did,
but if it's your fault, apologize to him.
Don't make things awkward for everyone.
I will.
And don't cry so often.
When someone has given you advice,
you should take it. Why would you cry?
You're making me look bad here.
Did I say anything wrong?
No, I'm sorry.
This is our last meal here.
Don't cry, mother.
Things happen.
Let's eat.
I remember when we first moved here.
I was so happy we were able to buy a house.
We sent rice cakes to every neighbor.
When was that?
I was in 8th grade.
Subak was in 9th grade.
Haebak and Daebak weren't even born.
I was in 7th grade.
Things went so well after we moved here.
I had Haebak and Daebak.
It was a very lucky house for us.
We didn't even have room before then.
Remember, Hobak?
There were only two rooms,
so we all share one room with grandmother.
I slept next to Bong and Anggeum.
Right.
I was so happy when we moved here.
And mom and I had our own room.
You did? That's so interesting.
Gwangbak and I became friends in middle school,
and visiting this house was so much fun.
There were so many people,
and everyone went wild over food.
Grandmother saying "The Korean War was nothing compared to this!
and Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo" was so funny.
Father, we'll be fine in the new house.
My father's in heaven right now.
Right.
The new house will be small.
Why don't you go back to your mother?
I won't.
She won't.
We want to stay together, Bong.
Cold! Hey, stop!
Come here! How dare you!
Hey, be careful, be careful.
I envy you.
Yeongdal, go home if you don't want to help.
Don't yell at my wife!
This is nuts.
Yeongdal, bring me that broom.
Don't. Even I don't have her do anything.
Heo Yeongdal.
Okay.
Here.
Hobak, what's taking you so long?
Hurry up and finish that!
Loser, she's my wife.
She's my niece.
I need help.
- Okay!
- Man...
She was talking to me, not you.
- Not true, Goof-off.
- Right.
Good job! Ask me, not him, if you need anything.
This is nutty, nutty, nuts!
You said you'd respect me!
When?
Whoa! I can't believe you!
When you asked for my permission!
I don't remember.
Loser! You!
Why you little! Come here! Come here!
Why are you hitting me?
Let me go!
Hey! Stop!
Just pack what we need.
We'll send the rest to storage.
Good job, Bong.
You too.
Did you say goodbye to every corner?
I don't think I can say goodbye.
My eyes keep tearing up.
We fixed every corner of this house.
When we first moved here,
it needed a lot of fixing up.
The front door, every windowsill,
the floors...
We oiled them and painted them.
We polished them and scrubbed them.
It was our house, so it didn't matter.
We just couldn't believe this was ours.
We thought it was a dream come true.
Remember when we hung the doorplate up?
Hanging that plate up with your name on it,
I thought the hard days were finally over.
I couldn't believe it.
We had finally bought a house.
Remember how hard we cried that night?
Will I be able to hang this up again?
The kids say we can start again,
but I'm over 60, so how can I?
I won't ever have my own house again.
I'm too old to get a job.
I wouldn't even be hired as a housekeeper!
If we were young, we'd have time,
but we're nearly at the end of our time.
And that breaks my heart.
I wish this happened when I was younger.
Now that my house is gone,
there's no joy left in the world.
My knees are giving in.
I don't think I can stand up again.
- Hurry up.
- Okay.
This is nuts.
Keep going, a little more.
Are we there yet?
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
I should put this here.
Hold on.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Be careful.
Oh, give it to me.
Let it go.
Oh, hold on.
I'll see you again, Salla.
Goodbye, Daese.
- I'll call you.
- And text me, too.
I'm fine.
I think we're settled in, Bong.
We're a big family, so that didn't take very long.
Why don't you spray some water here?
Good job, everyone.
Mother, good job.
Let's try to do our best here.
Here.
Let's put our hearts together.
We can do it!
We can do it! We can do it! We can do it!
Father,
my stomach's been growling like crazy!
You must be hungry.
Mother, are you hungry?
I've been starving to death!
Should we order something?
Yes, let's order some Chinese.
- What should we order?
- Noodles!
- I want...
- Fried rice.
- Noodles?
Black bean noodles?
Noodle soup?
Hey, how can you put your hearts together
when you can't even agree on the menu?
It's black bean noodles for everyone, then.
- Loser.
- Is this the Chinese place?
It's so small we can't even sit together.
It's suffocating.
I like sitting this close together.
Me too.
I can see everyone's faces better. It's nice.
More love comes from smaller homes.
Right, mother?
I can't believe my ears!
Don't steal my lines.
Maybe I should've made some rice.
You're supposed to eat this when you move.
It's actually not that bad.
It was fun.
How should we decide on the rooms?
- Rooms?
- It's me.
Huh?
Oh, Minjung, welcome.
- Oh, Jungji.
- Get that for him.
I'm sorry, baby.
Oh, yes, yes.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
How precious.
It's a bit shabby, huh?
But Hobak and Gwangbak did a good job.
I didn't even see you taking Jungji.
How did you make deliveries with a kid?
I'm not doing that anymore.
The how will you support yourself?
I'm running my old company again.
Huh?
The creditors didn't like the man they hired,
so they asked me back.
It's not mine yet, but after 3 years,
they'll give it back to me.
Oh, Minjung!
That's great news. The hard days are over.
Good for you.
Congratulations.
Minjung's the only lucky one.
Minjung, come by often.
I'm very sorry for leaving my children here.
Thanks. I'll take it.
I'll come and take them when I can.
You should get back together with Subak.
You should see her before you go.
I should go.
Right. It's cold. Go.
The living room is too cold.
Women, big room, men, small room.
Man...
Ugh...
Go.
Oh, boy.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo!
Mother, are you asleep?
No!
We can't do this to the newlyweds.
I can't sleep.
Yeongdal.
How can we sleep like this?
I know. What can we do?
Oh, boy.
Oh, my baby.
There's no room!
Go sleep with your uncle.
Uncle.
Come here, Daebak.
Sleep with me.
Father, this is wrong.
I agree with you.
Who suggested this?
Mother should sleep in the room.
Bong, I can't sleep with you out here.
We don't have to sleep together.
What do we do then?
Oh, cold.
Uncle's cold, too.
What?
Ouch! Who was that?
Oh, that Yeongdal!
What is it?
I can't believe this.
This is all your fault!
You caused misery for the whole family.
Because of you, the family's ruined!
First your ruin Minjung, and now your father!
I don't want to see your face!
Grandmother, stop.
It's hard for her, too.
No, it's not!
She does whatever she wants.
You drove Minjung into bankruptcy,
and now look at him!
After he divorced you, things got better.
Your mean personality caused all this!
Grandmother.
How dare you sleep here? Get out!
I hate everyone who breaks my son's heart.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo...
Subtitles by KBS World
I'll get the house back, no matter what.
I won't come back before that.
Father, please forgive me.
Where is she?
She won't come back without money.
You threw her out!
What?
How can you make my daughter live here?
Mrs. Park, calm down.
You stay out!
What's going on?
Apologize for what you did.
My son's on my side.
So don't get cheeky.