Subtitles by KBS World
Don! Wait for me!
What were you doing?
What were you doing with Loser?
I didn't do anything!
Then why did you run?
I ran because you chased after me.
That's nonsense!
Stop hitting me!
What if something happens to me?
What? What could happen?
Huh?
It's nothing, mom.
Don was here to ask me something.
Ask you what?
About stuff.
You're acting really suspicious.
What do you mean?
I think Loser's interested in you.
No way. He's not interested in me.
I think he is!
He's been following you around lately.
Don't fall for him!
I won't.
I'm not a leaf. I don't fall.
You're talking like Loser now.
He thinks you're easy, but he's wrong.
Let's go.
Where were you?
Are you having an affair?
Yes.
Don't be cheeky with me.
Go to bed.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Why won't you believe me?
If that's true, I'd be jumping up and down.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
The house seems empty.
Almost desolate.
Like there are a lot less people.
It's because Gwangbak's not here.
Where's Minjung?
He's busy.
You can relax, Bong.
Three of your daughters are married.
We still have a long way to go.
We have Haebak and Daebak.
Haebak's fine, but I'm worried about Daebak.
Haebak will get a scholarship,
and she'll become a judge for sure.
But what will become of Daebak...
He'll be able to take care of himself.
A fortune teller told me he'll be successful.
Incredible! Grandmother, you're the best.
I'm furious.
I couldn't sleep because of it.
After giving my blessings!
- We're off to school.
- See you later.
Pay attention to your teacher.
I'll make you spicy rice cakes when you come home.
Dad, you're the best.
Get me a fresh bowl of soup. It's cold.
Okay. Is it cold?
Give me lots of vegetables.
Can't you get your own soup?
I did this for him when he was unemployed.
And I actually have a job.
Here.
Eat up and go to work.
Why aren't you eating?
Sedal, don't you have anything sour and sweet?
There's nothing to eat here.
How can you complain about the food?
Why not? He's the cook, isn't he?
What's wrong with her?
She hasn't been eating so well.
I think she lost her appetite.
Make something special for her later.
Leave her be.
She'll eat when she's hungry.
I want you to do it.
Okay.
Looking back,
I think we had a very mundane life.
When did we ever laugh together or hold each other and cry in joy?
I wasn't able to make you happy.
Anyway, I'm sorry things turned out like this.
I asked to see you today
because Gwangbak's married now
and we should finalize the divorce.
Is that all you have to say?
What else can I say?
You're impossible.
You don't want to divorce me?
There's no reason for us to stay together.
You said you wanted it.
I don't care what you think.
But I'm thinking right now.
About what?
What is there to think about?
We have children.
Don't use them to force me to stay.
I have no intention to do that.
I'm thinking about what to do with the kids.
I'll call you when I decide.
You keep thinking and thinking.
That's all you do.
You're always thinking.
That's what's wrong with you.
You never think things through, including this.
So? What's wrong with that? It's nice.
Shut your mouth.
Do as I say, no matter what.
I'll call you later.
I'll raise the kids.
What right do you have?
I'm their mom.
You said you're worried about the kids.
I'll raise them.
They are my kids.
I can't let a woman like you raise them.
Then take them with you.
- You!
- You're going to slap me again?
Slap me again.
I'll get a medical report and sue you.
Why is everything so...
Do you ever think about anything?
I wish I could be like you.
Then be like me.
Our relationship has been ruined,
so divorce is the only natural course.
And volunteering to raise the kids.
What's wrong with that?
You're really going to raise the kids?
How can I?
My mom will raise them.
But you must pay child support.
Don't call me before I call you.
I won't answer your calls.
I'm so annoyed.
Why?
He won't divorce me.
I want to divorce him so I can marry you.
But he won't sign the papers.
He has no self respect.
Maybe he can't let me go.
You want to marry me?
Of course.
It took us so long to get back together.
Does your husband know who I am?
I don't think so.
Only that you're my boss.
Don't let him find out.
I don't want trouble.
I know that.
Oh, what's that smell? Huh?
It's for when the kids return from their honeymoon.
Oh, don't burn anything, okay?
What time are they going to be here?
Around dinner time, I think.
Minjung.
I'm going to be really late.
I'll try to finish early,
but don't wait for me, mother.
- Yes, father.
- Put her on.
Hold on.
Here. It's my father.
Yes, father.
Where are you?
We're on our way back to Seoul, father.
How long will it take?
Well?
We'll get there in about two hours.
Father, it'll take about two hours...
Come home within two hours.
Excuse me?
Don't make me repeat myself.
But we have to drop by my parents house.
Come home within two hours!
Father.
What do we do?
Father wants us home in two hours.
We...
We can't see each other again.
We can't, never again?
I'm sorry.
Sunjeong.
Yes, Daese.
Are you okay?
You don't look well.
I'm fine.
Can you prepare dinner?
The kids are coming.
Aren't they eating at her parents house?
I told them to come home.
You did?
Miho, get the door.
Mom, it's aunt. Should I open the door?
Open it.
Hello.
Hi.
You look just like your mom when she was little.
You're not going to be pretty at all.
I'll be prettier than you, aunt.
And don't chew gum so loudly.
It makes you look uncouth.
What?
Teach your girl some manners.
You should act like an adult first.
How could you say that to a child?
Why not?
And spit out your gum.
Mind your own business.
Why are you so busy?
I'm cooking for the kids when they come back.
They're not eating at her parents house?
They didn't want to cook for them, huh?
You don't know anything, so be quiet.
Stop! You haven't washed your hands.
My hands are clean.
I washed them at home.
Don;t be such a neat freak.
Did you make bulgogi?
It's Sangnam's favorite.
He doesn't eat that, don't you know?
Why not?
He ended up at an ER after eating that when he was little. Remember?
You were there and you don't remember?
It was your bulgogi that made him sick!
He ate it when I made it for him last time.
I'm sure he was pretending.
Please try to be considerate.
Go sit in the living room.
You're so rude.
I don't want to be in the same room with you.
I'm enduring it because of Daese and Sangnam.
Me too!
I would never see you, if I could.
Are you dating anyone?
It's none of your business.
You're mean because you're not dating.
I'm not you!
But I'm right.
Women should date because being in love softens you up
and changes your personality.
See how good tempered I am?
Do you keep in tough with that man you dated?
Be quiet.
I don't want you talking about him.
Don't be so pissy.
I'm still your older sister, girl.
You don't know what happened to him?
You could find out, if you wanted.
I think I heard he runs his own business.
I can't believe you've gotten over him.
Heartless.
Dating for 7 years is like being married.
Don't you think so?
Please shut up!
I can't believe how rude you are.
I said shut up.
Girl,
you're scaring me here.
You're getting meaner with age.
When you get older, you should soften up.
But you're mean and nasty.
My son in law, Sangnam.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Did you have a nice dream?
I didn't.
I didn't sleep at all.
How could he get sleep?
All night, they...
Mother.
They were busy staring at each other all night.
What did I say?
You should let me finish.
You're right.
Father, I know everything.
Saying you should stare at each other is
wrong with sex education now.
I didn't know that, sir, I apologize.
How does it feel to be married?
Really happy?
Yes, I'm really happy.
I'm wondering why I waited so long.
For me, it doesn't feel real yet.
It's because you're here.
It'll hit you when you go to his house.
You didn't get hanbok?
You need to wear it when you go home.
They skipped it to keep the wedding small.
They didn't get hanbok.
Where's Hobak?
Something came up at work.
Where's Minjung?
He's busy.
Minjung hasn't been home for days.
He told me he'd try to come.
Call him and tell him to come home for dinner.
Why? He'll be here when he can.
And don't call him when he's busy.
I wonder if he's eating.
Is he sleeping at the office?
I think so.
You're talking like he's a stranger.
You should check on him.
He's your husband.
Let's have dinner.
Mom, we have to go.
Why?
Have dinner and hang out.
Father wants us home.
What was that?
Who does that?
You have dinner at the wife's side of the family
when you come back from the honeymoon!
Sangnam, how can you let this happen?
I told him we'd be there.
My family is big, but he's all alone.
He's not! He has Sunjeong and Miho.
How could he tell you to come home?
He didn't.
We'll come another time, mom.
Let's go, Sangnam.
Sit down. We should eat here.
Mother, we'll eat here.
It's okay.
You should go.
We're fine.
No, we're eating here.
Where are they?
He must be stuck in traffic.
Maybe she took him to her parents house.
Where are you?
I'm at Gwangbak's house.
We're having dinner here.
What? Didn't I tell you to be here?
I'll explain to you later.
I have to go.
Why you...
Hey! Sangnam!
How dare they!
How dare they disobey me?
Whoa, I don't believe this!
It's not Sangnam.
It's her family.
You should nip this in the bud.
Manjeong.
What? I'm right.
Gwangbak, you have to come now.
Uncle is furious.
Okay, Miho. Thanks.
Call me if anything else happens.
Everything is so delicious.
Oh...
Eat up.
Chew slowly.
You'll get indigestion.
Slow down.
What's wrong?
Do you feel sick?
Huh? Get the medicine.
Oh, no! Anggeum, you gave him too much.
I'm fine.
I'm just so happy.
I've always envied kids with big families.
When I came home from school,
my house was always empty.
But when I went to my friend's house,
there were brothers, sisters and a mom.
They welcomed me and fed me.
Whenever I went to my friend's house,
I didn't want to come home.
I stayed until my father came to get me,
thinking how nice it would be to live there.
Being here tonight reminds me of that time.
Incredible.
I've already envied those with no siblings.
They don't have to share anything.
I know.
Right.
We grew up envying friends with no siblings.
You try living with a mom who hits you and yells at you.
And fights over food, crying.
It was hell for us.
We all said not having siblings was the beset kind of life to have.
Thank you for saying that.
Thank you.
Everyone longs for someone they don't have.
You should let it all go because we're your family now.
Wang's family.
I will.
Mother, can I come here every day and eat?
As long as you pay for the food, sure.
You're nuts.
Oh, this is nuts!
I'm the one who's going nuts!
Hobak's getting worse because you let her!
Try standing up for yourself.
Even a mouse cries out when cornered.
Why can't you do that?
Why would I even try?
Mom, I'm doing this because I want to.
I don't want to get a job.
I like running the house. It's nice.
But you're a young man!
You're my son, not my daughter.
Why did you turn into a housewife?
I can't sleep at night because of you.
Oh, I'm happy.
Your father's furious.
Miho's been calling and texting me.
Don't worry. You have me.
My mom and father are much more forgiving than your father.
Can't you just help me out?
Don't do anything to upset your father.
But we were supposed to eat here tonight.
My father was being unreasonable.
I'm their son in law.
I should do my part to your parents.
We didn't do anything wrong, so relax.
I'll get yelled at, not you. Let's go.
The bride and groom are...
Who do you think you are?
What were you thinking?
This is how you want her to act?
My own son thinks I'm a joke,
so why would your wife respect me?
Didn't I tell you to come home?
I'm sorry I didn't listen to you, but
it's tradition to have dinner at her house.
What?
I still think what you did was wrong.
You should've asked your father first.
We all waited for you without eating,
and you show up this late?
I think it's up to the woman.
She asked me to come, but I told her no.
Even if Sangnam wanted to stay for dinner,
you should've pushed him to come home!
I told you to be home within two hours!
I'm sorry, father.
Father you're being unreasonable.
You can scold her,
but you should do it when she deserves it.
She did nothing wrong.
How dare you defend her?
If you're going to act that way with your wife,
you're not my son.
Daese, this is her first night here so we...
Forget it!
what are you wearing?
You didn't get hanbok?
How can you wear that instead of hanbok
on your way back from the honeymoon?
They didn't get hanbok because...
You stay out of this.
There isn't a thing I like about her.
You!
Yes, father.
What's this?
Why is this...
Oh, my!
You gave this to him?
Unbelievable.
You really made no effort, huh?
I'm sure she didn't do it on purpose.
The mistake itself shows no effort.
I'm sorry.
I put the wrong letter by mistake.
The real letter is at home.
Forget it.
I don't want a letter that's copied.
You said you'd be good to me.
You said you'd make me happy.
Yes.
And this is you being good to me?
How can you lie every day?
Why are you crying?
Don't make me regret giving my blessings.
Father, that's too much.
I'm too much?
Yes.
People make mistakes.
It's not right to say such harsh words...
Sangnam.
You fool.
Calm down and let them pay their respects.
For what?
She has no respect for me!
Go in.
You stay here.
Your father has every right to be angry.
She should've been more careful.
It seemed insincere.
You could think it's nothing,
but that's when things are good.
That was why he told you to come straight home,
but you ignored it, so he's acting like that.
Father, I'm sorry.
This will never ever happen again.
Father, please let me bow.
There's no need.
You're stubborn, but I'm stubborn, too.
Don't bother bowing.
After my husband passed away,
you know how hard it was to raise them?
Sedal is my only son.
He was the light of my life.
I put him through law school.
But then you happened to him.
He wanted to become a prosecutor,
but thanks to you,
he lived like a loser on $3 a day.
He made the mistake of falling for a rich woman,
and now he's paying for it.
Imagine how I feel watching this.
You have sons, so you must know.
So mother,
just accept what's going on.
There's nothing I can do.
Even if Sedal did nothing wrong,
this is how things must be.
Just look. It's nice.
Sedal has something to do.
Being a housewife isn't a job!
Lots of men do it these days.
You working made your mom sad,
and I'm sad when I see my son cooking.
Times change and men and women are equal
but all moms with sons feel the same.
They want their sons to make money, doing what they love, not to be a housewife.
But what else could we do?
Sedal's the only one available.
He needs something to do.
You're not doing this because you need him.
This is your revenge!
Fine. This is my revenge.
I can't take Sedal back, just like that.
He has to make up for what he did.
Or I wouldn't be able to take him back.
So mother, please be patient until I get over everything.
I would've dumped him if I could,
but I can't.
He's my husband.
He's the father of my children.
I hate him and I want to leave him, but I can't.
So what can I do?
I want to torture him until I feel better.
How long will you keep this up?
I don't know.
Just think of me as your son in law.
Or you can move out if you can't handle it.
What?
You're telling me to move out again?
If you can't take this, maybe you should.
You go inside.
I've said all I have to say.
Mom, why are you being so stubborn?
I got myself into this.
She's not heartless. She took me back.
She's being heartless right now.
She'll torture you until you die.
What else could she do?
How could she just forgive me?
Could you do it, if it were you?
Mom, I went to hell and back.
I'm happy now. I agreed to do this.
Even if she insisted on doing this,
if I didn't like it, I would've said no.
I'm fine with it, so all is well.
Housekeeping is actually fun.
It's perfect for me.
You're an idiot.
I'm embarrassed.
What if other people find out?
Why should you be embarrassed?
Lots of men do what I do now.
Quiet!
Be discreet when you go grocery shopping and when you take out the trash.
Such an idiot... Ugh...
This is nuts.
Are you sad?
The welcoming party was too much, right?
It was my fault.
I made the mistake.
He didn't like me from the start,
so I should've been more careful.
My father was too harsh.
I put myself in his shoes.
He had every right to react that way.
Don't worry.
I'll do my best to the end.
I'll show him what kind of person I am and make him love me.
I'm glad you feel that way.
Hey, wife.
It's our first night in our own house.
Did you sleep well?
Did you?
Yes.
Uh, no, I didn't.
I feel really badly about everything.
You should brace yourself.
Sleep well and eat well.
this won't be a temporary residence for you.
I need to learn a lot, about everything.
All girls these days are like that.
But take your time. I'll help you.
Just be here when I go to my class.
Clean these.
Who came to dinner last night?
It must have been a big party.
Sangnam was really happy about that.
Everyone except Hobak's family and Minjung came.
Minjung seemed like a really nice person.
Yes, he really is.
He's actually nicer than Subak.
Let's go to the market later.
Yes, aunt.
Did you sleep well, father?
Sunjeong, I'll see you later.
But you need your breakfast...
He goes to the construction site first.
See you later, Daese.
Father, I'll see you later.
I'll get the breakfast ready for you.
Aeji, it's me.
Dad.
How are you, Aeji?
Dad, come home.
Why won't you come?
I'm really busy.
Aeji, if you miss me,
you can call me anytime, day or night.
I'll come and see you.
Dad, I miss you.
Me too.
Aeji, goodbye.
He's not coming?
He says he's busy so I should call him later.
He must be really, really busy.
I wonder if he has time to eat.
- This one is fresher.
- Oh!
Yes, yes.
You're really fresh.
I am?
Huh? Minjung!
Gwangbak.
Hello.
Yes, hello.
You're back from your honeymoon already?
Yes.
Sangnam couldn't take time off,
so we went to a ski resort for one night.
I was sad because you weren't there last night.
I heard you are very busy these days.
Yes, it's the end of the year.
Your absence was really big.
Everyone waited for you.
They did?
I should go. I'm behind schedule.
Go, Minjung.
I wish you all the happiness.
I'll see you again.
What are you doing?
You scared me.
Why would you get scared?
How did you get in?
What? You left the door open.
Shouldn't you say hello instead of how did you get in?
Your father in law should yell at you more.
Make me something. I'm hungry.
You want me to eat this?
I'm sorry.
This is all I have right now.
Fried egg?
What kind of daughter in law serves fried egg to her mother in law?
You should at least make me some stew and fish!
I'm sorry, mother.
I don't know how to cook yet.
I'm learning so I'll make it for you next time.
Your mom didn't teach you how to cook?
I can't believe your mom.
How dare she let you get married?
And you.
I wanted to say this last night,
but why haven't you been calling me?
Excuse me?
You should've called me the minute you got to your hotel, don't you think?
Like I said before, Sangnam's my son.
You should be good to me.
Do you understand?
You're here. Wait for me here.
I'll take a shower and be out in 10 minutes.
Let's go have dinner.
Did you like that last restaurant?
I made reservations there.
Your mouth is so small.
Why is it so hot in here?
Isn't it hot in here?
It feels fine.
Maybe it's because I just exercised.
May I unbutton my shirt?
Go ahead.
Here.
Ah...
It must take a long time for you to eat.
I couldn't eat much since I was a girl.
You've done a great job keeping your figure.
I don't do anything.
I was born with it.
Oh, did I sound conceited?
No, you didn't.
When you're beautiful, it's okay.
My hand feels soft, doesn't it?
Feel it.
Oh, it's really soft.
Oh, my...
Who is it?
It's bothering me.
Is it a woman?
No.
- What?
- You're not coming for dinner?
I'm having dinner with a guest.
But you should come home to have dinner.
Why would you call to say that?
Mind your own business. Bye.
Okay.
What did he say?
He has an appointment.
He told us to enjoy our dinner on our own.
He thanked me for calling.
Who was that?
My kid's mom.
Do you talk to her often?
No.
She came to attend the wedding but she hasn't gone home yet.
Do you live with her?
No.
I met her because of our son. That's all.
She's going home soon.
Okay.
It's too cold to eat out here.
This is better for the baby.
The air's nice.
Here.
My princess.
You eat, too.
I'll eat after you're done.
The rich men you dated must have taken you to nice places,
but now you're stuck with me,
eating cold chicken in the park.
I'm fine with it.
The men I dated before didn't give a hoot
about me or what I wanted to eat.
They sway your true colors come out when you eat,
and they ate all the drumsticks.
I even broke up with a guy during dinner.
We were having chicken gizzards.
And they were messy when they ate.
Where did you find guys like that?
Heartless bastards.
I know.
I'll always give you the best part of everything.
Here.
I don't want you to catch a cold.
My princess.
Okay, my prince.
Ah.
Eat.
Let's get on the next one.
The elevator's here.
Where should we go next?
Karaoke! Karaoke!
Should we stay on or get off?
We can do this again next time.
Get in before someone sees us.
I don't want to say goodbye.
Give me some time.
I'll talk to Bong and set the date.
You're the best thing that ever happened to me.
I hope that I'm the best thing that ever happened to you, too.
I miss you already.
Me too.
What's that? It's yours?
Yes.
Why are you reading that when you're single?
Why can't a single girl read this?
I want to be ready before I get married.
What the...
Read it after you get married.
You do the weirdest things sometimes.
We have a cooking lesson at No. 1905.
Oh, we do? At what time?
Oh, recycling is a problem, did you know?
Hello.
Oh, hi.
I'm the neighborhood association leader.
Oh, hello.
This is my day off, so I'm helping my wife
with the cleaning and the trash.
You don't have to say that.
The word's out.
We have lots of men like you here.
So don't be embarrassed.
You'll do this for the rest of your life.
Not for the rest of my life.
I'm taking a leave of absence right now.
That's what they all say.
But you'll get used to it.
Come to the monthly meeting.
And drop by my house sometime.
Drop by?
We have coffee together.
Come by. We can chat.
We're home!
Hi!
Wow! Spicy rice cakes!
It's great to have you home, dad.
Stay home and don't go anywhere.
Yes! Yes!
We got lonely because nobody was home,
but now, it feels great.
- It does?
- It does, it does!
Eat this and do homework.
Make mom happy.
Okay.
So dad, you're mom and mom's dad?
That doesn't matter as long as you have a mom and a dad.
Go wash your hands.
Okay!
Oh...
I'm so happy.
You have a doctor's appointment today.
Don, my mom went out.
I have to stay at the store.
But this is the only break I have.
Okay. Hold on.
Oh, how precious!
Are you a doll or human?
- Look at his hands!
- Be careful.
- Oh, my!
- Peekaboo!
So precious, aren't they?
Our baby will be even more precious.
Your grandson is cute.
Take care.
Go in.
Thank you for coming.
Ms. Heo Yeongdal!
- Yes!
- Yes.
Heo Yeongdal!
Watch out!
Don't fall down! Watch out!
Hey! You!
Mother! Hit me, not her!
What? Mother?
It was my fault! Hit me!
You come here!
How could you do this to me?
Of all men, why did it have to be Loser!
Oh, I want to die!
You and I are both dying today!
Nobody's dying! She's pregnant!
Oh, I don't believe this.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Ugh, you!
I don't care if you're pregnant!
Over my dead body!
You come here!
Mom, I'm sorry.
Don't hide behind him!
Come over her!
Mother!
Don't call me that!
How dare you call me mother?
How can this be?
Your life...
How could you fall for Loser?
Mother!
Hit me.
I don't care if you beat me to death.
Yeongdal didn't do anything.
It was all my fault.
If you give me your blessings,
I'll give my life to Yeongdal and the baby.
Mother!
Oh, my dear husband!
Oh, mother!
Sedal! Sedal!
What? What happened?
- Water, water.
- Huh?
Okay.
Mom, water, water.
What?
What happened?
What's wrong with mom?
Did she have a fight?
You go and beat Loser up right now.
Beat him up or kill him.
Loser? Why?
He did the same thing you did!
What same thing?
Oh, my dear husband...
What do I do?
How could you fall for him?
Mom, mom.
Mom, I'm sorry.
We'll live happily.
Happily?
How could you possibly?
You life's ruined!
How did this happen?
Hold on, hold on!
What are you talking about?
How could you let your friend run wild?
How could you let Loser do this to your sister!
That's what happened?
You guys are together?
Hurry up and tell us.
What is it?
- Mom.
- Huh?
Bong, Anggeum.
I want to get married.
What?
Married?
You have a woman?
Yes.
What does she do?
How old is she?
When did you meet?
You never told me.
She's outside.
Outside?
Hey, tell her to come in.
How can she just show up like this?
Oh, boy.
Come in.
Hello.
You're the woman he's seeing?
Yes.
How did this happen? Huh?
It just happened.
Sit. Have a seat.
Sit.
You must be surprised.
We're beyond surprised.
How did this happen?
This is good.
It's someone we know.
What did the beauty salon woman say?
Right, her mom called him Loser.
Please help me out.
She's really angry with me right now.
How dare she be angry with you?
It's not like her daughter's anything great.
I'm sure she has her reasons to be against it.
Let's think about you getting married.
You should date first.
Sir, we have to get married soon.
We can't do that.
You're really something.
Gwangbak just got married.
Uncle, I'm sure you're in a hurry,
but two marriages in one year isn't proper.
Let's do it next year.
Here.
What's this?
You're...
You're pregnant?
What?
How?
Because of alcohol.
We really got drunk that night.
The Korean War is nothing compared to this!
What do we do?
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Mom. Mom, take this.
Take it, take it.
Where's Yeongdal?
I don't know.
She left while I was getting your medicine.
I told you not to let her out.
Oh, man.
Where are you?
At my in-law's.
In-law's my butt!
You want mom to go crazy?
Not you too!
Goof-off, we need to talk.
You!
I'm going to kill you!
I don't mind dying,
but if you yell at Yeongdal, I'll kill you.
She's pregnant.
What if something happens?
How dare you!
Loser, come over right now!
Yeongdal.
It's me, not Yeongdal.
Uncle, please take care of Yeongdal.
Don't worry about us.
She's pregnant, so try to comfort her.
Bye.
How can you smile at a time like this?
This is great.
For whom?
You only care about your uncle!
You don't care about Yeongdal!
I'm sure she's in love with him.
My uncle didn't force himself on her.
They were meant to be together.
How could you say that?
The same thing happened to me and Sedal.
Your son and daughter are so much alike.
Like brother, like sister.
Are you trying to make me angry?
Oh, father, welcome.
- Yes.
- Mom.
Hello.
You! Come here.
What are you doing?
Yeongdal, go to me room. Careful.
Where's your mother?
She's lying in her room.
You little...
Come here! Huh?
Sedal, calm down.
How can I calm down?
My mom's in shock right now.
Be quiet.
Father, we made our decision.
We're happy about them.
When did I say that?
This is nuts.
Please ask your mother to come out.
I said she's sick!
Mrs. Park, come out.
We need to talk.
You lying down won't solve anything.
I have nothing to say.
I don't want to see you.
So just leave.
Don't be like that. Come out.
Think of they baby your daughter's carrying.
Are you kidding me here?
If you won't come out, we'll come in.
Mrs. Park,
please excuse us.
Don, ask for her forgiveness.
Mother, I'm sorry.
There you go calling me "mother" again!
Who's your mother?
How dare you call me that?
Please let us get married.
I'll be good.
Married? No way!
You'll be good?
I know you won't be!
Mrs. Park.
I'm sorry things turned out this way.
It's my fault for not watching over my brother.
At least you know that.
How could this happen?
He ruined my daughter's life.
It's so embarrassing.
How can I go on?
What are you going to do about this?
That's why we came.
They have to get married.
What?
You asked what we'll do.
Your family's shameless.
What did you say?
Mrs. Park, I'm very sorry.
But what else can we do?
I'll get a place for them, so let them get married.
We have a baby to think about.
Why are you crying?
You think we're happy about this?
I don't want to hear about marriage, so go.
I can't process anything right now.
I need time to think, so please go.
Meanwhile, your girl's belly will grow big.
What?
It's not that simple, can't you see?
If you were me,
would you let your daughter marry Loser?
We did!
You took our daughter from us!
You think we were happy about Sedal?
Don and Sedal are just about the same.
At least Don has a job!
What was Sedal doing back then?
Now you'll know how we felt back then.
What? How dare you!
How dare you say that!
I'm sorry. You stay out of this.
Loser, come with me.
Stop it. Stay here.
I'm going to beat him up and go to jail.
You know Yeongdal's the apple of my mother's eye!
- How could you...
- I said stop!
- You!
- Hey!
Sedal, have a seat. Let's talk.
I'll get you for this.
Mrs. Park,
I know my little brother isn't good enough,
but please give him your blessings.
Why are you begging?
They should do that.
What?
Don didn't do this by himself.
They did it together.
Yeongdal isn't a child.
She's old enough to know how to behave.
Are you picking a fight?
That was what you said to us 9 years ago!
What did you say to Hobak?
You said she ruined your young son's life!
So let's not do this.
I don't want this!
I hate Loser,
but I don't want you as my in laws again!
One is enough!
That's plenty! Ugh!
Hah! As if!
Go. This wedding isn't happening.
But what about the baby?
We'll take care of the baby.
I don't believe it!
You think you can do what you want?
I won't let some baby ruin my daughter's life and marry Loser.
So please go home.
Ugh.
Oh. Oh, boy. Oh.
Why are you doing this?
No! I said no!
I married a man who runs his own business!
Not someone who delivers parcels!
I regret marrying you,
and I regret having your kids! Satisfied?
I want a divorce!
Minjung!
Where are you coming from?
We had to take care of something.
Did you eat?
You've lost weight.
You can't be that busy!
Let's go in.
Okay.
There's something I must tell you.
What is it?
I'm sorry I have to tell you this.
Subak and I
are getting a divorce.
Subtitles by KBS World
What did Subak do?
She...
No! You can't divorce her. No way.
Don't forget to pay me child support,
since you agreed to it in court.
Take good care of the kids.
Mom, say yes.
I promise he's a good guy.
I rather die than see her marry him.
I don't want anything to do with that family.
You told your husband you have too much work?
She didn't!
I was just saying what I felt.
You stay out!
You know something, don't you?
No, I don't.
There's no need to hide it. Tell me.
Stay in touch with me, please!
Minjung!