Subtitles by KBS World
Gwangbak, it's been a while.
Say hi to your aunt.
Let's not do that when we're alone.
Married life must be easy on you.
It is.
There's no stress?
I just ignore everything.
In one ear and out the other.
I'm great at that.
Nothing bothers you, huh?
I envy you.
Your mom gets on my nerves, but it's okay.
I married Don out of love, so I can take it.
You're better than me, Aunt Yeongdal.
Gwangbak, married life is hard, isn't it?
Yes. I have a lot to learn.
Being book smart is useless.
I guess I wasn't ready to get married.
It's the same for everyone.
It's not just you.
Gwangbak, don't worry.
There's something you can try.
What is it?
How to be friends with your mother in law.
Honey.
You! You stay right there!
You're dead! Hey!
Stop right there! You're dead!
Hey!
Don't answer all his calls.
- Don't?
- That will drive him mad.
Okay. I got it.
- The person you have called...
- Man!
After the beep...
Man!
Answer it this time.
- What is it?
- Where are you?
What do you think?
At a karaoke place.
Near the shop.
Hobak! Have a drink!
Hobak! It's your turn to sing.
Sing a song! Sing a song! Sing a song!
Aren't you supposed to be working?
I'm busy. I have to sing. Bye.
Hey! Hey! You! You! Hey!
I don't believe...
Oh... Where is she?
Good job.
- You too.
- Thanks.
Hobak.
What are you doing here?
I asked him to come.
So we can put on a real show.
He'll be your driver.
Okay. I got it.
Do what I told you.
Oh, my.
Oh, oh...
Why that...
How dare she...
Ugh...
Get me some water.
You get it.
What?
You have hands.
Why are you talking like that?
- Get me some water.
- No.
You're defying me?
Tell him to get it for you.
- Who?
- The one who drove you home.
What the...
You watched me from the cold balcony?
You must have been really bored.
You think I'm a joke?
How can you bring a young man here?
I don't believe you.
Get me water before I get really mad.
You...
Oh, this is nutty, nutty...
Ugh...
Leave it there.
We need to talk.
About what?
Go ahead.
What have you been up to these days?
I don't know what I'll do if you keep it up.
What do you mean?
You drink all the time with your co-workers.
You didn't drink?
We just sang at the karaoke place.
He drove you home when you didn't drink?
I can't believe this!
Leave me alone.
Why don't you just...
Why don't I just what?
Quit my job?
You can't say it, can you?
You can't tell me to quit, can you?
You're mad, aren't you?
Don't pick on my weak point.
Tread on a tiger and it will turn.
You mean worm.
Whomever I see, whenever I come home,
just stay out of my business.
Aren't we married?
Did you forget?
We decided not to talk about my past.
When did we decide that?
You're the only one who decided that.
I'm going talk about until the day I die.
So don't be cheeky. I'm tired.
Oh, I shouldn't have become a model.
Why?
People won't leave me alone.
Who? Who won't leave you alone?
They got my number from somewhere,
and they've been texting me all day.
Even the headquarters server is down.
The other models must be ugly.
Why are they texting you?
And the server's down? Hah!
They must be blind.
I know.
I didn't know I was this popular.
Don't wear any makeup from now on.
Work is work.
Don't go there to show off.
So stop putting makeup on.
Whatever. Get ready for the Lunar New Year.
Me?
I've never cooked holiday dishes before.
So this will be your first time.
I can't come home early tomorrow.
It's not my father's ceremony but your father's!
Your father will be very happy
because his son is cooking for him.
Oh, this is really nuts!
What's wrong with your niece?
Why can't you control your niece?
She's your wife. You control her.
She won't listen to a word I say.
I wish I could tell her to quit her job,
but I can't do that. Can you understand? No.
Who'd understand? Nobody.
I know.
What's wrong with Hobak?
She's cheating on me.
What? Hobak is?
Crazy jerk. Hobak's not like you.
I'm serious.
She comes home with a young man!
And that modeling thing's made her conceited!
She's so full of herself, she'll explode!
I've experienced it.
She's almost there.
I can't even go to sleep because I'm mad.
If I leave her alone, she'll cheat on me.
Loser, you don't know, do you?
But I do because I've been there.
The signs are all there.
It's a good thing, then.
Hobak can experience what you've experienced,
and you can experience the pain she did.
That's our family motto, remember?
I'm sleepy. I'm hanging up.
Hey, hey, Loser! Hey, Loser!
Man! This is crunchy nutty nuts.
Oh, how annoying.
Minjung, come to me.
I'll raise the kids.
Your kids are like my kids.
You can't live by yourself.
And the kids need a mom.
I'll raise them.
He has a woman.
Look. you can tell she's been here.
What if he gets remarried?
You'll be the loser in this situation.
How will you take care of the kids?
Here.
It's for me?
It's for the memorial ceremony.
You should make plenty of food.
But we should be saving money.
Don't save money on food.
Prepare a feast.
There will be 3 son in laws this time.
One might not come, though.
He has to come for the kids.
It's me. Can we meet?
Okay.
Mom! Mom!
He wants to meet?
Yes.
Hurry up and go. And look pretty.
Look pretty? I was born pretty.
I was in the Miss Korea pageant.
You're finally smiling.
Aren't you happy?
Well...
You have to look extra pretty today.
If you do, he can't hate you.
And beg him to forgive you.
Don't scream and yell.
I won't.
Hurry up and get ready. Go.
You're not going to your father's house?
I'm going this afternoon.
Eat.
I haven't been to a place like this in so long.
I used to eat out all the time before.
I didn't know how happy I was.
I spent all the money you made,
and I didn't know how lucky I was.
I didn't know how hard it was to make money.
I was so stupid and immature.
Don't blame yourself.
It's in the past.
I'm sorry.
I really am.
Forgive me.
When you called me, I was so happy.
I don't even know how I got here.
My makeup looks awful, right?
I haven't worn it in a while.
You look pretty.
When I saw you outside,
it reminded me of the first time we met.
On that blind date.
Your first impression was awesome.
Your smile was nice and your voice, too.
I love a man with a nice voice.
We only dated for 3 months, but it was nice.
When I had Aeji, you were in Busan.
And you drove all the way to the hospital.
You were so happy it was a girl.
We have many good memories.
Let's stop talking and eat.
Okay, let's eat.
You know how to make pancakes?
I'm not great, but I'll try.
Pan fry these and clean these vegetables.
I'll come back and finish them.
Okay.
Incredible! How unbelievable!
No. 505!
Yes, hello.
- Why did you buy so much?
- Oh,
this is for the memorial ceremony.
By the way, what's so funny?
No. 304 is pregnant.
She is?
Isn't she old?
That's why it's unbelievable.
They were always fighting,
but now they are like newlyweds.
Should I have a baby, too?
Go ahead. I heard it's amazing.
How did she get pregnant when they fight all the time?
It was the alcohol.
Alcohol made the wife so attractive.
Thank you for lunch.
I didn't know what was good in the past,
but now I'm thankful for everything.
I'm glad you're happy.
Subak.
Yes?
If I got remarried...
You're getting married?
If.
What would you like to do about the kids?
You're seeing someone?
You are.
So my mom was right.
She said she sensed it.
What should we do about the kids?
You said you'll let my mom raise them
until they go to elementary school.
I want to raise them.
You want to take the kids?
She'll raise them?
That's why I'm asking.
I want to know what you want.
Your opinion is important in this.
If you want to raise them, you can.
Or I can take them.
If you raise them, I'll pay child support.
Your mother's having a hard time.
I've always felt badly about that.
What should we do?
Don't cry.
Yes.
Minjung, I'm making a lot of food so drop by to pick them up.
What time are you going to your father's?
I have to finish something up at work.
Okay. I'll be there later.
What do you want to do?
I'll think about it.
Why are you back so soon?
Subak!
Right? He's seeing someone?
So what did he say?
He asked what I want to do with the kids.
If I want to raise them, he'll let me.
What?
She must've told him she's not raising them.
That's why he told you to raise them.
How can he get married again so quickly?
So what did you say?
I told him I'll think about it.
What is there to think about?
Who'd raise another woman's kids?
He obviously wants you to take them.
I'll get him for this.
So who is she?
I don't know.
Why didn't you ask him?
When did they meet?
I don't know. I couldn't ask.
You fool!
I'm sure he didn't meet her recently.
He wouldn't marry someone he just met.
He's been seeing her for a long time.
How come you didn't know?
He divorced you for her!
And you fell for it like an idiot.
He got a call.
She asked him to come over.
Let's go. Get up.
Don't go. What are you going to do?
I'll catch him in the act.
Over my dead body!
Mom! Mom!
You're earl...
Wait.
Who's this?
Sangnam's aunt?
Hello.
Hah!
Hello?
I knew something was off.
What do you think you're doing?
You must be completely out of your mind!
How dare you do this here?
Please don't!
You seduced my son in law?
You ruined my daughter's life!
How dare you hold your head up!
They didn't get divorced because of me.
And don't you think you're overreacting?
Too much?
How dare you!
You!
Hey! You! You!
What are you doing?
Oh!
I'm glad you came.
What are you doing?
How can you do this to Subak?
Stop it. It's not what you think.
Go home.
Why would you put up with this?
Hah!
You're siding with her?
This is who you are?
How could you do this?
Oh, hello...
What's going...
Oh, my! Hey! Sunjeong!
You're making a mistake.
A mistake?
When there's evidence here?
When did you start seeing her?
Way before your divorce, right?
This isn't what you think.
I've known her for a long time.
I knew it.
You got divorced for her, didn't you?
It wasn't like that.
She has nothing to do with the divorce.
She?
How can you repay me like this?
I don't want to hear another word. Please go.
Mom, let's go.
You idiot. He fooled you!
I heard everything. Let's go.
What more can you say?
Let's go.
How can you betray me like this!
You tricked Subak into divorcing you!
How can you fool all of us?
Oh this is outrageous! Outrageous!
And I thought this was all Subak's fault!
Let's go. You're making me feel even worse.
This is why he takes you for a fool!
Just tell me one thing.
When did it start?
When she became your father's caregiver?
Wait, what are you talking about?
His father's caregiver?
She was his father's caregiver?
Yes.
You bastard!
You're home.
What's going on?
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Go in.
What's going on?
We were fooled.
He stabbed us in the back.
I'm beyond angry.
Minjung has a woman.
She's been coming and going.
And guess who she is.
Unbelievable.
It's Sangnam's aunt. That's her.
What are you talking about?
How can that happen?
I told you I saw her, remember?
I saw her getting in his truck once.
When her father in law was hospitalized,
she was his caregiver.
How can this be?
Those two tricked our poor girl.
Why won't you say anything?
Say something.
Aren't you enraged?
You should call him and yell at him.
I can't accept this divorce!
But it's all over now.
Don't pay attention to what Minjung does.
He's a stranger to us now. Accept it.
I can't accept it.
I wouldn't have let them go through with the divorce if I knew.
Bong! Do something!
He's getting married, leaving behind the kids!
Are you Subak?
She's not saying anything, so why are you?
This fool won't, so I have to do something.
Don't tell Gwangbak.
Why shouldn't I?
It's for Gwangbak.
Why can't you see that?
You're wearing hanbok?
I rented it.
I wore this to get in the holiday spirit.
Daese will be happy.
Did you make the pancakes?
Yes. Will you see if they look okay?
Good job.
Aunt, are you not feeling well?
I'm feeling a bit under the weather.
Maybe you're coming down with something.
Maybe.
Come out. I'm at the front door.
Sunjeong.
I'm sorry.
Are you hurt?
I don't know.
My head feels funny.
I'll know better tomorrow morning.
What do we do?
I'm worried about you.
It must have been crazy.
I could handle it.
I can't believe what happened to you.
I'm sorry you had to deal with that.
My mother in law is very possessive.
I think I understand how she feels.
I'm sure she didn't want to lose you.
And she might misunderstand our situation.
She thinks I caused the divorce.
It's frustrating.
Sunjeong?
Huh?
You came to see my daughter in law?
No, Daese. It's him.
Huh?
My... It's him.
What are you talking about?
He is?
Hello.
I can't believe this.
He's right here, but I can't believe it.
It's nice to meet you.
Sunjeong was so...
We should grab a drink.
I have a lot to tell you.
I thought you were her husband.
If only I were that lucky.
Let's get together after the holidays.
Okay.
Daese, you should go inside.
Huh?
Uh, okay. okay.
I can be so dense sometimes.
I'll see you again.
All the food is ruined.
What will you do?
My father's friend prepared all the food.
You did all that for nothing.
You should go.
Traffic will be bad.
Okay. Take good care of yourself.
Okay. Drive carefully.
Go inside.
Make them pretty.
Don't worry.
I've been making dumplings every year.
Gwangbak, if you make pretty dumplings,
you'll have pretty children.
Mom, am I right?
That's rice cakes!
They're both made by hand, so it's the same.
Your hanbok puts me in the holiday spirit.
I know.
It really feels like the holidays, father.
Father, Sangnam eats on regular schedule,
so he gets sensitive around meal time.
And he can't handle being hungry.
He takes after me.
You get sensitive, too?
Of course.
Our belly tells us it's time to eat.
And if we don't eat then and there,
we start getting annoyed.
And later, we lose our heads.
I know.
Food seems to be very important to him.
When we were dating, he watched me eat,
but now, he eats everything!
He gave you all the food before?
Yes, father.
But now, he doesn't.
And father, Sangnam is really stubborn.
He also got that from me.
Totally stubborn.
And he doesn't know when to stop,
and he looks narrow-minded.
You should've beaten some sense into him.
You are right.
Had I done that, you wouldn't be suffering.
I know. And father,
there's something I'm really disappointed in.
He's a blabbermouth. He can't control it.
I even stuck a note calling him Mr. Blabbermouth.
You did what?
You called your husband Mr. Blabbermouth?
Why did you enter the audition, then?
Sangnam is my son.
How dare you say that in front of me?
Imagine Sangnam telling your parents
how you say whatever is on your mind
and how rude you are to your husband,
asking them why they let you be that way?
How would you feel?
You should learn to cover his faults.
How can you talk about them to me?
To me, he's a very precious son.
You're working, and you put hanbok on,
so I was trying to get along, to humor you.
Even if I were talking badly about him,
you should say how great he is and thank me
for raising him to be such a nice husband!
From what you said,
my son is a blabbermouth and a stubborn and heartless glutton.
Why do you live with them, then?
Father, I'm sorry. I didn't mean that.
Forget it!
I'm his father. So?
He takes after me. Happy?
Daese.
You make all of them by yourself!
What happened?
I've been sending you signals to stop.
What did she do?
The books said to gossip about the husband
with the mother in law, so I told her that.
Daese, you should laugh it off.
She did that to get closer to you.
By speaking ill about her husband?
Who would believe that?
She went a bit overboard,
but some people get closer by doing that.
Am I her friend?
How can she think that?
She's naive, so she takes...
That's not naive! That's stupid!
She's dense and says anything on her mind.
She has no manners.
Daese, she's a considerate girl.
She just tried a little too hard,
so be more accepting.
No.
I can't accept her when she's unacceptable.
I can't believe I have to cook with my son.
Maybe I should've had more sons.
Pretend Hobak's your son in law.
That'll make you feel better.
But isn't cooking with me fun?
Yes, it's loads of fun.
It's so fun it's nuts.
You're good.
You want the original version?
This is nutty, nutty, nuts. Ouch.
This is nuts.
Ugh...
I wish I had 12 arms.
But you only have 2 pockets.
If I had 12 hands, I'd have 12 pockets.
Where would you put them when you sleep?
Six over your head, six down the sides.
But this house is too small for that.
If everyone had 12 arms,
it'll get in the way.
- It's small already.
- You're right.
Stop talking nonsense and work.
We have to make dumplings and stew.
Call Hobak, Anggeum.
You don't seem to like Subak that much,
but you like Hobak, don't you?
She's my brother's wife.
It's me.
Yes, mom, what is it?
You're coming to help out, aren't you?
I'm at the shop. I'm busy today.
But it's a holiday.
We're getting new clothes, so I'm busy.
Sedal's cooking the food at home.
Hobak!
Mom, I have to go.
Hobak, hello?
She can't come?
She's busy.
What's she so busy with?
She's been extremely busy.
After she became a manager, it's been crazy.
She's not giving me any money.
She hasn't even given me any gifts.
she sells clothes, but I haven't seen any.
But Hobak got us this house.
She didn't do it alone.
Gwangbak helped.
Still, she spent her own money,
so she has to be more frugal.
I can't seem to be able to love her.
I wonder where Haebak is.
Everyone comes home for the holidays.
Mom!
Speak of the devil!
You're a bad girl.
Mom.
Oh, you're such a bad girl.
Mom, I don't want to have any regrets.
I want to follow my dreams.
Please let me do this.
If I give up, I'll regret it later.
Huh?
Say something.
What's the use?
She made up her mind.
All our girls are so stubborn.
Mom.
If you must, you must.
Don't blame me for ruining your life.
Don't say that.
Thank you, mom.
Oh...
None of my children does what I tell them.
Is it like this everywhere?
It's like this everywhere.
No. 304 is pregnant and they're so happy.
I'm home.
What is it?
There's no other choice.
Let's move out.
We can't live like this anymore.
You're stressed out and I'm stressed out.
I can't focus when I go to work.
I worry about what will happen today.
Let's find an apartment after the holidays.
No, I don't want to move out now.
I'm going to win him over.
I want to beat him at this.
What?
I want to be accepted by him.
I'm going to make it happen.
Then I can move out of this house.
At this rate, things will just get worse.
So Sangnam, will you wait for me?
Why can't he see how lovely you are?
Oh, what's that smell?
Sedal, Sedal!
Oh, you're home.
When did you come home?
Why don't you lie down?
I was waiting up for you.
You weren't watching from the veranda?
Two handsome men drove me home.
You better stop!
By the way, what's that smell?
Did you pour the whole bottle on you?
I cooked all day, so I smelled greasy.
Oh, it's too much.
You're giving me a headache, so go out!
Sintong, Bangtong, bow to your grandmother.
Take the apron off.
That's not your uniform!
It's become a part of me.
Sometimes I wear this to the shower.
Good for you!
Happy New Year.
Okay.
Grow up quickly and take care of your dad.
We will.
Study hard.
And be healthy, okay?
- Okay.
Give that to me.
Let me have it.
It's theirs.
I will put it in the bank for them.
And give me what you get at grandpa's, too.
Okay.
You're like children laborers.
The house feels empty without Yeongdal.
She'll come after the memorial ceremony.
Send Yeongdal home when you get there.
I'm going to work today.
- Again?
- I'm busy.
Are you a workaholic?
But you used to be addicted to money.
I switched to being a workaholic.
Take the boys to my parents house later.
- Ugh!
- Ouch!
It's like you're my daughter in law.
Oh, mother!
I mean, mom.
- Mother.
- Yes?
Would you like another drink?
Sure. Let me get drunk.
Bong, here.
Okay.
- Mother.
- Yes?
The pancake brings back memories.
Memories of how difficult life was.
Everyone's having a difficult time now,
but we're all here, having a feast. It's nice.
It's not that nice.
You think it's nice?
I can't believe what happened to us.
Honey, why didn't you look after Bong?
Your father probably cried when he came.
I'm not sure if he came at all.
How could he find such a dump?
You shouldn't suffer like this at your age,
but look what happened to you!
Please stop.
If you're drunk, you should go to bed.
What?
This is all your fault.
This wouldn't have happened without Subak.
Why are you blaming her again?
You want her to go somewhere and die?
Anggeum, mom wasn't saying that.
You should stay out of this.
Just take care of yourself.
You're living off Bong with your wife,
so you shouldn't be talking right now.
You're not feeding my boy.
Bong is feeding him, okay?
Did he ask you for money? Did he?
You still don't get it, do you?
You should feel badly about this.
You and Subak are the same.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo!
Please stop.
Why are you jinxing the New Year like this?
You want Subak to go and kill herself?
Is money more important than her?
What?
That's the money Bong worked really hard for!
Please stop it!
Anggeum, please don't yell at my mom.
What kind of example are you setting for my wife?
Uncle, stop it.
Why are you and grandmother doing this?
I'll go and kill myself, okay?
Subak, you stay out.
Don't butt in when the adults are talking?
What?
Look at her!
You didn't learn anything, did you?
To me, all of you are freeloaders.
Uncle, Yeongdal, you should move out.
You think Subak is all happy?
You're so mean.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
I'll be back.
Where are you going?
Didn't I tell you yesterday?
I'm volunteering to make soup for the elderly.
Have a good day.
Go to your parents house with Sangnam.
Okay. Thank you.
Let's go!
Oh, how exciting!
You're that happy?
Yes.
I'm going to tell my parents how oppressed I've been.
You blabbermouth!
Sangnam! Sangnam!
Let's go.
Say hello.
These are my employees who live alone
or can't make it to their hometown.
Go make some rice cake soup.
I'm sorry?
Yeongdal, where are you?
I can't come today.
Why? Mrs. Lee won't let you come?
It's not that.
The mood here is a bit...
What's wrong with the mood?
I don't know.
I've never seen this before.
They were all fighting at breakfast.
I tried to stop them,
but I'm still scared.
This family's weird.
Sedal took Sintong and Bangtong over.
They're not here yet.
Mom, I'll come tomorrow. Bye.
- Grandfather!
- Grandmother!
Be quiet.
Why?
It's horrible here.
What happened?
They had a fight.
I'm worried about Wangdal.
Mom's waiting for you. Go home.
I called her and told her I can't come.
Then she'll be home alone.
She'll cry if she's home alone.
Sedal, you should go home, then.
Bong isn't home and mother's sleeping.
Where's Loser?
He went looking for Bong.
He ran away from home.
Really?
He left, so I guess he did.
Don't tell anyone we're related.
Then there's nobody to hang out with.
They need to make money.
Subak.
Hey.
Where's Hobak?
She went to work today.
Sintong and Bangtong wants to bow.
I don't feel like doing that.
Oh, that shouldn't matter.
It's the tradition, so...
Close the door.
Okay.
Oh, Daebak.
Sintong and Bangtong wants to bow.
Let's call it even.
What?
Give them what you were going to give me.
Incredible.
Hey, you scored!
You scored.
What is it, father?
Are you doing the dishes?
No, I was just taking the dishes out.
Get us some drinks and some fruit.
Okay, father.
My family must be waiting for us.
I don't think they'll finish anytime soon.
Sangnam, I'll get the drinks for them,
so you go and see my parents.
It's the first Lunar New Year after the marriage.
They'll be upset if you don't come. Go.
Should I?
I'm sorry for going alone.
I'm okay. I'll go later.
Scored!
It's me, Sangnam!
- You're here?
- Yes.
Mother, let's go in so I can bow.
It's too crazy here for that.
Where's Gwangbak?
We had some unexpected guests.
She'll come later.
Unexpected guests on a holiday?
I'm sorry. She'll come later.
After the memorial ceremony, you come here.
Ask anyone on the street.
How can he hold her hostage like this?
And why did they come to your house?
Have they no manners?
- Gifts...
- Leave them.
- Bow...
- Nobody wants that.
And my husband's not home.
- Grandmother...
- She's sleeping.
- How about you...
- I said no!
Sangnam.
Come in.
Oh, even at my in laws house...
Hello, uncle?
We were having a family gathering on our own.
Have a drink.
I have to go.
We have guests over.
Oh, just have one drink, okay?
Boys, bow to your uncle.
This is your chance to make money.
- Happy New Year.
- Uncle, let us bow.
- Okay.
- There you go.
Enjoy yourselves.
Sangnam, should I bow, too?
Bow to me.
I'll give you a dollar.
Why you little...
One for Daebak, one for Haebak.
Okay.
- And Aeji, Jungji.
- Okay.
You can't trust him.
I'll give it to them.
I know how it's done.
Uh, hey.
I want to go home.
I'm bored, Jangbi.
You know how lonely I get on holidays.
Then go meet your girlfriend.
I'm tired.
Then you go, but they're staying.
Gwangbak should visit her parents.
They must be waiting for her.
Oh.
Men who are taken are useless.
Park Salla, get yourself together!
Honey.
Huh? Why did you come back so early?
Your mother didn't look so happy.
And your father wasn't home.
I heard they had a fight.
Oh, I can picture it.
Grandmother probably started it about Subak.
So you didn't bow to my father?
No. I called, but his phone was off.
I gave the kids money and came home.
Oh, director!
Oh, what brought you here?
I heard the managers are working today.
You're working really hard, aren't you?
We're almost done.
I'm taking other managers out, so join us.
Let's celebrate your successful model debut.
Okay.
Oh, it's cold.
Where were you?
I was waiting for Hobak.
She came home just now, completely drunk.
When? I didn't see her.
You must have missed her.
I should yell at Hobak.
How can she come home so drunk?
She's doing it because she's not afraid.
What if she cheats on you?
If she meets someone else, you're finished.
This is all your fault.
This is nuts!
Oh, oh.
They got pregnant because of alcohol.
Hobak.
Hobak. Hobak.
Are you asleep? Honey.
You stay still, I'll do everything
Is it true or not? I'm not sure
I didn't know what love is
Make yourself at home in my arms
- Get me some water.
- Water? Okay.
Here is water with honey.
Make yourself at home in my arms
I'm dying.
Why are you singing so early in the morning?
You must have energy to spare.
Did something happen?
Of course.
Something amazing happened.
You like getting older?
Just hold on.
For what?
You'll find out.
How did I come home last night?
You don't remember?
Ugh...
The director and other managers all came after me, and I blacked out.
You really don't remember anything?
I do.
What? What do you remember?
Come to think of it...
Why? What is it?
I had a weird dream.
Dream? What kind of dream?
I was being chased by someone.
Oh, that's a bad dream.
And someone pounced on me.
They did?
Yes.
I think it was a tiger.
A tiger this big pounced on me.
It must be a bad dream.
That's actually a pregnancy dream.
What are you talking about?
There's no way!
It's not like we did anything.
Who knows?
Take care of yourself.
Don't be cheeky. It's horrible.
Anyway, why are you smiling?
If you were me, you'd be smiling, too.
What the...
Make me some soup.
Oh, ouch!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
How's your stomach?
My stomach's fine!
Don't overreact. Ugh.
I'm worried about your stomach.
Oh, my stomach.
My stomach's fine.
But that stomach might not be.
Munjin Middle School.
This is Wang Bong.
The president?
Okay. I'll be right there.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I had to go to work, so I couldn't come.
You never brought me clothes before.
Is this leftover from last season?
No, mom. That's new.
That's for you,
this is father's, and this is grandmother's.
I didn't get anything for others.
Where's everyone?
Why is it so quiet?
Why did you get grandmother anything?
Don't be like that.
Oh, I heard you had a fight.
I don't even want to talk about it.
It was decided by the board of directors.
You need to quit before next semester.
Please sort things out by next month.
Hello, mother.
Daebak's not home.
Hey, don't ever come here again.
Leave!
Get out. Like mother, like daughter.
Miho.
What are you talking about?
You're taking the kids?
Over my dead body.
Aeji and Jungji are my grandchildren.
Nobody else can raise them.
You can't have them.
Mother.
Don't call me mother.
If that's what you want, don't come back.
They are my kids.
They are Subak's kids, too!
And I'm the one who's been raising them!
You and Subak stay out of it!
This won't solve anything.
I'll come back and take them soon.
He wants to take them?
She must have told him to bring them.
You're going to let him take your kids?
If the kids are gone, it's really over.
I'm not sure if I can say this,
but Minjung's seeing a woman.
I saw them at the beach.
She told you to never come again?
Yes.
Did you do something wrong?
She said something about you.
No.
I did nothing wrong.
Hello?
Sunjeong?
This is Subak.
You know who I am, don't you?
Let's meet.
Subtitles by KBS World
We're getting back together.
Don't you know him at all?
We'll see about that.
You want me to slap you around?
I'm scared to meet him.
Why should you be?
You have the kids.
Sunjeong, I'll come to you.
Minjung.
Why are you checking my phone?
Who is he?
What's wrong with you? Who?
What should I do?
Jungji fell asleep.
Then you should spend the night here.
Let's cut to the chase.
I want to see you.
I don't think I should.
I don't want traces of you at his place.
You can't go in.
- Step aside.
- I won't!