Subtitles by KBS World
I'm begging you.
Please forgive my idiot daughter.
Do it for me, please.
Minjung.
Why did you come out?
You weren't asleep?
I woke up.
You weren't there.
What is it?
It's nothing.
Is something bothering you?
It's work stuff.
Let's go inside.
- Honey, honey.
- Yes, yes.
What is it?
You want water?
I don't want anything.
Why do you moan every night?
I do?
Don't you sit at your desk all day?
I'm getting old.
- Can I have some water?
- Sure.
What happened to your hand?
Let me see it!
Why is your hand all rough?
I got hurt working at the school.
Your hands used to be softer than mine.
Men's hands aren't that soft.
Stop talking and go back to sleep.
I'm not sleepy.
I have too many worries to sleep.
What are we going to do about Subak?
Why do you open your mouth?
That's what I want to know, too.
Why do I open my mouth when I do this?
Watching you put on makeup is interesting.
I used to be famous for wearing makeup.
You're bluffing again?
Why you little!
Mother, I'm going to work.
Okay. Watch out for the cars.
I will.
I'll walk out with you.
I'm going to start working again.
But you're pregnant.
Are you sure?
It should be better than being stuck at home.
Father, have a nice day.
I'm going to work, too.
Do you need help before I go?
It's okay.
Huh? Are you going somewhere?
Yes, I'm meeting someone.
Watch the store.
How is Subak treating you?
I think her father was pretty hard on her.
She looked depressed.
She's a huge problem for them.
She ruined the family, literally.
I feel sorry for her.
No one respects her and she got dumped.
She deserved to be dumped.
I would never do what she did.
I'm going to love only Don.
Right, Wang Dal?
Oh, boy.
Mom.
It's like you're our enemy!
This is all your doing!
You said you didn't but who else is there?
Why won't you believe me?
Why didn't you make Subak stop?
I tried.
But she wouldn't listen to me.
Then why didn't you tell me?
Or you should've kept your mouth shut.
You got your sister divorced.
Whose side are you on?
Minjung or Subak?
I want to be on Minjung's side, but I couldn't. Subak is my sister.
I'm mad at Minjung, too.
But why can't I believe you?
When your mom's really sick,
you should take time off to take care of me.
Oh, how annoying!
Get out! I don't want to see you.
Why are you taking it out on me?
I'm not coming back, so good luck.
Why that!
Hey!
Excuse me. Excuse me, there!
Oh, I'm so out of breath.
Why won't he even answer me?
Hello? Can you please come out of there?
Can you step out from there?
Hello, Mr. Security Guard?
Can I take these boxes here?
Oh, he looks just like my son.
My son is the vice principal at that school.
Everyone in the neighborhood respects him.
Thank you.
Oh, boy.
Thank you, thank you.
Oh, I got so lucky.
What's wrong?
You can't tell a towel and rag apart?
Help me turn around.
I'll get bedsores.
How...
Help me turn and put the pillow on my back.
I got it.
Oh, no!
You're such an idiot!
Why can't you do anything right?
Can you do anything right?
This is crazy.
What am I going to do with you?
You lost the house and had an affair.
I'm so furious!
You're driving me crazy!
Ouch...
Can you do anything right?
You can't take care of your kids, let alone take care of me!
So what do you want?
Dealing with you isn't easy!
Stop this, please!
Stop saying that!
I'm going crazy here, too!
Ouch...
Oh...
Now she's beating me up.
Oh, I'm dying here.
Hobak, you don't have to go your mom's?
I don't.
But you got the afternoons off for her.
Did something go wrong?
They can do fine without me.
Don't lift anything heavy.
I got a call asking me to look after you.
Who? Was it from Sedal?
Yes. He said you must be careful.
What the...
Anna, I better go.
You should. Or you'll feel badly.
- Take this.
- Oh!
Mom, I brought sweet potatoes.
You wretch. Why did you come? Go.
I don't need anyone.
What happened here?
Where is Subak?
I yelled at her and she left,
leaving all this behind.
I want to die.
Oh, even the blanket's wet.
How can she leave it like this?
Oh, boy.
I know it must be hard to just lie there all day.
But what else could you do?
Getting angry will frustrate you even more.
So don't say anything to Subak.
What's done is done.
She's probably the most upset of all of us.
Mom, let me change your blankets.
Oh, that's cold.
What is it?
Where are you?
At my mom's.
Again?
If something goes wrong, you're dead!
Whatever. Bye.
Hello? Hobak!
Oh, this is nuts.
Oh. Ugh...
Hobak! Hobak!
Okay! I'm coming!
What is it?
What do I do?
It's my stomach.
I didn't mean to.
It's okay.
Don't feel badly about anything.
I'll boil some water.
Oh, man! Get up.
Why did you come?
I said get up.
Man! Keep it down!
Man!
Don't!
Tell her, okay? Tell...
Man!
What's wrong with you?
This isn't helping me.
How can you do this?
Your doctor told you to be careful!
He said I'm fine.
Where's Subak?
Is she gone?
She's taking time off?
She's not.
She had an argument with my mom.
Unbelievable.
Your mom will finally know who cares more.
Wait, who am I kidding?
Don't do this.
I need peace of mind.
Doing this makes me feel at ease.
I don't feel at ease when I'm lying down.
What's done is done, so let this pass.
It'll only be for 2 weeks.
I don't get your family.
Subak has nothing to do,
so why must you take time off from work
and come here to take care of your mom?
Just go home and make me something yummy.
Okay?
Oh, man...
This is nuts.
I was afraid of getting married before,
but after meeting you, I want to do it.
When should we do it?
Give me some time.
I have grown up children,
so I can't just do what I want to do.
Are they against it?
They wouldn't believe I've been seeing you.
I've never dated anyone until now,
and I've been living like a nun.
Hold on.
Are your hands warm?
Yes, they are.
I think you're a player.
But I don't do this for just anyone.
I'll only do it for you.
I'll keep your hands warm.
And when we get married,
your feet, too.
What is it?
I want to carry you on my back.
Your feet must be hurting, right?
I'm okay.
Here, get on my back.
Here.
Yes!
Yay!
Oh!
Woohoo!
Oh, I'm dizzy, I'm dizzy.
Oh, no...
Let me get off.
Huh?
Sedal! Sedal!
Oh...
Sal...
Son?
Let's talk.
I have nothing to say.
I told you not to fall for it again.
He's not like that.
He's a really good man.
You should meet him.
When did you first meet him?
About 2 months ago.
2 months?
How can you know if he's good in 2 months?
You should give him a chance.
I don't want to talk to you.
Sedal.
I'm old now.
Now that Yeongdal's married, I'm so lonely.
You have me.
So why do you feel lonely?
You need a man to not be lonely?
You have Yeongdal and grandchildren, too!
You're saying that because you're young.
When you're old, you need a partner.
Think about it.
How would you feel if you didn't have Hobak?
You've been doing great until now.
It only looked like I was doing great.
I was miserable inside, but I laughed it off.
When people around me told me to remarry,
I didn't, because of you and Yeongdal.
Now you're all married, and I'm done,
so why can't I meet a man?
I don't want to be a burden for you.
Mom,
I haven't forgotten it.
It's still clear.
What is?
When you had a hair salon in Myeongdong,
you lost it all because of that bastard.
I was so scared about you running away.
I slept every night, holding on tightly to you.
I was scared you'd abandon me and Yeongdal.
I was only 9 years old.
You knew about that?
He left you in huge debt.
Don't you remember how you lost your
hair salon and how we ended up here?
Mom, snap out of it.
You can trust anyone!
They're all trying to take advantage of you.
You're running a makeup shop,
so he wants to swindle money from you.
He's not like that.
I didn't know you remembered that.
Oh, my...
But I never thought about abandoning you.
He told you to abandon us.
He did that every day.
I heard it all.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
You were scared I might run away?
You thought I'd abandon you?
You're so thoughtful.
How could you bottle that up all these years?
Oh, I thought you were an immature boy.
I had no idea.
I won't run away. I can't.
How could I leave you behind?
- Mom.
- Sedal.
Mother, I'm home.
You're home?
Did you have dinner?
I didn't have much of an appetite.
With Anggeum lying on her back,
I lost my appetite and will to live.
Just give her a little time.
Bong,
I saw someone who looked just like you today.
You did?
Many people look alike.
But the similarity was only in appearance.
He was a security guard.
I see.
Mother said she saw a security guard who looks like you.
Who says we look alike?
We don't look alike at all.
It's raining outside.
- It is?
- Yes.
Where's Mr. Ko?
Should we call him?
Hey.
When are you coming home?
Oh, I meant to call you.
I have to work overtime.
So you're not coming home?
Okay. Be careful.
He has to work until morning.
He must be hungry, then.
He must be.
Should I make something for him?
Yes. He'll love it.
Let's see.
What should I make?
What are you doing?
Just wait.
I don't want to see you. Go home.
Minjung.
Please, please forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I know what I did was wrong.
I deceived you when I married you.
On top of that, I cheated on you.
You probably want to beat me to death,
but take pity on me and give me a chance.
Give me a chance to make it up to you.
I never cooked for you
or even washed your clothes.
I never cared for you when you were tired from delivering parcels.
I'm pathetic...
But please take pity on me.
I'll make it up to you. I will.
Just give me a chance.
Have you been drinking?
Don't do this. Go home.
I can't let another woman raise our kids.
I want to raise them with you.
They're our kids.
Please...
Forgive me.
Don't do this.
It's over between us.
I don't hate you or blame you anymore.
There's nothing left between us.
Please, please...
Subak,
you should go home.
I can't.
I won't unless you forgive me.
Stop this, please!
You're suffocating me.
You think this is easy for me?
You think I'm fine?
When I divorced you, my heart shattered for Jungji's sake.
So how can you do this now?
Please let me go!
Taxi!
I appreciate everyone working so late.
Can you reserve a restaurant for us?
I will, Mr. Ko.
Hello?
Dad!
Yes, Aeji.
There's a talent show at my kindergarten.
Are you coming?
I'm sorry, but I can't.
Go with mom.
But mom's sick!
Don't cry, Aeji. Dad will be there.\
Mommy.
Jungji.
You're here.
I heard you were sick.
But I had to come.
Thank you for coming.
Mom.
You're home early.
I think I'm catching a cold.
We should go see a doctor.
Mom, I saw Mr. Ko.
Where?
At Aeji's kindergarten.
He went to the talent show with Subak.
Mr. Ko is weird.
Why is he still seeing her?
It's because of Aeji and Jungji.
They still have to meet because of them.
But still.
It feels weird.
Come in.
What brought you here?
Have a seat.
I brought you some fruits.
I was feeling a bit hungry.
Let's eat together.
You eat.
It's good.
Why didn't you come home?
You said you'd come afterwards.
It ended in the morning.
I didn't call thinking you were asleep.
And I went to the sauna right after that.
I didn't know you could lie.
You promised to tell me how things were going.
You've been distant lately.
I saw you two on my way to bring you food.
Last night, in the rain...
I wasn't trying to hide it.
I didn't want to worry you.
They have nothing to do with me.
I'm completely over Subak.
Is that really possible?
- Trust me.
- Minjung,
let's really think about it.
Can you really sever all ties with her?
When her whole family wants you back,
can you really turn your back on them?
Let's say we raise the kids.
She'll keep calling you because of them,
and I won't feel comfortable watching that.
And you'll start lying "for my sake,"
and I'll start being suspicious.
And that will continue to happen.
- Sunjeong.
- Let me finish.
Only you can resolve this.
You didn't draw a line,
and that's why they keep coming back.
You need to be decisive on things like this.
How much more decisive must I be?
What else do you want me to do?
I should go?
I don't want to fight.
Can't you just wait for me?
Will I break my promise?
I promised to come to you.
So trust me and wait.
I can wait.
But why did you let Subak hug you?
Why couldn't you push her off?
That's who you are.
I don't need anything else, so be honest.
I don't want you to come out of promise.
I want you to truly want me.
If you want me, walk straight toward me.
Why should you falter on the way?
That's too sad.
It's not like that.
I'm not faltering.
I'm coming to you.
I've been coming to you.
It's hard for me, too, Sunjeong.
Why can't you give me a break?
She's my kids mom.
We had two kids together,
so how could I turn my back on her
whens he came to me drunk and
got down on her knees in the rain?
I got a cab for her and sent her home.
Was I supposed to step all over her and slap her face?
Is that what you want?
I don't know.
I don't know what either of us want.
Sunjeong,
I can't live without you.
You're the only woman who makes me laugh.
I want to spend the rest of my life with you.
Mother.
What are you doing here?
You didn't go home?
I came back.
I ended things with him.
He beat me up because I didn't bring  money.
Can you give me some food?
Oh, that hit the spot.
How have you been?
That was quick.
When you're starving, nothing else matters.
Everyone who's full can think of others.
I didn't come here to ask for anything.
I came to see Sangnam one last time.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes, Dokdo Island.
Dokdo Island? Why?
To open a tea house.
What?
I want to run a tea house in Dokdo Island.
Can you do that?
You won't have any guests.
It's Korea, so why can't I open a tea house?
Japanese claim it's their land,
so I've decided to go there and protect it.
I'll go to Ulleungdo Island first.
If I can't, I'll open one in there.
When I open it, it'll be a huge success.
I'm going to quit chewing gum now.
It makes me look cheap.
Mother, this isn't much.
If you can't open a tea house, call me.
I'll talk to Sangnam for you.
Thanks, Gwangbak.
Visit me in Dokdo Island.
Sangnam is lucky to have you.
I'll buy you a brand name handbag after I get rich.
Okay.
Get on the bus, mother.
Come in.
Miho is already sleeping?
She has a cold, so she took some medicine.
Living here must be hard on her.
It's my fault.
Don't say that.
You shouldn't even think that.
Aunt, I'm going to China on business soon.
If anything happens, call me right away.
I'll drop everything and come back.
Take care of yourself.
But what about your wife and your father?
I know.
They'll fight again.
I'm sorry, Sangnam.
I feel badly for everyone.
You, your father,
and your wife, especially her.
Don't be, aunt.
You can't force love.
And you didn't do this on purpose.
Are you catching a cold, too?
You don't look so great.
Is something wrong?
No.
Aunt.
I don't know what to pack.
I'll pack.
How long will it take?
I don't know yet.
You haven't called aunt, have you?
I can't.
No, I don't want to.
She was worrying about you.
About you and father being left alone.
I know how good she was to me.
That's why it's even harder.
I can't hate her, so it's that much harder.
But Subak's my sister.
Aunt left the house for you.
Miho caught a cold.
You don't feel badly about that?
Put yourself in my shoes.
What if you had a brother and this happened?
I still can't understand you.
She's my aunt.
You'll have to see her since we're married.
What about my sister, then?
But this is neither of their faults.
Things just happened.
It's Subak and Minjung's issue, to be frank.
So why are you blaming my aunt?
Aunt didn't make this happen, but it was her who caused Minjung to make that decision.
We're repeating ourselves. Let's stop.
We must finish.
You can't leave things like this.
There's still time until your flight.
I have to do something at the airport
and keeping this up will lead to a fight.
We're already fighting.
We should finish it.
Finish what?
It'll be the same!
How can you do this?
You don't want to live with me anymore?
You're home, father.
How about dinner?
I already ate.
Where are you going?
To the supermarket.
What's that?
Huh? It's trash.
Are you...
Am I...
Sneaking things to my parents?
What?
Look.
You can check.
It's all trash.
I packed the trash to take to my parents.
What are you doing?
You were suspecting me of something.
When did I do that?
Father,
you've been disrespecting my parents.
I'm so disappointed in you.
My parents didn't raise me like that.
They didn't raise me as a thief.
This is my home, so why would I take anything?
Since you suspected me of stealing,
I'll take these to my parents.
Hey!
Please don't call me "hey."
I have a name.
I'm Wang Gwangbak.
Why that...
What are you doing?
Who cares what I'm doing...
Father.
What are you doing?
I'm drinking.
It's so nice to run into you here.
Remember this place?
When we were enemies,
we ran into each other here!
Father, have a drink with me.
This is embarrassing.
Let's go home.
But I have to finish this.
Father, I feel so happy.
I took the trash to my parents,
and they loved it, saying I've become a good girl.
They want me to bring it every day.
I have to collect all the trash now.
So I can take them to my parents.
Father, can I do that?
- Let's go home.
- Yes, let's.
Let's go, let's go, let's go. Let's go.
Let's collect trash!
Oh!
Gwangbak.
Don't wobble when you walk!
Walk.
How embarrassing...
I can't believe this.
Oh!
Drink. Drink and snap out of it.
What? Your parents loved the trash?
You're trying to make me mad?
You were being suspicious of me.
Don't disrespect my family.
I'm not a beggar.
I wouldn't take side dishes to my parents.
If I were to steal, I wouldn't be so petty.
When did I do that?
When I said "Are you?" before,
I was going to ask if you were going out
now that Sangnam went on a business trip!
I'll talk to you when you're sober.
When Sangnam comes back, move out.
Ha! I'm not moving out.
Why? You want this house?
How did you know?
I can't move out of such a nice house.
I'm going to stay and inherit this house.
I've been counting the days.
Didn't you see the circles on my calendar?
Buying a house in Korea is really tough.
I'm not going to miss this chance.
Look at my parents.
Subak ruined them.
They're in complete ruins!
Father... My poor father...
Mom... Mom...
Is this a monologue?
Father,
please stop hating me.
I don't want to but I keep making mistakes.
And I keep saying the wrong things.
This is my first time being married,
so can you please be more understanding...
I have to take the trash...
Hey!
Are you dead? Huh?
Please check the rest and send them.
- Okay, I will.
- Yes.
I'm working late again.
Don't wait up for me.
Ouch!
I...
Father.
Father, I'm so sorry.
I can't believe I got drunk and did all that.
I deserve to be beaten to death.
I'll gladly take any punishment you give me.
If you want me to put my arms up, I will.
If you want to whip my calves, you can.
I must have been out of my mind.
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry, father.
Father.
Father?
I've made soup for you.
You embarrassed me in front of everyone when you got drunk.
Poor me. Why do I bother living?
I'm leaving the house for a while.
I'm going to school.
Daebak,
what does your father do at school?
Why has he been so busy?
But he's not at school.
What?
I mean, I haven't seen him.
Tell me what that was about.
Why isn't your father at school?
I don't know.
Daebak!
Why that little...
Mother! Mother!
She's summoning me from her room.
You should go before she gets angry.
You should humor her now and teach her a lesson when she's better.
I will.
Of course. Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
What do you want?
Please sit down.
I'm sitting down. So what?
Where was that building?
What building?
Where you saw the man who looks like Bong.
Being stuck here is really frustrating.
Can you go and meet that security guard?
You're not doing it right.
Put some elbow grease on it!
Elbow grease!
- There, right there.
- Oh, okay.
You have to wipe it clean.
Okay, I will.
Get some fresh water.
That water's too dirty.
Okay.
Bong.
Mother.
Don't tell Anggeum since she's sick.
Get up right now.
Your back isn't broken!
It is.
Anggeum, how can you do this!
Bong quit school and he is working as a security guard!
Wha...
What did you say?
Mom!
That security guard was Bong?
He was down on his knees,
wiping the stairs clean.
This is all your fault!
Grandmother, let's talk outside.
Let go of me!
Mom, what did you say about Bong?
What do we do?
I don't need any of you!
I don't need you or your daughters!
You're sucking the life out of my son!
Mom, come out.
Look what your daughter Subak did to us!
Look what you did to my son, Bong!
If it weren't for you, he'd be happily retired!
This is all your fault!
You did that to Bong!
Divorce him! Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo!
- Mom, mom.
- Let go of me!
Let go!
Let me have the phone.
Call him later, mom.
Father had his reasons.
Give it to me!
Hello?
Is this school?
Can I talk to the president?
Mom.
I'm vice principal Wang Bong's wife.
How could you fire him like that?
Why couldn't you tell him in advance?
He gave his whole life to teaching,
but you fired him just like that?
He worked so hard for your school!
To him, school was most important.
In his sleep, when he was awake,
when it snowed or rained,
he only thought about the school.
What?
What was that?
You stay right there!
I'm sorry.
My wife's a bit upset.
I'll drop by later.
What did you do?
They gave you until the end of the month?
But you resigned?
Why didn't you beg them to let you stay?
What do we do now?
We don't have anything!
How could you quit your job?
Mom, stop it.
It's hard for father, too.
Then why did he have to resign?
He should've sucked up!
Fine. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for not sucking up.
Is being a teacher that great?
I guess I'm useless.
I'll go and kill myself!
Father.
Father!
Father, stop!
Father! Ouch...
Father...
You get out, too!
Why didn't you tell me?
It wouldn't have changed anything.
I could've gone to the school and begged.
You're really sly.
You broke up your sister's marriage
and didn't tell me about your father.
I don't know what you're thinking.
I can't love you. I just can't.
Get out! I don't want to see you.
Sedal, it's me. Doctor.
I need my doctor.
Okay. Wait for me.
Hobak didn't tell you?
I asked her about Subak,
but she wouldn't say a word.
So don't blame Hobak.
Then how did you find out?
I overheard you talking.
What happened?
What happened to our baby?
I'm sorry.
She should've been more careful.
How about my wife?
She's fine.
Man...
Sedal, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
That wasn't just any baby.
It was a bridge that connected us again.
I thought of it as a chance from god.
A chance for me to make up for everything.
Using the baby as an excuse,
I wanted to pamper you like a queen.
I'm sorry.
I'm not letting them get away with this.
Sedal!
Sedal, no!
Don't!
Mother, I can't believe you.
She was pregnant, didn't you know?
What?
Hobak is pregnant?
She had a miscarriage.
She's at the hospital now.
Her doctor told her to be careful,
but she took care of you, changing your diapers.
She withstood all your complaining,
she let you take everything out on her.
She changed your diapers, for god's sake!
So how could you hate her so much?
You're horrible.
Subak, you're horrible, too!
Is Hobak the only one you can order around?
You have Subak and Haebak.
What have you ever done for her?
When she got pregnant, we were so happy.
I wanted to treat Hobak well.
We're not coming back here again.
If I don't look after her,
you'll work her to death.
Goodbye.
You're driving me crazy.
I can't even stay here because of you.
Are you out of your mind?
Don't yell at Sedal.
Father.
You should've told us.
You silly girl.
You're too tight lipped for your own good.
Hobak, I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what to say.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
What about mom?
How could you leave her alone?
She fell down on her way here.
Really?
Subak is with her.
Your mom was crying.
Mom did?
Yes. She was sobbing.
She wants you to come over.
Father,
I want to see mom.
I'm coming right now.
Okay. Let's go.
Mom.
If I could get up,
I get down on my knees.
I don't know why I was so mean to you.
Maybe it's because you were an easy target.
I made you change my diapers.
I took my anger out on you.
Who would be a better daughter than you?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
I wasn't very sweet to you.
And I only cared about money.
I craved for your affections,
but I never did anything to deserve it.
Everyone deserves love.
All children deserve love.
I never even brushed your hair for you.
I'll be a good mother to you from now on.
I'll be good to you.
I love you.
I'm sorry and I love you.
Mom.
Oh, Hobak.
Subtitles by KBS World