Subtitles by KBS World
Father.
It's ice to meet you. I'm Wang Gwangbak.
My daughter in law.
It's you?
Why are you here?
What happened?
Why is this rude girl here?
- Get out of my house.
- Father!
I never want to see you again.
Get out!
What's wrong?
What happened?
What is it?
Remember that rude girl he was talking about?
It's her.
I don't understand.
Sangnam brought his girlfriend,
and she was that rude girl.
What? How could this be?
I know. I can't believe what happened.
This pot has history, so it's our family treasure.
What's going on?
Hobak's gone?
This is nuts. She won't answer my calls.
After I talked to her!
Why did she leave?
Why did she take the boys?
I know.
I really hope she doesn't do anything stupid, like in the news.
Like in the news?
People kill their children and themselves.
Oh, I'm too scared to even talk about it.
She won't die with the boys over a divorce.
She's just awful.
Call her parents. They would know.
She doesn't go there anymore.
Who knows? Maybe she told them.
Go in.
Alone?
Of course!
Then why did you come along?
Because I'm worried.
We'll wait for you here.
Okay. I'll be right out.
Sedal.
Yes, I'm here.
What's up?
You're here?
What's going on?
I was just passing by.
As if you're a traveler.
Welcome. Did you eat?
Not yet...
Get him some rice.
Okay.
Did you come alone?
There were three, but only I came in...
I mean, I was passing by alone.
Did Hobak pass by here before?
No, she didn't.
What's taking him so long?
What's he doing?
I'm hungry, mom.
Grilled dotted gizzard shads.
People say they bring wandering husbands back.
Okay.
Not husbands. Daughters in law.
The grilling smells so delicious that they come back, after running away.
Do they really bring back daughter in laws?
Of course.
Whoever it is, if they left home, that's it.
They won't come back to eat some fish,
unless they're a few bricks short of a load.
The fish is just an excuse.
Right. If they really hate you, they won't come back.
I can see why they would come back home.
I better get going.
Is that a new watch?
Yes.
You bought it?
You must be doing well.
That looks expensive.
Wow, this is the famous...
It's a knock off.
I know. But it looks just like the real one.
Have you ever seen a real one?
No way.
What took you so long?
They don't seem to know anything.
Mom, let's go grill dotted gizzard shads.
They bring daughter in laws back.
Should we file a missing person report?
She's not missing. She left me.
His law school degree is paying off.
So we file a runaway report?
Father, let's talk.
I have nothing to say to you.
I know how you feel.
I heard so much about that rude girl,
and even I would feel awful.
But I think there's been a misunderstanding.
What if I didn't?
I'll prove it. Just give her a chance.
You never really got to know her.
- Just meet her...
- There's no need!
I don't have to!
Then at least accept her apology.
Why would I do that?
My meeting her means I accept her apology,
and that means I accept her as my daughter in law,
which I have no intention of doing.
Father.
Don't mind me. Why do you care?
You're an adult. You can do as you please.
You don't mean that.
Why would you say that?
I can't believe you fell for a girl like her.
Father!
What do we do?
Aunt, what am I supposed to do?
I don't think an apology will do any good.
You and I both know how upset he's been about her.
I know, but she's not like that. You met her.
But I only met her once and you can't be sure.
Maybe she hasn't shown that side to you yet.
You only met her recently,
and women are good at hiding things.
Aunt, I know everyone has two sides.
But she's not like that.
If father talks to her, he'll be able to see.
But he's really angry at her.
She won't answer.
Where's Gwangbak?
Why won't she pick up?
She must be busy dating.
Gwangbak is seeing someone?
He came to say hello to the family.
Who? What does he do? What's he like?
Is he a doctor?
No, he only finished middle school.
What? Middle school?
What's wrong with her?
How can she meet a middle school graduate?
She's unemployed so she couldn't do better.
I feel sorry for her parents.
Poor Gwangbak.
Try calling her.
The person you called is unavailable...
Is she screening calls? She won't pick up.
Maybe she's embarrassed.
Let's see if she left any suicide note.
Why would you say such a horrible thing?
You want me to be on the news saying,
I did nothing wrong. I asked for a divorce,
and she just took the kids and left.
How could this happen to me?
Hey, don't film me!
How can you laugh?
Right. This is no time to laugh.
She wouldn't clean the apartment like this unless she's going to die.
This is nuts.
Yeongdal, take the kitchen. Mom, living room.
I'll take the master bedroom. Search!
Oh...
Oh, man.
She was in the Miss Korea Pageant.
I knew I'd seen her before.
Are you two an item?
No, she works for me.
I'd like an employee like her, too.
You're funny.
You didn't drink.
I don't drink when I'm working.
Oh, really?
But I have you.
So I'm drinking for you?
Just get the party going.
I'll give you any position you want.
That's it?
What is it? What is it you want?
I'm home.
Why can't you come home early?
Excuse me?
I think I'm coming down with something,
but neither his mom or dad would come home.
Am I the nanny?
He won't even go to sleep,
but I have no one to bark for him.
I'm sorry. I'll put him to sleep.
Since your wife is working, you should
come home early and look after your boy!
I know you don't deliver at night!
That's enough. He's had a long day.
Am I wrong?
They don't care if their mother's sick!
They just dump their kids on me!
Why are you yelling at Minjung?
Where is Subak?
It's her first day. She can't come home early.
I'll take Jungji.
Try to put him to sleep.
He keeps waking up every five minutes.
Subak was such a mild tempered baby,
and she'd fall asleep right after feeding.
I don't know why he's so sensitive.
Oh, this is crazy.
Did you have to say it like that?
Stop it. I'm dying here.
What?
What? What? You're so dull.
You're getting worse as you get older.
Look who's talking. You're the dull one.
Just listen to the stuff you say.
What's wrong with what I say?
Don't speak so harshly.
Minjung's still your son in law.
Even if he lives here, he's still a guest.
He's not a guest!
My friends and their son in laws are friends.
They make jokes with each other,
and they treat them like their own sons.
I don't think they should.
I think you must watch your manners.
Son in laws aren't really sons and daughter in laws aren't really daughters.
You can fight with your children,
but you can't do it with others children.
You should know that already.
Minjung and I aren't the same!
Why is that. He's someone's precious son.
So watch what you say to him.
Verbal violence leave deeper scars.
Try to be more caring towards me, your wife!
Who's going to be by your side at the end?
You'll regret it when you're really old.
Lie down.
Excuse me?
Lie down on your stomach.
Here. I'm lying down.
Oh.
I'll teach them a lesson.
How dare they use my old wife!
You will?
Of course.
You're my precious wife.
I can't believe my ears.
Oh, that feels good. Right there, there.
Come with me.
Bye.
Good job.
The investors really liked you.
You're my Miss Korea.
You're the only one who understands me.
How many years has it been?
Did you miss me?
Of course. Did you?
I never forgot you.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Stay a little longer.
I have golf early in the morning.
Fine.
You can come to work in the afternoon tomorrow.
Goodbye.
When did you get here?
What are you doing out here?
I was waiting for you because I got worried.
Are you my wife?
Like a wife who's waiting for her husband carrying a baby on her back.
It's embarrassing.
What if he catches a cold?
You're really clueless.
Did you drink?
There was a business meeting, for work.
You used to say this all the time.
Okay. I didn't say anything.
How did you get here?
The bus was just here.
Why do you want to know that?
It's dangerous to be out late.
I'll come and meet you from now on.
What for? Are you crazy?
They drive me home when it gets late.
Don't do this again.
It's over protective.
I'm home, father.
Why are you home so late?
There was a business dinner.
Did you drink?
They usually take you out to welcome you.
Don't you know what time it is?
You should've come home before ten.
You're a mom with two kids,
so how could you come home after midnight?
And all drunk!
Your mom is sick.
Why didn't you answer her call?
It was so loud that I didn't hear.
Your mom's old.
Babysitting isn't easy for her.
You should come home early for your kids instead of staying out until midnight.
You're not single.
Go upstairs.
Father, I'll come home early starting tomorrow.
Agh!
You scared me! What's wrong?
Oh... I had a nightmare.
You did? You're sweating.
This is going to kill the three of us.
Where did she go with the boys?
Let's report it to the police.
Mom, I think she's going to...
Going to do what?
Who's calling so late?
Is it Hobak?
I don't know this number.
Answer it.
Hello?
Hello? Please speak!
Hobak?
Hey, can you deliver noodles?
What the...
Sure, why not?
Ugh! This is nuts.
So?
He asked if I can deliver noodles.
Crazy bastard.
Hobak is so mean.
We're all worried sick.
She should at least call us!
Man...
- Ugh!
- Oh, my!
Mind your own business!
Why do you care if I'm barking like a dog?
Why do you care if I got dumped?
Why do you care if I get married?
- Let's not see each other again.
- Right.
Why do you keep doing this to me?
This is the worst coincidence.
We can't be together, can we?
I never want to see you again. Get out!
Come out.
Daese,
Sangnam's in love. Please say yes.
What you've seen may not be everything.
I know what I'm talking about.
What she did to me showed me who she is.
But you should meet her once and...
No. Once a rude girl, forever a rude girl.
You may not want to hear this.
I already went through it with your sister.
I knew who she was, but I thought she'd change.
But people don't change.
She was vain, unfaithful,
and she committed frauds and lied.
She never changed.
But that girl isn't my sister.
I trust Sangnam.
He wouldn't bring just anyone home.
You can decide after meeting her.
Don't do this.
Don't take Sangnam's side.
He's in love so he can't think straight,
but soon he'll realize the truth.
She's going to make Sangnam miserable.
Run over to the beach.
Let's see who wins! Ready, go!
I caught a crab!
You did?
Let me see.
Wow, it's a big one. Whoa!
Be careful.
Ganghwa-do Island? Why?
Just because. I brought the boys.
I didn't tell Sedal, though.
I heard he came last night but said nothing.
He probably went there to check.
I didn't answer his calls.
Should I come?
It's okay. I just want to be with the boys.
I'm using my vacation days.
Good for you.
Relax and have fun.
Don't tell anyone at home.
I don't want to worry father.
It's nice to see the boys have fun.
Why didn't I do this before?
I was so stupid.
I only focused on making money and didn't think to make memories with them.
Why in the world did I live like that?
What's more unbelievable is that
even though I lived like that,
I have nothing left anymore.
I was such a fool.
Hobak, don't blame yourself.
You've done really well.
From now on, do what you want to do.
Okay. Call me if you need anything.
Man...
Hey, Wang Hobak!
Where are you?
You think I'll let you get away with this?
How dare you take the boys?
Heh, Hello? Hello? I can't believe...
Your call will be forwarded to voice mail.
Oh, this is nuts!
Where are you?
Be quiet. You haven't learned anything!
If you scream again, I'm hanging up.
Oh, okay. I won't scream.
I'm furious,
but I'm trying to calm down. So answer me.
Where are you right now?
Are the boys safe? Tell me.
I don't have to.
Why did you call so many times?
Where are you?
I'm hanging up.
Okay, okay. I won't scream.
Don't call or ask questions. Just wait.
Wait until I feel like coming home.
What about the boys? Are they safe?
Yes. Your kids are safe, so don't worry.
Heh, heh, hello? Hello!
Hey, Wang Hobak! Ugh!
Hey! What are you doing?
Hey! Stop right there! Thief!
What did you call me? Thief?
Why did you kick my door?
Look at this! You burned my hair!
You brought bad luck!
You shouldn't be a hair dresser!
What? I shouldn't be?
I had a beauty salon in Myeongdong!
Why are you taking out your anger on me?
Your bad luck has nothing to do with your hair!
You want me to beat you up or something?
Are you trying to make me even angrier?
Look! Look how you burned my hair!
I want compensation!
Are you trying to get money off of me/
What? What did you say?
Am I trying to get money off of you?
Oh, my...
Hey, wake up. Wake up!
What happened?
You're alive, right?
Oh, my...
Mom, I'm going to work.
This late?
People might become suspicious.
Isn't that too short?
You're a mom.
Everyone says I have great legs.
Yours are just long. Her legs were pretty.
My legs?
They're not pretty anymore.
I used to get compliments on my legs.
Men followed me home because of my legs.
My legs were pretty, right, mother?
I was kidding.
Hey, Subak, what happened?
With what?
You said you'll find a woman for your uncle.
Oh, I'm asking around right now.
Don't get someone who's really poor.
You want a rich woman?
Right. And she can't be too ugly.
Rich and pretty women would love uncle.
Right?
I was kidding, too.
Okay. I'll try.
Aeji, I'll see you later.
Yes, mom. Bye bye!
You should try to find him a bride.
It's like you want him to die a bachelor.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
I'm sorry the class ran late.
Hurry up and deliver this.
Okay.
It's open.
Put it here.
Open the box.
You can't do it?
If I knew it was you, I wouldn't have come.
Why I'm a paying customer.
Where are the pickles?
You didn't bring any?
Pizza and pickles are like siblings.
How could you forget the pickles?
You're so stupid.
What?
Go get them. I can't eat pizza without them.
Or I want my money back.
Man.
Oh, man!
Here are the pizza's siblings.
I never heard pickles are pizza's siblings.
Man!
Gwangbak's uncle.
What is it?
Read it.
Man...
You little!
As you can see, I can't go out.
So help me out.
Man...
Can I help you?
Your wife sent you?
She's lucky to have such a caring husband.
Don't ever ask me to do this for you.
And why did you call me Gwangbak's uncle?
I'm your brother's friend. Don't call me that.
Thanks, Gwangbak's uncle.
So? Should I go alone?
Just wait.
For how long?
Stop whining. I'm trying to think here.
Fine. I'm going alone.
Would you like to go ahead without me?
I'll come after I sort things out here.
Okay. That watch.
- Yes?
- Give it back.
What did I just say?
To go ahead without you.
My darn mouth!
When I'm nervous, I just blurt things out.
I'm coming with, of course.
Give me one hour, Okay? Darling?
Whatever!
Oh, man. This is nuts.
Man!
I found a clam!
Where? How nice! Wow!
I didn't get anything.
What are you doing?
Ugh! You! You come back here!
My stomach hurts. You don't care if I die?
My head hurts. It's about to blow up.
When you come back, I'd be dead.
I think I'm going to die of anger.
What? What do you want? What is it?
I really am sick.
Whatever! I told you not to call me!
Hold on!
Tell me where you are and I'll feel better.
Hearing your voice made me feel better.
Tell me where you are and I'll get well.
Why do you want to know that?
I should know where you are!
I must know where my wife and sons are.
Since when were you so interested in me?
Mom, the water's coming in!
Come here! It's dangerous over there!
Bye!
Parcel service. Please sign here.
Where are you?
I need to see you. It won't take long.
Minjung.
What happened?
That's what I want to ask.
Why did someone else deliver to my house?
When I ran into your husband the other day,
it felt like someone smacked me in the head.
I kept forgetting it,
but when I saw him,
I realized you belong to someone else.
I don't think we should keep running into each other like this.
We each have our own families.
Are we doing something here?
But I don't feel comfortable.
I feel badly for your husband, a bit guilty.
I felt like I was caught stealing something that day and my heart was pounding.
I'm not a bold man.
I think I still have feelings for you.
That's why I feel this way.
I'm not going to deliver to your house until I feel nothing when I see you.
Don't worry about the deliveries.
Someone else can take care of it.
You're happily married,
so I don't want to cause troubles.
And your husband won't like it.
Minjung, actually...
Actually, I'm...
Hold that thought.
Parcel service.
I'm coming. I'll be there in 10 minutes.
Sunjeong, I have to go.
Oh, what were you going to say?
Huh? It's nothing. Go. You're busy.
I hope you're not hurt by what I said.
I'm doing this for you.
Be happy.
Minjung,
I missed you a lot after we broke up.
If you were dead, I could've forgotten you.
I would've looked for you, but I felt guilty.
I'm being honest.
I'm not asking for anything else.
I just want to keep seeing you.
Please.
Let me see you every now and then.
Seeing each other,
we're not allowed that.
We each have our own families.
I don't want to put my family at risk.
Giddy up! Ha! Ha!
I'm home.
Yes, Miho. Come here.
Mom, what's wrong?
I feel badly for you, Miho.
Mom, why would you feel that way?
I have you, uncle, Sangnam,
and even Daebak. Don't you agree?
Yes, you're right. I shouldn't feel that.
I can't breathe. Let me go.
Just one more minute, Miho.
I just want to hug you.
Dad, give me some more.
Okay, here. Eat up.
Mom, this is so good. This is the best!
Yes, yes! It's good!
Eat slowly. You'll get sick.
Mom, you eat, too. Ah!
Mmm, yum!
It's more delicious because you gave it to me.
Bangtong, why don't you give me a bite?
Have one more.
Isn't it good?
Bangtong, you shouldn't stare at people.
We have a dad, too.
If you like dad so much, go live with him!
I'm living with mom.
Mom, tell dad to come.
You, dad, Sintong and I are a family.
It's sad if anyone's missing.
Keep eating.
This is where we stand financially.
Who wants to do it?
You want to do rock, paper, scissors?
Go! Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors! Rock, paper, scissors!
Oh! Father! Father!
You two do it.
Stop it! You can't decide it this way!
Subak's our firstborn, so she can't.
And my baby son can't either!
You can't send two of your daughters to college and tell your only brother to quit.
Bong, do the right thing!
Loser, let's hang out!
Stop crying.
Who cares about a college degree?
You already have a future husband.
What do you mean by that?
You know what I mean.
Was that a proposal?
Sort of.
You're uncle's friend and you're younger.
Who cares about those things?
And it's only one year. I'm in law school.
The Constitution doesn't have anything about dating your younger uncle's friend.
Answer me. Will you marry me?
Tell me. Will you or not?
If you catch me, I'll tell you.
Man. We're shooting a movie now?
Hey! Hobak! Wang Hobak!
Oh, it's dangerous!
Hey, you'll get hurt!
Oh, what's this!
Sintong! Bangtong!
Dad!
Hello. It's me, Choi Sangnam.
Yes, hi.
I'm glad I ran into you here.
Have you had lunch yet?
I have.
If it's okay, may I buy you coffee?
No, thank you. I'm busy.
I'll visit you this weekend.
I'd like to see grandmother and mother.
Gwangbak hasn't told you anything?
Excuse me? Tell me what?
You should go.
Goodbye. I'll visit you.
Start the engine!
Okay.
It won't start?
Man.
Jangbi, where's Sangnam?
I don't know.
I didn't tell him anything.
I thought you told him about my father.
He seemed a bit unhappy.
He asked me if I heard anything.
Is there something you haven't told me?
No, of course not.
He probably felt awkward, running into you.
Okay.
You're sad, aren't you?
We should stick together.
Leave everything to me.
You made it snow, so of course I will.
Did you hire those men?
Yes. Let's meet there when it snows.
Under that street light.
Really? Promise me.
But what if your father doesn't say yes?
It doesn't matter. I'm moving out.
You can't.
My life with you is more important to me.
It's my life, not my fathers.
I'm not going to wait until next year.
Who is it?
I don't know. Maybe it's the magazine.
I'm Sangnam's father. Are you with Sangnam?
Excuse me?
Send Sangnam back to work right away.
Please don't ever meet my son again.
I'm sorry.
Please let me apologize to you in person.
I'm so sorry.
You and I will never meet again.
I don't have to tell you why, do I?
Don't ever see my son again.
father, I'll talk to you later.
I'm hanging up.
Father!
You're skipping work?
Have you lost it?
I finished everything. I'm disappointed in you.
How could you say such mean things to her?
What? You're disappointed in me?
That useless rude girl has turned you against me!
How dare you call her a useless rude girl!
She's the woman I'm dating.
I'm asking you not to pass judgment.
What? You're already siding with her?
You're making me side with her.
I didn't know you were like this!
If you really trusted me,
you would at least meet her once!
How could you make her leave crying?
You called her and told her not to see me.
You always speak of character and culture.
Is that what you meant by that?
What did you say? Huh?
How dare you talk back at me like this?
I'm very disappointed.
Hey! Choi Sangnam!
Stop! Stop right there!
I have nothing more to say!
Just who do you think you are!
Why I ought to... You!
Let go!
You let go first.
How dare you...
I said let go.
I didn't do anything wrong.
How dare you!
You've really lost your mind over that girl.
Stop it! What are you doing?
Let go. Let go!
Sangnam, you let go first.
How dare you! Come here!
Sangnam, rung! I'll hold him here!
You!
- Daese!
- You!
- You come back here!
- Stop!
- Daese!
- You!
- Daese, calm down!
Hey! Choi Sangnam!
Calm down!
Wang Gwangbak! Come out!
Be honest. You didn't tell him?
Father.
How could you be so childish?
Is this who you are?
You've been lying to both sides?
I was flustered when I ran into him.
How could you be so stupid?
Instead of doing what your father said,
you go behind my back and do what you want?
Was this why you didn't send the gifts back?
I can't break up with him, father.
Please let me marry him.
I told you why you two can't work.
You should've given it some thought.
You're well educated, so why can't you see?
Oh! Hello, uncle.
You shouldn't drop by like this.
Excuse me?
My brother said no to you, but if you keep coming here, it reflects badly on you.
My brother's headstrong.
Wait here. I'll get Gwangbak.
But this is the last time.
Gwangbak, come out. Your friend's here.
Who?
Yeongdal.
Tell her to come in.
She can't. Gwangbak.
Tell her I'm not home. I can't see her.
She wants to ask you something. Come out.
Just listen to me.
Go.
Follow me.
How could you lie about that?
I'm sorry.
We should be on each other's side.
How could you lie?
How long were you planning on lying to me?
I was worried
that you were hurt because of my father,
and I was bringing you flowers.
I was going to ask you to give me some time
because I can change my father's mind.
I was going to tell you not to worry.
I was trying to change my father's mind.
I couldn't tell you because it'd hurt you.
We should break up.
Sangnam.
I can beat my father, but you can't.
And there's nothing you can do here.
We're not meant to be together.
Ending this here will be better for...
No! This isn't right!
I'm not good enough for you.
I must have been dreaming.
You and I are too different.
Our family and educational background,
and our jobs.
I only finished middle school,
and I grew up in a broken family.
Don't say that.
You said I have emotional scars.
You grew up in a normal family,
so you'd never understand.
My inferiority complex will torture you.
Your parents are right.
How can a middle school graduate marry a former teacher and a future writer?
That's nonsense.
Let's pretend this never happened.
Don't! Those things don't matter.
I can persuade my family.
No.
Persuasion won't work here.
It's how things are.
No, this can't be!
This is too hard for me. I'm going.
How could you...
I won't break up with you.
Don't leave me, please!
What am I supposed to do?
We're in love and that's all that matters.
We're both adults.
We don't need our parents permissions.
Please don't do this to me. Please!
Subtitles by KBS World
I'm disappointed in you! You are two faced!
Please let me breathe.
What do you mean by that?
See me free for one month.
What happened to Hobak is mostly your fault.
What?
You're not a good mother.
I even feel ashamed. My heart is breaking.