Subtitles by KBS World
Yes, Subak, what is it?
Father, mom's hurt.
What?
She fell down and we're at the hospital.
But why? Why wasn't she more careful?
How serious is it?
What did the doctor say?
She's getting x-rays and she hurt her back.
What?
That's not good!
Please hurry over.
I can't come right now...
Make sure she gets through the tests okay,
and take good care of her.
If she needs to be hospitalized, help her.
And call me when something changes.
I want mom!
I want grandmother!
You need to come right now. Hurry.
Okay, Minjung.
How bad is it?
Does she need surgery?
No, it's a hairline fracture to the pelvis.
Right here.
What do we do now?
We have to wait until it heals.
Does she need to be hospitalized?
It's up to you.
But there's nothing much we can do for her.
She needs to stay in bed until it heals.
I'm going home.
I'm not wasting money to stay here.
But it'll be more comfortable here for you.
But all I have to do is wait, right?
That's right.
Ouch, being here won't speed it up,
so I want to lie down at home.
Nothing gets done without me.
You can't mom, mom.
Don't worry about me.
Subak, go and bring the kids back.
How dare you feed my boy?
How dare you hold my child?
Aeji!
She just fell asleep.
Aeji's having a hard time, too.
Then why did you bring them here?
You're scaring the kids.
You...
Are you kidding me?
Don't mess with me.
I'm about to lose my mind,
so start packing.
I can't do that.
You want to pick a fight?
They are my kids.
And I'm taking them, so stay out of it.
But they are Minjung's kids, too.
You should talk to Minjung first.
What?
I don't believe this.
You think dropping his name will stop me?
Disgusting.
Give him back to me. I was feeding him.
Stop it!
How dare you try to win my kids over?
You think you can get them, too?
You're shameless!
Aeji, wake up!
Mom!
Aeji, carry this.
Let's go.
Hold on. Wait.
Minjung, you should come home.
He doesn't have to!
I'm taking my kids, so stay out of this!
You all stay out!
What should I do?
I'll be right there.
Don't let them leave.
You can't leave like this!
Then how should I leave?
Should I break everything up and beat you?
If you have a conscience, you can't do this.
You think you could become their mom?
Dream on!
Aeji and Jungji are my kids.
Let's go.
- Where's dad?
- Be quiet.
Why can't you even walk right?
Get up!
Oh, no.
Did you see?
Did you see what you did?
It must hurt.
Let's go home and put some ointment on.
Did you tell him to bring the kids?
Aeji can hear you.
Kids are smart so don't speak like that.
You're ashamed?
I'm not.
Let's go. I'll walk you home.
Aeji,
get on my back.
Where are the kids?
I took them home.
What are you doing?
Why did you take the kids?
Bring them out.
Did she tell you to bring them back?
She's really sly.
Sly fox who acts like she's an angel.
You don't know her.
Aeji!
Aeji's hurt.
Why? How bad is it?
Dad!
What happened?
I fell down.
- Does it hurt a lot?
- Yes.
My mom's hurt, too.
How?
Because of you. Because of you two!
She fell and cracked her pelvis chasing you.
She can't even move now.
Oh, Minjung.
Why did you take the kids?
How do you feel?
Who cares about how I feel?
How will you raise them?
It wasn't his idea.
It was hers.
She's saying she'll raise the kids
because she wants to have you,
but she'll only be a step mom.
I've seen some unbelievable things happen,
but I can't watch my precious grandkids
being raised by a step mom.
Their real mom is right here,
so how could I do that?
Enough said.
I'm raising the kids.
We should do as we agreed before.
You gave all of them to me, remember?
That was then.
Do you always keep your words?
Situations can change things.
I'm their mom, no matter how bad I am.
I don't care if you get remarried.
Just let me keep the kids.
If not, I don't know what I'll do.
Go easy on him.
How can I go easy on him?
People might think you're fighting.
If we need to, we can fight.
I'm sorry I have to say it here,
but I can't let a woman like you raise them.
What did I ever do?
Subak.
Stop it! I can't even talk?
Shut up.
You're qualified to raise them.
How about you? You're qualified?
Subak!
Mom, you stay out.
You don't know anything.
I do!
Minjung, you should go.
Don't pay attention to what Subak says.
What's wrong with you?
Why don't we talk about this?
You think you're qualified?
You made her take care of your father and conspired to divorce me.
What right do you have?
Isn't that a crime?
You're out of your mind!
He's blaming me for everything here!
Be honest with me.
How did you feel?
When you tricked me into believing that?
Were you glad? Were you happy?
Subak, please.
Minjung, she's gone mad, so just go.
I made mistakes, but you did, too,
so let's call it even.
I'd rather die than hand my kids over to her.
You should be quiet.
Why should I be?
Subak.
Why do you keep cutting me off, mom?
I'm sorry you got hurt because of me.
Leave the kids here for now.
Your place is too cold for the kids.
I'm moving to an apartment.
Then take them after you move, okay?
Do it for me.
I'll take them after I move.
Forget it!
Ouch!
My whole body aches!
I should just kill you!
What's wrong?
You weren't looking at land, were you?
I can't believe how dense I was...
How can you cheat on him?
You're a mom!
I'm afraid the neighbors might find out.
You deserved what you got.
It wasn't like that.
Minjung knew about it really early.
If your father finds out, he'll go nuts.
You! Ouch!
Stop! What if your pelvis breaks?
Who cares about that?
I can't believe how shameless you are.
How can you scream at Minjung like that?
He cheated on me, too!
What?
Who are you?
You used to get horrible grades,
but look how calculating you are!
Why do you always talk about my grades?
I made a mistake, but he intended it.
And that's worse.
He knows about the other thing, too.
What other thing?
You know what.
I don't even want to talk about it.
He submitted the papers because of that.
How did he find out?
What do you think?
Was it Hobak?
She said no, but who else could it be?
How's mom?
Was it you?
What do you mean?
You told him, right?
Tell him what?
Even mom said that. Stop it!
It wasn't me.
Who else could tell him?
How's your mom?
Father.
Oh, dear.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
This is my dream come true.
Lying on my back, having my husband feed me.
I'm going to enjoy this.
That mouth of yours is unbelievable.
I feel lost here.
You feel lost because I'm lying on my back?
How can we do anything now?
What about our meals?
Try taking care of yourselves.
What did the doctor say?
It's a hairline fracture, so she can't move.
Why didn't you check into the hospital?
I told her to do so, but she didn't want to.
Being hospitalized won't help me heal!
What about the money?
Who would take care of me?
I'd rather have Subak do it at home.
Quit your job and take care of your mom.
I already talked to my boss.
Anggeum, you're too old to run around!
Bong, you be careful, too.
Old people must be careful.
I'm sorry for being old.
I should just die.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
How could you leave your post?
I was at the bathroom.
I've been standing here for over an hour.
I'm sorry. My wife got hurt.
Being a former vice principal,
I thought you'd be a hard worker.
This won't happen again.
I'm sorry.
Mom!
Hi.
How serious is it?
See for yourself.
Mom!
I'm not a spectacle.
How did it happen?
A hairline fracture?
I'm going to be pampered now.
Don't cry. This is great.
I'm so upset.
Why are bad things happening to us?
Mom, eat.
Oh, ouch...
- Is it hot?
- It is.
Give me a little bit at a time.
Hold on.
I can't work anymore.
I know.
I wanted to buy father a house.
I guess I'll have to win the lottery.
Why are these things happening now?
I should go.
It must be uncomfortable for you.
Actually...
Subak, I'm sorry.
Why should you be?
Why does it have to be her?
You're home.
At least I can say goodbye.
Goodbye.
Hold on.
You must hate me, but I want to tell you this much.
Nothing happened before the divorce.
I don't want to hear it.
But you believe your brother in law, right?
Remember what you told me?
He is a better person than your sister?
That was when I didn't know about this.
He never once tried anything with me.
I looked after his father,
but he just needed my help. That was it.
He was actually very cold to me.
He didn't even call me right after his divorce.
Please believe me.
I don't like hearing you defending him.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it like that.
I should go.
Be happy with Sangnam.
Your father in law is hot tempered and loud,
but he's soft inside.
Try to get along with him.
Thank you for everything and I'm sorry.
Miho.
Mom!
Let's go.
Where are we?
Our home.
We'll live here until we move to the apartment.
Just the two of us?
No, with Mr. Ko.
And maybe his kids.
- Miho, is it okay?
- Yes, I'm glad.
But I didn't get to say goodbye.
You can do it later.
I only want one thing.
Just to be happy with Sangnam. That's it.
You have to brace yourself.
Sleep well and eat well.
You'll live here for a long time.
Oh, no...
I know how hard it must be for you.
Aunt moved out?
I heard what happened.
Are you sick?
Yes. My heart and my body.
I ache all over.
How could this happen?
Why does it have to be Subak?
I'm sorry it had to be Subak.
I heard thorns in your words.
My aunt didn't start it, I'm sure.
You have to believe it.
Did you say something to her?
Don't you think what you did was wrong?
How could you go after a married man?
He was married to my sister.
How could you break up their marriage?
How did it feel to see me every day?
Have you no conscience?
You said those things?
I wish I did,
but I couldn't.
I understand how you feel.
But I hope you don't hate my aunt.
You understand how I feel?
You shouldn't be so sure.
Even I don't know that, so how could you?
I've been relying on aunt,
and how it ended breaks my heart.
How will I live without her?
But I can't be on her side.
Even if she and Minjung had every right,
even if it was all Subak's fault,
I still have to side with Subak.
Because she's family.
My sister.
Aunt is the winner now,
and my sister lost.
Miho.
Mr. Ko.
I brought pizza.
Thank you.
Go wash your hands for dinner.
I'm happy to have Miho here.
It feels like the place is full.
That's because this is a tiny place.
Miho, I'm sorry you don't have your own room.
It's okay.
Mom and I've been roommates all this time.
I just hope you don't snore.
When we move, my kids will come, too.
That's okay. I'm glad.
I can take care of Jungji.
It's snowing.
Should we go and watch?
Let's go, mom.
Oh, my!
It's so pretty.
I get worried when it snows.
You're still a kid at heart.
Right.
If you start worrying over snow, you're old.
We're getting a lot of snow this winter.
Mom, it's so nice here.
Isn't it?
Minjung, isn't it weird?
When something good happens, it snows.
I thought of that, too.
Snow is very special for us.
One, two, three.
Mom, do they sell dads anywhere?
I wish we could buy us a dad.
How is your mother?
The same.
She's frustrated. And she nags.
I'm sure.
She's great at saying mean things.
Your doctor told you to be careful.
What could I do?
What do you mean?
Don't go to your mother's house.
She orders you around, so why do you go?
Tell her you're busy.
You're pregnant.
What's Subak doing?
She quit her job.
Ouch...
Should I rub your shoulders?
- Channel 5.
- Okay.
- It's boring. Channel 9.
- Channel 7.
- 7?
Channel 7.
- That looks good.
- Okay.
Eat.
There you go.
- Head.
- Head?
There's no channel head.
Your head's in the way.
- Okay.
- Mmm.
- Ah!
- Okay.
Tada. Ah...
What are you doing?
Are you the remote control?
She's tired.
Even if she is!
How can the wife lie on her back
and order her husband to change the channels,
move his head, and feed strawberries to her?
I can't watch it anymore.
I feel sad because I have no husband.
You don't know anything.
She's preg...
She's what?
Huh?
Don't ask. You should already know.
What?
Pass.
Hobak, you shouldn't act this way.
You think you're special because you work,
but I went back to work after giving birth.
Mother, don't talk about the old days.
My grandmother and mother used to fight over that.
You're just like your mom.
You picked up her bad habits.
You talk just like your mom.
We are mother and daughter.
We are bound to be alike.
Mom, don't mind us and go to your room.
- Awful boy!
- Ouch!
You're making me want to get a husband!
Oh, this is nutty, nutty, nuts.
That stung.
Should I look for a man for you?
I don't really need that.
Don't.
Why not? Mother's pretty young.
Forget it.
Mom will live with us forever.
Right, mom?
You should live by yourselves.
Why do you want to include me?
- Noodles.
- Okay.
Here.
I brought you noodles, your highness.
It's been a while, right?
Say hi to the pot.
I don't want to.
It's old. Throw it away.
No.
This pot looks like you.
Me?
I can't throw it out because I love it.
That's you. Eat up.
You did a good job.
But about mother...
Stop it.
You know what I was going to say?
You want my mom to get married?
No, thanks.
Why not?
Mother's still young, so she should remarry.
She had a hard life raising you,
so she should live her life now.
I think she's interested.
I should've talked to her about it.
After Yeongdal got married, she became...
What?
I don't want you to talk about my mom.
How do you feel?
Why did you come home so late?
I meant to come home early,
but I had a lot of work.
You should come home early at a time like this.
Does it hurt a lot?
I'm lying here,
and I don't have to do anything,
so I want to relax and enjoy it,
but it's like torture.
It's more frustrating than painful.
When I was young, I healed quicker,
but now that I'm old, I'm useless.
Using the bathroom must be a problem.
It's more than a problem.
Having to wear a diaper is pathetic and humiliating.
I can't ask Subak to help.
You should. She should be glad to help.
She's my daughter, but I'm not comfortable.
I'm embarrassed and I feel sorry.
I feel more comfortable with you.
Can't you take some time off?
Isn't this spring break?
Well...
Remember?
I'm working on a project.
Did you hear?
Old Geezer got fired.
- He did?
- Yes.
Says who?
Everyone knows.
He wasn't at the staff room.
We're getting a new vice principal.
I hope the next one's not like Old Geezer.
Father, where are you?
What do you think?
At school.
I know you're not at school.
Tell me where you are. Hurry.
Yes?
Give me my package please.
Okay.
Here it is.
Why couldn't you just bring it?
The guy before used to do it.
I told you several times.
I can't leave my post.
Unbelievable.
Your paycheck comes from my maintenance fee, so how can you say that?
Honey, what's wrong?
What happened?
He wouldn't bring the package up.
Why couldn't you do that?
It's hard to go up and down the stairs.
Mr. Wang!
Oh, uh...
It's been a while.
How are you?
What happened?
You're the security guard here?
It just happened.
I didn't hear about your retirement.
It's about time. I'm pretty old.
It was too boring to just stay home.
Uh, okay.
Don't cry.
Dad.
You got fired?
I didn't, so don't let it bother you.
You don't believe me?
I do.
I respect you the most in this world.
Thanks.
Don't tell anyone, not when mom's sick.
Okay.
But isn't this too hard for you?
It isn't. It's actually fun.
Dad,
stay strong.
You have me.
I'll grow up quickly and take good care of you.
Ugh!
I can't eat anymore.
I can't even take a shower.
I feel too dirty to eat.
And I have indigestion.
Bring me a wet towel or something.
Don't get so angry.
I boiled some water.
Huh?
Did you use all the hot water?
Yes. I washed my hair.
Subak, my stomach seems bigger, right?
Didn't I tell you?
I won't talk to you if you call my name.
You're funny.
I'm your aunt and 5th in rank.
And you're below me.
That's enough.
You want me to beat the crap out of you?
I can't believe what you just said!
How dare you speak like that to your aunt?
Maybe I should teach you a lesson!
I've been keeping quiet until now.
What?
Be careful.
If I open my mouth, you're dead.
You...
What's going on?
Subak is being really rude.
And she orders me around.
What?
Huh? When did I do that?
Grandmother, I didn't.
Aunt, when was I ever rude to you?
What? You were!
You were glaring at me!
Oh, don't joke around.
Aunt, please do the dishes.
I'm so busy.
But she's pregnant.
Grandmother, you had babies, too.
Is sitting all day good for you?
Not really.
Right?
Aunt, please come out.
Don't work too hard.
Take it easy.
Just until Anggeum gets better.
Ugh.
My princess, what are you doing?
Calling me your princess is useless!
I'm more like a servant girl.
My princess is doing the chores?
Come out.
I'll get yelled at.
Even mother is on Subak's side.
Don, can you yell at Subak?
She orders me around and never calls me aunt.
She says, "I'll kill you!"
What?
How dare she!
Subak! Ugh!
Subak, can I see you?
Why?
Just come out.
What is it?
When I tell you to come out, just come out.
What?
Hurry up!
What is it?
Subak,
can you do me a big favor?
Think of how you're making me look here.
Yeongdal married me out of love,
so if you're mean, how could she live here?
Can you please treat her as your aunt?
But she doesn't deserve it.
That's why I'm begging here.
Subak, please?
Tell her not to disrespect me either.
Okay. I'll talk to her.
So please be nice to her, okay?
Subak, you're so pretty.
No wonder you were in the Miss Korea pageant.
Got it? You better do as I say!
Did you hear that?
Don, you're the best!
She'll respect you as her aunt.
So you should act like her aunt, too.
She's an adult, so treat her as one.
You're her younger sister's friend.
What should I call her?
Miss Subak?
Miss Subak sounds so funny.
My princess, got it?
I'm leaving.
If you're done here, fold the laundry, aunt.
Didn't Don talk to you?
He did.
That's why I'm calling you aunt.
I'm not glad to see you.
But it's not your fault.
It's your aunt's fault.
How could she break up a family like that?
She didn't. You're mistaken.
Are you defending your aunt?
Go. I don't want to hear it.
Mother, here.
Take care of yourself and get well soon.
What is it?
Uh...
Can I learn how to operate an excavator?
An excavator? Why?
I need to make money.
I'm going to get our house back.
You're still too young to make money.
I'm not.
Wait until you graduate from high school.
If you still want to then, I'll teach you.
You're in 9th grade right now.
Nobody will hire you.
And you're too young to get a license.
I understand how you feel,
so you should continue to study.
And don't worry about your family.
Mr. Bong,
the toilet's clogged.
What?
Jungji, chow time.
Subak, help.
Huh?
Why? Is something wrong?
My stomach's been hurting...
Oh, this is bad.
What do we do?
This is bad.
Help me get up.
Oh, no!
The doctor said not to move.
What do we do?
Why can't she do it?
Why can't she look after her own mom?
You cleaned after her, so she should do it.
Hobak, can you come right now?
Why?
Mom needs to go.
Oh...
Then you should help her.
I can't!
I can't leave her like that!
Oh, this is crazy.
Oh, boy...
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Anggeum, are you sleeping?
Please leave.
The rice is so good. Try it.
I said leave.
What's that smell?
Oh, Jungji, did you go poo poo?
I said leave!
Just hold on.
Jungji, let me check your diaper.
Didn't I tell you to leave. Leave!
It's clean.
Then what's this smell?
Get out!
Subak.
Go in.
- Did you boil some water?
- Yes, I did.
You need a towel, right?
Oh, this is horrible!
Hobak, hurry, hurry!
Mom,
let me see you.
Oh, this is so sad.
This is so horrible.
It's okay. I'm your daughter.
Oh...
I can't believe this.
All patients are the same.
Go to the hospital and see for yourself.
You're a patient, so don't be embarrassed.
No one can live without pooing.
Hobak, water. Ugh...
Ugh...
You must relax.
I told you to be careful.
The fetus isn't very healthy,
so don't get stressed out or work too hard.
You have to take time off.
Do you have stomach trouble?
That's because you haven't eaten all day.
I thought I wouldn't get morning sickness.
How is your mother?
She can't move.
That must be hard on you.
Hi.
It's me.
Minjung, welcome.
You must be busy.
I wanted to check on you.
I wish I were dead.
It's like prison.
Mom, lunch.
Minjung, did you eat lunch?
Not yet...
Subak, get Minjung some lunch. Hurry.
- It's okay.
- It's not. Hurry.
Minjung, I'm sorry.
What Subak did,
I know nothing can make up for that.
It's my fault. Can you please...
I don't want to talk about it.
I hope you get well soon.
You got hurt because of me and I'm sorry.
Goodbye.
Oh...
Don't do it.
It's done. Stay and eat.
Jangbi, let's go.
Let me finish this up.
Who did you go drinking with last night?
Somebody.
A woman?
I haven't been dating for a while now.
I met a friend.
Which friend?
Gwangbak's father?
Yes.
Things aren't working out for him.
What do you mean?
Should I tell you or not?
I think you should know.
You,
what did you do with the holiday bonus?
Excuse me?
The holiday bonus Sangnam gave you.
Did you spend it or put it in the bank?
He got a bonus?
I don't know anything about it, father.
You don't?
He didn't give it to you?
Father, you're home?
Come with me.
What is it?
The bonus.
What are you doing?
Okay!
Did you know?
About what?
About Gwangbak's family losing their house.
How did you find out?
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want to worry you.
What did you do with the holiday bonus?
Excuse me?
Did you give it to them?
Gwangbak's mother's sick, so I did.
I knew it.
You're sneaking money to them now?
It's not like that.
My mother in law got hurt, so I thought...
What did you say when you got married?
You said you won't give any money.
But this is a special circumstance.
Gwangbak's father quit his job, I heard.
What?
His family doesn't know but he's working as a security guard.
I shouldn't have let you marry her.
Really?
Shh.
Oh, poor father.
Subak, you didn't know?
I didn't.
He goes to work every morning,
so nobody knew.
I can see why he kept it a secret.
Poor father...
He's pretending to go to school.
I'm sure he feels miserable.
How sad? What do we do?
We can't cry.
Let's pretend we know nothing.
Let's wait until he tells us.
- Father.
What are you doing out here?
We were waiting for you.
Father, you must be tired.
He's not! He sits all day at school.
Right. All he does is scold the bad students.
Or is it bad teachers?
Gwangbak, why are you here?
I came to check on mom.
You shouldn't come here so often.
Hobak, thank you.
You must be busy.
It's okay.
Father, I've boiled some water. Go wash up.
Okay.
Father, I should go.
- I'm leaving.
- Okay.
Hobak, thank you.
- Don't worry about it.
- Bye, father.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
Go.
Father, let's go in.
Don't.
I didn't boil that for you.
Let me use some.
Then you should boil your own water.
You're so mean!
I have a bad temper.
So I'm mean to those who deserve it.
You act like you're the queen of this house,
but I won't let you get away with that.
Oh, my!
So? Why don't you go tell grandmother?
Is there some hot water?
Mom needs a bath.
- Use this.
- Okay.
Subak, I'll get you for this!
I was nice because I felt sorry for you!
Did you hear?
She's driving me mad.
Even she is being disrespectful.
Did Minjung drop by?
He felt badly, so he came to check on mom.
What did he say?
He won't talk to me.
He won't even look at me.
Why don't you go see her, then?
Talk to her, woman to woman,
and tell her how you feel. Who knows?
You have two kids.
Oh!
Cold.
What's that?
A chair.
I found it at the recycling bin. It's like new.
Where are you going with that?
Hobak's parent's house.
I'm bringing this for her mom.
I think this could help her sit up.
As if she'd appreciate it!
You closed the shop already?
I'm going to get Yeongdal at the sauna.
I'll be back.
I wish you took such good care of me, too!
I'll find something nicer for you later.
Oh, mom, this is really comfortable.
When your back feels better, you can sit here.
Did you find it somewhere?
Yes, at my apartment complex.
I thought you could use it.
Good for you.
Now you'll rummage through all trash cans.
I'm not using that.
Who knows where it came from?
But it's clean.
It's better to sit on this than the floor.
Of course. Let me sit.
Oh, this is nice!
It's awesome, mother.
Then you should take it.
But his back is fine.
Too fine. That's how the baby...
You were made for each other.
Why couldn't you buy me a new one?
I don't want things people threw out.
Wash the blankets before you go.
Make some side dishes, give Jungji a bath,
and make dinner for your father.
Mother, you should tell Subak to...
Okay, mom.
Where's Subak?
I didn't see her.
She had to go somewhere.
Thank you for coming.
I came here to beg.
Ms. Oh,
can you please give him back to me?
I'm so sorry.
I acted like that because I was cornered.
I can't live without Minjung.
I was stupid before,
so I didn't know how important he was.
But now that I've lost him, I know.
I want to start again with him.
You know he won't abandon his kids.
You're a woman, too...
Can you please be more understanding?
I'm sorry.
There's a reason why I can't back down.
What reason?
But you have nothing on him.
I have two kids.
What reason could top that?
I'm begging you.
I'm so sorry.
I was bad to Minjung,
and I was bad to you.
I'll be grateful for the rest of my life.
I came here tonight to let you know where I stand.
Please don't call me anymore.
And please know that I have a good reason.
Goodbye.
Ms. Oh, Ms. Oh!
Ms. Oh...
Mom.
It's cold. Why are you out here?
I was waiting for you with Mr. Ko.
Where were you?
Out.
I met someone.
Mom, something's fishy.
I know.
Then call the police, why don't you!
Let's go in.
Let's go in. It's cold.
Oh, man!
The more the think about it, the angrier I get.
Why do you have to do everything?
Who else could do it?
Subak!
Let her favorite daughter take care of her.
Why should you do it?
What has your mother done for you?
Why do you have to clean up after her?
This is nuts.
You have no feelings?
Oh, I don't. That's why I live with you.
You...
Your mother is shameless. And Subak, too.
What have they done for you? Nothing!
Subak can't do it alone.
She has to raise the kids and run the house.
She's gotten better.
She couldn't even wash her own undies before.
Unbelievable.
I talked to the director.
I'm taking the afternoons off for my mom.
But you're pregnant.
You didn't tell her that?
What for?
- Tell her.
- Stop it.
Should I tell her?
It'll only be a few weeks.
She says I make her feel comfortable.
Only when she needs help, right?
When she's fine, she turns to Subak,
but when she needs help, she turns to you!
I don't believe this.
That's your problem.
You think you're the only one who can help.
The Earth can rotate fine without you.
You think it would stop if you weren't here?
I did think it would stop.
I can't believe you're laughing.
I'm going nuts here.
Nothing better happen to you, okay?
What's gotten into you?
I can't believe you're worried about me.
Oh, I feel chilly.
Get me another blanket.
Aren't you catching a cold?
I don't know.
This is bad.
You can't even take medicine.
Oh, now I hate Subak!
Ask anyone.
Why would you have to go there and
do all the work when your mom never loved you?
Subak's funny.
Why can't she clean her dear mom's poop?
You shouldn't go there.
Let them take care of themselves.
Who cares if she poos on herself?
Don't be.
Be nice if you want a pretty baby.
Don't let anything happen to the baby, okay?
This is nuts.
Where is it?
Father, are you looking for something?
Yes. I don't see any hallabong oranges.
You ate the last one a few days ago.
I did?
I think some side dishes are missing, too.
Your aunt's absence is showing.
Did you take them to your parents?
Excuse me?
If you didn't, forget it.
Oh, my! Bong!
Where are you coming from/
Mother wanted some roasted sweet potatoes.
How are you, Mrs. Park?
Not good.
Please tell her to stop bothering Yeongdal.
I mean your eldest daughter.
I almost went to beat her up.
She won't let Yeongdal use hot water,
so I had to take her to the sauna.
I'll talk to Subak.
Mom, later.
When later? I should say it now.
How can she make Yeongdal work when she's pregnant?
What if something goes wrong?
She's in no place to act that way!
She lost the house, got divorced because she had an affair...
What did you just say?
Oh, mom!
It's not like I made that up.
Dad, you're home.
Did you have an affair?
That's why he divorced you?
Father!
- Oh, no!
- Let's go.
- Father! Father!
- Come with me.
Father!
Father.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Get on your knees! Right now!
What are you doing?
Hurry!
Beg him for forgiveness.
Beg for forgiveness in front of me.
I'm sorry, Minjung.
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry.
I did a bad job raising her.
Everything is my fault.
I'm begging you to forgive me.
Don't do this. You can't do this.
No, this is my fault.
Don't do this, please!
When you were getting divorced,
I suspected it was Subak's fault,
but I never thought it could be that.
We deceived you when you got married.
At that time, I was conflicted.
Should I tell you or keep my mouth shut?
I made a cowardly choice.
I prayed you'd never find out,
and when time passed, I forgot about it.
This is the kind of person I am.
I'm ashamed to face you and the world.
I can't believe I was a vice principal...
Please forgive my idiot daughter.
Do it for me, please.
Subtitles by KBS World
You were caught cheating on your husband!
You're driving me crazy!
You think it's easy to deal with you?
Excuse me, there!
How do you know if he's a good man?
Please take pity on me.
I'll be good to you!
- You came.
- I heard you were sick.
Thank you for coming.
How can you blame my aunt for everything?
How can you say that?
Why didn't you come home?
I worked until morning.
I didn't know you could lie.
This is all your fault!
Let's talk outside.
Let go of me!
Divorce my son!
Ouch, oh, Sedal!