Subtitles by KBS World
We're getting a divorce.
I'm very sorry.
Did you discuss it with Subak?
Or is it just you?
We agreed on it a long time ago.
To be honest, the reason I didn't come home wasn't because I was busy.
I needed time to think about it.
This is so out of the blue.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you getting a divorce?
Tell us what this is about.
Did Subak do something wrong?
Tell us. It's okay.
She didn't do anything wrong.
Then why is it?
Things are starting to get better for you.
So what's the reason?
Is there someone else?
Don't say that.
What else could it be?
Minjung wouldn't just ask for a divorce.
I'm totally heartbroken.
Just tell us the truth.
I'm really sorry.
Please forgive me.
It's all my fault.
Don't say that.
What about the kids?
How can you do this to them?
I was really worried about them and gave it a lot of thought.
Mother,
please take good care of Aeji and Jungji.
I'll pay child support,
and I'll pay you for your time.
Will you raise them until they enter elementary school?
I don't think I can work with peace of mind if someone else took care of them.
I know it's wrong of me to ask that of you,
but mother, please, I'm begging you.
I'll take them when they enter elementary school.
Goodbye.
Oh, Minjung! Oh, you can't divorce her.
You can never divorce her.
Is it because of me?
I've been horrible to you.
I'm begging you, please don't.
We can't live without you.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Minjung! Minjung! Oh!
Minjung, don't go.
Don't go, for me.
What will I do if you leave like this?
Minjung, whatever it is, I'll take care of it.
I'll fix Subak, okay?
I can't live without you.
How can you leave like this?
Let him go.
How can I? How?
You have nowhere to go.
It's freezing. Where will you go?
Say something! Tell him not to go!
You should go. We'll talk later.
Goodbye.
Minjung! Minjung!
Minjung...
Why did you come here?
I told them everything.
Told them what? What?
About our divorce.
Why did you tell them?
We could've done it in secret.
How much did you tell them?
I asked how much!
What are you afraid of?
I'm not afraid!
I just don't want to stir things up.
We decided to keep it between us.
I never promised you anything.
Must we pinky swear?
You should've known better.
So you told them?
You want my father to kill me?
Then why did you do it?
What did I do?
I didn't. It's too filthy for my mouth.
We'll make it official tomorrow.
Oh, man.
What's the reason?
There's no reason. Just because.
Just because?
Who gets divorced just because?
Is marriage a joke?
When did you first talk about it?
Who brought it up first?
A while ago.
We pushed it off because of Gwangbak's wedding.
Why did he come here and stir things up?
He's thoughtless.
You're the thoughtless one.
How could you try to get a divorce behind your parents back?
Who brought it up first?
I did.
What?
I mean, Minjung did.
What did you do to make him want to?
I didn't do anything.
Be honest!
You must have done something!
I said I didn't! That hurt!
I won't get mad, so tell us why.
We just, we just grew apart.
Grew apart how?
After his business went bankrupt, it happened.
How can it happen when you have two kids?
Mom and I both think you did something.
How could you?
How could you blame me for everything?
Whenever something happens, you blame me.
But that's so unfair.
You never believed in me, not even once.
When a couple decides to get a divorce,
they both have problems.
It's not just one person's fault!
Did you borrow money from a loan shark?
I didn't.
I'm not that stupid.
Then did you cheat on him?
Father.
Then why is he divorcing you?
He's not. I'm divorcing him.
Why are you?
We decided together!
You're completely out of your mind!
You can't do it.
When Hobak wanted to, you let her.
So why can't I do it?
Hobak's different from you.
Hobak can take care of herself, but not you.
Divorce isn't a reward!
Why do you want it so badly?
Did you have children for fun?
Why can't you put them first?
How can you get a divorce when there's no good enough reason?
I can't live with him in the same house.
I'm sick and tired of him.
That's the reason.
What more do I need?
I'm getting a divorce.
How dare you!
Oh, boy.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
My wedding's off, right?
Why would it be off?
Look how things are going right now.
If she waited until Gwangbak's wedding,
why didn't she wait until your wedding?
She's so thoughtless.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
You all blame me.
Why do you say it's my fault all the time?
Minjung wouldn't do this for no reason.
You can tell your mom.
Every breakup has a reason.
Did Minjung cheat on you?
I don't know.
Did he?
No, it's not like that.
I just fell out of love.
Mom, there were problems from the start.
We married 3 months after we first met.
And we lived together and had kids.
It wasn't because there was love.
And when he went bankrupt, I hated him.
You said you're worried about me.
Don't. I'll do better than Hobak.
What does Hobak have that I don't?
Only Minjung can stand you.
Beg him for forgiveness before he signs the papers.
But I didn't do anything wrong!
Other moms encourage their daughters when they think of getting divorced,
saying you shouldn't stay unhappily married.
Why can't you do that?
Staying together until death do us apart?
Who does that now?
Oh, unbelievable. I can't believe me ears.
You're out of your mind!
I'm done talking.
This is my problem and it's my life.
Mom, you stay out and tell father that, too.
I'm going to my class.
Okay, Aunt Sunjeong.
I'll see you later.
Who is it?
Can't you see? It's me.
Hello.
Who is it?
When you saw me?
You should've said, hello, mother.
- What were you doing?
- I was vacuuming.
Clean every corner.
You should open the windows.
That's father's seat.
Did someone train you to say that?
Let me see your room.
It looks the same.
The wedding cost you nothing, huh?
No wedding gifts, no new furniture.
You brought nothing with you?
The bed is new.
You only brought a bed?
Talking to you is making me thirsty.
Do you have anything to drink?
There's jujube tea.
Miss Kim, one jujube tea for table 5.
I used to do that.
Go.
You already made it?
I had made a fresh pot a little while ago.
I'll have it downstairs.
Are you trying to save jujube?
Excuse me?
It doesn't tastes like jujube. It's water.
Why do you think they call it jujube tea?
On TV, the main characters appear the most.
Jujube is the main character of this tea!
Where's the jujube?
What did you learn before getting married?
Your mom didn't teach you anything?
When I ran a tea house, I didn't do this.
Customers would get angry if you did this.
Can you make Ssanghwa tea or kudzu tea?
No.
I'll teach you later.
My tea house was a happening place.
Especially my Ssanghwa tea.
Can you float an egg yolk in Ssanghwa tea?
No.
Men go wild over them.
You didn't get any wedding jewelry?
No, I only got a wedding band.
You should've gotten some wedding jewelry.
There must be something wrong with you.
Foolish girl.
You gave nothing to your father in law?
I gave a small gift to him.
Like what?
A tie pin and...
Ugh.
Talking to you is making me hungry.
Get me something to eat.
But the side dishes...
You can make fried rice, can't you?
I can try.
I will make it.
Mother.
I will make it, mother.
I'm so tired. I need to lie down.
Not in father's room.
Says who?
Aunt Sunjeong did.
Hey, you should know who's more important.
I'm your mother in law.
She's just an aunt.
I'm like the owner and she's the server in a tea house.
Don't be cheeky.
Mother.
Can I put some ham in it?
You can put anything you want.
Why do you have to ask that?
Mother.
The serum is perfect for this season.
Look at me. I use it.
I'll take it, then.
Have a nice day.
- Mom.
- Don't even call me mom.
Mom, I'll be happy.
Shut up.
Oh, mother, how are you?
Not good.
I'll drop by soon.
There's no need for that.
How are you at housekeeping?
I'm still learning.
But I'm trying to do my best.
That's not good.
You should do it well.
Making money isn't easy,
so don't waste any.
Don't snack like that and save money.
Your wife's working really hard,
so how can you eat stuff like that?
But I only ate one.
Did you get that for free?
If Hobak finds out, she'll flip out.
I won't eat stuff like this again.
What are you going to do about your sister?
Why is your mother being so difficult?
To be frank, we don't really care.
It's your sister who's in trouble.
You mom said that to me about Hobak.
She had no idea this would happen to her.
Why does it take 3 months?
Why does it have to be so complicated?
It should be much simpler to get a divorce.
Having to wait is too inconvenient.
So are we divorced or not?
Let's say we are,
even though we're not yet officially.
Goodbye.
Hold on.
Child support and money for my mom.
You promised to pay, so don't forget.
Thanks for divorcing me so quickly
and for not saying anything to my parents.
Should we grab lunch?
My treat.
I don't want to eat with you.
Take good care of the kids.
I'll send child support to your mother.
I'm clearing out of the office soon.
Make sure none of the investors find out.
Yes, Mr. Seo.
I'll talk to you later.
Congratulate me.
I'm coming from the courthouse.
It's done?
Of course.
I feel like a decade of baggage has been lifted off of my shoulders!
That baggage was too much for me.
Baggage?
10 year old baggage.
Don't they say that?
I feel so much lighter now that it's gone.
I guess it was easy for you.
When I got divorced, it was really hard.
I'm not one of those desperate kinds.
Yes, father.
I'd like to see you.
There's nothing more I can tell you.
Even so, let's meet.
I miss you.
And I have something to say.
Let me ask you one thing.
What was the reason?
Subak won't say it and you won't say it.
Who gets divorced without any reasons?
I've been married for forty years,
but when there are kids, divorce isn't easy.
I can't pinpoint a reason.
I think things just got all built up.
They say little things matter,
and we've have troubles for a long time.
I'm sorry.
You're not a man who'd do this to your kids.
I know what kind of person you are.
Isn't this Subak's fault?
You can tell me.
At least I should know.
She needs to fix whatever she did.
You can't just divorce her like this.
Father.
We already filed the papers.
What?
We have a 3 month waiting period.
This is all my fault.
Don't come down too hard on Subak.
Please let her move on with her life.
What about the kids?
The kids...
Minjung...
I will take them, no matter what.
Please look after them for now.
Until, until they enter elementary school.
Goodbye.
They filed the papers.
He sounded really determined.
How can they do it so quickly?
They just brought it up!
I think they've been planning on it.
What did he say?
Nothing much.
He asked me to look after his kids.
He got choked up when he said it.
Something happened, I'm sure of it.
They have a three month waiting period,
so let's try to change their mind.
What is it, mom?
Is it about uncle?
I can't even think about your uncle right now.
Have you seen Minjung lately?
Minjung? No.
I saw him last at Gwangbak's wedding. Why?
Did you tell him about that thing?
What thing?
Why would I?
I swore I'd take that to the grave.
You really didn't?
I didn't.
What's going on?
Why did you ask me that?
Your sister got a divorce.
What?
Minjung.
What's going on?
I heard from mom.
Where are you staying?
I got a room.
It's not far from your parents place.
Because of the kids...
You look sick.
Did you take medicine?
It's not working.
It must be a severe cold.
Oh... You don't look well.
Minjung, you can tell me.
Why did you do it?
You already know why.
But I didn't tell your parents.
Subak is seeing her boss.
Minjung...
The problem was,
she demanded for a divorce even after what she did.
How could anyone do that?
I can't believe I had two kids with someone like that.
She should've apologized, at least.
Minjung...
I'm so sorry.
For the sake of my kids,
I wanted to stay together as a family.
But I just couldn't...
I know how that feels.
Others may not, but I know.
I just want to go somewhere and die.
I'm sorry.
I can't even ask you to forgive Subak.
Hobak.
Let me ask you one thing.
How long has she been seeing her boss?
She didn't meet him at work, did she?
You know something, don't you?
No, Minjung.
I don't know anything.
There's no need to hide anything now.
Please be honest with me.
Hobak.
You're not even human.
What did you do to Minjung?
All you care about is Minjung!
I warned you to stop.
To end it before Minjung found out.
How could you let him find out?
You should've at least kept it a secret!
You understand him, but not me, do you?
Have you ever been on my side?
What are you going to do?
About what?
I'm going to marry him.
You're insane.
I'm sorry, but I'm not insane.
I'm actually glad.
Mom, father, and you may think Minjung's great,
but he's not right for me.
If I had married the other man,
I'd be living large, spending lots of money.
How can you be so mean?
You told me to never speak of it.
Then you should know better.
How could you date him again and get a divorce?
Go to Minjung and beg him to forgive you.
He said he wants to die.
Let him do whatever he wants.
Subak.
You met up with him again?
Mom asked me if I told him that.
That's why I met with him.
He's really sick,
but he's been working. He looked awful.
Don't you have any conscience?
You must think of mom and father.
They had to hide the fact that you were living with a man!
Was that a sin?
You weren't proud, so you hid it.
You always say you're the eldest child.
You want people to talk about your divorce?
Father's a respected vice principal in this town.
You should've done better!
I will do better.
Let's cut to the chase.
Win Minjung back in three months.
Why is everyone on my case?
It's my life!
You butt out!
Minjung doesn't know about that yet.
Don't let him find out.
Tell him!
It's over now, so who cares?
Don't do something you'll regret.
Don, really?
What do we do now?
What can we do?
We can't see each other until they say yes.
Don!
Don't cry.
Don't you miss me?
Of course I miss you.
I want to run to you and take you away to the ends of the world!
Bye.
Don! Don!
Don't cry, Yeongdal.
You shouldn't when you're pregnant.
What do I do, Hobak?
Don says we can't meet until mom says yes.
Don't worry.
You have a powerful weapon. The baby.
Just focus on your baby.
Think peaceful and beautiful thoughts.
Hobak, thank you.
And I'm sorry.
When you married my brother,
I thought you were really pathetic
for getting pregnant and becoming a burden.
But that's right.
We're both pathetic, so we got pregnant to marry great guys.
Don't cry.
What's for dinner?
It smells good.
Stewed tofu. Your favorite.
Don't make it too salty.
I know.
Sedal,
I want us to agree on everything.
You mean Yeongdal?
Whatever it is.
We'll speak out as one.
That way, our opinion will have more weight.
Oh, boy...
What were you doing?
It was my turn to do the dishes.
Bong, come and sit down.
What is it, mother?
What are we going to do about Don?
He should get married before the baby comes.
He should.
I'll get him a place when Mrs. Park says yes.
Where will you get the money?
She's right.
I think they should live here.
He's too young.
I must take care of him.
Having Subak is bad enough.
I can't have Don live here, too!
I don't think so.
What?
Her mom won't let her marry Don.
I've never seen a meaner person.
She wouldn't shut up in front of Bong.
You should go talk to her.
I don't care what happens.
Leave her alone.
She'll come and beg us.
Her daughter's stomach is growing as we speak.
But you've experienced the same thing!
Think of when Hobak was pregnant.
Hobak and Yeongdal aren't the same!
If Don were my son, I would never let him marry Yeongdal.
She'll be your sister in law. Be nice.
Oh, I don't care!
I'm already upset.
He's more upset than you!
What's done is done, but he's afraid of you.
And Yeongdal's family won't approve of him.
No wonder he paces the yard all night!
He should go to work!
Just look at him.
Your bride wants red bean porridge.
Wait! Hold on!
I'm leaving red bean porridge by the door.
Eat it with your mother.
Hobak, it's red bean porridge.
Don left it by the door.
Oh, my uncle is so caring.
Go get mother.
I can't believe Loser.
Stop it.
Mom, come out.
Have some red bean porridge.
I don't want any.
Oh, my!
I can't believe how quickly he came.
What about mother?
She said, "I don't want any."
Yeongdal, eat.
You must eat what you crave to have a pretty baby.
Sedal, come here.
Come and have some.
I don't want any.
My uncle sent a lot so you can have some.
Yeongdal just gobbled it up.
It's really delicious. Please get up.
Sedal never did this for me when I was pregnant.
Yeongdal is really lucky.
My uncle is so caring.
This is being really lucky?
Really lucky?
Are you trying to make me go mad?
If you were me, would you let her marry Loser?
I wouldn't.
I'd want someone rich and handsome.
But what can we do?
She's pregnant.
Mother, my uncle isn't much right now,
but he'll cherish Yeongdal.
It takes him time, but he'll be successful.
My grandmother had him when she was older,
so he's always been a late bloomer.
- But in the end...
- Stop it.
I've known him since his middle school days.
Like you always say,
you must wait until the end...
I don't want to talk about this.
To see how your life turns out.
That's what you said.
How can you laugh at a time like this?
Take this and get out!
Congratulations, Daese.
Congratulations, father.
Father, you're amazing.
I'm proud of you.
This is made with 24 carat gold.
When I goth this, my heart was pounding.
I was so touched.
Your father's really amazing.
The employees collected money and bought it
for him for the foundation day to show gratitude.
When it comes to business, he's the best.
He never missed a deadline and never missed employees pay day.
Father, I really respect you.
You're amazing.
Your employees must respect you so much.
He cried when he got this at the office.
Let's give him a big hand.
Uncle and Yeongdal...
I'm not listening.
Sit down.
Why did you leave this out?
Fish cake?
Mom told me she saw it.
You were eating fish cake.
Huh? Uh...
Why did you leave that out?
Sorry.
I'll never leave it out again.
I'll record everything.
Please forgive me.
We're even, then.
About what?
My uncle.
No way.
Sedal, do as I say.
Sedal.
Didn't you see him getting porridge?
You never did that for me, remember?
My uncle's different.
He's the kind of man a woman should be with.
Yeongdal loves him and she's pregnant.
That's enough.
We started out like that, too.
What's done is done, so you should...
If you make my sister cry, I'll kill you.
You're giving me your blessing?
Respect me as your wife's older brother.
Thanks, Sedal.
I'm furious to give my sister away to a loser like you!
Sedal!
Who are you to give them blessings?
I'm not much,
but I'm Yeongdal's older brother.
Loser's an okay kid.
His only flaw is having no money,
but who doesn't have any flaws?
But that's a huge flaw!
We've been friends since middle school.
He's a nice guy and he's genuine.
And he'll never cheat on her.
He won't beat her or break her heart.
Mom, let them get married.
I'll vouch for him.
Your father said never to vouch for anyone.
I will do it this once.
Mom, let them get married.
My precious daughter's ruined! She's ruined!
I didn't raise her to give her away to Loser!
I spent so much money on Yeongdal!
And now she's marrying a penniless man!
I didn't get my money's worth, so I can't!
But this is Yeongdal's fate.
I gave up so it's your turn to give up.
Yeongdal's in love.
I can't give up.
Why are both of my kids putting me through such ordeals?
Why couldn't you marry someone I approve of?
How can the Wang family take both of my kids?
I'd rather die than see that happen.
I don't want anything to do with that family.
Why didn't you answer your phone?
I called you many times yesterday and today.
I have no time to answer my phone.
You're that busy?
I had to do the laundry, clean the house,
and this house is huge with lots to clean.
I'm a beginner, so it's really hard.
But you need to write, too.
I have no time to write.
Your mother came yesterday.
She did?
You two must be close.
Huh?
Honey, it's nice to be married.
I made up with mom because of it.
She deserves your compassion.
She's staying in Seoul to get to know you.
For how long?
I don't know. I think she likes you.
Good morning.
You're an early riser.
I'm not but I'm trying really hard.
They eat breakfast early, so we have to.
I heard my sister came yesterday.
Yes.
She's my sister and Sangnam's mom,
but she's not a nice person.
Don't let her push you around. Be wise.
Do you understand what I mean?
Any news?
You're married, so there should be news.
But we just got married, father.
Everything comes in due time.
Why? Other's have kids just like that.
Water.
Who washed this cup?
I did.
I washed it.
Why is it so dirty?
Don't you know how to do anything?
Father.
Am I wrong?
When you clean the bathroom, wipe the floor dry.
I almost slipped walking in.
I'll remember that.
She works hard all day.
She's not a housekeeper.
It's her first time, so give her credit.
What?
- Sangnam.
- Aunt Sunjeong, let me talk.
Father, I want to say something.
What's wrong, Sangnam?
Aunt Sunjeong cooks the meals,
but Gwangbak's too busy with cleaning and laundry.
She didn't marry me to do housekeeping.
She wants to be a writer, but she has no time.
In marriage, two people must help the other to grow.
And I promised her that.
What are you trying to say?
Sangnam, later.
After we both go to work,
I want her to have some free time.
We should all leave her alone so she can have her own time.
That way, she can read books and write.
Was it you?
- Excuse me?
- It wasn't her. It's all me.
You're already manipulating your husband?
How long have you been married?
How much work did you actually do?
She had nothing to do with what I said, father.
You stay out!
I know both of you are in on this!
Good for you, idiot.
You let your wife manipulate you.
How could you do this to me?
I'm in trouble now.
Is this your way of helping?
I don't know what just happened.
I didn't mean for it to turn out like this.
How did my words get so twisted?
Don't try to help me from now on.
- I meant...
- I know.
I do, but the method was wrong.
Just pretend you don't know anything.
Even if your father and I end up fighting,
I want us to work things out.
It's better to do that than you butting in whenever something happens.
Anyone could've taken it the wrong way.
What do I do?
Did you see aunt's face?
Why are you making enemies?
Oh, this is hard.
I made another mistake?
This is my first time getting married.
Whatever.
Parcel service.
I'll be there in ten minutes.
Mom, are you coming from your class?
Yes.
What's that?
It's money.
Why did you laminate this?
That's the money that man gave me.
You didn't spend it?
No. I'm going to keep it.
I miss him.
I don't think he's at Daebak's house.
Mom, I'm going to my piano lesson.
I miss him.
I do, too.
Daebak, eat.
It's my sister's fault, right?
No, both of us are at fault.
That can't be.
She never cooked for you, and when your business went bankrupt, she was mean.
I know all that.
But can you change your mind for mom and father?
They think of you as their own son.
My father can't even eat these days.
Can't you be their son, just until I grow up?
Daebak, where have you been?
Did you finish your homework?
What will become of you?
You're not even studying.
I want to quit school.
Why? What's wrong?
Is there another girl?
It's not a girl.
My family's a mess.
We never have any peace at home.
Why? What happened?
Miho, I'm saying this for your sake.
Don't marry into my family.
You won't be able to handle it.
I'm letting you go out of love, so just go.
Daebak, tell me what it is.
What's going on?
Mom. mom. He got a divorce.
What?
He signed the papers, packed up and left.
He's been living alone for a while now.
No wonder I didn't see him.
Why? For what?
I don't know, but Subak did something.
My in laws are in trouble.
The person you have called is unavailable,
so your call will be directed to voicemail.
Where are you, Minjung?
Can we meet?
I made some side dishes for you.
Don't worry about me.
Have you been eating?
Yes. I'm working right now.
It'll only take a minute.
I'll come out to where you are. Okay?
Oh, yes.
Minjung!
Why did you come out?
I wanted to give you some side dishes.
And I wanted to see you.
Here's your daddy. Oh.
I brought him because I knew you miss him.
I brought some kimchi and other side dishes.
You're the one who made this kimchi,
so how could you leave without eating it all?
Whenever I eat it, I think of you.
When everyone eats it, I think of you.
When I think about you carrying me to the ER...
Are you cooking your own food?
Kind of...
It's not easy for a man to live on his own.
Where are you staying?
I just got a small room.
Is it far from here?
No.
Can I come by sometime?
I'd like to cook something for you.
It's okay.
I don't have time to eat at home.
My family's a mess.
My husband just might kill Subak.
We all believe it's Subak's fault.
Minjung, can't you give it another thought?
Drop by anytime to see the kids.
Jungji's been asking for you.
Huh?
He calls every man he sees "daddy."
I don't think he can talk yet.
He can!
When he sees men your age on TV,
he points to him and says, "Daddy, daddy."
Jungji, say "Daddy. Daddy."
He said it before.
Say "Daddy. Daddy."
It's okay.
He must be feeling shy.
Whenever you want to see Aeji or Jungji,
just drop by the house.
If you don't want to see Subak,
come during the day when she's at work.
Goodbye, mother.
Thank you for this.
But don't bring me anymore food.
I'll drop by when I want to see the kids.
Take care of yourself.
Okay. Go.
Drive carefully, always.
Even if you're not married to Subak anymore,
don't cut off ties with me, okay?
And he turned around and my heart was...
I couldn't believe what's happening.
We're being torn apart here.
I grew fond of him
and thought of him as my own son,
but he left, just like that.
I don't know what to do.
I want to go somewhere and cry.
What did he say?
What could he say?
He looked awful.
His face shrank to this size.
He burst into tears when he saw Jungji.
But he tried hard not to cry.
It breaks your heart to see a man do that.
So where is he living?
Somewhere close.
He got a room near here.
Why didn't you get his address?
Oh, I should've.
I didn't think of that.
Let's go.
Already?
Have dinner with me.
I have a dinner appointment.
You seem to be very busy these days.
Men should keep busy.
Then call me later.
You can call me anytime.
I don't understand your parents.
They let you get a divorce?
I thought they wouldn't allow it.
What could they do?
I wanted it.
See you tomorrow.
I'm home.
What is it?
I met Minjung today.
Why did you meet him?
Why can't I?
He's my son in law.
Not anymore. We're divorced.
Legally, you're still married.
I brought Jungji with me and he cried.
How insane!
Why did you have to go meet him?
Just let me live my life, please.
You're always picking on me.
Everyone treats me like I'm invisible at home.
When I say hi, nobody replies.
Grandmother doesn't say, "You're home?"
It's because you're getting a divorce!
Go meet Minjung.
It's over between us.
If you keep this up, I'm moving out.
What about your kids?
How can I live here when you nag me?
If you want to leave, take your kids.
I have to work and make money!
You said you'd raise the kids.
Why would I do that when you're not here?
Minjung's going to pay you for raising them!
You're completely out of your mind.
My daughter's divorced, so how can I raise
her kids and get money from her ex-husband?
You're a bigger fool than I thought.
Why are you calling me a fool?
You're not giving me much choice.
Wait and see. I'll do great.
I can't live with someone who's poor.
So stop nagging me and just wait.
Something amazing will happen.
My song comes back in a whistle
Memories build up in my small space
I don't understand why I'm tearing up
I put my little heart together and write
A poem, but it's not enough for you
I'll become dust and fly
Blown by the wind
To your side...
Minjung.
Minjung!
Subtitles by KBS World
Don't think about anything.
Just get better.
Cheer up, Minjung.
Get me the deed to the house.
Why do you want that?
You can't take it.
Get as much money as possible.
There's no time.
I need it right now.
It's my family.
Actually...
I think there's a reason why you come
when nobody else is home but me.
You're pretty smart.
Are you taking things out on Sangnam?
You're trying to come between me and him.
Is that how you were raised?
Did you want me to wait for you?
I won't say thank you.
I'll just remember it, always.