Subtitles by KBS World
Sunjeong! Sunjeong!  Sangnam!
What are you going to do about this?
This is all your fault.
You shouldn't have left the house empty!
What happened?
Your father's golden key got stolen.
What?
And the tie pin and cuff links are gone.
I told you not to leave the house empty!
That wasn't just any key!
Let's call the police, father.
Right, call them now.
Daese, I don't think we should.
Why not?
It might create more problems.
They'll ask us to come and go, drop by here,
and you'd have to go there, too.
This happened because of you!
Was my sister here?
Yes.
And she went into Daese's room?
No way. She couldn't have.
I'm sure of it.
It felt weird, so I said no to the police.
What if they find out it was Sangnam's mom?
How embarrassing would that be?
And how would Sangnam feel?
I really hate her. I should...
Aunt, hold on.
I'll take care of this.
Please leave this to me.
I know what to do.
Minjung, I waited for you.
I hope everything is okay with you.
The court sent you documents.
Reheat and stew and have dinner.
[Divorce by Consent Application]
Submit this to finalize the divorce.
If you don't, it will be null and void.
Why aren't you asleep?
Why did you come out?
To go to the bathroom.
Happy birthday, honey.
I don't know where one of my children is.
So how can I celebrate my birthday?
Don't worry. She won't die.
She sent $50.
If I didn't have Haebak and Daebak,
I'd want to give up everything.
Don't say that. There's mother.
Don's married so he can take care of her.
Yeah, right.
You'd never be able to let your mother go.
And mother will give up without you.
How about you?
What do you think?
You'll go on fine without me.
Of course.
If you don't want me to, don't give up.
Don't go, Bong. I'm scared.
What did you just say?
Don keeps Yeongdal company.
Why don't you do it?
I'd rather die.
I'd rather run away from home.
So not romantic.
Daebak, Daebak.
You asked me to wake you up.
What is it?
It's nothing. Go back to sleep.
But the living room's too cold.
The water's frozen.
You should sleep in the room.
I'm sorry. I should be sleeping here.
Mrs. Park almost killed me for that.
Bong, it's not there.
Oh, boy.
Mother, it's me.
Get in here.
Oh, your body is ice cold.
Oh, cold. Ugh...
There's hot water in the kitchen.
Huh? There wasn't any.
No?
Did you use all the hot water?
Yes, I washed my hair.
How could you use it all up?
That was for those going to work.
But I thought I had priority.
Don't yell at her.
She's our treasure.
I can't believe my ears.
She's more like a headache.
What are you then?
Oh! Stomachache, right?
Right, stomachache.
Hah...
My stomach is growing.
It's too early to grow.
I've been taking pictures and it is.
Look.
No need. What you're saying is nonsense.
You have to be at least 5 months.
Let me see.
It is!
Right? It's bigger than yesterday.
Bong, look at my stomach.
Uh, I...
That's nothing to brag about.
Grow up. You can't show that to him.
Bong, why aren't you eating heartily?
I'm not very hungry.
Of course he can't eat.
He sleeps on the freezing floor,
he can't use the bathroom in the morning,
and he had to use cold water to wash up.
His old body can't take it.
So how can he eat?
He has no strength.
He's full. If he's hungry, he'd devour...
Right, Yeongdal.
It's because I'm full.
If I were hungry, I'd devour everything.
Everything here tastes so good.
Eating with everyone makes me so anxious
about others eating all the good side dishes.
Eat up. Don't be timid.
I won't let you go hungry.
Then pitch in.
You eat too much.
At that rate, your baby will be too big.
But aren't you glad she's eating so well,
even with just kimchi on the table?
Hey, something seems to be missing.
It's Daebak.
Daebak ran away from home?
He went to study.
He did?
Hurry up. The lunch crowd will be here.
Making money isn't easy.
Others could do that in 30 minutes.
But you take over an hour.
No other restaurants would hire you.
You'll get fired, just like that.
I actually did.
Thank you.
God will bless you.
So what happened to you?
Things happened.
Life is a mysterious thing.
It looks like you have stories to tell.
I have tons of stories to tell.
It's me, mother.
I'd like to see you.
I have some things to say to you.
Glad you called.
I wanted to see you, too.
When can you come?
Right now.
Right now?
Turn around.
Why do you look so surprised?
You all get surprised to see me.
Perfect timing, right?
I locked the door. How did you get in?
With this. I can open anything with this.
I could sleep because you didn't apologize properly.
Have a seat. I'll get you some tea.
Mother.
What did you say?
Give me back the golden key.
And the tie pin and the cuff links.
have you gone mad?
I know you took them.
Oh, my!
How dare you accuse me of such a thing?
What did I take?
You're turning me into a thief?
I better call Sangnam.
Go ahead.
What?
Sangnam can take you to the police.
How dare you...
You!
Don't yell.
I won't back down until you give them back.
That wasn't just any key.
Father's employees gave it to him to
commemorate the years of hard work.
So how could you steal that?
That wasn't just gold.
So give it back,
if you don't wan me to call the police.
How dare you!
Did you see me take it?
You went into that room that day.
And that makes me a thief?
You're impossible!
How dare you accuse me of stealing?
Fine! Let's go to the police. Let's go!
Do you mean it?
Yes. Let's go.
I'm not scared.
Fine.
You're not giving me any choice.
I'll buy that from you.
What?
You won't get much if you sell it.
I'll pay you double of what it's worth.
Double?
Yes.
I'll tell everyone I found them,
so sell them to me.
You have nothing to lose.
I always keep my promises.
I'll keep this a secret from father and Sangnam.
Uh, you promise?
Of course. Going to the police is a bother.
Then pay me three times.
That's too much. Three times
I'll throw in the tie pin and cuff... Whatever.
They weren't worth much anyway.
Fine.
I still have some money to give you,
so I'll pay three times its worth.
Give them to me.
I don't have them now. They're at home.
Bring them tomorrow when nobody's home.
You can't change your mind.
Don't worry.
Oh, this is...
- What are you doing?
- Huh?
They look perfectly fine.
- Can I take them?
- You can't.
But I'll let you, just this time.
You can take anything you want.
We're having coffee, so join us.
There are lots of pretty women.
But they're all married!
Come with me.
Huh? Don't...
This is nuts.
Hey, hey, hey!
Here's a new member.
Number 505.
- Welcome.
Hello. I'm Heo Sedal.
We use apartment numbers here.
Okay. I'm Number 505.
Have a seat.
Don't stand there looking so awkward.
We're all in the same boat.
Come and sit down.
Okay.
So, what happened?
What do you think?
She went through the mobile phone, found her and slapped her.
Oh, it was invigorating.
Mobile phones tell you if anyone's cheating.
Right.
You can never trust men.
They all have a wandering eye.
Number 505, you try it.
Your eyes are big, so they're be perfect.
- Right. right.
- They're perfect.
Like this?
Wandering, wandering, wandering.
Oh, perfect! You passed!
Who were you talking about just now?
We were talking about a TV drama.
Uh, okay.
I thought it was someone you knew.
Women are just as bad, I heard.
Number 103 is having an affair.
The guard found out first from the way she dressed.
Office wife and office husband are popular.
What's that?
Acting like a couple at work.
It's a glorified term for cheating.
Oh...
It's me. Are you coming home late?
I'm going out with co-workers.
What time will you finish?
I don't know.
Will you be drinking?
We will, I'm sure.
Who will be there?
Why do you ask?
And why do you care about drinking?
Don't ask stupid questions like that.
Uh, Hobak!
Oh, man...
There's a perfect article for you.
Newlywed journal.
What do you think?
Newlywed journal?
You can write about others or yourself.
The title will be "The Truth About Marriage."
The raw truth about married life.
Make the single women feel better.
Is it too much for you?
No, I think I'll have a lot to say.
I'm giving this to you out of sympathy.
Thank you, editor.
Where's the cake?
I ate it.
I'll get you another one when I get paid.
Mom!
Miho.
Oh, did you enjoy it?
Yes.
Was it fun? You didn't get sick?
I'm going to see Daebak.
Man...
I can't believe her.
Daebak, what happened?
You never answered my calls.
Are you cheating on me?
I don't have time to cheat on you.
What are you doing at the library?
Is there a girl?
If I catch you, I'll kick your butt.
I have no time for that.
We moved.
Moved? When?
I can't go into detail.
I have to go back in and study.
My only hope is to study.
Are you okay?
Have you gone made?
I'm perfectly fine.
My family went bankrupt.
What?
Mom! Mom!
- Is that true?
- Yes.
Daebak's family moved to a tiny house.
[Marriage is...]
Is it going well?
No.
Have some of this.
Thank you, aunt.
What are you writing about?
It's nothing.
It's a project I got.
Why didn't you tell me?
I heard from Miho just now.
Your family's going through tough times?
Oh...
You heard?
It must be hard.
And you just got married.
I'm sorry.
I know how difficult it must be for you
when something like that happens.
I've been there, too.
Yesterday was my father's birthday.
But I couldn't even tell Sangnam because he'd want to go visit them.
You should've told me, at least.
Please don't tell Sangnam.
Or father.
I don't want them to find out.
I know.
It's embarrassing and discouraging.
I've experienced that because of my sister.
You didn't look so happy,
and I thought it was because of Daese.
I had no idea this had happened.
Please don't tell Sangnam.
I'll tell him in my own time.
May I have 2 sweet buns, please?
My pretty princess.
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
He's such a cheapskate.
He only bought two?
He's so inconsiderate.
It's not me who's eating this.
Wangdal's eating it.
Who's Wangdal?
We're calling the fetus Wangdal.
They give names to their fetuses now.
Is there honey in there?
I don't know. I think it's sugar.
It's sugar.
Is there pine nuts, too?
I think so.
I'm sorry I can't offer you any.
That looks good.
I shouldn't star at people eating.
Then don't stare.
I'm trying not to, but I can't help it.
Today's fortune is bad.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
I'd like to share,
but I just can't do it.
I wasn't like this, but since I got pregnant, I became a total glutton.
I'll take this into my room.
Look, mother.
You cherished Don, but look where it got you.
Why didn't he buy a few more for you?
I'm not saying this because I want one.
You told me not to spoil my kids?
But you're living proof of its repercussions.
And it's going to get worse.
Why that little...
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo...
Give me that baby.
I'll take care of him.
- Oh, thank you.
- Thank you.
Just 10 minutes.
I need 10 minutes.
Oh, little boy.
Can you take care of him?
Okay.
Don't you miss your kids?
You should take care of them.
They like my mom better than me.
I can't go to Aeji's talent show.
I regret marrying you,
and I regret having those kids! Satisfied?
The rose of Sharon has bloomed.
Where were you?
I don't believe this.
Don't I pay you on time?
You didn't prepare any of the vegetables.
And you didn't do the dishes.
You said it'd take an hour. What time is it?
I'm sorry.
I'll do it now.
Making money isn't easy, you know?
I know. I know so well.
Go to sleep, Jungji.
Good boy, Jungji.
Oh, where is your mom?
Is she eating well?
Is she sleeping well?
Jungji, tell your mom to come home.
Say "Mom. come home."
Mom, come home.
Subak!
Subak! Subak!
She must be miserable.
Imagine how she must have felt,
leaving baby formula at the door.
She must be having a hard time herself yet...
It's not like she knows how to do anything.
She never even did her own laundry.
Where did she find the money to buy this?
Why that little...
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo...
I feel sorry for Subak,
even though I used to hate her.
Why didn't you follow her?
I called her and ran after her,
but it was too dark.
Honey, let's go find Subak.
Let's call the police or something.
Leave her be. She'll come back.
We know she's alive so don't worry.
Okay, let's go to bed.
Go to sleep.
Why isn't mom home?
She'll come home soon.
Dad, watch out.
Mom's pretty, so what if other men like her?
Your mom's not pretty!
She is. Other men all look at her.
What if someone steals her from you?
Everyone raise your glasses.
For great success!
For our success!
Manager.
- Cheers.
The person you have called is unavailable...
Oh, man.
[Missed calls, Home (12)]
Why won't you pick up the phone? Huh?
Where are you? Who are you with?
How much did you drink?
Are you with men?
Hah!
Hey! Hey! Wang Hobak!
Oh, this is nuts!
Man!
Why isn't she coming home?
Oh, it's so cold.
Oh, boy.
Oh, no.
Why did you drink so much?
- I was so happy.
- Oh, man!
- I drank too much.
- What's going on here?
Huh? Why are you out here?
Say hi. This is my husband.
Hello.
I guess I'll have to give her to you.
Oh, be careful.
Please take good care of my manager.
Goodbye.
I'll see you tomorrow.
It's been a great night!
- Sweet dreams.
- Goodnight!
What the...
Hobak. Hey...
Oh, this is too much. Ugh.
What's that?
Did you get in safely?
You were amazing tonight!
You are so great.
So sexy.
Did you get home okay?
I love you. Let's go!
Oh, man.
Ugh... Man...
_ Are you crazy?
- Oh, ouch!
That hurt!
My chin!
Oh, man...
Open the door!
Hey! Open the door! Hey!
Why isn't this open!
Open the door!
Why won't you open the door?
Don, are you sleeping?
Yes.
Wangdal wants noodles.
Tell him to sleep.
Doesn't he ever sleep?
How can you say that?
It's Wangdal who wants it.
Okay.
Yeongdal!
Eat.
Ouch, hot! Hot!
Slow down. Eat it with rice.
Nice going.
The wife goes out and gets drunk,
and the husband makes soup for her.
This family's doing swell.
Oh, that hit the spot.
Oh, I feel alive again.
Who was that man who brought you home?
Someone brought me home?
You don't remember?
I don't.
I don't believe this!
You really don't remember?
What if someone kidnaps you?
Who'd kidnap me?
Some young bastard brought you home.
Who could it be?
Oh, right. He's just an employee.
Don't call him a bastard. That's rude.
He kept calling you "my manager."
I hated it.
Why does the word "my" piss me off so much?
I hated "my" Minjung, too.
Are you office wife and office husband?
Where did you hear that?
Some women said that's popular.
Don't listen to them.
I can't believe you sit around gossiping.
We're not just sitting around.
We have so much to do at home.
Don't put it like that. It hurts me.
What's this?
What do you mean?
You kept getting texts all night.
Why did you read my texts?
And why did you call me so many times?
I told you I was going out.
What do you do when you go out?
Manger, you're sexy.
You're amazing.
- You want to know?
- Yes.
Why don't you show me?
I will!
- So?
- I can't believe this.
Going through my phone is vile.
Don't do it again.
Vile?
Yes. Have I ever done that?
I don't have a mobile phone.
Everyone has one but me!
So?
Are you upset?
Uh, no.
Don't hang around with those women and spread gossip about people.
They just gossip about the neighbors.
Don't do it, okay?
And stop watching so many dramas.
Read newspapers.
Don't you even read books?
If I don't watch dramas,
they won't let me hang out.
What?
I don't have any friends now.
They're the only ones who hang out with me.
But you're not a woman!
I'm half woman.
Eat.
Mom.
Let's go.
No, I have to work.
You're not working here. Come!
Mom, don't do this.
Come!
You.
Ouch.
This isn't going to work.
This will! Enroll, now!
We can't afford to pay college tuition!
I'll find the money, no matter what,
so take classes here.
I got a full scholarship.
You won't have to pay anything.
Mom, I'm going to become a captain.
I don't want to become a judge.
Don't you understand?
Please let me do this.
Don't you understand me?
Can't you let me win this once?
Please do this for me.
You want me to live in that rat hole?
If you become a judge, it'll go away.
You can save everyone.
Mom.
Becoming a judge isn't winning the lottery.
Even if I become a judge, I won't be rich.
Shut up! Come with me!
Oh, my! Hey!
Father,
I'm sorry
I didn't tell you before.
You know why your mom's acting like that.
I do.
If I knew this would happen,
I would've done what she wanted,
no matter what my dream was.
But I decided before all this.
What do you want to do?
I don't know.
I want to become a captain,
but with mom acting like that,
I'm thinking maybe I should go back to studying.
Father, what should I do?
Life is long.
Look further down the line.
Choose the path you won't regret after 10 or 20 years.
I don't care what choices you make.
You can follow your dream or you can become a judge.
Make a list
of the pros and cons for taking one path
and taking the other path.
Then you'll get the answer.
Only you can make this decision.
It's your life.
[Family Registration]
Hello.
Have a seat over there.
We want two soft tofu stews.
Okay.
- Two soft tofu stews.
- Okay.
- Make them extra good.
[Minjung]
Hello?
It's me.
Where are you?
The court sent documents.
We should meet.
Come get the soft tofu.
What are you doing?
You're working!
You can take care of it.
[Seoul Family Court]
Here are my divorce papers.
Okay.
Did you process the document I gave you?
No, not yet.
When's the deadline?
It's today.
If it's not processed today, it'll be nullified.
You won't be divorced.
No, mom.
But I can see Subak doing it.
Subak did what?
Minjung is really acting really suspiciously.
Why would he get a divorce?
Why don't you find out who she is?
Why do you want to know? It's over.
If Minjung has a woman, they can't divorce.
It's not like Subak is innocent.
What do you mean?
She made a mistake before getting married.
You can't call that a mistake!
It wasn't like she was engaged to him before she moved in with him.
She just did, without thinking about it,
or even finishing college.
What she did was terrible.
Minjung married her because he didn't know.
He wouldn't have, if he knew.
Nobody would.
If Sedal did that, I couldn't forgive him.
Please process this.
Okay.
Your divorce paper has been processed.
So I'm divorced now?
Yes.
You almost didn't make it.
I can't say this was right or wrong, though.
Minjung.
Congratulate me.
I'm finally divorced.
You submitted the documents?
Yes.
It was really simple.
Making up my mind was hard,
but all it took was submitting the paper.
How do you feel?
Weird?
Sort of.
I'm relieved.
And also excited.
I can really date you now.
- I'm not falling for that.
- I'm serious.
You and I have nothing to hold us back.
You are a bad guy.
You know how sad you made me?
- How?
- You told me to go.
And you kept breaking up with me.
I did?
See?
Classic. You forgot everything you did.
You turned to me when your father was sick,
saying, "Sunjeong, stay with me."
But when your father got better,
you tossed me a hair pin and told me you couldn't see me.
I must be mad to come and go as you say.
I really am a mean bastard.
Why do you keep following me around?
I didn't follow you around.
You just appeared.
That's how you are.
And I like you that way.
You only look at one direction.
You never failed your family.
You made me cry but that's who you are.
When we dated, the whole 7 years,
you never looked at another woman.
You always remained faithful.
And I really loved you for that.
For being so consistent.
Congratulations, anyway.
Thanks.
I would've had soju alone at home.
But I'm happy to see you.
Maybe we should have a party.
We're both divorced.
Be honest with me.
You were waiting for this to happen, right?
How can you say that?
How did you know?
I held my breath until my neck turned stiff.
Look.
[Provisional Attachment Notice]
[Seoul Family Court]
[Form: Divorce by Consent]
I did that?
You did. I'll be right back.
Hello, mother.
Minjung, what are you doing?
I had plans, so I'm out.
Did you have dinner?
Yes.
Have you been busy?
You haven't visited.
Aeji and Jungji want their dad.
Minjung.
I'll drop by tomorrow.
Okay.
Minjung, please come tomorrow.
Don't you feel bad for your kids?
Their mom is gone, so you should visit.
Goodbye, then.
Don't call Minjung so often.
I call him because of the kids.
Don't use the kids as an excuse.
It'll make him uncomfortable.
Why would it?
He hasn't come so I just got curious.
He's all alone so I'm worried.
He can take care of himself.
I know why you're doing it but stop.
Their divorce has been finalized.
It hasn't yet.
What's this?
Divorce confirmation.
This was in the mail.
Minjung must have gotten it already.
If he submitted it, they'd be divorced.
So stop calling him so often.
And the kids are our grandchildren.
[Mom]
Let's go.
Where should we go?
Let me think.
We should walk a little.
I came right away because you said you were having a bad day.
It's not just tonight.
Kids are useless. All of them.
It's cold.
Where do you want to go?
Somewhere crowded. Somewhere tight.
What?
It's cold, so let's go somewhere really crowded.
I want to go where there is no one around.
But that's boring.
How do you feel?
Warm, right?
Yes.
I love it when someone holds me.
Be them my hands or my shoulders.
It's pretty interesting here.
Isn't it?
I'm not unhappy anymore.
Tell me if you get hungry.
I'm not hungry. Let's walk some more.
I feel so relieved now.
The divorce paper arrived.
See Minjung and beg him to forgive you.
You have to think about the kids.
Sunjeong, we're leaving.
Have a nice day, Daese.
Have a good day, father.
Aunt, I'll see you later.
I think I'll have to go to China soon.
Okay.
Sign the contract while you're there.
I should.
Aunt?
Now?
Okay.
Is that true?
Yes.
Gwangbak told me to keep it a secret,
but I can't do it.
How could that happen?
They had to move?
Yes.
They moved to a tiny two room house.
How could she not tell me?
Aunt, a married couple can't be like this.
But you both have your pride.
She just married you,
so to tell you her family went bankrupt,
it would've been embarrassing.
People might think she's bad luck.
But that's nonsense!
We're married.
She must be miserable.
Don't tell your father,
but you should be nice to her.
Hello, mother.
Would you like some tea?
I want to make the exchange first.
Okay.
Give them to me first.
You really won't tell them?
I won't.
This is our little secret, okay?
Of course.
Then give that to me first.
You have to give me those first.
I have the envelope here.
So you should take them out.
Open them.
Why?
Please open them. I must check.
Then show me the envelope.
You can't do this!
You're pretty smart.
I went to college. I can't give you this.
You are just like me.
If we open a tea room, it'd be a success.
Happy?
Give it to me.
Let's exchange them at the same time.
Let go on the count of three.
One, two!
You're pretty tough.
How did you know I'd grab at two?
I went to college, and I was a teacher.
What's this?
How could you do this?
You tricked me?
I only got back what you stole.
I have no reason to give you money.
I'm your mother in law!
What kind of daughter in law does this?
What about what you did to me?
I did everything I could for you.
I gave you $10,000 behind Sangnam's back.
You hurt him when he was little,
but I was happy about you and him.
I didn't care if he got mad at me.
But you stole father's key
and turned Sangnam against me.
I won't let this go on.
You won't? How dare you?
I won't just sit here and...
Sangnam. Sangnam.
Sangnam, listen to me.
She's framing me!
Sangnam, listen to me!
- Sangnam.
- Get out right now!
- I said get out!
I'm embarrassed of thinking of you as my mom.
And I regret meeting you again.
I'm devastated you're my birth mother,
and I wish I could drain all of my blood.
I can't believe I thought of you as my mom.
You don't deserve the title.
Sangnam.
Please leave.
Don't say anything.
Leave.
Sangnam! Sangnam!
Sangnam! Sangnam! Oh, Sangnam...
Sangnam.
I'm sorry things turned out this way.
I didn't want anyone else to find out.
After some time passes and
Sangnam can  take you back again,
I'll call you.
Goodbye.
Why did you come?
I could've taken care of it.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I don't even know where to begin.
Sangnam, I know you're hurting.
I wish you didn't know.
It's okay.
I should know this.
Why didn't you tell me about your parents?
Why didn't you tell me?
We're married.
Did aunt tell you?
Yes.
How could you keep that a secret?
Why did you suffer alone? You fool.
When will I grow up?
I'm such a bad husband.
Ko Minjung, Wang Subak. You're divorced.
Here.
[Divorce registration, January 15, 2014]
Minjung.
Oh.
Hello.
Yes.
What are you doing here?
I know someone here.
I was here to see someone too.
Is Gwangbak doing okay?
Yes.
Please look after her.
And please talk to your brother in law.
I will.
Goodbye, then.
Goodbye.
I'm home.
- It's snowing?
- Yes.
It's snowing heavily.
It is?
Subtitles by KBS World
You know Choi Daese, don't you?
Who are you? Watch your manners.
How dare you!
I'll make up for all the pain I caused you.
It's like we're dating again.
Many couples get back together.
Mother, we're already...
Don't make him feel uncomfortable.
But you have kids.
Mom, please.
Please leave.
We can't go any further.
Yes, we can.
Minjung says no, but he has a woman.
How can I ask him to come back?
Get a hold of yourself, or you'll lose him.