Subtitles by KBS
I'm the one who's frustrated.
Why do you think I said I'm sick of them?
What's wrong with everyone today?
I'm miserable as it is,
and even mom got angry and hit me.
Because I have no money...
She's never done that.
Hobak's moving into her new apartment,
but I had to clean the dirty bathroom with my hands,
the one everyone's using!
A woman with foam around her mouth humiliated me in front of my friend,
saying she was in the Miss Korea pageant too!
I have a secret.
What is it?
When a woman says this, it's nothing.
I'm serious.
We
are moving.
- Really?
- Really? To where?
An apartment.
Yay! This is nuts!
Heo Bangtong!
I won't, I won't. I won't copy dad!
Is it big? Will I get my own room?
What does it look like?
Should we go and look?
It's on the 5th floor.
One, two, three, four, five.
It's the fifth one with the lights on.
Whoa.
Let's go in, mom.
We can't. Someone's still living there right now.
The owner said that when you move in there,
you'll become really smart.
Really?
What does my room look like?
What about mine? Mine?
It looks like this.
The apartment looks like this.
This is the living room, the master bedroom,
and this is Sintong's room.
What about mine?
Bangtong, your room is here.
And there are two bathrooms.
One in the master bedroom, one here.
Yay! Yay!
So Sintong and I have our own bathrooms?
Stupid. Mom and Dad need one, too.
Mom, a bed. All my friends have beds.
Of course I'll buy you one!
How about a desk?
A desk? Should I buy you one?
Please, please!
I think I can study hard if I have one.
The bad ones always blame their tools.
Fine. I'll buy you a desk, too.
Yay! Yes!
- Shh!
Be quiet.
People are sleeping.
Mom, I feel like I'm on the clouds.
I'm going to tell my friends.
Can I bring my friends home?
Of course.
They can come.
Bring the one who called you a beggar.
I'll teach him a lesson.
You're the best.
Huh?
Mom, are you crying?
Let her be.
Mom sometimes cries.
Oh...
Gwangbak! Gwangbak!
What is it?
I just fell asleep.
Old man's orders.
While I'm away,
exercise with your sister.
I pass.
Hah!
Get up!
Where are you going?
It's Sunday.
I'm going to workout.
Father, come with me.
The mineral spring near here is really nice.
Why are you going there?
You can go to the gym.
This kid I know wants to meet there.
Come with me, father.
No thanks.
I heard lots of hot women go there.
You go ahead.
Let me take a shower.
You'll take a shower afterwards. Just come.
I'm a gentleman.
I should wash my face and brush my teeth.
Hurry up, then.
I'll go first.
Okay.
Come on!
I'm sleepy.
I'm really sleepy.
You're too much...
Can you do that in a pretty way?
You'll never get married like that!
What's this? Huh?
What? What? What's wrong with this?
You're so ugly.
I said to do it pretty!
What if someone sees you?
Why are you making such a fuss?
Who cares if anyone sees me?
I'll exercise anyway I want.
Who exercises in a pretty way?
Look? It can't get any prettier than this.
Don't do stuff like that.
This is great for circulation. Stupid.
Good morning.
Sangnam!
It's not a good morning.
You're an early bird.
You exercise?
You're dead.
Gwangbak!
You should exercise.
I'm done.
She doesn't do that every day.
Does your sister like baseball?
Daebak, I can't believe...
Huh?
- What's this?
- I'm sorry.
Hey! Hey!
Me?
- Don't you know me?
- Excuse me?
How rude!
You should say hello to the elderly!
Uh, hello.
What are you doing? Huh?
I didn't see you. I'm sorry.
Whatever! When are you going to pay me?
Pay you for what?
What do you mean?
Pay me for the extra medical bill!
What are you doing? Seriously!
I don't know where or how you got treated,
but how is that my responsibility?
This is too early in the morning for this!
Next time, I'm calling the police!
Wait a minute.
You don't brush your teeth?
Excuse me?
You should brush your teeth.
Ugh, you smell rotten.
Ugh...
Wow, the food tastes so good.
I should go there every day.
It's so much better than the gym.
Right?
You should exercise, too.
I should. I'm getting a gut.
For men, you're finished if you get a gut.
This? This?
Miho, would you like to join us?
I prefer reading books.
Mom, I'm done.
Tell me about last night's drama.
I missed it yesterday.
Okay.
She's reading all your books.
Is that okay?
She's into dating books.
It's good to read many books.
But they're all about dating.
Oh, who cares if they are?
As long as they're not rated R.
I learned Korean with comic books, aunt.
There's nothing she shouldn't read.
I'm sure there is!
I read them all before I was 19 years old.
Once she really discovers the joys of reading,
we can steer her into another direction.
That'd be nice.
She's a regular dating expert.
I wonder what she's going to become.
She'll become successful, I'm sure.
Let's go look at a bulldozer after coffee.
It's used, but it's in good condition.
Okay.
Oh, why don't you come, too?
Oh, right.
I saw that rude girl.
Where?
On the way to the mineral spring.
She must be collecting trash.
She was walking around in sweatpants.
Why does she do that?
How should I know?
Go to that cafe when you have time.
She didn't even brush her teeth!
I told her to pay up but she said she'll call the police.
Father, I think you should stop.
I'm not serious about the money.
I just want to teach her some manners.
I have a feeling she's going to get you.
No way! I'm getting that money!
Just watch me.
Daebak!
I made them run into each other,
and she got mad at me.
Where did you meet?
At the mineral spring.
Wearing dirty sweatpants?
Yes.
- She didn't wash her face?
- No.
- She didn't brush her teeth?
If I were you, I'd go mad.
Why? You said it's nice to run into each other.
A dog would understand me better than you.
When will you ever grow up?
Hello?
Is this the parcel service office?
I have a question.
This is Sangdo-dong,
and who's in charge of this area?
Sangdo-dong?
It's Mr. Ko Minjung.
Mr. Ko Minjung?
May I ask you why you're asking?
Oh, he's here.
Should I put him on?
Hello?
How strange.
What is it?
Some woman asked for the man in charge of Sangdo-dong
and hung up when I offered to put you on the phone.
Was there a delivery accident?
No.
Welcome.
To my room.
Did you see?
Only a little.
Enjoy your stay.
The black shopping bag.
That's yours.
Excuse me?
I'm sorry about what happened before.
You look to be in good shape.
Do you work out?
What do you do?
I don't like to limit myself,
so I do a little bit of everything.
That costs no money.
You're pretty funny.
I hear that often.
They say I'm addictive.
You don't seem very old,
so why are you so casual with me?
Are you annoyed?
If you are, be casual with me.
Although I doubt you have the guts.
Ugh!
It's me.
What are you up to today?
I have plans.
Next week?
I don't even know what'll happen tomorrow,
so how can I know about next week?
Can I make a reservation, then?
You're full of confidence, aren't you?
Do you like movies?
I don't like the theaters.
That's great.
You will like it if you go with me.
I'll buy the tickets.
Don't make any plans that day.
I'll see you then.
Sangnam!
Can you take this to your sister right now?
What is it?
You'll find out.
- Gwangbak.
- Yes?
Can you mend my sock?
You do it.
Don't you feel sorry for your uncle?
Man!
Explain in English under 3 minutes
how feeling sorry for you and having a hole in
your sock are related within the metaphysical and behavioral psychological scope.
Incredible.
I'll mend it.
Why are you home so late?
Didn't I tell you to come straight home?
If you do badly at school,
I get yelled at.
Uncle, don't you have any friends?
Set her up with someone.
She's always after me!
How dare you!
I could get men line up at the front door if I wanted to meet one.
Who do you think I am?
You think I'm this way because I'm lonely?
No respect at all!
You get back down here!
He wouldn't.
You deserved that.
Uncle!
What are you doing?
Can't you tell? I'm packing.
Let's call the movers.
This is too much.
You know how expensive they are?
We don't have much stuff anyway.
I'll pack a little every day.
What's that?
A present.
Are you crazy?
How much was it?
It's not for you.
It's for me.
Who gave you that?
A guest.
Because I'm funny.
Where are the boys?
Asleep.
They passed out after playing soccer.
These are all junk!
Why don't you throw this away?
Man! Don't!
Throw that out.
That's just a pot.
Just dump it.
We're making money to spend it.
We don't have money to spend.
We must be frugal to pay back the loan.
We're being frugal to death.
I can't throw this one away.
This pot was my first love.
You said I was your first love.
Women always say "This is my first time."
They are all liars.
When we just got married,
we cooked instant noodles in this,
made soybean paste stew in this,
and made kimchi stew in this.
We started out with two spoons and this pot.
This is that pot?
Hey, pot! Long time no see.
Was it you who game me that big bump here?
You're all dented because of crashing into me.
You're happy to see me, too, aren't you?
He says yes.
It's been with us since the beginning,
so let's make this a family treasure.
That's a bit too much...
Knock!
Why?
What is it?
Let's go to the baseball game tonight with the matchmaker.
How can you give this to me now?
What time is it?
Hurry, hurry!
Let's root for our respective teams and meet back up later right here.
Who is it?
It's me.
Father.
I dropped by on the way home.
I bought you some meat and fruit.
Come in.
No, I should go home.
Where is Minjung?
He hasn't come home yet.
Not yet?
Minjung, are you in here?
Father, what brings you by?
Please have a seat.
You're staying here?
I heard you had a fight.
I'm sorry.
It was so much fun.
When my team hit a home run at the end...
The ball flew over Gwangbak's head, wow.
Did you see that?
That was amazing.
What were you doing?
Why didn't you jump and catch the ball?
How could I jump that high?
You can jump high enough when you're trying to beat me with your baseball bat.
Really?
Don't even get me started.
Once she goes crazy,
she goes all the way.
That's not true!
Especially when she got dumped.
I don't get dumped.
I dump.
Getting dumped is actually better.
The dumped can sleep fine at night,
but the one who does the dumping can't.
I don't know because that never happened to me.
Nobody here believes you.
I'll send you the pictures you took with those women.
Okay.
You look nice with beautiful women.
Hurry up and eat.
Don't you have homework?
Sangnam, how did your blind date go?
It's still going on.
Is she pretty?
I guess she is.
You don't like ugly women, right?
Right.
Me neither.
It's late.
Mom and dad must be waiting.
Let me go to the bathroom.
Do you still think of me first thing when you wake up?
Excuse me?
You said you think of me first.
You think of someone when you wake up.
That's a serious problem.
No, it's not like that.
It's not?
I was really upset at the time, so that's why.
Only because of that?
Oh, I see.
I thought you were being real.
Let's forget it, then.
What's wrong with you?
What?
I want to help, but you won't let me.
What do you mean?
Haven't you learned anything from other women?
What are you wearing?
Wear and mini skirt and show some cleavage.
What?
Men actually like stuff like that.
Nothing stands out about you!
You're all bland.
Who'd like that?
I wouldn't!
Mother.
- Have a seat.
- There's no need.
Are you happy staying here all alone?
Why do we have to suffer because of you?
I'm sorry.
You're always apologizing.
Why have you changed so much?
I heard my husband dropped by.
So why didn't you go home?
I can't believe how stubborn you are.
You're not worried about Subak at all?
She's very frustrated.
And how could you slap her?
It's not like you did anything to help her.
Go home and beg for forgiveness.
I wouldn't have taken this if things were different.
I'd tell her to get a divorce.
My husband yelled at Subak.
Go home tonight if you're really sorry.
Understand?
I'm so upset.
How dare you do this after losing all your money?
[Acacia Room Salon
1. Age: 20 to 25 (Female)
2. Inexperienced are welcomed]
Hello?
I'm Don.
- What are you looking at?
- Oh, mom.
Are you crazy?
Is this what you were looking at when you go out?
No, I don't.
Mom, give me ten dollars.
Ten dollars my butt.
Pants, pants... Pounding pants...
- What is it?
- Loser,
would you like to make ten dollars?
Ten dollars?
Who is it?
It's the new owner of this apartment.
Oh, okay.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Yes.
Here comes the C.E.O.
Don't you have slippers?
We don't.
The C.E.O. wanted to take a look around.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
Congratulations on moving in.
He doesn't shake hands with just anyone.
Oh, okay.
We're packing, so it's messy here.
The woman, I mean, your wife came alone and checked everything the last time.
My wife?
She's supposed to be in France,
so when did she come here?
- Don.
- Yes, sir.
Don't let the help run wild.
My deepest apologies.
I think the housekeeper was here.
Did she say she was my wife?
She checked everything here after signing the contract, so I assumed...
Hobak is meticulous...
I'll talk to her.
She sometimes does pretend to be your wife.
Fire her tomorrow.
May I?
I'd love to, but I'll let that pass.
Excuse me, but which company do you...
This guy is...
I mean, he is the C.E.O. of a big company.
That's all you need to know.
Or else I'll have to kill you.
It's too small.
I'd feel claustrophobic.
He rides a motorcycle inside his current home.
Excuse me, but if you want to see better,
you should take those sunglasses off.
Don.
He doesn't like to be talked to that way.
This, this, this.
Take all of these out.
She said she's going to use them.
That housekeeper woman.
Don.
Stop interfering while he's talking.
This, this and this, take them out.
And call Italy and get custom furniture.
And the ceiling.
Cry... The... Chan, chan... Hurry!
Crystal chandelier.
So you did major in English.
Import that.
And redo the floor with marble.
Get a new toilet and bathroom sink.
I'm sorry for interfering,
but that'll cost 10 times more than the apartment.
Maybe you should pick another apartment.
Don.
We won't interfere.
We won't.
Especially the bathtub.
Make one with gold.
And put diamonds all around the edge, okay?
Okay.
Did you see that?
This is the power of money.
You're totally nuts.
Did you see how they were looking at you?
They were looking at you like you're nuts.
Who cares?
Wow, I can feel how beautiful this world is deep down to my bones.
I'm going nuts!
If you had two apartments,
your bones would be burning up.
You think I'm a joke?
You're not a joke.
Where are you coming from?
Lunch...
Just how many hours do you need for lunch?
You think this is your playground?
Just what are you doing here?
I know, but...
You do?
I do, but you're too much.
You're younger, but you don't respect me.
It's not like I have to work here.
I don't believe this.
You still don't get it, do you?
Stop being so rude.
If you don't want to hear this, work hard!
Listen carefully.
If this happens again,
I'm going to fire you.
Go!
You only got this job because of your wife.
You should be embarrassed.
What are you looking at?
What? Your wife got this job for you.
You can't fire me!
I quit!
Oh, man!
I'm going nuts.
Oh, I should just die.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
I heard you went to a wedding.
You didn't bring any rice cakes?
Rice cake my butt!
What are you doing?
I'm mending my sock.
You look miserable.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm going to start working tomorrow.
I can't believe you.
Hey!
Why didn't you mend your brother in law's sock?
Why can't you introduce him to a woman?
I want to, but I can't sell him.
What?
How can she say that?
Stop.
You never win.
- How dare you!
- Oh, the needle.
What are you doing?
Huh?
You should've checked the inventory and made sure the stores are well stocked!
You're all awful!
Sis!
Don't call me sis.
When did you get here?
Just now. I didn't come earlier. No way.
What is it?
I wanted to go home with you.
I'm meeting Minjung, so join us.
Let's have dinner.
I heard about your apartment.
Congratulations, Hobak.
Thanks.
I have to pay back the loan to actually own it, but I'm happy.
Happy?
You're busy checking on others.
What do you mean by that?
She feels bad about Subak and you.
It's like buying an apartment is a crime.
It's not like she stole the money,
but she doesn't know what to do.
You don't have to be.
I know.
Stop it.
Minjung, enjoy.
I'm buying to celebrate.
I'll buy, to congratulate you.
No, I'm buying.
Whoever's buying, let's enjoy it.
You too, Sedal.
I will, of course.
I'm not going to worry about others.
Owning my own home feels great.
You don't know, do you?
Why wouldn't he know?
He owned a really big one before.
I had forgotten.
That was a long time ago.
As for me, it feels really vivid. Vivid.
Can I order one more portion of pork belly?
What are you talking about?
Don't make Hobak uncomfortable.
We're us and they are them.
She worked to get that place,
so congratulate her from your heart.
Did Hobak say I'm making her uncomfortable?
She didn't say that.
Whose side are you on?
What do you mean by that?
I was just...
You haven't been home for several days,
and all you can talk about is Hobak?
Hobak's more important to you than me, huh?
You've always been like this.
You always took Hobak's side.
You never paid attention to what I said.
When were you ever on my side?
Why don't you just go live with Hobak?
Watch what you say.
These are things you should never say.
But I'm right!
She knows better about what you like and don't like.
That's because she worked at our house.
That too.
When she worked at our house,
you got upset about making her work.
You told me to pay her more.
And now you want me to suck up to her?
She bought an apartment just to get on my nerves,
and now you're yelling at me?
You don't care about my feelings, do you?
Let's not do this.
Not do what?
I'm going crazy as I am,
so why are you so mean to me?
What's all the noise?
Please keep it down.
You always fight and cry.
I can't take this anymore.
I'm sorry.
You should be more considerate.
If you keep this up,
I'm kicking you out!
Ouch! Ouch, ouch...
Ouch... I have to pack.
I'll do it.
I told you we should've hired movers.
Did you do something wrong?
Not at all.
I just feel you've been working too hard.
Are you on drugs?
I can't afford any drugs.
They say you change when you're about to die.
You have me and the boys, so don't change.
I won't.
Honey, let's make a baby tonight.
I said my back hurts.
There, there! Right there.
Here? Here?
Oh, oh, that feels good.
You didn't quit your job, did you?
No way.
Go ahead and try it.
I'll kill you and kill myself.
We have to save every penny we can to pay back the loan.
I've been saving!
Every penny.
Wedding anniversary.
Black bean noodles.
Thank you.
Black bean noodles on our anniversary?
If you don't want this, don't eat it.
Oh, you're so stingy.
Let's see how well you do, making your husband starve.
I'm saving every penny until we buy a house.
This is the last time we're eating out.
Oh, it's delicious.
I'm going nuts.
Oh, man...
Mom.
What are you doing here?
I came during my lunch break to see you.
- I'll do it.
- Leave it.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Put yourself in other's shoes, as our family motto says.
I asked because you had the money.
You said no, though.
And you go and buy yourself an apartment?
How could you do it at a time like this?
I know.
I know the timing was really bad.
But it just worked out that way.
I didn't plan on it.
You shouldn't have acted like that.
She's suffering from depression.
Go see Subak.
I'm going to.
Subak, you're home, aren't you?
I'll drop by.
Hello?
Okay. I'll be right over.
I can't get it?
No.
We can't loan you the amount you requested,
but we can loan you half.
That won't do.
I must pay the balance on the apartment.
You have good credit, so I tried. I'm sorry.
Oh, how scary!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Hello.
And you are?
I've met you once before.
I'm Heo Sedal's wife. Sedal is...
I know why you're here,
but this won't work... Oh!
Oh...
What's going on?
Where are you?
I'm at the hotel, of course.
Where in the hotel?
At the lobby.
I'm at the lobby.
Why? Why are you there?
I came to see you but you're not here.
I'm up at the office right now.
I'm too busy to come down, so cut to the chase.
The bank won't loan me the money.
They won't?
How can they reject us after all this time?
How much are you short?
$20,000.
$20,000?
You bought an apartment when you don't have the money?
You sure are gutsy.
No one buys a home with their own money.
They all get loans.
Are you eating something?
I'm eating a bun.
How can you eat during working hours?
It's my break.
They gave me some snacks.
Don't take everything people give you.
Wait, the manager said something weird.
Something weird?
You met the manager?
What did he say?
Something like, "This won't work."
Don't listen to him.
He's a bastard.
You should go.
Don't hang around there.
Don't do anything stupid and keep this job.
Don't worry. Go!
People will talk if they see you.
It's all my fault.
I'll do my best.
I'll give you the respect you deserve.
So please, please give me a chance.
You'd be saving my life if you do.
Subak.
Are you sleeping?
What is it?
I got you some mangoes, your favorite.
The first time I'd ever tried it was at your house.
They were so good.
You like mangoes.
You're pretty funny.
I'm sorry.
I should've told you first,
but I couldn't because I felt so bad.
Please understand.
Do you cook?
Oh, why don't you cook?
There's nothing in the fridge.
These instant foods are expensive and bad for you, too.
These are for when you go camping.
Stop.
You just repeated what my husband said.
Did you two have a secret meeting?
What do you mean?
What did you say to Minjung?
I didn't say much.
I just said I feel bad.
You're funny.
How can you meet him behind my back?
I didn't want to say this, but you must be heartbroken
because the man you love is in trouble.
How could you say that?
There are things you should never say.
Shut up! How dare you talk to me that way?
Are you mocking me?
You're happy that I ended up here?
Why did you come?
To check to see if I'm dead?
To brag about your new place?
Fine! I am happy.
I bought an apartment to make you mad.
Are you satisfied?
What?
You're horrible!
You think you can say anything?
How can you just blurt things out?
Did you?
Did you feel happy when I was struggling?
You think I'm like you?
What? What did you say?
How dare you!
Why not?
You say whatever's on your mind! Why can't I?
You're the older sister.
So act like it!
You!
Take these back.
What do you think you're doing?
I won't eat what you buy.
They're disgusting.
Disgusting?
Yes!
Get out!
I don't want to see you!
Fine.
I'll give them to my boys.
You might think these are nothing,
but my boys have never even tried these.
Did you know that?
You're horrible!
Horrible?
How dare you!
You! Horrible?
Horrible!
That's right! I'm horrible!
Wait a minute.
- Oh, no.
- Excuse me!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Mom.
How dare you!
How could you!
You grabbed Subak's hair?
And you called her names?
I didn't. She grabbed my hair.
If your father finds out, he'll be furious.
How could you grab your older sister's hair?
How could you do that?
How dare you treat Subak like that?
You said you bought the place to rub it in her face?
You said you were happy she's bankrupt?
It's like you're having a barbecue while the next door people are starving to death.
Are you trying to drive her mad?
Mom.
She's suffering from depression already!
When I got the call,
I was so furious, so I came to see you.
Let's go.
Go and beg Subak to forgive you.
No.
What?
I said no.
I won't apologize.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Hey!
You're not going to see Subak again? Huh?
Hobak, mom wants you.
What's that?
It's for you.
It's so pretty.
I wanted it but she's giving it to you.
Why are you...
But you bought it for yourself.
I bought it because it's so pretty,
but I think it'll look better on you.
I have nowhere to wear this to.
You wear it.
Or give it to Yeongdal.
Oh, why would I give it to her?
It's for my daughter in law.
Wear pretty clothes and meet your friends.
You're a homeowner now!
I want you to do your hair, but you won't come.
Say what you want to say.
You're very sharp.
I heard you were a good student.
Please take me with you.
I would be very useful.
I'll take care of the boys,
and you can go meet your friends.
Right.
Mother.
I'm not going to change my mind.
I bought the apartment so the boys could have their own rooms,
so I won't be able to take you until I move to a bigger place.
You're heartless.
Ask anyone.
You're the worst daughter in law ever.
Yes, I am bad.
I'm already having a very hard time!
Oh, I can't believe you said that.
This is why your mother mistreats you.
Now I understand.
Your mom has a good reason to hate you!
She hates you because you're mean!
Please stop!
Oh, my...
Why are you yelling at my mom?
Why are you doing this to me?
You stay out of this!
Just leave me alone, please!
What's wrong with you?
Please might think I hit you or something.
I know.
Sintong! Bangtong!
Hobak!
Come out!
Where are you?
Hobak!
What are you doing?
Come out.
Come out. I have something to show you.
I shouldn't have bought that apartment.
Why?
Did something happen?
Is it because of the money?
I took care of it through my company.
Then what?
Why is everyone getting on my case?
So I bought a house. So what?
Did Don's sister in law say something?
She says I'm having a barbecue while Subak is starving to death.
She was having an all out party while we were starving to death!
Don't. Don't go.
Let go! Let go of me!
Hey! Honey, honey!
Hey! No! Don't go! Don't go!
No! Hey! Sedal!
Don't go!
Hey!
Hey! Heo Sedal! Stop right there!
Oh, no...
Mother!
Isn't that goof-off?
Mother, come out.
Mother, Subak, come out.
And father, come out, too.
We've been out for a while now.
Are you crazy? What are you doing?
Mother.
What? I'm here. What do you want?
If you have something to say, sit down.
I'm sorry, father.
I have something to say to mother.
Okay. Let's hear it.
Have you been drinking?
Yes, I had a drink.
You came here drunk?
You have no manners whatsoever, do you?
Don't you have any respect for me?
Goof-off, let's go.
Let me go!
Let him go.
Let's hear him out.
Go ahead.
I have no bad feelings toward you, father.
But mother,
you shouldn't be like that.
Why do you treat her that way?
And what way is that?
She deserves compassion.
Where's Subak?
I won't ever forgive her for this!
You won't forgive her?
How dare you say that?
Be quiet!
What did she do wrong?
The apartment she bought,
she bought it by living on a very tight budget, never wasting any money.
It's her sweat and blood.
Do you know how hard her life is?
She lives on pain relieving patches.
She works in a dusty warehouse,
doing things that are hard even for men.
She never buys anything for herself,
not even food, and she digs through clothes donation bins to get clothes for the boys.
She wears my old underpants.
That's how she bought that apartment,
so is that a crime?
Why do we have to tip toe around Subak and be accommodating to her?
Was Hobak adopted or something?
The whole neighborhood knows that you only love Subak.
Have you ever given my boys a hug?
You take care of Subak's girls.
But we had to leave our boys with strangers.
Have you ever taken care of my boys?
That was how she bought that apartment.
So why do you make her cry? Why?
- Stop it. Let's go.
- Let go!
We should go.
Let go!
Mother,
don't ever do that to Hobak.
If you ever
disrespect her
or break her heart,
I won't just sit and watch.
She is
my woman and my wife!
Let's go.
Subtitles by KBS World
Was yelling at his mother in law okay?
What he said was right.
Try living without your wife.
I don't think I can handle this much longer.
I can't stay with him.
Father's really angry.
I won't go back unless he changes.
Make your husband get down on his knees in front of mom and apologize.
Okay.
I don't believe my eyes.
You must be a very busy man.
You're very feisty today.
Let me know if you need anything.
I don't think I can come today.
What did you just say?