Subtitles by KBS World
I think I've seen him before.
Where?
I can't remember.
Stop staring at him like that.
Let me introduce my family.
Gwangbak, I'll do it. I know how it's done.
This is the eldest member of the family
and my best buddy's mother, Mrs. Angyesim.
She fled to the south during the Korean War,
and whenever something happens, she goes,
"The Korean War was nothing compared to this."
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Let's here from the original. Mom?
Why you little!
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
I should just die.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Next is the center of this family, father.
He says "What?" all the time and gets on
mother's nerves, but he always puts himself
in other's shoes, and he's a well respected
member of this community!
What is he doing?
It's funny.
She says she's never seen son in laws like us and keeps teasing us.
Such a tease!
What?
They say that in a comedy show.
The one who's always nagging on us, mother!
And she doesn't have any dollar undies.
I can't believe my ears!
Okay! Next is
the man who used to live in a huge apartment
but is now living with his in laws, Mr. Ko!
As you can see, our eyes are,
the son in laws here have bulging eyes,
so you have a long way to go.
You should keep smacking the back of your head.
I'll try my best.
The eldest daughter of this family.
I was in the Miss Korea pageant.
And she hasn't forgotten that experience.
Next is the second son in law,
and that's me.
You're not next.
I know.
Hello?
Can you deliver the next person in line?
Yes! The man just arrived!
My best friend since middle school.
No way.
"I know" is what this man says most often,
and he's the kangaroo of this family.
A penniless loser, Wang Don!
And you're a goof-off!
This is nutty, nutty, nuts!
The 7th person of this family, not me,
because I'm younger than Ms. Wang Hobak.
Ms. Scrooge.
A self made woman.
She has no special charms.
She does.
I'm sorry, but I'll ignore that.
And the third daughter of this family!
The woman of the night, Wang Gwangbak!
She was a teacher until recently, but she quit in order to achieve her dream
which led to endless nagging by mother
and has turned her into a kangaroo, Gwangbak!
Yes, yes, yes.
Even the applause sounds different as she is the woman of the hour.
Next is Wang Haebak who needs no description.
She's at the top of her entire student body.
What do you want to become?
Yes, she's going to become a judge.
Oh! The college entrance exam is near.
Is everything going okay?
Keep up the good work.
I want a professional in the family.
Let me introduce myself.
What about me?
Oh! How could you forget him?
Where are you?
Why aren't you replying?
Oh, my mistake.
No explanation is necessary.
Father and mother had him on an impulse.
This family's youngest child, Wang Daebak.
Incredible.
And finally, I might be
dark skinned and have bulging eyes,
but I'm the rising sun
because I just got a new set of wings
and is about to soar.
I went from just Sedal to "my Sedal,"
a Cinderella of all son in laws,
Heo Sedal.
I told you I'm at my in laws house.
It's not like I wanted to come.
I didn't want to cause any trouble.
Baby,
I'm here, but in spirit, I'm with you.
Yes.
Thank you so much for welcoming me.
I never met you before,
but I feel like I'm already a member.
It's a big family, so the introduction ran long.
What do you do?
I'm a heavy equipment operator.
Things like excavators and bulldozers.
Heavy equipment operator?
He owns his own company.
You're so young!
I know.
I didn't build the company.
My father built it and I expanded it.
And my father built his own fortune.
How much do you make a year?
It's different every year, so I can't...
But I make a decent earning.
That's not enough.
You should travel and buy expensive bags.
I make enough money for that.
You do?
You're lucky, Gwangbak.
Where would you live after you're married?
Will you buy an apartment?
He runs his own company, so of course.
Well...
We'll be living with his father.
There's no other family, and his house is big, so we can use the second floor.
Where's your mother, then?
It's just my father.
What kind of car do you drive?
I drive a truck.
He has a sports car, too.
What kind of sports car?
Everyone has a car, so we need to know.
It's not a very expensive one.
I used to have a luxury car, too.
But it's all in the past.
What did you like about Gwangbak?
I never told her this before,
but I fell in love with her at first sight.
Incredible.
No way.
How romantic.
After meeting her a few times,
I loved everything about her.
Those are some really colorful words.
You should be honest.
Can I have one of those?
Has your mother passed away?
My parents are divorced.
They are? When?
When I was in third grade.
Your father never remarried?
No.
They struggled a lot, but now they're like friends.
And his aunt has been running the house.
That's one thing I don't like.
People get divorced all the time.
Like marriage, divorce is a choice.
That's so irresponsible!
It's better than being unhappily married.
But divorce shouldn't be taken lightly.
But it was his parents.
Why did they divorce?
Did your father have an affair?
No, he didn't.
I heard it was because of financial difficulties.
Where did you go to school?
Excuse me?
I'm hungry. Can we have dinner?
Yes, I'm starving.
Let's get dinner ready.
Did you study abroad?
Actually,
I didn't go to college.
You didn't go to college?
No.
I dropped out of high school.
So you only have a middle school diploma?
You promised you wouldn't say.
I couldn't help it.
And I didn't want to lie.
What should we do?
They all looked really surprised.
Even my underclothes are soaked.
I've never been so scared and nervous before.
They'll say no, right?
If
they say no,
we couldn't marry, could we?
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
A middle school graduate?
She has no taste in men!
I don't like that his parents are divorced.
I know.
He said it was from financial reasons,
but who knows what really happened?
Maybe his father was caught cheating,
or maybe his mom was into gambling.
Getting divorced isn't a big deal now.
If that's true, why do unhappy women stay married until their children are married?
You have to consider the family, too.
I think that's important, too.
But he seemed pretty rich.
But money isn't everything.
Bong, what do you think?
I'm sure he feels the same way.
I don't know about the other things,
but his education is a problem.
Education based social system is a problem,
but middle school? How do you communicate?
That's not true.
I never felt any educational gap.
And he finished his junior year in high school.
He dropped out during summer vacation.
But everyone goes to college these days.
Why did he drop out?
Number 1, he was a bad student.
Number 2, he was a trouble maker.
Number 3...
He bought an excavator with college tuition and started working really early.
And that's how he built his company up.
It's much better than being unemployed even with a college degree.
Did you say that to us?
Us?
Don't drag me into it.
I don't believe you!
- I'll have to kill you.
- Mom! Mom.
How could you bring a man like that home?
All my efforts went down the drain!
You saved yourself all these years to meet a man like him?
A middle school graduate excavator operator?
How could you disappoint me like this?
How could you bring someone like that?
Are you out of your mind?
I had high hopes for you!
I wanted you to meet a doctor or a judge!
How could you meet someone like him?
Get out of my house!
I know what you're worried about,
but I love him as he is.
Despite his parents, he's a good man,
and I never thought about his education because he's smart and wise.
In my opinion, he's a great man.
I hope you'll respect my decision.
Why are you so quiet?
Does this even make sense?
Don't even think about saying yes.
Come down to the kitchen.
I'm sorry, father.
You don't have to be.
And there's no sense in dragging this on.
Before it becomes too serious,
I thought I'd tell you how I feel.
Father.
The final decision is yours, of course,
and to be frank, you two could get married.
It's not like it's against the law.
But as your father,
I can't say yes to this marriage.
You're getting a life partner.
A marriage isn't something
that's based on sparks between two people.
It's a major event in a person's life,
so you must look at everything.
What if he suffered some sort of trauma after his parents divorce?
And,
I'm not comfortable with his education.
Having skills is a good thing,
and I have a friend who's in that field.
It's a good job for a man,
and you don't have to worry about retiring.
But education is another matter.
I didn't know before he told me, father.
I never had trouble talking to him.
I actually learned a lot from him.
He read lots of books to overcome it,
and he grew up to be a really decent guy.
Father, what college he attended isn't important compared to how he's lived.
The size of his house isn't important compared to how great his character is.
Those things are more important to me.
Not having a college degree isn't a problem.
I'm not talking about the degree.
They don't just teach knowledge at school.
Why do you think people attend 16 years of school?
If it's just for the knowledge,
everyone can study alone and take exams.
Why would you bother to go to school?
Including knowledge,
you learn about life.
School gives you various experiences.
It may not be a problem now,
but later on, it could become one.
I wish
you would change your mind.
Before it's too late.
Can we talk?
You're still up?
I'm not sleepy at all.
It's like I'm waiting for my scores after a test.
What happened?
What did your parents say?
I bet there was a debate after I left.
Be honest with me.
What score did I get?
You flunked, of course.
I flunked?
I didn't pass?
We have to break up now?
Well...
Be honest with me.
Is that it?
No.
I was just kidding.
Passed!
You passed.
Really?
I really passed?
I passed!
Aunt!
She said I passed.
Really?
Can you whip something up?
Let's celebrate.
Why did you wake me up?
Have a seat, Daese.
Sangnam has something to tell you.
Okay. Go ahead.
Congratulations, father.
You're getting a daughter in law.
What?
You're awake now, aren't you?
I am!
Who is it? Bring her right now! Right now!
Wait until tomorrow.
I actually met her.
What? Without tell me?
It was like a pre-interview.
They do that before the main interview.
So? How was she?
She's perfect for Sangnam.
Sangnam told her he's poor, he dropped out
of school and has to live with his father,
and she still said yes.
She's a good woman.
Just the type I was looking for.
When did you meet her?
Uh, that's the odd part.
You know her, too.
The freelance reporter who interviewed me.
I thought she wasn't your type.
But I knew it.
I knew it from the way you drank that night.
I want to meet her parents.
You should meet her first.
Should I bring her this weekend?
This weekend?
Okay.
If you like her and if you like her,
I'm okay with her.
I can't understand the parents who oppose their children's marriage.
Can you get me a grandchild first?
Father!
Okay!
For my future daughter in law!
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
Subak!
You got here in a cab?
You could've taken the subway.
I can't do that on my first day.
That would look bad.
Where's your CEO?
The CEO?
I should say hello.
You don't need to do that yet.
Where's the shop?
I hope it's in downtown.
I don't deal with just anyone.
I want to go to Cheongdam or Apgujeong.
I was in the Miss Korea pageant, you know.
You need to be trained first.
I hate stuff like that.
I hate studying or training.
I couldn't stand studying, even as a student.
You already know that!
Can I just skip training?
If you don't want any training...
Follow me.
But your outfit is...
What?
That looks uncomfortable.
I was in the Miss Korea pageant.
I have class.
You can work here for today.
What am I supposed to do here?
They're all experienced, so learn from them.
She's new, so please work with her.
- Okay, manager.
- Yes, director.
Hey, Hobak!
Lady!
Me?
Is there anyone else standing there?
How do you expect to work in that?
We have to sort these and clean this room.
- Put this on.
- Oh, my!
I'm not putting that on.
Move all of these over there.
She's getting the same pay as us.
Where did they find her?
It's her first day, so go easy on her.
Give it to me.
Oh, my! Oh, my!
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Oh, man! I don't...
Move to a shop?
Yes, you've been here for a long time.
Thank you for all your hard work.
The position is the same but with more pay.
Thank you, director.
I love money.
Who doesn't?
I'm more extreme.
I think I'm addicted to money.
You'll be in charge of the biggest shop
and a few smaller ones, too.
Your work hours will be more flexible.
You have kids, right?
Really?
Thank you so much!
You have a driver's license, don't you?
You'll need a car.
I can't afford one yet.
The company will pitch in.
You need mobility to manage the shops.
Thank you, director.
Thank you so much.
Mom, are we going somewhere?
No.
I want to take a picture of you.
What for?
So I can look at it whenever I want.
Miho,
give me a big smile.
Oh, Miho, you're so pretty.
Look over there.
Can we stop? I think that's enough.
Stay still.
Now for a video.
Let's go eat.
Hey,
pretty lady.
Come with us.
We need to get pork rinds to wipe the dust off.
Pork rinds?
Of course.
Pork rinds and a shot of soju.
I can't eat stuff like that.
You look like you can eat anything.
Let's just leave her here. I'm starving.
Come with us, okay?
Oh, my!
I don't believe this!
Oh!
Hey, Subak.
Where are you?
How could you leave me here all alone?
Why are you alone?
Okay. I'll be right over.
How could you do this to me?
How dare you!
How could you get me a job like this?
I thought it was at a shop!
I was in the Miss Korea pageant!
You said you didn't want to train.
You need training to work at the shop.
But you're a manager!
Why can't you use your influence?
Did you do this to me on purpose?
Some man was trying to hit on me.
He did?
Whenever he saw me, he winked at me.
How could you put me through that?
He twitches.
He does that.
He does?
You said you wanted to see our daughter.
You have pictures?
I have a few.
Look.
She's our daughter.
She's pretty.
She looks just like you.
You think she's pretty?
Yes.
She is.
Good sho...
What's wrong with that ball?
It won't go where it's supposed to.
You should teach that ball a lesson, and me.
Baby, I'm sorry.
What are you up to these days?
I'm in a difficult situation.
It's hard to keep my in laws away from you.
Should we go on a trip?
A trip?
Where?
Wherever.
Somewhere nobody can reach us.
I'm concerned.
You went to work today? How was it?
She quit right away.
What?
She took me to a warehouse
and told me to clean it.
The men were all hitting on me,
and women teased me.
I tried really hard to stay, but...
She knows you can't work there!
You should work at a shop!
You'd attract a crowd!
Hobak did it to piss you off.
Don't say stuff like that.
It's me.
Speak of the devil.
- You're here!
- Yes.
- Dinner?
- I ate.
If you haven't, have some.
No, I already ate.
I thought you're a manager, so how could you do that to your sister?
She said she didn't want any training.
What training? I can just do it!
That's not how it goes!
Everyone needs some kind of training.
You should be grateful.
Then come to my school and work.
School?
Subak would be a great teacher.
You need a teaching license for that.
You can clean the restrooms.
What?
This is why Hobak looks down on her.
Subak can't do anything.
Was she a good student?
Did she ever have a job?
Cleaning the restrooms is perfect for her.
It is perfect for her.
Don't be too picky.
You have to make money when you can.
I know.
Uncle, you stay out of this!
You go clean the restrooms!
Why you little,
have you forgotten? Respect your uncle!
How dare you talk back at your uncle?
I can't believe you, grandmother!
Subak.
Quiet!
This is your pay.
How much is it?
I put in a full day's pay.
Of course, you should.
I spent a lot of money on the cab.
What?
Subak, I'm sorry.
You said you didn't want training.
There's only manual work without training.
If you wanted to, you could've!
I'm trying, but we just can't be friends.
Why can't a manager get me a job?
Okay, Subak.
I'll talk to the director and...
It's okay. Just go.
You really love me, don't you?
Yes.
What were you doing?
Thinking about you.
Meeting the boy made me love you more.
That was when your mom left you?
Some parts were just heartbreaking.
But you grew up to be such a warm man.
I'm very proud of you.
Thank you for that.
But yours is filled with stuff about food.
I ate this today,
I ate this with this person today. Oh, boy.
How come you didn't grow taller?
Oh, instead, your eyes grew bigger.
Good night. Sweet dreams.
Kiss.
This won't do.
I'm coming over. Wait for me.
No, don't come.
Why? You don't miss me?
I look awful right now.
But you always look awful.
No teasing.
Okay.
I won't come tonight then.
I should hang up. Good night.
Good night.
I wish you would change your mind.
Before it's too late.
I'm going home.
Okay.
Sunjeong.
The market?
Okay.
You're like her husband.
I'm like her brother in law.
She wants me to get chicken.
Would you like to come over?
It's okay.
Oh, don't make any plans for this weekend.
Why?
It's a secret. But don't make any plans.
It's mine.
What? I got it first!
No, I was first!
Why don't you pay my doctor's bill?
Why do you keep doing this to me?
Nothing could be more awful than this.
Look who's talking?
I said I never want to see you again!
Why don't you move?
It's you who should move.
I was born and raised here!
I should move?
I can't believe how rude you are!
- What?
- What's going on here?
- Actually...
- I wanted to buy this...
- I grabbed this first...
- He took it...
- I asked why...
- He's saying he had it first!
Excuse me?
This chicken is mine.
It's mine.
Who picked it up first?
- Me.
- It was me.
One of you should give it up.
I can't!
Me neither.
Fine. Let's check the video.
What?
You must have a surveillance camera, right?
In sports games, when the referee isn't sure, they check the video.
I'm at the grocery store. Come quickly.
I'm scared, so come right now.
Hurry up and come.
I can't beat her alone.
She's really good with words.
I think she's calling all her family.
Bring your aunt and Miho.
Oh!
Wait for me!
Oh, this is really hard!
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
I think you reached for it at the same time.
Let me watch it again.
I think I was first.
We watched it dozens of times.
Do you want to report this to the police?
We don't need any police here!
What's going on?
- Uncle.
- Yes?
I came to buy chicken for father,
and I'm sure I picked it up first, but he...
It sounds like it's your fault.
Why would a gentleman like you do this?
Why would you fight over chicken?
But it's age before beauty,
and we did reach for it at the same time,
but I asked her if I could have it...
Let's give this to her.
What's going on?
Let's go, mom.
Is it over?
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
I'm sorry, but let's never meet like this.
Oh, what happened here?
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
How can anyone be that rude?
She didn't let you have it?
I'm making tofu stew, so hold on.
I hope she gets food poisoning.
Father!
Are all girls like that these days?
Not all of them.
The girl Sangnam picked is so nice.
She's not like other girls.
She's polite and genuine.
I did pretty well, didn't I?
I lost because she had more people.
When you get married, have lots of kids.
Can I have a dozen?
I want to stand out.
I know how it's done.
You do?
Mom, can you open the door for me?
Where did all the chicken go?
This isn't going to do any good.
Break up with him.
Mom.
Father, please say yes.
I know we'll be happy.
I want to follow my heart.
Follow who?
Her heart.
I never met anyone like him before.
When I'm with him, I feel so happy.
Everyone feels like that at the beginning.
Your father and I were happy, too!
We smiled every day.
We think the same way, have the same values.
We're a good match.
A good resume doesn't make a good husband.
It's the man who's a good match for me.
I learned a lot watching Hobak and Subak.
You need love to protect your marriage.
Stop talking nonsense!
You quit your job to become a writer,
but you were dating that man?
What's wrong with you?
How dare you bring such a man?
Mom.
Shut up! That's enough.
Father.
I said that's enough!
Why are we even talking about marriage?
At the beginning, things are all so sweet, but don't think that's going to last.
I just can't believe my eyes.
I told you what I wanted from you.
Father.
What are you thinking?
It's nothing.
Huh?
You weren't thinking about me?
I was.
I heard women get worries before the wedding.
It's not that.
Actually...
Yes?
Do you need something?
Just tell me.
Well...
Yes!
I asked your brother in laws to meet me,
and Minjung already said yes,
and this is from Sedal.
I should go.
Now?
Oh, what did you want to tell me?
Later. It's nothing.
Go home. I'll call you later.
- You're going alone?
- Of course.
Don't worry. I can do it.
You trust me, don't you?
I told you about my brother in laws, right?
Good luck.
Okay. I'll get them all.
- You're here?
- Yes.
I was busy.
Thank you for coming.
I wanted to buy you a drink and get advice.
I'm glad you asked.
Welcome.
Yes.
The man of the night always arrives late.
But you're not the man of the night.
You didn't have to point that out.
Shouldn't we be ganging up on him?
We need to break him in.
Right.
What are you doing? It's cold.
Why aren't you in bed?
I'm upset because you're upset.
I can't control my own kids,
the married ones and the single ones.
I thought feeding, clothing and teaching them would be the end of it.
They worry you until you die.
That's what children are.
I know.
There's no correct answer in life, right?
So don't worry too much about it.
- I'm home.
- Why you little!
See how your father can't sleep?
Do you think he wants you to suffer?
You're so immature.
He's speaking from experience. Can't you see?
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
What should I do?
He's a proud man, so if he finds out, he'll break up with me right away.
Does he have an inferiority complex?
No, he doesn't.
I dropped out of college,
so I used to think I was being discriminated whenever someone with
a college degree got better treatment than me at work.
That was from my inferiority complex.
I don't know what to do.
What will you do?
I have to tell him, but I can't.
I can't break up with him.
I never felt this way before.
I wish I could run away with him.
What?
But I love him so much.
You need to change mom and father's minds.
I wont forgive you if just do what you want.
Golf is so much fun.
Did you play your first round?
I will soon.
Do you play golf?
I used to in the past.
Did you hit a hole in one at the Yeongnam Country Club?
Yes.
Do you play golf, too?
I'm not very good. I can play bogey.
I'll take you golfing sometime.
What were you talking about before?
Oh, there's a handicap 1 par 3 hole.
It's real hard but he hit a hole in one.
They planted a tree to commemorate it.
And I remembered seeing his name on it.
A tree?
They planted a tree?
When you hit a hole in one, they do.
It's when you hit from the tee box and make the ball go into the hole at once.
I know that. All in one.
Not all in one. Hole in one.
You hit it once, and it goes in the hole.
I said I know.
Hole in one.
I'm a bit drunk.
You're only a middle school graduate.
Are you drunk?
I'm not.
My speech is a bit slurred.
Did my in laws really say yes?
I doubt they'd welcome such an uneducated person.
Education isn't important.
Your skills are more important.
Of course it's important.
When you meet anyone,
they ask you which college you went to.
Drink.
You might have guessed already,
but my influence with my in laws is big.
I got married before Minjung.
I'm climbing up, rising sun.
He's climbing down, setting sun.
I got wings, he lost his.
He went from "my Minjung" to "your Minjung."
He hit a bogey.
I went from "your Sedal" to "my Sedal."
I hit a birdie.
Or is it an albatross?
Minjung, you're really something.
I couldn't have moved in with my in laws.
No real man should live with his in laws,
and I couldn't live with a mother in law like ours.
I'd rather kill myself.
You have to worry about where you'll be delivering tomorrow,
how to deal with mother's nagging, and how to console Subak.
I really feel sad for you.
Number 1, you're extremely mild tempered.
Number 2, you have no self esteem.
Number 3.
Sedal!
Can you walk home from here?
Yes. It's really close.
Minjung,
forget what Sedal said before.
I'm sorry I acted like that.
I must have had too much to drink.
He can be thoughtless with words,
but he's not a bad man.
I know.
The family evolves around the daughters,
so things can get difficult for us.
I know what I'm getting into.
You and Gwangbak look good together.
Thank you.
Good night, Minjung.
I'll call you.
Okay. Good night.
Okay.
What the...
Oh, my!
How...
Oh, man.
I'm sorry.
Just how much did he drink?
Thanks. You should go.
Yes. Good night.
Yes. Goodbye.
Oh, careful, careful.
Did everything go well?
Sangnam!
Don't.
Yeah, right!
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
You think you're a virgin?
What are you doing?
Why aren't you calling me?
I'm sleeping with my wife.
That's enough. You didn't get any sleep.
If you didn't know this would happen, you're dumber than I thought.
I don't need this from you!
Don't get mad.
Life is short.
You should do what you want to do.
Right.
What happened last night?
The three of us had a lot to drink.
He's a good guy.
Isn't he?
When you get him drunk, you know.
He drank a lot, but he didn't show it.
He watched his manners until the end.
He even took us home.
He probably passed out when he got home.
That's the kind of man you're going to marry.
Good morning.
I should go and exercise.
Water.
Give me water.
Huh?
Oh, man!
What did you do to me last night?
Get dressed before the boys get up.
You'll ruin their appetite.
You...
Tell me the truth.
Did we... Did we do it?
Why are you stuttering?
So did we?
We're married.
What's wrong with doing it?
Why are you acting so strange?
So you were singing out of joy?
Yes! It was great! I thought you had some snake stew for stamina.
This is nutty, nutty, nuts!
You'll wake the boys up.
Lower your voice.
Sintong! Bangtong!
Your mom violated...
What are you doing?
I'm never going to drink again.
The same thing happened 10 years ago,
and look where it got me.
Who delivered me here?
Don't you remember?
How dare he!
Why did he deliver me here?
This was a delivery accident.
Did you punch me?
I had no time to punch you.
Why am I sore all over?
My chin hurts and my butt hurts.
This is nuts!
Cosmetics shop?
Yes.
My friend worked there, and the business was really good.
Then why is it out in the market?
The owner has to move to the States.
And they really don't want to sell.
Mom, we should buy that.
Us?
Women still buy makeup even when they don't have money.
All women wear makeup.
Right.
My beauty salon has been in trouble,
but the problem is money.
If I had money, I would buy that cosmetics shop right now.
Can you sell your beauty salon and get a loan?
Mom, let's go and check the place out.
We can decide after that.
Hello.
- Who is it?
- It's me.
Don.
Oh, Loser, it's you.
I didn't recognize you in that helmet.
I feel so sorry for you.
When will you save enough money to buy a house and get married?
You're not seeing anyone, are you?
No.
I should go.
Goodbye.
I feel bad for him.
Why didn't you say hello to him?
You played with him when you were little.
Are you mad?
Right. Don't ever associate with him.
It's degrading.
Let's go.
The location is nice and there's lots of customers.
We have to buy this shop.
Mom, let's buy it.
You're the president and I'm the vice president.
If I had money, I would buy it right now.
I'll hit a hole in one.
Minjung did it, so I can do it.
This is nuts.
What's this?
I'm sleeping with my wife? What's this?
I'm asking you.
You sent me that last night.
I didn't send this to you.
I don't know why this keeps happening.
If this keeps happening,
I'm going to take extreme measures.
Stop saying stuff like that.
Have you ever hit a hole in one?
No.
Hitting a hole in one will be my goal.
I'm going to get a tree with my name on it.
Hold on.
Yes.
Do you have time for lunch?
Yes, sir.
It must have been hard for you.
I know Hobak can be difficult to handle.
She probably gave you a lot of stress.
She was frugal from the start,
and she never wasted a single penny.
I heard you got $3 a day.
That's just too harsh.
Even Daebak spends more than $3.
You know exactly how I feel!
Let me write it down.
I tend to forget things like this.
I'm a man, too, so I know.
Things happen.
After being married for 10 years,
you could get ideas.
Ideas...
But you must think of your family.
Hobak has made mistakes, but she did well, too.
She's a hard worker and she's frugal.
Even her mom complains about how she
never even bought her dollar undies.
Dollar undies...
But thanks to that,
you bought an apartment, don't you agree?
Yes.
I'm sure she's learned a lesson.
Be a man and be kind to her.
Women are all the same.
A man's word can melt everything away.
Do you understand what I mean?
Yes.
I took notes and it helped.
Thank you for understanding.
- Let's eat.
- Yes.
Please eat.
[Wedding anniversary]
What is it?
Send Sintong and Bangtong to mom's house.
And make yourself pretty and wait for me.
Really?
Okay.
Sintong! Bangtong!
Mom, come out.
Oh, my.
What's all that?
Who sent them?
Beef, fish, abalone, fruits.
There's even mangoes.
There's a card here.
Was it Sedal?
I'm Choi Sangnam, your future son in law.
Mother, I hope you like them.
I told her to break up with him!
Welcome.
This place is too expensive.
Let's go somewhere else.
I want to buy you a beautiful ring so you can show off to your friends.
I'm not making money to eat 12 meals a day.
I'm making it to spend on you.
You always know what to say.
Mom, I can't bark now.
Where are you?
You're with him, aren't you?
No, I'm meeting a friend.
You didn't tell that dropout?
You didn't tell him we don't want him?
How can you call him "dropout"?
He has a name, you know?
Future son in law my butt.
How dare he?
Don't get mad at him.
You should get mad at Gwangbak.
She's encouraging those bums.
Tell him to come and take these back!
And I'll talk to you when you come home!
He sent them, so just eat them.
You like free food.
Bye.
Did you send something to my house?
My mom really loves them.
You earned lots of points.
I'm glad she liked them.
But I think I'm making a mistake.
What do you mean?
You have so many sisters and I'm scared.
Oh, just thinking about it is...
Horrific?
Your father, mother and sisters are all tough,
and I heard the son in laws have troubles, too.
Like how daughter in laws do.
I'm starting to get worried.
Especially about Sedal.
I heard about it.
I passed out.
But we became friends.
Oh, come to my house this weekend.
My father wants to meet you.
You told him about me?
My father already okayed you.
Without even meeting me?
He's always on my side.
And my aunt helped too.
Let's pick one.
What do we do?
We must return them.
Those!
Are these expensive?
Do you like them?
I do, but...
Shh!
Give me your hand.
I'd be happy with a cheap ring, too.
Does it fit?
Like it was made for me.
It's so pretty.
How you feel is important,
but sometimes you need to show it.
This shows how we feel for each other.
You're mine,
and I'm yours.
It's expensive, so don't lose it.
Don't ever remove it from your finger.
We'll never sell them, even if we were desperate.
Subtitles by KBS World
Do you know what today is?
This is the day we're getting a divorce.
You don't feel sorry at all?
Let's not wait until next year.
After you meet my father, let's set a date.
Break up before your parents find out.
You two got rings?
No.
Don't even dream about it.
I'd rather both of us die.
Father, your daughter in law is here!
We have to flee.
Me too?
You're coming with me, aren't you?
I won't be responsible for anything that happens.