Subtitles by KBS World
Yes, yes!
Get up. Make breakfast.
I got it, father.
Minjung, I left when your fever broke.
I made porridge, so eat it and take the medicine.
You should take today off, but you can't, right?
Your heater's broken, so your room's cold.
I'll get it fixed this afternoon.
Don't think about anything.
Just get better.
I've heard about what happened to you.
Cheer up, Minjung and take care of yourself.
Wake up.
Why?
Call Loser right now!
Really?
Thank you for making up your mind.
What is there to thank her for?
She's the one who's desperate.
I'm not desperate.
We were desperate.
I think this was meant to be.
Thanks, friend!
You gave your son and daughter to us.
Thank you for raising your kids for us.
Please don't put it like that.
I'm already angry,
and you saying that is making me furious.
I didn't work so hard to raise my kids,
so they could marry into this family.
You awful girl.
Oh!
You can't hit her when she's pregnant.
Hit me instead, hit me.
What?
Don't feel furious. Think positive.
Right.
Think of this as a good thing, Mrs. Park.
So, what kind of wedding would you like?
I think they should get married right away.
We can't have it this winter.
We can't have weddings back to back.
In lunar calendar, it's two weddings in a year.
Nobody does that.
She can move in first and have the wedding later.
There will be no wedding?
What's wrong with you?
What do you take us for?
Let's go.
Mother.
This is why you seduced her?
Mom, I don't want the wedding now.
What?
I want to look good in my wedding gown.
I don't want to have it when I'm pregnant.
I'll  have it after I give birth.
Sir, I want my wedding after the baby's born.
He's not sir.
He's my older brother, so...
Older brother, I want my wedding later.
Don't say that.
He's your brother in law.
Stop being angry and furious,
and teach your daughter some manners.
How come you didn't teach her anything?
I didn't think she'd end up calling her friend's father "brother in law."
How about getting a marriage certificate first and having the wedding later?
Where will they live?
They can live here.
There's no room here.
Of course, there is.
Haebak can move into my room,
and they can move into her room.
Live with mother in law, brother in law and
his wife who's worse than the mother in law?
She can't do that.
Get them a place.
Can you cook?
No.
Then move in here.
Okay.
- Is it okay with you?
- Yes.
She can't do that!
They need to be on their own.
Don't think I'll cook for you.
I can't take care of both of you.
Let's just take them in for this winter.
How can these children live on their own?
They're not children!
They are old!
I'll find them a place when it gets warm,
so I think they should move in here for now.
Okay, bother in law.
I mean, brother in law.
I'll do it, mom.
Finding a place now is hard.
This is crazy.
How can you be so thoughtless?
You didn't know she was thoughtless?
Don't yell at Yeongdal, mother.
You can beat me up instead.
Why should she beat you up?
If you touch him, I'll get you, okay?
He's not the only one at fault.
Ask anyone.
Mother, that's enough.
She has every right to be upset.
Upset? It's like your heart is shattered.
Now you know how I felt? Mrs. Park?
You better buy furniture and wedding gifts.
Why do we need furniture for one room?
I want family wedding gifts.
You didn't send Hobak with anything,
so why would you say that?
Ask anyone.
Why does my daughter deserve this?
You know I'm being forced to do this, right?
Yes.
You know Yeongdal is precious to me, right?
Mrs. Park,
they just need a bed and a wardrobe.
If you can't afford even that,
we'll get the...
Where will you get the money to buy those?
We don't have money to get them a place!
We should get a loan for that.
I don't believe you.
What are we going to live on, then?
Daebak's still young and Haebak, too.
How can we give uncle everything we have?
We'll get retirement pension,
and we can move into a smaller house.
Ugh.
After Don leaves, it will be
mother, you, me, Haebak, and Daebak.
This house would be too big.
Give me the deeds to this house.
Why do you want that?
You can't.
You better not do anything with it.
That's like our life.
How can newlyweds live in here?
And why not?
This room is a lucky room.
A judge will come out of this room.
We'll have to wait and see.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
You really want to live in this room?
You dumped everyone who offered to buy you
a house and send you on trips abroad,
and you chose Loser?
Your life turned out all wrong!
I can start over.
That will do you no good!
Once it's ruined, it's difficult to fix.
Life isn't a game.
That's not what you said before!
What are you talking about?
You may be my daughter,
but I don't get you at all.
You never laid eyes on men who are poor,
but it's like you lost your head.
Stop drinking so much. I blame the alcohol.
Don said the same thing. Alcohol is to blame.
He regretted it after he got sober.
Is that true? He said that?
Hey!
I ran over from the market when you called.
What's up?
Congratulate me.
For what?
Did you get a job? Where?
It's better than that.
Better than getting a job?
Did you win the lottery?
That's nothing compared to this.
It's not a job or the lottery.
You can't be getting married.
Right. I'm getting married.
You are?
With whom? When?
You had a blind date?
Or that woman Subak introduced you to?
- I knew it!
- Ouch.
You're glowing!
Who is she? How old?
What does she do? Is she pretty?
You know her.
I know her? Who?
Yeongdal.
Yeongdal?
My friend? Sedal's little sister?
Yes.
Incredible.
That can't be.
She's joking with you.
It's not a joke.
She's moving in tomorrow.
Who'd believe that?
Moving in tomorrow?
What else can we do?
She's pregnant.
She doesn't even like men who are poor.
How could you...
Wait a minute.
What did you just say?
Pregnant?
It just happened.
Oh, my good.
She got pregnant? When?
Must I tell you when?
You're not yet, are you?
At least our kid won't be beaten up by yours.
Hold on.
I can't sort this out.
Yeongdal and you?
Oh, uncle!
This isn't a simple matter.
Can you handle Yeongdal?
I'll have to. Oh!
Did you know about Subak's divorce?
What? When? Why?
Oh, it's cold.
I was shivering like a dog.
What took you so long?
I'm sorry.
Make me some fresh fruit juice.
Keep the fridge tidy.
When I ran a tea room, it was so tidy
that all the coffee cans were lined up
and the coffee cups were squeaky clean.
It was the biggest tea room in town,
and it was always packed.
Those were the good old days!
I think she's trying to get something,
so don't let her push your around. Be wise.
Oh, my!
Is it ready yet?
It's ready.
Mother, I need to talk to you.
About what?
I think there's a reason why you come
when nobody else is home but me.
You can tell me.
You're pretty smart.
Come in, this way.
Watch out.
Any scratches, and I'm returning them.
Careful, careful, careful.
Yes, this way.
Mom.
What do you think?
What do you mean?
They told you to do this by yourself?
She's my only sister in law, so I should.
You must be a saint.
If I do my part, I can demand them to do theirs.
Your mother in law was unbelievable.
When you got married, she told the whole
neighborhood how you didn't bring any gifts.
How can she do this to us now?
But there's no wedding.
That shouldn't matter.
She should send the basic gift,
since she made such a big deal.
I'm going to be really hard on Yeongdal,
just like how her mom was hard on you.
Let's see how the beauty salon woman takes it.
Oh, she's now the makeup store woman.
Yeongdal's not your daughter in law.
Same thing.
She was so brazen, I couldn't believe it.
She didn't know how to hold her tongue.
As if being pregnant makes her special.
How imprudent!
I wasn't like that, you know?
Why are you laughing?
You were just as bad when I got married.
Be nice to Yeongdal.
She's Gwangbak's friend.
If you hate her, she won't be able to forget it.
So don't be mean. Try to be warm.
Whatever.
They were mean to you and mean to me.
I'm going to pay them back for it.
Minjung.
You're here?
Come in. You must be tired.
I made pollack stew, your favorite.
I made this for you once.
Remember?
Yes.
Did you take your medicine?
How do you feel?
I'm almost as good as new.
I feel like I'm in someone else's place.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Wash your hands and eat.
I'll go.
Do you have to go now?
Huh?
If you can stay, have dinner with me.
It's delicious.
Don't eat noodles. Try to have rice.
And when you eat out, try to get rice.
Don't have soup or stew that are too salty.
And don't drink when you're upset.
Eat slowly, especially when you're hungry.
When it's cold, you'll get a stomachache.
What is it?
I'm happy.
About what?
Hearing you nag.
Nobody ever nagged me to take care of myself.
I think I understand.
You never told me,
but I heard things from people around.
I know you had a hard life.
Isn't the floor warm? I got the heater fixed.
It's nice and warm.
Did the landlord fix it?
I went and talked to him.
I said, "This isn't acceptable.
You should've maintained it when he rented the room out.
How could you accept his money like that?
And why didn't you fix it when it was broken?
What if he dies in the freezing cold?
Will you take responsibility for his death?
Pay him what he's due for getting sick!"
You told him off like that?
Actually, I begged him to fix it.
But I wanted to say that to him.
Oh, boy.
This is the last night we'll spend together.
- Oh.
- Are you happy?
Of course, I am.
I'm sad.
You're lying.
Your smile couldn't be bigger!
I'm glad I don't have to listen to you snore.
I'll come sleep with you after I'm married.
What a liar!
Why you little.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'm not even having a wedding,
and my husband isn't even rich.
I'm at a loss for words.
You had such high standards.
What happened?
I can't believe you fell for him.
Yeongdal, think about it again.
It's not too late.
Mom.
I can't give you to Loser!
I can't take it back. I'm pregnant.
- You could...
- Shh!
Don't. My baby's listening.
Fast food tastes good once in a while.
It's just like that.
Think it over.
After tomorrow, it'll be too late.
Mom, I love Loser.
He's not like the other men I've dated.
I've been faking my affection until now.
I was never in love.
What do you mean?
Loser's seen me before my plastic surgery.
He's the only one who knows the real me.
I was ugly and I got bad grades.
Loser's the only one who knows about us.
I was never at ease meeting other men.
Mom, you know what a girdle is, right?
What about it?
What if you had to wear it all day?
How uncomfortable would that be?
Meeting other men was like wearing that.
But now, I feel like I took it off.
I don't have to be coy.
I can say anything.
I don't have to try to impress him.
He sees me as who I really am.
You're not making any sense.
I was just babbling on.
Mom, I'll be really happy.
Yeah, right. With a delivery boy.
He's going to open a pizza shop.
Who knows when that will happen?
Didn't you see his sister in law?
She won't let it happen, I'm telling you.
Even though his brother wants to do it.
I've done everything I need to do now.
I wanted to see you have kids before I died.
Now you can die happy?
Not really.
I want to see that child grow up,
go to school and go to the army.
It might be a girl.
Anyway, live a very long life.
I can send my daughter to the army.
Keep your wife in line.
Look at Anggeum.
Bong gave her an inch and she took a mile!
I never saw her take anything.
Why you little! I'm serious!
Mom!
Oh, hey, hey, hey!
He looks good in this outfit.
Clothes do make a man.
Hey, sir, how are you?
He looks like he's single.
You'd fall for him, if he was real, right?
I don't care how a man looks.
Then what do you care about?
Money?
Chemistry. Sparks!
But I don't feel anything with him.
Oh, I have to go.
Yes, go!
I'm sorry I have to leave again today.
I'll make it up to you.
Oh, it's so cold.
Don.
- You took a cab?
- Yes.
We can't afford to take cabs anymore.
Okay. I won't.
But it's not that expensive.
Don.
Look at this. How exciting.
It feels weird.
Me, too.
Now I feel like we're married.
- Are you happy?
- Yes.
You're not?
Now I'm tied to one woman for good.
My life is really over.
Huh?
Tie me down real tight.
Cut off my circulation.
It's not enough.
Get as much money as possible.
There's no time.
I'll get as much as I can.
Is your passport ready?
We can flee to Southeast Asia or China.
Okay, Mr. Seo.
I'll call you right back.
Don't worry.
I'll send the $5 million now.
What happened to my money?
Actually,
give me one more week.
It'll triple.
Triple?
More times means more interest.
That's nice,
but I need the money. It's my family.
This is top secret,
but is there anyone you want to help out?
Why?
They can invest, too.
It's almost over. Double.
For you, triple.
Invest?
I have no money to invest.
You don't have a secret stash?
You said all married women have some.
How could I, on our budget?
It'll double.
It's like popcorn, I'm telling you.
That sounds like a scam.
You always doubt everything!
To my boss, $100,000 is child's play.
You should invest.
Do it. A chance like this won't come again.
That's that, and this is this.
What do you mean?
Nothing. Hobak should invest.
Take out a second mortgage.
So if I invest $1,000, it'll be $2,000?
Your scale is so small.
It should be at least $100,000.
If that's true, everyone would be rich.
Let me know if you want to.
You have 1 week.
Oh.
How's it coming?
Why are we doing this here?
Shouldn't the bride's family do this?
Don't nitpick.
Father, you're home.
Are you going somewhere?
To Gwangbak's parents house.
Why go there at dinner time?
What about my dinner?
You said you were eating out.
You said you were meeting Mr. Kim.
I changed my mind.
I have to get permission from you?
So? There's no dinner for me?
I'll make it for you.
Father, we have to go.
What?
No, we don't have to.
I'll prepare it for you.
Her family's having dinner tonight
as a kind of wedding for her uncle.
A kind of wedding?
They can't have a wedding now.
Why can't they have a wedding first?
They have a baby on the way.
Father, hold on.
I'll fix you dinner.
It's okay.
I'll order Chinese.
Let's go.
How can we?
Didn't you hear?
He's ordering Chinese.
You're so dense.
Oh, what do I do?
Aunt isn't here and there's no food.
Is there anything you can cook quickly?
Anything?
Go buy me some chicken!
Mom.
You're here!
Hello, I'm here.
When things were difficult,
people got married like this.
- Bow.
- Okay.
The bride and groom will bow.
Have a happy marriage, dear sister in law.
Welcome to Wang's family.
Let's sit. Sit down.
The wedding's over.
Let's eat now.
We should put that away.
Where's Minjung?
Is he delivering parcels?
Oh,
he's too busy.
Where's Gwangbak?
Oh, she'll be a bit late.
Don, take good care of each other.
You know our family motto, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Yeongdal, our family motto is put yourself in other's shoes.
I know. I've seen it many times.
If you put yourself in other's shoes,
you'll be able to avoid many arguments.
Once again, welcome.
I'm sorry you have to start out like this.
Mother, stop sighing.
You always said, you must wait until the end to see how your life turns out.
I know!
Stop saying that.
I haven't said that in a long time.
And stop saying, "I know" or "No way."
It's not very polite.
He's your son in law now.
You have to respect him.
I learned this from Mrs. Lee.
Then you should be mean to my daughter in law just like you.
Mother, she's your sister in law.
How's your housekeeping going?
Well...
I'm not great, but I'm doing my best.
Making money isn't easy.
Money doesn't grow on trees!
Not now.
I'm going to drop by unannounced to check.
I got it, mother.
Don't squander Hobak's hard earned money.
That's enough.
I did that to demonstrate our family motto.
It doesn't feel good when I do that, right?
If you keep scolding Don in front of his mother,
how do you think she feels? Huh?
Anggeum, stop that!
It's my feelings, not yours.
Mr. Wang, let's take a photo.
Grandmother, come. Everyone, come.
Not grandmother, but mother.
She'll get used to it.
It won't happen overnight.
Hey, wear something warm.
The baby must be cold.
It's okay. The baby's in my stomach.
It's not in my legs.
Hobak, come.
Girls, come.
Let's take a picture.
Hey.
Hurry, come. Hurry up.
Take a picture.
- Go ahead.
- Do it.
Make us look good.
One, two, three.
Whoa!
It smells great.
How did you know?
That's my father's favorite.
You'll score some points for this one!
Go get him.
Father, come out.
She made your favorite.
What is it?
Father, enjoy.
I'm not sure if it'll be good, but I tried my best.
Father, doesn't it look good?
You're so dense.
You really have no idea at all, do you?
After fighting with you over that chicken,
I stopped eating it.
You rallied up your whole family!
Do you know how humiliating that was?
Who was that bastard who pushed me?
He wasn't a bastard.
He was my uncle.
The same uncle who got a girl pregnant?
Now I get it.
How can he do that to someone's daughter?
They had their reasons.
I think your family has issues.
Father.
Why? What is it?
You shouldn't say...
Was I wrong?
She mad it for you, so you should try...
I'm not going to eat this.
You eat it.
Father.
Why did you tell him about my uncle?
Father, I was inconsiderate.
I'll make you something else.
What would you like?
Forget it.
I can't eat when I'm upset.
Is this the Chinese place?
Don't try to help me from now on.
And that thing with my uncle?
That's nothing to brag about.
You didn't have to tell him that.
I didn't know, but you're a blabbermouth.
What? A blabbermouth?
You are.
I thought you weren't,
but now that we're married, I know.
How can you call me a blabbermouth?
I've never heard that before.
How could you say that?
Are you upset?
Don't be so petty.
It just came out.
Are you a blabbermouth.
You're so petty.
Petty? Are you serious?
Sunjeong.
I brought roasted chestnuts.
Daese.
It's good.
Why was he eating that?
You didn't make him dinner?
I made spicy chicken, but he got angry saying he doesn't eat chicken.
That's right.
He stopped eating it after that incident.
You didn't know?
No. I'm sorry.
Still, you should've softened him up.
How could you let him eat noodles?
You just go married.
This is really bad.
I didn't know how to talk to him.
I told him I was sorry, but it didn't work.
Try to be friends with him.
You have to try.
What else can we do?
It was bad to begin with.
It won't be easy.
But try to warm up to him, listen to him,
and make him accept you.
I got it.
I really need to work on a lot of things.
Thank god you came home.
Can we talk?
Minjung.
When did you leave?
A little while ago.
Why didn't you wait?
You wanted me to wait for you?
I had bought some roasted chestnuts.
I ran home, thinking you were waiting.
I'm happy when I work, thinking of you.
You are?
Only believe half of what men say.
And what could I not say right now?
Especially if I want you to keep cooking.
It's great to hear you joking.
I wasn't joking.
I hope you get over everything soon.
Minjung, I made stew.
Did you eat it?
Yes. It was good.
I'm doing the dishes.
You should've left them.
I could've done them tomorrow.
I'm good at doing the dishes.
I didn't drink today.
And I didn't eat instant noodles.
Aren't you proud of me?
I'm glad you're such a good listener.
You deserve an award.
Sunjeong, I won't say thank you.
I know you don't like it.
But I'll never forget it.
Good night.
You too.
Let's go.
Have a happy life.
Mom.
Don't worry about her, mother.
But it's hard to...
I want to take you home!
Look at Yeongdal.
She doesn't want to go.
Mom, let's go.
Please look after my baby sister.
Okay, Don?
Yes, sir.
Mrs. Park, don't cry.
I won't mistreat my precious daughter in law.
Yeongdal, have sweet dreams.
Uncle, be good to her.
Mother, let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
- Goodbye.
- Good night.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Let's go inside.
Sintong, Bangtong, come in.
Mom,
would you like to go singing?
No.
Would you like a drink?
This is nuts.
This is our first night.
Actually, it isn't really our first night.
There's evidence inside you.
I don't remember it, so it doesn't count.
So this is our official first night.
Yeongdal, my princess.
I'll work even harder.
I can't say you'll live like a queen,
but I won't let you starve.
I still can't believe it.
How could someone so pretty marry me?
I'm sorry about having to start out like this.
You should've worn a pretty wedding gown and have a beautiful wedding.
I promise you,
I won't ever make you cry.
I won't give you any scars.
I watched Bong and his wife,
and I learned that a woman's heart is a fragile thing.
Look at his wife.
I'm not like her.
I feel very responsible when I look at that.
I've never felt this way, but it's not bad.
I'm on edge as if I'm on a tight leash.
- Is that good?
- Yes.
That's good, then.
But Don, did you really blame the alcohol?
You said you regretted it afterwards.
Who told you that?
I owe my life to alcohol.
It brought you to me.
Let me ask you something, too.
What is it?
Did you mean it?
I wasn't good?
Oh! Hey, hold on.
- Why?
- Shh!
Don't do that!
Goodnight!
Have sweet dreams!
You must practice.
Not grandmother, but mother.
Mother.
Not Mr. Wang, since he's your brother in law.
Can I just call him brother?
You can't! You're not in a gang.
And you don't call Anggeum Mrs Lee.
I can't call them Mrs. Lee or Mr. Wang.
That's easy.
People are so dumb, right?
I know. But you're so smart.
Don, I won't memorize how to call them.
I hated memorizing when I was a student.
But you must.
Family hierarchy is important.
Hierarchy?
You're above Gwangbak now.
And above Subak.
Really?
So I can order Subak around?
No way.
You shouldn't order her around.
How do you know these things so well?
Your grades were even worse than Sedal's.
What's my ranking?
Let me see.
Mom, Bong, Anggeum, me, you...
Fifth?
Wow!
Be honest with me.
Was I really that bad?
It's a secret.
Don't! Don't!
Darling,
our baby boy got married today.
There wasn't a nice wedding,
but we got a daughter in law and a grandchild.
Please look after them for me.
Mother.
You're not sleeping?
I'm not sleepy.
Bet you feel a little empty.
Not at all. He's right upstairs.
But he slept next to you all his life.
But it's better to have him upstairs, right?
I'm so happy today.
I'm glad you are.
We'll have a big party next year.
We'll pass out rice cakes and grill up a whole pig.
Yes, we should.
Your father would've been so happy.
Why did he have to leave me so early?
I'll get him for it when I see him in heaven.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Mother.
Honey...
Yeongdal, Yeongdal.
Good morning, Anggeum.
Tell Yeongdal to come down.
I think the baby's making her tired.
I'm not trying to make her work. Go get her.
She's living with her in laws now,
so she should pretend to help out a bit.
I'll help out.
Clean these, then.
Okay.
What are you doing?
- Get out.
- I'll clean them.
Aren't you in charge of cooking?
Before Yeongdal came, but not anymore.
She's Gwangbak's friend.
She probably can't cook.
Mother, we'll be in trouble if you do this.
Remember what you used to say?
You can't show how much you love someone.
Yeongdal's going to give you a big headache.
How can she sleep in on her first morning
and not even show up in the kitchen?
But she's pregnant.
I better get pregnant, too.
Look how I'm being treated because I'm not.
If you can, go ahead.
Who's stopping you?
Where's Yeongdal?
She's skipping breakfast.
She's tired.
What did she do to be so tired?
Everyone feels tired after a wedding.
That little brat has no manners.
She should get her lazy butt up.
Subak, that was a bit...
She's your aunt.
Watch what you say.
I'm just no used to it.
She was Gwangbak's childhood friend,
so how can she call her aunt just like that?
And it's not like they got along that well.
How can she call her aunt?
Don't we have any manners?
Respect her as your aunt.
Yeongdal will do well.
I trained her all night last night.
That's not all you did!
Mom, don't say that!
Mr. Want.
No, brother! What was it?
I'm your brother in law.
Right, you are.
It's hard to remember.
You're going to work?
You're so hard working.
Go in and have breakfast.
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Ouch, ouch.
Are you okay?
An old man like you shouldn't run around.
Okay. You should go inside now.
Mr. Wang, have a good day.
No, brother. What was that again?
Oh, who cares.
Good morning. Mrs. Lee, food please.
Come and sit. Come.
Bring some soup and the fish.
Bring them.
What are you wearing?
You're married now.
The makeup woman taught you nothing.
Don't talk about my mom like that.
Right.
You think what you're wearing is appropriate?
Don't scold me.
I'm not your daughter.
We're the same level.
What?
In hierarchy, you and I are two steps apart.
Hah!
You can't wear that in this house,
so watch what you wear from now on.
I can't even wear what I want to wear?
This is what everyone wears.
Subak and Gwangbak all wear this,
so stop picking on me.
She's pregnant, so let her eat first.
Will you be late?
Let's go to my parent's house
since we couldn't go yesterday.
I have plans.
I'll go next time.
The petty blabbermouth is going to work.
Yes?
- Hello.
- Hi.
What brings you here?
She probably has something to say.
You're really quick.
I dropped by on my way to class.
Should I leave you two alone?
It's okay.
You know everything about us,
and you helped the kids with their marriage.
Daese, stop being so mean to Gwangbak.
When was I mean to her?
Imagine how scared she must have been.
You know I don't eat chicken anymore!
I have nothing more to say.
Daese, I feel so uncomfortable.
Can't you try to get along for my sake?
Set a good example. She'll follow suit.
You have to accept her first.
She should be scared of at least one person.
You've met her mother.
She couldn't have learned anything good.
She just blurts out anything.
She's indifferent to others feelings.
I'm trying to teach her, so you stay out.
I know how you feel.
But that can hurt Sangnam in the end.
Hurt Sangnam?
Women take things out on their husbands.
Who really loves their daughter in laws?
They do it for the sake of their sons.
So go easy on her.
Don't be too harsh.
Do I have to walk on eggshells?
You really don't get it, do you?
Why can't you understand me?
I'm still healthy.
I don't have to be careful around her.
I might, when I'm old and shriveled.
How dare she take it out on Sangnam?
She better not.
If you're curious, you should've come.
You betrayed us when you got married.
You don't call, you don't visit.
Should I come over with mom?
You said nobody was home.
We'll drop by, then.
Come in, mom.
Daughters are so useless.
You got married and don't even call me!
No news is good news.
It's because I'm doing well.
Would you be happy if I called and cried?
Am I invisible?
Subak, it's been a while.
Where's Jungji?
Miho's babysitting.
She's better at it than your grandmother.
I'm sure she could get married right now.
She's perfect for Daebak.
We'll see about that.
I heard lots of things happened.
Ugh...
How are you? How is Minjung?
Let's not talk about me. It's boring.
You want us to stand here?
Oh, right.
Sit. Mom, have a seat.
I'm not sitting there.
This darn chair!
Let me sit here.
He sat here, like he's someone important,
and he treated me like a servant.
Is your father in law good to you?
Yes, he is.
He's not giving you a hard time?
No, he's so nice to me.
But you've lost weight.
Are you pregnant?
No.
How is Yeongdal?
Don't get me started.
She's giving me a hard time.
Now my sister in law is ordering me around.
How can uncle fall for a girl like her?
He said no to a semi real estate tycoon.
You should come and talk to her.
You used to know how to deal with her.
Is she being rude to you?
Oh, the clothes she wears!
She shows too much skin.
I told her to cover up a bit,
and she talked back to me!
And she talked back saying not to talk about her mother!
I couldn't believe it.
I better show her who's the boss.
But she's our aunt.
Grandmother, your father, and uncle are
all on her side, saying she's pregnant.
I don't believe it.
Don't worry. I'll teach her a lesson.
Your house is nice. Give us a tour.
Oh, it's really nice. I envy you.
But it's my father in law's house.
But you'll inherit it. He only has one son.
Is this his room?
Don't open the door.
Mom, tangerines.
Subak, come here.
Oh...
What a great room!
I'm going to move into a small apartment
next year when everyone moves out.
Why am I living in such a full house?
I'm sick of it.
Yes.
I told Mr. Kim no when I met him yesterday.
My company will enter the Chinese market alone.
Right.
Sangnam will go to China soon.
He signed an agreement there.
Yes. Okay.
Okay.
Father.
Why are you so surprised?
Oh?
I'm not.
You came home so suddenly.
You want me to call when I'm coming home to my own house?
You're going to eat all these alone?
No.
I mean, yes.
I love tangerines.
Why are there so many shoes at the door?
I was cleaning. I'm sorting them out.
Is there jujube tea?
Let me have some.
Yes, father.
I'll bring it to your room.
I'll drink it here.
Are you taking things out on Sangnam?
Excuse me?
When I scold you, do you take it out on him?
I heard women do that.
When I say something,
you take it out on him?
You better not be doing that.
I never liked you from the beginning,
but I accepted you because you begged me.
But I don't like how you do things.
Trying to manipulate Sangnam behind my back.
And driving a wedge between Sangnam and me.
Is that how your mother raised you?
Don't complain to Sangnam. Do better.
If you do anything I don't like again,
I'm going to take extreme measures. Oh.
Oh, no.
Father!
I'll get it.
Father, you eat a new one.
I'll eat this.
Why did you have to scream?
Yes, Mr. Kim.
Really?
I'll be right there. Okay.
Cancel the jujube tea.
And don't forget what I told you.
Have a nice day, father!
You can come out, mom.
Oh, my heart.
Oh, this is how you live?
This is awful.
Mom, let's leave.
I can't take this anymore.
We'll talk later. Let's go.
Oh...
Oh, boy.
Goodbye!
Mom!
Oh, I'm still shaking.
It's like I was caught stealing.
I can't believe we got caught.
I can't handle stealing or hiding.
Who in the world can handle that?
Oh, poor Gwangbak!
Her father in law seems awful.
Why did you ask me to go there?
But you wanted to go!
You always complain about everything.
Don't blame me.
It was your decision to go.
Where are you going?
My boss wants me.
Huh?
Minjung! Min...
Minjung.
Oh...
I'm home.
Aren't you cold?
I'm fine.
Sleeping in a warm room keeps me warm all day long.
These are for you.
How nice.
It smells good.
I got beer too. Just one glass.
Nice.
This feels like a different place.
The plant looks pretty.
But you're prettier.
Don't be so happy, remember?
I know. Only believe half of what men say.
Look where believing it all got me.
Subtitles by KBS World
Sunjeong, I think of you
whenever something good happens.
Minjung, I better go. Something's up at home.
Yeongdal, come out.
She's not your daughter in law. She's mine.
End it.
This won't win me back.
You and I are over.
I don't want to hear that from you.
Aren't you going to move away?
What?
I hate running into you.
What's the extreme measure?
What are you going to do?
Honey, what was that?
Where is the deed to the house?