Subtitles by KBS World
What are you still doing up?
Please go to bed.
I don't want to see your face.
Do you want to be my lover?
Use it as you want.
The limit is a hundred thousand dollars.
This is nuts.
Congratulations!
You finally bought an apartment in Seoul.
I envy you.
Applause!
Thanks.
What's this?
It's your housewarming gift.
We don't do stuff like soap or toilet paper
Open it.
Whoa!
I can't wear this!
Of course you can!
Just put it on.
Your night will change.
First night in the new apartment, tada!
I heard it brings great fortune.
It brings great fortune?
Then I should put this on.
Wear this on your first night.
And tell us how it felt.
Are you coming home tonight?
I'm tired, so I'm going to bed.
The door code is our wedding date.
It's our wedding date.
What is it?
When is our wedding anniversary?
We got married?
Why you...
When was my wedding date?
How should I know that?
Ask Madam Park Salla.
Text it to me.
Don't be a smart ass.
Oh, this is crazy.
How can he ask me when he married?
Why did you have him, mom?
Respect your older brother!
Why wasn't I born first?
He doesn't act like he's older.
You can't blame Hobak for everything
We should actually be grateful.
What's wrong with Sedal?
There's no better than him out there.
Don't ever say that to anybody.
When did Sedal get married?
Why are you so startled?
You weren't sleeping?
Oh, I couldn't fall asleep.
You just got home?
Don't ask questions like that.
Looks like the move went smoothly.
What are you wearing?
What do you mean?
You can't dress up for going to bed.
We're at a new apartment,
so can't you be a new woman?
I'll put on a show for you later.
What kind of show?
I hope it's nothing see-through.
That's a new suit.
Did you buy that?
Wow, you look good.
I told you not to ask me stuff like that.
Take that down.
You told me to hang it.
And you took me seriously?
It's embarrassing.
This apartment is nothing to be proud about.
To the rich people, this is nothing.
But you said you were going to hang it up
and salute to it morning and night.
I can't make a joke?
You have no sense of humor.
Stop getting in my way and go to bed.
I came home thinking you were asleep.
Why did you hang this here? Huh?
This is pathetic.
You seem to like hanging things.
This pot is meaningful.
That meaning is meaningless.
Don't touch this.
I'm going to use it as a reminder.
There are painful but sweet memories in that.
Take that down.
How can you call those memories sweet?
They were totally pathetic.
We can't forget the hard days.
That's what's wrong with you.
It's better to forget bad memories as soon as possible.
Why are you picking a fight?
Did something happen at work?
You should have a look around.
I already have.
When?
I came with Loser and got a tour.
I didn't think you cared, but you did!
My darling honey.
Stop it.
Don't be coy.
Go wash up. Let's have a toast.
To celebrate our first night in our new house.
First night?
You're not planning anything, are you?
Like what?
Whatever it is, forget about it.
I'm exhausted. Just look.
Let's celebrate our first night here.
Stop saying first night.
Why are you so horny tonight?
A woman should be demure.
What the...
This is our first night in a new place.
Let's go to sleep.
Turn out the lights so we can save on electricity.
We still have to pay back the loan.
I think we'll do great.
Is the director good to you?
Yes.
Totally, amazingly, crazy and scary good.
Oh, that's great.
Don't lose this job, no matter what.
Be smart and do well.
Getting this job was hard.
This is nutty, nutty nuts.
Here.
Let's become rich.
Money's important, even between family members.
You just learned that now?
My boys aren't going to be poor like me.
When Sintong and Bangtong get married,
I'm going to buy each a house,
and I'm going to prepare for retirement,
so I won't have to rely on them.
Let's talk about retirement later.
We have a long life ahead of us.
What's that?
Oh.
A gift from my co-workers.
Tada!
That's for you?
Yes.
Have they gone crazy?
They said wearing this on the first night will bring great fortune.
Who said that?
That's nonsense.
How can people just blurt things out?
Why are you screaming?
I actually thought it was pretty nice.
Sedal, let me put this on, and...
Sintong! Bangtong!
You'll wake them up!
Be quiet. Quiet!
Don't do this! Stop it!
- What do you mean by that?
- Sintong!
Hey!
Ouch!
Who's that?
Director.
Answer it! Hurry!
What took you so long?
I thought I was quick.
Answer it before it rings three times.
I will.
Why did you call me so late?
Because I wanted to. Why?
I thought I'd say good night.
Okay. Good night to you...
Then,
I'll do what I've been wanting to do.
Father, thank you.
Do you feel better now?
Yes.
But I'm embarrassed.
Please keep this between us.
I'll have to see about that.
I really wanted to cry my heart out.
I wanted to,
and my heart was filled with cries,
but I couldn't do it.
I couldn't cry in front of my wife,
and I couldn't do it by the river.
But now that I've done it in front of you,
like a little boy,
I actually feel better.
Thank you, father.
[Yeoju]
Coming through!
Mr. Ko.
Oh!
What brings you here?
Did you come alone?
How did you find this place?
I came to your wife's funeral,
and I came here before Minjung's wedding.
When I got here, I could remember the house.
I didn't want to be bothered, so I came alone.
I wanted to have a drink with you.
I don't have much to offer,
but I can make chicken soup with one of these.
Oh, but you don't have to.
Stand here. I'll drive them to you.
Here they come!
Would you look at that!
Oh!
You'll get hurt before you can catch one.
This is really delicious.
They're different from factory chickens.
They are muscular,
so the texture is really nice.
Right.
This is really a treat.
Yes.
Mr. Ko,
you must be really worried about Minjung.
In life,
there are ups and downs.
Minjung won't let it ruin him.
Of course not.
I know he won't.
But watching your children go through such hardship breaks your heart.
I should've dropped by to talk to you sooner.
I'm sorry.
No.
I'm the one who should apologize.
Subak's suffering because of my son.
Subak is still immature,
and that's a big problem for Minjung.
You shouldn't say that.
It's my son's fault.
Actually, Mr. Ko,
I don't know how to bring this up,
but can they come and live with me?
I hate to see them living at such a place,
and I thought I could take them in
and teach my daughter better.
I'd like to take care of Minjung.
If they lived at a nicer place,
things might become easier to deal with.
I know what people say about a man living at his in laws house,
and they're not wrong.
I've seen marriages break up because of that.
But the same goes for a woman.
The best solution is to live far away from your in laws.
I understand that,
but I'd like to help out
while I can afford to help out.
Loser, have you ever spent $100,000?
Are you mad?
Let's say you have it.
You should see a doctor.
Just pretend you do and tell me.
I haven't even seen that kind of money.
Could you spend that in a day?
No way.
You need to have experience to do that.
How would you spend it
if someone gave it to you?
Who would give me $100,000?
Pretend someone did.
$100,000?
I could spend it if I put my mind to it.
It'd be easier than making it. Right?
Yes.
We spend $3 a day.
$100,000 would be?
Hold on.
I can't really calculate it...
$3 a day, 30 days a month.
3 times 3 is 9, 9$.
$90 a month.
That's about $1,000 a year.
That would last 100 years!
100 years?
If we split it, it would last 50 years.
Loser, that's why you're a loser.
Can't you spend it all at once?
Like a man?
What do you think?
It's perfect. Pretty.
You have an eye for style.
You weren't short?
No, and I pocketed the change.
I have to
because I'm unemployed.
It was actually perfect.
Will father like it?
He'll love it.
How about you? Are you okay?
I don't want to talk about mom.
I'm going to forget about it for now.
I want peace.
I'm just going to stop trying.
I feel peaceful right now.
How about you?
How's your writing coming along?
That question scares me these days.
It's not going well?
I quit my job to write,
and I'm going crazy.
Do you regret quitting your job?
To be honest, sometimes I do.
I can't ignore how people think and mom, too.
But I know life is long.
Oh, my darling little sister.
You're right. People would laugh at you
if you become a writer at 29.
You need experience to write well.
You should start dating, too.
I put out some feelers.
Really? Who is it?
Tell me later. It's my mother in law.
- Mother is that you?
- Yes.
Welcome, mother.
You too, Yeongdal.
I almost didn't come.
Please don't be mad.
Hello.
- Gwangbak, it's been a while.
- Yes.
Keep in touch.
You must have lots of free time.
I'm actually quite busy.
You used to be close friends.
Did you have a fight?
Why don't you visit?
No, but things got odd when we became in laws.
It wasn't when you became a teacher?
Don't think you're better than my daughter.
You never know what could happen to you.
I know.
I should go, Hobak.
Have fun. Bye.
You should stay.
Yes, have dinner with us.
Mother, have a look around.
I'll make dinner.
I can't believe they moved here by themselves.
I'm going to destroy them!
Mom, you have me.
Right.
I don't envy this apartment at all.
If my company carried this out,
safety will be ensured,
while reducing cost and construction period.
I will drive for you, too.
If you're done, you can go play.
Okay.
Aren't you seeing someone?
Not yet.
Being a teacher was your only merit,
so no wonder you're not seeing anyone.
Yeongdal's been very busy.
Men who are only interested in
pretty women are a problem,
but what can we do? Looks matter.
But Yeongdal had a lot of work done.
Everyone does that these days!
That's called making an effort!
People complain because they're jealous.
Why did you get fired?
She wasn't fired.
She quit to become a writer.
Aren't writers poor?
Star writers make really good money.
The Harry Potter writer is really, really...
That's only for the star writers.
You were bad at writing at school.
I wasn't bad.
I got good comments on my journals.
Just journals?
Everyone writes journals at school.
You can't become a writer from that.
You should've gotten married before quitting.
Your parents must be worried.
Especially your mother.
She always succeeds when she puts her mind to it.
So she'll make it someday.
I believe in her. She'll be a great writer.
It's been her dream since she was little.
You only had one dream?
Excuse me?
Yeongdal had so many dreams.
It changed whenever she woke up.
They were all different.
She took piano lessons for a month,
ballet lessons for couple months.
I even have a tutu.
She took acting lessons for a while.
That was very expensive.
She had many talents and many interests,
so she took cooking lessons, dance lessons,
and even gayageum lessons.
I bought a gayageum.
And was it sex crime victims counselor?
She wanted to become that and took classes.
She wanted to be a dog groomer,
so we bought some puppies.
Three puppies.
It was expensive, but she learned a lot.
She can fend for herself wherever she goes.
But you should focus on one thing.
But you've done two, teaching and writing.
I couldn't really stick to anything else,
but there's one I can never get sick of.
What is it?
Men.
My final dream is getting married.
I'm going to realize it.
Oh, Yeongdal's getting married.
When?
Oh, with that man she met before?
Yes.
He's totally into Yeongdal.
He asked her to marry him.
Oh, really?
But they just met.
People do things really fast these days.
He asked you to marry him?
He didn't say it, but it looks like we will.
He'll probably propose when he comes back from his business trip to China.
How do you know if he's going to propose?
Why would you say that?
It's bad luck!
I thought she's getting ahead of herself.
They just met.
I don't think you can be a good writer.
Relationships aren't bound by time!
Haven't you heard of love at first sight?
Even Subak got married in only 3 months.
She's getting married this year, okay?
She's your only sister in law.
Don't forget.
He sent me a text message from China.
I sent him one before.
What does it say?
Check it.
It's raining here.
I miss you more now that I'm here.
You miss me, don't you?
Your gift is safe and sound, so don't worry.
Watch over Seoul for me while I'm gone.
Oh, he's completely into her. He is!
He'll set the date anytime soon!
You know that.
He's bringing her a gift?
He asked if she wants an expensive handbag,
but she said she wants him back safe.
He loved it when she told him that.
Only rookies ask for gifts, she says.
Did you get dumped again?
I didn't!
I was at Hobak's place.
You always kick the door when you get dumped.
It's like a hobby for you.
Hey, hey, Gwangbak.
What?
Is Yeongdal seeing someone?
How did you know that?
I saw her coming out of the theater in the arms of some man.
Theater? In his arms?
Yes. While I was making deliveries.
But she didn't see me.
Don't you ever talk to her?
You're friends.
We're not friends.
We were classmates.
Did the guy seem like he liked her?
I don't know.
Maybe he does, maybe he doesn't.
I only saw them once.
But he looked pretty handsome.
She used to date ugly men because she was after their money.
Why can't you date someone?
What do you mean?
I should've known when you were getting dating advice from a 4th grader.
You should really think about it.
You were a better student than her.
Why can't you leave me alone?
Ugh!
I'll keep Seoul safe.
I miss you, too.
Come back safely.
Hot chocolate.
Cappuccino.
Good morning.
Sunblock.
He asked if she wants an expensive handbag,
but she said she wants him back safe.
He loved it when she told him that.
Only rookies ask for gifts, she says.
Mmm...
Sunblock.
Isn't it cheaper at the duty free shop?
I can't believe I did that!
I think he's going to propose soon.
Yeongdal, I miss you more now.
I'll be back soon.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo...
Can Minjung come live with me?
Are you going into your in laws house?
What are you talking about?
Your father in law came to see father.
He did?
Father called me today,
asking how bad things are with you.
I don't know how bad things are,
but don't forget you're the eldest son.
You acted like their son, and now they
want to have you move in
and make you do whatever they want.
It's not like that.
He's not that kind of person.
It'd be one thing if you had money.
But this is different.
If you want respect, don't move in with them.
And one more thing.
You're not going to take care of father?
I should.
How can the eldest son who must take care
of his father move in with his in laws?
And when do you think you can move out?
And where will you do the ancestral rites?
Where will father sleep when he visits?
He couldn't see you even if he wanted to.
My father in law said it because he's
worried about me, but I'm not interested.
You didn't have to say anything.
I'm going to forget what you look like.
Must I come and visit you, bastard?
Don't call me bastard, bastard.
I'm Mr. Vice Principal.
They love me here.
Yeah, right.
I know they call you names and talk behind your back.
We did that, remember?
How come you don't get any wrinkles?
I feel happy, that's why.
I don't have to worry.
And I love what I do.
I envy you.
You should've picked up a trade yourself.
I know.
Why didn't you come to the reunion?
I've been busy.
Everyone else is struggling, but we have to work.
The company president is good.
Our friends have gotten really old.
They say people live to be a hundred these days,
but what's the use of living that long?
It's okay to be 100 when you're strong,
but if you're barely breathing, that's hell.
Is there something you want to tell me?
Yes.
Is your third daughter still single?
Is she seeing someone?
I don't think so.
Good. Let me introduce someone.
Let's call it a blind date.
You have someone in mind?
Yes.
They can figure things out when they meet,
so I'll give him her number.
If they hit it off, that'd be nice.
I can trust anyone you bring.
And I trust your daughter.
He's on a business trip,
so I'll tell him when he comes back.
Sounds good.
If things work out?
I'll owe you!
Three big slaps on the face!
Bye.
Hey, hey!
You should say hello.
Why do you always bother me?
Sir, if you do this again, I'm calling the police.
What? Go ahead.
But I should be the one.
I can't believe how rude you are!
What would you tell the police?
You're the one who owes me money!
You must have nothing better to do to walk around making barking noises.
Stay out of my business.
Why would you be concerned about my barking noises?
What?
How rude!
You stay right here!
Yes.
Father, I think we can make it in China.
Our presentation was the best one so far.
Good. You can communicate with them?
You need to ask me that?
I told you about the Chinese market.
I'm glad I learned Chinese.
Good for you, son.
You're the best man ever.
Hey! How rude!
You! Stop right there!
Wow, I can't believe how rude she is.
What's going on?
Remember that rude girl?
I think she's crazy.
She's not normal.
Mr. Choi, the meeting is starting.
Father I have to go.
The meeting is starting.
Sunjeong!
I'm getting a delivery.
Can you sign for me?
Okay.
Delivery?
Daese.
Yes?
I have to go out today.
Oh? I'll tell them to leave it with the neighbor.
There won't be anyone home.
So can you have him come tomor...
Daese!
I'll be home.
I think I should be home.
I want to see him!
I think I should.
What are you talking about?
Nothing. I'll be home.
Hello?
It's okay. Someone will be home.
Please deliver it today. Yes.
Yes, I'm coming right now.
You're home?
Okay.
Father.
Minjung.
I'm at the Seoul Bus Terminal.
What's up? Why didn't you call?
I'm working, so I can't really...
It's okay!
I have the address, and I can find it.
I'm not taking a cab.
Don't worry about me.
Excuse me, you can't bring that on the bus.
I'll hold on to this.
It's new, so it's clean.
Please let me bring it onto the bus.
Don't let it get in the way, please.
I don't want any accidents.
I won't. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Oh? Uh...
Parcel service.
Please sign here.
Okay.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Excuse me.
Are you in charge of this area?
Uh, no, I'm not.
It's someone else, but he couldn't make it.
Did something bad happen to him?
Well, I don't really know.
Thank you.
Where are you?
Why do you want to know?
I told you to be home.
My father's coming and you're not home!
I'm sick and I don't want to be bothered.
Did you expect me to throw a party?
Why is he coming?
He has no clue.
Forget about it.
Father.
Why are you waiting for me out here?
Did you come because of this?
I wanted to give it to you.
It took longer because I got on the wrong bus.
I should've crossed the street.
I went all the way to the last stop.
I told you to take a cab.
Why should I?
I actually had a tour of Seoul.
It must have been so tough.
And people were probably giving you a hard time, too.
It's okay.
It's for my son, so who cares?
Would you like to try it?
I hope it fits well.
The length and the width must be perfect.
I had to guess when I made this.
How is it? Does it fit?
Yes, it fits.
It has to fit like a glove.
It fits better than a glove.
It's light.
That's because it's empty.
Anyway, I'm glad it fits.
This your first A-frame, isn't it?
Yes.
Living in the countryside,
I never let you use one of these.
I had your siblings help out at home,
but I never let you help.
I didn't want to see you wearing this.
Father.
But what can I do?
A man must do anything
to support his family.
You could hurt your back using this,
so when you get up, don't get up at once.
Put your weight on the stick like this,
and get up slowly. Like this.
Got it? Try it.
Like this?
Yes.
Watch your back.
Don't put too much on it at once.
Come in, father.
Let's go get a drink.
Father.
Slow down.
I'm sorry, father.
I didn't want you to see me like this.
This rain will stop, won't it?
Yes, it probably will.
No, it will stop. I'm sure.
Minjung.
Yes, father?
Move in with your in laws?
Subak's having a hard time, and so are you.
This won't do.
I won't be doing that.
I'm not sure what my father in law said,
but I'm not going to live there.
Do as I say.
I know how you feel.
But you need a break.
Let them help you out just for 3 years.
But not longer than that.
And pay them back for their kindness.
Just
don't forget you're my son.
Father, thank you. Thank you.
This is the best thing you've ever done.
Applaud, applaud everyone.
It'll get really crowded again.
But there's no room!
There's Gwangbak's room.
It's a big room,
so it's perfect for Subak and her husband.
I can sleep with the girls.
Gwangbak can use the storage room.
Haebak, is it okay?
You're a senior now.
I'll be fine.
I can sleep in the yard, if I have to.
Welcome, Minjung.
And Subak. I'm so happy.
If you're smart, you'll do well,
even if you don't have new pencils.
It's the stupid ones who blame their tools.
Did someone complain about pencils?
There's someone here who cried about pencils and refused to go to school.
You have such a great memory!
You only remember stuff like that.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
When are you moving in?
We'll move in on Sunday.
We don't have much to move. Why wait?
Right. You should move now.
Let's do it now.
We have Subak's old stuff in the storage room, so you can use those.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this!
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Oh.
We're moving out.
And going where?
To a 5 bedroom apartment.
Don't be mean to your tenants.
I really was in the Miss Korea pageant.
Oh, hello!
Yes?
You came to my MMA gym with Mr. Wang.
Oh, yes!
Hello.
- Are you going home now?
- Yes.
Come and exercise someday.
I don't have the time.
You can always make time.
It's great for stress and losing weight.
Many people do it these days.
It's good for your body.
You look great already, but it's for your health.
I'll give you lessons for free.
Really?
Oh, thank you.
If it's free, I'm coming.
You promised!
Uh...
Hey, eat, eat.
Eat all you want.
Take this chance and eat up.
Wow, it melts in your mouth.
I don't even have to chew it.
There's no time for chewing.
It just slips down your throat.
My stomach is pulling it in.
Oh, I wish there were two of me so I can eat for two.
I'm already eating for two right now.
That's kind of funny.
Goof-off, what's going on?
Why are you buying us dinner?
You always bought drinks for me before,
so this time, I'm buying.
And I won't buy you some cheap pork.
I'm shooting sirloin into your mouths.
Ra-ta-ta-ta-ta!
You're all dead, guys.
Come to think of it, you never had money.
Loser,
we were going to cut you off.
I figured that and that's why I'm buying.
Anyway, where did you get the money?
Did you win the lottery?
Don't ask any questions and just eat.
Hello?
Can I have more sirloin here?
Where are you?
Didn't you get my text?
I'm busy.
Why are you busy?
Isn't it your day off?
I'm moving stuff.
Moving stuff?
Are you moving out finally?
No.
Subak's family is moving in.
They moved today.
Really?
Oh...
Good work, everyone.
There wasn't much to move.
Thank you for helping us, everyone.
It was nothing.
It was fun, actually.
Where's Subak?
She wants to eat later.
Okay.
Minjung, welcome.
We're family now.
Think of this as your own home.
Okay.
Isn't there anything else?
Just eat.
I couldn't cook because of the moving.
But this is Minjung's first dinner here.
Look at the side dishes.
I'm okay.
They say you are what you eat.
How can you work with eating this?
Bring out some fish.
Or order something.
We have Minjung here.
Is Minjung a guest?
He is. He's your son in law.
I'm fine.
I love your kimchi stew.
Don't expect a feast at every meal.
You may be my son in law,
but I'll feed you whatever's available.
You can't live here if you're picky.
A teacher's salary isn't big.
So unless you can pitch in...
Father, should I make some eggs?
Yes.
Do we have beer?
Try to make better side dishes.
He works and needs to eat well.
Of course, of course.
You must eat well to work hard.
Everyone's my boss, everyone is.
Ma, ma, mother!
Is that Sedal?
Is he drunk again?
Father, mother!
Sedal is here.
Did you come to pick a fight again?
Pick a fight?
I wouldn't dare.
Oh, put them down here.
What's all this?
This is sirloin, these are beef bones.
These are ribs and these are fruits.
And et cetera, et cetera.
Where did you get these?
Did you steal them?
I didn't steal them.
Your second son in law, Heo Sedal,
bought them with his credit card.
Oh, Minjung, congratulations.
I heard you moved in today.
Yes.
Did you come alone?
I don't like going places with my wife.
Big animals are loners.
But you and I were a pair.
We were since 7th grade.
That's why they call us a married couple.
Why did Hobak send you here alone?
What's going on?
Where did you get the money for all this?
Don't worry about that, father.
Mother, do you like them?
I've never received anything like this from you.
I don't do those dollar panties.
Are you happy, mother?
I am.
Nobody hates getting gifts.
And this won't be the last time.
I'll be a good son in law for you.
What's wrong with the side dishes?
Mother, you should eat better.
Gwangbak, let's cook up the meat I brought!
Loser, hurry up and get it!
Should I?
Sure, why not?
Now that we have the beef,
why don't we have some?
Hurry up and grill it!
I haven't had meat in a long time!
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Grill away.
Hurry up.
What are you waiting for?
This is delicious.
Cut it into little pieces for me.
Here.
This is for you, mother.
Oh.
And this red ginseng is for you, father.
Thank you,
but I feel...
He's nervous.
Tell us where you got the money.
I didn't steal it, so don't worry, father.
Every dog has its day.
I never got anything like this from Sedal.
Mother, don't worry.
You can rely on me instead of Minjung.
After all, I was your first son in law.
Right, you were the first one.
Ten years and six years are different.
That's almost twice as long.
Goof-off, don't be like this.
You didn't get me anything.
Grandmother, what would you like?
Would you like meat or a dress?
My teeth are too weak for meat,
and my back's too bent for a dress.
Mom, you have more teeth than I do.
You have dentures.
That doesn't count!
They're not really mine
Nothing beats having your own teeth.
Loser, stay out of this.
Grandmother, I'll get you new teeth.
All of them.
Gwangbak, how many teeth does a person have?
About twenty, I think?
Isn't it forty?
Depending on the wisdom teeth, 28 to 32.
I knew you'd know.
Let's not count them.
Grandmother, get 50.
Or get 100.
50 upper ones, 50 lower ones.
Leave no empty space out.
Get 2 or 3 layers of them!
Get as many implants as you can.
Okay, let's do it, then.
Should I get gold ones?
Get whatever you want.
You can get colored jewels, if you want,
so they sparkle when you talk.
So you mean it?
- Mom.
- Yes?
It's dangerous to have teeth like that.
There are thieves who steal gold teeth.
What if someone comes in while you're
taking a nap and remove your teeth?
They do?
Oh, then I couldn't sleep!
How do the rich people do it?
I know.
I'm so glad I'm not rich.
I knew it.
Thanks to you, my Sedal, I can laugh.
I had nothing to laugh about these days.
Mother, what did you just say?
Did I say something?
I can laugh now.
Before that.
What did I say?
You said "my Sedal."
Mother, you said "my Sedal."
Oh, man.
Did you like that?
Of course! I really wanted to hear that.
Mother, all this time, I was observing
Minjung, you step aside now.
I got married into this family earlier.
I became her son in law 4 years before you.
But that won't change the status.
Gwangbak, you eat.
You eat, Minjung.
Wrap it with this.
I'm going to send you and mother on trips and be a real son in law.
Minjung, don't worry too much.
I'm sure I can find you a job.
You can't make money on parcel service.
How can you be so heartless?
Excuse me?
We're having beef,
so you should go get your wife.
How could you eat alone?
How can you be so selfish?
But Minjung hasn't eaten any meat yet.
This was his first piece.
Choose your words carefully.
You're too harsh.
But I'm right!
He should be thinking about his wife.
My Sedal, eat up.
Sedal, you're very handsome.
A man should be dark skinned.
Being pale isn't attractive.
But we both have bulging eyes.
But they're not the same eyes.
So?
Is this your way of apologizing for before?
I'd be grateful, if you forgive me, mother.
Forgive him.
I'd say this is enough.
Okay.
Say ah, my Sedal.
Ah!
Oh...
This is nutty, nutty nuts!
Subtitles by KBS World
From now on, show me some respect.
What?
Don't worry.
She doesn't even know you're a woman.
But don't get caught.
Don't you have any pride?
You don't feel ashamed?
You don't feel upset about Sedal?
Why can't you be happy for him?
Take these out and throw away the trash.
My son Minjung, forgive your dad.
The best gift. What was it?
Propose We had dinner and I got my gift.
Did he propose to you?