Subtitles by KBS World
Mother! Father!
It's me,Sangnam!
You came!
I'm sorry, I should've come earlier.
You were in China?
Huh? Uh, yes.
Thanks to you, we're having rib eye.
Eat up, mother.
I can't chew with my bad teeth.
Didn't Sedal promise to get me implants?
Hold on. I'll get them for you.
- Huh?
- What happened?
Maybe the light bulb burned out.
Stop, stop! Nobody eat!
Right. Nobody eat.
Should I light some candles?
Hold on. It'll come back on.
Nobody's eating, right?
No cheating!
Don't eat.
Don't worry. Nobody's eating.
I got you!
Oh, I didn't think you'd be eating.
When did this go into my mouth?
Did you put it in there?
I'm busy feeding myself.
I have no time to feed you!
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Incredible.
Aunt Yeongdal's the only one who yells at father.
I'm so embarrassed, Yeongdal.
Thanks to Sangnam, we're laughing.
Oh, oh. It's heavy.
Mother, stay strong!
He did?
Yes, he came and had dinner,
and he gave me money, too.
Don't worry about us and be happy with him.
Mom, I'm sorry I couldn't even help.
What do you mean?
You helped plenty.
We have to do well, so you can be confident,
so I'm sorry.
Don't be, mom.
I'm always confident.
Don't worry, mom.
I'll call you again.
The Blabbermouth Sangnam is home.
Oh, I'm exhausted.
I had to work late, so I'm tired.
I had dinner.
I had pork with others at the office.
I'll go wash up.
What is it?
You're the best.
You went to see my parents?
And you even gave mom money.
Who's spreading such rumors?
You're adorable.
Remember what your father said at our wedding?
Couples share their hardships.
Don't take this on by yourself.
Take advantage of your husband.
I will.
I'm sorry I called you a blabbermouth.
I actually like it.
I like how it feels.
I know.
Oh, right.
Don't tell your father about your mother.
Aunt and I decided not to.
If he finds out, they'll never make up.
I didn't want you to find out, either.
You're such a kind person.
You deserve an award.
I'm at the entrance of the park.
Just a minute. I'll be right over.
You already closed?
I'm sorry.
Can you come back tomorrow?
I'm not here to buy anything.
You know Choi Daese, don't you?
Who are you?
Where are your manners?
Me?
His wife.
His wife?
You got divorced long ago.
You're crazy if you think you're still that.
So?
Stop seeing him.
It's none of your business.
If you want to see him, there's a way.
A way?
You know.
If you want to see him, it'll cost you.
Spit your gum out first.
How dare you chew gum in front of me?
Hah!
You're feistier than you look.
How do I look?
Like I'll pas out if someone glares at me?
You wish!
People like you don't scare me at all!
Just who do you think you are?
I ran a tea house when I was young.
You think I'm a joke?
I ran a hair salon in Myeongdong!
You want to see what I'm capable of?
You want me to crush you?
How dare you?
I can't believe you just did that!
- You!
- Huh?
How dare you!
- You come here!
- Hey!
- How dare you!
The person you have called is unavailable...
How can you not take care of yourself?
It's bad business if you're sick!
I'll try harder.
Why did I hire you in the first place?
Did I wrong you in our former life?
I can't even kick you out.
Looking after you is hard work!
Customers.
Hello.
Oh my! Subak!
What's going on?
You work here?
You're mistaken.
I didn't. You're Subak. Wang Subak.
I'm not Wang Subak.
What's wrong with you?
If you're not Subak, who are you?
You said you were in the Miss Korea pageant.
So why are you acting like this?
I said I'm not her.
What would you like?
Hey, take them to the table.
Yes, sir.
Please sit over here.
What would you like?
Give us two soft tofu stews.
Okay.
Two soft tofu stews, please.
What's wrong with her?
Maybe she went mad.
She lost her mind after going bankrupt.
I can understand.
Just look at her working here.
I'd go mad, too.
Enjoy.
Subak, can we talk?
I don't know why you're doing this to me.
I'm not her.
Hey, Subak!
Leave her alone.
She says she's not her.
I don't believe this.
She's embarrassed.
Leave her alone.
Can we get some more kimchi?
Don't.
Why? She wants us to treat her this way.
Excuse me!
I'm coming.
Enjoy.
Did you see her face?
How can she be so cool?
She's a great actress.
Leave her be.
The old Subak would've dumped this on us.
Not just that.
She'd dump this hot soup on us.
Oh, I pity her.
What goes around comes around.
Maybe she really is divorced.
Let's finish this and leave.
I feel uncomfortable.
The person you have called is unavailable...
What happened?
Where did you find it?
Where it was found isn't important.
You don't need to know that, father.
That's not true!
It's definitely important!
Tell me where you found it.
I put it away while cleaning and forgot.
Everything you do gets on my nerves!
How can you be so forgetful?
Shouldn't you get nervous around me?
Father, we found it, so it's over.
I think you should stop now.
What?
Father, this will never happen again.
Don't butt in when he's scolding me.
We decided to cover everything up,
and in a way, it was my fault, too.
What happened to her?
I heard she lost her mind and maybe she did.
Did you hear she got divorced?
I pity her.
Mom, you look happy these days.
I do?
Yes. Like you met a man.
You!
I'm serious.
You look like you're in love.
Stop reading those weird books.
Now I'm reading about married life.
Sangnam reads books like that?
Yes. Dating and Marriage.
Marriage is the Grave for Romance, I think.
I'm almost finished.
You'll be great at dating and marriage.
Of course.
Miho,
how would you feel
if I married someone?
I'm happy if you're happy.
- Really?
- Of course.
You should get married.
You can't live just for me.
Not when I'm going to marry Daebak.
Oh, you!
Are you asleep?
Not yet. I've been working.
You should stop working and go to sleep.
How's Miho doing?
She's sleeping next to me.
Minjung.
Yes?
Being able to text you whenever
and call you whenever is really nice.
You're making me feel badly.
You should.
I'll make up for everything I've done wrong.
It feels like we're dating again.
Miho says I look like I'm in love.
She's a very sharp girl.
I wonder who she takes after.
Sunjeong, go to bed.
I need to wrap this up.
Oh, wake me up in the morning.
The divorce has been finalized.
Here.
Hello?
It's time to wake up.
Bye.
Hey, hey!
Oh Sunjeong.
That's too curt.
That's how these things are done.
Can't you make it sweeter.
Minjung, peekaboo, time to wake up.
No way.
Waking someone up is just protocol.
Bye.
Have you seen a doctor?
I took some medicine, so I'll be fine.
You can't serve food when you're sick!
Outside of being friendly, what are you really good at?
You make mistakes and you get sick.
This is just too much!
I'm sorry.
I'll work harder.
At least I'm good at one thing.
I'll work really hard.
I'll sorry about being sick.
You better work harder.
Everyone's asking why I hired you.
I don't want to hear that anymore.
Okay.
It's a small place but I'm a regular here.
Their soft tofu stew is amazing.
Hello! It's been a while.
Hello. How's business?
Pretty good, thank you.
Right this way.
This way.
Two soft tofu stew?
Yes.
It's really good. Give it a try.
I love soft tofu stew.
Side dishes.
They are special customers.
Okay.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
She's new and she's still learning.
It's okay.
Get that, too.
There, there.
What are you trying to do?
You said you'll work harder.
Why can't you even serve side dishes right?
If you're sick, you shouldn't work.
Get new side dishes, hurry.
I will.
Please excuse me.
Yes, Mr. Seong.
Enjoy.
This is your first time here, right?
I hope you come back.
I will.
Try it, Mr. Ko.
Oh, it's great.
Factories used to move to China in the past,
but now they move to Vietnam or Thailand.
You should think about it, too.
I will.
Who cares if you were in the Miss Korea pageant?
You're driving me crazy.
All you do is give me stress.
Just looking at you makes me mad.
Why don't you just quit?
I'm sorry.
I'm not feeling so well today.
Then you shouldn't work here.
You cry all the time!
Do you know how many dishes you broke?
If you're sick, it's your fault!
Where are you going, Mr. Ko?
Excuse me, aren't you being too harsh?
Excuse me?
It looks like she's sick,
and I think you're being too harsh.
You don't understand.
It's like she's never worked a day in her life.
She drops and breaks things all the time.
She makes so many mistakes every day.
And now she has a cold.
She's not very professional.
She should take better care of herself.
Don't mind us. I'm sorry.
How much do you pay her a day?
Don't. You're a valued customer.
It's okay. Take it.
I'll give you her daily pay,
so please let her have today off.
Oh, okay. Thank you.
He saved you.
Go to the sauna or something.
You're a very caring man.
That was very kind of you.
Goodbye. I hope to see you again.
Mr. Ko, please think over what I've said.
I'll see you again soon.
Let's do that.
- I'll call you.
- Please do.
You should go home.
Just look at yourself.
You know how worried your parents are?
You're getting the house back?
Be realistic.
Stop this nonsense and go home.
Don't you miss the kids?
You should go home right now.
I can't, not like this.
Minjung,
don't tell them I'm here. Don't.
I can't go home just now.
Mom, it's so great to eat in peace.
I can picture it.
You couldn't have picked a worse family.
I love it there.
How are you doing with that man?
Huh? Who?
The man who sends you texts.
How did you know?
How could I not?
I'm pretty sharp on things like that.
You should get married, too.
Having a husband is so great.
You and I were like two peas in a pod.
but now that I'm married, I worry about you.
I feel like I left you behind.
How can I meet anyone at my age?
I don't want to take care of an old man.
Then meet a younger man.
Forget it.
Is he an old man?
He's not.
But it's over.
Why?
His ex-wife is still in the picture.
Oh, disgusting.
Why is she still in the picture?
I know.
From now on, I should meet their first wives.
Oh, it was like a midsummer night's dream.
What good does meeting a man do at my age?
I'll have to cook for them, look after them.
And deal with the ex-wife?
Not a chance.
No romance is great enough for me to suffer such humiliation.
It's not like I made them get a divorce.
Don't you think so?
Right. So you broke up with him?
I ended it before it's too late.
Too bad.
It's Don!
Don!
Mother, it's me.
Loser, hi.
Don't call him Loser!
He's Wang Don.
His name sounds like a silk merchant.
You're right.
The silk merchant Wang...
Why are you here?
To pick up my princess.
Princess?
Yes. Don says I'm his princess.
Unbelievable.
Where's Goof-off?
He went to the neighborhood bazaar.
I couldn't believe it.
We're leaving, mom.
Already? Hang out with me.
My mom wants her home.
She gets upset when Yeongdal's gone.
Then why did she get mad about her snacking?
Yeongdal said she almost got indigestion.
She can't even use the toilet.
And she has to do the dishes, too?
I knew Anggeum would do that.
Don's been protecting me.
Don't let her sleep on the cold floor.
She's pregnant.
We're not sleeping in the living room.
Oh, what's the use?
My daughter's the one who's lost her mind.
Get out of my sight.
Take her home.
Okay.
Let's go, princess.
Oh, daughters are useless.
So get married.
She's getting married?
Yes, yes.
Okay.
Hobak!
Congrats, congrats!
You've become the company model.
Me? How?
They had a model contest,
and I submitted you along with me.
And we both got selected.
Oh, really? Oh, my!
Are we going to get paid?
I'm sure we will.
Really? And you're getting paid?
Yes.
I'll be home late tomorrow.
There's a photo shoot.
Wow, that's great.
Become a model and get paid.
What if others want to hire you?
You'll be a new star!
Don't get ahead of yourself.
This is nuts!
Shoot.
Is that true?
You met her today?
Where is she? Where is it?
A soft tofu stew place in the market.
She can't make soft tofu stew!
She's just doing the dishes.
She can't do dishes either.
She told me not to tell you,
but I thought you should know.
Of course. Lead the way.
Stay home.
I'll go.
Why are you coming with me?
The prince and the princess are a pair.
Father.
Get your things.
You're coming home.
I can't, father.
Not until I get the house back.
You can't do that, not this way.
You're breaking our hearts.
How can I leave you here?
Father...
I can't face the others,
and I can't face you, either.
I know how you feel.
I'm sure it's uncomfortable.
But this won't solve anything.
You have Aeji and Jungji to think about.
How can you do this to them?
They're asking for you.
Jungji's first birthday is coming up.
All the more reason for you to come home.
What is this?
It's a tiny house, but come home.
Good or bad,
you're still my daughter.
Father.
Father, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me, father.
Father.
I'm sorry.
Anggeum, Subak's home!
Oh, Subak!
Mom.
Oh, Subak...
Mommy!
Aeji! Aeji!
Mommy...
We should go inside.
I didn't know you had a family.
Your father talked to me.
He said to scold you if you deserve it.
Did you cause trouble?
Yes.
Then you should try to be better.
I've never seen you smile before.
I'm going to commute from now on.
I have to make money.
Yes?
I'm hungry.
Excuse me?
Make me lunch.
I got it.
Father, lunch is ready.
What's this?
Shabu-shabu.
Shabu-shabu?
I have to cook and eat with my own hands?
I don't eat stuff like this.
I can't cook anything yet,
and I couldn't find anything in the fridge.
Father, can you eat this just once?
I'll make you fried rice later.
Or I can get some noodles.
So you want me to have this for lunch?
You should try to make soup or stew.
A family should have a woman who can cook.
That makes men want to come home early.
And this is a family of laborers.
You know how important food is to us?
Why do you think I held that audition?
What's going on, Daese?
Sunjeong, look at this.
Don't I have every right to get mad?
Oh, man!
Some people don't like shabu-shabu.
You should've asked him ahead.
This is why living with in-laws is hard.
You can't do everything your way.
I'm sorry. I don't really know how to cook.
I'm sorry, aunt.
I don't know how to put on makeup.
You should learn.
You're a model now.
You'll look beautiful with makeup on.
You should try it.
What do I need to buy?
I'll pick them out for you.
Makeup is important for a woman.
I know that.
My mother in law runs a shop like this.
But she doesn't give you any makeup.
You're right.
Okay.
To the side.
Oh, this is nice.
No. 505!
Yes, hi.
Come with us to the hot spring next month.
Hot spring?
The whole building is coming. Join us.
But I'm the only man...
We don't care.
To us, you're not a man.
You're coming, okay?
I...
There's a photo shoot.
Sintong, wait for me!
Wait for me!
Here I go!
Sintong! Bangtong!
Dad!
Hold on.
You boys!
Why did you get so much dirt on you?
You know how hard it is to wash them?
These need to be hand washed.
But you told us to run around wild!
I know!
Okay, fine. You do that.
Should we go visit mom?
Wow! How exciting!
Let's ask mom to take us out.
Even more exciting!
Barbecue! Barbecue!
Let's go, let's go.
Yes, mother.
Minjung, can you drop by?
What's going on?
Just drop by. I have something to tell you.
Okay.
Minjung, when are you coming?
I'm making seafood stew.
I just need to boil it now.
Your mother in law called?
Why?
Is something going on?
Okay, Minjung.
I'll wait.
Mom.
Oh, you're home.
Did your boss let you go early?
He had a gathering, so we closed early.
Hold on. Minjung is coming.
You called me for that?
Yes.
Mom, stop this.
Stop what?
You have kids together!
You don't need to say anything.
Subak!
Don't let your pride get the best of you!
This is not time to do that!
You should be begging for his forgiveness!
It looks like I'm having dinner here.
Don't wait for me.
Where did Subak go?
She can't even sit and eat with us.
Subak's a considerate, loving girl.
If she didn't care what others think,
she'd be sitting here, as if nothing's wrong.
Who are you talking about? Subak?
Yes, we're talking about Subak.
Stop lying.
Everyone here knows Subak very well.
So how can you say she's considerate?
You don't know her that well.
Growing up, she shared her cookies with Don.
No way.
I'm sure she was too full.
She left home because she was sorry.
I'd leave home, too.
How could she stay?
She even got a job to get our house back.
She had it rough.
She should!
Considering what she did to Bong, she should.
Why do you hate Subak so much?
Not in front of Minjung.
I agree!
I ache all over, but I made kimchi casserole for Minjung.
You're sick?
I got sick after Subak came home.
Taking care of the kids must be hard.
It is hard.
But what can I do?
They're your kids.
I wish Hobak and Gwangbak were here.
I know.
I called Hobak, but she won't come.
She hasn't come since your birthday.
She works. She's busy.
She thinks she's too good for us now.
She's heartless.
Hobak isn't heartless!
She got us this place.
Gwangbak helped!
She didn't do it alone.
Gwangbak came earlier and gave me money.
She said she's working for a magazine, and I felt so sad.
She's working?
She is.
So Gwangbak quit writing?
She doesn't know how to persevere.
She quit teaching only after a few years.
Right, Don?
Right.
Minjung.
Can you take Subak back?
Excuse me?
Look what she did.
She was too ashamed to see you tonight.
She acts mean, but she's soft inside.
I know Subak caused you a lot of grief.
But you had two kids with her.
Many couples reunite after their divorce.
Your spouse knows you best.
Divorce isn't the end of a couple.
Mother, we're already...
Just hear me out.
Subak must have learned her lesson.
She's not the same immature girl.
I'm not telling you to get back with her now.
Take some time and think about it.
Give her time.
Subak will change.
After what happened, I'm sure she will.
There are lots of women worse than her.
There are women who addicted to shopping.
Isn't she better than them?
That's enough.
You're making Minjung uncomfortable.
I'm not! I'm telling the truth.
Minjung comes here to see the kids,
not to listen to you talk nonsense.
Divorce isn't a joke.
You can't take it back.
You know it was a hard decision for him.
So they should get back together.
You better go.
Come whenever you want to see the kids.
And don't come whenever she calls you.
Don't call him so much. He's busy.
Where were you?
I was at the park.
Why did you go there when it's freezing?
Subak...
I know what you're going to say.
But stop it, mom.
I'm not that thick skinned.
Maybe I was before, but I'm not now.
But you have kids.
Even so,
we got a divorce despite them.
He doesn't want to see me.
That won't last long.
It'll all pass.
That's why some couples get back together.
What if some other woman takes him?
He's doing well.
He's successful now.
And he'll get his company back.
What woman would say no to him?
Women will line up for a man like Minjung.
So don't lose him.
You have kids together.
Mom, please.
I want to, I do.
But how can I ask him back?
And it's not like he'll come back to me.
Oh...
Ugh...
Okay, Daebak.
Goodnight.
Here.
Mom, Subak came home.
She did?
Yes. And her husband went to see her.
Everyone wants them to get back together.
I'm cold.
Dad, I'm hungry.
You said mom would take us out.
I'm sleepy.
Dad, I'm hungry.
Hold on and stop complaining.
Dad, let's go home.
She's not coming.
Just hold on.
She'll come any minute.
Hold on, hold on, hold on!
Good job.
Oh, I hope I wasn't really bad.
You were really great.
Stiff, but great.
I should go home and practice.
How about a round of beers?
My treat.
Mom!
It's mom!
Stay away. What's wrong with you?
They're my boys.
Uh, honey.
Maybe we should go out another time.
Can we? I'm so sorry.
It's okay. You should go.
Have a good evening.
Hobak, I'll see you tomorrow.
Goodnight.
Bye. Goodnight, everyone.
Bye. I'm sorry.
Oh, it's so cold.
Dad, this is so good.
The best! Better than barbecue.
Boys, slow down.
Let dad eat, too.
Why are my boys such gluttons?
I can't believe you.
Wash your face.
It doesn't look good.
I can't wash my face.
I've never worn this kind of makeup before.
Where are the kids?
I put them to bed.
It's not easy being a model.
It was exhausting.
Beautiful, right?
Not really.
- What?
- You don't look good in makeup.
Look in the mirror.
It's weird.
You look strange.
I look pretty.
Just you wait.
When the TV ad comes out, I'll be a star.
I didn't know I was this pretty.
That's what everyone told me.
You shouldn't take them seriously.
Why not? It's the truth.
Look. I look amazing.
You must be insane!
What if I become a real model?
That won't be good.
Nobody's that crazy.
Your company hired you because it was cheap.
Don't do any more of that.
Why not?
It's not good to get your face known.
No privacy and you can't even fight.
If it's posted online, your life is over.
I feel so sorry for celebrities.
And why don't you post pictures of me and the kids on your blog?
When your co-workers stopped the boys,
I got really mad.
Post our family picture up, so they'll know.
You're married.
I don't get why people post those pictures.
Why don't they just hang them at the door?
So everyone can see them.
And were you out of your mind?
What do you mean?
What were you thinking?
The three of you looked almost homeless.
Why didn't you dress them up and wash their faces?
Life father, like sons.
I was so embarrassed.
You were embarrassed of the boys?
Not the boys, you.
You looked so shabby!
What will people think of me?
Put yourself in my shoes.
Wouldn't you feel embarrassed
if I should up at your workplace looking
all shabby with the boys?
I wouldn't.
You think you're so great, don't you?
What?
You don't care about me or the boy?
Ask anyone!
That's what I should say!
Ask anyone whose fault it was.
Fine! I'll dress up the next time I come!
Man.
Don, don't go anywhere.
I won't.
Anggeum, good morning.
You should learn to do this alone!
Don't make Don stand guard!
You're jealous, aren't you?
I'll ask Bong to stand guard for you.
Oh, boy.
Don't. You can't win.
You were made for each other.
Ugh.
Man...
Honey, honey!
Mom, I need some time by myself.
Don't worry. I'll stay safe.
I just need to sort things out.
I feel relieved now that Subak's back.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Father, I'm sorry.
Why are all our children trouble makers?
This must be their hobby or something.
It's because they're our children.
But they didn't learn this from me.
I'm sure she had no other choice.
Don't push her too hard.
But I'm doing it for her.
Be honest with me.
Are you really doing it for her?
She wants to be a captain.
Just think about it.
A daughter who's a captain is pretty cool.
You're not worried?
No.
You better not do this.
If you do, I'll kill you.
Oh, incredible.
Bong, you can use the bathroom now!
Hah!
Oh, you stop right there.
How dare you steal from me?
What?
I never stole anything.
How old are you?
How dare you act so rude to me!
What?
I'm ninety!
Yeah, right!
If you're ninety, I'm a hundred and twenty!
What did you say?
Ouch! Ouch!
Oh! He's killing me!
Help! Help! Oh...
Why are you hurting my mother?
Because she's stealing!
These don't belong to you! Finders keepers!
Mother, get up.
She's not doing this because she's all alone.
Her children are teachers, judges, and doctors.
She's doing this to keep herself busy.
She's not doing this for money.
Don't look down on her!
Don't! Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Let's go.
You saved me. You're the best.
If Bong finds out, he'll be mad.
What if you get hurt?
It'll cost a lot of money, you know?
You're not in pain?
I'm too furious to feel any pain.
Oh, don't tell Bong. He'll worry.
You really showed him off.
You're a good liar.
My children are judges and doctors?
Sometimes one must lie.
Right. Sometimes one must lie.
Anggeum, want a pancake?
Don't waste your money on pancake.
Think about what it took you to make that.
I'm making money to spend it.
Remember how much we wanted one?
Let's get one.
Give us pancake.
Pancake?
I'll get you a thick one.
How yummy.
There's no honey in here.
But there is. Look.
Oh, you do. But I don't have any.
Watch out.
The person you have called is unavailable...
Is something wrong?
No.
You seem agitated.
I can see it in your face.
And you don't whistle anymore.
What's wrong?
I'll be back.
Why won't you answer my calls?
Why are you doing this to me?
I deserve to know hwy.
Tell me if I've upset you.
You know how I am.
I pass out when someone screams.
You passed out? Why?
Who would scream at you?
Your wife.
What?
Your wife came to me,
spit gum at my face, pushed me,
and screamed at me not to see you again.
No one has every done that to me.
My heart is still pounding.
She said she'd leave me alone if I pay her.
Money? She asked for money?
It's not like I'm dying to meet a man.
Why should I expose myself to such brutality
and give money away to see you?
Just leave.
You and I are over...
Be quiet.
It's not over for us.
It's me. I need to see you.
Why? What's up?
I'll tell you when we meet.
Did someone say something to you?
No, nobody said anything.
I have something to give you.
Give me?
Okay. I'll see you there.
Oh, he did?
He started nagging about everything.
Don't wear makeup, don't be a model.
Post family pictures on your blog,
you're a married woman.
He went all crazy.
He wouldn't let me wear makeup this morning.
He's jealous.
- Jealous?
- Yes.
He's jealous because he loves you so much.
No way.
I'm serious.
You two are so funny.
Your roles have completely changed.
Remember when he came
with divorce papers?
Congratulations, manager.
You have the upper hand now.
You should have some fun now.
It'll be great.
Oh, that bastard.
He should be kicked out in his underwear.
I know how that feels.
Hello?
It's me. I'll be late.
Okay.
Why? Why? For what?
I have a work dinner.
Again? Where?
Hello? Hello? Hobak!
I don't believe this...
Good job.
He must be going mad.
Hey, get in.
You won't help me with the seatbelt?
They do in dramas.
Don't watch such dramas.
They're driving men mad.
Where would you like to go?
To the beach.
Do you have time for that?
I'll make time, if it's for you.
Where are we going?
Follow me.
I told my boss I'd be back in an hour.
That's not the problem here.
Where is this?
Come in.
This is where Minjung lives.
Look.
He says no, but he has a woman.
He looks better and he dresses better.
Men change when they have a woman.
I don't think they're living together.
There's only one toothbrush here.
She comes and goes.
She can't move in just yet.
Minjung.
Today's the day we first met.
We met 20 years ago today.
We did?
I had forgotten the date.
It's so nice to be out with you.
I was so excited in the car.
I still make you feel excited?
Minjung,
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
Minjung,
come to me.
What are you going to do?
About what?
You don't care if Minjung gets remarried?
Seeing all that didn't make you mad?
Wake up or you'll lose him.
Don't let another woman snatch him up!
Subtitles by KBS World
Honey.
You... You stay right there!
You're dead!
How can you bring him here?
Whom I meet is none of your business.
What if Minjung gets married again.
How will you take care of the kids?
If I do get married again...
You're getting married again?
If it weren't for her, we wouldn't be here!
Oh, please stop!
I'll go and kill myself!
Don't butt in when we're talking!
You're so mean!
You can't live by yourself.
I'll raise them.
What are you going to do?
I have to catch them in the act.
I'd rather die than let it go on.
What do you think you're doing?