Subtitles by KBS World
- Cheers.
What was that?
It sounded like a mobile phone.
Who's there?
I someone here?
Okay, Daese. I'll be right there.
Nobody's there.
People usually don't come up here.
Maybe it was the landlady.
I have to go.
Something came up at home.
My brother in law called.
You need a new lock. It's broken.
There's nothing to steal.
Nobody comes here.
Why didn't you answer your phone?
You called me?
It was really loud so I didn't hear it.
You should go home.
Your family called many times.
Where were you?
Why did you leave Jungji with Miho?
Jungji's not the problem here.
- Oh, my heart.
- What's wrong?
Here, there, everywhere.
I couldn't get anything done.
What are you talking about?
Ugh! Minjung is seeing someone.
What?
Why did you have to call me right then?
I should've burst the door open and checked.
You probably heard wrong.
You went to Minjung's place?
Yes.
Where does he live?
It's not that far.
What do we do?
The ink on the divorce paper isn't even dry,
and he's already seeing a woman!
He has no conscience.
Oh! Legally, they're not divorced yet.
Right?
I'm sorry, father.
She's been begging for forgiveness for an hour now.
It was totally your fault.
I know.
Your family can come for a visit.
They should've said hello,
instead of hiding under the table.
But Daese,
I think they were curious of how she's doing.
They probably wanted to drop by when nobody
was home, but you came home, unfortunately.
So I'm saying it was my fault.
My fault for coming home then and there.
Father.
You should let this one pass.
And we should invite her family over.
If they lived by themselves, they would've had a housewarming party already.
So I'm saying this was my fault.
Gwangbak is faultless.
I'm the weird one who caused all this.
I shouldn't have gotten on her nerves.
I'm very sorry for all this, Gwangbak.
Oh, honey.
We can never have a quiet day.
What will we do?
I'm disappointed in you.
Why?
I know I made father angry. It's my fault.
But how could you not say anything?
Looking at me like,
"It's all your fault."
You told me not to butt in.
But today, you should've said something.
Oh, boy. What am I supposed to do?
I'm damned if I do, I'm damned if I don't.
Because you do when you shouldn't,
and you don't when you actually should.
I knew it.
Just leave it all to you? Yeah, right!
Why can't your father just laugh it off?
You heard?
He called to complain, so I yelled at him.
Why did you come back?
I have to finish this.
This month was okay.
Winter is the slow season, but we're okay.
Thanks to you.
No, thanks to you.
You convinced the men to stay with us,
and you kept bringing in work.
But marriage isn't that easy, right?
How did you know?
Your wife's home, but you're here.
It's so difficult.
It's like my mind goes blank.
Sometimes I don't recognize her.
Even after dozens of years, you'd feel that.
If it gets too bad, you get a divorce.
You should work harder.
You're a man.
I would, if I knew how.
But no matter how hard I try, I just... Ugh.
Father, what happened today was my fault.
Please forgive me.
You say I have no respect for your family or you,
but I respect you deeply.
I learned a lot from the golden key you got.
I will remember what you said about love
and respect, and I'll work very hard.
A woman? He said that?
It looks like it.
Who cares if he does?
We're over.
You're not! You have kids.
Don't say such old fashioned things.
Who lives for their kids?
Everyone does!
Who else could you live for?
Mom, women in the old days might have, but not us.
My life is more important than my kids.
It's just you.
Everyone else puts their kids first.
My life is my kid's life, and vice versa.
You can't separate yourself from them.
How can you be so childish?
Anyway, change Minjung's mind before...
I'm not crazy!
Mom, stop it and go to bed.
And mind your own business.
I'm scared he might want to come back.
What? Oh...
Blabbermouth, narrow minded Sangnam!
Don't wake me up.
I have to get up early.
- We're off.
See you later.
- Daebak, have a nice day.
- Have a good day.
Gwangbak's father in law is really nasty.
Oh, really?
Are you happy to hear that?
Not happy. Just worried.
You clap and laugh when you're worried?
My princess is kind of different.
Princess my butt.
You know how weird you've gotten after marriage?
Did Gwangbak tell you that?
He comes home whenever he feels like it
and starts nagging at Gwangbak,
threatening to kill her if she's mean to his son. Unbelievable.
Right, father. I heard it, too.
"Don't control Sangnam behind his back."
Or was it beside? Where? His head?
I think it must be "behind."
People usually control others from behind.
You're smart, my princess.
Did your mother teach you that?
You better not get between me and Sangnam.
I'll get you!
Mrs. Lee, you're really funny.
Or is it sister? What was it?
Sister in law.
Why does law have to get involved?
Oh, quiet!
I mean, please keep it down.
How did you see that?
I heard it from under the table.
Mom and I went to her house,
but her father in law came, so we hid.
I was so nervous about getting caught.
Oh, you hid under the table? How funny.
I know.
Why did you have to go there?
I was wondering how Gwangbak was doing.
Is she doing well?
Where were you? She's miserable.
I feel sorry for Gwangbak.
I can call her Gwangbak, right?
I'm way above her.
Yes.
Don't ever try that again.
But I'm glad you didn't get caught.
We did.
You did?
Hello, Mr. Choi.
I'm Gwangbak's dad.
Hello.
I heard about what happened.
What my wife did was very rude.
I don't know what to say.
Can you find it in your heart to...
I thought about it, but I can't understand it.
Oh, I'm sure.
But she just wanted to check on Gwangbak.
She didn't want you to find out, but...
Mr. Choi, do you have time for lunch?
I have plans.
How about dinner, then?
I'm busy. Goodbye.
What did he say?
How could you be so thoughtless?
Didn't you think of Gwangbak?
I didn't know he'd come home.
Then why didn't you say hello?
Why would you hide under the table?
I'd be furious, too.
Gwangbak's in trouble now.
What you did was wrong. Ugh.
Oh...
What's that?
Beef in soy sauce. It's for Minjung.
But they are divorced.
He's still like my son in law.
Oh, I can't believe my ears.
Are you mad I stole your line?
Please babysit Jungji for me.
He ate, so you can just watch him.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Minjung, drop by for lunch.
I'd love to wait, but I have a class.
I'll call you later.
Oh, my legs.
Mother.
Why are you so surprised?
You scared me.
What are you doing here?
How did you know?
I have ways, you know?
- Were you expecting someone else?
- Huh?
Who else could visit you but me?
Unless you are seeing someone in secret.
Was someone here?
It's clean here and the fridge, too.
The stew looks like it was just made.
I made it.
You did?
I had to go get something.
Anyway, what are you doing...
What do you think?
To make you some food.
Please don't.
I can take care of myself.
I don't want you coming here.
How could you say that?
Are we strangers?
Minjung, let's sit down.
You're making me uncomfortable.
I'm grateful that you care,
but you're making things harder for me.
Yeongdal.
Tada! Blood sausage!
You're the best! How exciting!
Oh, wow.
Shh!
Say ah!
Ah.
Yeongdal!
Come down.
Why?
Why won't you even come out of your room?
Come down and help me.
Me? But I'm pregnant.
Hah! You think that's so special.
Since you're pregnant, you should help.
Two of you can do more work.
I was told not to move.
Who said that?
You have to move around. Come down.
Clean these.
Clean them, rinse them, and put them in the basket.
When that's done, turn the stove off,
rinse them in clean water and hang them.
I can't do stuff like this, Mrs. Lee.
Don't call me Mrs. Lee.
You should try doing things.
Oh, man.
Where is she?
What are you doing?
Mrs. Lee keeps giving me work.
You're too precious to work.
Come out.
Oh.
Yeongdal!
- What are you doing?
- Oh.
What do you want?
Yeongdal, come out.
You're going to boss her around again?
I only asked her to clean the bean sprouts!
Hey, she's my daughter in law, not yours.
But aren't we all family here?
Go and clean the bean sprouts.
Mother, you're crushing the rice cake.
How did you know?
Would you like some? Oh.
I won't eat rice cake you sat on.
Mother, I'm hurt.
About what?
I had 5 kids and you never bought me food.
It's not like they're expensive.
I should come before her,
if you want her to learn any manners.
You should respect the hierarchy.
Yeongdal was eating blood sausage that Don bought her all by herself. Did you know?
What?
Why that little...
- How are the kids?
- They're fine.
Why do you keep giving my mom false hope?
What do you mean?
We're divorced, so why do you hang around?
I heard you live near here?
I can't move far away because of the kids.
I'm not interested in you, so don't mind me.
You're giving my parents hope.
Stop sending them any wrong signals.
They're all nagging me now.
Just sever the ties.
I'm not going back to you.
Dream on.
Even if you begged me, I won't go back.
You and I are over.
We already signed the papers.
I met your mother because she called me.
I'm actually offended here.
Don't answer my parents phone calls.
It makes my life miserable.
Please find it for me, please.
You should go home and wait.
I'm not sure if we'll find it very soon.
I have to get it back. It's my livelihood.
I'm begging you.
Minjung.
Sunjeong.
How could this happen?
How could anyone steal a delivery truck?
Officer, please catch that bastard.
Minjung is a hard working man.
Men like that thief is the worst.
Wait until I get my hands on him.
I'm going to wring his neck.
How can he do this?
How can he steal a delivery truck?
Sir, please catch him. Please.
You were pretty good at swearing.
Me? When?
Just now. Remember what you said?
That bastard, wring his neck...
Minjung, I'm older now.
I'm not the same Sunjeong you used to know.
Try living in this world alone.
You can't help but swear.
You're right.
I'm good at swearing, too.
But what do we do now?
You'll have to pay for the packages.
I'll have to.
I can't believe this happened.
How far do I have to go down?
I have no more tears to shed.
Mom!
Where's mom?
Hi. She went to the market.
I heard your father in law's mean.
- Who told you that?
- Your mom.
I posted it and everyone's talking.
Why did you do that?
What's wrong with you?
What did you just say?
What?
I'm your aunt!
Whatever.
Let me ask you something.
You're family now, so don't cause problems.
Help my mom out with the chores.
I know you're pregnant and all
but she won't ask you to do hard labor.
You know grandmother and mom don't get along.
So you should be their mediator.
You're lecturing me now?
That's funny.
Just do as I say.
And why are you dressed like this?
Put on some decent clothes for your baby.
My family thinks you're obscene.
You're really rude, aren't you?
I'm your aunt.
Rude?
You think I'm still your friend?
How dare you talk to me like that?
You think you're better than me
because you got good grades in school?
Watch your manners!
What? Watch my manners?
Don't be cheeky.
I'm ranked fifth in the family.
You're tenth in the family.
I'm double that!
From now on, call me aunt.
So stupid.
And to think you used to be a teacher!
Do this again and I'm telling your father.
Your father does everything I say.
And he talks to me very politely.
You don't know anything!
Hey! You!
Hey, Wang Gwangbak!
Uncle.
What's wrong with you?
What?
Just because you got good grades doesn't mean you can behave badly.
You're so mean.
Don't come to my house anymore.
Just don't.
Did Yeongdal put you up to this?
She's your aunt now.
Is this really who you are?
You're siding with your immature wife?
I'm so disappointed in you.
I don't care if you are.
All I care about is my princess' opinion.
Princess?
Yes.
You think your princess is still your friend?
She married me, so she's your aunt.
You don't even know basic manners?
And to think you used to be a teacher!
This is why...
Your father in law is mean to you.
Call her aunt from now on.
Uncle!
Ugh!
Mr. Choi.
Yes, Mrs. Lee?
I just have to say this.
How could you be so mean to Gwangbak?
What did I teach her?
You'll get her if she causes troubles?
And what else? Extreme measures?
What is that? What are you going to do?
Force them to get a divorce?
You're not going to move away?
What?
I hate running into you like this.
Then you should move away.
My family's been here for 40 years.
I'm sorry I didn't get your permission,
but what you did was far worse.
You shouldn't mistreat someone else's child.
She's your only daughter in law, and won't
she have to take care of you when you're old?
Sunjeong! Sunjeong, water! With ice!
Aunt isn't home.
You're banned from visiting your parents.
Is business good?
Yes, it's winter.
What's up?
What happened? Investing.
I need to think about it.
What's there to think about? It'll double.
I'm too scared to try things like that.
And of course, I have no money.
Then you'll live like this forever.
Oh, whatever.
Subak, give me one more day.
I'll have to take out a second mortgage.
A chance like this won't come again.
I took out a mortgage, too.
But you don't own a house.
Do you have an account I didn't know about?
Well...
Is this the police?
I'm Ko Minjung.
You haven't caught them yet?
Okay.
I see.
How's your back?
It's getting better.
The weather's probably making it worse.
What brings you?
You probably know about the divorce.
I heard.
So I was hoping you could talk Minjung out of it.
Why did they get divorced?
I don't think there's a specific reason.
Little things built up and exploded.
I'm always on my son's side.
I'm sure they've really thought about it,
so I don't think I can change anything.
But they have little kids.
One is still a baby.
Mr. Ko, even if Minjung made up his mind,
your opinion might make him rethink things.
There's still cooling off period,
so please help me try to change his mind.
The person you have called is unavailable,
so your call will be directed to voice mail.
Are you sure?
Of course!
Mom, I'll be back.
This is nuts.
They got divorced?
I knew it.
Pretend you don't know.
How can I?
I watched them with my own two eyes!
How can this happen?
I'm shaking!
I can't let them get away with this.
Home-wreckers are the worst in the world.
They must be punished.
What are you going to do?
This is wrong.
Oh, nice.
Right now?
Okay, Sedal.
There are two exits, here and there.
Let's wait out here and attack him.
Okay.
Here.
I don't need them. I'll be over there.
I knew my mom had some money saved.
But this isn't even $100,000.
But this is all she has.
She's really excited.
But Hobak chickened out.
She'll never be rich.
Take good care of my mom's money.
Don't worry.
This is like petty cash. It'll be fine.
Let's go. I have an appointment.
We're not having dinner?
I'll take you somewhere nice next time.
Okay.
Subak, hold on.
What is it?
I was so happy to see you again.
Silly.
I'm serious. I won't forget you.
You sound like you're going somewhere.
How can I go anywhere without you?
Thanks, Subak.
When your father dragged you home.
I was at a loss for a long time.
He said he won't give his daughter to me.
It still echoes in my ears.
You should forget that.
I think I will be able to now.
You should come and meet my parents soon.
Sure. You should go.
I'll clean up here.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
Yes. Did you buy the plane tickets?
And the passports?
Okay.
Hey! Sangnam! Here!
Who are you? What?
Who are you? Huh?
- Who are you?
- Sangnam!
- Are you a thief?
Who are you?
Help!
What are you? Huh? A thief?
Wait, wait.
Sangnam!
This is for my brother in law.
Don't mess with another man's woman.
Watch your back wherever you go.
I'm warning you. Don't ever do this.
Who do you think you are?
I'll kill you.
Run!
How...
Minjung.
Sangnam and I paid him back real good,
so you can go to bed feeling reassured.
Don't ask what.
Just remember what I said.
Why don't you join us?
Next time? Okay.
Here is Sangnam.
Yes, Minjung. This is Sangnam.
We will protect you, okay?
Cheer up. We're the Wang's son in laws.
I'll buy you a drink sometime.
Okay. Whatever it is, thank you.
Bye.
Hey, your kick was amazing.
Hey, no need to turn around.
Minjung, you didn't answer my call.
Don't take this the wrong way.
I'm not giving this to you. It's a loan.
So don't say no.
You will get back on your feet soon.
Cheer up. You can do it.
Sunjeong, thanks.
I'll pay you back.
I'm glad I can help you.
Don't skip dinner and cheer up.
Hello?
Who is this?
Mother.
I'm home.
You're home?
Did you have dinner?
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
What is it?
I'm so heartbroken.
Why do I bother living?
I should just die.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Did Anggeum say something to you?
I'm more upset about Don.
I'm also upset about Yeongdal.
What happened?
Bong.
Are you coming home now?
Yes.
Uh, no, I got home a while ago.
Didn't you learn any manners?
Where do I go first when I come home?
The front door.
What?
You come through the door, right?
Which room do I go in first?
Mom's room.
Right.
And you've learned nothing from that?
I'm sorry, Bong.
And you shouldn't play favorites with food.
It's the worst of all.
What were you thinking?
Why didn't you get mother blood sausages?
Mom.
Oh, what's wrong with you?
You only care about your wife!
I don't matter to you anymore?
You don't care about your mother?
You're upset over that?
Why don't you get married, too, then?
Don't you have some old man you've been eying?
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
I wish I didn't have to see her.
Living with her is stressful.
You should try to teach her.
You think she'll listen to me?
Don is head over heels in love with her.
Maybe you should try talking to her.
I can't. She's my sister in law.
Why are you so forgiving?
You aren't with your daughters.
She's not my daughter.
When the weather warms up,
I'll try to find a small apartment for them.
With what money?
I'll have to see.
I have some former students who work at the bank,
so I can take out a mortgage.
You can't do that.
Don't touch this house.
Even when Subak had nowhere to go,
I didn't even think about doing that.
So don't touch this house.
What are you talking about?
We want you to run the company again.
We hired someone and the business was bad.
The company will go belly up at this rate.
Can you please come back?
Are you serious?
From what you've done in the past,
you could settle the debt in 3 years.
After that, you can have the company back.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I'm happy for you, Minjung.
I can't believe this is really happening.
How could this happen?
See?
I knew you'd make it.
I could even dance.
Would you like to?
You think I'd say no?
Then get up.
No.
The timing was perfect, too.
What if I actually used it?
I know.
If you had bought a truck with this,
it would've been a waste of money.
It's automatic.
What will you do with the parcel service?
I'm giving it back to my friend.
When good things happen, I think of you.
In the past, I didn't have anyone to share good news with.
My wife hated when I think about work.
I had to celebrate alone,
but now I have you to share it with.
I know how that feels, Minjung.
It was the same for me.
When I was raising Miho alone
when she first started crawling,
when she took her first step,
when she first said mom,
when she received awards at school,
I had nobody to tell,
so I cried.
Whenever she did something lovely,
I wanted to tell someone,
but I had nobody. It was so sad.
You should've called me.
Minjung, let's go.
Go where?
Follow me.
What are we doing here?
Let's get a suit. My gift.
You should wear something nice.
You don't have to. It looks expensive here.
Don't look at the price tag.
They have lots of nice suits.
You don't like the hair pin?
Huh?
You don't ever wear it.
I'm saving it for a special occasion.
What if I lose it?
If you lose it, I'll buy you another one.
Miho, did you see my hair pin?
No. Mom, my money is gone, too.
What money?
The laminated one that man gave me.
I haven't seen it. It's gone?
Has my sister been here?
Yes.
She went into my room, didn't she?
Give it back.
You say that whenever you see me.
Give what back? What?
That hair pin! Take it off!
Say hello first.
Take it off!
You came here for this stupid hair pin?
You're impossible.
Take it off before I get really mad.
Or I'll take it off for you!
Girl!
You don't even wear it, so why can't I?
This isn't something you can wear!
Oh, girl!
It's not even made with diamonds.
What else?
The money.
What money?
The laminated ten dollar bill.
It was only ten dollars!
I said give it back!
How can you steal from your niece?
Give it back right now.
Fine! Here!
I want the laminated one back!
I don't know where that is!
Go laminate that one.
You are unbelievable.
You think all money is the same?
You didn't think about why it was laminated?
When your niece got it laminated, even if you're money-crazy,
it didn't occur to you that it must be special?
Don't you dare come back to my house again.
It's not your house!
She's so rude.
Father!
Oh, hi.
Hello.
I should...
Why don't you finish eating?
What is she doing here?
Just because.
Just because?
She heard I hurt my back,
and she's been coming here, cooking me food.
I told her not to come.
Why is she doing that?
It's not like that.
What do you mean?
I'm glad, father.
I knew she had feelings for you.
Don't even.
What are you doing here?
You look happy.
Mother.
Hi.
Let me do that.
Leave it.
No, I'm good at doing the dishes.
Mother, you open that bag.
What is it?
Do you like it?
Of course I do!
Try it on.
If it doesn't fit, I'll get it exchanged.
Oh, it's perfect.
Whoa!
Shh! Shh!
If grandmother finds out, she'll be mad.
I'm not good enough for that?
Egh, hyo, hyo...
Oh, why did you buy this?
This must be expensive.
Mother, I'm sorry about everything.
I know you're upset about my father.
I know he can be too much to handle.
Actually, I was so upset that I didn't even want to see you.
It's not because of his coat,
but I guess I know how he feels.
My family motto is put yourself in others shoes.
Having to be on his own must have been hard.
I'll have to be more understanding.
Thank you, mother.
Oh, my. Wow...
Mr. Blabbermouth is here.
What? Do I even deserve your hug?
Mom called. It worked like magic.
Where did you get such an idea?
I put myself in her shoes.
My darling husband.
But I should spank you.
You were to talk to me when spending money.
I charged it. You have to pay the bill.
What?
I'm a blabbermouth?
Will you call me that again?
You've had a few days off, so come to work.
I can't run it on my own.
Okay.
Are you finished?
I'm getting ready to go home.
Would you like to learn how to drink?
I told you I'd teach you, but I've been busy.
Okay. Let me put these away first.
I'll do it for you.
There's no elevator here.
We should've gone to a place with one.
A tent bar in the winter is pretty nice.
It's perfect for learning to drink.
I've been feeling lonely.
Probably because your daughter got married.
It's not just because of that.
I get so lonely at night.
Turn the heater on high.
That doesn't help.
My feet don't touch anyone else's feet when I stretch my legs out.
I feel so lonely.
Daese, you don't feel that way?
I have no time to feel lonely.
I'm busy training my daughter in law.
You're training your daughter in law?
I should, if I don't want my son to suffer.
It must be nice to be so busy with that.
When I turn the pages of the calendar,
I feel so heartbroken, as if I'm dying.
I'll get another year older this year.
Age is just a number.
I've forgotten about my age already.
It must be nice.
I don't feel like drinking with no elevator.
Hey! You!
It's okay. Things happen.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
You should go.
Just like that?
You had a drink, so you'll sleep well.
Turn the heater on and don't stretch your legs.
Goodnight, Salla.
I'm not sure if I'll fall asleep well.
Goodbye.
Dream about me.
No thanks.
Mom, did you eat?
Yes.
Did you drink? With whom?
A friend. A friend who's clueless.
Daese, were you on a date?
How did you know?
You and Sangnam are the same.
You whistle when you meet women.
I got you!
You did.
Don't tell anyone.
I haven't felt this way in a long time.
I can't believe I can still feel this way.
I thought I'd grow old all alone.
It's like I'm back in my twenties.
You look the same, too.
I know you're lying, but I still feel good.
Good for you.
You deserve to be happy.
Who is she? I'm curious.
Later.
Don't tell the kids yet.
It's embarrassing.
I'll have to see.
If you keep being mean, I'll tell Gwangbak.
Daese, would you like to have a beer?
He's divorced?
Yes.
He moved out recently.
That's good.
Did you tell him about Miho?
Not yet.
Tell him! He's divorced now.
Daese,
I think I  must be a really bad woman.
I didn't show it, but when I heard
he was divorced, I was so happy,
as if I was waiting for that to happen.
I'm so mean, aren't I?
But it's natural.
You two were meant to be together.
She wasn't the right woman for him,
since they got a divorce.
Don't let him go.
It happened so he could be with you.
Is it okay?
Can I have him?
You weren't the cause of their divorce.
They broke up on their own.
You two are meant to be together.
It's a good thing, Sunjeong.
Your father in law dropped by.
I'm also worried about the kids.
I'm sorry, father.
I'm going to bring them when things improve.
How will you raise them?
They're my kids, so I must.
Welcome!
Thank you.
See how much I can borrow on my credit.
Or I'll have to take out a mortgage.
Yes. Call me right back.
Where is Subak?
She said she has plans.
Oh, she's such a goof off.
She leaves when there's work.
That's your nickname.
I'm making dumpling stew, your favorite,
so why don't you drop by?
You're busy?
Okay.
Judge, you don't have to do that.
Yeongdal, you move the dumplings.
Don't ask our judge to do it.
When's the announcement?
Huh?
Seoul National University.
It isn't yet.
Mom.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
I'm sorry, mom.
I can't become a judge.
I got into the Maritime University.
It was early admission, so I can't change it.
I'm going to become a captain.
What did you say?
What did you just say?
I'm going to become a captain.
What?
Are you out of your mind?
What's happening?
They were fine just now.
I think Haebak did something.
- Did she get pregnant?
- Man.
What are you going to do?
Let's go.
What's wrong?
Captain?
How can you become a captain?
I had such high hopes for you!
Anggeum, don't hit her.
How can all my daughters disappoint me like this? Huh?
Captain? How could you?
- Get out.
- Hey!
Uncle, let me go.
Daebak, tell your father to come home! Hurry!
Oh, boy.
Ugh!
Oh, what do I do?
Aeji, Jungji.
They're asleep. Sit.
Haebak, the kids are asleep, so tell me.
I've already been there, so I know.
You must be shaking with fear.
Don't be scared. The baby is your weapon.
Have you seen a doctor?
No.
No?
Who is it?
What do you mean?
Who is the bastard?
You have to tell me, so we can fix this.
He's a captain?
Huh?
A captain of which ship?
Is he hiding from you?
I don't know what you're saying.
I know everything.
Your belly will grow soon.
That captain won't take care of you?
That bastard!
Give me his number.
We should teach him a lesson.
Why are there so many people like us here?
How many is it already?
Hobak, me, you.
Come here.
You're dead. Come here!
Mrs. Lee, I mean, Anggeum, don't do this.
What's done is done.
I'll meet the captain and take care of it.
You don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, of course I do! I have experience.
When I found out, I wanted to die.
What are you talking about?
It's not that. Come here.
It's not? What is it, then? He's a captain?
The person you called is unavailable,
so your call will be directed...
Are you busy? You didn't have to come.
Because I was happy.
I've been having great luck since we started
seeing each other again, so
I wanted to take you out.
Would you like a picture?
Yes, please.
Minjung, is it okay?
Sure, let's do it.
Here it is.
What are you talking about?
I lost my house?
Hello?
Is anyone home?
Honey, what are they talking about?
They told us to move out of the house.
Oh, Bong. Oh...
The deeds to the house.
The deeds to the house!
Where are the deeds to the house?
Bong! Oh, no! Bong! Oh...
Subtitles by KBS World
Minjung, don't go into shock...
I wanted to tell you, but I couldn't.
Why are you hesitating?
Don't you know what this house means?
This is all your fault, Anggeum!
You and I should die!
- Get out!
- Mom!
Please leave.
I won't call you mother.
Stop it!
I won't come back again.
I came to see her, but she hates me.
Remember when we put up the door plate?
Will I be able to put this up again?
This is all your fault!
Get out!
Go somewhere and die or something!
Mother, I'm sorry.
Why would you be sorry?
I didn't raise my children properly.