Subtitles by KBS World
What is it?
Let's eat first.
What would you like?
Pick whatever you want.
It's my treat.
Do you want some meat?
It's lunch. I want something simple.
I'll get bibimbap.
Get meat. My treat.
You're always working too hard.
Excuse me?
What do you have for meat dishes?
It's okay, mom.
Meat's for dinner with alcohol.
I have to go back to work soon.
I'll just get bibimbap.
My daughter can't enjoy her lunch because of that darn job.
Hello? We'd like two stone pot bibimbap.
Make it extra delicious!
It's for my daughter!
Depression must be going around these days.
Depression?
Lots of people die from it.
I'm afraid to watch the news these days.
It's filled with stories about people who kill themselves of depression.
But that could happen to us.
But why kill yourself?
You should go on living, no matter what.
It must be unbearable for them.
Your sister might make the news, too.
Let's help her out just this once.
She wants to die.
It doesn't take much for someone to go mad.
She was sobbing, saying she just wants to die.
I never ever seen her look that lost.
What if she does something stupid?
Minjung wants her to go live with his dad,
but I can't send her when she's depressed.
We should help her find a place in Seoul.
You have money, don't you?
What money?
What do you mean, what money?
You've been saving up, I know.
Let's lend Subak that money.
I don't have money. I don't.
But you've been working for years!
I'm not asking it for free.
And it's not for a stranger.
Let's help your sister out.
I'll pay you good interest.
You can make money and do good.
Your father can't sleep these days.
Subak must move out by the end of this week,
so bring the money tomorrow.
I wonder if we can find a place quickly.
Got it? Let's go.
You're finished, right?
Mom!
I don't have that kind of money.
What did you do with the money you made?
I don't make enough money to save.
Sedal doesn't have a job, so...
I'll pay you back!
You think I won't pay you back?
It's not that.
The fortune teller said that your sister is destined to be rich.
I'll tell her to pay you back.
So lend her the money, just this once.
What's my bill?
Hello.
- Can't catch me!
- Stop right there!
It must be hard for you.
It must be since it's your first time.
Parcel service business is hard.
I don't mind it but I'm worried about Subak.
I'd like for her to remain in Seoul,
but I can't afford it...
Since we must take care of my father,
I'd like her to move in with him...
I know I have no right to say this now,
but I'm worried about him living alone.
I'm sure you are.
Your parents were a loving couple,
but now your father's all alone.
And you're the eldest son.
I'm living with my mother,
so I know exactly how you feel.
I'd put it off, so I could take care of him when things were better...
But with everything happening,
I really get why they say you should be good to your parents when you can.
My father's different from other men.
My mother was sick for a long time,
so he can take care of the household.
And he's worked hard all his life and being a farmer,
he won't make Subak work hard.
He'll take care of the girls,
and there's a room at the orchard,
so he can stay there.
What about you?
I can stay at the office.
Father, can you talk to Subak?
She won't even give me the chance to talk.
Look, isn't this really cute?
This is for you, Sintong.
And this is for you, Bangtong.
Mom, when are we getting new clothes?
We always get stuff people throw out.
We're not special at all.
Oh, yes you are special.
Just wait.
I'm going to get you your own rooms.
- Really?
Of course.
We're going to move to an apartment,
and I'll buy you beds and desks.
God, please let us buy our own apartment.
Yes, please!
What's all that?
Mom found these at the donation box.
Why do you keep doing that?
You want your boys to wear trash?
If we wash them,
they'll be as good as new.
And they're brand name clothes, too.
The boys don't mind.
Mom's going to buy an apartment.
You're wearing one too.
This is from the donation box?
- You didn't know?
- Man!
Ugh!
You liked it because it's brand name.
Put that back on!
What if the owner of this shirt sees me wearing this and goes,
"Oh, look at him wearing the shirt I threw out."
Would that make you happy?
You don't respect your husband at all!
I'm going nuts.
Your sons are more mature than you.
Ouch! That hurt!
I don't care about buying an apartment.
I just want good food, nice clothes and lots of time to play video games.
Me too, me too.
You two get out!
Mom, don't mind them.
They're just immature.
Oh, Sintong, you're the best.
Nice going.
Your own son says you're immature.
Put your shirt back on.
There's nothing to see.
Nothing?
There's plenty to see.
If you turn around
Would we be able to look into the other's eyes?
Bounce...
Mother.
I'm home.
Hi.
Did you have dinner?
I don't have an appetite.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
She made herself bibimbap in this bowl and ate it all.
You still fall for that after 40 years?
She's yelling at me all day,
but acts all weak when she sees you.
I wonder what kind of illness that is.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
You have to move out this week?
Yes.
Where will you go?
What do you mean by that?
She'll stay in Seoul.
But she can't afford to do that.
I know you're upset.
But Minjung's the one who's most upset.
But Minjung did this to himself.
She's done nothing to deserve this,
so she's the one who's most upset!
Is this a competition?
Get Minjung and find out who's more upset.
A married couple must work together,
especially when things become tough.
You had a good life until now, thanks to Minjung, so you should bear this with him.
What? Why should she have to bear this?
She must.
Your mom and I survived hardships together,
And look, she's the boss of me now.
That's how things go.
Your mom had a very hard life.
At least you know!
She did have a hard life.
She used to live with gold nuggets lying around,
using money as toilet paper,
but her life after marrying you was hard.
It wasn't as hard as yours who got arthritis from playing jacks with gold nuggets.
To be honest, what hardships did you suffer?
Did you have to make money?
Or was I a tough mother in law?
You had a good life.
I made money by raising kids and living with a tight budget.
And as for you, everyone already knows how you treat me.
They know you've been mean to me!
- Mom!
- Why? Am I wrong?
I never heard such a thing before.
We always veer off the subject.
I know.
Take the girls to your father in law's.
I don't want to.
I'm going to stay in Seoul.
Do as I say.
Why are you trying to force her to go?
What if something happens?
She's suffering from depression!
And how can she take care of an old man?
There's a room at the orchard,
and he can take care of himself.
Subak will have it easy.
It won't be.
Just hold on.
Hold on?
Is there another solution?
Are you getting money from somewhere?
- Size 90, 10.
- 90, 10.
- Size 95, 11.
- 95, 11.
- Size 100, 11.
- 100, 11.
Just a sec.
Mom, what is it?
My daughter, where are you?
Why are you working so hard?
Nobody will thank you for that, will they?
Hobak, did you think about it?
Mom, let's talk later.
I'm busy right now.
Okay, okay.
There isn't must time... Bye.
Who are you?
This must be the wrong place.
I'm looking for Sintong and Bangtong...
Oh, it's the apartment across the street.
- Oh, thank you.
- Sure.
Sintong, Bangtong.
Oh? Hello.
Oh, incredible.
This is the first time she's come to visit us!
Don't be rude. Please come in.
Your mom's not home yet, is she?
Grandmother brought you snacks.
This is so awkward.
Just let it go.
- Hello.
- You're home?
I'm always in the same place...
How did you find us?
You don't know where we live.
I do! I came to Bangtong's 1st birthday party.
Have fun.
Have fun with whom?
Come sit down.
I need to talk to you.
Well, I hear someone calling me.
I won't yell at you.
So come and sit down.
It's not that.
Someone's calling me.
See? Did you hear that?
I'm coming!
Okay!
Mom, mom, mom.
- What is it?
- Go over to my place.
Is it a roach again?
It's worse than a roach.
Hurry up!
Should we get our grandmother?
She'll be over pretty soon.
Sintong, Bangtong!
See?
What brings you here?
To see my grandchildren, of course.
Hello.
I wouldn't recognize you if I ran into you.
Your face changes every day.
Subak's the same.
It changes every 3 months.
Compared to Subak, I'm nothing.
Grandmother, can we take these to our room?
Sure, sure.
Take them to your room.
Did you recognize your grandchildren?
You couldn't recognize them if you ran into them on the street.
Of course I'd recognize my grandchildren.
They grow up so fast,
and you only see them once or twice a year.
Oh, you saw them on your birthday.
I'm amazed you found this place.
You never visit.
I found it find.
I don't forget if I see it once.
Since we're on the subject of seeing,
I feel bad for your eyes.
They must be shocked to see such a dreadful place after seeing Subak's grand mansion.
I heard she's in big trouble.
How sad. You can't rely on your son in law.
My heart's breaking for you.
If it is, tell your son to get a job.
I'd like to rely on my second son in law.
You always say I mistreat Sedal,
but am I doing that for no reason?
He should earn my affection.
He's making my daughter's life hard,
so how could I be nice to him?
I can't believe you're saying that here.
This is my son's place.
Your sons place my butt.
This is my daughter's place!
I'm sure she's paying for it!
What are you doing out here?
Don's sister in law is here.
I'm going nuts.
Stop that.
Your neck will break.
Don't worry.
I have a license in this.
I'm going nuts.
See? It's automatic.
Oh, boy.
What's my mom doing here?
Who knows? I sure don't.
She even brought the boys snacks.
I wonder what's gotten into her.
Call me when she's gone.
Don't go play video games!
I'll kill you!
I don't have money to go even if I wanted to.
Oh, you're home!
Oh, my poor daughter.
It must be so hard for you to support your husband, too.
I don't believe this.
You taught her to treat her husband badly just because she makes money.
She's doing that for a reason.
Oh, stop it, please.
You're home.
I put the boys to bed.
Oh, thanks, Yeongdal.
It's late.
Why don't you go home?
Your husband must be waiting,
so you should go.
I don't have a mother in law or a husband waiting for me at home.
So I don't have to go unless I want to.
I could even spend the night here.
Right, Yeongdal?
Right.
Like you know, I'm living with my in laws,
so I'm always busy.
But I do care about you guys.
I can't even buy my grandkids clothes.
Why? They have lots of clothes.
Well, actually, they're not really your grandchildren.
Their last name is Heo.
You were mean to her whens he got pregnant,
so why are you pointing that out now?
I had my reasons.
You sent her without a cent when you married her off.
Please, that's water under the bridge now.
Mom, go home.
I'll stop by tomorrow.
Okay then.
Let's talk tomorrow.
What about?
Talk about what tomorrow?
Mind your own business.
A mother and daughter have plenty to talk about.
You're always together like twins,
so how will you ever marry her off?
You and Subak were twins too, but you let her get married,
to a man who went bankrupt.
You don't have to see me out.
Just to the corner.
I live across the street, so don't.
Go inside and rest.
Bye, mom.
I'll see you tomorrow.
- Goodbye, Ms. Park.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye.
It's so dark!
They don't even turn the lights on.
It's an old apartment,
so there's no light.
Be careful. Don't fall down.
Ugh! Ouch, ouch...
Why can't she zip it?
She gets on my nerves.
Ouch it hurts.
Why did she come all the way here?
Who knows?
It's obvious.
She kept saying,
"my daughter, my daughter."
It's the first time you heard that, too, right?
She was probably unhappy to see your place.
She never talks about you with our friends.
She always talks about Minjung and Subak,
about what they bought her.
With good reasons.
People think you must be adopted!
And the grandkids, too.
She only loves Subak's girls,
complimenting their looks.
Sintong and Bangtong must've felt so awkward!
Did she come to ask for money?
Even if she calls you "my daughter,"
don't lend her any money.
I have no money to lend.
Nobody believes that.
Oh, I heard there are moms with several kids
who would take something away from one kid and give it to another.
Everyone in this neighborhood knows how your mom treasured only Subak.
You're too nice.
I wouldn't stand for it.
You're so mean to me, so why do you let your mom bully you like that?
If you're half as nice to me as you are to your mom,
I'd carry you around my back.
I'm too heavy for you to carry on your back.
People are so sharp when it comes to money.
It's like they can sniff it out.
Can I keep that money for you?
Excuse me?
Oh, man.
Wow, I'm really excited.
This is my first magazine debut,
so please make sure I look good.
And don't forget to give me the list of all the women who ask for my number.
Don't leave any of them out.
[Wang Gwangbak, Deposit $122, Woman Day
New balance, $375]
How funny!
Hey! Knock.
You munchkin!
I may be one but I'm very mature.
Don't treat me like a child.
You're not mature!
I'm going to open your door, too!
Suit yourself.
As if there's anything to see.
It'd do me more harm.
- You little...
- What do you want?
- Did you finish your homework?
- No.
- Did you go to the academy?
- Did you see Sangnam?
- No.
You didn't?
Don't you see him every day?
Why are you so interested?
I know why but stay away from him.
He won't fall for you.
If you're done, close the door.
Daebak!
Why are you so full of energy?
I don't like women who are too full of energy.
I had a big breakfast.
Daebak, have you grown much?
Stop pushing me.
I've been working out, though.
I'm going to wait until you're all grown up.
Hi!
Hi.
Stop that.
I said stop!
I'll get you when you're old.
Mr. Choi, good job!
You're the best!
Oh! Not there!
This way! This way!
No! Man...
Mr. Kim, get down from there.
Oh, man.
Do it like this, like this. Got it?
Lift it back up, and snap it back down, like this.
[Onset of boredom in relationships can be from...]
Oh, Miho, you're here.
Gwangbak, hello.
You look pretty.
Is that a new dress?
Daebak seems bored of me, so I got dressed up.
Men are visually stimulated creatures.
I heard you're a dating expert.
Yes, my friends ask me for advice.
Even the girls in 6th grade come to me.
They do?
If you have a problem, you can tell me.
Me? I don't have any problems.
But my friend does, a bit...
Your friend has a problem?
She says she does.
She met a man recently,
and some feelings were developing.
They weren't dating yet, but...
She was feeling him out.
Yes, she was. That's it.
You know so well.
That's why I'm an expert. And?
But one day, he just stopped calling.
Just like that?
Without any reason?
Yeah.
He's leading her on.
He's trying to play hard to get.
Leading her on?
Playing hard to get?
[Wang Daebak's daily schedule]
It looks good.
I'm not sure if you can keep it up, though.
I promised the geezer I'd cut back on the video games.
You're the hero of your own life.
If you want to study all day, sleep all day
or play video games all day, it's up to you.
Don't let others get to you.
I hope the rude had doesn't nag me.
Don't give her an excuse to nag you.
What should she do then?
It's simple. With men like that, you must make them fall for you and dump them.
Make them fall for you? How?
You must tantalize him first.
Tantalize? How?
What do you need to do?
It's simple.
Borrow $40,000 and disappear.
Uncle!
I'm right. If you borrow money and disappear,
he'd want to find you, desperately.
He'd go mad.
And?
Stop calling him.
Don't make advances.
Okay. I won't.
In a relationship,
if you lose at playing hard to get, it's over.
My sister's not the type of woman you like, right?
She's not pretty.
You're right.
But she can be cute sometimes.
She goes on blind dates,
and they're all unsuccessful.
Who'd like an unattractive, clumsy girl?
She didn't seem clumsy, though.
You haven't eaten?
Nobody made me anything.
Are you seeing someone?
No! I was just getting ideas for my novel.
From a 4th grader?
You should've gotten more experience.
I agree.
Come again!
What is it?
How does your expression change like that?
Come again!
What is it?
Try giving me an allowance!
I'd smile at you a hundred times.
- Since we're on the subject...
- Forget it.
You didn't hear what I have to say.
There's no need.
I don't have any. You know I'm having trouble paying my credit card bills.
Hey, Dal, Dal!
Hey, Dal... Dal...
Oh, man...
I'm going nuts!
Huh? That's my shirt.
Hey, why are you wearing my shirt?
It's not! It's mine!
That's mine.
My mom threw that out.
See here?
I made that scribble.
No! I did this!
You must be poor.
You don't even have your own room, right?
That's not true.
We're moving soon.
Liar.
It's true!
You're lying. You're a beggar!
We must send these out soon.
- Please hurry up.
- Okay.
Please check and count each size.
Okay.
Yes, mom. What is it?
I was wondering about what I asked you.
I'll stop by on my way home.
You will?
Oh, is there anything you want to eat?
I'll cook it for you.
Okay.
[Ms. Wang Hobak]
Your father can't sleep these days.
Help your sister out.
Welcome.
Please close out all my savings accounts.
All of them?
You only have a few months left.
You'll lose a bit of interest.
Is it okay?
That's too bad.
I need the money.
Okay.
Oh, Ms. Lee.
Hello.
What?
Bangtong did what?
Oh, no!
I'm so sorry, Ms. Lee.
I'll talk to him and teach him a lesson.
Why? Why did you hit your friend?
He was acting up!
That's not an excuse!
Didn't I tell you to be nice to your friends?
A mean boy like him deserves it.
How dare you!
Roll up your pants!
Hit me! Go ahead!
I still won't regret what I did!
What?
How dare you talk to me like that?
I hate you, mom!
You're mean!
Mom, don't hit Bangtong.
He deserves it!
You! You come here!
He had a good reason.
That boy called him a beggar,
saying he was wearing his old clothes.
What?
When he said we were moving to an apartment,
he called him a liar.
Saying a beggar couldn't move to a new place.
I was going to beat him up tomorrow.
So don't hit Bangtong, mom.
Bangtong, come here.
Mommy!
I'm sorry.
I won't hit you.
It's all my fault.
Why don't you quit your job?
Don't ask me to raise your kids!
Why should I?
When your mother in law won't?
I had to raise all of you and raise your uncle.
So how can you ask me to raise your kids?
It's like asking a man to enlist for military service twice!
Don't you agree?
It'd be a different story if you paid me.
But you won't so I can't do it.
How pretty!
She looks just like you.
Because I love you so much,
I love your baby, too.
Oh, precious thing.
Mom, you'll raise her, won't you?
Of course, I will.
You're just a girl, so you couldn't.
Mom, you're the best.
But don't forget to pay me for that.
Your husband makes a lot of money.
I didn't feel this with my own children,
but she's just precious!
I think it's because she looks like you.
- Grandmother, it's me.
- Hello.
You're here often.
You didn't bring anything again?
I'm sorry, grandmother.
I won't come empty handed again.
I don't believe you.
It'd be too later after I die.
Do it while I'm still breathing.
She has no money!
She makes must enough to feed her kids!
Oh, my daughter, you must be tired.
You could've come tomorrow.
What's gotten into her?
Huh?
Is she on drugs?
I haven't seen her take anything.
Did you eat?
I made some miso soup. Want some?
No, I've already eaten.
Mom.
Yes?
I gave a lot of thought to what you said.
But I'm sorry, mom.
I don't think I can.
You can't?
No.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Are you afraid I won't pay you back?
It's not that.
You shouldn't be like this.
Your sister's dying!
How can you be so heartless?
If you can't trust me, sign her apartment contract in your name.
Listen to me.
There's no need.
You said no.
Have I ever asked you for help?
It's only a loan.
I'm not asking you to just give it.
And to be frank, you shouldn't be that way.
Subak's been so kind to you!
She pretended to give you work so she could pay you and gave you bags and clothes.
How can you be so ungrateful?
Even strangers would want to pay her back.
You're so greedy and selfish.
Go home.
- Mom.
- I said go home.
You've been to my place.
That's how I live.
I live in a shabby place,
trying to save every penny.
I didn't tell you to live that way!
You can't blame anyone for that!
You don't spend the money you make.
You're right.
I haven't been spending the money I made,
so I can provide a better life for my kids.
So their friends won't call them beggars.
What are you talking about?
Subak's had a good life until now.
I want to live in my own place where my kids have their own rooms.
I deserve that.
I've worked really hard for 15 years.
rain or snow, even if I was sick,
even if my kids were burning up,
I never missed a day of work.
I cried every morning when I went to work,
leaving my little kids behind with someone else.
It's not like you worked to make me money!
I got married with no money.
I saved every penny I could and I made them wear clothes people throw out.
And frankly,
I saved up, getting yelled at for not buying you any gifts and working at Subak's house.
I can't use this money on anyone else.
I'm going to use it on my kids.
Go ahead! Who's holding you back?
People would think I'm trying to steal it.
If I asked to borrow it for myself,
you'd have gone mad.
So mom, don't hate me.
And don't be disappointed, either.
I'm your daughter, too.
My daughter my butt.
How can you do this to your own mom?
I can't stand you, so leave!
I'm sorry, mom.
Father.
What's going on?
I said what's going on?
It's none of your business.
Did you ask Hobak for money?
You said you found a way,
and that was robbing her savings?
You heard her.
She won't be robbed.
What's wrong with helping her sister out?
I can't believe how heartless she is.
You're the one who's heartless.
Do you even know Hobak?
I'm asking if you know your own daughter.
Oh, man!
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
You favored Subak since they were young.
Who favored whom?
You did.
That's because Subak was good to me.
She helped us out whenever she could,
she gives us allowance,
and look.
Subak bought us this fridge.
She bought us the TV and the washing machine.
What did Hobak do for us?
She's never even bought us underwear!
Where are you going?
I'm still angry!
I'm going to buy some underwear!
I'm sick and tired of you and the underwear.
What? You don't have any underwear?
I'll buy you a box full of them.
You can put on two or three pairs at once!
I only say that because I'm upset.
People are all the same.
It's natural for you to love the child who treats you better.
Other moms told me that not all children are the same.
What kind of parents are they?
You should learn to control your emotions.
How can you favor one child over another?
Don't you know that it will all come back to bite you later?
No, I don't.
Well, now you know.
Why do you think I put that up there?
Look. Put yourself in other's shoes.
If you do that, you'll find the answer,
but you never do that!
Look at it whenever you pass by it.
I will, I promise so...
Let's tell Subak to move in with us.
What?
We already have a kangaroo,
and now you want a salmon?
She's physically able and capable!
No way!
We have a kangaroo?
He says we do.
Me.
Why are you a kangaroo?
You're human.
I know.
Mom came to see me at work.
Asking me to lend Subak money.
She's never been there, but she found it.
She even came over to my place with snacks for the boys.
Her smile was so warm.
I don't think I have seen that before.
She held my hand asking,
"Did you eat?"
"Are you hungry?"
"Would you like some meat?"
"My treat."
"My daughter's working so hard."
It's the first time she's ever said such things to me.
She called me "my daughter" for the first time when she asked me for money for Subak.
She's acting like it's her money,
and I thought how could she do this to me?
When I told her I couldn't because I want to let my boys have their own rooms,
her expression changed...
Hobak...
Mom doesn't love me.
I don't know why I feel this way.
I'm married and have two kids of my own,
but I still want mom's love.
I must be immature.
Wanting your parents love is natural.
You're quite amazing.
Why?
If I were you,
I wouldn't even have gone over.
And I'd be jealous of Subak.
Don't you hate mom?
I do.
I don't know why she had me.
You're going to heaven.
I must smell like money.
Everyone's asking me to lend them money.
Who else asked you?
My mother in law.
She treated me to pork belly and asked.
I'm scared of people who want to take me out.
There are some at work, too.
How can they ask me for a loan so easily?
It becomes a habit.
It gets easier, I guess.
You do look kind of loaded.
When you get dressed up, you look like a former announcer with a rich husband.
Announcer? No way.
Your dream was to become an announcer.
It was.
I was going to apply after graduating.
But you had to drop out of college because of Subak.
Still, you're amazing.
You're a manager.
Right.
Men aren't attracted to women who look loaded.
You have to look cheap to attract men.
Hobak.
Hmm?
Would you like me to buy you some meat?
Hey!
Oh, man!
What is it?
- Let's go somewhere else.
- Why?
You're home late.
Studying must be hard.
Studying isn't hard.
You can't be one of us.
Hello?
Am I calling too late?
It is late.
I'm sorry. Were you in bed?
No, I was working out.
In the middle of the night?
You're amazing.
You must have been busy these days.
Well, the magazine...
The magazine?
You told me to forget it. Is it out?
No, no. It's not out yet.
I'll bring you a copy when it comes out.
There's no need.
I'll buy one when it comes out. Bye.
Hello?
If you run wild, you lose.
Don't call him.
I lost.
Gwangbak's so funny.
She said it was about her friend.
She's just embarrassed.
Miho, you've been very busy.
You have to check on Daebak's studies and give advice to your sister in law.
I need to earn points.
Miho!
It's uncle. Uncle!
Aunt.
You must be tired.
Would you like some juice?
I'll drink water.
Did she call?
I think she knows I'm looking for her.
If she has a conscience, she couldn't face you.
She wouldn't dare.
I wonder if she's okay.
Are you worried about her?
Don't you hate her for what she did to you?
Of course I do.
But compared to you, it's nothing.
She's your mother.
What's going on here?
What do you mean?
You're whispering to each other.
Are you conspiring to sell me off?
We were going to,
but nobody wants to buy such an antique!
You! You little!
Oh, I don't believe him.
How am I an "antique"?
Don't you agree?
Don't expect me to answer that.
It's too difficult.
Oh, father!
Father!
You're pushing yourself too hard.
I have to be healthy.
I have three unwed children and a brother.
Stand aside.
One, two,
three, four,
five.
Make me some vegetable juice.
I'm doing to drink it every morning.
What's wrong?
He never drank that before.
Make him some.
Mom, where are the vegetables?
Are you having an affair?
Why are you checking out your bald head?
Choose your words carefully.
I'm not bald.
My hair is thinning.
What are all the doctors doing?
If someone invents something that makes your hair grow, he'll become rich.
Who cares if you can go to Mars or the moon?
They can't make hair grow back.
Did someone complain about your bald head?
I was going to have Subak take care of Daebak, but now I can't.
So I'll have to live longer.
I wonder if she's eating okay.
I'm sure she is.
Right, mom.
Don't worry about Subak.
Daebak, you know how things are here, right?
What do you mean by that?
Don't get into any trouble.
My bat's been begging to be used again.
Lots of people deserve the bat now.
Just say it's me.
Why? Did you do something wrong?
Mother.
You got your report card?
Oh, good job.
If you keep this up, you'll be set.
We need a judge or a prosecutor.
There isn't much time left, so work hard.
You're the only one I can depend on.
I know how it feels to be praised.
Like hell you do!
You quit your teaching job and became a kangaroo.
It's because I'm having a bad year.
I can't believe my eyes.
She's number 1 in the entire school!
My relatives are all smart.
Don't even try!
Haebak takes after Bong, and Daebak...
Daebak's stupid because he takes after me?
Yes. That's it.
Incredible.
Where's your report card?
It's not out yet.
Not yet?
How did you do?
I did as I normally would.
I did pretty well, so don't worry.
You did well?
How did you do?
I don't want to get into...
Tell me Korean, English and math scores.
30 on Korean.
30? Out of 100?
There's one who did worse than me.
I did much better on the others.
What did you get?
I'm good in English, so I got 40.
As for math...
Can I get a new math teacher?
He's too hard.
Don't try to avoid it.
25.
Ugh!
You said you did well!
I'm sure my ranking went up.
They all said they did worse than me.
It's because you asked the idiots!
How many scored below you?
One in my class, and ten in the whole school.
Don't make father worry!
Leave him alone.
I'm proud of him for not dropping out.
You shouldn't be proud.
What did you do?
Why didn't you tutor him?
I don't want to hear that he takes after me!
I'm not a child!
Don't baby me.
I can take care of myself.
I'm going to school.
Okay.
I'm going to school and coming home late.
Why?
I'm going to the karaoke place.
A bad student like you shouldn't go singing!
Come home early and study.
I have to.
Remember my friend Yongpal?
Yongpal?
How can you hang out with such...
Don't make fun of his name.
He's number 1 in school.
You're friends with the number 1 kid?
They're best friends.
He was crying his eyes out because he got 2 questions wrong, so I have to console him.
The worst student in school is going to console the best student in school?
Because we're friends.
You didn't learn anything from seeing him cry?
I did.
You did? What did you learn?
He's so funny.
Why would he cry over that?
How can he survive in the harsh world?
That's what I learned.
I'll see you later.
Let's not talk about grades when we're eating.
How about sex, then?
I was just making a joke. Let's eat.
Really?
Thank you executive manager.
I don't know how to thank you.
I'll tell him to take you out when he gets his first paycheck.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Hello? We're Angels. Please stop by.
- Hello?
- We're Angels. Hello.
- It's great.
Hello, we're Angels.
Yes, thank you.
I'm going nuts.
Loser,
I heard something important yesterday.
When a man's rich, he's unhappy.
That can't be.
Right?
I wish I were rich, even if I'm unhappy.
I know.
I'm MUWG and you're MUSG.
Is that for food?
It sounds delicious.
I'm Mr. Unemployed whose Wife Gave up on.
You're Mr. Unemployed whose Sister in law Gave up on.
Loser, when can we become employed?
What kind of work do you want to do?
That's simple.
Free work hours,
easy work and a big salary.
Me too.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Goof-off, how are we going to finish handing these out?
Goof-off? Don't call me that.
Why do you call me Loser, then?
Because you're a loser.
Follow me.
Okay, okay. Get in line.
Me! Me!
Quiet down!
Get in line.
If you're nice, I'll give you two.
- Here.
- Yes, here.
- Thank you.
Give it to your dad.
Not your mom.
That's right!
Come, come.
- Get in line.
- Here.
And two for you. Yes.
Give it to your dad.
Don't give it to your mom. You can't.
Hey! Stop right there! Stop!
Stop right there! You!
Walk faster!
Oh, I don't want to.
You don't want to? Why not?
Handing out fliers doesn't pay!
I hate that manager.
But that job's perfect for you.
You just need to stand there in a suit.
There's even a pool at that hotel.
You can watch women in bikinis all day.
Follow me!
Heo Goof-off!
I'm coming!
I'm going nuts.
- Come.
- Okay, okay.
Walk faster.
I don't want to.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Oh, man!
- Go, go, go! Hurry up!
- Oh, man!
Go for it! Good luck.
Oh, man!
How amazing!
Oh, nice!
Oh, no!
I'm just so happy to see you.
You must be well connected to have come back.
I didn't want to because of you.
I happen to be your boss.
So please show some respect.
I hope we can work well together.
Oh, that little... That little...
I'm having lunch with some clients.
Okay, father.
Then I'll eat with the others.
We'll go out for some pork ribs.
Okay.
Huh? Oh, oh!
I spotted the rude girl! Bye!
Hey!
Hey! You!
Hey, hey!
Oh, that rude little...
I'll meet you there.
- Okay. Hurry up.
- I will.
Let's go.
What's up?
I have to have lunch.
I'm a worker, so...
I know.
You must eat on schedule.
Were you playing with me?
Excuse me?
Why wouldn't you reply to my text messages?
You left me hanging.
You ignored my text message about Daebak.
We weren't seeing each other,
but Daebak introduced us,
well, I guess he didn't introduce us.
Anyway.
Why are you acting this way?
You made me very upset.
Is this how you handle people?
You're a total player!
Don't you have anything to say?
Say something!
Give me an excuse, at least.
I guess I misunderstood.
And there I was trying to do something nice.
But it wasn't because I was interested in you!
I thought you shouldn't act like this,
so I came here to impart wisdom about life.
But it seems like there was no need.
Goodbye.
You're the total player!
I was honest with you and you made a fool of me!
What do you mean?
Made a fool of you? How?
The magazine.
The magazine?
- You read it?
- Yes.
I read how you turned me into a total bastard,
ruined me, and tore me to pieces!
Subtitles by KBS World
I trusted you, but you fooled me twice.
Go to hell.
I'm going to hell.
You go to heaven and I'll go to hell.
Did you buy a house?
You're buying a house?
No, not yet.
How am I?
How am I as a woman?
I think you're not so bad.
Do you have a girlfriend?
My wife's so scary that I wouldn't dream of it.
I can't handle being ruined like this.
What do you want me to do?
Let's stay in Seoul.