Subtitles by KBS
Episode 26
Who's she?
Hello, madam.
I'm the caregiver.
You're the caregiver?
Yes.
I'd better get going.
She looks like a good caregiver.
Her husband must be unemployed.
She's not flirting with you, is she?
You're a pretty handsome man.
At least you used to be.
Nonsense.
What are you doing here?
It's for the caregiver.
I kept my promise.
Not everyone can take care of sick people.
Trying to pay for a caregiver is just as hard.
I should go.
You're not going to say hello to father?
Oh, when did you get home?
Just now.
I must be making things hard for you.
No, you're not.
I always eat out.
It's Miho who has it hard.
Anyway, where do you go every day?
I'll tell you later.
You're glowing.
Are you seeing someone?
If I were, I'd tell you.
Sangnam should be fine, right?
Since he's not home yet, he must be.
I hope she's a nice girl.
Someone you and Sangnam will like.
I hope she is.
- How did it go?
- I'm home.
Did you like her?
Here, here. Sit down, sit down.
Come over here.
Yes.
She knows about me, but she doesn't care.
About my family and education.
Of course she doesn't.
Her father was a teacher, too.
And she's a college graduate.
Are you going to see her again?
Yes.
Good. What did you talk about?
We didn't talk much. We just met.
What did you do then?
It's pretty late.
Were you just staring at her?
Yes.
You must be hungry.
I'll get you something.
It's okay, aunt.
I ate lunch late so I'm not hungry.
I'm going to go up to my room.
What is it?
I'm curious.
About what? I told you everything.
Did you like her?
She's someone I could marry.
But you're not attracted to her?
It's hard to meet people like that.
But that's what you look for in a woman.
Tell father I'll do what he wants.
Aunt, I want to go to bed.
I'm tired because I was nervous.
What is it?
Nothing. Take a shower first.
It's here, right here.
It's from over there to over there.
This whole area will be developed with a country club and a resort.
A resort and a country club?
Yes, with a 36 hole golf course and a resort at the center.
Sunjeong, I'll be right there.
Don't worry. Take your time.
And drive carefully.
Okay. Thanks.
Why is Aeji sleeping here?
Subak's not home yet?
She's sleeping because she's tired.
No matter how tired she is,
she should sleep with her child.
Leave her alone. Don't wake her up.
She's going somewhere early tomorrow.
Is her job going okay?
I think so.
She's been giving me money.
How much?
She'll give me more after her first paycheck.
She gave Minjung money to hire a caregiver,
so it must be going well.
Subak looks happier since she started working.
She's less mean to Minjung.
Right. Everyone should work.
Put him down.
He starts crying when I do.
Why don't you bark for him?
But it makes him cry.
Gwangbak's not home yet?
She goes out every day to write,
but who knows where she goes?
I don't think she's been writing.
And she hurt her arm somewhere.
I was frustrated so I said something,
and she started yelling out of the blue.
Oh, it was crazy.
She must be miserable.
Don't push her. Just leave her be.
That's all you say, just leave them be.
When she quit her job,
we should've made her go back!
When I think about that, I get mad at you.
You're mad at everyone in the family.
Go to sleep, go to sleep.
Go to sleep, go to...
Go to sleep, go to sleep...
Hey, honey.
Huh? What is it?
Do you need something?
I don't. You should lie down.
He started crying when I put him down.
You're going to get sick.
What else can I do?
Give him to me.
Go to sleep now...
Father.
Take your medicine.
You can't even sleep because of me.
I'm sorry I caught a cold.
Oh...
Oh, you're home?
Yes, I need to change before going to work.
You're going exercising?
Yes.
How is your father?
He caught a cold.
Oh, no.
I feel badly about your father,
but I'm worried about you.
You're not getting any sleep.
I'm okay. I'll see you later.
Okay.
Oh, father.
Yes?
It's not an appropriate topic for now,
but about Gwangbak,
she's really miserable.
Love sickness...
I met the guy,
and you may not be happy with him,
but he is a great guy.
Father,
can you reconsider him?
Gwangbak's not eating or sleeping.
She's like a walking corpse.
He's a great guy.
Why did you bring it up?
Mother.
When did you get home?
Just now.
Subak didn't come home last night?
She did. But she went to work.
Already?
You talked to her on the phone last night.
She had to go to the countryside early.
But there was no trace of her.
How do you know that?
People leave traces when they come home?
What are you doing home at this hour?
You're coming home now?
Huh?
Yes, I had to go outside of Seoul.
Do you know what time it is?
It's morning now.
How could you come home now?
Who cares if it's morning?
I had to go somewhere with investors.
But this, this can't happen.
Your mother said you went to work early,
but you're coming home now.
Unless you're hiding something, why lie?
Mom made a mistake.
I'm exhausted.
Why are you bugging me?
You think I'm cheating on you?
What?
Think about it.
I had to work all night, but you're mad.
I can't believe you're doing this to me.
I'm making money, too.
I'm making money you can't, okay?
Unbelievable.
Did you tell him I came home?
What's wrong with you?
What do yo want to say?
You think Subak is cheating on you?
It's not that.
Then what is it?
She goes all over the country, looking for real estate properties.
If I were you, I'd worship her.
She's making money to pay for babysitting and for your father's caregiver.
Didn't you get money from her?
I did, $200.
She works her butt off all day,
and you interrogate her like this?
You came home late when you ran a company.
You know how it is in business.
I didn't want to worry you, so I lied,
and you can't understand that?
You're not making enough money,
and you're making your wife work,
so why are you being so difficult?
You should be grateful instead.
Put yourself in her shoes.
When you're out working your butt off,
would you like to hear your wife nagging?
When you ran a company,
you often didn't come home.
I always came home.
Coming home after midnight doesn't count.
That's like coming home the next day.
Right.
You're coming today, right?
Of course.
I'm going to be there for your presentation.
And dad? I'd like him to come, too.
He's away on business.
I'll be watching for two people.
That's okay, right?
Oh, I'm bored.
Why? Should I entertain you?
Shopping is boring.
Let's play golf.
It's too cold.
Golf is no fun either.
But it's starting to get fun for me.
I even play it in my sleep.
Good shot!
It's suffocating.
I want to travel around the world.
Travel around the world?
The whole world?
Not just a few countries?
Go sailing on a yacht and go on a cruise.
And fly on a private jet.
This is nuts.
Let's go. Why not?
It could take several months.
Several months?
You can't go.
Have you played golf by the sea?
Me? By the sea?
It's nuts.
Bring them to my room.
Okay.
Today?
I thought it was next week.
Director, I have an important engagement.
Okay.
Anna, I have to attend an exhibition.
- Right now?
- Yes.
Sign it.
What?
Open it.
Sign it.
I'm begging you.
Let me breathe, okay?
You're suffocating me.
Why are you so stubborn?
You're older!
I hate older women.
It's exciting to be with younger women.
You have no idea.
Whenever I hear "oppa," it drives me crazy.
I can't travel the world because of you!
It's different from those package tours or going backpacking.
Sailing across the Atlantic Ocean and hitting a gold ball into the ocean!
It's totally nuts...
Where are you staying?
You don't need to know.
Sintong's giving a presentation at school.
You should go and watch him.
He's not a politician.
Parents shouldn't run to school whenever their children are doing something.
Anna, I'll see you later.
See you later, manager.
Hey! You have to sign this!
You... What are you doing?
- Please throw this out.
- I will.
Hey!
Ugh...
Man...
Hello, I want to be a magician
because I can make people happy
by doing magic for them.
I think about that when I learn magic tricks and I feel happy.
This was voted the best item of the season,
and we think we should name it "Hug."
Hug?
Yes, it shows the strength of the jacket
and adds stylish and trendy feelings to it.
And by using it as the ad concept, it will increase the sales.
Mice like dark places and run when they see people.
But the mouse robot I made...
likes people and gets along with them.
You don't have to do a thing
I'll do it all for you
Is it reality or no? Is it truth or no...
What is it?
So?
Okay.
We'll talk again with a lawyer.
Is it reality or no? Is it truth or no...
Don't hesitate
That's boring.
Oppa,
good job.
That's the end of the exhibition.
Sintong!
I'm so sorry.
Sintong, I'm really sorry.
It's all my fault.
Oh, please forgive me.
I was extremely busy.
There was an emergency meeting.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Should I quit my job?
You're not going to look at me?
I'm begging you, please forgive me.
Sintong!
Ugh. You won't even talk. I should go.
Bye.
Other moms all came.
Even their dads came.
I was the only one without a mom and a dad.
I waited, but you never came.
And I did a good job today.
They all clapped for me.
Here.
Pizza!
Pizza! Pizza! It's pizza!
What's going on? Miss Scrooge.
Not in front of the boys.
They know their mom is a Scrooge.
- You know, right?
- Yes.
Enjoy. Don't pay for it. It's my treat.
No! I didn't come here for that. Just kidding.
Thanks, uncle. Join us.
I have to deliver this.
Sintong, I'm really proud of you.
You gave a presentation without me or dad.
I'm really sorry.
This won't ever happen again.
Promise.
Be a man.
Oh, my darling son!
What about me?
Bangtong, you're my darling son, too.
It would have been nice if dad came at least.
Dad went on a business trip.
Let's eat.
Here.
Where did my side dishes go?
I threw them out.
Ms. Eun hates anything that smells.
Why didn't you ask me first?
Those were for me.
This is nuts.
Let's eat!
It looks delicious.
I'm going to eat first!
If dad doesn't come back,
could just the three of us live together?
Why wouldn't dad come back?
His business trip might take longer.
Why would it take longer?
This is a maybe.
If dad comes back a year later,
we could live without him for a while.
No, no.
Our family is dad, you, Sintong and me.
The four of us!
Tell dad to hurry back, okay?
Sintong, how about you?
If you're happy, I'm okay.
You don't miss dad?
I don't think dad's our family.
Since he got the "oppa" text messages.
My friend's parents divorced, too.
Father.
Yes.
Welcome.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Baek Jihwa.
What would you like?
The side dishes are really good.
My aunt is a great cook.
I should learn from you.
There isn't much to learn.
If your parents are okay with it,
I'd like to meet them this weekend.
My parents said yes.
You're really going to marry Sangnam?
Yes.
She's just upset about him getting married.
She thinks she's losing him.
She's my rival, then.
If the wedding's going to happen this year,
you'll be really busy.
Sangnam, show her your room.
Later.
Hey!
Did you drink?
Man...
Drink this. It'll help you sober up.
I drank to get drunk.
Drink this, girl!
Or you'll ruin your stomach.
You're driving me crazy!
Why would you go drinking so late?
Where did you drink?
At a club.
A club?
Don't go dancing there. You look cheap.
Are you kidding me?
It's none of your business.
I'm your brother's friend.
I'm your niece's friend, Gwangbak's uncle.
Come with me.
I can't sleep even with medicine.
You're in a hard place, too, right?
I'm trying to forget,
but it's not working.
I'm dying for him to call.
Like Subak said, if I get plastic surgery
and stay home with my face all swollen,
will I forget everything?
How about exercising?
When you work out, you forget.
I forget when I'm working.
And I can't exercise like this.
You lost a lot of weight, Gwangbak.
So sad...
He is so cruel.
He didn't even drunk dial me.
How could he not call once?
Others do it all the time after breaking up,
but he's so cold.
He thinks he's the one who got dumped.
Love is so...
It doesn't feed you,
it doesn't buy you a house.
I thought
only rich people fall in love.
I thought it's something
that's nice
but could live without.
But why do we always learn
the importance of something after losing it?
I should've been nicer to him
so he wouldn't fall for anyone else.
What's the use of driving myself mad every night after everything is done?
I didn't know it then.
I thought he'd be there forever.
Eating kimchi stew from one pot
with everyone in the family,
laughing at the boys doing funny dance moves.
I didn't know I was happy back then.
Him being there was enough for me.
Even if he didn't do anything,
just having him around was comfort enough.
I learned that after he left.
Hobak...
Sedal will come back.
You have kids.
I don't want him to come back for that.
I won't be happy if he came back just because of our kids.
But I envy you.
You can at least see him.
I can't
see him, even if I wanted to.
You have the kids,
but we have nothing to connect us.
He doesn't even miss me,
while I'm going crazy here.
What is it?
[Sedal. Divorce! Divorce! Divorce!]
This is what he sent you?
He sends me that all day long.
What are you going to do?
Yes, Minsuk.
Thank you.
There's nothing to do because of Sunjeong.
She even shampooed father's hair yesterday.
He was so happy.
He thinks Sunjeong is a real caregiver.
Don't tell him anything.
If he finds out, he'll be upset.
I know.
Father went down for an exam.
I'll be with him today, so take your time.
Okay, thanks.
Hey, ugly girl, where are you going?
Who wants to know? Ugly man!
Get in before I change my mind.
Hey! Get in.
I don't get into the car with just any man.
I don't ask just any woman into my truck.
You went to the market?
Yes.
I'll take you home. I'm going that way.
Can I tag along with you today?
You want to?
I smell roasted sweet potatoes.
You have a sharp nose.
Miho loves roasted sweet potatoes.
Me too.
Right.
You do, too.
It's hot. Be careful.
Mmm... It's good.
You used to peel them for me before.
That night, your wife didn't say anything?
She said we looked good together.
She did?
I was worried that she might have felt something
and put you in a difficult situation.
She's not that interested in me.
Parcel service.
Yes, I'm on my way.
I'll be there in 30 minutes.
Minjung, let me help.
Where does this one go?
Number 404.
Parcel service.
Yes!
Is Mr. Kim Dohun here?
Huh? You're new?
No.
I'm just helping him today.
Oh, you're his wife!
Excuse me?
Yes.
Daebak,
I'm sorry.
About what?
Sangnam's getting married.
He is?
The woman came to the house.
Their parents are going to meet.
Don't tell my sister that.
I can't even bring myself to face her.
How could this happen to them?
Wang Daebak.
It's been a long time.
You won't shake my hand?
Are you mad?
You're you, and Gwangbak's Gwangbak.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
Daebak, I'll be waiting,
so come see me anytime.
When you get over this.
You could still see me.
I met you before meeting your sister.
Congratulations on your wedding.
So that's what love is?
If love is that easy,
I'm never going to fall in love.
[You are my sucker]
[File the number under spam?]
[Save]
You're coming from the market?
Teach your daughter some manners.
She won't even say hello to me.
Hello.
You go everywhere together, like twins.
Did you attend kindergarten together, too?
We work at the same place. That's why.
It's nice to work with my daughter.
You have lots of daughters. Are you jealous?
If you are, you could go to the cafe down
the street and serve coffee with Gwangbak.
What?
You didn't know?
I forgot to tell you at the funeral,
but everyone's talking about Gwangbak
serving coffee after she quit teaching.
You didn't know that?
How many people in your family work part time now?
Your brother in law, Gwangbak,
even Subak's working part time,
and you're a part time babysitter.
The whole family works part time.
You!
Mom...
When we marry,
I'll be faithful to you.
I can promise you that.
But..
If you catch me staring far away,
don't ask me what's wrong.
Other than that, I'll be faithful to you.
I know what you're talking about.
Everyone has memories.
Did you just propose to me?
I'm not one to make it into a big event.
And I'm not good at giving gifts.
My proposal was really boring,
but I hope you would understand.
It'll be like this after we're married, too.
I'm not the type of person who gets overly excited about special events.
It's the thought that counts.
We're very much alike.
What's wrong with you?
Are you out of your mind?
Tell me, what's wrong?
You quit teaching to become a writer,
so why are you serving coffee there?
Are you on something?
Even Yeongdal looks all glamorous,
running a make up shop with her mom,
and look at you right now!
You want me to have a stroke?
You want me to have a stroke and die?
Will you understand how furious I am then?
Gwangbak!
I don't believe her!
Ugh...
Mom, I'm home.
Can you come in here?
What is it, mom?
I saw something weird today.
Something weird?
Some woman go into Minjung's truck,
carrying a grocery bag.
I saw it on my way to the market.
She must be someone he knows.
She looked pretty young.
Maybe around your age?
She must be a customer.
He could give a ride to his customers.
Just forget it.
I'm not interested.
Even if he's cheating on me, I wouldn't care.
Mom, forget about it.
You'll get wrinkles.
How is this one?
Isn't it pretty?
Yes, yes. I got it.
I'll see you then.
- I'm home.
- Oh!
You're home.
How was it?
What do you mean?
How did you two get along?
Don't ask him too many questions.
You and I are nagging him so much that Sangnam won't ever date again.
He wouldn't have to.
He's getting married.
I talked to her father just now,
and he wants to set the date right away.
She must have said nice things about you.
We don't have a lot of time.
Is it okay with you?
Do whatever you want.
Sangnam.
What is it, aunt?
Are you really okay with this?
What do you mean?
Meeting her parents means you're really getting married soon.
I know.
You'll be walking down the aisle in no time.
Are you sure you won't regret this?
I've made my decision, aunt.
She's a nice person.
She said yes to a man like me.
You shouldn't base your decision on that.
There's nothing wrong with you.
You can't marry someone because of that.
To be honest, I don't have feelings for her.
But she'll be nice to me,
she'll understand my situation,
and she'll be a decent wife.
Aunt, don't worry about me. Get some rest.
I want to go to bed early.
But you don't really love her.
I think you're being pushed into this.
You're in love with someone else.
Aunt,
please leave.
I want to take a shower.
It's me.
Talk to me, Sangnam.
This will probably be
our last phone call.
Let's meet. Let's talk face to face.
There's no need for that.
I miss you.
I miss you so, so much.
Let's talk face to face, okay?
Where are you?
I'll come to you.
We should do this in person, okay?
I don't want to see you.
Not at all.
I told you. I'm a player.
I never date
anyone for more than a month.
You saw me earlier.
I'm seeing another woman,
so stop crying
and get over me.
You're skin and bones.
You should eat well,
sleep well,
don't trip and fall down,
and never look back.
And in the future,
if you run into me,
you should just slap me
and move on.
Goodbye.
Don't do stuff like that.
Go wash your face!
But I'm not going anywhere.
Did you brush your teeth?
I'll brush them after breakfast.
Excuse me,
do you have anything different?
Like what?
Something that brings the appetite back.
You can't have kimchi.
I'm not saying it has to be kimchi,
but I've been having indigestion lately.
Yes.
I'm having breakfast right now.
Today?
Okay.
I'm going out today. I'll be back late.
Sedal.
Where are you right now?
Don't ask me where I am.
I wish I could fart as much as I want.
What? Someone told you not to fart?
Something like that.
Mom, do you have kimchi?
Everyone has kimchi.
I would love to have some
kimchi and pork stew
with a bowl of rice.
Mom, can you come here?
What are you doing with that kimchi?
It's none of your business.
I'm sorry.
Ugh...
Oh, darn it!
Hello? Hey!
Thief! Robber! Robber!
Who was that? He's a robber?
No, he owes me money.
Friend!
Hello. You went to the bathhouse?
Yes.
Oh, he was filthy,
so I dragged him to the public bathhouse.
Where are you going?
There's somewhere we have to be.
Why, you're all grown up!
How come you don't come and visit anymore?
Both Gwangbak and Yeongdal are busy.
You're not getting married?
Mom, we should go.
Oh, okay. I'll see you again.
- Okay.
- Goodbye.
What do you think about her?
What do you mean?
Oh, you're so dense!
You shouldn't even have to ask.
How is Yeongdal as your wife?
She was all smiling with her eyes.
Men must fall for her all the time.
She looks like she can have lots of kids,
and she looks like she could nurse an army!
That's how a wife should look, understand?
I don't.
Why you little...
Dream on! She likes rich men.
But do you like her?
What I think isn't important.
She only wants someone rich.
Like how I like rich women.
So we're like two parallel lines, mom.
Parallel lines?
Like railroad tracks.
They never meet together.
Why you little...
Loser hooked up with Hobak,
so why couldn't you hook up with his sister?
You're so dense!
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo...
Oh...
You got a package.
Take a day off. You'll die this way.
I'm getting married.
Sunjeong.
Sangnam!
How do I look?
I don't even have to ask, right?
Right.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Sangnam.
This is wrong. And you know it.
This isn't how you marry someone.
Living with another woman in your heart is hell.
Sangnam, let's cancel this.
She likes me and that's enough.
But you should like her, too.
You don't smile at all.
I haven't seen you smile at all lately.
You didn't smile once when she came here.
You used to smile even when you were alone.
When you were dating Gwangbak,
you laughed all the time.
You even whistled.
You were like this crazy man.
That's how it should be.
That's how love is.
Aunt.
It's over between us.
So don't talk about her.
Aunt.
Aunt!
What's wrong? Sunjeong!
Hello.
Let me ask you one thing.
What's going on with you and Sangnam?
We broke up.
For good?
Yes.
He sent me his ring back.
Sangnam met a woman.
I know.
We're meeting her parents today.
And we're going to set the date.
And it will be over for you two.
Is that really okay?
I think you two are still in love,
and you don't want to break up.
Am I wrong?
Tell him I wish him happiness.
And thank you for coming to see me.
Subtitles by KBS World