Subtitles by KBS World
This is so unfair! Unfair!
Sintong, Bangtong, get him back for me.
What good will your learning taekwondo do
if your dad is getting beaten up like this?
What are you blabbering about?
You don't need to know.
Let me see.
Stay still, please!
I didn't even touch it, crybaby!
Ice will make the swelling go down.
You should've been more careful.
You fell down because you were careless.
You look like you got beat up.
I didn't get beaten up!
You cause more trouble than the kids!
Massage it with this.
Where did you fall down?
Don't ask too many questions.
It's making me hungry.
It hurts to answer.
How will you go to work looking like that?
I already called to say I couldn't come.
And? What did he say? He said okay?
Of course.
I go to work and come home whenever I want.
Oh, don't be like that.
You're being too cocky because he likes you.
You should be good to him.
I shouldn't be too good.
I should try to keep things exciting.
Exciting? You're not dating!
- That hurts!
- Ugh!
That hurts! That really hurts! I'm not kidding!
I took care of it.
So you just focus on yourself.
You're a good boy.
You were worried about Hobak, weren't you?
Yes.
You're an interesting kid.
I think you're like me.
Oh gosh!
I'd like you to take that back.
I think he learned his lesson.
I'm going to keep tabs on him, too.
Do you even know what that means?
How can you even ask?
It means to mark where he goes with tabs.
That's not completely wrong.
Don't tell Hobak, though.
I know. Ignorance is bliss.
I don't have time. I'm busy.
But I have something to tell you.
I'll see you some other time. I'll call you.
Hey, hey! Sedal!
Bye.
Man...
Hello?
Sedal? It's me.
Since you bought me drinks the other night,
I want to buy you dinner.
Let's meet tonight. My treat.
I'm full.
And it's not like I'm craving for anything.
Come on! I have something to discuss with you.
I'm really busy these days.
I'll call you when I have time.
Hey, Sedal! Sedal!
As if you kept in touch with me before!
I can't believe you.
You never discussed anyone with me before.
You're all on your own, boys.
I know why you want to take me to dinner.
It's called the power of money.
You never answered my calls before,
afraid I'd ask to borrow some money.
This is how the world works.
The amazing power of money!
Welcome. May I help you?
I'm here to see the director.
Oh, which director?
I don't know his name,
but he's pretty young.
There are many directors, so I don't know...
Hon, how are you feeling?
Are you in a lot of pain?
Oh, you should've been more careful.
I can blow on it to make it better.
That tickles. That tickles.
Yes! How is it? Is it better?
She's one of our directors.
It's not her.
I'm looking for a young male director.
I don't know.
I'll need his name.
Okay.
Okay, honey.
Take care of yourself.
And bring me glass noodles next time.
The rice rolls were good, too.
Hello again!
Yup.
- Is anything going on?
- Yeah.
- Are you getting married?
Is "yeah" all you can say to me?
Yeah.
- You think I'm stupid?
- Yeah.
Hey!
Just pretend you don't know me.
You're so annoying!
Why you little!
Hey! I'm your older brother's friend!
Blind date?
You'll never find anyone good. So try it.
No thanks.
He works at a big company.
Who cares about that.
You'll be thirty next year.
Do it while you're still in your twenties.
Men don't like unemployed girls.
So I won't try it.
When I become a famous writer,
I'll be making much more money than them.
Don't see that truck guy!
Yeongdal's getting married.
When?
I didn't ask.
She was glowing.
Who would marry Yeongdal?
She's a gold digger who wants to marry a rich man.
He must be totally crazy.
How dare you call him crazy?
He's not crazy.
What's up?
You're getting married?
Your uncle is a blabbermouth.
How far did you go?
- What?
- How far did you go with him?
I didn't go anywhere with him.
You know what I mean.
Did you sleep with him?
- What?
- I said did you sleep with him?
Did you or didn't you?
THis isn't the 19th century.
Nobody gets married after merely looking at each other's faces.
What do you mean by that?
Quitting your job must have made you slow.
But then again, you've never dated, so...
Gwangbak, when a man and woman decide to get married,
they've already crossed the river.
They've already done everything, stupid.
I'm a player.
Don't fall for someone like me.
I hate it when girls cry and get clingy.
Why did you come after all these years?
There's nothing for you here.
Our mother-son relationship ended long ago.
Don't ever come to me again.
The person you have called is unavailable.
Leave your message at the tone.
Gwangbak, did she do what I said?
Was fishing successful?
Yeah.
So they're dating now, right?
Things are getting more important now.
She must get him drunk.
What if he turns into a dog when he's drunk?
There are some dumb women who ask about
when they can fart in front of their men,
but why is that important?
Farting is embarrassing even when you're alone.
She can never fart in front of him.
And if she feels one coming when she's  with him, she should clap like this.
And fart really softly, and go like this.
Oh, why is it so hot?  Why is it so hot?
And she has to shake it off.
Did she fart in front of him?
No, she didn't.
She didn't even get the chance to do that.
Miho.
I broke up with him.
Gwangbak.
I did everything you said, but he dumped me.
It wasn't my friend. It was me.
Sorry.
I was too embarrassed to tell you.
It's okay. I knew it was about you.
You knew?
Miho, I'm going to try going on a blind date.
I wanted to fall in love.
It was the first time I'd met someone so perfect, but...
He's not attracted to me.
Gwangbak, don't cry.
You're not "not attractive."
Forget all about him.
Your prince will come.
Will he?
Of course.
Gwangbak, don't worry.
I'll teach you more.
Miho.
She did? Is she crazy?
She came to my work and demanded to know if I slept with him.
I can see why.
She's not going to become a writer.
I pity her.
I envied her because she was a good student.
Being a good student means nothing.
You must wait until the end to see how your life turns out.
Right.
Why are you home so early?
Why aren't you out on a date?
He's not answering his phone.
Crush him.
He should tell you where he's going.
Right. I'll crush him when I marry him.
Oh, this is nuts.
Look what he did to my face!
Who?
What do you mean who?
It's your loser uncle.
What about my uncle?
Huh?
It's nothing.
Here.
Give this to your director.
What is it?
Will it look good on him?
Of course it won't.
He doesn't wear anything like this.
I want to show him how grateful I am.
I went to see your director today.
What?
Where did you go?
To the hotel.
Hey! How dare you go there?
So? Did you meet the director?
I didn't meet him.
You shouldn't.
What's the director's name?
Why do you want to know that?
I should've asked for his name.
They have several directors there.
Of course.
It's a big hotel.
You thought there was only one?
What's his name?
It's top secret.
Why would his name be top secret?
Stop worrying about stuff like that and just be a good wife. And make glass noodles.
Glass noodles?
The director wants glass noodles.
Living in the States for so long,
the director misses homemade glass noodles.
Are glass noodles in now?
Oh, right. I saw a woman director there.
What?
She was very stylish.
Can a young woman become a director?
I don't know.
She was talking about glass noodles with someone on the phone.
That was then?
What?
I mean, when you went there,
that woman director passed you by?
Anyway, I'll take care of my job, so you stay out of it!
Before I go nuts.
And you wear this.
Hello? I came right over.
My boss told me to call you because you were so sincere.
We want to use your parcel service.
You do?
Oh...
Thank you.
Ill do a really good job.
You came here every day for a month.
That was impressive.
Thank you so much.
If you need any help, even with cleaning, call me.
We send a lot of fragile things,
so please pay special attention to them.
Of course. I won't disappoint you.
I'll do better than your previous company.
And please tell other offices about me.
I will. I think you're a very hard worker.
Thank you.
Is something up with Sangnam?
Why? He went out on business.
Madam Park called.
Madam Park?
I'm sure I paid my bar tab.
I paid for all the drinks the last time we were there.
It's not about the tab.
I feel like I'm tattle telling.
What is it?
She said Sangnam came alone during the day
and started drinking. He's never done that.
Bastard.
Were you playing with me?
You said I was your destiny!
Have a nice life.
Congratulations on getting engaged.
Sangnam.
Drink some honey tea.
Let's forget about what happened.
You've been fine without your mom all this time.
You should forget about that woman.
I'll be your mom.
I know I won't be enough,
but I'll be your mom.
Sangnam!
Sangnam.
Sangnam, Sangnam!
What's wrong? What happened?
Sunjeong, look at me and tell me everything.
Why is he acting like that?
We met my sister.
- What?
- I thought he should meet her.
Are you crazy?
I told you not to meet her!
I'm sorry, Daese.
We won't meet her again.
We'll never meet her again.
Why didn't you listen to me?
I said I'd kick you out if you let him meet her.
Get out of my house!
I'm not going to live with you anymore.
I want you out of my house before I come home.
You're home?
What are those?
There was a sale at the department store.
You went to the department store?
Isn't this pretty? It was pretty cheap.
I got five for the price of one.
Subak, you know we can't afford this.
I didn't waste the money!
These are for our girls.
You hate spending money on our girls?
It's not that I hate it.
I'd like to buy them everything, if I could.
But we must save every penny right now.
It's not like they have no clothes.
Why did you have to buy five?
They grow up so fast.
I want Aeji to feel confident at her kindergarten.
Especially now that she's a new kid.
Confidence from clothes?
Of course!
If the kids look shabby, the moms get blamed.
I need this so stay out.
You're not even using the expensive stroller.
I've been using it every day.
Hello?
Subak?
It's me.
How are you?
Thanks.
Excuse me?
I got the money you sent.
But don't worry about me.
And don't send me any money again.
I can take care of myself.
I'm getting some money from the government.
I don't have much use for money here.
You should save money and move out.
What is it this time?
Is your father the only person who matters?
You sent $200 to your father,
and you yelled at me for buying Aeji clothes?
How can you send $200 to your father without talking to me first?
How much have you sent behind my back?
Tell me! How much?
This was the first time.
I felt badly about cutting him off,
so I sent him $200 today for the first time.
I can't believe you! I can't believe you!
I'm sorry I didn't talk to you first.
And how can you call him "your father"?
He's not my father.
Don't be like that, Subak.
I know you're angry, but I don't like it when you call him "your father."
If I were doing well, it wouldn't matter,
but now that this happened to me,
I can't seem to be able to handle it.
What's going on?
Why are you screaming again?
He sent money to his father.
What?
How can you do that in your situation?
I know.
He doesn't know how hard it is for me.
I can't help it but get mad.
I was in the Miss Korea pageant.
I used to think shopping channels were
beneath me, but now I shop from them.
I can't get spa treatments anymore,
and my skin is breaking out.
All I can afford is sliced cucumber now.
So how could you send him money?
Are you crazy?
Is sending $200 to my father crazy?
You should take care of your wife and kids first.
Not your father!
Subak, Aeji and Jungji come first.
I can't believe how immature men are.
I know. Does he want to divorce me?
You're living with your father in law,
mother in law and grandmother in law.
I'm sorry.
Just because you're wife's nagging you,
you can't start yelling back at her.
You just need to keep your mouth shut until she runs out of things to say.
Before you moved in, it was peaceful here.
You fought on the night you moved in here.
Don't ever fight again.
Move. That's my seat.
It's not like your name is on the seat.
Did you buy this table?
What?
Huh?
It's you again?
It's like we're mortal enemies.
I should move out of this neighborhood!
What?
You should say hello first!
How dare you call me your enemy?
I'm not in the mood for that.
I'm sorry, but please don't get on my nerves.
Oh, I don't believe this!
You're the one who sent me to the hospital!
The least you can do is say hello!
Where did you learn your manners?
Didn't your parents teach you any manners?
Why do you always pick on me? Why?
Who are you to criticize my parents?
I already wish I was dead.
So please don't pick on me tonight.
Hah! I don't believe you!
Why are you taking it out on me?
Did your boyfriend dump you?
This is why he dumped you!
I bet you can't even get married.
What?
It's none of your business!
Why do you care if I get married?
What's it to you?
I'm right! Your boyfriend dumped you!
Did you see me get dumped? Did you?
I don't have to.
Seeing you drink beer here is proof enough.
Stop taking pictures!
It's obvious to me, too!
You drinking beer here tells me how your family is doing.
Your wife kicked you out, didn't she?
Stop taking pictures!
Turn that off!
You're wrong.
I don't have a wife.
Upsetting, isn't it?
Oh, now I know.
She ran away because you're like this!
You look like a lonely old man.
I feel bad for your children.
What?
What is this ugly girl saying?
Ugly words from an ugly girl.
What?
How dare you call me ugly?
Why did you see a urologist?
What did you do to get injured there?
Oh, it's disgusting.
What? What? Disgusting?
Stop filming me!
What are you doing?
Why you little! How dare you!
You should apologize to each other.
It's not like you had a fist fight.
- No.
Are you going to sue?
Yes, I'm going to sue for defamation.
I'm going to do that, too.
And assault. Verbal abuse is assault.
He picked on me and belittled me.
And include blackmail.
He threatened me to pay for his medical bill.
That wasn't blackmail. That was just!
I had to see my doctor one more week because of you!
You bumped into me here and made me cry,
and I had to walk around like this!
Sit down!
Okay.
Fine. Let's take this all the way.
I have nothing to lose.
Me neither.
Then you two are suing each other.
Let's go to the police station.
Get out.
We're here. So get out.
We don't have time. Hurry up.
Well...
You go first.
Age before beauty. You go first.
I'm okay with this,
but it looks like you're not even married,
and I don't want to see your parents being
dragged into this and getting upset.
And you'll never find a husband.
I'm fine with this,
but it looks like you have a family to take
care of and I can't make you a criminal.
Let's never see each other again.
I know.
Oh, boy.
Miho!
Stop! Stop!
Daese.
I'm going to work.
Why won't you play with us?
He's lost his mind, so how could he?
What are they saying?
They're mad because you don't play with them.
Sintong, you shouldn't get mad.
Don't get mad.
Say goodbye.
Dad, make lots of money.
Money is all you talk about. Ugh.
See you later. And don't fall down.
Mom.
What is it?
Dad got another weird text.
It's spam.
Didn't it say girls and liquor?
Don't spy on dad's phone.
It said "honey."
And it said "kiss, kiss."
That's what they always say.
They call everyone that.
Stop worrying about that and go study.
The same thing happened to my friend's dad.
And his parents got divorced.
Stop talking nonsense and do your homework!
We'll visit grandfather's school when you're done.
Honey, I'm home.
Honey, welcome home.
Dad.
Oh, my baby. Did you have a good day?
Honey, here's your dinner.
Okay.
Have some.
Yum, yum...
Is it good?
It is good, honey.
Then may I have a kiss?
Stop kissing her and come out.
Okay.
Clean the yard.
Take the trash out,
wash the pots over there. Do it together.
Okay.
I wish they'd do it without me asking.
I can't believe I have to ask.
And clean the bathrooms.
Minjung, clean the upstairs bathroom,
and uncle, you take the downstairs one.
- How about you?
- Taking care of my baby.
Uh...
Oh, no!
What's this?
How could you break the soy sauce pot?
I can't believe you did this.
Oh, what do we do about the soy sauce?
I was saving it for special dishes.
Why can't you do anything right?
I'm sorry.
Who did this?
Was it you, Minjung?
How can you be so careless?
How can you deliver parcels the way you are?
If I asked you to clean again,
the house would be in ruins!
Did you clean the bathroom?
Yes.
Don't stand there like an idiot. Take these out.
What's this?
I don't know. Who put this here?
Oh, they're chestnuts.
Oh, boy.
They're wild chestnuts. Yummy.
He sends them every year. Boil some.
Bugs got to them first.
Huh? What's this?
- Chestnusts.
- Did Minjung's father send them?
He should've called first.
He just left them by the door.
He didn't even come in?
He must have heard you yelling at Minjung.
It must have been then.
As if he was spying on how Minjung's doing.
How can he just leave without coming in?
This reminds me of your mother.
Excuse me?
When you married my son, your mother came
to our town and spied on you. Remember?
Too bad.
With your brain, you could've been successful.
Are you teasing me?
I won't answer that.
You can buy chestnuts in Seoul,
so why did he bring them and cause trouble?
I'm sorry my father came here without calling.
Don't eat them.
Why were you eavesdropping?
I listened because I could hear it.
You never appreciated anything my father sent.
He worked hard for these chestnuts.
It's not like I said anything.
Subak.
Minjung, it wasn't like that.
It's not like we made stuff up.
We must be some really honest people.
What are you talking about?
We say what we want to say, no matter what.
She was talking nonsense, that's why.
He should've called first.
How can he just toss it by the door?
Right. My father shouldn't have done that.
I'll tell him never to come again.
Why are you overreacting?
Fine. I'm overreacting.
Minjung, we'll eat them.
They are wild chestnuts and they are good.
Being really honest isn't a good thing.
We should watch what we say.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Forget the painful memories of the past
Like passing wind
You are not alone anymore
You have your beloved, me!
Be still!
For I'll do everything for you!
Is this a dream or reality?
Don't be confused
Didn't know it then
Make me your home
Make me... Home...
Okay! The moment you've been waiting for!
What was that?
What's wron here?
I could do this before.
Women used to line up to hear it pop.
How boring.
I'm bored.
What should we do?
Let's go for a drive. Get the car.
I'll be right out after I change.
Okay.
Oh, my!
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Go.
Hey, Loser.
Fine.
To where?
Hey!
I have to answer it. It's my job.
Oh, man.
The phone is off...
I'm sorry I beat you up that day.
Did you have to apologize here?
If I don't answer quickly, she gets mad.
Fine, fine.
Remember what we used to say when we ran
out of money while playing arcade games?
We used to say we'd sell our souls for money.
That we'd become old women's boy toys.
We survived on $3 a day,
not being able to get a decent job,
working here and there part time,
and being looked down on by our families.
You and I were Goof-off and Loser, the duo, for over 20 years now.
It's been that long?
That sounds too long.
So how could you assault me like that?
Sedal,
I understand you,
no matter what people say.
We were willing to be an old woman's boy toy,
and a hot, rich woman appeared before you.
Of course you fell for her.
Who wouldn't fall for her?
Right?
It's really nuts.
Blood is thicker than water, and money is thicker than blood.
Says who?
Me.
Everyone said this the other night.
That they'd do anything if they can find a rich woman.
These days, both men and women dream of becoming Cinderella.
Women dream of Prince Charming,
and men dream of rich, fat women.
But Goof-off,
you are
just a toy to her.
She's not a rich, fat woman,
so why would she fall for you?
She's fooling around with you out of loneliness after coming back from the States.
Nobody would care if I sold my soul, but not you.
You have a wife and children.
Even if money was thicker than blood,
this isn't right.
Who is it?
Parcel service!
Wow, parcel service!
Please sign here.
My kids love seeing you.
Oh, thank you.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Goodbye. Thank you.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Hello?
These are for delivery.
Thank you.
Come with us.
What's wrong?
You don't know?
There's something called business ethics.
How dare you steal this from me?
Do you know how hard it was to get that job?
I should kill you!
Don't! You don't want to go to prison.
Let go!
Don't ever show your face in our district.
I can't believe you did this.
Why can't you do anything right?
Sorry. Something came up.
Get up.
Huh?
Come on...
Can't you hear me?
Are you angry with me?
Why didn't you answer the phone?
I told you to answer before the third ring.
Actually...
You said you'd do anything I asked.
You broke the contract.
How dare you?
It wasn't like that.
I won't stand for this.
You're fired.
Excuse me?
The car key.
The credit card.
Excuse me?
Don't make me repeat myself. It's no fun.
Get out.
Parcel service.
Parcel service!
It's parcel service!
What was that?
Who delivers parcels this late at night?
I didn't order anything.
Parcel service!
Oh, boy.
It's parcel service!
What's wrong with you?
You all came out.
You all came out to get your parcels.
I don't ever see you when I come home,
but you came out at the sound of "parcel service."
Why are you doing this?
Are you drunk?
If you're drunk, go upstairs to your room.
Yes, I did have a few drinks.
But I'm not drunk.
I feel completely sober.
Let's go up. You're drunk.
I'm not drunk!
Then what's this about?
Be quiet.
Am I really family to you?
Other families love to see me.
Why?
Because I'm the parcel service guy.
Everyone in Korea loves to see me.
Parcel service!
When I say that, even puppies come running.
That's who I am.
But when I come here,
I'm invisible.
Nobody's happy to see me.
When I come home from work,
I want the lights to be on,
I want you to greet me with smiles,
ask me if I'm hungry and get me food,
look into my eyes,
and ask me about my day.
That's the life I want.
I want to be treated with decency.
I came home after a long day of delivery parcels to strangers homes,
and nobody's glad to see me.
I never get to see you.
I go to work alone and come home alone.
Who am I?
Am I not family to you?
Display the new items
where the customers can see,
and please keep the shop tidy.
This is our company's best shop,
so please make sure it's always clean.
I will.
What is it?
Really?
Okay.
Make sure you look good.
I hate ugliness.
Thank you.
Is today a special day?
It's not a special day.
But it's going to be a good day for us.
A good day?
What is it? It's not my birthday.
Not our anniversary, either.
Did you get promoted?
Let's have dinner first.
Scalloped potatoes, caprese salad, and chickpea soup.
Squid ink croutons with seasame sauce caviar mixed with 25 year old balsamic vinegar.
And yellowtail ceviche with bell pepper and onion.
And we'll go with short loin.
Not too rare. Medium well done.
As for dessert, macaron, facquoise and florentine.
Oh, for wine, let's go with a vinage one, nothing too heavy.
You know all that?
Of course.
Oh, my.
Why did you order so much?
I thought your order was a bit long.
Isn't this expensive? How much is it?
Stop talking about money and just eat.
The director gave me a gift certificate.
It's your favorite. It's "free." Okay?
Oh, I should've brought Sintong and Bangtong.
Stop saying stuff like that and let's eat.
Like my mom says, I can't believe my eyes.
I've never had such food before!
You can't believe I'm here, right?
I can't believe my ears.
Can we get a doggy bag for these?
I know you can finish that.
You just might come after my food.
Oh, it just melts in my mouth.
So what's going on?
Let's finish eating first.
Talk to me.
Then you wouldn't be able to eat.
Don't you know me?
Even when there's thunder and lightening,
even when there's a war,
even when the world falls apart, I can eat.
And I've never had anything like this before.
What is it?
Didn't Minjung's father say anything?
He never came inside.
Minjung's father was here?
Why did he have to pack them for us?
It's going to go into the trashcan anyway.
Is that all you can say?
Don't eat it.
Don't eat the food my father gave me.
I won't.
Get married within this year if you can.
Do you understand?
She's meeting someone to get married.
Did you share the rice rolls I made with her?
You give me $3 a day,
but she gave me a $100,000 credit card!
I don't need you, either.
This is beyond nuts!
How much will it take?