Subtitles by KBS World
The magazine?
- You read it?
- Yes.
I read how you turned me into a total bastard,
ruined me, and tore me to pieces!
Hold on, Sangnam.
Hold on! Just listen to me...
There's nothing to listen to.
What's left to say?
- Explanation?
- Excuses, you mean?
No, no, I won't make any excuses.
Please, give me 10, no, 5 minutes.
I'll tell you everything.
I'll confess everything.
I don't want any excuses.
I know how shocking the article was.
But that wasn't what I wrote.
The editor turned it upside down to attract more readers.
It's true women don't like men like that.
Not me, but women who are airheads.
It was so different from what I wrote
that I had a fight with the editor
and got fired from my part time job.
I need to catch my breath...
Stop it.
I know it's my fault.
I should've stopped the printing.
I'm sorry.
But I never meant to hurt you.
Oh, you can come with me to confirm it.
Yes, I think we should.
Come with me.
There's no need.
I'm disappointed in you.
You betrayed me.
I believed you understood who I am.
But I feel like you stole from me.
I feel violated. Understand?
I know how that feels.
But I never ever thought that way.
I never stole from you, never!
And what else?
Oh, violated. I never did.
I'm serious.
Please don't think like that.
Thank you for teaching me.
The world is full of biased people.
You made me see that again.
Goodbye.
Mom, what is it again?
I can't, I'm busy. Bye.
Mom, later.
Hold on!
I have proof.
- Proof?
- Yes.
We can talk after you see it.
I'll email it to you, so take a look at it.
How's that?
See it and decide.
I'll send it right away.
Ugh, it stinks in here!
What's this? Man...
How disgusting.
Incredible.
I told you never to touch my computer!
Oh, sorry. Mine's too slow.
You!
Hey! Hey!
I should just die!
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
You stop right there!
I'm not crazy!
If it caught a virus, you're dead!
Why don't you go get married!
Huh?
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Wang Daebak!
Welcome. How may I help you?
Excuse me, where's the lounge?
It's over there.
Where's the lounge?
I will show you.
It's this way.
This is the lounge.
You're very nice.
I think you're too good for this job.
Can I have your number?
Oh, I don't give out my number,
but rules are meant to be broken.
I'm a law major, so I'm good with rules.
Go, go and take care of it.
The guests in the next room are complaining.
Excuse me...
Who are you?
I'm sorry. I'm Heo Sedal, and I work here.
So?
Is there anything you need?
Yes. I need you to get out.
There was a complaint.
You're like a noisy neighbor, so to speak.
Get out. Leave me alone.
I'll take that as a positive sign.
If you need anything, speak instead of crying.
What do you think about me?
What do you mean?
As a woman, how am I?
I think you're not bad.
Not bad?
Do you have a girlfriend?
That's my dream,
but my wife is a dragon lady, so I don't.
You're married?
I didn't mean to but...
I thought I'd never get married, but one day
I woke up and found myself married,
which is tragic and horrible.
Who's better, your wife or me?
You're far better than my wife, of course.
I can't even compare you to her.
I don't know what anyone said to you,
but don't lose hope,
and please refrain from crying out loud.
If you really want to cry, you can,
but please do it under the blanket.
Enjoy your stay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Dad!
Yes! You even greet me differently now!
I can hear how happy you are to see me.
Your dad Sedal came home from work.
From work, from work, from work, work, work...
What's all that for?
Commemorating my first day of work.
It's a historical day. Write about it.
Okay!
I've decided to stay there permanently.
Watch me.
I won't miss a day.
This is cake and these are toys.
Wow!
- No!
- Mom, you're mean!
I knew it.
What's wrong with you? Huh?
No. I'm exchanging these tomorrow.
But the cake is okay.
Happy first day of work!
Happy first day of work, dear dad!
I feel so great!
This is nutty, nutty, nuts!
So amazing!
Why are the lights off?
Did you eat?
I was always in the middle.
With studying, with sports,
with singing, with everything.
My classmates and teachers,
not many of them remember me.
Hobak was a great student, won awards,
was popular with other students,
and even the teachers liked her.
Me, only my mom loved me.
I was an ordinary child who deserved no special attention.
I wasn't bad to look at, a quiet girl.
That was who I was.
But,
after I met you, my life changed.
People started gathering around me.
Thanks to you, I became Cinderella.
With a house and furniture like this,
with three bathrooms,
a housekeeper and an imported car.
I was like Cinderella who everyone envied.
But the clock struck midnight.
With the sound of the clock's chime,
I must go back to being poor.
Being driven to poverty like this,
I can't do it.
My father said this at an ethics class.
God only gives you what you can handle.
I can't handle this,
so why is god putting me through this?
What am I supposed to do?
How am I supposed to handle this?
Let's stay in Seoul.
Let's rent a room or something.
In return, give me just 3 years.
I'll have you back here in 3 years.
You must keep them in shipshape in order for them to last longer.
They're just like people.
You can't fix them if it's too late.
Okay.
Machines need to be taken care of.
I'll remember that.
I replaced two hydraulic jacks last time,
but I think the others need replacing, too.
Okay. And check the motor oil.
Okay.
Safety.
First.
I'm very sorry, but the file is gone.
What should I do?
I didn't want to send this reply,
but I'm forced to.
I trusted you, but you fooled me twice.
Go to hell.
Hello?
I understand why you feel this way.
It may sound like a joke but I swear.
The file disappeared,
and I had a print out, but it's gone.
I'm serious. Please believe me.
I'll get my computer repaired
and prove it to you.
Sangnam?
Hello?
Ugh! Wang Daebak!
Here.
Why couldn't I find it?
Where are you going so late?
I have a date.
I wish!
I won't be difficult, so get married.
How about you?
You don't want to remarry?
Excuse me?
You can't live alone forever.
You're still young.
If there's a nice man, I won't say no.
Really?
Daese, I'm happy as I am.
Unless you're happy, I'd like to leave things as they are.
But you're lonely.
I have no time to feel lonely.
I'm busy taking care of Miho.
And there's too much to do around the house.
Taking care of you and Sangnam is a lot of work.
It's just that I'm worried about Miho, too.
She needs a father's love.
I'm trying my best,
but I'm only her uncle.
- Would you like me to lift you up?
- Yes.
Okay. One, two, three!
Dad, one more time.
Okay. Are you ready?
One, two, three.
Siyeong, you're great!
My little girl.
Do you want to go to an amusement park?
Mommy, don't they sell dads anywhere?
I wish we could go and buy a dad.
You came here alone?
Can I join you?
I'm not here alone. I'm sorry.
What's up?
Were you working on her?
I only work at the construction site.
I wanted to have a drink with you.
It can't be work.
Is it a woman?
It's not.
You got hurt.
I really believed
she understood my work and why I do it.
Let it go.
You can't change how people think overnight.
Do women really dislike technicians?
It's the society that made them that way.
They only like white collar workers.
Did you tell her you own the company?
No, I didn't.
Why didn't you?
Not only do you run it, but you own it.
What does that matter?
I started out as a heavy equipment operator.
I couldn't like a woman who would like me because I own a company.
Do you like that reporter?
She's not my type.
Ugh.
I'm here. I just need to park my car.
I'll be right up.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'll be up soon.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry. I'll pull out.
I'll help you park.
I can't do it.
Just do what I tell you to do.
- Okay.
- Pull up a little.
Stop. Turn the handle to the left halfway.
Back up.
Stop. Pull up a bit. Just a bit.
Stop!
Make the steering wheel vertical.
Back up.
More, more, more.
Unwind the steering wheel.
Okay. Stop.
Oh, how amazing!
I did it! I parked my car. Thank...
Excuse me...
- This?
- Yes, thank you so much.
The person you have called is not available...
There is one new message.
Press 1 to listen, 2 for information...
First message.
I remembered.
I told you we've met before.
I went to a publisher last winter,
and I was having trouble parallel parking,
and you helped me.
You helped me parallel park with ease.
It was so amazing.
There's something special between us.
Please call me when you hear this, okay?
Oh, you can't get a 2 bedroom with that little.
You can't even get a 1 bedroom.
They just don't have that.
I have something that's perfect for you.
Would you like to see it?
Yes.
The owner's in a hurry, so the price is great.
There are two bathrooms?
Yes, we're in a hurry, so we're selling it below the market value.
I see.
This is the only thing available for that price.
Okay.
Subak.
If you hang new wallpaper, it'd be better.
We don't have time for that.
We have to move today.
Please hold on.
Subak!
This is a lucky apartment.
My kids were healthy and did well at school,
and now we're moving to a bigger place.
You are?
I hope I get that kind of luck, too.
Thank you. Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
- Yes.
[Apartment purchase contract
Name: Wang Hobak
Name: Heo Sedal]
Huh?
Sis.
Hobak.
Minjung doesn't like scallions.
And he eats instant noodles without eggs.
How do you know that?
I worked at your house for many years.
Put the rice in the soup.
Minjung, you too.
Would you like some boiled beef?
Subak, would you like some?
My treat.
What's going on?
You never spend any money.
I'm just happy to see you.
Running into you unexpectedly is great.
If it happens again,
you just might go slaughter a cow.
It's just lunch so lets keep it simple.
Okay, then.
Minjung, you shouldn't skip your meals.
You've gotten so thin.
Is my husband the only person you see?
You're skin and bones too.
There's no need to mention it.
You should eat.
How can I eat at a time like this?
I'm barely breathing!
You eat fine.
I don't understand why you lost weight.
People would think I'm stressing you out.
Did you buy an apartment?
Huh?
You told mom you're buying an apartment.
Well, I...
Are you buying an apartment?
No, not yet.
Then why did you see a realtor?
I wanted some information.
Why did you see one?
We're looking for an apartment.
That's no apartment! It's just a room!
You're staying in Seoul?
Subak can't handle it, so what else could I do other than renting a room?
Subak, that's great.
Good for you, Minjung.
Renting a room is great?
Can't you be more careful with words?
That's not what she meant.
Are you on her side too?
Oh, Subak.
Let's eat.
We must hurry if we want to move today.
You're moving today?
We have to move out by today.
Then you should hurry.
Where's your apartment?
I said it isn't an apartment!
I said it's just a room!
Subak...
Let's go. People will show up soon.
Come on.
There.
Oh, my! Oh, my!
Oh, man...
It's all built in.
We'll hang the wallpaper later.
We'll find time.
A mouse! Mouse!
Come back. It's gone.
No, no!
It won't bite you.
I said no!
I can't live in a place like that.
I feel bad for the dishes.
These are all from England.
What are you looking for?
There might be mice and roaches.
Poor Subak...
Are you happy she's here?
You're sisters!
You could've lent her money.
Did you think she'd run off with that?
Subak paid you $100 to wash the dishes.
You could buy a house with the money she gave you.
You saw a realtor earlier?
Did you buy a place or something?
I was just getting information.
How could you pick now to buy an apartment?
It's like you're trying to stick it to her.
Don't be disrespectful to Subak.
I asked around and she has amazing fortune.
Those around her can benefit from her great fortune.
Do you understand that?
I'm sure you don't understand.
Mom!
How about the bathroom?
It's communal.
It's communal?
The tenants must take turns cleaning it.
That's not good!
Your sister can't do it so you do it.
I'll do it on my days off.
But I've been really busy...
You'd find time if you're serious about it.
Hey, you're good.
I'm great wife material.
You change her diaper.
Ugh, incredible.
You won't change our kids diapers later on?
Then I'll run away!
We'll talk about that later.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Hold on, Jungji.
You come back here!
It smells! Come back here!
Congratulations on moving into a new place.
New place my butt.
This is a house warming party. Applause!
Applause my butt!
Happy apartment rental...
Happy moving dear Subak and Minjung
Stop that! Happy rental apartment?
Why should we applaud? I could cry!
Why would you cry?
They just moved, so we should applaud them.
Minjung, Subak, blow out the candle.
Say something. Thank us for coming.
You sure are excited.
Me?
You're right.
I'm excited.
I, Heo Sedal, finally got a job.
You got a job?
That's great.
When?
You never told me that.
I'm telling you now.
Traitor! How could you do that?
Where is it?
The hotel he worked at briefly before.
We sang "Happy first day of work" and blew out a candle, too.
Why? You'll probably quit any day now.
Don't worry, mother.
I promised Hobak I won't quit this time.
Lots of great things are happening now.
I got a job and Minjung moved.
Are you joking?
Of course not.
His business is my business, and vice versa.
I'm just trying to lighten up the mood.
My heart is being torn apart too.
There's no need for that.
You've hit bottom, so the only way to go is up now.
Yes, sir.
Actually, living in a place like this will make you love each other more.
You can't sleep in separate rooms.
This is better than the place we lived in when we first got married.
It was much smaller, wasn't it?
We climbed up from the bottom,
and you're going down from the top.
You're climbing up,
and Minjung's climbing down.
Will you two meet in the middle?
You're very smart, mother.
Life has ups and downs.
When you're down, you can take a break.
What's life?
If you don't own, you rent.
Either unemployed or have a part time job.
I wasn't going to say that but it came out.
If you climb up or down,
own or rent, you two are the most important.
When you're poor, you get into fights,
and lots of people divorce because of that.
I believe in Minjung.
I'm giving it 3 years.
We must live here for 3 years?
You can do it.
Others live here.
Who knows?
It might take 3 or 30 years.
If words were all it took,
I'd own at least 12 homes by now.
Sedal, you're right.
Words mean nothing.
Oh my poor daughter.
I raised her as a princess.
I'm sorry, mom.
I never wanted you to see this.
I'm sorry, father.
I meant to do well.
I'm sorry you had to see this.
Oh, mommy!
- What is it? What?
- Mom!
What is it? What?
Oh, it's just a roach.
How can you kill that with your bare hand?
We had lots of practice where we used to live.
She's really good at it.
She doesn't need any tissue. Ugh.
You should kill all the roaches for them.
Oh, she can kill mice, too.
My poor Subak...
Why should you feel that way?
Is her husband or kid dead?
She just lost money.
How can she live in an apartment filled with mice and roaches?
Why not?
She doesn't work so she can kill the roaches and mice.
Didn't you see Hobak?
She can fend for herself because she can kill them.
Who told you killing roaches means you can fend for yourself?
I did.
Others live there.
Whatever they do, just leave them alone.
She'll become a better person.
Are you saying Subak isn't a good person?
I can't believe my ears!
She had you take care of her girls and the housekeeper run the house.
She worked her husband like a slave!
It's not a crime to have a good life.
It is.
When you give birth, you must be a mother.
She's old but she's a crybaby.
You tell my mother she spoils Don,
but you're no different.
Subak and Don aren't the same!
How can you compare those two?
You're still up?
I must check on my grandson.
If it weren't for him,
the family name would have died out.
Anggeum must treasure him.
You shouldn't treasure your children.
You should love them,
but you must be strict with them.
You're right.
If you love your children, you must be strict.
You're upset about Subak, aren't you?
You must feel like you lost your right hand.
You could rely on Minjung before,
but now, he lost it all.
When your children are in trouble, it breaks your heart.
Oh, the trouble we're in right now...
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
I wish I could help them out.
You raised them and married them off.
What else could you do?
If it weren't for him,
I would help them out with my severance pay and get them a better apartment.
Don't be so stupid.
Excuse me?
Don't let them take advantage of you.
Don't let your kids suck you dry.
Leave your severance pay alone.
You need money when you're old.
Don't give it to anyone.
Hold onto it.
And don't give it to Anggeum, understand?
Hello?
How can you sleep?
How can you?
Oh, mom.
Don't you feel bad for your sister?
How can you sleep after seeing her like that?
You're heartless.
How could you be like that?
You're really something.
I feel lost after seeing her like that, and you're sleeping?
You're heartless. I'm hanging up.
Ugh...
Oh, you're Sintong's aunt!
- Hello.
- Where are you going?
To my mom's house.
You look pretty bad for someone who was in the Miss Korea pageant.
You look awful.
What happened to you?
Oh, I heard you have mice at your place.
Yes and roaches.
But I'm in a hurry.
I heard your husband is in parcel service.
My son works at a hotel.
I heard. Congratulations. Goodbye.
It must be really tough for you.
Why don't you get a job, like Hobak?
I'm in a hurry.
I know.
Should I ask around?
You have a college degree, right?
I must get going.
Why are you sweating?
You look sick.
Would you like to sit down?
It's okay.
I'll see you again.
I'm not going to let her get away with it.
What's wrong with her?
Why couldn't she just let her go?
I can't believe I'm washing poo out of my daughter's pants.
- What are you doing?
- Mother!
What are you washing?
It doesn't concern you.
Is someone making fermented soybeans?
Fermented soybeans?
Who's making that? Who?
It smells really good.
Hey, let's make some too.
I've been craving fermented soybeans for a couple days now.
Please don't mention that.
Yes, Daese.
Sunjeong, I'm getting a package today.
Okay.
Hello.
What's up, little girl?
I'm not a little girl.
I'm Daebak's girlfriend.
I know.
You're the little girl who's after Daebak.
I'm not after him.
What do you want?
Daebak's at the teachers office.
I need to talk to you.
Me? About what?
What's this?
It's a yellow card.
A yellow card?
They use this when they play soccer.
You know what it means, don't you?
Don't flirt with Daebak again.
If you do, I'm giving you a red card.
You know what comes after that, don't you?
Expulsion.
What are you doing?
What are you doing at my school?
Daebak, I was waiting for you.
Let's go, Daebak.
Hold on.
Are you going to the academy?
Daebak!
Fine, I'm coming.
Daebak, what should we eat?
Oh, she's cute.
She's so funny.
Daebak is incredible.
Bye, Haebak!
Hello.
I want to send this by certified mail.
Okay.
He asked me for my high school yearbooks.
So I told him they got lost in the fire.
Slap them on the mouth when they say that.
How dare they...
Hey, hey!
If that's who you'd set me up with, forget it!
How dare she!
You can't tell I got work done.
Everyone gets that much work done.
You can't tell you got any.
Don't you agree?
Excuse me?
You're too young to have worries!
Your face is filled with worries.
I can tell you have some sad stories to tell.
Oh.
There are rumors about you.
Rumors?
They're saying you living with your brother in law is weird.
Is it okay to live with your brother in law?
I guess you could.
If they're divorced, it should be fine.
It's not like that.
I have a reason.
We are still related.
Aunt Sunjeong.
Yes?
Should I wait for you?
It's okay. You go ahead. I'll catch up.
Okay. Take your time and get more pretty.
Who's that? The son?
Yes, he's my nephew.
Oh, wow.
This car is...
It's a wise choice. This car is...
Shh...
Yay! This is nutty, nutty, nuts!
This is nuts!
Hey! You stop right there!
Hey! Come here!
You! Hey!
Hey!
Are you out of your mind? Are you?
A car is a man's pride.
How dare you!
I'm going to kill you!
Hey, my shoes...
So? I can't return it?
Hey! Who says I can't return a car?
Stop talking nonsense!
Hobak, open the door.
Hobak.
Hobak, the door!
Hobak! Hobak!
You've been out here all this time?
Why are you back so late?
Hey! Open the door! My mom's here.
And the sister.
My sister's here, too.
Open the door!
Hobak!
Open it!
No!
I need to teach him a lesson.
You're being really stuffy.
Everyone needs a car these days.
We should have one too.
Of course!
Open! Open! Open!
What are you doing?
Who doesn't have a car these days?
Mom, go for it. Open!
Open it now! You're embarrassing us.
- Open!
- He has a job. He can get a car!
Mother!
There's so many packages to deliver.
I don't think I can go home this year.
That's that, but why can't Subak come?
I can't send her alone.
Why not?
She's acting like that because of you!
She's been sick lately.
She hasn't been well.
I'm sorry, Minsuk.
I'll drop by and see father another time.
So please take care of...
Minsuk!
Hello?
Here.
What is it?
A chamber pot.
Use this.
Using the communal bathroom is hard,
and you can't run to your mother's place every time.
I don't want this.
I heard it's convenient. Use it.
I said no!
Must you make me feel pathetic?
What do you mean?
You're making me feel pathetic.
Did you think I'd thank you for this?
It's embarrassing, humiliating,
and it feels like my face is on fire.
Do you know how embarrassing it is to not be able to hold it in?
And now you want me to use a chamber pot?
You know how I get constipated whenever I'm away from home!
We'll get through it.
It's only for 3 years.
How can I not poo for 3 years?
I'm not tell you to do that!
Use this.
Everyone else does it.
I got this at the market, and it means others use it too.
That's not embarrassing! Just go here!
Stop it!
I was in the Miss Korea pageant!
Oh, man!
A blind date?
Yes.
You saw her at the beauty salon.
I didn't. Is she pretty?
I would've remembered if she were pretty.
She's got a face most men would like.
Would you like to meet her?
Why not? You're hooking us up after all.
Not really. She asked me to.
She fell for you the moment she saw you.
So just give her a chance.
Okay.
Sangnam,
I'm saying this out of concern,
and I know I might be overreacting...
Don't beat around the bush.
Don't hold onto the past.
It'll only make your life hard.
Do you still have feelings for her?
She was your first, so it would be hard.
But she broke your heart, so forget her.
Sangnam,
I just want you to be happy.
Not pretending to be happy,
but really, truly happy.
You know what I mean, don't you?
I will be.
But I'd like to ask the same of you.
I want you to be happy, too.
I'm happy. I have everything I need.
Sangnam, let's go.
I'm coming.
Oh, aunt, your hair looks pretty.
You're the best.
I'm going to hell.
Bastard. I hope you're happy!
You don't trust anyone, do you?
I can't seem to be able to become like you.
It doesn't happen overnight.
Are you coming from somewhere?
The academy. I got bored.
I thought your grades were bad.
The kid who's head of the class cries when he gets his report card.
I don't get it.
How much more must you study to not cry?
It seems like you're the only one who can be successful in your family so work hard.
Okay. I will.
I'm leaving.
Goodbye.
Here.
I found it on my sister's desk. Read it.
She wrote great things about you.
But don't fall for her.
She's not pretty.
"The World of Me's Jobs"
September Special,"Great Income, Fit Body!"
By Wang Gwangbak
The mobile phone has been turned off...
Where are you going?
Hey! Sangnam!
Answer your phone!
What?
Why did you turn your phone off?
I turned my phone off because...
[Arrogant Bulldozer]
Hello?
Come to the playground right now.
Hey!
Fine. I'm coming. I am!
You want a piece of me?
Fine! I'll give you a piece of me!
You reckless bastard.
This late? Crazy bastard.
I'm here! What do you want? You bastard!
Why did you want to see me this late?
You don't understand how I feel...
You really shouldn't live like that.
You should learn to trust people.
You think I would deceive you? For what?
I don't even care about you.
I cut you out. Snip!
Are you disgusted?
I'm the one who's disgusted.
I got fired because of you.
Like my mom said,
I'm having a bad year.
I was going to treat you to dinner with the money from the article!
But forget it!
I think of you when I open my eyes in the morning.
What the heck.
When I open my eyes, I think of you.
You! First thing. Crap!
I told you we met before.
You taught me how to park last winter.
I could park at once.
You were pretty amazing back then.
Why would you ignore my texts?
I'm not playing games, you jerk!
Is there anything you want to say? No?
Bye.
I'm going to hell.
You go to heaven and I'll go to hell.
Let's go. Let's go to hell.
Subtitles by KBS World
I think I got drunk and made a mistake.
I'm not this kind of woman.
I'd love to have a drink but I have plans.
That's too bad. I'd like to, too.
Hello? Is this 911?
Are you hiding something from me?
No. Subak, I have to go back to work.
How much longer will you ask your mom to take the kids?
Bring them right now.
I regret marrying you,
and I regret having the girls! Satisfied?