Subtitles by KBS World
You didn't know Miho's your daughter?
Dad, let's eat.
Did you tell Miho to call me dad?
No.
Miho said she wanted to.
I'm grateful, but I hope she doesn't for now.
It's Aeji.
Miho is...
It's nothing.
Let me see.
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
Don't be surprised.
I tried to tell you, but I couldn't.
What's he doing?
It's Mr. Ko.
Please open the door.
Huh?
How...
Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you tell me about Miho?
I didn't want to give such a precious gift to someone who didn't want her.
I wanted to wait for the right moment.
But I never got it.
Come home.
Are you getting on or not?
I'm getting on.
Sunjeong.
I'm leaving.
I'll call you when Miho gets married.
You can walk her down the aisle.
That's all we need.
Sunjeong.
Sunjeong!
Sunjeong! Sunjeong!
Don't, please!
Please don't hurt me.
Please don't call the police, please.
Give it.
What?
The money from selling my in-laws house.
I don't have it...
Sedal,
talking to him won't get the job done.
There's nobody here.
We can take care of him without anyone finding out.
How should we handle him, Sedal?
Calm down, calm down.
Let's hold off on that for now.
Remember the guy we buried 3 days ago?
Wait, did we use this excavator?
Where did we bury him? Around here?
Huh? You bastard!
Please don't kill me.
There's too many for me to remember.
Uh, please! Please hold on.
I'll give you the money back,
so please don't call the police.
Please.
Yes! We did it! We did it!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
What happened?
Why are the kids here?
Don't even bring it up. Aeji got hurt.
How?
She's been through so much that
she tried to come home all by herself.
Raise them like they are her own?
Yeah, right.
I couldn't do that.
Women who raise other's kids are saints.
Even your own kids drive you crazy.
Just cut to the chase.
Must I spell it out?
She was abused.
I just can't believe that woman.
Aeji said she was really mean to her.
You can't believe everything kids say.
What did Subak say?
She said she's keeping them.
She was furious.
Where did she go?
She went to get training.
Father! Mother!
Oh, my!
What? Is that true?
Bong, we're saved, we're saved.
I can't believe my ears.
Is that true?
Oh, God, Buddha, thank you.
- How did you get it back?
- Well,
Sangnam was on the same plane with him.
It was like a Bond movie.
Minjung was with us, too, but he had to go.
The 3 of us captured him and beat him up,
and we told him to spit out the money.
And I was acting all angry and crazy.
It was actually quite fun.
I'm sure the Korean was nothing compared to it!
Right, grandmother.
It was like an action film.
Oh, this is nuts.
Sedal, you're amazing.
Hey, what did you do with him?
We took him to the police.
He begged us not to take him there,
but we took him right over.
Good job.
Good, good.
Today was the auction day,
so we went to court and got the house back.
For some reason, it didn't sell.
Because it's our house.
They put that notice on the door
so every neighbor could see it,
but it was meant for us.
I wanted someone to buy it...
Good job, Sedal, Good job, Sangnam.
Our son in laws saved us.
I'm worthless.
That you are!
Sedal!
Don left.
Hey come back inside!
Come in, come in! Make us some pizza.
Wang Subak! Wang Subak!
Good news! Great news!
Really?
Is that true, uncle?
Yes!
Your parents are ecstatic.
I can't believe this really happened!
Don't cry.
You must be so happy.
You can finally relax.
Look how excited you are.
It must have been really great.
You caught me.
Unbelievable.
You didn't even say hi to me at the airport!
- Who was she?
- What?
That girl you followed.
Who was she?
- Girl?
- I saw you following her.
You did?
Wasn't she pretty?
Tell me who she was.
After I change.
Tell me!
I went to the airport because I felt badly
for sending you after a fight.
[I'm sorry about the fight]
See?
I'm going to do this for you.
[I'll be good to you]
I was going to flip these pages.
[I'll be a good wife]
I was so excited about this.
Do it now.
Are you kidding me?
You wrote them, so let me see them.
Forget it.
I won't do it again. I'm sure of it.
Wow, this is like in the movies!
When did you make this?
Don't look at it!
Yes, mom, what is it?
Sangnam? He's here.
What?
What do you mean?
You got the house back?
Really? Really, mom?
Oh, my.
Okay, mom.
My darling husband.
Oh...
Thank you for welcoming me like this.
But what do I do?
I need to go see her.
Oh, no, no.
Don't go, don't go.
Everywhere.
Kiss me everywhere, to a point where it makes you wonder if you should be doing it.
How can you be such a darling?
Honey, I have something to tell you, too.
Sweetie!
Yes, father!
Sweetie?
Did he just call you that?
Yes, I'm sweetie.
Father and I made up.
We had a drinking competition.
Really? Who won?
I did, of course.
But I think I shouldn't have done that.
I should've let him win.
I didn't know what he had in mind.
Why am I so slow at catching things like that?
You just realized that now?
Ugh!
Sweetie!
Yes, I'm coming, father.
I like him much more than you.
He gave me a cafe.
I'm materialistic, you know?
Father, I'm coming!
Oh, how exciting!
- The weather's so nice!
- It's so light!
I'm so happy that it doesn't feel heavy!
Oh, my!
House, it's been a while!
How have you been?
Oh, it's so nice to be back.
Let's go in.
Bong, you go in first.
Okay.
We should get our stuff from the storage.
Yes, yes.
It's been a while.
How have you been?
Oh, home sweet home!
I'm so happy.
Oh...
Hey! Hey!
What is it?
Where's the doorplate?
- It's gone.
- What?
You said you won't need it.
I tossed it into the fire.
How dare you!
Get out!
The doorplate is more important to me!
Oh, I can't believe this.
Here, here it is.
I packed this first.
You would've thrown me out if I hadn't.
Of course.
This is a very important doorplate.
Good-off and Hobak look good.
You don't fight anymore?
They haven't fought in a while.
How are you feeling?
Good.
You should have another baby.
When you get pregnant, I'll take care of you.
I'll cook you anything you want.
I'll take care of you after you give birth.
You promise?
Hobak, let's go.
Where?
She wants us to make a baby.
Let's go and...
Stop this!
Why you little...
How about you?
Hold on. It's coming.
Say that after you get pregnant.
I know. It only took us...
That's nothing to brag about.
Right.
You should focus on each other from now on.
We will. We won't have time to be otherwise.
I did take him back to get my revenge.
I didn't understand women who take their
husbands back after they've cheated on them.
But now I do.
Although I did it to make him work for me.
Be honest. You did it because you love him.
I didn't love him back then.
I wanted to pay him back for what he did,
but marriage is a funny thing.
If that happened with a friend,
we would've become mortal enemies,
but it was different. I felt sorry for him.
That's what marriage is about.
Love turns into that after 10 years.
You feel sorry you can't do more for your spouse.
The two of you become one.
That's how a marriage lasts.
- Did you hear that?
- Yes.
I pity those who are old and single.
That reminds me of Sedal's mother.
Your mom must feel very lonely.
Find out if she wants to meet someone.
You don't need to worry about my mom.
She has me and Yeongdal, so she's happy.
- Sedal.
- That's enough.
I don't feel comfortable with it.
- You don't know anything.
- But I do.
- What?
- I heard.
So? Mother is human and a woman.
And she never abandoned you.
You went to sleep at night,
holding onto her skirt, afraid she might run away.
But my mom isn't a bad woman.
I know.
She was younger than me at the time,
so I understand her and feel bad for her.
It must have been really hard for her.
I don't know if I could've done the same.
You should get over it.
You have me.
Oh...
Sedal,
we should get her free.
Are you sleeping?
No, I'm not sleepy at all.
Ugh...
You must be the happiest one here.
I'd never imagined it.
I wanted to buy you a house.
As if that will ever happen.
You should take care of yourself first.
Has Minjung called?
No.
He didn't even call when the kids are here?
He must have completely lost his mind.
Men are like that.
I'm going to wait and see.
Don, I'm so happy.
I had no idea how happy I'd feel about having a room all to ourselves.
I don't want a house.
All I need is a room.
Yeongdal, I love you because of this.
You used to like rich men before.
I was crazy back then.
Meeting you changed my views.
You must really love me.
My beautiful princess.
Oh...
Get me some tea.
The person you called is unavailable...
It's our opening day, so let's do a good job.
Let's do this!
- What are you doing?
- When did you come?
Just now.
I'm going to start writing.
You'll ave a writer daughter in law soon.
[Go for it!]
I heard this is the best drink on the menu.
You pour chocolate over it?
Thank you.
I'll drink this and write like mad.
And badmouth your father in law?
No, I have nothing bad to say about you!
Not having any flaws is your flaw.
You...
Hello?
Yes. I'll see you there.
Medical report, tax report, family record.
Were you upset because I asked for these?
No.
I know you're worried about your mother meeting some worthless bum.
Thank you for understanding.
I'll review these and call you.
But haven't we met somewhere?
I thought that, too.
Did you attend Yeongnam High School?
No.
College? I majored in law.
I didn't go to college.
How about army service?
I was stationed in Gangwon-do Province.
I was stationed way down south.
Oh!
- The fishing vessel!
- The used excavator!
No...
Let's think about it.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Oh!
The wedding!
Right! You were the host!
You're Gwangbak's father in law!
How can this be?
You won't need these, right?
I should check the medical exam.
Just look at me.
From head to toe,
from bones to blood,
from muscles to fat,
I'm totally clean.
Why couldn't you recognize me?
Man.
What is it?
Give me some new skin care stuff.
Is it a gift? For whom?
My step dad.
What did you just say?
Your step dad?
I met him and he seemed decent.
But promise me you'll be happy.
If you're not, I won't let it slide.
Oh, Sedal!
Mom, please...
Oh, mom.
I love you.
Really?
Sedal, you're so amazing.
Good job. Kiss, kiss!
I'll see you later.
You look like you're newlyweds.
We're stuck together, so I might as well...
Whatever, Hobak.
You're really amazing.
I thought you were going to kill each other.
Tell me how you did it.
I'll tell you when you get married. I'll be back.
- Come in.
- Okay.
Huh? Father.
Welcome.
Say hi. My mom.
Hello.
Why are we...
Let's have lunch. Sit.
Okay.
Sedal, your mother is beautiful.
You're a smart man. You pass.
Is today a special day?
Sedal told me to wear a suit, so I did.
We're going to be brothers.
Hello.
Oh, welcome. Sit down.
They called you, too?
Of course.
Hello.
I'm her one and only daughter in law.
I heard I should thank you for making this happen.
Thank you.
There's no need to be that formal.
I'll work on that.
Hobak, what happens to our family tree?
It's too complicated to talk about.
Let's have the wedding in the spring.
And let's keep it simple.
Wedding?
Who's getting married?
You don't know?
I just came because Sedal called me.
What's going on here?
Man...
Where have you been?
Just look at them.
I still don't get it.
Oh, no.
Sangnam, what's going on here is...
You idiot.
You can't tell what's going on here?
Hobak's mother in law and your father are getting married.
Really?
You thought I'd say that?
I was just pretending.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm serious. I knew it all along.
What's so funny?
- Huh?
- Hello.
Jangbi,
this is the woman I'm going to marry.
Congratulations.
Take good care of our immature Daese.
I'm immature, too.
It's my treat. Start ordering.
Can I order a large order of the noodles?
Or can we get the lunch course?
Mother, that's my leg.
Oh, no.
What were you doing under the table?
Mom!
Daese.
Sunjeong, it's me.
Congratulate me.
I'm getting married.
You are?
Come to Seoul and say hello to her.
I'm sorry, Daese.
I'll just come to your wedding.
I don't want to go to Seoul just yet.
Okay. Is Miho doing okay?
Yes.
Daese, don't worry about me.
We are doing fine here.
It's like I've returned to the beginning again.
Nothing has changed.
Take care and good luck with your wedding preparations.
Goodbye.
The person you called is unavailable,
so your call will be directed to voice mail.
Sunjeong, where are you?
Just tell me where you are.
If you don't want to talk, text me.
I'll come right over, okay?
Please answer the phone.
Sunjeong, I'm sorry.
I'll get down on my knees and beg.
Sunjeong, where are you?
Please tell me.
Just tell me where you are.
I miss Miho.
How can you be so dense?
Would she live with you if Miho wasn't yours?
I just can't believe how dense you are!
Miho looks just like you!
Sunjeong, please answer my call.
I want to hear your voice.
Tell me where you are.
I've been awful to Miho.
I want to hold her in my arms.
I want Miho to call me dad, Sunjeong.
I know I don't deserve an ounce of pity.
You raised my girl all alone.
Can I hold her in my arms?
Sunjeong, where are you?
Where are you?
Please.
Sunjeong!
Success for Wang Don's pizza!
Success! Success! Success!
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Tough days are over for you, Don.
- Mom!
- Yes, yes.
Don, I hope you become successful.
And make lots of money.
Yes, Bong.
I'll be the breadwinner from now on.
So you just enjoy yourself.
Let's all enjoy ourselves from now on.
No, I'm still young.
I'm going to open an after school program.
The kids have nowhere to study.
Many of them can't afford academy programs.
I was a teacher, so I should do that.
Gwangbak said she'll help.
Hello.
You're here!
Loser! You finally have your own business!
Loser? Stop calling me that.
- Beat him up.
- Oh!
Do it. It's okay.
Don, congratulations!
Mother...
Congratulations, Mrs. Park.
Your son's still good for nothing,
but your son in law is the owner here!
What are you implying?
I'm not implying anything.
You gave your children to us.
What will you do from now on?
The thought of that keeps me up at night.
It shouldn't keep you up at night.
You did a good thing.
You raised your children well.
I thought they weren't all that special,
but Sedal and Yeongdal are all very nice.
You really think so?
Of course.
I actually envy you.
You ran a hair salon and now a makeup shop.
You've done everything you wanted to do,
and now you're getting married again.
But I envied you.
People respected you for your husband,
had five children,
and your husband is alive and well.
That's nothing to be envious of.
Try living with my husband for a week.
Then you'll know.
The grass is always greener on the other side.
Right.
I hope you have a happy life.
I'll come to your wedding.
What are you two doing?
It's a secret.
Did you pack everything?
Just about. I'm coming back.
I'll come to the orientation party.
I feel relieved now we got our house back.
You have to become a captain.
Life isn't all that special.
So do what you want to do.
- Mom.
Mom.
Why are you all here?
We came because Haebak's leaving tomorrow.
Oh, it's not like she's getting married.
She's doing what she wants, so I'm okay.
Then why do you look like you'll cry?
I'm not!
Mom.
Tada!
What's that?
Dollar undies.
Tada!
Really?
She went to the factory to get them.
You can put two or three pairs on now.
Look at how she loves them.
I'll get you more if they get worn out.
I'm in charge of mom's undies from now on.
Lucky you, mom!
Aunt said she'll supply you with makeup,
uncles said he'll feed you pizza,
Subak said she'll buy you handbags,
and Hobak will buy you undies.
What will you get me?
Your favorite! Money!
Look at her laughing.
She loves money.
No! I'm sick of money.
Oh, that's great news!
Mom, I heard money plays games, too.
It only comes to you when you're not into it.
That's why I'm not going to be into it.
Subak, isn't your job hard?
I heard you have to learn things.
I hate learning, but this is fun.
Even the training is fun, too.
How is your writing coming?
I feel like I'm a writer already.
We'll see about that.
But am I not the most successful?
Subak missed the Miss Korea pageant,
- and Hobak...
- Didn't become an announcer.
- What?
- Stop that!
I can become Miss Korea if I want to.
I was in the Miss Korea pageant.
I'm my company's announcer.
- Mom, what was your dream?
- Me?
It wasn't anything special.
In the old days, everyone wanted to
meet a nice man and build a family.
Then you realized your dream.
Madam Lee Anggeum,
how do you feel about realizing your dream?
You sound like a real announcer.
IN my next life...
I hope to study and become a great person
and do whatever I want to do.
I want to meet men and go abroad and study.
Not just as a wife or a mother.
But live as myself, Lee Anggeum.
Then you should study, like Subak.
In my next life!
It's too late for me now.
Mom, do you regret having us?
What do you think?
Mom! Ouch!
The number you have dialed is not in service.
Please check the number again.
Please.
Tell me where she is.
She won't pick up the phone or answer my texts.
And I think she changed her number.
I'm going crazy.
Sunjeong doesn't want to see you.
I'm begging you.
When she left saying she's going to be happy from now on,
she was glowing, but as time went by,
she lost weight and was full of worries.
I'm sorry.
I think it's over between you.
You should move on.
I have nothing else to say.
I...
Daese.
He says he's going crazy.
Sunjeong, I think you should see him.
No.
I left him for a reason,
and I don't want to get back with him.
What we had between us has been long gone.
It was silly of me to try to reconnect.
I should've just kept him in my heart.
He lost a lot of weight.
He found out about Miho after you left.
I'm sure he's dying inside.
That can't be helped.
He'll just have to deal with it.
But think about Miho.
I'm doing this for Miho.
I don't want to hurt her anymore.
I couldn't deal with it anymore.
He didn't know she was his.
Daese,
I appreciate you coming here.
But I won't change my mind.
I won't go back.
You might feel sorry for him now,
but he'll go back to his other kids.
My presence will only make things hard for him.
Let's not talk about him.
What about you?
Are you okay?
If he's okay, I'm okay.
It was like that in the past.
When he smiles, I smile.
When he's in pain, I'm in pain.
And it's the same now.
I was happy while it lasted.
Does Miho know?
No, I haven't told her.
I'll tell her when she gets married.
Her dad should walk her down the aisle.
She grew up without a father.
She should at least get that.
That's enough for us.
You can be pretty scary, you know?
I have to be, if I'm to raise my child alone.
Daese,
don't tell him where I am. Never.
You're here.
- Want a drink?
- No thanks.
You are just too much!
I knew you were crazy about her,
but this is too much.
Why didn't you come to me to apologize after kicking Aeji out?
How come you didn't say anything to me?
How can you just turn your back on us?
This is what you wanted, wasn't it?
Now that you've kicked my kids out,
are you enjoying yourselves?
Yes, I am.
I'm so happy I can fly.
I'm keeping the children.
But you should come and see them.
You're their dad, so be there for them.
Okay, I will.
And...
You're mistaken.
She never mistreated the kids.
She's not like that.
She was great to them.
You're defending her in front of me?
You're impossible.
She's gone.
She left that day.
You're not living together?
Miho...
She's mine.
She's my daughter.
I found out after they left.
She never told me that Miho's my daughter.
She never did.
I didn't even know that.
When Miho called me dad, I told her to stop.
Aeji kept crying, saying that I'm her dad,
telling her not to call me dad,
so I told her not to.
I only thought about Aeji.
I didn't care about how Miho felt.
I'm worthless.
I don't even know where they are.
If they are alive or dead...
Miho!
Mr. Ko!
How have you been?
Fine.
What are you doing here?
I came to see you.
I wanted to see you, Miho.
Can we shake hands?
Miho,
may I give you a hug?
Miho!
That looks so good on you.
I think that purse was waiting for you.
Goodbye.
Aeji.
Mom's getting paid today.
Aren't you happy?
Of course, I'm getting you a gift.
Wait with your dad.
Hi. Isn't it cold?
It's gotten warmer.
It's spring.
Jungji, give mommy a kiss.
Mom!
How was your day?
What did you buy?
They're not for you.
Sunjeong, it's me.
Welcome.
Oh, that smells good.
I made spicy octopus.
Oh, that's my favorite.
You must be hungry.
Dinner's almost ready.
The kids just ate.
Minjung, open these with the kids.
Where's Miho? Miho!
Hello.
You're studying again?
You're nothing like me.
I hated studying when I was a student.
This is yours.
It's a dress.
I hope you like it.
Thank you.
Everything you buy is so pretty.
Wow!
How do I look, dad?
Pretty. The prettiest.
Aeji, isn't she pretty? Right?
Yes.
Here, the short armed, short legged, dense,
and uselessly taciturn
Ko Minjung brought you coffee.
Should I give you a kiss as a tip?
No thank you.
Being taciturn isn't good.
It can drive someone crazy.
You should tell her how you feel.
I won't take you back if Sunjeong dumps you.
If he acts mean, call me right away.
Okay.
He's been texting some woman at work.
Really?
No way!
Who is she?
I should go slap her silly.
Give me your phone.
When did I ever?
Why would you say that?
I should hide before I get into more trouble.
You're not going to do the dishes?
Call me later.
Is it true?
I was joking.
How could he?
With his short arms and legs?
Sunjeong,
don't tell anyone this.
I submitted some proposals at work,
and they said I'm wasting my talent.
They asked me if I'm interested in studying,
and suggested going to Italy to study.
Really?
Wow, that's amazing.
I'm going to study handbag design in Italy.
Please don't tell the kids.
You'll be successful. I'm sure of it.
You're not going home?
I am. I was about to.
Why don't you check on the kids?
No, I should just go.
Take her home.
It's okay.
Hurry.
Don't bother. I'm fine.
Walking with you feels weird.
We never did this even when we were married.
I know.
Why did I live like that?
I'm a fool.
Why didn't I know before what a good man you are?
But I'm glad you're happy.
Whenever I visit, you feel like a stranger.
I've never seen you laugh like that.
You look so happy.
Everyone has someone they're meant to be with.
And that breaks my heart.
May I hold your hand?
I'm really sorry.
And thank you.
Don't say that.
I'm the one grateful. And I'm sorry.
- Go in.
- It's okay.
This is enough. Bye.
Take care!
Oh, it's cold.
You're back already?
Why didn't you walk her home?
She wanted to go alone.
Oh, man. You're impossible.
Subak! Subak!
What time is your flight?
Let me come.
It's okay. I want to go alone.
I feel bad letting you go like this.
Thank you for what you've done.
If you hadn't come to see me,
I wouldn't be so happy right now.
Please take care of my kids.
I'm the only one who can convince you.
Can you take care of Aeji and Jungji?
Please.
Minjung looks like he's about to die.
Help me save him.
I was never able to take care of them.
I was never a good mother.
I gave them up when I divorced him,
but I used them to hold onto Minjung.
I'm not doing this because I'm nice.
I think this is the only way.
Please come back.
I'm not raising your kids because I'm nice.
I rand away because I couldn't handle it.
I chose to do this to make myself feel better.
Don't worry about anything here.
I'll take the kids to the airport when you come back.
And I'll send their photos every day.
Thank you,
Sunjeong.
Okay, clap your hands and focus!
[30 years later]
Today is Gwangbak's 60th birthday.
And except for Daebak who's in the US,
everyone came to celebrate it.
First of all, happy birthday, Gwangbak.
Oh!
Thank you.
60th birthdays are such a bother!
That's why we only got a cake.
Who knew we'd really live to be 100?
How old are you, mother?
After I hit 100,
I stopped counting.
Funeral homes all went bankrupt, I heard.
I can't believe my ears.
Believe it because I've heard that, too.
Me too.
Okay,
now that the original members are all here,
tell us what you've been doing.
My parents have passed away, so I've been thinking of this family as my own.
The kids are all grown up and married.
My company became the 3rd biggest in the world.
You know how many awards I've won,
and the last handbag I designed was a huge hit,
and I'm exporting them all.
Even the US President carries my handbag.
The domestic branches were a huge success,
and now my pizza shop is in China, too.
As you know already, I'm a best selling writer.
My most recent book sold 10 million copies in 1 week.
I'm sick and tired of counting money.
So I got a money counting machine.
I make a lot of money, too.
I quit my captain job
and passed the coast pilot test.
Retirement age now is 80, right?
Yes.
I have a dozen or so years left,
and they want me to be their vice president.
I'm trying to have a baby.
Medicine's so advance these days,
that it's actually possible.
Stop lying, all of you!
You're all liars!
This is nuts.
How amazing would that be if that were true?
I know.
Writer, captain.
Who cares if you couldn't be those?
If you're healthy, that's all that matters.
Of course.
You shouldn't be too greedy.
How does it feel to be old?
You're right, grandmother.
When you're old, money doesn't matter.
I wonder why I worked so hard.
I should've enjoyed myself more.
I know.
Why you little!
The outcome isn't important in life.
Every step you take is important.
Having an ordinary life is not easy.
Right, right, Minjung.
Even if you work hard, it ends the same way.
You come empty handed and leave that way, too.
Being over 100 years old made me see that.
But I still can't see the answer, mother.
It's because you're still young.
You'll know when you're my age.
Isn't it time to take a picture?
Oh, my bones are making noise.
Take the picture!
Who's taking the picture?
Who? This is nutty, nutty, nuts.
This is nuts for me, too.
Once I sit down, I don't want to get up.
That's the problem with getting old.
You don't want to get up. Ugh.
Didn't we take a picture last year?
Right. They look all the same.
They don't!
I'm wearing hair mousse today!
Daebak used to send gifts every year.
- But mother?
- Yes.
I never got to realize all my dreams,
but I was happy while trying.
- Me too.
- Me too!
Let's pretend we took a picture.
- Let's shout, "Wang's family!"
- Okay.
Wang's family!
Parcel service!
The Korean War was nothing compared to this!
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Subtitles by KBS World