Subtitles by KBS World
You look good. Good luck, okay?
Let's do this.
Yeah!
I think I've seen his aunt from somewhere.
I'm sure you did.
We live in the same neighborhood.
We will now begin the presentation...
Of Choi Sangnam and Wang Gwangbak's...
Official wedding plans.
What was that?
Just hold on.
We will present the plans for our wedding.
And the plans for our future to all of you.
First, the wedding will be within this year.
Can we get things ready?
I know.
There's not enough time.
There's nothing to get ready.
We're going to have a small wedding.
We're going to have it at a nice restaurant.
And not at a wedding hall?
We should have it at a hotel.
A restaurant is not...
It's going to be small but meaningful.
We're inviting 30 guests per family, making it 60 guests in total.
Thirty?
I have over 100 friends, and from business,
I can't even count!
You know how many friends I have?
Remember how big our family is?
Grandmother, uncle, you, me,
Subak's family, Hobak's family, and... What?
There are at least 300 outside the family.
We could fill a soccer field.
My husband has thousands of students.
Let's move on for now.
Second,
we won't buy any furniture or wedding gifts.
We're fine with these wedding bands.
Not buying any new furniture is good.
All kinds of problems arise because of that.
You did well there.
We should get what we're supposed to get!
Sunjeong, this is nonsense, right?
Let's hear them out first, Daese.
But you should give the bride her gifts.
She'll only get married once,
and that's all she'll get out of it.
Excuse me, but we're not finished yet.
Please let us finish the presentation.
Continue.
Gwangbak will move in with me.
You're not letting them move out?
My house is huge and he's my only son.
I never even considered it.
The size of your house doesn't matter!
You shouldn't live with your married son.
Who lives with a single father in law?
We renovated the second floor recently,
so it should be okay for newlyweds.
But taking care of a single father in law is hard.
I'm letting them live with me.
I don't have to rely on my son and his wife.
I can support myself.
So buy them a house and...
We'll live there for 3 years,
save enough money, and move out.
Gwangbak is handing out a report on my financial state and future goals.
My savings, salary and business plans.
Please read it.
I know this wasn't what you expected,
but we decided to tell you how we plan
on living our lives in the future.
The important thing is that we will always support each other's dreams.
And the biggest part of our married life
will be us, second will be our children,
and third will be each other's family.
Okay.
The vice principal's wife?
You call her.
Hey, hello?
They always ask me to run errands.
They know she and I aren't close.
What is it?
They switched the meeting dates and asked me to tell the vice principal's wife.
Should I go tell her?
Good boy.
Ugh.
Hello?
Isn't anybody home?
Mom!
You, you, wha, what are you doing here?
You think I came to see you?
My mom sent me.
The meeting has been moved to tomorrow,
and if she doesn't show again, she'll pay a fine.
I blame the alcohol.
I agree!
Goodbye.
This is crazy!
What do you mean by that?
They will visit their in laws in turns on holidays.
That's what people do these days.
But that's nonsense!
Why is that?
It took just as much efforts to raise my daughter!
They're not even married yet.
Let's leave it up to them.
And we can't give you any allowances.
No way! You have to!
I worked hard to raise you!
We'll do it on your birthdays and holidays.
We have to buy a house and raise children.
If we want to move out, we must save money.
But if you're in trouble, we'll help.
Oh, boy.
By the way, why did you get a divorce?
Mom, we shouldn't talk about that...
Sons take after their fathers.
We have to sort this out for prevention.
Who knows if you cheated or were violent?
I understand why you'd be curious,
but my brother in law isn't like that.
It was because of financial reasons.
It had nothing to do with his character.
You keep butting in,
but you're only his aunt, not his mother.
I'm not really sure why you're here.
Had I known, I would've brought my family, too.
She's not just his aunt.
To Sangnam, she's like his mom.
Then she'll continue to live with you?
Of course. We're family.
I'm already upset they're not getting their own place,
and they have to live with her, too?
I'm upset about having my son get married
without getting proper gifts from your daughter.
I hope he's good to my family.
I have two son in laws, and they're great.
I hope he learns from them and be just as great.
You might have several son in laws,
but I'll only have one daughter in law.
She'll be too busy being my daughter in law to pay attention to her family.
I said yes only because they're in love.
Doctors and judges wanted to meet Gwangbak.
- She's joking.
- I'm telling the truth.
She almost met that doctor the other time.
No, I wasn't going to meet him.
Why can't I say it?
It's the truth.
Everyone wanted her as their daughter in law.
I'm sure, but my son is just as desirable.
Women lined up to meet him.
Then why didn't you find someone else?
You think I'm happy about your daughter?
Then why did she take the audition?
Audition?
What is he talking about?
Did you come here to work or goof around?
If you're weak, you shouldn't have come!
- I'm sorry.
- Man...
He won't even call.
What if he's starving himself?
And it's freezing outside.
He won't go starving.
He's too clever.
I'm sure he's getting food from somewhere.
Yeongdal, get the most popular gift set and all the samples there are.
For what?
Didn't you see?
Her mom is just like her.
Like mother, like daughter! Just think!
She has an attitude, don't you think?
She kept talking back to me.
I would never have said yes had I known.
How could she be so brazen?
Maybe I shouldn't have gone.
Forget it.
They have no right to say to stay or leave.
His father has an attitude problem.
Did you see how he was dressed?
How could he wear such a tight suit?
I was worried his pants might rip open.
If I had the body, I'd like  to wear that, too.
Really tight.
Gross.
Why do they want such a wedding?
People might think we're embarrassed about our son in law.
That's what decent people do these days.
We've experienced it with Subak and Hobak.
It was just crowded and complicated.
But I can't accept it.
I've spent a lot on the weddings of my friends kids!
Don't think like that.
All I have is one son.
No wedding gifts?
That's so inconsiderate.
How can he do that to me?
What if people ask me what I got from Gwangbak?
They'd think I didn't get anything because Sangnam wasn't good enough for her!
Then you'll have to give gifts to the bride.
What I want is to give and take.
I think the kids are being wise.
It's a huge waste of money.
I had a fancy wedding, but it was useless.
I was actually proud of them today.
They obviously gave it a lot of thought.
It's because you're only his aunt.
You'd feel different if you were his mom.
And didn't you hear?
They want him to be like their son.
Over my dead body!
A wedding isn't a joke.
No wedding gift?
You get only one wedding!
I can't blame anyone.
Gwangbak's so stupid.
I heard single father in laws are horrible.
I can see how miserable she'll be.
You embarrassed yourself at lunch.
Why? I asked what needed to be asked.
Why would you mention doctors and judges?
How could he hold an audition?
They're all the same!
Daughter in law audition? I'd never!
I couldn't believe my ears.
Oh, that's one down.
Now that our parents have met,
we can start planning for our wedding.
My husband.
You'll be my husband now.
But I'm worried about my mom.
I'm worried about my father.
I'll see your mother once in a while,
but you'll see my father every day.
Can you deal with that?
With the power of love, I shall endure!
Yes!
I won the daughter in law audition.
We won't let anything bother us.
You take your mother and I'll take my father.
And don't pass on any bad news.
Okay.
We can do it.
Sangnam.
I can't believe what you did!
Why would you enter an audition?
How can you be so man-crazy?
You danced with random girls and raced carrying a pillow?
You even did a triathlon?
Had I known, I wouldn't have said yes.
Is he a prince?
Is he a millionaire?
Have you no pride?
I can't believe you're doing this.
You auditioned to marry a high school dropout?
That audition thing was too much.
Why did you come?
What do you think?
It's because you're my son.
I wasn't there for you,
and I'm going to make it up starting now.
I don't know what your dad told you,
but that's not the truth.
You should hear my side, too.
I have so much to tell you.
But we'll do that later.
I couldn't help it.
I hope you understand.
I've always missed you, Sangnam.
The few years I have left in life,
I'd like to dedicate to you, beg for forgiveness.
I'm over him.
We're done for good.
I had to act like I wasn't happy to see you because of him. I had to.
You understand, right?
He's been beating me all this time.
Sangnam, I don't want anything else.
I just want to be able to see you.
Who's decision was it to skip gifts?
Was it that rude girl's idea?
No, it wasn't, father.
She didn't talk you into it?
She wouldn't, and I wouldn't fall for it.
You should know me better than that.
And stop calling her "that rude girl."
She'll be my wife.
She'll be your daughter in law.
We don't know that yet.
I won't let you do it like this.
How dare she try to skip buying furniture and wedding gifts for her in laws?
But we don't need any new furniture.
And wedding gifts are useless.
Think of this as you getting a daughter.
That's gift enough.
They're getting a son, too!
I want to do everything other people do.
Oh, you're not being yourself.
Father, please let us do what we want.
It they offer,
I would say, "Oh, there's no need."
That's how it should be done.
You can't just announce it like this.
I'm the one getting married here.
Making money isn't easy.
So I don't want to waste it on that.
I'd rather invest it in my company or put it towards buying a house.
Father, we're not losing anything here.
We're actually getting a family member.
They're losing a daughter.
If anything, they should be mad.
Don't you think so, father?
He's fallen completely for that rude girl!
And I was so good to him!
I feel like I'm losing my son.
All parents with sons feel that they're losing their sons to the wives.
Wait and see.
He'll act like their son and not mine.
That rude girl will make him.
Just look at her mom!
They'll partner up and make him miserable.
You're acting like an evil mother in law.
What is it?
Did father say something?
You should try to understand your father.
I was proud of you both,
but your father might feel disappointed.
He's different from other fathers.
He raised you alone all those years.
He's not only been a dad, but a mom, too.
Don't try to force him.
Give in a little.
That'll make things easier for Gwangbak.
We want to do this our way.
If we give an inch, he'll take a mile.
It's not just our family.
Gwangbak's family must want something, too.
And our plans will be ruined.
Then try talking to him nicely.
Or you'll make things hard for Gwangbak.
For some reason, you're being really harsh on your father about your marriage.
It's because I have to.
He deserves compassion.
You know it, too.
Being a single father isn't easy.
I'm raising Miho by myself,
but it is far from easy.
For men, it's even harder.
You should rest.
Aunt Sunjeong.
Yes?
It's nothing.
What is it?
Maybe later.
Okay.
Sangnam,
how many years do you think I have left?
I want to be there for you.
These are the most popular items.
Women just love them.
And these are some samples.
They are all the samples we have.
You like samples.
What's going on?
You didn't want to give me any before.
Anyway, thank you.
Hobak,
about Sedal...
Don't talk to me about him.
Can you take Sedal back?
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
Hobak.
Over my dead body.
Why? He wants to come back now?
Why wouldn't he?
He has his sons!
I can't even reach him, so please tell him
to meet me tomorrow noon at the courthouse.
I can't reach him.
I don't know where he is.
I don't believe you.
I know you're in touch with him.
I don't want these.
Please, take them.
I won't talk about him.
Hey! Hey! What are you doing?
Get away from there.
That's my place!
It's first come first...
Okay.
I was trying to keep it warm for you.
Good night.
I'm going to work.
Oh, you should have breakfast.
I don't have time for it.
Wake the boys up and send them to school.
Sit down and have a bite.
You can't go to work on an empty stomach.
I made tofu stew, your favorite.
I'm not hungry.
And find a place to move out to.
Well, Hobak.
If we moved out, will you take Sedal back?
Don't try to negotiate with me.
Nothing you say will change my mind.
You're so mean!
You should give your husband a chance.
How can you be so selfish?
You should think of your sons.
Don't you feel feel sorry for them?
They miss their dad!
You want them to grow up fatherless?
They'll have to deal with it.
I can't help it.
Please find an apartment and move out.
Oh, Sedal's driving me crazy!
Why did you have him in the first place?
Don't say that.
My heart is breaking for him.
Just thinking of him makes me cry.
Where is he staying?
He was kicked out in his boxers.
I can't help but cry.
- Come back for more.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy your meal.
I'm home.
Have you been to the hospital?
Hospital?
I'm not sick.
Where your father in law is!
He has a caregiver.
And I'm busy.
But you're his daughter in law.
You should visit.
He's being discharged soon.
Hello.
He just fell asleep.
Thanks for everything.
The bed sheet looks a bit...
Try to replace them often.
I changed it just now.
Just do as I say.
Don't talk back to me.
Have you done this for a long time?
Excuse me?
Yes, a bit...
Other caregivers bring food from home.
Uh, what's that smell?
Did you give him a bath?
How can she give him a bath?
Why not?
She's a caregiver.
We're paying her!
She should keep him clean.
Thank you.
You should go home.
Okay.
Excuse me,
can you do something for me before you go?
What is it? It's late. Let her go home.
It's nothing difficult.
There's a juice place outside.
Get me some juice.
I came straight from work and I'm thirsty.
I'll go and get it.
It's okay. I'll get it.
Keep the change.
How can you ask her to do that?
Why not? We're paying her.
She's a caregiver for my father.
Making her get juice is too much.
What? You're overreacting.
She said yes.
I told her she could keep the change.
People might think you have feelings for her.
Oh, you're here.
Yes, father.
I'm here, too.
It's been a while.
No it hasn't.
It's only been a few days.
I've been visiting often.
Before it was just on holidays.
You look good.
No, I'm exhausted from working.
Father, would you like a different caregiver?
I heard you need a very good caregiver.
The one you have seems a bit slow.
She's not slow.
She's really good.
I'm so grateful because she's so caring.
Treat her to dinner and thank her.
Why would I do that?
You're being silly.
Dad!
The class is over?
Bangtong isn't home yet.
Okay.
Hey! Heo Bangtong!
What took you so long?
You should come straight home!
Where were you?
Whatever!
What the...
Ugh...
I'm too scared to go home.
Me too.
I'm probably the only person who's
afraid to get kicked out by her daughter in law.
Mother!
Mother. Yeongdal.
Wake up.
Mother!
I know you're not asleep.
Get up. We need to talk.
Mother! Yeongdal!
Mother!
Yeongdal!
This won't solve anything.
I won't give up, you know?
If you keep this up, I'm going to take care of this my way.
Oh, I can't do this.
What do we do, mom?
I'm not trying to be presumptuous.
I hope you understand that.
I won't, Aunt Sunjeong.
You heard about Sangnam's childhood?
His father went through a lot trying to raise Sangnam.
It's not easy for a young man to not marry and raise a child alone.
It must be upsetting to see his precious son
get married and have nothing to show for.
I'd feel that way, too.
I like the idea of being down to earth, but...
I think I understand what you mean.
Nothing too extravagant, something simple.
Sangnam will say no, so don't tell him.
Do you understand what I mean?
What she said makes sense.
He only has his father and his aunt, right?
Proper wedding gifts are important.
That's how the Korean society is like.
Your way is great,
but get something for his father.
My mother in law treats me badly still for that.
That hurt me a lot.
You'll live with him after you're married,
so I think it's better to show respect.
Show your appreciation.
It's not about the gift.
It's the thought that counts.
Where's your daughter's wedding invitations?
Small weddings are popular, I heard.
We're keeping it simple.
We're not inviting any guests.
But it's a wedding! Don't keep it a secret.
My husband wants to keep it simple.
Where are you having it?
We're renting a restaurant.
Why is it so hush hush?
Is Gwangbak pregnant?
She's not pregnant!
Hobak got married because she got pregnant.
I remember how she was all upset.
Ugh...
What does he do?
He runs a company.
He's the president.
She won't have any money trouble.
Everyone these days is a CEO.
What kind of wedding gifts did you get?
He must have sent so much!
We got all sorts of things!
Diamonds, pearls, rubies, sapphires.
He covered the basics.
Isn't he a high school dropout?
He's a high school dropout?
Huh? I didn't say that.
Okay, okay, okay, okay. Oh my!
Okay, okay.
Mom, when are you coming?
This is crazy!
Hurry up and come home!
You take care of him today.
I haven't been out in so long.
He's your son so take care of him.
I'm hanging up.
Things are crazy in your family, too.
My daughter in law is babysitting for me.
Grandmothers aren't the nannies!
The government should do something.
Or we should get paid properly,
so we can plan for retirement.
But they won't really pay us.
They give whatever they can afford.
Yes, and I can't force them to pay me.
I know how hard it is for them.
But you can't let them take advantage of you.
Tell your children to pay you $1,000 a month.
The problem is that I'm getting sick.
And I'm worried that he'll get hurt.
What if he gets sick?
I feel like it's my fault. It's crazy.
Right. Who would understand that?
Unless you've experienced it, too.
I'm nervous my daughter in law might get mad.
But isn't it better if it's your daughter?
It's worse.
I feel shamed before my son in law!
My daughter's worse than ten daughter in laws.
She's worse than my husband.
Why would you raise your grandchildren?
You raised your own children, and that's enough.
My friend got arthritis from raising her grandkids.
I'm starting to feel it.
It hurts everywhere.
I told my kids I'm not doing it.
How do you keep yourself busy?
Raising my grandkid makes me happy.
Sure it's hard, but it brings so much joy.
It beats having a puppy.
He's so cute I can just eat him up.
Right, that's why I do it.
What about your life?
You worked hard all your life,
so why would you raise your grandkids?
If you have free time, find things to do.
Right, right.
Go singing and exercising.
Don't let your grandkid become your life.
Make your children pay you.
Will they take care of you if you get sick?
You can save the money for when you're old.
I should do that.
What are you doing?
Homework.
Do you want pizza?
Should I buy you pizza?
No, thanks.
You don't want pizza?
No.
I thought pizza was your favorite.
Not anymore.
Mom always gets it for us, so we got sick of it.
Sick of pizza?
Why you little...
Don't be ungrateful when I'm trying to be nice.
Do you want pizza or not?
You're weird!
You never bought us anything!
We don't want pizza.
It's okay, Bangtong. Let's eat it.
You should've said that earlier.
You always try to make me mad.
Hello? Is this the pizza place?
Where is he?
I called ages ago.
It's here!
You boys go to your room.
- Why?
- Hurry, hurry!
I thought you wanted to buy us pizza!
Here's your pizza.
You're the delivery boy?
No, the man paid me a dollar to deliver this.
Sintong! Bangtong! Come out and eat!
Wow! Oh!
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
Why won't you come to my house?
You're ignoring me?
Why did you make that boy deliver it?
Because I wanted to!
This is crazy.
On top of feeling horrible, I feel dirty!
Why are you acting this way?
What do you mean?
I'm furious because a loser like you is ignoring me!
I'm sorry.
I wasn't trying to,
but I don't want anything to do with you.
You must be upset, but I'm upset, too.
I've never made such a huge mistake before.
Let's just forget about the whole thing.
So you're just leaving like that?
You think I have nothing to say?
You had your say.
You said you feel dirty.
Go take a bath.
What are you doing, mom?
There's no room to put this in.
I should clean out the fridge or something.
You're putting the cutting board in the fridge?
Huh?
Mom, you're doing it again.
Why don't you put that in the wardrobe, then?
What's wrong with me?
I've been so absent minded.
This is all your fault!
I was humiliated when I met with friends.
I'll live happily ever after, mom.
I'll throw a party for all your friends.
Forget it.
You know the money you've been keeping for me?
Can I get it back?
What for?
I need to use some and I'm going to manage it.
You're not buying any furniture or gifts,
so why would you need your money now?
We're going to open our financial state and build a portfolio.
He's told me all about his.
You saw it at lunch.
You must be crazy.
Why would you tell him?
It's your money.
Why would you tell him about it?
He told me about his money.
We need to make plans for our future.
You idiot!
Why would you take money to him?
Did he ask you to?
No, I thought...
Leave your bank book with me.
You can come to me when you need money.
Can I just have it?
You're so dense.
I agree.
Kids never appreciate their parents efforts.
She thinks I'm going to keep her money.
I'll give it to you when it's time.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know it would upset you.
Since I'm getting married,
I thought I should manage it.
Ugh!
Oh, how could you be so inconsiderate?
You were a teacher for heaven's sake.
Give that money to mom.
Give it to mom?
Yes. You won't need it now.
Sangnam's rich, so why do you need it?
I envy you.
You must be full of love, marrying a rich man.
Marring a rich man fills you with love?
Of course.
That hormone or something?
What was that?
Dopamine, endorphin, oxytocin, phenyl ethylamine?
Oh, yes!
They come out when you see money.
They're released when you fall in love!
When you see a rich man,
he looks so handsome,
and you miss him all day.
Aren't they the same hormones?
You're excited about money.
Material girl.
Who isn't material these days?
If a man came to you driving an imported car,
buys you a designer handbag,
takes you to an expensive French restaurant to wine and dine you, you'd fall for him.
Women who've never met men like that use phrases like "material girl."
Look at me.
My marriage went south when money disappeared.
When we had money, we never fought.
Now we fight whenever we see each other.
And there's no release of hormones at all!
- Hello.
- Oh, I remember you!
It's nice to meet you.
This place is very important for a ship.
For humans, it would be like the head, so to speak.
Where are you coming from?
Uh, I met a friend.
Become and judge so I can move out with you.
I hate them all.
I hate Subak and Gwangbak.
A captain?
You're going to become a captain?
Yes.
Didn't you want to become a judge?
I never said I wanted to become a judge.
It was mom and dad.
But they think you're going to law school.
How could you do this?
It's too late now.
I got into the Maritime University.
What am I going to do with you?
I thought you would understand me.
You quit teaching to become a writer.
I know!
That's why you should do what mom and dad want.
What did you do when you quit?
I talked to father about it.
How could you do this?
You should've at least talked to father.
I'm going to become a captain.
The best female captain in the world.
Fine. But keep it to yourself for now.
We'll tell them after things settle down.
Oh, this is insane.
Where's my father?
With a client.
Can you give me $5,000?
For what?
I need it for something.
But please don't tell my father.
How have you been, my darling son?
Have you eaten?
I lost my appetite.
How can I eat at a time like this?
I can't even live with you.
Would you like to go and eat?
No.
When I'm with you, I feel full.
Chewing gum helps me forget.
I didn't realize this before,
but being able to see you makes me happy.
Here.
- What is it?
- It's not much.
Don't stay in Seoul for me.
And you should work things out with him.
I'm not going back.
I'm sick and tired of him.
You're making me uncomfortable.
But I'm your mom! Silly.
Sangnam, let's be friends, okay?
You wanting it is enough for me.
I better get going.
Take care.
Come in.
It's clean.
How much is the rent?
How long are you planning to stay?
Who knows?
I could be a month or two months.
I want this place.
Sunjeong!
Yes?
Find out what people do about wedding gifts.
For what?
Just find out.
Ugh...
What's wrong?
You want to go ahead with this wedding?
We already met his family and everything.
I don't know how to make this work.
I even tried putting myself in their shoes.
Do we have to let her marry him?
What's wrong? What don't you like?
I hate everything. Everything.
She's not getting any jewelry,
and her wedding will be at a restaurant.
All my friends were asking me why I'm marrying my daughter off like that.
We got plenty of blessings for Subak and Hobak's weddings. Isn't that enough?
But I gave my friends lots of gift money!
It's all about giving and taking.
I'm mad I'm not getting a doctor son in law,
and Gwangbak's only getting a ring?
And she had to audition on top of everything?
I feel humiliated.
Don't you?
You're not happy, are you?
Why did Gwangbak have to audition?
Why do you think she went through with it?
She's in love.
That's why she did it.
We can't cancel the wedding.
Not after meeting his father.
We can if we really wanted to.
Don't say that.
It's bad luck to say that.
When you go over to their place tomorrow,
be polite.
Say we'll do everything they want.
And don't say anything else.
I'm furious.
She asked me for her bank book today.
You should give it to her.
Were you planning on keeping it?
- Han Taeju!
- Yes!
- Good job.
- Thank you.
- Ko Minho!
- Yes!
- Good job. I'm serious.
- Thank you.
Oh, Heo Sedal.
Yes, thank you.
Here.
- Ju Minsik.
- Let's hurry it up!
- Ju Minsuk.
- Oh, yes.
- Hobak.
- You're home? How was your day?
Hobak, isn't it cold outside?
I'm going to give you a facial.
I gave the boys a bath and put them to bed.
I checked their homework and got them school supplies.
Come lie down.
We'll give you a facial.
No, thanks.
Give this to the boys.
If you don't sign that right now,
I'm taking you to court.
Meet me at the courthouse by noon tomorrow.
Sedal! Sedal!
Don't do this!
Don't go. Please talk to me.
Stop this, please!
I said I'm sorry.
Let me go!
Look. I have nothing.
Isn't this a great parting gift?
Nobody would ask for a divorce on their wedding anniversary except you.
Hey! I have nothing to do with this woman!
I don't care if she lives or dies!
What was that?
Sorry. Yeongdal broke that vacuuming.
I'm sorry. I was trying to help.
Why won't you let me sleep?
Clean that up before the boys get up.
Okay.
Hobak,
I shined your shoes.
Even your shoes are pretty, like you.
Hobak, I prepared breakfast.
Have some.
I'm not hungry.
I have an early meeting.
Just have a bite.
I made all your favorites.
Yes, Hobak.
Just have a bite, for mom.
I got up really early to cook these.
Have some.
You wasted your energy.
I'm not changing my mind, so stop trying.
Living together is uncomfortable for everyone.
I'm not uncomfortable.
We've been living like this forever.
I'm not uncomfortable either, Hobak.
I don't feel hurt when you yell at me.
Have some breakfast.
What more can I say so you'd understand?
I don't my ex's mother cooking for me.
I'll get indigestion.
Don't say that.
You're not legally divorced yet.
It's almost as if we are.
Legally, you're still married.
So you stop that.
Divorcing won't do you any good either,
unless you're seeing someone.
Mother.
You were happy about my divorce.
Did you forget that?
I just can't understand you.
Why won't you move out?
Hobak.
Move out as quickly as you can.
I'm divorcing Sedal no matter what.
I don't know why you're doing this to me.
Then give me money.
Excuse me?
This apartment is in Sedal's name, too.
I'm not leaving empty handed.
If you don't want to, take us to court.
Is that what you really want?
I have all the evidence, including the bank books.
I can prove Sedal didn't contribute anything.
Your son's law school years must have rubbed off on you.
Fine! Take us to court!
How could you be so mean?
I'm groveling like this!
The least you can do is let it slide.
How could you be so heartless/
Mom, stop it.
Hobak, I'm sorry.
She's just upset, so don't mind her.
Let's say it was all my son's fault.
But don't you know you gave him the reason?
You made him cheat on you!
You mistreated him, caring only about money.
How did your parents treat him?
They treated him like dirt!
They always yelled at him.
He left you because he couldn't take it anymore!
Mom.
A man could make a mistake.
How could you ask for a divorce over that?
God will punish you!
I'll receive the punishment gladly.
Whatever you say, I won't budge.
Move out right now!
Mom!
What do you think you're doing?
This is my house and these are my things!
You're so mean!
Am I your housekeeper?
How could you treat me like this?
Am I a beggar?
How can you tell me to move out?
I'm still your mother in law.
How could you act this way?
I'm begging for your forgiveness,
but you won't even listen!
Where can we go in the middle of winter?
You'd treat beggars better than me!
How could you be so inconsiderate?
Your mom hates you because you're like this!
You're heartless and mean!
Nobody knows how life will turn out.
You think your luck won't ever run out?
We'll see about that!
Have a great life!
Hurry up!
Oh, hold on, hold on.
I think you should just leave!
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, this is crazy.
Mom...
Excuse me...
Sedal...
Sedal!
Sedal! Sedal! It's me, your mom!
Sedal! A thief!
Mom...
Oh, my god...
What happened to you, Sedal!
- Mom...
- Oh, Sedal!
Oh, Sedal...
Bounce, bounce...
Where are you going?
To my in law's. But who knows if he'll really become my in law.
Hey, watch what you say.
Don't ruin this, okay?
Mother...
Bounce, bounce.
Pounding, bounce.
Come in.
Daese.
You're here.
Yes.
Have a seat.
There's no need.
She me their room.
Come this way.
Sunjeong, wait.
I'll take her.
Follow me.
They need a bed and a dresser, right?
Don't just go anywhere.
Here.
We buy our furniture from here, so go here.
Get the style that goes with what we have.
I want antique style furniture.
It's up to us.
Why should we have to go here?
The style has to go with what we have.
Both the color and the size.
Let's go down.
The kids said no furniture or wedding gifts,
but I think we should cover the basics.
That way, I won't have to lie to my friends.
He's my only son.
I heard mother in laws get mink coats and designer handbags.
Mink coats and designer handbags?
I can't believe my ears.
It's not like your son's a doctor.
He only graduated from middle school.
What did you just say?
I was just talking to myself.
I'm being really accommodating.
They'll take turns visiting during holidays and give allowance only on birthdays and holidays.
There are two of you but only one of me.
What does that have to do with anything?
You're acting like a real cheapskate.
Excuse me?
Don't you think so?
You're nit-picking about money.
If that's what you want, let's do it formally.
What will you get for my daughter?
Excuse me, I don't feel comfortable butting in,
but I think you should stop.
This isn't what the kids want.
You should work together, as their parents.
Who cares what others think?
You're not his mom, so don't butt in.
I'm sorry.
While we're at it, let me ask you something.
Why do you hate my daughter so much?
Can I be frank about it?
Go ahead.
She's just so rude!
My daughter's rude?
The best bride material in town is rude?
Haven't you heard?
Why do you think I had that audition?
It was all because of your daughter.
My son has a weird taste in women!
I didn't say yes because I like her.
What's so great about your son?
He's a high school dropout heavy equipment operator!
How dare you put my daughter through the humiliation of auditioning?
Ask anyone if what you did was right!
What? A high school dropout?
How could you say that?
Why can't I?
Tell me what's so great about your son!
Audition?
My daughter was crazy for entering that,
but you're not normal either.
Sunjeong, water! With ice!
I can't let my daughter marry into this family.
Let's cancel the wedding!
Cancel it?
Fine.
Let's cancel it.
Subtitles by KBS World
I told him we're canceling the wedding.
You canceled the wedding?
Gwangbak's not getting married?
Cancel the wedding.
What?
Stop this nonsense!
Let's go home.
I can't, not like this.
I'll come home when I'm successful.
It's weird. I can't help it. I just like him.
What are you doing?
You won't listen so I took action.
You're just so mean!
I'm mean?
She dumped him, so he wants to come back?
Don't even dream about it.
I didn't imagine that, did I?
Wasn't that the bastard?
He doesn't deserve to be called that.