Subtitles by KBS World
This is my house.
My oldest niece used to live here.
Right. I was her landlady.
I rent these out,
and I live at the top, alone.
Okay.
Semi real estate tycoon.
I get a lot of money in rent.
I have no financial trouble.
I can support a man.
Do you want me to buy you a car?
A car?
I can afford to buy you a car.
Don, you should get a woman like me.
This house is over $300,000.
That's big money.
You don't see that everyday.
Come inside for some tea.
There's nobody home.
No thanks.
I'm not the type who's stingy with money.
I splurge. Like how I spent lots at that Japanese restaurant.
Yes, you do splurge. Like mad.
Good night.
We need to say goodbye properly.
Mom!
Agh!
- What?
- Don!
Don!
How did it go?
It went well, didn't it?
I'll talk to you later.
Is she pretty?
I think he's too shy to talk about it.
Tell me if things go well.
Hey,
I'm dying to know.
What does she look like?
She's rich?
Ii heard she's rich and single.
What is it?
You didn't like her?
She's scary.
Why is she scary?
I can't explain.
Why you little...
Get married so I can come live with you.
Take a look.
Incredible.
Grandmother, you're up for lunch today.
What?
Lunch is grandmother and uncle.
The older person goes first because father went first last night.
You have to give me a break. I'm old.
No exceptions, grandmother.
Right, father?
Huh? Yes, right.
You're really making the winner marry Sangnam?
That's not right.
You need to know when to be stubborn.
If you're always stubborn, you look like a jerk.
If I can break that rude girl,
I don't care if I look like a jerk.
Man...
The final one is the physical test!
If you want to live long as a happy couple,
you need a sound body and a sound mind.
Patience, resilience, endurance!
You must use every ounce of energy!
I'll lead the way.
Ready!
Go!
- Number 4, faster!
- Run! Run!
Number 4, run faster!
Jangbi! Number 1!
- Number 4!
- Number 1!
- Number 4! 4!
- Yes! Number 1!
- Number 4!
- Run!
A little more!
Number 4, a little more!
Run! Jangbi!
Number 1! Number 1! Yes!
Number 4!
- Jangbi...
- Number 4! Number 4!
Mom! I won first place!
You did?
Aunt! Aunt!
We will award the plaque to the winner.
We name you the winner of Choi Daese's
Daughter in law Auditions!
Thank you.
It's your turn to do the dishes, mom.
I'm going to work.
Anggeum, I'm leaving.
Don't you have any warm rice tea?
Rice tea?
It's cold.
Give me some warm tea.
Grandmother ran away.
Thank you!
Smile!
Man...
Gwangbak!
You're incredible!
Father! Thank you!
Thank you for everything!
Oh, man...
Mom.
How did it go?
I didn't make it.
What?
You spent so much money on learning things,
so how come you didn't win?
You can dance, you can run,
you can play the gayageum, and you're cute!
I wasn't a good student.
So why would you embarrass yourself like that there?
People will talk about you failing now!
How humiliating!
Don't even come home!
Man...
Mom!
What's this?
The person on lunch duty didn't do the dishes.
This isn't working out.
There's no order in the family,
and nobody respects you.
We posted that up so everyone would follow.
"You're home?"
and she'll fake some illness.
You deal with her, if you want to fall for it.
Leave them. I'll do them.
Oh, I'll do them.
Why would you?
It's not your turn.
Step aside.
Go easy on them.
You'll break them all.
Wash this one again.
Oh, you're creating more work.
Wash this one again, too.
Should I go get Bong?
He's good at this.
God will punish you.
Let him, then.
Hello, father.
Hi.
I heard you went on a business trip.
What's up?
I brought some pork belly.
Have you eaten?
Thanks. I was worried about what to cook.
So why did you bring pork belly?
I'm going to start spending money now.
I'll get you better meat next time.
Where's grandmother?
She's doing the dishes.
Huh? Grandmother is?
Things changed, thanks to Minjung.
Everyone's taking turns doing house chores.
Oh, wow! That's great.
Minjung is better than any of you.
But you shouldn't make mother do it, too.
She's healthy,
so it's better if she does some chores.
My sentiment exactly!
I'm home.
- Hi.
- You're back?
- Was it a research trip?
Yes. I brought someone.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Welcome.
- Come in.
- It's been a while.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
It's about meeting my father.
When does he want to do it?
He thought we could do it this weekend.
That sounds good.
Did you come just to tell us that?
Yes, I really wanted to tell you this.
I know you're in a hurry
but you followed her home
from her business trip?
You must really love her.
I'll tell you about that another time.
I should go.
I'll come back and visit again.
Stay for dinner.
We're having pork belly.
It's okay.
I have to get back to work.
Oh, okay, then.
I'll see you this weekend.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Take care.
- Bye.
Take care.
Get some rest.
You must be tired.
No.
You shouldn't do this here.
I'll call you later.
Let's celebrate.
Mother, doesn't the food taste better after doing the dishes?
Don't talk to me.
The pork belly tastes really good.
Well,
I have something to tell you.
Congratulate me.
I'm getting a divorce.
- What did you say?
- Divorce?
Please don't say anything.
I've made my decision, so please accept it.
It's not a big secret,
but until Gwangbak's wedding,
I'd like to keep it in the family.
Oh, this feels weird.
I'm fine, so congratulate me.
I don't have an ounce of regret.
And I'm completely over him.
Making the decision was hard,
but now I'm glad it's over.
I'll be really happy.
I'm sure of it.
My mother in law always says you never know how your life will turn out.
Do you want to go singing?
My treat.
Man!
Hey, start clapping your hands.
It's raining,
and I'm on the train to the south! Clap!
As I look out the window!
Woohoo!
There are raindrops, yeah!
And there are my tears!
The mobile phone has been turned off,
so you'll be directed to voice mail.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes.
So this isn't all an act?
No.
Thanks for being on my side.
Of course, we're family.
Let me know if you need me.
I'll teach Goof-off a lesson.
There's no need for that.
We're strangers now.
Hobak.
Yes, father?
Have a seat.
Are you okay?
I think this is for the best, father.
I'm trying to be positive about it.
Things may get tougher than you think.
Our society isn't kind to divorced women.
It's a difficult world for women.
Money issue aside,
there are times when a man comes in handy.
And raising two boys won't be easy.
And they are sons, not daughters.
Boys need their dad sometimes.
I know.
I'm okay with everything else,
but I feel like I'm taking their dad away.
That really breaks my heart.
But father,
I've given it my all, so I have no regrets.
I...
Even got kidnapped.
What are you talking about?
You got kidnapped? When?
It wasn't real.
I just wanted to test him...
But...
He wasn't any different.
Even when my life was on the line.
What more could I do?
If I was kidnapped,
he should try to rescue me, no matter what.
But he turned his phone off.
That's not family.
I don't want to spend my life with him.
How could you do that?
I didn't want to lose him.
No,
I think I was trying to let him go.
I had to be sure,
so I can let him go without any regrets.
He was
my first love.
Father,
I'm only 36.
I'm not going to live foolishly anymore.
If the boys need a dad,
there's you and uncle.
And if that doesn't work,
they'll just have to tough it out.
You must have been in a lot of pain.
Can you really get over him?
I'll have to.
I think I can now.
I've tried everything,
so I have no regrets.
Oh, man...
What is it?
Ugh...
Ah ah.
What do I do?
What should I do?
Ugh...
I am...
What's wrong with you?
We're here to sing, so stop that!
What's wrong, Don?
Things were going great last night.
Don, I think this is destiny.
I feel like spending lots of money on you.
I don't care about any destiny,
and I don't want you spending money on me.
I appreciate you buying dinner last night,
so I'll pay for this.
Don!
Don! Don!
A bottle of soju, please.
What are you doing here?
Don't talk to me.
You don't have an empty table?
Oh, I don't.
He's alone.
Can you sit with him?
Is it okay if she sits with you?
She's really pretty.
Oh, you're a handsome man.
Sit, sit.
Sit down.
Give me a bottle of soju.
Where are you coming from?
Are you running away from home?
I went on a trip.
I said don't talk to me.
If you're coming back from a trip,
why are you drinking here alone?
Who did you go with?
Stop asking me stuff like that.
Ah...
You're not eating anything?
I'll gain weight.
You can't drink on an empty stomach.
Should I order you something?
No thanks.
I don't eat with just anyone.
I'm not just anyone.
I'm your brother's friend.
No thanks, Gwangbak's uncle.
How embarrassing.
Pretend you don't know me.
Stop looking at me!
Tell me when there's an empty table.
I think you should keep sitting together.
You two look good together.
Don't you dare say that!
Another bottle please!
How annoying!
Where's my gift for winning the audition?
Oh, I forgot.
What would you like?
What's that in your pocket?
My pocket?
You said you threw them out.
I was going to,
but I couldn't because they were so expensive.
I'm so materialistic!
We promised, remember?
Let's not ever take them off again.
Okay.
We never will.
But I'm worried about this weekend.
Your father and my mom won't be easy to handle.
Let's just keep moving forward.
How?
Yeongdal,
you were much prettier before the surgery.
I said don't talk to me.
You think I like you?
No thank you.
You're not my style.
How dare you! You loser!
What?
You are a loser.
You have no real job,
and you never had a relationship. Loser.
How about you?
You only care for money,
and look what happened to you!
I know you were after a rich man.
Getting bigger boobs did you no good!
What?
You better not say that again!
I'll kill you.
Excuse me!
Give each of us a bottle of soju! Separately!
I'm so upset.
Hello.
I lost because of common sense!
I'm stupid!
Goodbye.
Come again.
Agh! Hey!
Mom!
Man!
Why...
Tell me what happened! Now!
Why are you screaming?
This is crazy!
You forced me here, didn't you?
Am I crazy?
Why would I do that?
Turn around, so I can get dressed.
This is just awful!
What do I do?
This is crazy.
How about me?
It's not awful for me?
What?
I never follow anyone out.
Did you seduce me?
Are you mad?
I seduced you?
You forced me here!
How will you fix this?
You got drunk and you blacked out.
- Hey!
- Oh, my!
Ask anyone whose fault this is.
Mom...
Stop crying!
This is humiliating!
This is awful!
I'm ruined!
This is horrible!
It's not horrible.
You got lucky.
I got lucky?
This is me getting lucky?
It's horrible!
I'm the one who feels horrible here.
Let me go! Let me go!
How dare you! You're a loser!
This is humiliating!
I never want to see you again.
Don't tell anyone about this.
I won't be able to get married.
Oh, my!
Look who's talking!
Hey! Loser!
Oh...
Where were you?
You told me not to come home!
So you didn't come home?
How dare you!
- Where did you sleep?
- At a sauna.
Why are you screaming?
You failed the audition!
I've had horrible luck!
Totally horrible!
I'm never going back to that sauna again!
Huh?
What the...
Uncle, you're just getting in?
Did you have a good time?
What?
You were with her?
We waited up for you until midnight.
You're home?
Were you with that woman you met?
We should start planning for the wedding!
What wedding?
I drank all night alone.
Subak, she kept doing this!
I know I have nothing to offer, but still!
This is all because of her!
What are you talking about?
Forget it!
Get up.
You're not going to work?
Forget it!
If you didn't tell me not to come home,
this would've never happened!
What? What happened?
Mother, there's something I must tell you.
What is it?
Can you come out?
Yeongdal, you too.
What? You're getting a divorce?
Are you serious?
Yes.
Oh, good for you.
You should've done so a long time ago.
You thought about it during your trip?
Are you serious?
She said yes.
You should live your life now.
You two weren't meant to be together.
Sedal would've never married you if you didn't get knocked up.
So many people get married because of that.
I just don't understand them.
I know lots of girls who did that.
They meet someone, test the waters, get pregnant and get married.
This apartment is in both our names,
but you know I bought it, don't you?
- So I was thinking...
- It's okay.
It's not even a lot of money.
You don't need to split it.
Just take it.
You'll be raising the kids, right?
I wasn't going to give you anything.
But for now,
you and Yeongdal will have to move out,
- so you'll need...
- It's okay.
Keep your money.
We're not after your money.
Sedal will take care of it, I'm sure.
He met a very rich woman.
He might just buy us an apartment.
Right.
So you figure out how to fend for yourself.
Congratulations on your divorce.
The phone has been turned off,
so your will be directed to voice mail.
Your brother won't answer.
And he hasn't called in a while.
He hasn't called me either.
He lives in heaven, so he forgot us.
He must be having a party every day.
Should we drop by with Sintong and Bangtong?
What's this?
Yellow corvina stew.
Oh, it looks delicious.
You should eat it while its hot.
You must be busy with your father and work.
It's cold, so you need some hot food.
Hurry up and eat.
Thank you, mother.
Don't thank me.
We're family.
Subak's making things hard for you, right?
Looking back,
I think I spoiled her too much.
Everyone was disappointed she wasn't a son,
so I treated her like a princess.
No other man could put up with her, I know.
I'm glad I moved in here.
If it were just the two of us,
we'd be fighting all the time.
Living with you and father makes me happy.
Thank you for saying that.
Where's my gray suit?
Mmm... That smells delicious.
I made some yellow corvina stew.
Minjung loves it.
Have some.
You eat.
You have to go to work soon.
Mother, it's really delicious.
I'm glad. Eat up.
Why can't you be nice to me like that?
What do you mean?
Why wouldn't you cook me something?
Then you be nice to me like him.
What?
When I burned my foot, he rushed me to the hospital.
Who else would do that for me?
You realize that now?
I learned that a long time ago!
I was just upset about his company.
What if I got kidnapped.
What would you do?
I'd say good riddance.
You won't pay ransom to get me back?
Why would I want to get an old man back?
What would you do if I got kidnapped?
I'd pay them and thank them for taking you.
How dare you!
I shouldn't be laughing.
Now we're going to have a daughter who's divorced.
That's why they say there are no certainties in life.
And nobody can predict it.
If it's possible, I want my kids to avoid divorcing,
but if it isn't, what could we do?
Hobak seems like she's in a hard place,
but she might be better off without him.
Having to raise the boys alone will be difficult, I'm sure.
Of course it will be.
Having a husband is a big deal.
You knew that?
Right now?
Okay, Mr. Seo.
Let's go.
He want us now?
Yes.
Mr. Seo wants to see us right now.
No! I have to go to Aeji's play!
Aeji's playing? But we're busy.
No, Aeji's in a play.
Mr. Seo likes you, so you have to come.
Call home. Hurry.
Oh...
Why didn't you answer your mobile phone?
Oh, I'm busy.
I was working in the kitchen.
I can't come to Aeji's play today.
That's not good!
Aeji will be mad.
I know. Can you go?
What?
Mom, I'm sorry.
Subak!
Oh!
Oh, no.
Oh.
Oh, I have to take care of Jungji!
Mother! Oh...
Oh...
Mother, you didn't have to come.
I have to.
Everyone else's mom and dad are here.
I don't want Aeji to feel neglected.
Aeji's grandmother!
Welcome.
Oh, hello, Mrs. Principal.
Where's Aeji's mom?
She's busy.
You must be Aeji's dad.
Yes, he's my son in law.
Hello.
Your son in law is handsome.
Isn't he?
And he's so good to me.
He's like my son.
Aeji, your grandmother came.
Where's mom?
Say hello to your grandmother.
Mom's not here, so no!
But grandmother and dad came. Don't pout.
Other moms all look really pretty!
You're just like your mom.
Aeji, break a leg.
Aeji, let's go!
Let's go.
What's that?
Our family.
- Take dad out.
- Why?
Dad's not here.
He never comes home.
No!
Sintong, Bangtong!
Tada!
Mom!
You're home.
What's wrong?
What happened?
Sintong keeps telling me to take dad out.
But there are four people in our family.
Here.
Isn't it yummy?
Yes, it's yummy!
I wish I could eat pizza every day!
Well, Sintong, Bangtong,
I have something to tell you.
I knew it.
You buy us pizza when you need to talk to us.
Dad and I won't be living together anymore.
You're finally getting divorced.
You are?
Mom, don't divorce dad.
Don't cry.
Bangtong, please...
I'm not finished yet.
I'm really sorry, but we couldn't help it.
Please understand.
Then who do we live with?
With me, of course.
But you can see dad whenever you want.
Is that okay?
It's not okay.
I'm okay.
I can live fine without dad.
Mom, I hate you!
Sintong, I hate you!
I don't want to live without dad.
You come with me.
Stop it. Stop!
Why are you acting like a baby?
You think I'm happy here?
Mom's really sad.
If you keep crying like a baby,
it'll make things harder for mom.
Do you want mom to be sad?
I don't.
But I don't want to live without dad.
Dad has changed.
I knew this day would come.
You knew?
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
You're still young.
Lots of my friends parents got divorced.
But they survived it.
You're okay?
I'm pretending to be okay.
You can trust me.
If your friends tease you, tell me.
I'll beat them up for you, okay?
Bangtong, don't make this harder for mom.
Imagine how hard it must be for her.
She has to raise us without dad.
Other moms would have run away.
Mom didn't run away.
But what if I miss dad?
We can see him behind mom's back, stupid.
Oh, stop crying!
Your dad and I went!
You always start crying for no reason!
Oh, you're just like your mom.
Stop it! Stop!
There's my in law!
Oh, we're not in laws anymore.
You missed the meeting with our friends.
You must be busy being the nanny.
Are you happy they're getting a divorce?
You're looking really good.
It's not such a bad thing.
Everyone lives according to their own fate.
Then why are you still living at my daughter's place?
That's none of your business.
I'll leave when I want.
None of my business?
Just look after your own family.
After all, we're not family,
now that the kids are divorced.
Oh, look at all those wrinkles!
How much do you get paid to be in that prison?
You must have gone mad.
You're acting like we'll never see each other.
Are you picking a fight with me?
Don't get upset.
You'll get more wrinkles.
We talked about going to the hot springs,
but you won't make it, will you?
Instead of thinking about going there,
move out of my daughter's apartment!
Who lives with their divorced daughter in law?
Why would you want to mooch off like that?
What's the big deal?
I'm moving out! So don't worry!
Why that...
I don't believe her.
Why is it her business?
As if she ever cared about Hobak!
You're home?
Yes.
Did you find a place?
What place?
The place where you'll move into.
Stop pushing me. I will move out.
I can't believe you two.
Did you tell your mom?
I'm not comfortable with you here.
Rent an apartment or something.
Rent an apartment?
You think I'll rent an apartment?
Please move out as soon as possible.
Fine. I will.
Like mother, like daughter.
Stop nagging.
You're just like your mom, did you know?
Man...
Hey did you hear that?
Let's move out of here, mom.
I'm sick and tire of this place.
Let's move to somewhere really far.
I thought you liked this neighborhood.
I got sick of it last night.
Call Sedal so we can move.
His phone is off again.
He's not ignoring us, is he?
Is he dumping us?
What?
You saw her.
She didn't even say hi to us.
She looks Korean, but she's not.
The concept of taking care of her
in laws may be foreign to her.
No, that can't be.
We just left that day,
but I'm going to teach her a lesson.
I'm going to destroy her.
How rude!
Let's go.
Okay.
I'm going to teach her a lesson, too.
She's dead.
We'll be back.
You're going apartment hunting?
Yes, I am.
You wait and see!
You'll be really sorry!
Hobak, don't be so mean.
It's not like we want to stay here.
Ouch! Hot!
Mom.
What is it?
What did you wear to Aeji's play?
What?
She called me all crying.
What did you wear?
She said you embarrassed her today.
She was embarrassed about what I wore?
Who does that selfish girl take after?
How can you say that?
Why didn't you go and make her feel good?
Why did you ask me to go? Huh?
Grandmother wasn't home,
so I had to take Jungji there.
Am I your nanny?
I couldn't even go to my meeting,
and I can't even go to the spa!
You're not doing this for free!
I pay you!
You can't do this after taking my money!
I should just hire a professional!
What did you just say?
How dare you yell at your mom?
Is your mom a nanny?
What? You pay her?
How much do you pay her?
Do you pay her thousands of dollars?
Wire the money to her account every month and give her days off.
How dare you take advantage of my wife!
You go to that spa.
Just leave the kids here.
Why did you take them in the first place?
Who'll take care of you if you get sick?
If you yell at your mom again,
I'll kick you out of my house!
Oh, man!
Ugh!
You should've come to Aeji's play.
I was at work!
Why does everyone get on my case?
Why do you pick fights with everyone?
Because everyone's picking on me.
Working is hard and mom's always mad.
Now dad's also mad.
So please leave me alone.
Jungji's our kid.
And you're Jungji's mom.
But you leave him with your mother
and yell at her whenever you want.
How could you do that to your mother who had to
carry Jungji on her back to Aeji's play?
You should've disciplined Aeji instead.
You need to make time for the kids.
You should've gotten today off or something.
Why do you make money?
What?
You said you do it for the kids.
Can't you see what's really good for them?
I don't even know what you're up to these days.
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
Your father fell asleep just now.
Sorry I'm late.
I was going to come right over but...
I went home for a bit earlier.
He can walk by himself,
and he can eat alone now if I set the table.
It's easier for me now.
I owe it all to you.
Thank you.
I think he can go home now.
What?
Sedal isn't here?
He got kicked out a long time ago.
He got kicked out in his boxers.
In his boxers?
Mom.
Why? Why did he get kicked out?
How can she kick him out in his boxers?
In this cold!
Oh, I don't know what happened.
There was a snow storm,
so I felt really sorry for him.
Please leave before Miss Eun comes home.
What do we do?
Did you find a place?
I'm not feeling well.
Mom's really sick.
Stop pushing her.
We'll move out when we can, so stop it.
Mom, let's go.
Oh, what do we do?
Where did your brother go, in his boxers?
Quiet down. She'll hear you.
My poor Sedal...
What do I do now...
Why is his phone off?
Where is he?
Why did she kick him out?
What did he do?
What if your brother did something stupid?
What do we do, mom?
What if we get kicked out of here?
Shh!
Be quiet.
Oh, Sedal...
Why won't you call?
What are you doing?
Why did you get up so early?
I'm making tofu stew, your favorite.
Go back to bed.
Yes, Hobak.
I'll wake you up later.
You're making me feel uncomfortable.
You couldn't find a place, huh?
We're looking.
It's not easy to find a place.
It really isn't, Hobak.
Give us more time.
Renting apartments isn't hard.
Step aside. I'll do it.
It's okay.
Let me finish what Ii was doing.
You go and get ready for work.
Yeongdal, wake Sintong and Bangtong up.
They have to get ready for school.
Don't do this.
This is uncomfortable for both of us.
And I don't want to eat your food.
Why not?
I can't cook for my daughter in law?
Lots of mother in laws cook these days.
Then you eat the food you made.
I'll eat something else with the boys.
Do you have to act like this?
Let's act like family while we're here.
For Sintong and Bangtong's sake.
Yes, Hobak.
Do you think this is easy for me?
Divorcing Sedal wasn't an easy decision.
So I don't want to live with you.
Should I look for a place for you?
I'll leave when Sedal comes back.
I won't leave before that!
Stop fighting!
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
Come back for more.
I'm hungry.
Finally, some food.
That wretched girl.
She seduced my sweet Sedal then kicked him out in his boxers?
It was partially his fault.
He lost his mind over money.
Why would she fall for a married man?
With two kids, at that!
She was just bored,
but he couldn't see what she was doing.
Not everyone can become Cinderella.
What if he's starving?
Where is he sleeping? It's cold!
He got kicked out in his boxers.
What if he's going around like that?
Is it Sedal?
I don't know this number.
Hello?
Say something.
Mom.
Is it you, Sedal? Sedal!
Sedal, where are you?
Where are you?
I heard you got kicked out in your boxers.
Don't tell Hobak that.
It's embarrassing.
Who cares about that?
Come home.
Why couldn't I get a hold of you?
I lost my phone.
Don't wander the streets.
Come home, okay?
Come home to me.
I can't.
How can I?
Sedal, where are you?
I'll come and get you.
Where are you?
Just wait, mom.
I'll come home when I become successful.
Please look after Sintong and Bangtong.
Goodbye, mom.
Sedal! Sedal!
Mom,
what did he say? What did Sedal say?
Where is he? He's alive?
Yeongdal, close the shop.
Mom!
Oh, she's not here!
Why are you doing this?
- She's not here.
- Hey!
Where is my son?
Where is he?
You must leave!
I told you not to let strangers in.
Drag them out of here!
What? Drag us out?
You little...
What are you doing?
How dare you kick my son out!
Why did you fool around with my son?
We should teach her a lesson!
What are you doing?
My son's getting a divorce because of you!
You think you'll get away with this?
You'll burn in hell!
You're a home wrecker!
God will punish you!
I won't let you get away with this!
Sedal...
Mom, mom, get up.
Oh, Sedal...
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Daese, your daughter in law is here.
Don't call her that.
They're not even married yet.
But they will get married.
She's your future daughter in law.
Hello.
I gave my blessings,
but that's because of what I promised,
not because I actually accept you.
If you act rude, I won't take it.
I understand, father.
That will never happen again.
I'll be watching you.
You can't fool me.
I'm his father,
so I'm letting him have his way.
But my heart is like Siberia.
She'll melt your heart, little by little.
Your adorable future daughter in law will.
Sangnam, show her your room.
Wow.
It's so much nicer in person.
- It is?
- Yes.
But your father is so scary.
I'm scared.
Don't worry.
You have me.
You can rely on me.
You're not going to disappear, will you?
I won't.
Why did you close the door?
You're supposed to keep the door open!
That's basic knowledge.
Where did you learn to behave like this?
Father, we're getting married.
But the wedding hasn't happened yet.
I'm sorry.
You should be helping Sunjeong in the kitchen!
I will.
Father,
she's a guest.
We can't make her do things.
You're siding with her?
You're an idiot.
Don't forget your place,
if you don't want this family to be in trouble.
Don't we have to go too?
It'll just be the parents, to keep it simple.
But he doesn't have a mother, right?
He has an aunt who might as well be his mom.
Hobak, you look great.
I do?
It's probably because I'm relaxed.
Right. Everyone needs that.
Uncle, did something nice happen to you?
What could happen to me?
Good or bad,
there's nothing going on.
But you look different.
It's like you've become a man.
Is that because of that woman?
Don't even bring that up.
Actually, uncle, you look more handsome.
Stop teasing me.
You always tease me.
- No!
- No.
- Uncle, you're handsome.
- Right, you are.
- Oh!
- Uncle, you're the best!
I know it's tough.
You should overcome this to become great men.
I'll be there in place of your dad.
My uncle isn't much help,
but I'll be a great uncle to you.
And both of you have dreams.
So never get discouraged.
Okay, uncle.
But I still miss my dad.
He's breaking my heart...
I can't take this.
I never want to see you again.
Don't tell anyone about this.
I won't be able to get married.
Ugh!
This is horrible!
How dare you!
You're a loser!
This is humiliating!
Oh, no!
Wang Haebak.
What is it?
It's nothing.
I'll tell you later.
Let's go.
Father,
don't brag about me there.
They'll think you're silly.
Did the rude girl tell you to say that?
Father!
I can say whatever I want to say!
And there's nothing to brag about you!
Things like girls lined up for me,
and how I'm the best husband material.
What's wrong with him?
I don't know.
When did he get so cocky?
Ugh! Stop smiling! Man...
Mom, don't blurt random things out.
Don't brag about me there.
Don't say things like how smart I am,
how I was a teacher, and how doctors lined  up for me. Don't, okay?
There's nothing to brag about you.
Let's go, Miss Unemployed.
The phone has been turned off,
so you will be directed to voice mail.
Mother, where's Sedal?
His phone's been off for a while.
You must know, don't you?
I know you're in contact with him.
I'm not.
I haven't been able to reach him.
I'm busy. I have to go.
Sedal's driving me crazy!
Why did he cheat on Hobak?
- Wow!
Huh?
It's dad.
Dad!
- Dad!
What's wrong?
It's dad.
- What is it?
- I saw dad.
Dad looked like a homeless man.
What?
He looked like a beggar!
He probably just looked like your dad.
Right, our dad's not a beggar.
Let's go.
This is for you, and this is for you.
Yay! How nice!
- You like it?
- Yes.
Let's go.
Oh, your hands are cold!
- So warm!
- Wow!
Subtitles by KBS World
Women lined up to meet him.
Then why didn't you get someone from there?
Why are you interested in my daughter?
The bed sheet looks a bit...
I changed it just now.
Just do as I say.
Don't talk back to me.
You were the happiest to hear of the divorce.
I just can't understand you.
Why aren't you moving out?
I'll be watching you!
Have a nice life!
What's wrong with my daughter?
She's really rude.
What's so great about your son?
You didn't just say that!