Subtitles by KBS World
You told me to keep my mouth shut, so I did.
It's in the past.
You made a mistake.
But Subak, don't do this.
You don't know what you're doing, do you?
It's the most horrible, cowardly,
and evil sin in the world.
I've experienced it, and it's hell.
My spouse being with another person.
That's hell.
It destroys one's soul completely.
Subak, I'm begging you.
End it now.
What if Minjung finds out?
It'll destroy everyone.
You, Minjung and your kids.
Minjung.
How long have you been standing there?
Huh? I just got here.
He wouldn't sleep so I just kept walking, and here I am.
What are you doing out here?
It's cold.
I was yelling at her for coming home so late.
Even if she has a job,
she shouldn't come home so late.
I'm more experienced in working.
I never come home this late, and she has
a little baby which mom is taking care of,
and you too, so she shouldn't be like this.
Aren't you glad I scolded her?
I am.
How rude.
She thinks she's my older sister.
She thinks I'm an idiot.
She thinks she's so much better.
Minjung, try to give her a break.
It's her first job, so it must be hard.
She can't say no to business engagements.
I'll see you later.
See you.
Minjung, goodbye.
See you again.
You can't control your kids.
She brought a man she wants to marry,
and I don't like him.
He's nice, but it's the things about him.
But my daughter wouldn't give up,
so I met with his father,
but oh, boy.
What's wrong?
His father is nothing but trouble.
My wife saw him to talk about furniture,
and she canceled the wedding.
My daughter's crying her eyes out,
but my wife keeps saying no.
I'd say yes if things weren't so bad,
but it feels wrong.
He's so weird that he held a daughter in law audition.
I couldn't believe it.
What did you just say?
Daughter in law audition?
Yes. Why?
Why did you call me so late?
Is something wrong?
Come and meet me.
Excuse me?
Just come and meet me right now.
Hey, Daese!
Oh, hi.
Hello.
How come you two are together?
It just happened.
Hello.
I don't understand...
Sit, sit, sit. Sit.
Daese, this is meant to be.
You trust me, don't you?
Bong, you trust me too, don't you?
No words needed.
You two are in laws now.
Just trust me
and let your son and daughter get married.
What is it?
You can't sleep?
What if Bangtong dies?
He won't. Not from this.
He'll be fine when his fever breaks.
Go to bed.
Why aren't you in bed?
Grandma, Bangtong's sick.
He is? Why?
I don't know. He has a fever.
Yeongdal! Bangtong is sick!
Bangtong is sick?
Oh, my, he's burning up.
Shouldn't we take him to the ER?
It was worse before.
He's a lot better now.
You didn't get any sleep, did you?
We'll look after him. Go to bed.
I know how upset you must be.
Yes, Hobak.
Get some sleep in our room.
Mom and I will sleep here.
It's okay. You can go to bed.
Dad.
Bangtong, it's grandma.
Wake up!
Bangtong, open your eyes.
Why are you waking him up?
Dad... Dad...
See? He's not sleeping.
What did he just say?
He's calling for his dad.
Oh, my.
He's sick and he's calling for his dad.
He got sick because he misses his dad.
- Poor boy.
- Dad.
I know.
Hobak, don't break your son's heart.
Forget it. Please leave.
You're telling us to leave now?
Where could we go in the middle of winter?
Whenever you tell us to leave,
my heart jumps.
It's like I'm becoming neurotic.
You can't do this to me.
I mean leave this room. He can't sleep.
Mom, she wants us out of this room.
Let's, go, let's go.
Call me if you get too tired.
- One more time!
You don't know what you're doing, do you?
It's the most horrible, cowardly,
and evil sin in the world.
I've experienced it, and it's hell.
My spouse being with another person.
That's hell.
Minjung, come over here.
I don't feel like eating.
Have a bite.
I made soft tofu stew.
I'm not hungry.
That's okay.
You can't work on an empty stomach.
You have to eat if you want to work.
My stomach hurts, so I'll skip it.
Why would your stomach hurt?
I had indigestion last night.
You did?
You shouldn't eat so quickly.
You eat like someone's coming after you.
Don't eat so quickly, even when you're busy.
I wish you'd have a bite, at least.
Leave him be. He's not hungry.
You cooked for nothing.
I should go.
Get something later, okay?
What's wrong?
Minjung skipped breakfast.
His stomach hurts and he's not hungry.
I hope he's not sick.
I know.
Why did you get so drunk last night?
Oh, I'm dying.
Get me some honey tea.
Have some hangover soup.
You were pretty drunk last night.
Oh, that hit the spot.
I feel better now.
Who did you go drinking with?
None of your business.
Your soup is amazing. Top class.
Tell the rude girl she better cook like this.
Or I'll kick her out.
Excuse me?
Father.
You're saying yes?
Nobody will cook for me if you were gone.
Teach her how to make it just like this.
I will, Daese.
Father, thank you!
Oh, let me go!
I have to eat this.
Stop it!
Father, what did you say?
Honey, this is wrong.
I'm not saying yes because I'm happy.
You say you can't live without him,
and I don't want you to die a spinster.
You better not regret this!
And don't blame us for not stopping you!
I won't, I won't!
The number you have called is busy...
Sangnam.
Congrats, congrats!
You're getting married!
Our fathers had a drink last night.
I heard.
We're really getting married?
After I break up with the women who loves me.
Huh?
Let's celebrate later.
Okay.
Yay!
How could you decide that on your own?
Didn't you say his father's weird?
He's actually a decent man.
He's picky, but he's a good person.
Even the meanest mother in law has a good reputation in her neighborhood.
Did you mean me?
Everyone likes you in our neighborhood.
Why you little...
I only want one thing.
A woman can mess up a man's life.
Lots of marriages break up over the wife's side of the family.
Don't let them intimidate you.
Don't be at their beck and call.
You're my son, not their servant, got it?
Father, I'll be fine. Don't worry.
I'm worried about his father.
Did you make him swear that he won't give her any trouble?
But Gwangbak loves him more.
She even entered that audition.
Father...
You're so weird.
I would never do anything like that.
Do you know what makes you the happiest?
Being warm and well fed makes you happy.
And having a brand name handbag.
You don't even feel hungry when you do.
That darn brand name handbag.
I'll sell this house and buy you one.
I'll buy you one, mom.
And me?
Mom, you have me.
Don't ask your granddaughter for one.
You have a son here.
Let me talk.
Why are we talking about that?
Go ahead.
Where was I?
Do you know what makes you the happiest?
You just finished saying that.
Okay.
Doing what you love while living with the person you love.
That's what makes you the happiest.
Yes.
You're right, father.
Oh, you must have been so unhappy.
You couldn't become a singer or live with the woman you love.
I'm glad you know.
What?
But I got half of it.
I'm living with the woman I love.
Stop lying.
You had a crush on the miller's daughter!
How did you know that?
Mother told me.
I never told you that!
You forgot already?
You said the miller's daughter was tall,
thin, and beautiful every day to me.
A tall woman wouldn't look right with Bong.
I'm perfect for him.
She was the one who had a crush on me.
Whatever.
I'm not going to cook for you anymore!
How about you?
You didn't have a crush on anyone?
Of course I did!
So many young men fell for me that
my father had to stay up all night
making number tickets to keep them in order.
Stop it, liar!
Mom, I will be happy.
Father, thank you.
Look at how big her smile is.
- Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
- Congratulations.
- Good luck.
- Ugh!
Anna, I have to take the morning off.
Okay, Hobak.
If something comes up, I'll call you.
Can I come, too?
I don't want to stay home.
You have to, even if you don't want to.
What if she takes our stuff out?
We'd be kicked out, just like that.
She's not even going to work today.
I can't believe this.
One of us must stay home from now on,
so Sedal can come home.
If we get kicked out, we'd be ruined.
This is crazy.
How does it feel?
It's not the nice smelling lotion
that moves one's heart. It's the person.
Don't you think so?
Of course I do.
Hello.
Oh!
You're my first customer.
Oh, I am?
The lotion I bought here was great.
I knew it!
The weather's turning my hands really rough.
Do you have anything for that?
Would you like to try our hand lotion?
Okay.
Right here, please.
If you love your body, your skin improves.
Wash your hands and work the lotion in.
Work it in.
Rub it in like this.
Done.
May I have some on this one, too?
Hello?
Sangnam, did you tell her?
To come and see me?
Uh, not yet.
She doesn't want to see me?
It's not that.
I didn't get the chance to tell her.
You didn't?
I'm supposed to be her mother in law,
so you can't introduce me at the wedding.
I have to see her.
I'm very curious about her.
Okay.
Father.
I heard you couldn't go to work.
Is it serious?
The fever broke.
It must be a cold.
He threw up.
Did you take him to see a doctor?
Yes.
I know you'd never miss work.
You went to work even when your kid got surgery.
It breaks my heart to think of that, father.
I'm not going to live like that anymore.
My boys were the most important,
but I lived to make money.
From now on, I'm going to be there for them,
build memories with them, eat good food and travel with them.
I feel horrible about not doing that.
You can start now.
Don't beat yourself up over that.
Let me see.
Your mother in law came over upset the other day.
She went to your house?
She's just upset.
Hobak, I'm a man, too,
but it takes men longer to become adults.
Maybe it's because we don't give birth,
but it takes us much longer than women.
I know what you're going to say.
But I...
For your boys, can't you just reconsider it?
I told you I don't want to maintain a loveless marriage because of my kids.
I know how you feel right now,
but Hobak, men need time to grow up.
Some men actually do change.
He might change if you gave him time.
I'm saying this for you.
I don't want you to have any regrets.
He wouldn't have come back if that woman hadn't dumped him.
Father, I'm not some trash can.
I can't do that to myself.
- Uh, mother.
- Oh, you scared me.
I knocked...
How have you been?
Not good, thanks to you.
Why are you here?
I wanted to see you and tell you something.
I don't want to hear anything from you.
How dare you come here after all you've done?
Mother.
I'm not your mother!
Get out!
How dare you come here?
You're just like your mother!
Get out!
Uh, I just need a minute. I have...
I don't want to hear anything from you!
You have a lot of nerve to show up here!
Uh, mother...
Stop calling me that. Get out!
Mother, I'm sorry.
Please hear me out!
Mother, open the door, please.
Mother! I'm sorry! Mother!
Mother!
What are you doing?
She won't even open the door.
Would you, if you were her?
Loser, what should I do?
Why are you asking me that?
Can I have some more soup?
She won't see me,
so I can't even beg for her forgiveness.
Neither my brother nor his wife wants to see you.
If you were them, would you want to see you?
No.
Hobak always sticks to her decision.
You know that.
But she takes a long time to decide.
Why didn't you go back when she asked?
I was out of my mind back then.
Right. You had crazy eyes back then.
I know.
My eyes, brain, and heart were all crazy.
Why didn't you stop me?
Beating you up didn't work, so how could I?
This is nuts.
Goof-off,
I kind of understand you.
I feel sorry for you.
I can't throw stones at you.
But I can't be on your side.
You broke Hobak's heart.
You should give up.
I can't.
Can you be my messenger?
I won't forget this.
I couldn't do it if I wanted to.
Hobak won't listen to me.
She won't even listen to her father.
Unless you can bring her lots of money,
you should just let her go.
How much is it?
Three dollars.
You should stay and finish this.
This is nuts.
Bangtong.
Sintong.
How are you feeling?
I'm better now.
Here. Cards.
You said you wanted them.
I miss dad.
Don't you miss dad?
Mom.
Yes, hold on.
I'll make you something to eat after this.
Can you tell dad to come?
Bangtong misses him.
He won't even take my cards.
He's asking for dad.
What are you doing here?
To buy gifts to celebrate our wedding.
Oh, how nice!
Come to think of it...
I'm materialistic, right?
I'm a material girl.
It's not for you.
I'm buying Christmas gifts for my nephews.
You have nephews?
Isn't Miho your cousin?
Your nephews.
I want them to be on my side.
Really?
Oh, you're so amazing!
I can't believe this!
But I don't want you spending money without my permission in the future.
Afer we're married, I won't.
I'll ask you whenever I spend a penny. Happy?
I should spend lots of it before our wedding.
Should I buy gifts for my ex-girlfriends?
Ugh!
You're impossible.
These are from your future uncle.
Christmas gifts.
Wow! How exciting!
- You're the best.
- He's the best!
I thought your mom didn't go to work today.
She just did.
Bangtong's not sick anymore.
Your future uncle wants you to feel better.
So don't get sick again.
If I can see dad, I won't get sick, aunt.
Gwangbak, I know what you're saying,
but don't talk to me about Sedal. Please.
Everyone's been talking to me about him.
I know. I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
You're not. And it's Christmas.
I'll talk to you later.
Father, hi.
Hi, Minjung.
Show us your lightest and warmest coat.
Show us the best, regardless of price.
But you don't have to.
Let me buy you one, Minjung.
Then get me something cheap.
An expensive one, okay?
Okay.
I'll get the best, most expensive one we have.
Father, stay here.
Minjung, what's your favorite color?
Hobak,
can I see you after work?
I don't understand what you're saying.
Be honest with me.
I caught some of it the other night,
but I want to know for sure.
I think I should.
But I didn't say much.
Hobak.
Minjung,
I don't know what you think you heard,
but I already told you that night.
I yelled at Subak for coming home late.
I told her to go home early and help mom out.
I told her you'd be worried, too.
I'm serious, Minjung.
That's what I said.
Minjung,
what's wrong?
I don't know.
Minjung.
Something's not right.
I just have this feeling.
But Hobak,
I don't know why,
but I want the truth,
and at the same time, I'm afraid of it.
I'm scared.
Maybe I want to avoid it entirely.
Whatever the truth is,
I want to cover my eyes and ears.
Minjung,
I know how that feels.
I know it too well.
Dying to know the truth but wanting to avoid it.
Wanting and not wanting it at the same time.
Feeling lost and scared.
I know that.
I've been there.
What do I do after I find out the truth?
I was scared.
But Minjung,
Subak isn't.
She's not cheating on you.
She can't afford to do that right now.
She really isn't.
You misunderstood.
I didn't finish because of Minjung, but...
Yes, you did!
Subak.
What? What more do you have to say?
You know what.
- End it.
- I can't.
Subak.
He's my path to survival.
I work at his company.
You're nuts.
How could you work at his company?
Does that mean you see him every day?
Subak, snap out of it!
This is wrong.
What if Minjung finds out?
He might have already.
He's dense, so he won't.
My father's going home tomorrow.
I'm spending the night at the hospital.
Who is it?
It's your brother in law!
He's spending the night at the hospital.
You don't want to divorce him.
I will, if I have to.
Don't talk like that.
You're not alone.
You have two kids.
You have to resign.
Who do you think you are to tell me that?
You said you see him every day.
All men are the same.
Nobody is that special.
When you have a job, some men seem special.
How amazing it would be to be his wife?
But when you meet their wives, they all say this.
Try living with him for a week or a month.
You're upset because you couldn't marry him,
but if you did, you might already be divorced.
He's not the right man for you.
Subak, I hope you and Minjung don't go through what I did.
Go.
And mind your own business from now on.
I'm fine. Let me down.
I said I'm fine.
Thank you for everything.
Don't mention it.
Take care of yourself.
I hope you stay healthy.
I'll see you later. Thank you.
You should go.
Here, take it.
Is it my paycheck?
It's a bonus.
I'll be back soon.
What is it?
Mom, I wired you the money.
You did?
I wired $1,000, just like you asked.
Don't you just love me?
Thanks to you, I'm making money now.
I'm getting my monthly paycheck.
When you turn around!
My eyes might meet yours!
Why didn't you finish hanging up the laundry?
I didn't?
I can't believe this.
I think you should see a doctor.
I know.
I keep forgetting where I put things.
What if something bad happens?
How's your business?
- Hello.
- Hi.
What's good today?
Oh.
I don't see anything I want.
I'll come back another time.
Have a good day!
The bank!
Oh, my.
This is fur.
Let me see.
Hello.
I'm Wang Gwangbak.
Hi.
You're perfect for my Sangnam.
You're very pretty.
You look like I did when I was young.
I heard if the mother and daughter in law look alike, they get along well.
Really?
Yes.
Let's sit down. Sit.
You must have been surprised.
I actually wanted to meet you.
It was meant to be then.
Should we go out for dinner?
I'd love to cook for you, but...
You're very kind.
You look so good together.
I only want one thing.
I want you two to be happy.
If Sangnam is happy, I'm happy.
Should we get something?
I'll go get it.
I'll get it.
What would you like?
I just want instant coffee.
They have that here, right?
Me too.
I'll get the closest thing.
What's your number?
I'll store it in your phone for you.
What should I save my name as?
Your name.
Daughter in law.
Can I call you?
Yes.
What are you making?
Spicy raw crab.
Subak's favorite.
You only care about Subak?
Subak paid me today.
People are such simple creatures.
Being paid makes all this a piece of cake.
I should've asked Bong to pay me.
It's bad to go money crazy.
I'm not the type of person who could.
Jungji's taking a long nap for a change.
Can you go check on him?
Where did you put Jungji?
He's not in your room or Subak's room.
He's not?
Gwangbak...
Mom, what is it?
I'm home.
What?
Okay, mom.
What is it?
Oh, no!
Minjung,
what do I do?
I lost Jungji.
Okay, mother.
I'm on my way home.
Mother, don't be so scared.
Calm down.
I'm sure we can find him.
I'll hurry up.
Mom! Mom!
What do I do?
Mom, pull yourself together and think about it.
I'm sure we can find him.
- Jungji!
Jungji!
- Mom, here.
- Jungji.
Gwangbak!
Oh, Hobak.
What happened?
Mom took Jungji out on his stroller,
but she can't remember where she left him.
But we looked everywhere.
What do we do?
Mom, try to remember.
I can't remember where I left him.
What do I do?
What do I do about my Jungji?
Calm down and think.
Where did you go?
I bought some blue crabs at the market,
and I talked to the fish vendor.
Where did I go next?
Oh! I went to the bank.
The bank?
Let's go there, mom.
Where's Subak?
We couldn't reach her.
Man. How about Minjung?
He's on his way.
Oh, no.
Did you see a stroller here by any chance?
It's a pink stroller.
A stroller?
I didn't see any.
- Mom!
- Mom.
I can't do this. I can't.
Mother.
- Minjung.
- Mother.
Oh, Minjung, what do I do?
What do I do?
I'm so sorry.
I can't remember.
I can't remember where I left him.
I should just die. I should die.
Don't do this, mom.
Stop this.
Mother, stop this.
Mother!
- Mom!
- Stop this.
Honey.
What do I do?
I'm home.
Oh, man!
Something awful happened.
We lost Jungji.
What?
What happened?
How did this happen?
How could you lose my baby?
Be quiet.
We reported it at the police station.
Mom, are you crazy?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
What do I do?
It's cold...
Where did he go...
What if something happened to him?
Oh, Jungji...
My baby...
Why did you take him out?
When you're so forgetful?
What if something bad happened to him?
That's enough.
Mother's a mess.
How can I stop it?
I paid you!
How can you let this happen after I paid you?
Subak, stop it.
Mom's not well.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Look at what happened.
What if we never find him?
Mom, what will you do?
How could you lose my baby?
I'm not letting you get away with this!
She's your mom.
Can't you see she's out of her mind?
Can't you see she was worried sick all day?
Just look at her right now.
She's shaking like a leaf right now!
How dare you say such a thing?
After being gone all day!
Take your kids and get out of my house!
You're going to kill my wife.
She gets aches and pains at night.
She can't even sleep because of your kids.
And this is how you treat her?
I'm not putting up with this anymore!
Get out of my house.
I don't need any of you.
The most important person to me is your mom.
Subak!
Take your family and get out!
Fine! I will!
We'll leave!
What?
Come here.
Let go!
Why do you always do this to me?
You've always hated me and yelled at me.
You yelled at mom for favoring me,
but you were always on Hobak's side.
You weren't happy with anything I did.
You never said anything nice to me.
Stop. This is no time for that.
Hello?
What?
Someone just called me. My baby.
Over there.
Jungji!
Jungji.
My baby!
Let me hold you, my baby!
You saved me, you saved me.
Oh, my baby!
Where have you been?
Oh, thank you, god!
Oh, my baby...
My baby...
Maybe this house is cursed.
Not a day goes by quietly.
I'm just glad we found him.
What if we lost him for good?
Or, it's horrible just to even think about it.
Hobak,
about Goof-off...
Stop.
I feel sorry for the guy.
He asked me to talk to you.
Uncle.
I know how you feel.
You can't know unless you experience it.
So don't say you know how I feel.
Just look the other way.
Stop telling me how he's doing.
If you can understand just a fraction of how I feel, don't say anything.
You two are friends, so you can see him.
But,
don't talk about him to me.
You should resign.
What?
You need to quit your job.
I can't.
Why not?
You don't know why?
I don't know why you have to keep working.
Especially after what happened today.
I don't get it.
I'm doing it to make money, not to party.
If you could make enough money,
I wouldn't bother working.
So stay home.
What's wrong with you?
Hobak goes to work when she has two kids.
She went to work when her boys were hospitalized.
And now she's a manager.
But that's Hobak.
Why?
You don't think I can do what Hobak does?
Why are you asking me to quit my job?
Did Hobak put you up to this?
Just do what I say.
I want to protect our family.
For our kids,
just do what I say.
Don't get mad at mother for losing Jungji.
You stay home and raise the kids.
If you want to work,
do it after Jungji's grown up.
Are you crazy?
Fine. Let's say I'm crazy.
So do what I say before I go totally crazy!
Quit your job right now!
Oh, my...
Why are you screaming?
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo...
Try this.
You like red bean cake.
I don't want to eat.
But you'll die.
You won't eat any porridge.
It's hot. It's really good.
Try it. Hurry.
You're the only one who cares about me.
Subak won't even come down to check on me when I'm this sick.
They say a husband is better to you
than 100 children put together.
Even if he's old and sick.
And now I understand why.
Without you, I'm nothing.
I'm so mad.
I was so good to her.
Don't think about that.
Kids are useless.
So let's take care of each other.
Eat this and get better.
It's good.
You have some, too.
Okay.
I pity those who are old and single.
So be nice to mother.
You always talk about your mother.
What is it?
Where are you?
I'm getting some tangerines.
Hurry up and go home!
What if she puts our stuff outside?
She went to her parents house.
Mom, I'm hanging up.
Hello, I'm Wang Don.
- Let's go in.
- Yes, let's go inside.
You're more handsome than I thought.
And you look kind.
Thank you.
You're in the same pizza class with my friend?
Yes.
I came because she kept pushing me to,
but I'm not used to dating.
I don't really know how to...
Then would you follow my lead?
We're not in our twenties,
so let's go get a drink and talk some more.
Sure.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Why are you here?
How could you do this?
How could you do this to me?
What?
What am I doing to you?
Who is she?
- She's nobody.
- I am.
his wife.
Hey!
This is wrong!
She's not my wife.
She's my friend's little sister.
I am his friend's little sister.
And I married him.
When did that happen?
This is nuts!
Honey,
this is wrong.
How can you cheat on me like this?
Let's go home. Our kids are waiting.
What kids?
Our twins are crying so hard.
Apologize to this woman.
Don't you feel badly for her?
I'm very sorry.
Let me apologize for my husband.
Honey,
it's okay to break my heart.
But what are you doing to her?
Why are you doing this?
She's not my wife.
Honey!
What a creep!
Goodbye.
What are you doing?
Are you mad?
No, I'm not mad.
Don't ever show your face in front of me,
and don't ever see my brother again.
That night was the most awful day of my life.
I can't believe what happened.
You,
you weren't so good that night.
Loser,
What was that?
It's cold.
It's probably just the wind.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo!
Where were you?
Where?
Why?
She changed the code.
She did?
Hobak, open the door!
Hobak, it's freezing.
Please open the door!
Hobak, Hobak!
Promise to move out this week!
I promise.
We'll move out this week.
You're so mean.
How could you lock us out?
You promised.
Move out by the end of this week.
Why you little!
If you don't, I'm throwing your stuff out.
Fine.
If you want us out, we'll have to.
I told you not to leave the apartment.
I didn't know she'd do this.
Maybe mother lost her appetite.
You should just go to work.
Can you make something...
Enough. I'll take care of her.
Mother!
I'm old, too.
Doing this is hard on me.
Forget it. I'm not eating.
You said the older you are, the more you must eat.
I don't want to eat.
I should just die.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
What bothered you this time?
I won't know unless you tell me.
Tell Bong to buy me a burial plot.
Who buys burial plots these days?
Kids don't take care of their parents graves.
Can bong do it?
Can Don do it?
Kinds are useless.
I know.
You should take care of yourself.
Relying on your kids will end up killing you.
I was sick last night,
but nobody brought me even a glass of water.
But your husband brought you red bean cake!
That cake gave me indigestion.
I got punished for not sharing it with you.
Where to?
Anywhere. Just go straight.
Hello. Do you need a prescription filled?
Hold on.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Well, that...
What would you like?
That...
That?
Oh!
1, condoms,
2, birth control pills, 3, pregnancy test.
3! 3! I want number 3.
Here it is.
How did you know?
When women your age come here looking nervous,
it's because they're looking for one of them.
Stop it.
Water canon!
Shoot!
It broke.
Please, please.
Are you still accepting applications?
Have you made up your mind?
You can't take this lightly.
I'm ready.
When are we leaving?
Thank you.
See you again.
Hello?
Mom.
Yes, Sedal.
How's the sauna?
Mom, I'm leaving.
What? Where to?
Where are you going?
I'm going to become a fisherman.
I'll come back when I'm rich.
Mom, don't get sick. Take care.
And don't worry about me.
Sedal, Sedal, no!
Don't go! Don't go!
Hello? Sedal! Sedal!
Oh, Sedal, Sedal...
I have to go make rounds.
See you later, manager.
How could you do this?
How could you do this to Sedal?
This is my workplace.
You kicked my son out and you're happy?
You can't do this.
I never kicked him out.
He walked out on me.
But you didn't take him back!
Would you have if you were me?
You're too young to understand.
Kids need both parents.
You know what that does to you?
A cheating, gambling husband
is better than a dead husband.
I don't want to hear that.
Go home.
Sedal's going to become an ice fisherman.
Why do you think he's doing that?
He's never even been on a ship.
He's sick and tired of life,
and he turned to that.
What if something bad happens to him?
Good for him.
He can't stay unemployed and expect to get $3 a day in allowance.
He doesn't even have a wife anymore.
Let him catch shrimp or whales.
He has to make money now.
I'm busy.
God will punish you!
Fine.
Oh, man...
It's been a long time.
Subtitles by KBS World
We can't meet like this anymore.
We can't?
Be good to mother!
My mother's more important!
Understand?
I'm pregnant.
What did you just say?
We're not husband and wife.
He's never been on a ship before.
How am I going to live now?
You don't deserve forgiveness.
Let her go!
Father!
Get out of my house!
I'm not seeing a man!
Are you crazy?
Whatever you were doing,
stop it right now.