Subtitles by KBS World
He looks excited.
Daebak, is your brother in law having an affair?
Is that what he's doing?
You really have no idea, do you?
How would Hobak feel if she found out?
She'd feel bad.
This is divorce bad.
A kiss isn't worth a divorce.
If you like each other, you could kiss.
How can a married man kiss another woman?
It wasn't me.
Will you when you get married?
I'd have to wait and see.
If you do, I'll destroy you.
Go ahead.
I hate scary women!
You must get back at her, okay?
But we're family.
Why you little!
You have to squash Anggeum, okay?
How can I squash my older brother's wife?
Sit on her?
Get a job right now.
I'm delivering pizza.
That's not what I mean.
Look at Goof-off.
He's not any better than you!
Look at the job he has right now.
He got a job, so why can't you?
He's such a disloyal friend.
Why can't you find a job like his?
I know.
You're always home, looking for snacks,
and that's why she looks down on you.
Even her kids treat you like crap.
Don't you feel angry?
I know.
Why you little!
Who do you take after?
How come nothing bothers you?
It's because you were a grandma when you had me.
I wasn't a brandma when I had you!
I'm young enough to have another child!
Father's looking down on us,
so who's child would you have?
Do you have someone in mind?
Am I getting a step dad?
I don't want to see you face. Get out!
Did you have a good day?
Yes.
Mother.
Oh.
I'm ho...
Oh, no.
Are you ill?
Oh...
Why do I bother living?
What is it?
You lost your appetite again?
It's not that.
I should just die.
Was it Anggeum again?
Oh...
I can't do this anymore.
Anggeum and Subak paired up and attacked me ferociously!
I just can't take this anymore.
Since Subak moved in, Anggeum's been really mean to me.
Don and I are nothing to them.
But I'm too old to fight back.
I just have to sit and take it.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
What can I do?
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo...
- You.
- Just one more word!
How was the amusement park?
Was it fun?
We should take the boys sometime.
It's just an amusement park.
Wasn't it weird for two men to go there?
Didn't people stare at you?
They said we looked good together.
They did?
They must have thought you were friends.
Uh,
should I take a shower?
Do whatever you want.
It's your body.
Why would you ask me?
Hey, don't start getting ideas.
I'm really tired tonight.
Oh, I'm exhausted.
Hold on.
For what?
Oh, man!
Do you know how tiring today was for me?
I had to wait in lines for hours,
get sick on the rides,
fetch cotton candy,
and put on a hairband.
Hairband? For two men?
Huh?
He said he wanted to try it.
He never tried it in the States.
It must have been really funny.
It was. I'm laughing.
Let me take a shower.
Wait for me.
Shower...
This is nuts!
You'll break your neck!
Get me a pain relieving patch.
For what?
I threw out my neck.
Really? Where?
Don't touch me!
Ugh!
I knew it.
You can't go to work like this!
It's hurting like crazy.
You joked about a neck spinning license.
It serves you right!
I know how impatient you are so
this is so that it won't be too hot.
You're ugly...
impatient and foul mouthed.
What else?
Of five cards, three are bad,
but the other two are pretty decent.
So far, at least.
What are they?
They are a secret.
That's not fair!
You have to tell me.
Just like that?
I'll pay for the noodles. Hurry.
I'm really curious about what good qualities I have.
Shh!
The noodles are getting soggy. Let's eat.
I wanted fish stew.
You caught a cold.
I had it with someone else.
But you said you'd have it with me.
Ouch! Hot!
I told you to blow on it.
How did such a nice guy become a player?
I'm not a nice man.
Those who were hurt become players.
I told you when you interviewed me.
That I don't live with my mom.
Growing up, I never knew mother's love.
After my mom left,
I couldn't trust women.
I'm suspicious, obsessive,
afraid of them leaving,
and scared of getting dumped.
It's from experiencing lack of attention.
Don't look at me like that.
I decided to become a player.
I won't let anyone in.
Because if I do,
I'll get hurt.
I never told anyone this before.
How weird.
Maybe it's something I ate.
It's autumn now.
Don't try to look pretty.
Just wear something warm.
And don't catch a cold.
I used to be scared of autumn.
When the leaves fall,
my heart would break.
Don't we scared anymore.
You have me.
Even when the leaves fall,
I'll hold your heart together
so it won't break.
Poor player.
Mommy! A bug, a bug, a bug!
A bug! Agh!
- Mommy!
- It wasn't a bug.
It was a leaf.
Agh! It was a bug!
How can you...
- Hey!
- Agh! Don't!
Uncle, uncle.
Open the door, please.
Uncle!
Oh, it's like torture every morning.
Getting up early in the morning is so hard.
I'm used to it and it's still hard for me.
You can nap when your father goes out.
This is expired. Should I dump it?
Don't dump that.
You can still drink it.
It won't kill you.
Someone drank it yesterday.
Minjung didn't come home last night.
What?
Minjung, Minjung.
Why are you sleeping out here?
Did you and Subak have a fight?
No.
The door was locked.
Why didn't you call me, then?
I did, but nobody answered.
And I didn't want to knock when everyone was sleeping.
Where are you coming from?
I'm not coming from anywhere.
Now you're sleeping somewhere else?
What's wrong with you/
Peekaboo. The morning air is very nice.
Poor player came to work.
Are you still in bed?
Can we talk?
Peekaboo.
So hard working.
You're already at work?
- Of course, I'm a laborer...
- I know.
So you must wake up and eat on schedule.
You're talking like a laborer's wife.
What are you doing today?
I'm meeting a friend who is getting married.
I have to be her bridesmaid.
And I'm going to start writing today.
I'm supposed to get published this year.
Oh, I can't wait to read it.
But can you?
When your love life is a mess?
Let me be the first to read your book.
If you lie about it again, I'll get mad.
Have a good day.
Are the dried corvina gone?
What dried corvina?
The ones we got for Chuseok.
Of course they are gone.
Chuseok was a long time ago.
You should've left them for Bong.
How could you eat them all?
What a great housewife you are.
There weren't that many to begin with.
We didn't get many gifts this year.
He's not popular any more.
People don't bring him gifts anymore.
Being a teacher is not a popularity contest.
And the economy is bad.
I used to get gifts from old students,
but now it's hard to find jobs.
When I was young, on holidays,
we used to have so many guests.
Did your family get many gifts, too?
Of course.
The gifts we got lasted until next Chuseok.
People with gifts lined up for 10 meters.
Hey, don't brag about a measly 10 meters.
Our line was 20 meters.
But it wasn't just one line for us.
There were 4 lines of 10 meters.
- What?
- Mom, eat your breakfast.
Why you little! You eat yours!
Our shed got so filled with gifts that we had to build a new one every holiday.
Have you heard of the five sheds?
We had five sheds,
and that's where the phrase came from.
Really? Impressive.
It was quite impressive!
Mother, have you been to the bank?
I have. What about it?
You know how they give you numbers?
Stop that.
Why are you talking about numbers?
Mother, eat your breakfast.
My family started that number system.
People had to get numbers to enter our house if they wanted to give their gifts to us.
My father would stay up all night making the number tickets before the holidays.
We got sick of getting gifts.
How did your father live without sleeping?
From what you've told me, it looks like your father never got any sleep.
She's bluffing, mother.
I'm not bluffing.
Mother, you can't beat me,
so stop talking about your family.
If you stop, I'll stop too.
Did Minjung have breakfast?
I'm going to have to talk to Minjung.
What for?
He didn't come home last night.
Since he lives with us,
he should be more careful.
How could he not come home?
That's not what happened.
Was he with you?
No.
He got locked out, so he slept outside.
He called but nobody answered.
He couldn't knock because we were asleep so he slept outside.
He still could've knocked.
And why didn't he tell us?
Who locked the door last night?
Who locked it while someone was still out?
How can we not these days?
Then you should've waited for him.
And why didn't you hear the phone ring?
Subak, you went to sleep
while your husband was still at work?
She can't wait up.
They're not newlyweds.
How can you lock the door and sleep
while your husband was still out working?
You should've waited up for him.
Why do both of them have to suffer?
We always kept the door open,
but someone locked it by mistake last night.
Are you Subak's spokesperson?
I knew he'd yell at you.
From now on, no matter how late,
wait until Minjung comes home.
And get him something to eat.
Delivering parcels is a hard job.
Subak has it hard, too.
She's raising two kids.
Subak, starting tonight,
have the girls sleep in your room.
She can't because they get cranky.
She's their mother!
Right. She should sleep with her kids.
Look at me.
I'm sleeping with my kid.
I know.
After a hard day's work,
it's nice to see the kids.
But he goes to work early and comes home late, so when can he see them?
And it's not easy to come to our room.
- Understand?
- She did!
Subak, you answer.
Stop glaring.
Your eyes might pop out.
Uncle, why did you bring that up here?
You knew your brother would get mad.
Why are you getting angry at him?
You were the one who brought it up.
Daebak, did you tell Hobak?
No. I forgot.
Daebak, listen to me carefully.
If they get a divorce, Hobak has to take care of Sintong and Bangtong alone.
Daebak, you have to nip this in the bud.
Welcome.
Daebak.
Sedal.
What brought you here?
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
Let's get some food. My treat.
Oh, boy...
Daebak!
Eat, Daebak.
Do you eat this every day?
Not anymore. I'm sick of it.
Drop by sometime. My treat.
Eat.
Yes, it's your honey speaking.
I have a guest. I'll call you back.
Me too.
Sedal.
Yes?
I'll give you all the game items I have.
I got lots of items,
and you can have them all.
Why? I don't need stuff like that anymore.
Still, take them.
And this.
What are they?
Coupons.
We go to the same internet cafe, right?
These are the Chinese restaurant coupons,
and one more will get you free noodles.
There are 9 here.
Daebak, what's wrong?
Don't divorce my sister.
What?
You think I'm going to divorce your sister?
I'm worried about my nephews.
For the sake of their dreams, don't do this.
Their dreams?
You don't know?
They never told me.
What are their dreams?
Sintong's is buying his own house.
Bangtong's is having a retirement plan.
Until Sintong buys a house and Bangtong
gets a retirement plan, you must help them.
If there's anything you don't like about Hobak, tell me.
I'll make sure she changes.
There are a lot of things I don't like.
She looks down on me because I'm younger,
talks back at me, and has no respect for me.
Did you know she gave me $3 a day?
It was heartbreaking.
Even I couldn't survive on $3 a day.
I know.
And just look at how she dresses.
She's not feminine at all.
She wears stretched out shirts.
And why does she wear my old underwear?
They have holes in them.
That's not attractive at all.
When you get older, you'll understand.
I understand.
Sedal, thank you for putting up with her.
I'm happy you understand how I feel.
Oh...
Oh.
Eat up, Daebak. Eat.
Daebak.
You should dress up more.
What?
Just because you're a year older,
don't look down on him.
People hate being treated like a child.
And Sedal's old.
And dress nicely.
And don't wear Sedal's old underwear with holes in them.
Men are all alike.
We like pretty women.
Did you see Daebak today?
Yes. Why?
What did you tell him?
Something he needs to hear.
But he's only in 7th grade.
Why would you tell him about
how I treat you like a child
or your underwear?
He already knows everything.
I knew everything when I was his age.
You should take his advice.
The director is here. Bye.
Hon, let's go shopping.
Okay.
Please sign here.
Thank you.
- I'm sorry, but...
- Yes?
Can I use your bathroom?
I really need to.
Oh, no.
Hello, ma'am.
There's no package for us, right?
Right.
May I use your bathroom?
Oh, you can't.
Why don't you check down there?
Yes, parcel service.
I left it at the front desk.
Okay.
Hello.
I deliver parcels here,
and I'm sorry,
but may I use your bathroom?
I really need to...
Go ahead.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I'm very sorry.
Please excuse me.
Goodbye.
Open your eyes.
Do you like it?
It's so pretty.
We met
one year ago today.
I'm sorry all I can afford is this.
Don't be.
I'll wear this until I die.
Don't do that.
Wear it for 3 years.
You always say 3 years.
What will get me after 3 years?
Umm...
I'll buy you one with a diamond this big,
so heavy that you can't hold your head up.
Really?
You promised.
Parcel service.
Yes, I'm on my way.
You'll be home, right?
I'll be there in 10 minutes.
Mom.
Why did you come?
I came because I missed you.
Mom, don't be upset.
I'm sorry.
I got off work early to come and see you.
I brought your favorite snacks.
You like the chicken from the market.
I don't want it. You eat it.
Mom.
Would you be able to get over it like this?
Because I sure can't.
You can't apologize after yelling at me.
I'm sorry.
You said you'll never see me again.
You said you won't come back.
I'm going to pretend I never had you,
so do whatever you want to do.
I didn't mean it, mom.
Don't force yourself.
You don't want to see me.
I don't want to see you or hear your voice.
We'll be like enemies from now on.
Isn't this what you really want?
Don't ever come back.
What's up?
You got off work already?
Yes. I left early.
I didn't want to work myself to death.
And it's been a while since I saw you.
I missed you, too.
Is everything okay?
Yes.
Share this with the other teachers.
I bought some chicken, sausages, and buns.
Did you visit home?
These are your mom's favorites.
Hobak,
I think she needs more time.
She'll come around someday.
So don't try to think about anything
and just go on with your life.
How did you get in?
Is that your hello?
I got in by opening the door.
You should say hello.
How did you know the code?
I should know the code to my son's place.
It's the date of your wedding.
I don't like you dropping by unannounced.
What's wrong with that?
We're family.
You won't say that when you get married.
You never come visit me anymore.
How can you make me come visit you?
My comforters need washing.
Come and wash them on your day off.
We'll be having dinner here from now on.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Don't you have anything to eat?
She's hungry. Go make her dinner.
Where are you?
You skipped your private lessons?
Do you need me to remind you again?
My bat's crying for you, okay?
Come home right now!
I'm busy. Bye.
Hey! Wang Daebak! Hey!
Thank you. Thank you.
Goodbye!
Hello.
Yhank you, sir.
Sir?
I'm sorry. We'll take good care of you.
Go ahead, then.
Loser,
let's go.
Drink!
Let's soak our souls in this!
Soak! Soak! Soak!
Bottoms up!
Soak it all the way!
Let's get on with the casting.
My dream, retirement plan.
Buying my house.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
It's time for your tip.
Come and get it!
Hooray for Sedal! Hooray!
Did you think that was it?
There's more!
- You'll hurt your wrists.
- Oh, I will?
Slowly, slowly.
One, two.
- One, two.
- Right. One, two, three.
- One, two, three.
- And.
Duck.
Oh!
Right.
Okay, one, two.
One, two.
- One, two, three.
That was too much.
Mine went a lot further than
yours since we were kids.
Remember? We had a competition.
Not that.
The money you spent tonight.
How much do you make a month?
The director gave me a bonus.
Sedal,
can I please meet your director?
Why would you meet my director?
What do you want to know?
I don't want to know anything.
I really want to be like you.
Can I be your people?
You're mistaken.
You and I are completely different people.
I'll mention you,
but don't get your hopes up.
How does it feel?
It's pretty nice.
I'm not sure about the effect though.
Now that I'm old, I'm gaining weight.
I eat the same food,
but my belly and arms are getting fat.
But you look healthier than before.
You've seen me before?
Yes.
Mr. Wang told me about his daughters.
And I ran into you many times.
You probably don't remember.
That feels a little strange.
I was weird, wasn't I?
You weren't that weird.
Oh, no. I always look weird.
Tell me, what was I wearing?
I can't.
Oh, no!
You're mean.
Oh, man!
Designated driver!
Thanks.
My father would pass out if he found out I was living this way.
Sorry, sorry.
I'm completely drunk.
I'm so happy that I'm going nuts.
Pay up.
Tell me what you want.
A hug? A piggyback ride?
A piggyback ride.
Get off.
But you're drunk.
I am,
but I can still give you a piggyback ride.
Okay.
Come on.
Whoa!
Come and get it!
How dare you!
I'm your brother's friend.
Honey, sorry.
Hon, you're the best.
Oh, man!
Here.
Oh, man! This is nutty, nutty, nuts!
Oh, man.
Why aren't you in bed?
What about you?
I'm not sleepy.
It's because you don't have a dream.
You...
Stop talking about dreams.
I'm already angry.
What's wrong with you?
It can't be about school.
Tell your uncle.
Can I?
Of course!
If anyone's picking on you, I'll stop them.
Who is it?
Harder.
Do a good job.
Yes, sir.
Will this make my skin white?
If it does, I'll give you a big tip.
Goodbye, dark complexion of mine!
Can you make my eyes less bulgy?
- Oh, no!
I'm sorry.
Oh, you startled me.
Who are you?
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
Oh, man.
I'm not going back to the States, dad.
I'm going to live here.
I'm tired of being your little puppet.
I never got to do anything I wanted.
I did everything your way.
School and marriage.
I ran away because I had to.
Just leave me alone, please!
I want to be free.
What are you doing?
You...
Why are you doing this?
Tell me why you're hitting me!
Oh, man...
Oh, I'm dying here! Help!
You bastard!
Loser! I mean, Don! Are you mad?
Please don't hit my face.
My face is what got me my job.
I know you're jealous of me...
But please don't hit me on my face.
Just let me keep my face, okay?
I'll talk to the director and get you a job.
Hey! Don! Don! Don't do this!
Don, it's me. Sedal.
Heo Sedal. Goof-off Sedal.
We're friends.
I'll get you a job, okay?
Don't ask that woman.
End it before Hobak finds out.
If you hurt Hobak,
I won't forgive you.
Hey, hey, it's not like that.
There's been a misunderstanding.
It's not like that.
Oh, man. I'm bleeding.
Mom!
You're unbelievable.
Let's say I lost my head because of money.
Still, how could you use such violence...
This is against the law, did you know?
Don't you remember the old days?
I was so good to you.
When we entered middle school,
you and I sat together.
They were doing a survey about our families.
[Father:passed away, Mother: Park Salla]
I glanced over,
and you wrote in the parents' section,
father, Wang Chang,
and mother, An Gyesim (Don't have one.)
So I thought you didn't have a mother.
This is nuts, man.
I shared my lunch with you.
I gave you all the good side dishes.
That's why you're bigger than me.
If you forgot that, you're not even a man.
Why you little! Where were you?
Congratulations.
I'm starving. Let's go out for Chinese.
- Chinese?
- Okay.
Let's go.
Who's that?
My mom.
You said you don't have a mom.
No way.
You wrote "An Gyesim (don't have one)."
My mom's name is An Gyesim.
That was her name?
This is nutty, nutty, nuts.
I thought you didn't have a mother,
so I was nice to you for 3 years.
Are you angry?
I never told you I didn't have a mother.
I'm not angry,
but go easy on me.
Goof-off,
I can let you get away with anything.
You can trick me,
and you can steal from me.
I can take you treating me like a loser.
But
not Hobak.
After today,
if you betray Hobak again,
I won't let you get away with it.
Oh, man...
Oh, it's me.
Are you craving for something?
How did you know?
I'm a player.
I won't be if I didn't know stuff like this.
That thing we never got to eat.
Which one?
There were so many of them.
Fish stew. I want something spicy today.
I'll see you there.
Okay.
Aunt.
You're home early.
I have to go back out.
I have plans for dinner.
I'll go wash up.
Okay.
It's me, Sangnam.
Are you sure?
I'll be right over.
Aunt,
he found her.
I'll see you later.
Sangnam!
One fish stew.
Okay. Just a minute.
Can we have some kimchi?
Okay.
Take her order.
She can't have that table and not order.
We have a business to run.
Im sorry. Let me wait a little more.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure...
You're really sure?
Yes, I am.
- Did you ask?
- Yes.
Why don't you order something?
You've been sitting here for an hour.
This is a restaurant.
I'm sorry.
I'll come back another time.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
We're not open yet.
We're not open.
Do you recognize me?
Of course I do.
You look old.
How many years has it been?
How did you know I was here?
Why wouldn't I know?
It's a small country.
You sound mad.
Do you recognize him?
You must be Sangnam.
You're all grown up.
If I ran into you in the streets, I wouldn't recognize you.
Are you married?
I'm not.
You must be needing something,
but you've come to the wrong place.
This is how I live.
I can't give you any money.
It's been 20 years,
and that's all you can say to your son?
What am I supposed to say?
- Sis.
- Why? What?
Then why did you come to me?
There's nothing for you here.
I'm barely making ends meet.
We're not here to get anything from you.
Why can't you spit that gum out?
Stop picking on me.
You saw me, so go.
I don't want my neighbors seeing you.
And don't blame me for anything.
I had my reasons.
You dad probably painted me as a witch,
but you'll understand when you get married.
Are you 30? 31?
I'm 20.
You are?
Why did you look for me?
I'm barely making a living here.
I'm barely getting by.
I can't believe you!
Aunt.
Let's go.
We should've have come.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for coming to see you to see if you can help us out.
How could you say that?
He came to see you because you're his mom!
Is that all you can say?
How can you be so mean?
Why didn't you ask him to sit down?
How can you talk to him while chewing gum like that?
What's wrong with you?
He thought of you as his mom...
From the way I feel right now.
I could just slap you.
Go ahead. Slap me.
How can you say that to your older sister?
You're not my sister.
Do you even know what you did to my life?
What did I do?
You married a rich man, thanks to me.
Why would you end it?
I heard you divorced him.
You had an affair, stole money from Daese,
borrowed money under our parents name,
and sold your own little sister.
And you're still living with that bastard!
Bastard? He's your brother in law!
Brother in law?
Yeah, right.
Because of you, I was sold.
I had to dump the man I love
and marry for money to pay your debt.
You're crazy.
You married a rich man and had a good life,
but instead of thanking me, you cry.
I knew you were a wretch,
but you're worse than I had remembered.
Don't you feel bad for what you did to Sangnam?
Don't you feel guilty as his mom?
Aren't you grateful he grew up to be such a nice man after you abandoned him?
Instead of cooking him dinner,
you had him stand here and kicked him out!
Sangnam can't even date anyone because of you.
Did you know that?
How can he meet anyone?
He seems to be doing really bad.
Like father, like son.
He'll be poor for the rest of his life.
You must have come to ask for money,
but as you can see, I don't have any.
Is that all you can say?
We didn't come for money!
Why did you come?
Because you're his mom! His mom!
To be honest,
I was going to let bygones by bygones
and forgive you and I hoped
Sangnam would finally get a mother.
Are you afraid of your family breaking up?
You call that a family?
Is your child with him your only child?
Sangnam is your child, too!
God will punish you.
You shouldn't do that to your own child.
Don't ever come to us.
Daese told me never to find you.
Now I know why.
I shouldn't have come.
Have a nice life, you wretch!
Hey!
Hey! Ugh!
What are you looking at?
Wow, that's a very expensive car.
Who is he?
Let me give you a tip.
Don't fall for me.
I hate it when a woman cries.
We had fish stew tonight.
The most delicious fish stew in the world.
And girls, congratulate me.
He finally proposed to me.
Yay!
I finally met him.
The man who says he'll do anything for me.
Today is the happiest day of my life.
Father.
Where are you?
I'm out.
You have to come quickly.
We have to fix an excavator,
but the service center is closed.
We'll have to fix it tonight if we want to use it at the construction site tomorrow.
Okay.
Sangnam, check if there's oil leaking.
Here.
Check the connecting pump.
Where? Here?
This won't do.
Sangnam, go fetch the rope.
Pull! Pull harder! Harder!
- Pull!
- One, two!
Sangnam, tie that up over there!
Pull! Harder! Sangnam, pull!
Pull harder! Harder!
Pull harder!
Subtitles by KBS World
I'm left breathless from running around all day, in search of love, in search of life
Beneath the skies of Seoul I get closer to my dreams
Both love and friendship coexist under the sky
I'll meet that man. As soon as possible.
He should tell you where he's going.
When we're married, I'll destroy him.
I went to see the director.
What did you say?
Is your father the only person who matters?
Are you crazy?
Was sending $200 to my father crazy?
I want to be treated like a human being.
I never see any of your faces.
I go to work alone and I come home alone.
Am I not your family?