Subtitles by KBS World
Oh, cold.
Where were you?
Go back to sleep.
I wasn't seeing a woman, so don't worry.
You better not!
Don, I have to go to the bathroom.
Bathroom?
Don, don't leave me. Stay, okay?
- Okay.
- You must, okay?
Okay.
Don!
Yeah?
Are you there?
I'm here, so don't worry.
Don!
I'm here!
Don't go. I'm scared.
Don't worry. I won't go.
Ouch, ouch...
Don.
Yes?
Why are you out here?
Yeongdal said she was scared.
What?
But it's not a public bathroom!
She should be ashamed of herself!
Don!
Don, are you there? Don?
Don?
I'm not Don.
Is it you, Bong?
I'm scared, so can you stay there?
Huh? Uh, okay.
Bong!
Uh, yes.
I thought you left.
I'll stay here.
Is someone in there?
Yeongdal.
Still? She's been in there forever!
Hey, hurry it up, won't you?
There are other people here, too, you know?
It's okay.
Some people have to go to work.
How can she just sit in there?
Please give me a few minutes.
She's so dense, so dense.
Hurry up!
Bong, are you still there?
Yes, I am.
Can you get me some toilet paper?
Uh, okay.
Hey, Don, Don...
Yeongdal, here.
Mother, did you sleep well?
I kept having bad dreams.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo...
Telling me to hurry up won't help,
especially when I'm constipated.
Oh, boy.
Huh? Mother...
Don't do this.
Enroll in a test prep course, judge.
Mom.
You've seen how things are going here.
You're the only hope for us.
There's no money for a test prep course.
I'll pay for it, no matter what.
So start studying again,
if you don't want me to die of anger.
It's too tiny here. I'll get indigestion.
This reminds me of when I fled from the war.
We didn't have a table like this back then,
so we ate on newspaper.
Oh, the bathroom is a problem.
It's too cold in there.
I thought my butt was going to freeze.
I thought my butt was going to freeze, too.
Bong didn't your butt freeze?
Huh? Uh, yes.
Oh, right.
I should be more polite, right?
Bottom.
No?
We should decide who goes first.
You can't just go in there early and stay there for hours.
Those who go to work should use it first,
and those who don't can go later.
Bong had to run to school this morning.
It was good exercise.
Running to the bathroom is not exercising!
Father, uncle, and Daebak should go first,
and the others can go later, I think.
Let Yeongdal go instead of me.
I can hold it.
Yeongdal's pregnant, so let her go first.
She has the priority pass.
You're the best, the best!
I'm eating!
Stop talking about the bathroom!
- Mommy!
- What is it? What?
I killed several yesterday.
My palm hurts.
You should learn to kill them.
It's not scary.
I can't do that!
You're eating with that hand?
You should go and wash your hands.
What about Subak?
Is she on a diet?
Don't give her any food!
She doesn't deserve any.
Look how she's acting.
She's still sleeping.
She won't even come out.
She hasn't learned anything from this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
She's too sorry to come out, I'm sure.
I'm going to wash my hands.
Haebak, take this to Subak.
Give it to me. I'll take it to her.
Subak's not here!
- She's not?
- No?
She's not here either.
Where did she go so early in the morning?
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen her all morning.
Me neither. But she slept with us.
Mom!
Look and her bag is missing.
Oh...
Mom, I'm sorry.
Father, I'm sorry.
I can't stay here. I must go.
I'll come back when I make money.
Mom, I'm sorry for being a bad daughter.
Please look after Aeji and Jungji.
I'll get our old house back.
I won't come back before that.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Father, please forgive me.
She's crazy...
I can't believe she's done this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo...
Where did she go?
She has nowhere to go.
She can't even do her own laundry.
How can she make any money?
She must be penniless...
What do we do?
What if something happens?
Don't cry.
You're wasting your tears.
She needs to be punished for what she did.
She needs to suffer, so she'll wise up.
She'll be 40 soon and she can't even do laundry.
That's embarrassing!
She's healthy, so she'll be fine!
This is all your doing!
She was already scared out of her wits,
so why did you have to scream at her?
What if something awful happens to her?
What?
Mom, stop it.
I hope Subak doesn't do anything stupid.
How childish. When she's that old.
Do you have to go now?
Yes.
Can we talk?
I have to go to the construction site.
But you've been there already.
I have other places to go, too.
Sangnam, I'm sorry.
It was all my fault.
I shouldn't have treated your mother like that.
I'm sorry.
If you did that to my mom, I'd be mad, too.
I'm really sorry.
Hobak.
Can we talk now?
Yes, I'm in my room.
Subak is gone.
What?
Do you know where she could've gone?
I don't know...
What's wrong with her?
I know.
How can she leave home right now?
What about her kids?
I'm sure she was upset for making everyone move there.
But what about mom and father?
This is nuts.
See if you can figure out where she went.
Okay, Hobak.
Imagine how she must have felt.
Imagine how awful she must have felt.
I was really angry at her, enough to want to beat her up, but I'm heartbroken now.
Where could she have gone?
I have no idea.
You can't even guess?
I really can't.
Doesn't Subak have any friends?
I don't know.
But you were married for so many years!
I know.
She didn't go to any of her friends.
I don't think she kept in contact with any.
Then where could she have gone?
What if she does something stupid?
She wanted to die when you went bankrupt.
The letter didn't have anything like that.
You should wait. I'll drop by after work.
Did Subak call?
Don't worry too much.
Okay.
Hey.
Did you bring it?
I couldn't because of the Old Geezer.
He goes through your bag at the gate.
Oh, I'm furious.
Why won't the Old Geezer transfer out?
He makes me not want to come to school.
I came because I had to.
Shouldn't he retire soon?
He must be ancient.
Why is he still working?
What did you just say?
We didn't say anything.
We were talking about Old Geezer.
Don't call him Old Geezer.
What's wrong with Old Geezer?
You call him that, too!
Does he like you because you're a Wang, too?
What are you doing?
Want Daebak, you stay.
The rest of you, go.
Come with me.
Tell me. Why did you fight?
Just because.
Were you smoking?
You know I've been feeling really badly.
How could you add to my problems?
How can you get into a fight?
How can you go up against three boys?
Will seeing you getting beat up make me glad?
You'll know how I feel when you have your own kids.
Do you know what you did wrong?
No.
What?
I don't think I did anything wrong.
How dare you!
If they do it again, I'll get them.
How will you get them?
Please don't cause problems at school.
How will I face the other students?
And how will I face other teachers?
If they knew you were my son,
they'd think I'm a bad teacher.
Keep this up and I'll tell everyone.
Please don't!
Then try listening to me.
Go.
Is this Yeongja?
Are you keeping in touch with Wang Subak?
Okay.
Yes?
Can we talk?
I'm busy at the moment.
Let's talk later.
Honey, I sent you $30 yesterday.
You spent that all?
When will you pass the exam?
Just give up.
I'm getting tired.
And why won't you answer your phone?
You're not seeing that girl, are you?
If you are, I'll kill you.
I'll talk to you again.
Hello, editor.
What brings you here?
I was passing by and thought of you.
Who'd believe that?
Why? You need something from me?
You're very sharp.
I'd like to work.
Do you have anything open?
I thought you got married.
Is your husband unemployed?
No, he isn't.
You yelled at me about my unemployed boyfriend.
I have an appointment.
I'll see you later.
Editor.
Please.
I have to work.
You didn't think you'd come back to beg me for a job, did you?
Take these pastries back.
Don't you have to save every penny?
Come in.
Hello.
How are you?
You came to see your husband?
Yes.
Why won't you come visit?
I don't want to trouble you.
It's not trouble.
Come by for dinner.
And this is for you.
Thanks. I'll have it later.
Sangnam, I'll be back.
I'm meeting Mr. Kim.
Have a good meeting.
Goodbye.
What is it?
Can you buy me lunch?
I have plans.
How can you drop by like this?
I have a job.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to be.
Didn't her vice principal father teach her any manners?
It won't happen again.
I'll talk to her.
I couldn't sleep because I was so sad.
I'm supposed to be her mother in law,
so how could she talk to me like that?
If she respects you, she wouldn't do that.
Don't you think so?
Men these days are too nice to women.
You shouldn't be like that.
What if she treats your father like that?
She wouldn't.
How would you know?
You didn't date her very long.
You couldn't know her that well.
I'm okay, but
you should talk to her for
you and your father's sake.
I'll make her apologize to you.
I'm not saying this to make her apologize.
Where have you been?
There should be someone home.
How could you leave the house empty?
I thought aunt was home.
She has her cooking lessons!
I'm sorry.
I hate coming home to an empty house.
I never liked it.
You should get permission to go out!
Daese, I'm sorry.
Sunjeong, make sure you teach her well.
I'm tired of spelling everything out.
Why didn't you tell me you were going out?
I would've skipped my class if I knew.
I forgot.
I had an errand and I went to Sangnam...
You should be more thoughtful.
And don't cry so often.
Crying all the time is not a good thing.
And a newlywed shouldn't cry like that.
I won't.
No experience, no work history.
There's only manual labor.
Like what?
Restaurants or cleaning.
Even those are hard to come by.
You must get a medical check.
Have you done housekeeping or babysitting?
I'll do anything.
I'll get in trouble if you do badly.
How about working as a bar girl?
I can't do that.
Do the dishes and clear the tables.
Be quick on your feet.
Okay.
Hello.
Kitchen's that way!
Oh, what are you doing?
Be careful!
You can't make money like that.
This is all I can give you.
Be glad I'm not charging you for broken dishes.
[Sauna]
You'll freeze to death.
Cover yourself with these.
Mom! Agh!
Mom!
Hey!
How dare you...
Where is she sleeping?
How can she do this to us?
She'll come home eventually.
She's just awful.
May I help you?
Well...
You can tell me.
I'm sorry,
but can I stay here until the morning?
Bounce, bounce
Pounding bounce, bounce...
Oh, I can't sing because I'm upset.
There was an older girl who worked here,
but she was just awful.
She got fired because she was bad.
I hope you do better than her.
Keep the windows, floor and the bathroom clean, memorize the menu...
Memorize the point card and discount cards,
don't forget to stamp the coupons,
and don't make mistakes on orders.
Done?
Hello. May I take your order?
I'd like an Americano.
What size would you like?
Tall, please.
- Do you have the point card?
- Yes.
You can't!
You're too young.
I can do a good job.
You're pretty persistent.
How can you do this for two hours?
I have to make money. Please!
Fine.
Get your parents to sign this.
You're underage, so I need their permission.
Thank you.
Hiring
Server / Kitchen helper
Room and board provided
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You've never done this before?
I have but it was really hot.
I'm sorry.
Goodbye.
What are you doing? Clean that up.
Okay.
Can we have some radish kimchi?
She was talking to you.
- Got it?
- Excuse me?
Radish kimchi.
What about kimchi?
Bring some to the customer.
Oh, okay.
Bounce, bounce...
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
- Excuse me!
- Yes?
They belong to someone.
Oh, they don't belong to anyone!
They belong to who get them first.
I'll come by early tomorrow for more!
Bounce, bounce...
Pounding bounce, bounce...
When you turn around
Our eyes might meet...
Hey!
How come there's none here?
Some old lady came and got them all.
What? That witch!
Here.
Oh, this is it?
I've actually given you a lot.
But I brought you a whole bunch!
Anyway, that feels great.
Oh, boy.
Don't you know what this house means...
Don't you know that?
She's having a hard time?
But she does whatever she wants!
You drove Minjung to bankruptcy, but when he divorced you, his luck changed!
How could you do such a horrible thing?
You're not even human!
Sangnam, I have an important engagement.
- Do whatever you want.
- Can you tell...
Excuse me,
I'm sorry, but can I get $100 in advance?
But you just started working here!
Is this what you've been doing?
Then can I get $50?
I really need it.
I'm begging you.
Gwangbak, how are you doing?
I'm fine.
Mom, I'll drop by for dinner.
Did you make father seaweed soup?
Seaweed soup?
Oh, I can't believe this.
I forgot your father's birthday!
You did?
What do we do?
Why do I bother?
Like your grandmother says, I should die.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo...
I'll talk to Hobak and bring some food.
We can have a party.
I'll see you, mom.
Oh, boy.
Anggeum,
today's Bong's birthday.
I remember because Gwangbak called.
What do we do?
You and I are both useless.
How can we forget Bong's birthday?
Why didn't you remind me?
This is all Subak's fault!
You should make seaweed soup for dinner.
The girls are coming for dinner.
And stop talking about Subak. I hate it.
You still need to listen to it.
It's your fault for raising her like that.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Let's make everything except for the soup.
What will you make?
Braised short ribs?
You can make that?
Okay. Make that and some salad.
I'll make some noodles and get some sashimi.
I'll see you at dinner.
Subak!
What happened?
Oh, man!
Where are you staying? Huh?
You don't need to know that.
I was so worried!
And you won't answer the phone!
It's cold. Let's go somewhere.
I can't. I have to go back.
Here.
What's this?
Today's father's birthday.
You didn't forget?
How could I?
It isn't much.
Please give it to him.
Tell him happy birthday.
Subak, let's go home.
They are all worried about you.
I can't go home without money.
No, I won't.
Hobak,
I'm grateful for you and Gwangbak.
You got them a place to live.
I'm the eldest, but I've been a nuisance.
Subak.
You're the eldest daughter now.
Pretend I don't even exist.
How can I do that?
Subak, tell me where you're staying.
Take care of mom and father.
And take care of the others.
Hobak,
I'm sorry.
I should go.
Subak. Subak!
Subak! Subak, hold on!
Come here! Wait!
Wait, hold on!
Subak! Hold on!
Subak! Hold on! Wait, Subak! Hold on!
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Subak!
Subak! Oh, no!
Subak is impossible.
She's so childish.
Stop it.
It broke my heart to see her like that.
She's nothing but trouble for your parents.
And I'm nothing but trouble for you, right?
Dad!
Yes, how was your day?
Go wash your hands and do your homework!
Look at them!
They won't even look at me.
Of course. I'm their mom.
You're not popular here anymore.
Sintong, Bangtong, you don't see me?
We do.
See? This is why I live.
That smells delicious.
Dad, what's all these?
How dare you!
Can I have one?
No! These are for your grandparents.
Where did you learn your manners?
I've never seen such bad table manners.
You eat so much and you never get sick.
I told you to wash your hands!
Go change and do your homework.
Fine.
Dad, I hate you.
Those little devils.
I don't know who they take after.
Such goof-offs.
Just like their dad.
What is it?
This is how you act?
You're like a mom.
You're a perfect housewife now.
Of course.
I do everything perfect.
You hurry up.
We have no time to waste.
Fine.
- What are you doing?
- Mommy!
You never say father?
Sunjeong calls for men when she's startled.
What's that? That smells good.
Braised short ribs.
You're taking that somewhere?
Well, yes...
You're stealing from this house?
How can you say that?
I caught you red handed, huh?
Give me herbal tea with egg yolk.
I can't make that.
I told you to learn how.
Oh, I'm still full from the sushi yesterday.
Is it because I ate it with my son?
I don't think I need anything else.
You had sushi with Sangnam?
Sangnam didn't tell you?
We had lunch yesterday.
He was so sorry because of you.
He kept apologizing for you.
You better be good to me,
if you want your husband to love you.
How can you not know that?
Don't you have a college degree?
Or did you get it illegally?
Excuse me?
Forget about it.
Who cares how you got your degree?
The important thing is who I am to you.
Oh, that sounded cool, right?
- Did you get it?
- Mother,
I didn't want to hurt Sangnam, so I said nothing.
About what?
You know what.
I don't believe you.
Are you talking back at me again?
Now I really have to get it from you.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
And i don't have any money to give you.
Wait!
Oh, I'm thirsty.
Get me some fresh fruit juice.
That girl!
Where are you going?
Huh? Oh.
I forgot about an appointment.
Cancel the juice.
I don't have to pay, right?
What are you doing?
Mop the floor. Don't sit down!
It's not easy to make money!
You want me to deduct your pay?
That's mean.
That was the first time I sat down all day.
I ended up here because of a reason,
but don't be so mean to me.
I was in the Miss Korea pageant.
Miss Korea?
Yes.
Who cares if you were?
Can you cook? Can you clean?
I wasn't going to tell you this,
but I had models and actresses work here.
You don't know what you're talking about.
Hurry up and mop the floor.
Make it shine so you can see your Miss Korea face off it.
It's suffocating here.
Sit closer together.
Is someone sitting comfortably?
Father, you're an exception.
Since it's your birthday, you're forgiven.
Oh, I forgot to get cake.
Minjung's bringing it.
We should've made
seaweed soup for breakfast.
I'm so sorry, Bong.
I forgot, too.
I've never forgotten your birthday before.
You should just dump me.
It's okay. I'm glad everyone's here.
Thanks
for coming to celebrate my birthday.
This is all my fault.
Blame me.
We'll laugh about this one day.
Mom.
Father, don't cry on such a nice day.
We will laugh about this one day.
Yes, Bong.
Let's all eat.
Happy birthday, Bong.
Thank you, mother.
Not liking my in laws is affecting me.
You wait and see.
Like mother, like daughter.
I'll make her cry!
What else could I do?
[Provisional Attachment Notice]
Yes, mother.
Hey. Go in.
We don't live there anymore.
I'll explain what happened.
I'm here.
Go!
You're here?
Welcome.
Squeeze in.
The house will explode.
I can't believe my ears.
Sit here, Minjung.
Even Minjung is here, so where's Sangnam?
He went to China on business.
Father, I made these ribs.
And Sedal made this.
He's like a housewife now.
Housekeeping is getting more fun.
I'm becoming an expert now.
Good. Housekeeping is actually fun.
Father,
here.
Is that money?
Subak wanted me to give that to you.
You met her? Where is she?
How did you meet her?
She called.
She gave that to me for your birthday.
Oh...
She gave you that for him?
What is she doing?
I asked, but she wouldn't tell me.
She won't come home unless she makes money.
But you should've found out.
I tried, but I lost her.
How did she look?
She lost weight and she cried.
Oh, no.
Don't feel sorry for her.
She needs to suffer, so she'll learn.
She didn't want to live here, so she left.
I'm sure she didn't leave because of that.
Her letter said she'll get the house back.
You believe her?
How can she make money?
She left because of you!
What?
She left because you were mean to her.
Imagine how she must have felt!
You were so mean to her when we moved.
She was miserable already,
so how could you yell at her like that?
How could she stay here?
It's not like she borrowed money for her.
She was just trying to make money
because Minjung wasn't making enough.
So how could you be so mean?
You threw her out.
You're crazy.
You spoiled her rotten and you still haven't learned anything!
Mother, please stop.
Right. It's father's birthday.
Okay, let's move right on
and sing the birthday song.
Grandmother, mother,
put your strength into the singing.
Go!
Happy birthday to you! Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear father, happy birthday...
Father, make a wish and blow out the candles.
- Happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
Are we there yet?
It's up ahead.
We're almost there.
You keep saying that!
Where is it?
Oh, I'm dying.
Here.
Mom! Bong!
Come out.
Oh...
Go.
I went this morning.
Go and pack!
No.
Do it now!
Don't scream.
You'll startle the baby.
Who cares about the baby when my daughter's dying?
I can't believe all of you.
How can you not tell me what happened?
How can you make my daughter live here?
Neighbors!
Oh, stop it, mother.
Why are you calling the neighbors?
You stay out!
Mom.
You stay out! You're all useless.
How can you be so sneaky?
Mrs. Park, please calm down.
You stay out!
How dare you scream at my husband?
It's okay. I'm sure she didn't mean it.
I'm sorry.
I said go pack!
No! I'm not packing.
Don.
You come right here!
- Mother!
- Oh, mother.
Stop it! Loser, how can this be?
Loser? Don't call him that.
He's your son in law.
How rude.
But you call my son Goof-off!
Let's go.
You don't even have your own room here!
How can you make them sleep out here?
I wanted it!
I told you to take the room! I'll sleep here!
Ask anyone! How can this be?
Let's go!
You should go with her.
No! I'm not going!
She won't go and I can't let her, mother.
Mom, mom. Let's go.
Mom, let's go home.
Let me go!
Father, we're leaving.
- You come here!
- Let's go, let's go.
Oh, boy.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
What are you going to do?
You were supposed to take good care of her.
You're 35, no, 36.
How can you have no money at all?
Mother, if you just hold on...
Hold on? For what?
You should at least have your own room!
The whole family's there with you!
How can you sleep in the living room?
I'll get you a room, so move out!
I won't do that.
Why not?
I don't want your help.
So please remember that.
I'm different from Sedal.
What did Sedal do?
Did Sedal get help from your family?
Hobak supported him.
- Hey!
- He's right.
I'm going to support my wife and kid.
I won't get any help from anyone.
So stay out of our business. Bye.
Loser, you!
And I'm not Loser.
Call me Don.
If you keep calling me Loser,
I'll call you Mrs. Park.
Oh, my! Did you hear him?
He's right.
You're wrong!
If your family went bankrupt,
you should've told me!
Go and get her!
I can't drag Yeongdal here against her will.
Let her stay there for now, and if she can't
take it anymore, we'll go get her.
But we should leave her there for now.
Ditto.
What?
I agree with her.
Mom, just forget about her.
Let her live there, no matter what happens.
When I married Hobak,
we lived in a basement apartment.
What if her family dragged her home?
But she's different from you!
We're the same. Exactly the same.
All your kids are the same.
This was meant to be.
Ugh! Oh! Ugh!
This is nutty, nutty, nuts.
Oh, that stung!
I can't support you both.
Uncle has to go to college, too,
and Subak's in a different city so
I need to send her living expenses.
Hobak, you should drop out. You're younger.
Subak's the eldest.
Father, that's not fair.
I'm a better student.
I have to graduate. I can't drop out.
I want to become an announcer.
You can't.
How many times must I tell you?
The eldest should get a college degree.
You only care about Subak.
This isn't fair.
Subak.
Yes, father.
You must study hard.
You're studying for Hobak, too.
You're the eldest.
My firstborn, okay?
Minjung?
A registered letter came for Mr. Ko Minjung.
Thank you.
[Seoul Family Court, Mr. Ko Minjung]
Now only our family's here.
I'm in this family, right?
Of course, you are.
Thank you for staying with us.
I know.
Mr. Wang, wait.
Not that.
I keep forgetting.
This is my paycheck.
We should save money to buy a house.
We can do it if we worked together.
Oh, you should keep it.
It's okay.
I'm family, so I should pitch in.
She's offering so let's take it.
Oh, I didn't mean it.
I won't take money from Yeongdal.
Just pitch in a little bit.
You should save it for when you move out.
Remember how angry your mother was?
Bong, I made money, too.
How did you make money?
You don't need to know.
Mom, did you collect boxes?
How did you know?
It's obvious.
I brought a lot and he gave me just that.
Mother, please don't do that.
What if you fall and get hurt?
I won't. I'll walk carefully.
Making money was fun.
Father, I got a part time job, too.
Where?
I'm working at a cafe.
Shut up!
I won't yell since it's your father's birthday.
Enroll in a test prep course.
I will put you through college.
Father,
can you sign this?
[Employment Request for People under 15]
You want to work at a convenience store?
Yes, if I can get your signature...
Don't.
What's your job?
It's studying.
That's how you can help me.
But I'm a member of this family.
Aunt is giving her paycheck,
so I should help out, too.
I'm the eldest son.
Let me work during vacation.
Daebak,
there are others who can work,
so wait until you go to high school.
I'm against the idea, too.
Thank you, everyone.
I feel encouraged.
I feel strong.
I think I can get back on my feet again.
Okay! Bong's going to get back on his feet!
So I will sing a song now.
And I'll dance, since I know how its done.
Great!
Goof- off and Yeongdal are life savers.
What would we have done without them?
I know.
Be good to Yeongdal's mother.
We want to but she keeps ruining it.
Tonight's your night,
so why don't you sing a song? Singer Wang!
I will if you ask.
Yey! Applause! Yay!
One, two, three, four!
Every parent feels the same
They want their children to be happy
I'm rooting for everyone
Don't call me stingy and make fun of me
I still have some spirit left
Wonderful, wonderful, a father's youth
- Bravo!
A father's life!
Hey, singer!
Right now? Why?
You'll find out.
Is something up at home?
Okay.
Hello.
Sit.
What's going on?
I thought we couldn't let this pass.
Apologize about last time.
Hurry.
I'm very sorry about what happened.
Please forgive me.
I was disappointed that day,
but now you apologized, I feel better.
Let's try to get along, okay?
Sangnam, get me some coffee.
Okay.
Did you see?
My son's on my side.
Don't be cheeky.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
What are you doing?
I left the house empty. Goodbye.
This is my fault. I can't blame anyone.
She has no respect for me.
She left?
Leave her alone.
At least she apologized.
Sangnam!
Oh, hot, hot.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
You're upset about apologizing?
But don't you think you should've?
- So I did.
- But this is wrong.
I wanted you to be sincere.
You forced me to apologize.
I wasn't prepared to do it.
Why do you need to prepare?
Why do you need that for apologizing?
I'm sorry.
She's my mom.
All else aside, she brought me into this world.
I won't let you mistreat her.
You forcing me to apologize
and me apologizing without sincerity
made us the same people, so I'm sorry.
Satisfied?
Just forget it.
Subtitles by KBS World
Are you office wife and office husband?
Did the document get processed?
Not yet.
After today, that becomes null and void.
Minjung didn't know it,
but who could stand that?
How can you do this?
How can you turn Sangnam against me?
I won't let it go on.
How dare you talk to me like that?
What are you doing in this neighborhood?
I know someone here.
Go see Minjung and beg him for forgiveness.
You made me cry, but I still loved you.
You remained the same.