Subtitles by KBS World
Who is it?
It's me.
Oh, father.
- Did the moving go well?
- Yes.
I finished late at the Office of Education,
so I hurried over.
Im late, huh?
You didn't have to.
Come in, father.
Is everyone gone?
They're in such a rush!
It's a nice apartment. Roomy.
Where's Sedal?
He's on a business trip.
I haven't unpacked yet.
I'll give you a tour.
This is the master bedroom.
It's nice and roomy.
There's a bathroom.
Nice. Why didn't you get a bed?
Later. I can buy other things used,
but the bed, I want to buy a new one.
Okay.
- I'll show you the boys' rooms.
- Okay.
Nice job on moving.
And nice job on buying this apartment.
Buy something with this.
It's not much.
Since it's from you, I'll take it.
I need a clock so I'll get one with this.
I'm not sure if that's enough.
If it's not, bill me.
I'll get a real expensive one and bill you.
Have a seat.
No, I should go home.
It's nice and roomy.
And the wallpapers look new.
Was it Sedal?
Yes.
You can enjoy a decent life now.
What's wrong?
Were you crying?
I'm so happy that I cried.
What did your mom say?
Wasn't she happy?
Father, I'll throw a real housewarming party.
Please come back then.
You had one already so it's okay.
I'm going, okay?
Go to bed.
What's that?
It's nothing, father?
What is it?
Why did you throw all the food away?
[Name: Wang Subak]
Hello?
It's me.
It's me, too.
Why are you calling at this hour?
You didn't call to hear my voice,
and mother is at the senior citizen's center.
What else do you want to know?
Let's have lunch together.
Lunch?
You've been worried about Subak so much,
so come out and take a break.
I can't afford to do that.
I have to make lunch for mother.
She can skip lunch once.
I can't believe my ears.
If she did, the Korean War would mean nothing.
She's having lunch at the center.
She is?
Okay. Where should I see you?
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Your reservation is under?
- Wang Bong.
Yes, this way.
Mom.
I called her to join us since she moved.
Come in.
Did your moving go well?
Yes.
I couldn't go because I was aching all over.
I'm glad it went well.
Where should I sit?
Next to your husband, of course.
Hobak, you sit there.
It's not that good.
But expensive.
But you ate it all.
Why am I the only one drinking?
I have to go back to school.
Hobak, have some.
Since we're done eating and since we're all together...
I already know.
When you only called us over,
it means you want us to get it out.
Not get it out.
Talk things out.
You should be able to work things out.
There's nothing to work out.
I'll take a stroll so talk to each other.
Hobak, tell her everything you want to say.
Did you ask your father for this?
No.
I didn't know.
He just asked me to lunch.
It doesn't matter if you knew.
Since we're here, say what you will.
Go ahead.
On the day I moved,
I was sad because you didn't come.
There's nothing to feel sad about.
Talking about feeling sad,
I could talk about it for 3 straight days.
I know.
Like you said, I never bought you anything,
and I never gave you any allowance.
And I disappointed you when I got married.
I'm glad you know.
I know I made some mistakes,
but still, mom,
you only loved Subak,
and that really breaks my heart.
You always compared me to her, told me I'm not even half as good to you as her.
But you really are not good to me.
Is that why you beat me?
Why did you beat me?
When did I ever beat you?
You beat me whenever you got mad.
You beat me until the day I got married.
You grabbed me by my hair,
dragged me around,
pushed me against the wall, spun me.
You beat me with whatever was in your hand,
be it a frying pan or broom.
If I'd deserved it,
I wouldn't have been so upset.
Now that I have my own kids, I understand.
3 years ago, Sintong fought with a kid at his kindergarten, so I spanked him.
It broke my heart.
I cried so hard.
I could never hit him again.
That's how moms are.
Didn't it hurt you when you beat me up like that?
What's wrong with you?
I don't remember any of that!
You don't?
How can you not remember?
Shut up.
I can't believe you'd make up such things.
Get up. Let's go.
Mom.
What's wrong with you?
Tell me one thing before leaving.
Tell me you're sorry before you go.
What?
Tell me you're sorry, that's all I want.
That you're sorry for beating me.
Say you're sorry for mistreating me.
I slaved away raising you and this is what I get.
You treated me like I was a nuisance.
When Subak played with dolls, I was in the kitchen doing the dishes.
She always had new clothes while I only got hand me downs.
You always loved Subak more than me,
and even now, you still do that.
Did you know that I thought you were my stepmom?
You think I don't have anything to say?
I was abused because of you by your grandma.
Because I had two girls in a row.
Do you know how difficult she made my life?
How can you say that?
How can a mom say that to her daughter?
Why can't I?
Fine.
Let's talk about it then.
You say I don't love you like I love Subak,
but you should think about it.
She's married but she always took care of  the family, so of course I love her more.
And think about what happened to her.
She's bankrupt and you bought an apartment!
It's like having a party next to a funeral,
and having a barbecue next to a burning house.
You're heartless.
I'm disgusted with what you did.
I did go to the bank after we met.
I cleaned out my account to help Subak.
But when I heard someone call my boys beggars, I lost it.
I couldn't give the money to her.
So I decided to buy an apartment.
Was that so wrong?
What's going on?
Everything's fine.
Do you know what my dream was?
You never had a dream.
I wanted to become an announcer.
Everyone knew, but you didn't, did you?
You try taking care of your mother in law and raise several kids at the same time.
You wouldn't be able to remember anything.
I had to quit college because of Subak.
If only I had gotten my degree...
There's no guarantee you would've made it.
But you're doing fine right now.
Why are you bringing ancient history back?
You're getting old, too,
so what's the use of talking about how I abused you?
I'm not trying to make use of it.
I want us to be on good terms,
like how other moms and daughters are.
No,
like Subak and you,
I want to go to the sauna with you,
and go to a nice restaurant with you.
You say you get angry when you see me.
I wonder if you ever loved me!
You're totally crazy.
I raised you because I loved you.
You're married and have two kids,
so how can you ask such a thing?
And you call yourself human?
Let's pretend I did those things.
But why would you bring that up now?
At a restaurant of all places?
This is the thanks I get for raising you?
Let's go.
Don't just sit there and take it.
I agree.
Not you. Hobak.
Wait for me outside.
I can't believe she attacked me like that.
Why in the world did you invite her?
Why didn't you go to Hobak's new place?
I said I was sick.
Would you have done that to Subak?
That's why she acted like that.
You were so harsh on her when she was a kid,
so try to be warm to her from now on.
Don't break her heart anymore.
Love flows from top to bottom.
Reach out to her first.
She's your child.
I was outside listening, and I couldn't stand it.
You go and teach your students instead of trying to teach me.
I feel sorry for those married to teachers.
I know a woman whose son's wife is a teacher,
and she acts like she's a teacher at home,
treating her mother in law like a student.
That's because she deserves it.
Did you two plan on this?
I can't believe what just happened to me.
Hobak is your own daughter.
Put yourself in her shoes.
Pretend you're Hobak.
I'd feel the same even if I did.
If I were Hobak, I'd be thinking,
oh, my mom's upset because of me.
I wouldn't flip out like that.
Don't you feel proud about how far she came from that basement efficiency?
Even strangers would congratulate her!
Is Subak your only child?
She ordered Chinese and waited for you.
Imagine how she felt when she had to put all that food in the trash.
She never spends money on herself.
She'd skip meals just to save money.
How would she have felt?
You understand your daughter very well,
so why can't you understand me?
Try to think about how I feel!
You don't understand your own daughter,
and you expect me to understand you?
We're not the ones related by blood here.
Think about what you did,
if you don't want to lose her forever.
Come with me.
The address is right, but that's not ours.
I'm sorry.
Parcel service.
Oh, yes.
Nobody was home, so I left it with No. 502.
How can you leave it with No. 502?
We hate each other.
Excuse me?
We don't even talk!
You have to get it back!
It's right next door.
Hello? Sir?
Parcel service.
I've been looking for your house for an hour.
It's the right address.
Excuse me?
You moved yesterday?
Please bring them here.
It's one town over.
It'll only take 10 minutes.
Well, that's not my area.
Who cares? It's the next town.
You have to bring them now.
Hello.
Oh?
Mr. Wang!
Hello.
Can I use this place for a short while?
Of course.
I sent everyone away just for you.
Nobody will be here.
Say hi. She's my daughter.
Hello. I'm Ho Namhyeong. I was his student.
Hi.
He's the coach here,
and he's a few years younger than you.
I hope you have fun.
Let's go.
Put these on.
Go ahead.
Why...
You should learn to blow off some steam.
Don't hold it all inside.
You'll get sick if you do.
With your husband and with your mom.
If you need to argue with them, do so.
If you want to yell at them, do so.
You can't do it at them,
but swearing at the punching bag
and beating it senseless will make you feel better.
People talk about "healing" all the time,
so I'm calling it "the swear healing."
Punch it.
Father...
It can be anyone,
anyone you hate or who broke your heart.
I'm giving you permission, so it's okay.
Do whatever you want.
Why did you?
Why did you treat me like that?
I want to be love by you, mom.
I want to be appreciated.
So why do you hate me?
Why couldn't you say you're sorry?
Why couldn't you say you love me?
Mom...
Mom... Mom...
Let's meet at the cafe.
I'm only going to wait 10 minutes.
Brush your teeth first.
You have bad breath, according to Daebak.
I don't believe my eyes.
I gave you 10 minutes.
Putting that on took 30 minutes?
I got an urgent call.
You must be a busy man.
You're very feisty today.
I thought I should see you before I went on my business trip.
You're going on a business trip?
Tell me if you need anything.
A present?
Can it be an expensive thing?
Of course.
Sunblock. It's cheaper at duty free shops, right?
What brand?
It doesn't matter.
I don't care about brands, only men.
Shh, what would you like?
Anything...
Making a man want to kiss.
Want to kiss?
How?
When you order something at a cafe,
stock your lips out and say hot chocolate.
Anything?
No,
hot chocolate.
We're out of hot chocolate.
Oh, you are?
Then I want a cappuccino.
You shouldn't...
- Two of those.
- Okay.
On your lips,
get milk foam. Like this.
It's from China. Excuse me.
I'm sorry. It's work...
It's okay.
This is Choi Sangnam.
Oh, okay.
Men get excited when they see collarbones.
Okay, Gwangbak.
Don't be too discouraged.
I'll teach you again.
The spinster student?
Yes.
How far did she go?
Physical contact.
You're teaching about physical contact?
She doesn't know anything.
Is something wrong with her?
You're only in 4th grade.
She thinks she's smart, but she's really bad at this.
She failed again today.
Hot chocolate. Is this so hard?
What? What did you teach her?
Hot chocolate.
And getting foam on the lips?
How did you know?
Did you read this, too?
The name of your spinster student is...
Gwangbak. Wang Gwangbak.
She's Daebak's sister.
Well, Miho,
you didn't tell her about us, did you?
No.
Don't tell Daebak, either.
I don't like telling others about our family.
I know. I don't either.
Let's order something cheap.
Your husband must be having a hard time.
Hand over the money and the book.
It's better to be safe than sorry.
I'm home.
This is why we're getting roaches.
I told you, this isn't temporary.
This is bad for you, so you should cook...
Leave me alone, please!
I'm sick and tired of it.
Stop saying that!
What's wrong with getting take outs?
I already know it's bad for you!
It can't get any worse than this!
What's the point of staying healthy when you have to live like this?
What's that?
It's for you.
Me?
It's here! Yes!
What's this?
Can't you tell?
It's a baby stroller.
I can tell, but where did you get it?
I bought it of course.
Where did you get the money?
But they said it would take months!
It's so pretty. Oh, my!
How much was it?
Subak.
What?
How much was this?
It wasn't much. It was cheap.
How cheap?
$3,000.
$3,000?
They have ones that are far more expensive.
This is on the cheap side.
But we can't afford...
When did you buy this?
- A long time ago.
- When?
I ordered it right after I had Jungji.
Don't lie.
The address is here.
Where did you get the money?
I got a loan.
- From where?
- A private loan company.
You went into debt to buy a baby stroller?
A baby stroller that is $3,000?
Who cares?
It's for our baby.
It'll be her first car.
We have Aeji's old stroller.
Are you crazy? That was ages ago!
Can't you understand?
It's just like why men want import cars.
You don't want this for her?
It's not that...
I'm out of words.
I can't spend a measly $3,000?
I was in the Miss Korea pageant!
What does that have to do with a stroller?
And what's this?
I'm sending Aeji to an English academy.
Everyone at her kindergarten goes.
It doesn't have to be this expensive.
You don't want her to get an education?
Just look at us.
How can we afford thousands of dollars?
We have to invest in their education,
so they don't end up like us.
Move Aeji to a cheaper kindergarten.
What?
I've been meaning to tell you that.
We can't afford that kindergarten.
What are you trying to do to our girls?
I don't go shopping anymore.
I don't even buy clothes.
And I can't do that for our girls?
And you're calling yourself their dad?
Not being able to afford those things means I'm a bad dad?
Of course it means that.
You should be able to keep up with others!
Subak,
do you know how much I make a day?
Even if I run around all day,
until my heart's about to explode,
I make less than $2,000 a month.
I deliver a sack of rice or corn and make 80 cents. 80 cents.
I don't have time for lunch,
so I eat a rice roll in the truck,
and I can't even go to the bathroom.
I have stomach, back and joint problems,
and they keep me up at night.
Did you know?
And did you know how hard it is to deal with difficult customers?
So? What? What?
Of course I want to provide for the girls.
But I can't afford it.
I just can't afford it...
Subak, let's try harder.
When I make more money, I'll make it up.
I'll make up for everything.
Let's return this.
Are you crazy?
Yes, I'm at the verge of going crazy.
What are you doing?
Don't mess with me.
This is the only thing I want.
Even if we live in a place like this,
I want my baby to have the best stroller!
Who's that?
Hey!
Welcome.
Excuse me!
Oh, this is so pretty.
What brand is this?
It's an imported brand.
Oh, it's good.
You sure can cook, Sunjeong.
I can't eat out because of your cooking.
Eat up. I made plenty.
You should be getting a daughter in law.
You're not going to let Sangnam get married?
It's not me. He doesn't want to yet.
People in our business should settle down.
I don't think he's found the right girl yet.
What happened to that girl from before?
They broke up a long time ago.
Can you find someone nice for him?
I don't know any girls, just men.
Oh, there is one!
- There is?
- Who?
- What kind of girl is she?
Why didn't I think of her earlier?
I think they'll be a great match.
I'm very curious.
Yes, father.
Have a nice trip to China.
I'll have a present for you ready.
I don't say no.
But you don't know what it is.
It's obvious.
What I love the most, a woman?
You sure are my own blood.
Have a nice trip.
He said yes.
They should meet first.
I'm sure she's great, since you're recommending her.
I hope things work out.
What are you doing here?
Did you come to see me off?
Correct.
I've been waiting here for an hour.
Incredible. I'm touched.
I was aiming for that.
But I have to go right now, actually.
I've seen you, so it's okay.
Come back without a scratch.
Go.
Bye.
Would you like to do homework at my house?
Your girlfriend gave me a warning.
She's not my girlfriend.
Not even close.
I've been tutoring her.
You've been tutoring her?
Incredible.
Why are you here?
I came to take you home.
Did you forget about the yellow card?
I'm warning you again.
Don't flirt with him.
He's mine.
But you're just a little girl!
I may be little, but I'm taking care of him.
I'm checking up on his studies, babysitting his nieces,
and teaching his sister dating tricks.
Can you do all that?
If you can, I'll let you have him.
How can I do all that?
Daebak, did you hear that?
Let's go.
Uh, okay...
- Please sign here.
- Okay.
You seem to use the parcel service often.
Yes, I like online shopping.
I see. Thank you for using the service.
Would you like something cool to drink?
It's okay. Thank you.
What's wrong with that woman?
She was the first one in.
What time is it?
It's 2 o'clock.
Well...
That stroller looks suspicious.
She's had the cover on the whole time.
Excuse us.
What is it?
This baby stroller...
It was imported.
It's not that. Please come with us.
Why?
It'll only take a minute.
There's something we must check.
Check what?
What are you doing? Let me go!
Oh, my! Oh! Let me go! Let me go!
I said let me go! Let go! Let go!
What are you doing?
How dare you drag me in here like this?
I'm sorry but can we look at the stroller?
Why? Why would you do that?
You came in at the opening hour,
and you haven't bought anything for...
So what is it you want?
Please let me check this.
Check what?
How dare you! Don't!
I said don't!
You'll wake up the baby!
What are you doing?
You think I stole something?
I'm sorry. We made a mistake...
I don't believe you!
I was a VVIP here!
Get the president here! Bring him!
I'm sorry.
Let go! How dare you belittle me like this?
I was in the Miss Korea pageant!
How dare you!
Minjung?
I'm fine, of course.
You're not ill, are you?
Isn't delivering packages hard?
I'm okay, father.
I'm used to it now.
Father, is there an A-frame you can spare?
It'll come in handy with a heavy package.
A-frame?
A-frame would make it easy to carry.
I'll look for one or make you one.
Drop by sometime.
Okay, father.
Don't skip your meals.
And don't worry about me.
Father, I'm getting a call.
Goodbye, father.
Parcel delivery.
Excuse me?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
She came in at opening hour, and she walked around for 4 hours buying nothing...
We'll drive her home.
Let's go.
I can't.
I'm going to sue you.
I'm going to post this online and ruin you.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
Do your job right!
Look at the list. I'm Wang Subak!
I was this department store's VVIP!
Let's go, Subak.
Uh, Minjung, don't you know me?
I'm the second son of the village head.
Huh? Yes...
You work here?
Yes, it's been so long.
What's going on?
What's up with your outfit?
Let's talk another time.
What are you doing?
It hurts.
He's from your hometown?
And he treated me this way?
You're all dead!
Oh, man!
Ouch! It hurts!
Do you know him?
He's from my hometown.
I wonder what happened.
He was running a big company.
His father threw a party in honor for him.
Man...
Wow, nice car.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Oh, my! Oh, that woman must be crazy.
She looks almost crazy to me.
I hate people who disregard traffic lights.
If there was an accident, I'd get blamed.
And I'd have to pay for it.
That may be so.
People just don't get it. They don't.
She must sell rice cakes.
She doesn't.
You know her?
She's your acquaintance?
No way.
I don't associate with married women.
Especially women like that.
I know, after tonight, yo!
You will leave me,
and the sadness of our final kiss...
Are you really leaving?
Oh, hot! This looks good.
Is it here?
Yes.
How big?
126 square meters with 2 bathrooms.
It must be suffocating to have four people live there.
Would you like to be my lover?
Compared to the apartment before...
Excuse me?
What did you just say?
Be my lover.
But I'm married.
So?
That means I have a wife.
In other words, I had a wedding.
So?
Since I'm married, I can't have a lover.
That's what I'm told although I don't agree.
If you want to, you can.
You're more old fashioned than I thought.
That's what the average Korean would think.
Did I ask you to marry me?
Excuse me?
I'm not, so why are you scared?
Give it some thought.
You have 3 days.
Here.
What is this?
A credit card.
What am I supposed to do with this?
You tend to ask questions you know the answers to.
Use it as you want.
The limit is a hundred thousand dollars.
A hun-hundred thousand?
Get out.
I'm going nuts.
Delicious.
You'll be rich.
Right? It came out perfect.
Why did Ms. Scrooge pass rice cakes out to the neighbors?
I've never felt so happy about giving something to someone before.
I envy those who own houses in Seoul.
Where's Sedal?
He's coming today.
The director must like him.
I told him to stick with the director.
I told him to do whatever he says.
Take this home.
You take it home.
I'm not going to visit.
I think both mom and I need some time.
My father thinks we should.
I understand what you mean.
Do whatever you want.
You have my support.
That's what my father said.
Like older brother, like younger brother.
Hobak,
I work now, so stop giving me money.
Uncle, I love you.
I love you so much.
Stop that.
Let's drop by Hobak's new apartment.
You go alone. I'm not going.
Are you still upset about Sedal?
Don't even bring up Sedal or Hobak.
The rice cakes came out perfectly.
If the rices cakes come out delicious,
you'll become rich.
As if I'll be sorry.
I'm going to watch how well she does.
Try some.
No thank you.
You eat it all.
It's me.
Hello.
What's up?
Shouldn't you be working?
I'm taking a break.
Jungji's asleep and Aeji's at kindergarten.
I came to see you, not the girls.
I'd like you to go and check on my wife.
Why? Is Subak okay?
She's been acting strange.
What do you mean?
She bought a $3,000 baby stroller.
What?
Where did she get the money?
She got a loan from a private loan company.
Is she crazy?
You want her to go crazy, mother?
Can't you understand why she did that?
She pushes that stroller around all day.
What's wrong with that?
When I was her age, I'd walk around,
carrying my baby on my back all day long to show off the baby's blanket.
Stop lying.
Everything you say is a lie.
Hey, try this rice cake.
This is from Hobak.
But the stroller is empty.
Is she an old grandmother?
Why is she pushing around an empty stroller?
Oh, I should talk to Bong about her.
Try it.
Okay.
You picked this moment to tell me that?
You came all the way here to rat on her?
I came because I'm worried.
Isn't it good?
Yes, it's good.
How can you eat at a time like this?
I can't really eat.
Yes, parcel service.
Excuse me?
I'm Aeji's father...
What did you say?
Let go! Let me go!
You awful woman!
Let go! Let go!
Parcel service? Parcel service?
How dare you keep coming here?
Dad!
Yes, Aeji.
Don't cry. Don't cry.
Are you crazy?
Subak!
Mom! Mom! Mom!
Careful, be careful.
Oh, no! What do we do?
I can't believe my eyes.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo...
You're crazy too.
How could you do this to me?
Why do I have to live like this?
I used to be a classy woman!
I never fought!
Why do I have to be belittled by her?
I don't deserve that.
I was in the Miss Korea pageant!
You got eliminated in the preliminaries.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
Didn't you learn anything from that?
That woman teased her about your job!
Who could actually take that sitting down?
I'm still shaking right now.
She never had a fight growing up.
Mom, that's enough.
Why didn't you manage your company better?
You were so rich before,
so how could you lose everything?
What if something bad happened to her?
Why don't you just set her free?
Mom.
You should divorce her while she's young.
She has her whole life ahead of her!
Don't think I'm being too hard on you.
I'm saying it because I'm frustrated.
Get out. I don't want to see you.
Minjung.
Minjung...
Oh, boy...
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo...
Minjung! Minjung!
How could she do that at her kindergarten?
Is she out of her mind?
I told you!
She's out of her mind.
What if something bad happened...
Leave her be.
It's her life.
Honey...
So many people have it harder than her.
Why can't she handle that?
Please let me help them.
Let's have them move in with us.
Stop that.
Leave them be, whatever happens.
But that's not a good idea here.
I came here because I'm desperate.
Even Gwangbak thinks so.
I'm too worried about Subak to leave her be.
Honey, think of this as a favor for me.
It's me. Open the door.
Why are you here?
I'm staying here for now.
This is a motel.
How can a mom stay at a motel where people with things to hide come in and out?
It was you who made me come here.
Give me the money to go to a hotel, then.
Let's go home.
No.
I'm too scared of father to go to mom's house, and I have that basement efficiency.
I'm sick and tired of that landlady,
and I hate the roaches and the mice!
Get up.
Subak.
Are you busy?
Even if it's late, come to my school.
Okay.
I loved seeing your smiling face.
When you first came to my house,
I gave my permission because of that smile.
Even for a man, your smile was really nice.
But I haven't seen that in a while.
Minjung,
you're hurt, aren't you?
I don't know how to resolve this.
I feel bad for you and Subak.
I'm heartbroken because I can't help you.
I shouldn't say this to you,
but I'm so frustrated.
I can't end my life because I'm afraid of hurting my father,
hurting my little girls,
and turning Subak into a woman
with a horrible fate.
I know.
I understand how you feel.
Minjung,
what would you like to do most right now?
Excuse me?
Tell me what you want to do.
You should let off some steam.
We can grab a drink,
or if you want to go on a trip, you can.
Or take the girls to your father's place.
You need to be able to breathe,
so you can take care of your family.
Tell me what you want to do.
I'll make it happen.
Can I really do it?
Of course.
If you want to go on a trip, I'll pay.
No, thank you.
Then,
would you like to grab a drink?
No, father.
Well,
I'll do what I've been wanting to do.
Subtitles by KBS World
Is the director good to you?
Yes.
That's nice.
Just do whatever you're told.
Getting that job was really hard.
What took you so long?
Answer my calls before the third ring.
Yeongdal is getting married.
Did he propose to you?
I think he will when he comes back.
How do you know that if he's going to propose or not?
You're moving in with your in laws?
I'm not interested in moving in with them.
Thanks to my Sedal, we're finally laughing.
She just called me "my Sedal"!