Subtitles by KBS World
From now on call me "honey."
Honey?
Of course.
You want us to be lovers.
We can't be too formal if we're lovers.
If you don't like it, forget about it.
Fine.
I've never called anyone "honey" before.
I never had anyone call me that either.
I thought you were married.
She's older.
She's older?
How did you meet?
I bet it was interesting.
It wasn't interesting at all.
My life became a mess when I met her.
Outside that is "no comment."
Tell me. What kind of lover will you be?
You must have something in mind.
I want to try everything lovers do.
Let's call it a dating game.
By everything, you mean...
Don't get ahead of yourself.
What do people do on dates?
They eat, drink coffee, and see a movie.
They drink coffee, eat, and see a movie.
They see a movie, eat, and drink coffee.
They see a movie, drink coffee, and eat.
And sometimes they go on a trip.
Go to good restaurants, see movies,
go to the theme park, drink draft beer,
and take a train to somewhere.
That's what I want to do.
I went to the States when I was 15.
I couldn't do anything a young girl does.
Including dating.
I lived as my dad's little puppet.
I had no freedom.
I lived like a princess under my dad's watch.
With no friends.
How sad.
Everyone has heartbreaking stories to tell.
I have mine, you have yours.
I got hooked by an older woman when I was young and look where it got me.
We have a lot of similarities.
There's only one thing different.
You're loaded, I'm not.
But don't get caught.
Women have a sixth sense.
I can't stand things getting messy.
Don't worry.
My wife's so dense, she has no idea.
She doesn't even know you're a woman.
She doesn't even know she's one.
You didn't tell her?
She didn't ask.
[Ugly Pumpkin]
Who is it?
Don't worry about it.
Call me "honey."
Hey!
Honey?
Again.
Honey.
Honey!
Again.
This is nuts!
How can she say it like that?
In front of everyone, the kids, too.
That's how my mom talks.
You know that.
My parents never talked to me like that.
She's going to get worse.
Can you talk to her?
You can't live here if you react like that.
You can't be picky when things are this bad.
Who is it?
Gwangbak? Uncle?
That darn cat!
It's a cat?
Yes, I think so.
But it meows weird.
Oh, Mr. Ko.
Yes.
I'm sorry to be calling so late.
Mr. Wang, let me just say one thing.
Please take good care of my son.
I should thank you.
They moved in today.
I won't give him a hard time, so don't worry.
Good night, Mr. Ko.
Yes.
Let's talk.
I need to sleep.
How can you sleep?
I have to.
I have to go to work early.
You have no pride?
You have no shame?
You don't feel upset about Sedal?
Stop that.
Why should I stop this?
You don't care about how others feel!
You don't care if your wife is going nuts,
as long as you feel comfortable.
Yes, I feel comfortable.
Living with my in laws is very comfortable!
Why are you yelling at me?
You think I'm happy?
I'm trying to convince myself this is better than the basement efficiency,
that I can working without worrying about you,
so how can you start nagging again?
Why can't Sedal have his day?
It looks like he's finally doing well,
so why can't you be happy for him?
Are you a saint?
You might be able to do that,
but it's driving me crazy!
Don't go crazy.
Hold on for just 3 years.
Let's depend on your father to feed us.
I can get back on my feet in 3 years.
There you go again!
People these days don't starve to death!
Getting fed isn't the most important thing!
This is what I hate about you!
You felt nothing watching Sedal?
Even Hobak is acting like she's better than us, and you don't feel upset?
How can you not get upset?
You can't let everything bother you.
Don't pay attention to it.
Pretend you didn't hear or see it.
Why would I do that?
Because I'm living with your parents!
So that's what I'm going to do.
Let me sleep! Please!
I need to sleep to go to work tomorrow!
Leave them alone.
I didn't know what noise complaint meant,
but it's not just apartments who have it.
He knows you and I are downstairs,
so how can he yell like that?
Our daughter's voice is louder.
He made her cry!
Why should...
Hey!
Oh.
Why don't you go up?
She's crying.
She's crying because she's angry.
Talk to Subak.
Tell her not to nag Minjung.
She has good reasons for nagging him!
He deserves every bit of it.
They settled down now.
You must act like an adult from now on.
If he were my son,
I wouldn't have done it.
I did it because it's Subak,
so be nice to Minjung.
Imagine Subak living with her in laws.
Why are you laughing?
Don't laugh in the middle of the night.
It's Sedal.
My Sedal made me laugh for the first time.
How could you transfer to Sedal so quickly?
He's not a bus.
I didn't transfer.
You used to go my Minjung, my Minjung,
and now it's my Sedal, my Sedal?
What would mother say?
She wouldn't say anything.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo...
Why you little!
What?
Mother would've said that.
I know how to impersonate her, too.
Why are you home so late?
Be quiet.
Do you know what money tastes like?
The taste of money, the power of money.
I went from just Sedal to "my Sedal" tonight.
This is the power of money.
Did you know?
Stop talking nonsense and go to bed.
You wouldn't know anything.
You saw nothing, heard nothing.
I feel sorry for you.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Go to bed.
The moon is so bright.
What?
Did the moon say something to you?
No way.
I feel bad for you for waking up in the middle of the night, sitting out here.
And I feel bad for you who can't sleep.
Are you upset because of Goof-off?
You must be.
You were inseparable, but now he has a job.
Now you have to suck up to your friend.
Stop that.
Why you little!
He married Hobak by hanging out with you.
So why can't you do the same?
Oh, mom! Stop that.
I'm furious as I am.
You're furious?
I'm going crazy here.
Oh, I should just die.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Mother, did you sleep well?
No, I didn't.
Your fighting kept me up.
I'm sorry.
If your wife is mad, you should try to make her feel better, not get upset!
You should learn to be careful here.
You have no respect for me or my husband.
Oh, and those cats!
What are you doing?
I'm looking for water.
You can't find water?
It's right here!
Come with me.
Take this outside.
We have to take out the recyclables today.
Okay.
You can't even lift that?
I'll take it out, mother.
Go inside.
And take the trash outside, too.
Okay.
Good morning.
Shouldn't you be heading out?
After I take these out.
- Are you exercising?
- Yes.
Did you have breakfast?
I'll get something at work.
Why didn't you make breakfast early?
Why?
Minjung went to work on an empty stomach.
You can't work without having breakfast.
You want me to make him breakfast?
I'm already tired of doing it for you.
Why should I get up earlier to make breakfast for my son in law?
I can't believe you just said that.
I wasn't telling you to do it.
I'm asking you to make Subak do it.
Go wake her up.
She can't get up early in the morning.
What?
He'll get something at work.
He won't starve.
People eat better when they work.
Don't tell him to do chores.
He goes to work really early.
Did Minjung say something?
You know he didn't.
Put yourself in his shoes.
If he was your son, would you do the same?
If he wants to live here,
he must help out.
He can't act like he's a guest.
Neither you nor uncle will do it,
so Minjung has to. Don't you agree?
My son Minjung,
forgive your father for
not being able to help you out more.
Picturing you use this A-frame
breaks my heart.
I raised you as my precious son,
but I feel like I've put
the heaviest load on your shoulders.
But son,
if you thought of what happened as a chance,
not as hardship, it'll be easier to handle.
Every father in the world did so.
Son,
I hope one day you'll be able to
get rid of this A-frame.
Let's see, a good restaurant.
Let's make it really amazing.
It's me. Come. I found a good restaurant.
Okay.
Make sure you look pretty.
Oppa Gangnam style.
I don't deal with ugliness.
I already have an ugly one at home.
Here.
What are you doing?
I want a bite.
Here.
Oh, can't you see I have a big mouth?
This piece is way too small.
Mmm, now we're talking.
Good job.
You dig me, don't you?
Say, "Honey!"
Honey!
I'm taking you to a good restaurant.
Okay?
Okay.
Just do as I say.
You'll become happy.
I'm great, right?
Hello.
Sit down.
Lovers wipe chairs for each other?
I'm doing it because I'm a great guy.
- What is it?
- Did you...
steal money from your director?
What?
Oh well.
You don't have the guts.
Whatever you're doing right now, can you
ask your director to let me do it, too?
Loser, I'll see you later.
Drinks on me.
Who was it?
It was Loser.
He thinks he and I are the same. Ugh.
Would you like to come over to my house?
What did I do?
Look what you did to me.
You drove my friends away.
That girl is your friend?
A man and a woman can't be friends.
How many times do I have to tell you?
You're tiring me out right now.
So what are you saying?
Let's take some time off.
Do you want to break up with me?
I told you I'd let you do anything, right?
So you should let me have this one thing.
Don't you agree?
You're older than me.
You're four years older,
so you should let me have this.
Am I wrong?
Forget about it.
Why should we?
Do you understand what I said?
Answer me.
I understand.
Are you upset?
I don't know.
Don't be upset.
I'll be better to you.
Here.
You can be so cute.
This is why I can't break up with you.
How adorable.
Daebak!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
We had a fight and made up.
You guys fight?
I wouldn't. She's a kid.
How could you even think that?
Your friend has a problem again?
Daebak's listening.
Let's talk later.
He wouldn't know what we're talking about.
My friend thinks he's a player.
He's an expert at playing games.
He makes her feel really anxious,
not calling her,
and he's seeing other women.
He is a player.
He is.
You want to know how to make a player yours/
Yes. How do you do that?
You have to label him as yours.
Yes?
Are you busy?
How's your writing coming.
Not very well.
You need experience to be a writer.
You should travel, meet people, meet men.
Are you seeing anyone?
Can I introduce someone to you?
Is it formal?
Don't think of it as that.
Think of it as a blind date.
I'm not interested.
I have work to do.
Next time, father.
I can't afford to.
I don't even have a job.
I really missed Korean food.
They have Korean restaurants in China.
I couldn't go because I was on business.
This hit the spot.
And now for the present.
I told you not to buy me anything.
Present.
You told me to come back safely.
Right.
I do what I'm told.
If you asked for a brand name handbag,
I would've gotten one.
Was that a mistake?
Oh, no.
Thank you for coming back safely.
Jangbi, it's me.
My daughter's not interested in marriage.
They won't get married now!
Tell her to meet him first and decide.
She quit her job to become a writer,
so she's just too preoccupied.
I guess it's not meant to be.
But he's a really nice man.
But what can we do?
She's not interested.
Okay.
She's not interested?
But I was so excited.
How disappointing.
Father!
You must be tired.
How about dinner?
I ate.
Miho, how were things?
Sangnam.
Okay.
You're back.
Yes.
This is for you, Miho.
Wow.
This is for you, aunt.
You didn't have to.
You must have been busy.
It's a Chinese silk scarf.
Take a look.
- It's pretty.
- Isn't it?
I thought it would look good on you.
This one's for you, father.
It is?
How do I look?
You look like a movie star.
Once I dreamt of becoming an actor.
Whatever. Father, what about my gift?
Well, she said no.
She turned me down?
She's not ready to meet a man.
She must be busy.
Whoever she is, it's her loss.
She can't be that busy.
She must have time to date.
She doesn't know what she's missing
because she hasn't met you.
I guess it's not meant to be.
How disappointing!
What?
Why you little...
He finally came back from China.
He gave me the best gift.
I don't think I can sleep tonight.
Where are you?
Home.
I saw the picture.
What was the gift?
I went to the airport to greet him.
You did?
Did he ask you or you just went?
He asked me.
We had dinner and I got my gift.
Did he propose to you?
Propose?
You said he'll propose after his trip!
Women these days are pathetic.
They put too much meaning into the proposal.
And they don't even know what it means.
They complain about their husbands not
proposing even after they're married.
They're totally nuts.
How did they get married in the first place?
Anyway, did he or didn't he?
It's a secret.
So he didn't!
Hey!
Why are you screaming?
I'm just curious.
You're so impatient.
If it happens, I'll tell you first.
No thanks! I don't what to know!
She's green with envy!
I need to crush that woman.
You don't like being proposed to?
But everyone does it.
I said that to annoy her.
She was really upset the other night.
I'm sure she never had a real boyfriend.
She isn't much to look at.
Why isn't she getting surgery?
Mom, I'm going to get the most romantic
proposal and post it all over online.
Even President Obama will see it.
Even Obama?
He's only a few steps away.
People are so weird these days.
They don't need to tell everyone,
so why do they advertise everything?
Didn't he bring you a gift?
No. He said he would've, had I asked him.
He's all words.
How could he come empty handed?
I was a bit disappointed.
Why didn't you say something?
I didn't want to scare him off.
I made sure I didn't show my feelings.
What if he's rich but stingy?
He can't be.
I heard some rich people
don't know how to spend money.
I know someone who owned several buildings,
but never spent any money and just died.
His children fought over the inheritance.
Oh, no.
A man should know when to spend money.
If he keeps that up, break up with him.
You don't want a stingy man.
I'm home.
Where are the girls?
With mom.
We should sleep with them.
Can you do it?
Do you know how many times Jungji wakes up?
It must be hard for mother.
I think you should take care of them.
They girls like her more than they like me.
When can I see their faces, then?
I can't see them in the morning,
I can't see them when I get home.
You never cared about them before.
You were too busy with your company.
I saw them sleeping every night.
Have them sleep in this room from now on.
You have their pictures in your cell phone.
Don't be too picky.
Ugh, what is this?
I can't even pay to get this done anymore.
It's crazy.
I was in the Miss Korea pageant.
You have no time to miss the girls.
You should focus on making money so I can enjoy my life again.
Who's there?
Was it that cat again?
Maybe I should put out a trap.
Mother.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to make dinner.
You didn't have dinner?
I missed my timing.
I'll clean up.
Do go to bed.
You go to bed.
Instead of making a mess, try to help out.
Did you make that cat noise?
Excuse me?
It wasn't me.
It wasn't you?
The cat sounded just like you.
I heard it and I thought it was weird
because it sounded very much like me.
It came from behind the kitchen.
There are lots of stray cats these days.
I've seen them in every neighborhood.
They move around in packs.
All over the place.
Aunt, are you asleep?
No, I'm not.
What is it?
Are you hungry?
No. Did you see a yellow shirt in my bag?
I washed it. Why?
No, I thought I had left it in China.
Okay. Go back to bed.
Aunt.
Yes?
Were you crying?
No, I wasn't crying.
It's because you woke me up.
You must be exhausted. Got to bed.
Hello, grandmother.
You're Sedal's mom.
Where are you going?
I was coming to your house.
Why doesn't Anggeum come to the meetings?
Things at home are too complicated.
Should we be friends?
Excuse me?
Our sons are friends, so we should be, too.
You're right.
This is the butcher's daughter's wedding invitation.
My friend, please give this to Anggeum.
It'll cost you.
I could take you out.
I was just kidding.
We had a feast thanks to your son.
He brought a bunch of meat and fruits.
Who?
You have more than one son?
You mean Sedal?
Yes, mother.
I can't believe you.
Excuse me?
You controlled my son and changed him!
You only think of your parents?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, I'm sure you do!
I know you two planned this!
Even if Sedal wanted to take care of your
parent's first, you should've told him no.
Didn't you learn any manners?
You're older than him so you should be more mature!
You should know who comes first.
I should come first!
You don't have any respect for me at all.
Is it because I don't have a husband?
Excuse me, mother, what are you talking...
Stop it!
Mother.
Sintong, Bangtong, dad's home.
- Oh, pizza!
- It's pizza!
Boys, shouldn't you say hi to me first?
Where did you get the money?
Eat, eat. Eating is living.
Don't plan anything for Sunday.
We're going to an amusement park.
Amusement park! Amusement park!
Yes! Yes!
Don't jump. They'll hear you downstairs.
Kids are supposed to jump. Don't nag.
Jump, jump.
No. I told you not to jump.
I'm walking on my toes.
We shouldn't have moved here.
Take that to your room.
You're on a roll.
Where did you get the money?
I got a bonus.
The director really likes me.
Don't waste it all.
It's a credit card.
I heard from Gwangbak.
You bought stuff for my parents?
It felt really good.
Wash up. Let's go to your mother's house.
Huh?
Honey, are you busy?
I had fun last night.
Let's go to an amusement park next time.
Mom, dad got a weird text.
Don't play with dad's phone.
Put it back.
Someone called dad "honey."
It's spam. Put it back.
Subak, after you moved in,
your mom and dad look peaceful.
I feel better.
Daebak, did you think about your dream?
Yes.
But there are so many things I want to do.
Someone became unemployed doing that.
What happened to your dream?
I'm working hard on it.
Your dream isn't important.
It's better to have a job everyone envies.
That may be right,
but I'm sad I never realized my dream.
And disappointed.
What was your dream?
You became a vice principal.
That's enough.
Was it to become the principal?
No.
I liked teaching,
and I feel proud about my job,
but I had a different dream.
What was it?
I'm not telling.
Tell us.
Don't laugh.
Singer.
What?
Singer?
Father, are you serious?
Incredible.
You get 20, 30 points at karaoke,
so how could you?
But that was my dream.
My father didn't like it, so I couldn't pursue it.
Oh, father, thank you.
If you had quit your job,
we would've been ruined.
Now I remember.
Your father beat you up because of that.
I remember something, too.
Was it when I gave birth to Daebak?
The hospital tried to call your father,
but he was nowhere to be found.
After I gave birth all alone,
he appeared at the hospital,
saying there was an emergency at school.
But later I found out that he was on that singing contest show.
He was?
Incredible.
I almost didn't find out, but mother told everyone that your father passed the first round.
So? What happened?
What do you think? He failed.
He failed.
Look.
Bastard. Sons are worthless.
I don't have a son.
Oh, am I your daughter, then.
Oh, who made Madam Park Salla mad?
Who was it? Who?
Forget it.
Your in laws did nothing for you!
They treat you like dirt,
and you bought them gifts?
And you forgot about your mom?
I didn't forget about you.
Bring them, hurry.
These are from the department store.
They're different from the local store ones.
And the beef is top grade domestic beef.
Have you even seen them?
Madam Park Salla?
Stuff yourself with this, thinking about me.
Where's Yeongdal?
She'll be home late.
I felt sad.
I felt like I had no son.
It was like they stole my son from me.
Look at Subak's husband.
When he was rich, he acted like their son!
Don't worry, mom.
My one and only love is you.
Trust me, okay?
I went there to show my mother in law that she can't be mean to me anymore.
You shouldn't have.
You should've come here first.
You're siding with me?
If Sintong and Bangtong did the same to me,
I'd be really disappointed too.
I'm glad you know.
Oh, mom, you were upset?
From now on, I'll put you first.
If you and her mom fell into the river,
I'd save you and watch her get carried away by the currents.
Really?
Of course.
It'd be fun to watch her float down the river together!
You save your mom.
No, let her favorite Subak save her and you come with us.
Oh, my darling son.
Having luck at the beginning means nothing.
When it comes to life,
you must wait until the end.
All the luck Minjung had has come to you!
Absolutely!
Anyway, stick close to the director.
That's what I'm doing now.
Mom, you're all better now.
You must mark him as yours.
Your teeth.
I brushed them.
Your gift.
Oh,
thank you.
I'll think of you whenever I put it on.
You don't have to.
Whenever you put it on is a bit...
Will you buy another one when it runs out?
That's not hard,
but where did you learn that?
What do you mean?
It wasn't that bad.
You never dated, have you?
What do you mean?
How old do you think I am?
I've done everything other people do.
Alcohol works wonders in romance.
As a thank you for your gift,
I'll buy you dinner.
No, buy me a drink.
I can see you want to go drinking.
When men drink, they think all women are beautiful.
Have some beer.
Cheers.
But I have to drive.
You can call a designated driver service.
I'll pay for that.
Cheers.
Slow down.
No bottoms up?
I want to drink slowly.
You can't do that!
I drank all of mine.
Hurry.
Don't I look prettier than before?
No.
That's weird.
Hurry up and drink.
I knew you were impatient,
but I didn't think you'd drink like this.
Oh, I'm out of breath.
So? I look pretty, right?
No.
How much does he have to drink?
- Mom.
- Yes?
That grandfather's looking at you.
Why is he looking at me?
Because you're pretty.
No way.
We're walking in a line, so we look weird.
I'm too old to be pretty.
Did you like it when I said you're pretty?
He wasn't looking at you.
Hey!
Why you little!
Hey! Stop right there!
Oh, the apartment looks really nice.
This is our apartment.
Look.
Oh!
I went grocery shopping so bring something.
You go grocery shopping now?
I like spending money.
You worked so hard to buy an apartment.
Your dream came true.
Yes. I need to prepare for retirement now.
- Yes.
- Hobak,
can I go play with the boys?
Sure. Go to Sintong's room.
I'll bring you something to eat.
Grandpa, can I play with your phone?
Mine doesn't play any games.
Didn't you feel anything?
What do you mean?
Lonely old man.
How dare you! Ugh!
A man has to have a dream.
What are your dreams?
No answer?
That means you don't have any.
A dreamless life is like a cheese-less pizza.
If there's no cheese, it's not good.
I know.
So tell me.
- You first.
Oh, uncle, I got it.
What is it?
Buying my own house.
Your dream is to buy a house?
Yes, I want that.
My mom did it, too.
Me! Me! I have a dream too.
- What is it?
- Lonely old man.
Ugh!
You want to be like your grandfather?
Pick something different.
Retirement planes?
Retirement plans.
What's that?
I don't know. Just pick it.
Mom said she's doing it.
All adults do it.
Then I want that. Retirement plan.
Fine. Sintong, yours is buying a house,
and Bangtong, yours is retirement plan.
You both have dreams now, okay?
So you must work hard for your dream.
- Okay?
- Yes, uncle.
Yes! Buying my own house.
Yes! Retirement plan.
Oh? But how should I work for it?
Really hard.
Cat noise?
Yes, he swore it wasn't him,
but the "meow, meow" sounded like him.
Why would he do that?
It's not attractive.
Why couldn't he just tell me what happened and apologize?
I should catch him in the act.
Bottoms up.
Men these days are cowards, right?
Why?
They're too scared to kiss.
They're afraid of sexual harassment.
Funny.
That's a valid concern.
You need confirmations these days.
No, no. I'm not like that.
Kissing out of love isn't sexual harassment.
Not kissing is sexual harassment.
I feel sexually ashamed when that happens.
That makes sense.
I'm not a rookie.
So don't worry.
What am I worrying about?
Things like sexual harassment.
I'm not like that.
I don't have to worry?
We agreed to do this, okay?
Don't change your words later.
Shh!
Yes, father.
We need to fix the bulldozer tonight.
It takes too long if we call a mechanic.
Let's fix it with Jangbi.
Okay. I'll be right over.
Let's go.
Bye.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Bye.
Mom.
Who was that?
Nobody.
Then why were you waving at that truck?
Did you drink?
A bit.
I don't believe you!
Now you're dating a truck driver?
It's not like that.
Why did you quit your teaching job?
You used to get doctors, judges and lawyers.
Now you're getting a truck driver.
What if you never find a good husband?
Everyone knows your father here!
Mommy! Mommy!
Stop right there!
She was crying?
Yes.
Is something going on with her?
There must be something going on,
but I could never ask.
Why don't you talk to her and find out?
Hey, munchkin!
What is it?
Is something wrong?
She failed again.
Did you tell her to go drinking?
How did you know?
I read the same books you read.
She needs something powerful.
Can you think of anything?
I can't find it here.
I have the answer.
You do? What should she do?
It's not easy for me to say this to you.
That man. Your first love.
If you can't get over him, let's find him.
Daese.
I know how you feel.
I know you've been crying.
And I know why.
I know how it feels.
You were together for 7 years,
and you broke up right before your wedding.
I can never forgive her for
what she did to you.
Don't hate my sister so much.
She brought Sangnam into this world.
She ruined two families.
My family and yours.
She ruined my life
and she ruined your life, too.
And Sangnam.
I'm sure she's being punished somewhere.
I hate her, too.
But so much time passed,
and I've accepted it as fate.
Why don't you look for him?
I'm sure you can find him if you wanted to.
Should I look for him?
No.
Don't bother, Daese.
I broke his heart.
I'll explain to him why you had to leave him.
If he finds out it wasn't your fault...
Don't, Daese.
What we had is over.
What can we do after all these years?
I don't want to open old wounds.
Please don't mention him to me again.
Yes.
It's about Gwangbak.
Can you find a man for her?
I'm not doing that!
I'm fine with anyone who has a good job,
a future, and ability to support his family.
And it'd be nice if he's good looking.
You know how pretty my daughters are.
And we're talking about my third daughter.
She's the best looking one of all.
Mom.
And he should have money, too.
See if you can find someone.
I'll buy you a dress.
Bye.
Nobody has everything!
No trucker!
I'm not going, Madam Lee Anggeum!
Don't be crazy!
Be honest.
Is Gwangbak really the best looking one?
You had work done.
Gwangbak is all natural.
Mom!
- What is it?
- I found the solution.
You did? What is it?
Excuse me! Excuse me!
What's up?
Let's go fishing.
Fishing?
Yes, night fishing.
Okay. Let's go fishing.
I'm not sure what I'll catch.
Subtitles by KBS World
I left breathless from running around all day, in search of love, in search of life
Beneath the skies of Seoul I get closer to my dreams
Both love and friendship coexist under the sky
Each day passes by differently from the last
I'm furious, that's why.
The beauty salon woman,
she's acting like she owns the world.
Why did Minjung have to make a delivery just then?
He came to that restaurant?
I'm leaving.
Just like that?
How long have you been sitting here?
- What?
- We didn't have any fish stew.
And we didn't kiss.
Let's save it for a special occasion.
How dare you yell at my son?
If he makes a mistake, I can scold him.
I have a right to, don't you think?
Grandmother, what's wrong with you?
How dare you yell at her?
She's my mom.
Your mom yelled at my mom first!