Subtitles by KBS World
Why did you throw away the pot?
You said you wanted to keep it forever.
Because it was pathetic.
It was pathetic, like me.
I didn't want to see it.
Why did you come?
How did you know I was there?
You can't hide from me.
That was where I proposed to you,
and we went there on our honeymoon.
Hobak,
were you happy living with me?
I'm not sure I was.
I don't think I was ever really happy.
You know what kind of misery your family put me through, don't you?
Being your parents son in law was downright horrible.
Especially your mother.
Every word your mother said to me stabbed me in the heart like thorns,
and they left scars.
She said I was a bum who was leeching off of you for a living.
I'm a man.
I have feelings, too.
I'm someone's precious son.
But your mother treats me like dirt.
She always compared me to Minjung,
discriminating me with food.
Whenever that happened,
I felt so small and degraded.
She destroyed my self esteem.
Last New Year's Day,
Minjung's dumpling soup was overflowing with dumplings,
but mine only had broth.
I stirred it with my spoon,
and I found only two busted dumplings.
But she asked Minjung
if he wanted deep fried dumplings.
If she had more dumplings,
why couldn't she have given me some more?
Whenever I reached for something with my chopsticks, she slapped my hand.
Was I there to beg for food?
When I go to my moms, I just sit there because my mom does everything for me.
But
whenever I go to your parents', I'm a nuisance.
What did I ever do to deserve that?
Am I a criminal?
Did I steal something?
Is being unemployed a crime?
But do you know what hurt me the most?
It's not your mother,
and it's not Minjung or your big sister.
It's you.
You, Hobak.
No matter how much your mother hates me,
no matter how much your family mistreats me,
if you were on my side,
I wouldn't have felt so sad.
Have you ever,
even once,
stood up for me in front of them?
Whenever your family treated me like dirt,
you just sat there, doing nothing.
Why do you think I visit your family?
For you.
If you weren't my wife,
I'd never have to deal with them.
Please,
let me breathe.
That's all I want.
What do you mean by that?
Set me free for a month.
Let's be separated for just one month.
This is a chance for me,
and I don't want to miss it.
I won't get another chance like this.
I want to take this elevator.
Where are you planning on going on that?
I don't know where the elevator will take me to.
And you won't regret it?
If I don't do this, I will regret it.
I'm begging you.
You saw him, too.
He change completely.
Hanging out with that awful girl changed him for the worse.
Daese,
maybe this isn't my place to say anything,
but I think you're over estimating your son.
What?
Sangnam is a great kid.
He's really nice. He's like no other man.
But see him through the society's eyes.
He dropped out of high school.
Most people these days are college graduates.
Women don't like blue collar workers like him.
Jangbi.
I know he runs his own company.
But his parents are divorced.
What does that have to do with him?
Even if your kids are in love,
the parents look at everything.
They look at the family, financial situation, education and looks.
It's not like it used to be when love was everything that mattered.
So?
Are you saying Sangnam is flawed?
I'm not saying that.
But you are!
Are you drunk?
Just hear me out.
Who's against this marriage?
Me.
That's the problem.
Despite Sangnam's situation, her family's not against it, so why are you?
It's them who should be against it.
Why are you so picky?
Jangbi, I only want one thing.
She has to be a decent person.
Her character is all I look at.
Living with such a rude girl will turn Sangnam's life into hell.
Who knows if it will be heaven or hell?
I do!
I've lived with someone just like her.
Apparently, people don't change.
If you fall in love with the wrong woman,
your life turns into hell in an instant.
I will never put my son through that kind of misery.
Never.
Man...
Gwangbak! Gwangbak!
Uncle! Uncle, you're here!
People might think I'm you're boyfriend.
How did you call me in this state? Let go.
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go to hell! Ouch!
Gwangbak! Gwangbak! Gwangbak!
My burning heart!
Oh, you're heavy.
My heart's on fire!
Will it ever burn again?
I don't want to say goodbye.
No!
Like being hit by a bullet!
Stay still. You're heavy enough as it is!
I don't want to say goodbye.
One, two, three, four!
Yongpil! Yongpil!
Like being hit by a bullet...
How can you sing so many songs at once?
Just stick to one song, would you?
My heart hurts so much!
There you go again.
Uncle, do you know how I feel?
No, I don't!
What's so special about a college degree?
It's not!
Even with a college degree, you're jobless.
Go easy on my, please.
They're jobless,
I'm jobless and he's jobless.
Who cares if you're a high school dropout?
He's a thousand times better!
You went a little too far there.
Is being divorced a sin?
It was his parents, not him!
What if someone saw?
I can't believe my eyes.
Why didn't you just dump her somewhere?
Take her to her room before he sees her.
You won't get away with this!
How embarrassing.
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
Father!
You have something to say?
Can't you let me have my way, just this once?
I really love him.
I won't meet anyone like him again.
I've never felt this way before, father.
Please let me marry him.
How dare you!
If you're drunk, just go to bed.
We'll talk when you're sober.
Father!
What's wrong with you?
Let's go to bed. Let's talk tomorrow.
Father, I'm disappointed in you!
You're a hypocrite!
Hey! How could you!
Come with me.
Father, she's drunk. Don't listen to her.
Mom, take father inside.
What did you teach your students?
You said college isn't important!
You told them to do what they want, instead of dwelling on getting a college degree!
I still remember it.
Remember what you told me on my first day of work as a teacher?
He told me never to hurt my students,
never to discriminate them for their grades.
You told me not to have prejudices against kids from divorced families.
You said that's what a true teacher does.
Where did that man go?
Father, answer me!
I can't believe that girl!
She's totally out of her mind!
You won't get away with this!
Oh, she's totally crazy.
She's taking her anger out on her father!
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo! Dear god!
He broke up with me.
He won't marry me if my parents are against it.
What do I do, Subak?
Oh, dear...
What do I do...
Don't fall in love again.
It breaks my heart to see you like this.
Why aren't you in bed?
You're upset because of Gwangbak?
Just forget it. She was drunk.
Mother,
I am a hypocrite.
Gwangbak's right.
I'm a different man when I'm teaching
my students and my own children.
I'm a real hypocrite.
You're a parent.
A parent is different from a teacher.
Teachers say it's okay to fail,
but parents want their kids to get A's.
Let's say there's a fire.
Teachers say you must go in and rescue people.
But parents say never to even go near where there's a fire.
Parents can't always be right.
That's what teachers are for.
Mother,
there's no correct answer in life.
It gets more difficult as I get older.
But that's what makes life interesting.
Bong,
she's not old enough to see what you see.
Don't stress over such impossible question and go to bed.
Don't do this all night.
Go.
You're right.
Everything you said was right.
I think I understand how you feel.
Nobody else could put up with it.
I'd be demanding for a divorce, too.
Even women don't put up with that now.
Sedal,
I'm sorry.
I didn't stand up for you.
Whenever your mother was mean to me,
I blamed you for just letting her do it,
but I never put myself in your shoes.
If you say it that way,
I don't know how to reply to that.
I'm sorry you had to go through such misery with my family because of me.
Go.
Do you mean it?
I don't know where that elevator will end up, but go.
So you won't regret it.
But let's keep this between us.
Business trip? For how long?
About a month.
A month long business trip?
It might take longer, but for now, it is.
Where are you going?
Somewhere far away.
Where? Busan?
Oh, Busan sounds nice. I want to go there.
Nice? You think I'm going on a vacation?
I have to train new employees there.
You're gong to train someone?
What's wrong with your tone?
It's just that I can't believe it.
He went to law school, so believe it.
He knows all about the law.
What does the law have to do with hotels?
When are you leaving?
Now.
Now?
Your husband is going on a business trip,
and you're just going to let him go?
But he said he has to go today.
I told him to go tomorrow.
Make dinner for us.
We should throw a party for him.
He's going away for his job.
This is why I don't approve of you.
What have you done for him as his wife?
All you care about is money.
That's enough.
Go grocery shopping right now.
And make something my son likes.
Okay.
Where's Gwangbak? She's not eating?
She's sick.
She's too embarrassed to come down.
Don't give her any food.
How dare she talk to her father like that?
Mr. Choi!
See?
He knows he was wrong.
He should!
He can't beat his father.
Sangnam is a much bigger man than you.
He better not try anything like that again.
I told you I have emotional scars.
You grew up in a normal family,
so you could never understand.
A middle school graduate like me wanting to marry a former teacher who will be a writer?
That's nonsense.
Let's pretend this never happened.
Get up.
You have no right to pout!
You got drunk over a man and came home on your uncle's back.
What if any of our neighbors saw you?
Do you want to ruin your father's reputation?
You said you'll become a successful writer.
So forget getting married and write.
You never had a boyfriend before, so why would you start now and cause such trouble?
Mom, leave her alone.
She's heartbroken.
Why would she be heartbroken?
They've only been dating for a few months!
Even if you've been dating for 2 or 3 years,
you still can't know a man, so what's wrong?
Mom, I'll talk to her.
Ugh, you're impossible.
Why don't you go out or something!
I'm sick of seeing you like this.
You've become a total idiot!
You used to be a teacher, for heaven's sake,
and this is how you've ended up?
I can't believe my eyes.
Ugh.
Why don't you go out and get some air?
Staying home will just make mom madder.
[Accepting applications for part time jobs]
Mop the floor first.
And when you're done, clean the bathroom.
You heard what the manager said, right?
So do what I tell you to do.
I will.
Did you have any other part time jobs?
This is my first one.
This is my first one?
How can that be for an old woman?
I'm not old.
You are! You said you're 29.
I'm 20.
I've been here 3 months longer than you, so don't make any mistakes and do as I say.
Keep the windows, floor, and bathroom clean, and memorize the whole menu,
the codes for membership and discount cards, and don't forget to stamp the coupons.
Stay alert when you take orders, and don't make mistakes of the sizes, okay?
No, this is Sangnam's.
Can I use it? It's pretty.
He doesn't want anyone else to use it.
It's okay, Miho, you can use it.
Really? Thanks.
No, Miho! Bring that back.
It's okay, aunt.
Let Miho have it.
Sangnam,
your ring...
We broke up.
Sangnam.
That's awful.
Are you okay?
I miss her.
Everything else aside,
I just miss her.
Not being able to see the person you miss is hard.
Sangnam,
you should keep seeing her.
You're not Romeo and Juliet.
You're both adults,
so why would you care?
Your father's acting like that right now,
but in time, he will change his mind.
If you miss her, go see her.
Or you'll get sick.
Imagine how hard it must be for her.
It's not because of father.
Aunt,
actually, her parents
don't want me.
Her parents?
Yey! How exciting!
You guys!
You're excited when your dad is going away?
I'm excited because of the food!
Me too, me too!
You must've been starving them!
Stop being a Scrooge and feed your kids.
I'm going to, from now on.
Grandma, don't yell at mom.
We had yummy food at the beach.
I'm sure it was something really cheap.
No, we had pork belly, shrimps and clams.
Like I said, cheap.
Okay, let's get on with this.
Who is it?
Huh?
The director.
Mom, I have to go.
I'm supposed to go tonight.
You can go early tomorrow morning.
Director,
my mom and my sister came over for dinner.
I'll talk to her. Give me the phone.
- Hey, no!
- Give it to me.
You, what are you going to say?
Oh, mom, mom!
Hello, I'm Sedal's mom.
I've heard so much about you.
I'd like to come over and say hello.
We're actually having a goodbye dinner with the family,
so would you mind if he came tomorrow?
Except when he went to the army,
I've never been separated from my son,
so I don't want to just send him off.
Okay, then.
Have him leave first thing in the morning.
Don't worry, director.
I'll take him to the Seoul Station.
The Seoul Station?
Yes, I heard he's going to Busan.
He can take the train, right?
Goodbye, director.
See? I knew I could change her mind.
She said to go ahead.
You're the best, mom.
I've always been a persuasive person.
Right. Whenever there was a problem at school,
you went there and solved it.
Can you imagine?
I went and met his teacher whenever he didn't do his homework,
was late to school, got hurt playing with his friends, and wet his pants.
Mom, the boys are listening.
I'm sure they already know.
I also went to school with you, you know?
And that's how I became so successful.
Successful?
I'm not satisfied with this.
You're supposed to become the president.
Grandma, dad's going to be the president?
You believe her?
Don't become the president.
It's a whole lot of headache.
Right.
Even a kid knows it's a lot of headache.
Even he knows.
You're a smart boy.
Just wait and see.
There's no need to become the president,
but you'll come awfully close.
And that will make you happy, too.
Will you make manager when you return?
I'd probably be made director.
Really?
The director must really like you.
Be loyal to her.
And you drop him off at the Seoul Station.
I will.
Let's blow out the candles.
Happy business trip to you!
Happy business trip dear dad!
This is nutty, nutty, nuts!
You're killing your dad!
Your sons are killing you!
There are four people in our family,
you, dad, Sintong and me.
It'll be sad if anyone was missing.
Here's five hundred thousand.
Put it in the safe, not in the bank.
The safe is already full.
Then shove it in my car trunk.
I'm paying him tomorrow morning.
Good job, Director Wang.
Thank you, sir.
But without those two,
it won't be five hundred thousand.
Really?
You may leave.
Yes, sir.
- Don't lose any.
- I won't.
I'll pay you next time.
You handle millions of dollars with this hand?
How amazing!
I've never seen five hundred thousand in cash.
I thought your husband was successful.
He never brought money home.
He doesn't know me at all.
He's so dense.
Mmm... I can smell money.
I love the smell of money.
It's blissful.
Let's go.
Already?
It's almost midnight.
I want to grab a drink.
But you have kids.
My mom's taking care of them.
I don't usually take care of them.
My housekeeper took care of them before.
I can't take care of my kids.
Shame on you.
We can't go out for a drink?
You have nobody waiting for you at home.
You said you're living alone now.
Do you have a girlfriend?
How can I?
I'm too busy for one.
I have golf early in the morning.
Okay.
Go.
I'm going only because of golf.
Should I come to work late tomorrow too?
Yes.
We have special investors, so look pretty.
I'm always pretty.
- Good night.
- Night.
Oh, you scared me!
You're home late.
I told you not to wait up.
Why did you?
You think I'm cheating on you?
What?
You think I'm hiding something?
I don't think that.
I was worried because it's past midnight.
Stop it.
Did I tell you to worry about me?
They take me home when it gets too late.
So don't stand by the bus stop or the door.
It bothers me.
Did something bad happen at work?
Why would you ask that?
If I'm not home, just go to bed.
Just go to bed instead of waiting for me.
You doing this bothers me.
You never did this before, so why start now?
Mom, the bathroom's so clean. It's great.
She even bought a bidet for the boys.
It has to be better than our beat up apartment.
It must be nice to live in such a big place.
Even the floor feels nice.
It smells different, too.
I can breathe better because it's big.
I breathe like this
in our apartment,
but here, see?
I can breathe more relaxed.
Mom, you're outrageous.
Mom, wouldn't it be nice if we lived here?
Hobak would cook for us, too.
Are you asleep?
I am.
Sedal.
I said I'm tired.
Hey!
You...
What are you doing?
Mom and Yeongdal are outside.
Please, let me hold you for a moment.
I can't breathe.
This is nutty, nutty, nuts.
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
Am I going there to die?
You're not keeping your promise.
You said you'd send me away with a smile.
So why are you acting like this?
You don't have any pride?
I told you I can't stand you,
so why are you getting all choked up here?
Just dump me. I'm a bastard.
You really have no clue, do you?
You're only pushing me away further by acting this way.
This is nuts.
Hey, you!
How dare you steal from me!
I worked really hard to grow them!
You bastards!
Bastards!
You can't take them!
How dare you!
Bastards!
No, you can't! You can't take them!
I don't believe this!
Yes, I'm on my way.
I'll be there in 5 minutes.
Yes, parcel service.
Minjung!
Minsuk, can I call you later? I'm busy.
Father had an accident.
What?
He's in surgery right now.
He hurt his back.
There was a robbery at the orchard.
The doctors don't know how serious it is.
Minjung, Minjung!
Poor father. Poor father...
- Father.
Minjung, Minsuk.
Father, are you okay?
What did they say?
The surgery went well,
and the nerve cells weren't damaged.
But you have to stay here for a few months.
You were lucky.
I'm sorry, kids.
Why did you call your brother?
I don't want to burden him.
What do you mean?
I should've been the first to know.
People get mad if their parcels come late.
I'm okay, so go back to work.
Don't worry about it.
I got someone else to cover for me.
Anyway, what happened?
There are many robberies in the countryside,
and they steal agricultural products.
I was patrolling the orchard,
and there were people at the shed.
I was going to sell them and help you out.
The insurance will cover the treatment,
but the problem is taking care of him.
He'll be bed bound for months,
so he'll need someone to take care of him.
I'd do it, but my in laws and the kids...
Minjung, can you talk to your wife?
I know she's not the type to do this,
but we have no other choice.
She's working now.
She is?
What do we do, then?
We'll have to hire someone.
You know how much that costs?
It'll take more than $2,000 a month.
I can't even pitch in $100 a month.
I'm so upset.
I have no time or money.
What do we do...
Done! Done!
All done!
Let's go.
Is this the moving company?
I asked for a truck ages ago!
Now? Okay, hurry over.
He's coming. Are you all packed?
Just about.
Mom, you're so smart.
I was famous for being clever.
Go to Myeongdong now.
Everyone has heard of me, Park Salla.
Everyone talked about how clever I was.
I think Sedal takes after you.
Oh, how are you?
You look pretty.
Director, what should we do with this?
Put them in the fridge. They are mine.
They smell. Throw them in the trash.
I'll throw them out.
Oppa, come out.
We're having a barbecue.
I'm coming.
Manager Wang Hobak, congratulations.
Thank you.
I'll put all my effort into making this the best branch in the country.
To the infinite growth of our company!
Let's go for it!
Hey, that's not how it's done.
You have to give it love.
Luh, luh, love.
There.
Say ah.
Ah.
Good girl.
Here.
We'll be on a deserted island for a week.
I wouldn't care if it were a prison.
I'm the prisoner and you're the guard.
This isn't a dream, is it?
I can't believe this is happening to me.
This is nutty, nutty, nuts!
Thank you, come again.
What is it? I'm busy.
Mom!
Sintong, why are you crying?
My room's gone!
What? Your room's gone?
What the...
Mother!
Yes, we're here.
Let's live together like a big family.
How could you do this to me?
Don't start. My son went to law school.
This is wrong.
How could you just move in like this?
This is my apartment.
Your apartment? Did you just say that?
It's my son's apartment, too.
Mom, she looks angry.
Who cares?
I'll crush her if she tries to kick us out.
You do that, mom.
Is that true?
He said it was a business trip to Busan,
but I think he went with that woman.
What is she going to do?
She has to divorce him, of course.
I don't know why Hobak's holding on to him.
Your father's going to pass out.
What are you talking about?
Why would I pass out?
What brings you here?
Hello, Mrs. Park.
I came to see Hobak.
She's not home right now.
She didn't come home yet?
I don't know.
Hello, grandpa.
Yes, yes. Hi.
Grandpa, grandma stole our room.
What?
We moved in.
We moved in today.
My son's on a month long business trip,
so I thought I should move in,
help her out and keep her company.
It took a lot of work.
It's a dangerous time,
so I could look after the boys.
Oh, I see.
Where is your mom?
I don't know. She got angry at grandma and...
Okay. I should go.
Goodbye, Mrs. Park.
To be honest, I'm angry at Hobak.
She only moved here with her family.
And look what happened today.
We moved without her help,
and she yelled at us and left.
She didn't learn any manners.
But she comes from a teacher's family.
I wonder whom she takes after.
I don't think it's you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't move here to be a burden on her.
I would be a big help.
I'll look after the boys and do the dishes.
I'd wash the rags, too.
But she keeps talking back at me.
The person you're trying to reach is unavailable.
Your call will be redirected to voice mail.
Why won't you divorce him?
Don't you have any feelings?
You have a good job.
And don't use your kids as an excuse.
What happened to us is your family's fault.
When I think about how your mother treated me,
I get really sick. Did you know that?
Hobak.
Father.
Why did you let him go?
What else could I do?
He wanted to go.
I couldn't stop him.
I had to, so he would return.
You think I'm a fool, don't you?
Why didn't you tell me?
You have parents and siblings!
I'm here for you, so why didn't you come to me instead of bottling it up like that?
You held everything inside as a child.
Your marriage should've turned out better.
I'm going to teach him a lesson.
He said he suffered, too.
How dare he say that?
He never made a penny!
He never worked!
That was what was hard on him.
Being unemployed must have been hard.
On top of that,
being mistreated by my family
was hard on him, too.
I know you were against our marriage,
so I wanted to make it work...
Father, I'm sorry.
Don't think about how others feel.
Hobak, if it's too hard for you...
I'm not getting a divorce, father.
You're the vice principal...
I don't care.
Your happiness is more important to me.
And I'll be retiring soon.
Are you living for your parents?
You should live for yourself.
Lots of women put up with cheating husbands.
I don't have the nerves to get a divorce.
I don't know if I can raise the boys by myself.
I'm really scared.
That's how I feel.
I'm not ready to let him go yet.
I'm being stupid. I know.
I can't help it, father.
I don't want to regret later on.
I'm going to tough it out a little longer.
I can't imagine my family without him.
My family is him, me, Sintong, and Bangtong.
I don't want to lose anyone.
I'm going to wait for him as long as I can.
I'm not sure how long it will be,
but I can be patient for now.
Okay.
I'm on your side,
no matter what.
Understand?
Give me a bottle of soju.
I will charge it to this card.
Please sign there.
Thank you. Enjoy your coffee.
Wake up.
Hey.
What is it?
Wake up.
What time is it?
Where are you coming from?
How could you sleep?
How could you, after what happened to Hobak?
Were you drinking?
Yes, I was.
I had to because I was so frustrated.
Why couldn't you spend any money on Hobak's wedding?
What?
Why are you bringing that old subject up?
Did someone say something to you?
Did you run into the hair salon woman?
If she hadn't gotten married with nothing,
her in laws would've respected her,
and her husband would've been nicer to her.
Is it my fault Hobak's marriage fell apart?
I don't believe you.
If you're drunk, just go to bed.
Why are you acting all drunk on me?
You think I'm saying this because I'm drunk?
It's already happened. I can't do anything!
She's just unlucky. That's all.
I didn't force her to marry him!
Why are you blaming me?
Everyone blames me for everything.
Having a bad husband is my fault.
Having a cheating husband is my fault, too.
Shut up!
You never feel sorry for anything you did!
How could you be so heartless?
Did a war break out or something?
Put yourself in her shoes.
Even with dogs, if their owners love them,
other people love them, too.
You treat Hobak like dirt,
so who could possibly love her?
The whole town knows you only love Subak.
But you only love Hobak! Don't you?
Don't be like that.
When you mistreat your child, it comes back as bad karma.
You were mean to Hobak's husband, too.
You compared your son in laws.
How could you be so mean?
You were mean to Sedal,
and you ruined their marriage.
What?
Did I raise the kids alone?
You raised them with me!
Why do you blame me for everything?
There's a big part of Hobak's issue that you've caused.
You compared Minjung and Sedal,
and you only cared about money.
And you call yourself a mother in law?
Son in laws are not like our own children,
no matter how close we are to them.
How could you mistreat them?
Don't you feel embarrassed to act like that?
You're so materialistic.
What did you say?
Materialistic?
I'm materialistic?
You're calling me that after all I've done for you?
Yes! Materialistic.
You're horrible.
I know you had a hard life after marrying me,
but you don't deserve to be a mother.
I feel ashamed.
My heart is breaking.
I'm supposed to be a teacher,
but I can't keep my family in line.
I'm a teacher,
but my wife runs wild.
I'm ashamed!
All because of you! Did you know?
I'm a horrible woman?
I'm materialistic?
Who made me this way?
I chase after money?
I only care about money?
I had to be that way because I had to
support your mother, father,
your four brothers and sisters,
and your five children on a teacher's salary!
How do you think we were able to afford this house?
I saved every penny I could,
cutting back on everything I could!
That's how I bought this house!
People don't respect you if you're poor!
We have this house because I chased after money!
You're the one who turned me into this!
Oh, boy.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
This family is falling apart. Egh, hyo, hyo...
Mother, your breakfast is read. Yeongdal.
Sit down, mother.
I will sit down, but...
Where are the boys?
They went to school and kindergarten.
Mother, I'm sorry about yesterday.
It's just that you didn't let me know,
and I was sad about Sintong's room.
I talked to the boys.
You did?
I'm scared because you changed overnight.
Don't be.
With Sedal gone,
I was worried about being lonely,
so I'm glad you moved in.
Mother, welcome.
I'm sure we can get along great.
Hello?
Who is this?
Yes, yes.
Yes. I will come right now.
This is nuts.
Ugh.
Why did I answer that?
Why did you want to see me?
Mommy!
Oh, man.
What brings you here?
Let's pretend we're not in laws.
I'm going to beat you up!
Did you get up on the wrong side of the bed?
You did a swell job raising your son.
On top of putting my daughter to misery,
now you turn my husband against me?
Have you gone completely mad?
Why would I turn your husband against you?
You should keep your son in line!
Why are you badmouthing my son?
You're his mom,
but you have no idea what he's up to!
What do you mean by that?
I'm going to kill you.
Why are you doing this?
Father, why are you doing this?
Use words!
You taught me never to use violence!
Help!
- Come with me!
- Hey! Hey!
Come with me.
You never treated my son well.
I should be the one screaming at you!
You hated Sedal because you hated Hobak.
Whenever we met, you bragged about Minjung,
saying my Minjung, my Minjung!
I couldn't ever forget his name!
Do you know how much you hurt my son?
That has nothing to do with cheating on Hobak!
If your in laws mistreat you,
it's okay to cheat on your wife?
So, are you saying what he did is okay?
I can't believe how brazen you are!
What are you doing?
Oh, hey!
Why are you attacking my mom?
You stay out of this!
Watch your manners when adults are talking.
Screaming at someone's workplace is being well mannered?
Causing a disturbance at someone's business is a crime!
Leave before I call the police!
Leave now!
Oh, my! Hey! Oh, my! Oh, my! Oh, my! Mom, mom.
Mom, mom.
Oh, ugh, ugh... Ugh... Hey!
Hey! You!
Open the door! Open!
Open!
Hey!
I won't say this twice.
Go back to your family today.
Today?
I can't today.
What?
I have to sort things out,
and to be honest,
Hobak and I came to a decision together legally,
so for a third party to butt in like this is a bit...
- You little...
- How dare you!
Father,
I can't get a divorce yet.
I'm going to tough it out.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Subtitles by KBS World
Can you check on my father?
Please do something for him.
You don't even have a hundred thousand?
You'll turn that into two hundred thousand?
I thought your father's a vice principal.
Teachers have the best credit.
How could you do this? Get out.
Bastard!
They didn't break up because we said no.
He was two timing!
He wouldn't do that to me.
He couldn't do that.
Mother, I can't come home tonight.
You're my husband and you won't give me any credit!
Do you even know how I feel?