Subtitles by KBS World
You pulled a ligament.
And the tendons around it are swollen.
What's wrong with your arm?
I said what's wrong?
I fell and I pulled a ligament.
Why would you fall down like that? Huh?
Don't you watch where you're going?
What have you been up to these days?
Are you writing anything?
After you quit your teaching job,
you look really bad!
Why are you adding to my misery?
What am I supposed to do with you?
Just leave me alone, please.
What?
What do you know about me?
You don't care if I died!
You just want me to make lots of money!
All you care about is a daughter you can brag about to other people!
You don't care about me.
You just want me to be successful so you can brag!
How dare you!
You're acting like this over a man?
Ugh! Seriously!
Where did you get those from?
I wanted you to eat them before going on your business trip.
You love pancakes.
I love the ones you make.
I'm too weak and I've lost my touch,
so I can't make them like I used to.
There's a place that makes old style pancakes.
Did you have lunch?
Yes, I did.
No, you didn't!
Your face looks gaunt.
Bong,
you're upset with your children and wife.
But don't be.
They'll live according to their destiny.
Try some.
Okay. You eat, too.
I had lunch at the senior center.
Mmm, it's good.
Mother.
Seeing you like this...
You've gotten so old.
Me?
I didn't know it at home,
but here, you look like a grandfather.
I'm not. I look younger than my friends.
People would think you're my husband.
Don't worry.
I'm as strong as a horse.
Mother.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
I shouldn't starve myself.
It's not like anyone cares.
I should just die!
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Is anyone home?
What are you doing?
I took some medicine.
Did you eat?
I didn't.
I haven't eaten anything in days.
There's rice stuck to your lips.
Did you eat mixed rice?
I see chili paste.
You shouldn't lie.
If you ate something, just say so.
Why would you lie about that?
I'm coming from Bong's school,
and oh, seeing him outside the house,
he looked old enough to be my husband.
This is all your fault.
Bong getting wrinkles is my fault?
You lost control of your daughters and that stressed my son out, making him old!
I can't believe my ears!
Time goes by and people get old.
You should feel sorry for your husband.
You'll know what I mean when you lose him,
and people start treating you differently.
Your children respect you because of him.
But what if he's gone?
They'll treat you like nothing.
Without your husband, you're nothing,
so be good to him.
When I die, your son will be nothing, too.
If I starve, it's my loss.
Nobody understands me.
Sangnam!
I know we're both men, so I shouldn't say this,
but I just have to say one thing.
My sister
is sick.
Maybe you've been with many women,
but my sister...
For her, you're the first man!
She's not pretty and she's ill tempered,
but she's a very good sister.
Why would you make her cry?
You should've never let go of her!
A real man must protect the woman he loves!
Oh!
Good shot!
What was that?
It's hard. This is really hard.
Hello.
We have specially priced items.
If you need help, let me know.
This winter is going to be especially cold, and
this coat is warm but extremely light weight.
Would you like to try it on?
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Ugh!
I'm home!
- Hobak!
- Yes!
You won't even come out and say hi?
I was busy cleaning.
How was your day?
Oh!
Mom, look. Hobak must have cleaned the room.
She has to. I'm her mother in law.
I have something to say to the both of you.
What is it?
Have some.
Mother, how's your shop going?
Very well. We'll pay back the loan soon.
- Whoa!
- There's nothing I can't do.
I heard I won't ever run out of money.
I know.
Can you bring me some samples?
I heard it's good, so I want to try it.
I can't! They're for the customers.
You should buy them.
You make money.
I've never seen you buy and skin care products.
Cosmetic companies will go bankrupt if everyone was like you.
And beauty salons, too.
After using the samples,
I was going to buy some.
I'm dressing up more now.
You have changed since you've become manger.
But you still have a long way to go.
It does matter how you take care of yourself.
Now that I handle customer service,
I must make a good impression.
You just wanted to ask for samples?
No.
I'd like to divide the chores up.
What?
I have a full time job, and I have kids,
so I was hoping you could help.
You're not the only one who works!
I know.
All three of us work and are busy,
so let's help each other out.
We live together now, and if things don't
work out, we'll end up hating each other.
As you know, my mom suffered a lot
because of my aunts and my grandmother.
They're still not on good terms,
and I don't want that to happen here.
So let's try to be considerate.
How do you want us to be considerate?
First of all, I'll do all the cooking.
But if you cook something special sometimes, that'd be nice, too.
Who will do the grocery shopping?
I joined the bundle program.
What's that?
Farmers send you the things they grow once a week.
Every week it's something different, and it's fresh.
I joined it after I moved here,
and it's convenient.
How about the dishes?
When you eat something, you should do it.
You two can do the laundry and cleaning.
Yeongdal, you clean the bathroom.
Me?
Or mother, you can do it.
Oh, man...
I finally went out to the field!
But I didn't do as well as I expected.
I was really good at the range.
That's normal.
What did your wife say?
Nothing. People around her say stuff, though.
Her family?
Yes.
It would've been so wonderful if you'd met me before getting married.
Oh, I'm craving for something spicy.
Don't you have anything different?
Spicy? Like what?
Something salty and savory.
Like kimchi or...
I don't eat kimchi. It's not classy.
Korean men are weird.
They have to have food like that.
I didn't eat kimchi before.
Don't underestimate me.
Have you thought about it?
Is it a sure thing?
You think I'd lie?
You'll turn a hundred thousand to two in a month?
Yes.
Oh...
I would love to do it.
I told you how to do it.
I'm scared.
It's not easy to make a hundred thousand.
You can give your father ten thousand.
That'll make your father very happy.
If it goes wrong, he'll kill me.
And I have younger siblings.
Forget it, then.
I was being considerate.
Let's go.
So it's a sure thing?
If the others found out, they'd kill me.
I'm letting you in behind their backs.
We never take investments that small.
It's always in millions.
You know that.
I do, but still...
Should we go on a trip?
When?
To where?
Soon.
You pick where to go.
I want some time off to clear my head.
You've set fire to my heart.
Ugh.
Nice. Nice and roomy.
This is so nice.
What are you doing up?
What about you, mother?
I can't sleep because Bong's not home.
Oh, I wonder if he's in bed and if the room's warm enough.
I'm sure he's sleeping really well
at a very nice hotel with a plush bed.
You can't sleep because you miss him!
I can't believe my ears.
With my nagging husband gone,
I feel as free as a bird.
It's freedom for me.
It must be nice to have all that room.
Oh, of course!
I have lots of room to roll around.
And I don't have to get up early and cook.
Good night.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Let's see...
Oh, he was so young back then.
He looks younger than me in this picture.
He looked so old and wrinkled.
He could pass as my husband.
You've gotten really old, honey.
It's your fault, did you know?
Then who made me this old?
This is our 100 day anniversary.
Honey!
You're the best!
Let's love each other forever.
Forever my butt.
Leave her alone. She's drunk.
You think it'll last forever, don't you?
Dream on!
Don't trust men.
There is no such thing as love!
What's wrong with you?
How rude!
Leave her be.
Let me go.
Hey, it looks like you got dumped.
You look really pathetic.
What?
Pathetic?
Hey!
I can't believe this.
So? What are you going to do about it?
I just feel really sorry for you both.
You're crazy!
This is why you got dumped!
Yes! I was! I was!
I got dumped. So what?
I'm as miserable as can be. So what?
Oh, Gwangbak, let's go.
Hey, pull yourself together!
Your boyfriend's here.
I'm not her boyfriend.
How awful.
How dare you...
Love is difficult.
Hey, ugh...
Ugh! Man...
Uncle, she hasn't been eating.
It's because this was her first love.
Haebak, you should practice dating.
When you go to college, start dating.
She's suffering from love sickness.
What do we do, uncle?
This is love sickness?
I know what it is.
- Father.
- Yes?
Minsuk will be here soon.
It's a very busy day for me.
It's Tuesday.
You should go.
But you didn't get any sleep.
I took a nap when you were asleep.
You should sleep a little more.
I really like the caregiver.
Where did you find such a nice person?
You like her?
Yes, and she's considerate.
She's a great cook, too.
She's perfect in every way.
Has she done that for a long time?
I think so.
I'm glad you like her.
But,
if she comes every day,
it would be expensive.
Don't worry about it.
Just get well.
Minjung.
Yes, uncle?
Can we talk?
Love sickness?
What else could it be?
What do we do?
Why are you asking me?
Is there anything we can do?
This just might end up killing Gwangbak.
Did you sleep well?
I didn't. Ugh...
Where's Subak?
She must be sleeping in her room.
But she's not there.
Where else could she be?
I don't think Subak came home last night.
Why would you say that?
She's sleeping in my room.
She slept with me last night.
I didn't see her.
I was up pretty late.
She came home really, really late.
You don't know anything.
What? What? What are you doing?
I have to ask her something.
Ask her later.
Do you have to wake her up?
She got home really late.
You can call her later and ask.
Why are you coming home now?
I told you I left really late.
Shh!
Say you came home really late last night.
If your father finds out, he'll be furious.
Minjung came home early in the morning.
Why didn't he go to work from the hospital?
He came to change before going to work.
I told him you were asleep.
Don't tell him what really happened.
I wasn't out partying. I was working.
Sunjeong.
Yes?
Tell Sangnam I found a woman for him.
Okay. I'll meet her.
Huh?
Sunjeong!
- Sunjeong.
- Minsuk!
Sunjeong! Sunjeong!
Minjung told me about you.
He said he ran into you making deliveries.
Yes.
This was meant to be.
You look the same.
You do, too.
I've grown old.
It's all in the past,
but after you left him,
he was totally messed up.
I thought he was going to die.
He might have done something stupid
if it weren't for our parents.
But after a year, he started working hard.
He was lucky and he became successful.
What if you waited for him?
We used to talk about you a lot.
Mom and father never met you,
but they talked a lot about you.
People started introducing women to him,
and he married Subak 3 months after meeting her.
I thought he was rushing in,
and it was because of you.
He was trying to forget you.
But he's not happily married.
I'm telling you this because I trust you,
but Minjung married the wrong woman.
She looked pretty in the picture.
Who cares about looks?
She's not nice.
She's never done anything for my parents.
She's never once cooked them a warm meal.
He has no control over his wife.
He's a kind soul.
He's not. He's stupid.
You should've married him.
He'll get mad if he finds out I told you this.
It's a secret.
Anyway, Sunjeong, thank you so much.
I owe you one.
I'm paying back for my past mistakes.
I know it's not enough.
I'm doing it so I can feel better.
It'll double in a month. Double.
Invest a hundred thousand.
I'll double it to two hundred thousand.
Mom!
What are you doing?
Huh?
What are you searching for?
Oh,
have you seen Aeji's red sweater?
She wants it.
Aeji's clothes are in your room, not here.
I only have Jungji's clothes.
Right. I forgot.
Ugh.
Mom, you're not going to the market?
I'm not.
Go to the sauna, then. I'll pay for it.
I'm too tired for it.
I'll boil them,
so you go to the sauna and relax.
You've been really tired lately.
And father's been stressing you out.
I don't feel like it.
This is how you get old!
Don't be like this.
You have to live until I send you on a cruise.
Whatever.
I'm never going on a cruise.
You will!
Mom, go and meet your friends.
You haven't seen them lately.
Go singing with them or something.
I can't sing when I'm depressed.
What's wrong with you?
I'm too tired.
I want to make you feel better.
Yes, it's me.
What?
How did it happen?
That is so tragic.
Right now?
You want to go now?
Okay.
Mom, are you going somewhere?
Someone died and I have to go to the funeral.
Oh, right now?
Didn't you hear me right?
Someone died and I'm going to the funeral.
Oh!
I think I heard wrong.
Mom, I'll do this, so go get dressed up.
I can't get dressed up for a funeral.
Oh, what's wrong with me?
I keep saying stupid things.
Call your boss. Say you can't come to work.
Don't worry about that.
I should take care of the kids.
Take the laundry in later.
Okay. Don't worry.
Take good care of Jungji.
I said don't worry.
I'll be back.
Life is so futile.
Nobody knows when he or she will die.
Mom, see you later.
Oh, honey...
How am I supposed to live...
How could you leave me like this...
Father...
I should've been better to you...
I should've stopped nagging...
I'm sorry.
Honey, I'm so sorry...
I'm sorry...
I can't go on...
How can I go on alone?
Calm down, calm down.
Who am I going to talk to now?
How could you leave me just like that?
Why wasn't I better to you?
Mother! Mother!
What are you doing?
Bring some water!
This could happen to anyone.
He died from a heart attack.
How sad...
Her husband retired.
I think he was forced to retire early,
and she was really mean to him for that.
Right. She didn't even cook for him.
They slept in separate rooms, too.
But she must feel really guilty now.
She might be bawling now, but she'll recover.
I feel sorry for the dead.
Right. Look at me.
When my husband died,
I thought I'd die too, but I'm alive.
My husband must be tired of waiting.
You can't die.
You have children.
But they can't beat having a husband.
Even if he's bed bound, he's the best.
- Right.
- Yes.
No husband, no respect from your kids.
I envy you the most, Anggeum.
Our husbands are all old and retired,
but your husband is still a vice principal.
What's the use of saying I should've?
I should've been better and stopped nagging.
If you still have husbands,\
treat them well, instead of regretting later.
Right, right.
I'm going to start being good to my husband today.
Let's go.
I have to make dinner for my husband.
Since I'm single, I should go to work.
Anggeum, let's go.
Oh, my!
Oh, seriously...
Haebak called us, saying you might die.
Was he a two timer?
No, that was a misunderstanding.
Stop working here.
You can't even eat, so how can you work?
When I'm here, I can forget.
I can't stay home.
I keep checking my phone all day.
Waiting for him to call me.
I keep deleting and saving his number.
And I keep checking the phone again.
It's driving me crazy.
Oh, boy.
I don't know what to say.
Trying to console someone is the hardest.
You should get plastic surgery.
What?
Why?
After you get surgery,
you'll be swollen and stuck in your room.
You'd be horrified about getting calls.
It happened to me once.
I forgot about men and looked in the mirror.
That makes sense.
Tell her something she can actually do.
I'm just frustrated. That's why.
Then you should convince father.
I'm sure she couldn't even try because mom and father fought over my issues.
Love causes all kinds of trouble.
Don't worry. I won't die.
I'll try to beat this.
You need time.
You two could run away together.
This isn't the Joseon Dynasty.
Who breaks up because of their parents?
He's pretty awful.
He broke up with you over that?
Did you really break up with Gwangbak?
How could you give up so easily?
I was so frustrated, so I called you.
Gwangbak can't even eat.
She's a kind and innocent soul.
You can't just leave a woman like that.
I've lived longer than you,
and meeting the perfect mate isn't easy.
You think you'll find another one? No.
If someone feels right,
don't let go of her.
If I could've, I would've a thousand times.
I would've done everything I could.
I would've begged her parents to say yes,
but this isn't something I can change.
It's about my education and family.
I didn't want to make things hard for her.
Oh, you're a good boy!
You're such a good boy.
Where are you going?
Grandma, grandma.
Let's see how yummy this is.
Is it you, honey?
It's your honey's little brother.
Why are you out here?
I was just taking out the trash.
Mother, I'm home.
Oh, you are!
How was your trip?
- Grandma, hello.
- Hi.
Good. How have you been?
I missed you so much that I almost got sick.
I don't think I can live without you.
I can't either, mother.
You must be really happy to see him.
- Father, you're back.
- Hello.
Yes.
- Let me have that.
- Okay.
Why don't you say hi?
You waited for him.
I didn't wait for anyone!
You cooked all these for father.
I cooked for everyone, not just your father.
Oh, it's a feast.
This is better than my husband's ancestral rites feast.
You only care about your husband, don't you?
I didn't cook all these just for my husband.
Father,
mom was outside the door waiting for you.
I wasn't!
I saw her waiting for you, too.
She didn't sleep last night,
saying she missed you.
Why would you all say such a thing?
Did you miss me that much?
I can't believe my ears.
- Mother.
- Yes?
It was so nice I didn't want to come home.
I came back because of you.
I don't believe a word of that.
A wife came back from her class reunion all annoyed, so her husband asked her.
What's wrong?
Did your friend bring a new luxury bag? No.
Are you jealous of someone's son? No.
Then did someone come in an imported car? No.
So why are you acting this way, he asked.
Oh, I'm the only one with a husband! Right?
They don't know what they're talking about.
But it's nice to hear you both laugh.
The mood was icy the last couple of days.
The most important people in this family are Bong and Anggeum, understand?
Where's Gwangbak?
She went to the library.
Father, about Gwangbak...
Let's not talk about her.
Subak, what's going on?
- What do you mean?
- A woman for Don.
Stop putting it off,
and just find someone already.
All my friends have girlfriends.
What?
Half the kids have girlfriends.
Ugh...
The school should provide sex education.
Not just about eggs and sperms,
but about how to use condoms and stuff.
Thank you for dinner.
I'm shocked.
That's nothing.
Father, Daebak's right.
The school should provide real sex education.
Kinds these days are so precocious.
I actually agree with you.
Did you think about what you did?
You should think about what you did.
Was it nice sleeping alone?
Of course.
I rolled around the room all night.
What are you doing?
What happened to you during the trip?
Be still.
Man.
I was really harsh, wasn't I?
I said awful things out of anger.
I'm sorry.
I must be getting old.
Little things seem to bother me greatly.
We're both getting old.
It's the same for me, too.
It's hard to age gracefully.
I keep getting meaner,
and everything is getting rough.
My hands are getting rough,
and even my words are getting rough.
Oh, right!
The grain shop woman's husband died.
But he's not even 70 yet.
I know.
I went to the funeral and it felt weird.
Why?
Are you afraid of becoming a widow?
Not afraid. I was jealous.
No making breakfast, no nagging.
I was so jealous of her.
Oh, where are you going?
I'm going on another business trip.
You're not going anywhere!
Oh, boy.
Coming back from the funeral,
I felt really weird.
Who will be by my side at the end of my life?
Who will massage my aching body
and bring me a glass of water?
You have to live a long life.
You can nag me all you want,
but stay by my side for a long time.
The person you have called is unavailable,
so you will be connected to voice mail.
Sedal, I need to talk to you, so call me.
It's not going to be bad, so call me.
It's me.
Oh, yes, yes.
Can you come and meet me?
I have a few conditions.
Conditions?
Tell me.
It can't be anywhere secluded.
Not like the riverbank, like last time.
I want to meet somewhere crowded.
And don't bring Loser or a baseball bat.
I'll see you there, then.
Okay.
Sedal, I'm glad you came.
Where's Loser?
I didn't bring him.
And I didn't bring a bat.
Sit.
Make yourself comfortable.
I won't beat you.
I didn't ask you here to beat you up.
Really?
- Sedal.
- What are you doing?
You said you won't beat me.
I won't.
Sit, sit.
What would you like to drink?
I'll pick something later.
I'd like to talk first.
I'm sorry about before.
I was too emotional.
I thought about it and I do understand you.
You do?
I knew you would understand me.
That's why you're a teacher.
Life is long,
so you might want to cheat on your wife.
Right?
You feel that way too, don't you?
Oh, be honest with me.
You do, don't you?
Let's say I do.
There is no "let's say."
Oh, now we're communicating.
I'm sorry I didn't treat you better.
I'm apologizing on behalf of my family.
Everything you said was correct.
I'm sorry.
It's too late for an apology.
In the past, punishment for sins came late,
but now, it comes right away, with speed.
See? You treated me like that,
and look what happened to your family.
Your favorite son in law went bankrupt,
Gwangbak is now unemployed,
and I left your daughter.
It's a total mess.
Father,
you should become a strong leader.
Don't let mother push you around.
She's all bark and no bite.
Sedal,
let's pretend none of this happened,
and go home.
Where would you find anyone like Hobak?
She became stubborn to make a living,
but she really loves you.
But I loathe her.
Who's going to take care of you when you're old and sick?
Think about who will be there for you when that happens.
The answer will be easy.
When I'm old?
Yes.
Just think about it.
I knew it.
Goof-off! God's punishing you!
I'm so glad you're sick!
I'm hungry. Give me some food.
Food?
Have you lost your mind?
Why did you cheat on me?
I told you I'd get you back!
You deserve more pain than this!
What's that?
Oh, yuck! I hate you!
I wish you were dead!
Oppa.
Girls, say hello.
They are your caregivers, oppa.
Money can buy anything, so don't worry.
I'll get you new organs.
Let's enjoy a long life together.
This is nuts.
I got my answer.
Huh?
What's up?
Look at you! You don't look right.
Dressing up will do you no good.
- Let's get some coffee.
- No.
I want a divorce.
What?
It's not working out.
I want a divorce.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
- Hey!
- What?
I'm being extremely patient here!
Don't be patient.
There's no need for that.
I don't want to talk about this ever again.
You said you wanted a month of freedom.
But why should we wait a month?
You're so weird.
Why do you love me so much?
Even so, it just won't work.
I'm living in a different world now.
So think about it.
I can't go back to how I was before.
You live the way you used to before.
I'm Choi Sangnam.
It's the first snow.
Meeting you tonight feels very meaningful.
You didn't make any special plans tonight?
Excuse me?
People make plans to meet up on the day of the first snow.
Lovers say that, too.
Well, I'm here because I have nobody.
You're right.
It's not like our friends introduced us.
It was our parents who got us together,
so I don't want to waste any time.
I like you, Sangnam.
What do you think about me?
I appreciate you saying that,
but do you know about me?
Like what?
Everything.
You can't fully know someone,
so I don't know what kind of person you are.
But I know what you do and about the environment you grew up in.
I heard from my parents.
Is there anything else I need to know?
My parents are divorced.
It happened when I was really young.
And I dropped out of high school.
I heard.
I don't care about that.
Your parents divorce isn't your fault.
It's wrong to think you'd be weird because you grew up in a single parent family.
And a college degree isn't a must these days.
You have a good job and you're set,
so who cares about your education?
It's snowing a lot for the first snow.
Should we go for a walk?
I wore comfortable shoes, just in case.
May I pet him?
Yes.
You must like dogs.
I want to kiss you under a street light
when it snows for the first time.
Let's meet when it snows for the first time.
You're here.
I'm sorry I'm late. It's snowing outside.
It is?
It really is.
It's the first snow.
Why didn't you tell me?
About not being married.
About him being your brother in law.
I thought it would break your heart if you found out I was divorced.
If your ex is doing well, you get upset,
if she's miserable, you feel sad,
and if she wants you back, you get a headache.
Is that so?
That sounds about right.
Everything happened because of my sister.
She was so wild,
and she ruined our family in no time at all.
I had to get married
to save my family,
and my husband was
nineteen years older than me.
Right after I married him,
I knew it was wrong.
I couldn't live with another man
while the man I loved still
remained within me.
I had to see him every day,
eat with him,
and sleep in the same bed,
and I just couldn't do it.
I left him right after my daughter was born.
I lived with him less than a year.
I had to support my daughter,
so I worked really hard.
I had to bring my baby to work,
and people didn't like it.
Eventually, I ended up in Geoje-do Island,
and I ran into my brother in law there.
He brought us back to Seoul.
He had built up his business in Seoul,
and now I live with him and his son.
Our lives were ruined by my sister.
And now we all live together.
My story is pathetic, isn't it?
No.
I'm comfortable and happy.
I have a place to sleep,
there's always food on the table,
I can send Miho to school,
and I met you.
That's all I need.
You've had such a hard life.
I had no idea.
Should we go out in the snow?
Like in the old days?
Oh, this is nice.
Hey! You!
Don't!
It's snowing and I miss you.
Can we meet up now?
I want to walk in the snow with you all night.
Like in the old days.
Your father might wake up.
We should go back.
Who is she?
Subtitles by KBS World
Subak didn't come home?
She did.
But she went to work early.
It doesn't look like she came home.
What are you doing home at this hour?
Sign it.
I'm begging you. Let me breathe.
I want to meet her parents this weekend.
My parents said yes.
I miss you so, so much.
You should forget about me.
They're setting the date.
And it'll be over between you two.
Tell him I wish him happiness.