Subtitles by KBS World
Oh, my!
Excuse me.
Where am I?
Excuse me...
I don't know how we got here,
but can we pretend this never happened?
I think I got drunk and made a mistake.
I'm not this kind of woman.
But I'm not saying I don't like you
or regretting what happened last night,
but I feel rather awkward and embarrassed.
I'll leave first.
Keep your eyes closed until you hear the door.
I'll call you later.
What? What are you doing? You can't do this!
What do you mean by that?
Mom, how did you find me?
I came to beat the crap out of you.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Are you really?
Mom, he's done nothing wrong.
It's all because I got drunk.
Are you still drunk?
- Huh?
- What are you talking about?
He? Who?
Huh? What? Why am I here?
Quit drinking so much!
How can you drink every night?
And why did you bother your brother instead of going to bed in your own room?
And why did you try to kiss him?
Me?
You said something about a matchmaker and tried to kiss him.
You know what he did?
He slept in my room.
Thank god your dad's on a business trip.
He would have kicked you out!
What did you mean about the matchmaker?
I don't know. I blacked out.
Nice going!
Ouch, that hurts.
I can't believe you quit your teaching job.
Help around the house, at least.
Ugh, you wreak of alcohol!
Don't you feel embarrassed?
Daebak said you had sewer breath.
What? I don't have sewer breath!
You do! I can smell it from here!
Go and brush your teeth.
Ugh! I washed this two days ago.
What if people start talking about you?
Who cares about what people say?
What?
I'm just having a bad year, okay?
Why that little...
Ugh!
I'm leaving.
There isn't much time left.
Study hard.
You don't need to tell Haebak that.
Are you okay?
- I'm dying.
- Don't come to my room!
You jerk!
I'm not going to fetch you soup.
Go get it yourself.
Remember what Bong said?
It's better to go wild when you're young.
The law of the total amount of wildness.
Look after Jungji today.
She kept me up all night.
Come home earlier and make the dog noise.
Uncle, can you do it?
When I do it, she starts crying.
I'd cry, too.
Why don't you have Subak take care of them?
She can't do that now.
Why not? They're her kids.
I raised my kids and took care of my in laws during the war.
People can't understand the mother in laws
who talk about the old days and nag their daughter in laws.
Ask anybody on the street if you want.
Why would I ask people on the street?
They'll get upset if I stopped them.
I'm going to watch how good you are to Daebak's wife.
Leave me out.
I won't put my wife through it.
I know how it feels.
You haven't sent it yet?
But I've been waiting for it.
Okay.
Sunjeong, I'm sorry.
It'll arrive some time tomorrow.
Receive it, but don't open it.
What is it?
Why are you so concerned?
It's a secret.
Oh, no...
Aren't you writing?
You said you would!
I will! I will!
Hello.
This is my table.
I always sit here whenever I come here.
How did you know?
It beckoned me.
Careful, your mouth will split!
Where are you coming from?
I was looking for a job.
Goof-off got a job without me.
How about you?
I couldn't take mom's nagging anymore.
I have to move out if I don't get published this year.
Get a two bedroom so I can tag along.
Ugh!
Gwangbak, buy me some skewered chicken.
Oh, really?
That sounds like a lot of fun.
Tell me more.
I don't think it's all that interesting,
but I'm grateful you think so.
Do you still see those friends?
Yes. We drink soju every now and then.
Oh, soju!
But I'm not much of a drinker.
But that's no fun.
That's how you learn about life.
I'm not saying I can't drink at all.
I take sips.
Excuse me.
I'd love to have a drink, but I have plans.
That's too bad. I'd like to, too.
I wanted to continue this at a bar.
Oh, I love bars, too.
Just a second.
Stay still.
Look what I found.
Good for you, Hobak.
Good job.
You've worked so hard,
and you finally bought your own place.
Yes, father.
I finally bought my own house.
But Sedal doesn't know yet.
I'm telling you first.
I'm proud of you.
I remember the first place you lived in.
It was your first visit after I had Sintong.
It was such an awful place that I didn't even have a housewarming party.
I walked into the basement floor,
1 bedroom apartment with no windows,
and you were lying there in the dark, all swollen right after giving birth...
It's as if it was yesterday.
That was the first time I ever saw you cry.
You didn't make a sound,
but I still remember
how your shoulders shook.
I couldn't even pay for your college tuition,
and I couldn't even give you a decent wedding because of Subak and Don.
Whenever I think of you,
it hurts right here.
It's okay, father.
I'm rich now.
It's a 3 bedroom and 2 bathroom apartment.
I didn't finish college, but I'm a general manager,
so I'm doing pretty well.
Owning an apartment in Seoul is a big deal.
Father, I did well, didn't I?
Of course, of course.
I'm very proud of you.
But I can't tell mom.
I feel like I've done something wrong.
Don't think that. Be proud of yourself.
I will.
I'll tell mom and Subak later.
You do that.
Oh...
I feel so relieved now.
You finally did it.
Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Okay.
Subak.
What are you doing here?
No reason.
Did you go grocery shopping?
Are you buying furniture?
I was just looking around.
In case my boys need something later.
Are you hiding something from me?
Of course not.
I have to get back to work.
It's my lunch break.
I'll drop by to clean your bathroom.
Bye, Subak.
No way.
I'm sure!
She bought an apartment.
Father.
Why are you here?
Why are you here so late? Huh?
Why are you telling at her?
She came to see her girls.
I thought I made it clear.
Don't let her come here.
You were here all day, weren't you?
She came just now.
Mother, when did she come?
I don't know.
She never says hi or goodbye.
Maybe she's been here since morning or yesterday, but I didn't see.
You saw her come just now!
What do you mean, yesterday?
I said I didn't see her come in.
- Did you see?
- No.
Take your girls and go home.
Why aren't you taking care of your girls?
You can't raise kids there.
There's no sunlight,
and it's infested with roaches.
You don't know what you're talking about.
Kill them.
Look at Hobak.
She's raising her boys,
killing all roaches and mice.
Learn from your little sister.
She couldn't finish college because of you,
but she worked really hard and now she's bought...
Don't tell them, father.
She bought an apartment, didn't she?
I'm not saying she did.
I'm saying she's working hard to buy one.
Hobak's not relying on her parents.
Haven't you learned anything from her?
Go home and stop coming here!
What's wrong with you!
Why would you tell at our poor daughter?
What he said was right.
Burying coal won't turn it into a diamond.
I can't believe my ears.
Subak's coal and Hobak's a diamond?
She's been suffering from depression!
How could you yell at her?
In front of everyone?
You shouldn't have talked about coal.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
Come out.
Don't keep shaking your head like that.
You might hurt yourself.
Oh, how disrespectful!
You're treating me differently now that I'm working.
I actually felt like having some beer.
Pour your husband a glass.
How dare you! I'm older.
Me first.
I don't believe this!
This can only mean one thing.
Sintong! Bangtong!
You'll wake them up!
I'm exhausted.
I won't touch you.
I can't believe you're thinking about that.
Pour me some beer.
Yes, older woman.
Congratulate me.
Congratulate you?
Don't ask any questions.
Just say, "Congratulations."
I'm going nuts.
Why?
You have a knack for such things.
What? What do I have a knack for?
You got pregnant with Sintong on your own,
and you had Bangtong without talking to me.
And now you're pregnant with a third baby?
Don't get ahead of yourself.
It's not a baby.
You're not pregnant?
Oh! Thank god.
Don't even think about it.
Look at the boys names.
Sintong and Bangtong.
What could we name the third child?
All I can think of is Ddongtong.
There are plenty of choices.
Kobrangtong. Sintong, Bangtong, Kobrangtong.
It's perfect.
We can't use Kobrangtong! Kobrangtong.
Actually, it's not bad.
Here.
What is it?
Open it.
It can't be divorce papers.
What's this?
You bought an apartment?
Yes.
Are these really the deeds to a home?
Like Don's sister in law says,
I can't believe my eyes!
This isn't fake, is it?
It's real.
So in other words,
we are finally homeowners?
I'm going nuts!
Hey, hey!
Hey!
What do I do?
Oh, what do I do?
Are you seeing him again?
Of course.
I can't understand girls who don't get asked back out after blind dates.
Good for you.
Grab him. I heard he's rich.
He's really handsome, too.
Nice face, nice voice, muscular arms.
Rich and from a good family.
He has everything.
If this works out, I can crush Anggeum.
I get mad just thinking about what she's done to me.
Maybe I should change my name.
Park Salla. I hate my name.
Just you wait, Mrs. Park Salla.
Men don't escape from me.
How scary!
Goof-off.
How can you get a job without me?
Don't be such a loser, loser.
My treat, so eat up.
I don't need stamina food like this.
It'll only give me insomnia.
Your niece is dead.
I'm going nuts!
You're crazy.
Say that after the fact.
What happened?
Don't ask.
I'd love to, but I'm holding my tongue.
Hobak told me not to say anything.
What are they?
How come he has three women?
He's not more handsome than me.
He's not darker nor have more bulgy eyes.
This.
He must be loaded.
It's very obvious.
Women these days only care about one thing.
Only money.
If I had money, I'd go to one of those bars
where I can line up a dozen women and pick.
Hey, you, get out.
Why is an ugly girl like you here?
Go home and wash the dishes.
Hey, you, come over here.
Ugh, just look at your face.
Why did you come here for?
I already have an ugly one at home.
Attention, at ease, stand up, sit down.
I'll show them who's boss.
I know.
Don,
I can't stop myself.
I finally bought an apartment.
No way.
Look.
Incredible!
I even made a copy for myself.
I'm utterly happy.
Finally, Heo Sedal has everything.
You should be grateful for Hobak.
You accused her of getting pregnant on purpose.
I envy you.
I'd love it if some pregnant woman appeared out of nowhere and said,
"You're the father of my child."
Where could she possibly be?
- Who?
- My other half.
She's growing up somewhere.
She's getting old somewhere.
Who cares.
If she's rich, she could be a grandmother.
I could be her dog.
Let's go, if you're full.
Ugh, I can't get up.
You go ahead.
Already?
Eels are amazing.
Your niece is dead.
Finally, Heo Sedal has everything.
I have a wife, kids, an apartment and a job.
Everything.
What do you have?
Nothing.
Have you thought about your dream?
What?
Old man living alone. Perfect.
Mother.
Why did you give birth to me?
I'm always being picked on by that goof-off and mistreated by my own nephew.
I went to school like others and finished my army service like others.
I never did anything special,
and now I'm already thirty-five.
The eels didn't do a thing for me.
I'm actually getting hungry.
Should I make some instant noodles?
Why? Instant noodles?
Are you hungry?
Wake Anggeum up.
No, no. Mom, go back to sleep.
I should.
I must sleep to dream, dream to see my love,
see my love to pick berries, pick berries...
You'll stay up all night.
Pick berries to make money to go see dad.
Okay?
Yes, yes.
I must see your dad.
You're so...
What are you doing?
I said get ready.
Get ready for what?
Just go to sleep.
Let's make a baby!
Let's do it for the country.
Oh, I'm exhausted.
This doesn't happen every day!
I ate eels for dinner.
Oh, no! Are you crazy?
Why did you have eels?
You get sick when you do!
Right.
Are you okay?
Hey, hey!
Pants, pants
Two, three, pants, pants
I'm afraid, pants, pants
Mother, we're going.
Are you going to the bath house?
Yes.
Have a good bath.
We will.
What's that song you're singing?
Yongpil's song.
Pants, pants
I guess he's trying to sell underpants.
Why don't you buy Anggeum some?
She's always talking about them.
I don't know that song.
You're so good at keeping up with trends.
Teach me when you learn the whole song.
Okay. Have fun.
- Okay.
- We'll be back.
- See you later.
Yes, Aeji, grandfather will be back soon.
Bong,
watch out for the cars.
And don't run.
You might fall down.
Yes, mother. I'll watch out.
You do that.
Turn around now.
Is there anything you want to try out?
Not really...
Think about what you want to do.
You should try it while I'm still working.
Have a dream.
Life expectancy of 100 is a long time.
You have 65 years left,
and I have 85 years left.
Goodbye. Please come back.
Hello?
We were on a blind date a few days ago.
I'm Yeongdal, Heo Yeongdal.
It's Heo Yeongdal.
Yes, right.
I had some business to take care of near your office.
I'll be done in an hour, so buy me dinner.
That was your reward.
You brought a new woman again.
You caught me.
You brought other women here?
I'm a regular here,
so every now and then.
Let's eat. It's really good.
Okay.
Most women like fancy restaurants,
but I love these hole in the wall places.
Oh, no! Do you know how much this was?
It was a present.
I'm not vain or materialistic.
Not at all.
I don't care if you're vain, materialistic or even a gold digger,
as long as you're pretty.
I'm working really hard right now.
I'll try to meet the deadline.
Gwangbak!
Go do your homework.
You can't get married if you nag too much.
Wang Daebak!
Sangnam had a blind date and it went well.
Did I ask?
Be honest. Are you interested in him?
- No.
- You like him, don't you?
Wang Daebak!
Don't. You're not pretty.
Wake up. You're so ugly.
You're old and single.
Stop it!
Why are you crying?
You must really like him.
You!
Gwangbak's driving me crazy.
She's taking everything out on me.
It's because she's a spinster.
I know this guy and she has a crush on him.
Who is he?
Should we ask her to give her a chance?
He won't do it.
He likes pretty women.
What can I do in a situation like this?
To make it work, they must see each other often.
He'll grow fond of her if they do.
Can we make them run into each other?
Run into each other?
That was your reward.
Mommy! Mom...
- Oh, boy...
- Sangnam, what's up?
It's nothing, Mr. Park.
You look like you won the lottery.
I'd actually pass out if I won the lottery.
We fixed it but it keeps making noise.
You take a look at it.
Okay.
You bought an apartment?
Sedal and Hobak, congratulations.
You swore you didn't have any money.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
You bought an apartment.
It's all uphill from now on for us.
You bought an apartment, Sedal got a job,
and I'm getting married.
You're getting married?
You were seeing someone?
I was always seeing someone.
I'm popular.
Set some money aside for Yeongdal's wedding.
We're going to set the date soon.
She should pay for her own wedding.
Her older brother should pay for it!
Mom, don't ruin it for us.
We're celebrating us buying an apartment.
You're so weird.
Whose name is the apartment under?
We're co-owners.
She put my name on it, too.
Hobak, how did you decide to do that?
He didn't contribute anything.
Co-owners?
It should be under the man's name.
Sedal should be grateful.
The money's not yours just because you made it.
You were able to save it thanks to Sedal.
I asked around and they all said Sedal was president material.
President?
That's a lie.
He would've become president had he met a woman meant to be the first lady.
I'm sorry he didn't.
It's my fault.
You should be.
This means we must give notice on our place.
Why? Did you buy an apartment, too?
We'll have to come with you.
No. There are only three bedrooms.
Three's enough.
One for you, one for us.
Mother, I'm sorry,
but the reason why I got a loan to buy this apartment was for the boys.
I want them to have their own rooms.
So you're leaving us behind?
Fine! You go off and live on your own!
Hobak, that's mean!
We stuck together through difficulties,
and now you're leaving us behind?
Mother, I'm sorry.
Later...
Later when?
When I'm dead?
You're not even sixty yet,
so living together won't be comfortable.
You shouldn't be that way.
You could at least ask us to come with you!
Well, mother...
Oh, boy...
What do we do?
I'll take care of it.
Sedal! Mom wants you to come over!
Ugh... You look disgustingly happy.
Close your mouth!
It's structurally impossible to close my mouth.
And that's why I drool.
You drool when you see women.
Talk to your wife and take us with you.
She won't listen to me.
You should convince her.
How can you leave your mom and sister here?
Right. And move into a nice apartment.
Sons are useless.
Buying an apartment isn't great at all.
I'll do my best.
Please!
You go and get married!
Parcel service!
Is anyone home?
It's parcel service!
Hello?
Parcel service.
Is anyone home?
Sir! Sir!
Hello? Is this 911?
- Good job.
- Thank you.
He's such a good person.
Father.
It's me, Minjung.
How are you?
I couldn't go see you during the holidays.
I'm sorry, father.
Everyone knows how busy parcel service people get around the holidays.
Is everyone doing okay?
You're not skipping meals, are you?
Don't worry about me.
I'm not working too hard.
I work when I get bored.
The fruits this year aren't very good.
How are Subak and the girls?
They're all good.
Don't work too hard, father.
And take good care of your health.
If anything happens,
call me day or night.
I'll drop by when things settle down.
Goodbye, father.
Parcel service.
Are you Mr. Park Jaesam?
I'll be there in ten minutes.
Okay.
Welcome.
Are you checking in?
This way...
You must be happy.
She asked for you.
Specifically.
It's room service.
Take it up.
Room service.
In here.
What are you looking at?
I'm not looking.
It's okay. You can look.
Bring me a glass.
Yes, ma'am.
Where should I put it?
Over here.
- Excuse me?
- Right here.
Okay.
Why do you always do that when I'm around?
Are you doing this on purpose?
You think I wait for you to do this?
Unlike you, I'm a busy person.
As you can see, I'm a professional.
Ha! Professional my butt!
You lost all your customers to that new beauty salon.
What?
If you were good, you wouldn't lose customers.
What do you know about me?
I had a salon in Myeongdong when I was younger.
You wouldn't know because you were too busy cooking at home.
Anyway, I'm doing much better than you
who is busy raising your grandchildren.
Ha! I can't believe my ears.
I'm better off than you.
Don't get mad.
Anyway, congratulations.
About what?
Your second daughter's set for life.
You should've been nicer to Hobak instead of focusing on Subak.
Let's be honest here.
What have you done for her?
You're Mrs. Vice Principal,
and you let your daughter get married without any dowry.
Did you know that people talked behind your back about that?
I let it go because I'm a nice person.
Who said what? Who?
Which one was it?
Everyone talked about you.
You can go and ask.
Are you on drugs?
You seem determined.
You think I don't have anything to say?
She was carrying a child, and that should've been enough of dowry!
She gave birth to two healthy boys!
But she should've brought dowry.
You should be nicer when she moves this time.
Buy her a fridge or a TV.
I'm letting you know early.
Stop.
What are you talking about?
You don't understand Korean?
Your second daughter.
When she moves to the new apartment, buy her a gift.
Move?
You didn't know?
She bought an apartment across the street,
and they're moving there next week.
You're her mother and you didn't know?
Why are you scared?
Did you commit a crime?
You bought it with the money you earned!
Brag about it.
Go to your mother's and brag about it.
Why are you sorry?
Is what happened to Subak your fault?
Grandmother.
Oh, hi.
Did you bring something?
Have a seat.
What's that?
Buns. They are for you and mom.
You always came empty handed before.
I can't believe you.
I wouldn't get upset over buying a house.
Why would you hide it?
How devious of you!
You bought an apartment?
Yes, grandmother.
Oh, wow.
How did you do that? Where?
The apartment across the street.
Oh, that place is expensive!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hobak bought an apartment. Applaud!
- Oh, my!
- Oh!
Hobak, congratulations!
Wang Hobak, good for you.
Why do you look so sour?
Aren't you happy?
I'm too happy for words because I heard it from her mother in law.
She picked the moving date and bought new furniture,
but didn't say a word.
How could you let me hear it from that beauty salon woman?
I'm sorry, mom.
When Subak saw you walking out from the realtor's office with a contract,
you swore it wasn't true.
Did you think I'd steal it from you?
It wasn't that. I just felt bad.
So you know you should feel bad?
How could you do it at a time like this?
It's about time she bought an apartment.
I agree.
We should congratulate her, not scold her, don't you think?
You stay out of this.
You don't know what you're talking about.
I should've told you first. I'm sorry.
Don't be mad, mom.
I'm sorry.
I brought your favorite buns. Have some.
You eat them all! Crappy buns!
Right? She bought an apartment, right?
She's heartless.
It's like she's rubbing it in.
You really don't have any money?
Of course, I don't!
You don't have a secret stash put away?
What's that?
You've been married for long enough,
and you didn't secretly save any money?
Why would I do that?
That's how you help your mom out.
You didn't save any money behind your husband's back?
I don't have any such thing!
I would've used it if I had.
Why didn't you tell me this before?
I didn't know I could stash money.
And I never needed to do that.
I used what Minjung brought me.
Why would you hit me?
I'm just so frustrated!
You should've prepared for emergency.
I thought you had something.
I had no idea you'd be flat broke.
I can't believe you.
Talking to you is making me madder.
I'm already upset.
Don't add to that.
Give me back everything I gave you!
What?
Oh, boy...
Go inside.
I don't want to see you.
Ugh, I'm so frustrated.
Subak!
Oh, my! It is you!
I didn't think it was you.
So the rumors are true!
Is this your place?
No, I'm just visiting someone.
Don't be like that, Subak.
How could you live in a place like this?
There must be roaches here, right?
What are you doing here?
Oh, I had to collect money near here.
Uh, please keep this a secret.
Don't tell any of our friends.
Please.
Of course. I won't tell anyone.
Nobody would believe me if I told them that you're living in a place like this.
Oh! There you are!
You never answer your door!
Me?
You don't recognize me?
I'm your landlord.
I'm not good with faces.
Whatever!
Why aren't you cleaning the bathroom?
Didn't I tell you we must take turns?
But I don't use that bathroom.
What do you mean you don't use it?
Everyone must use the bathroom.
If you don't, you'll die.
I don't. I'm using a chamber pot.
Oh, you're using a chamber pot?
Oh, my...
Excuse me, she can't do that.
Can you leave her out?
She used to live in a huge apartment.
She was in the Miss Korea pageant.
Stop!
Who hasn't been in the Miss Korea pageant?
I was in it, too.
But I didn't pass the preliminaries.
Oh, she didn't either.
Stop!
You must follow the rules here.
Come with me!
Rub it clean! Clean!
Rub the corners, too!
You don't need to cover your nose!
It all came out from people's bellies.
Over here, rub here, too.
Oh, the people are awful.
Why can't they aim better?
It's parcel service.
I'll get it.
- I'll get it.
- Okay, Daese.
Why did you come so late?
I'm sorry. The traffic was really bad.
Here it is.
I stayed home because you were coming.
And you're two hours late.
This won't happen again.
I'm very sorry. Goodbye.
Let's see.
Uh, Sunjeong.
Come here.
Tada!
What do you think?
Do you like it?
It's pretty.
Here, it's for you.
Me? It's mine?
I bought it off the internet for you.
It's not my birthday...
Thank you, Daese.
I thought this would lift your spirits.
You didn't have to.
What?
I wanted to see the girls.
They went to bed.
Can I see them sleeping?
Why would you do that?
Putting them to bed was hard.
Don't wake them up. Just go.
Seeing them asleep won't change anything.
Aeji must be asking for me.
She's not.
Then please give these to...
Leave them there.
Do you know Subak has depression?
Don't walk around carrying cookies.
Try to make your wife feel better.
Hello, Minjung.
It's been a long time, Daebak.
Share these with Aeji.
Okay.
Aeji said she misses you.
She never said that!
Go to your room and study.
Go.
Good night, then.
So you want to see the girls?
Dad!
Yes, Aeji!
Aeji, I woke you up!
Dad, why didn't you come?
I missed you.
I missed you so much, too.
I will come every day to see you.
You woke her up?
Aeji, come here!
Grandma, I hate you!
I want dad!
What are you doing? Go!
I will.
Good night.
Aeji, I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Dad!
- Dad!
- No!
- No, Aeji.
- Dad!
- No!
I'm home.
We need to talk.
Get up.
What is it? I'm exhausted.
You're not cooking?
What?
Are you buying the rice and side dishes?
What's wrong with that?
They're delicious.
We're not out on a picnic.
How can you buy everything?
We won't save any money this way.
We should buy rice and make it ourselves.
The rice cooker will cook it for you.
How can you buy ready made food?
But I don't know how to do it!
You can try.
I want you to cook dinner for me.
You're always talking about food!
I'm all stressed out, and you're complaining about food?
Who cares what we eat?
Why does it have to be cooked by me?
I'm not saying that.
At this rate, we won't be able to move out of here in 3 years.
You're saying it'll be my fault?
Let's try to save every penny.
Buying ready made food doesn't seem much,
but it's a waste of money.
We must save...
Don't tell me to save money!
You make more!
Why are you picking on me?
I'm already frustrated as I am!
Do you know how I feel?
I'm stuck in this room all day long!
Then go out and do something.
You're stressed out because you stay here.
I don't have any money to go out.
I was in the Miss Korea pageant.
How can I go out without money?
It takes money to go anywhere.
Why do you need money?
You can go to the park,
get fresh air and think about what to do.
What do you mean by that?
Do you want me to get a job?
I'm not saying that.
Be honest with me.
You would like me to make money, don't you?
Just say you want me to go out and get a job!
Fine!
Why can't you go and get a job?
I'd be grateful if you got a job!
That's what you really want, huh?
Now it's my turn to make money?
You're not getting what I'm saying!
A problem shared is a problem halved.
If you are frugal with money,
you'd be helping me out.
Do you want to live like this forever?
How much longer will you leave the kids with your mom?
Bring them right now.
No.
No?
How can I bring them at a time like this?
What do you mean by that?
You can't raise your own children?
We should raise your own children.
How can I raise them here?
There are roaches and mice!
How long will you keep them there?
I don't know!
I don't!
I don't want to hear anything.
Don't you miss the girls?
I don't miss them.
I'm sick of them.
You're sick of them?
You're sick of your own children?
I'm serious.
Bring them tomorrow.
No! I can't take care of them.
It's hard enough for me to stay sane.
What?
I can't take care of them.
I don't want to!
I regret it!
What did you say?
I said I regret it! Why?
Say that again.
What did you say?
I regret marrying you,
and I regret having the kids. Satisfied?
Why did you slap me? Why?
What did I do wrong?
Subtitles by KBS World
Do you still think of me first thing when you wake up?
No, not really.
What? Your wife got this job for you.
You can't fire me! I quit!
Did you?
Did you feel happy when I was struggling?
Get out!
I don't want to see you!
You're horrible!
Where's Subak?
I won't ever forgive her for this!
You won't forgive her?
How dare you say that?
Why do we have to tip toe around Subak and be accommodating to her?
Was Hobak adopted or something?