Subtitles by KBS World
Tada! Look.
Our family treasure.
What's this?
We'll hand this on the wall of our new place
and salute to it every morning and night.
I pledge allegiance to the purchase contract
and to my wife's happiness, for which it stands,
until the day I can no longer move.
Salute!
Don't make that dumb pot our family treasure.
We should make this one it.
Where is it?
What's this?
- What's this?
- You'll wake up the boys.
Sintong! Bangtong!
- Dad's calling you!
- Don't.
They don't care about us.
Let's rely on each other.
My sweet wife.
I'm so happy to see you smile like this.
Oh, this brings back memories.
When I was pregnant with Sintong,
after agonizing about it, I told you, and...
I was amazing.
You disappeared right away.
Bastard.
That bastard disappeared,
my belly was getting bigger and I got scared.
But one day, Heo Sedal just appeared.
And he grabbed me by my wrist
and pushed open my front door, like today.
And he got down on his knees and said,
"Please let us get married!"
"If you want to beat me up, I'll take it."
Oh, you have no idea how amazing you were.
It was always my role to look after you,
but tonight, you were an amazing husband.
You're not upset because of what I did?
I'll deal with that later.
You're crazy about me, right?
Now you're like my baby sister.
I don't look like your wife?
Sadly, we're like family.
What?
Hold on, hold on.
Here, here.
We have to celebrate.
let's have some beer.
No, let's do it at the new apartment.
Let's do it there and here.
I'll pay for this beer.
Put it on my tab.
And expect an exciting night.
You said I'm like family!
It'll be like a daytime soap then.
I'll believe it when I experience it.
Why you!
Sedal, thanks.
There's no need to be so touched.
I think you like to be touched too much.
I'll make sure you're touched to death.
- Sedal!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Let go of me.
Look how I'm sitting.
Hey, hey, hold on a sec.
- Huh?
- Hold on.
Goof-off, you were pretty cool.
Be good to my niece.
Who?
Your uncle.
Loser, your niece is going to die tonight.
What Sedal said was right.
Will Anggeum let him get away with this?
I'm worried about whom she'll take it out on.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo...
Oh, man...
How did it feel to be yelled at by Sedal?
Don't add fuel to the fire.
What did you do to Hobak for Sedal to say that?
What do you mean by that?
I'm never going to see them again.
As if they ever did anything for me.
They never even bought me underwear.
Enough about the underwear.
I'll buy you a truck load, okay?
I keep forgetting to get them.
I'm not saying I need underwear!
I'm just making a point.
They are taking care of themselves without asking for our help.
You should be proud of that.
But Subak took care of herself and us.
You can't ignore that.
So? Are you saying Sedal was right?
What he said was right.
How could you...
Yelling at me like that was right?
How come there's nobody on my side?
You keep that up.
What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
I'm leaving.
What?
Try living without me.
You always say, what? What?
I can't stand that.
Are you deaf?
What?
Oh, no!
She's taking it out on your brother.
What do we do, mom?
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo...
Mom.
Why are you out here?
Father called.
He told me to send you right back home.
He thinks he's so smart.
What's going on?
I don't even want to talk about it.
Sedal was glaring and yelling at me.
Oh my, Sedal?
He was screaming and he said
mother, don't ever bother Hobak again!
Or I'll crush everyone be it you or Subak!
He went crazy like that,
and Hobak came over and dragged him out.
Oh my, he must be crazy.
He did that in front of father?
I couldn't believe my eyes.
His bulging eyes were glaring.
If nobody was there, he would've hit me.
Hobak put him up to it.
She grabbed my hair.
They were both in on it.
Right?
Hobak put him up to it.
Of course!
Sedal wouldn't have the guts to do that.
What did father say?
What do you think?
He sided with Sedal!
Why do you think I'm here?
I'm the villain, I am!
I'm never going home.
What about the girls?
Your father will take care of them.
What can father do?
Grandmother's there and Gwangbak's there.
They can take care of them!
I don't care.
Go there if you want to.
I'm not going home.
Come back right now!
Hear the baby crying?
How could you leave the kids here?
Send Subak here.
Hello?
Hey! Hey!
You...
I'm out with friends.
What's going on, father?
Your mom's gone.
What?
The baby's crying.
What should I do?
Huh?
Bark like a dog?
I can't do it.
Okay.
I can't take this anymore.
What if he loses his voice?
I know.
You do it.
She cries harder when I do it.
This is really crazy.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo...
Oh, oh, no...
Father, I'll do it. Let me.
Man...
I tried, but it didn't work.
You're good.
It has to sound like two dogs fighting.
I'll sleep with her tonight.
Father, you should leave mom alone.
What Sedal said was right,
but mom's having a hard time, too.
There's not a moment of peace in this house.
I'm getting wrinkles.
Don't get wrinkles, father.
Everyone's been really sensitive.
But still.
How could she just leave the kids behind like that?
I'm sure she's worried, too.
If she's not, she's not human.
Oh, this is delicious.
I didn't know they deliver this late.
They deliver 24 hours.
If you're rich, the world is a good place.
That's why everyone wants to become rich.
Your father thinks eating this will kill him.
But it's yummy.
It's more delicious late at night.
I'll get fat.
It's just for tonight.
Really?
I love everything other people cook.
Ugh...
When will I ever get a daughter in law?
I hate cooking every day.
I don't want to wake up in the morning,
because I hate making breakfast.
Everyone asks for food whenever they see me.
As if I'm a rice cooker.
You'll get one.
You have Daebak.
But he's still a little boy!
I'll die before he gets married.
What the heck.
This is my vacation.
Why didn't I think of this before?
He thinks I'll have a hard time!
I hope you have a really hard time at home!
You drink, too.
I love having you over.
I can't believe what Sedal did.
I'm going to get his mother for this.
She should've raised him better.
Ugh, how can I be this unlucky?
Both my son in laws are losers.
What did I ever do to deserve them?
Son in laws are good for nothing.
Mom, you're so funny.
Oh, I feel drunk.
I haven't had a drink in a long time.
And it's been a while since I used a chamber pot.
Mom, you must feel happy.
I'm not.
I feel miserable.
You must be, too,
but I'm so embarrassed.
I'm afraid someone will ask about Minjung.
I can't tell them he went bankrupt.
It's driving me crazy, too.
I'm afraid of him running into someone we know.
What if my friend recognizes him?
I don't know how long I can take this, mom.
I can't live with him.
I don't even want to see his face.
Or hear his voice.
He looks ugly now that he can't make money.
That's how everyone feels.
He must do well to appear handsome.
Who is it?
Subak, it's me. Open the door.
Huh?
- What time is it?
- Oh.
It's not even morning yet.
Why are you here?
I came to fetch you.
Jungji cried all night, so father and I didn't sleep at all.
You had a party here.
I don't believe this.
It's heaven here.
Let's go, mom.
Am I crazy?
I'm not going back to that hell.
What about breakfast?
Grandma will get mad.
There it is again!
Is everyone going to starve without me?
See? Without me, they'll starve to death.
You make breakfast.
Mom's stressed out.
I don't know how to cook.
Father's really angry.
Let him be.
I'm not scared of him.
I'm not coming home unless he changes.
He keeps going, what? What?
He has no respect for his wife.
And that's why our son in laws disrespect me.
I hate you too.
Go home.
You guys try living without me!
Mom.
Hey! Minjung!
Minjung!
Where are the socks?
Hey! Hey!
Darn it.
Father, what is it?
I can't find my socks.
Oh...
Here.
I tried, but I couldn't find them.
It's tough without mom, huh?
Not at all.
She shouldn't dare come home.
Just give her a call and say you're sorry.
Did she ask me to call her?
No, she didn't say that.
Tell her to live there permanently.
She didn't seem to miss home.
She ordered fried chicken, alcohol and pig feet last night.
She's having a lot of fun.
Stupid sock!
What's wrong?
It's inside out.
Can you make me an egg...
Let's eat.
Mother.
It isn't much, but try it.
There's nothing to try.
I know.
Oh...
I don't believe this.
What will your children learn?
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo...
What?
I got fired.
What did you just say?
You want me to repeat?
I got fired.
Since I came clean, don't be too harsh.
How about a 3 day probation?
You...
Hey!
- Stay still!
- Hey! Heo Sedal!
Come back here!
How dare you!
Would you, if you were me?
Are you trying to drive me mad?
Stop embarrassing yourself and come inside!
Hello!
You're taking out the garbage?
Why would you quit that amazing job?
I should have known!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Hobak, Hobak!
Hey, Madam Park Salla!
You haven't gone to work?
Not before I yell at you!
Come inside!
Nice going.
He might be younger, but he's your husband.
How could you kick him out in his underwear?
I had a good reason.
Is Sedal having an affair?
He can't because he has no money.
Then what did he do to deserve that?
It's embarrassing.
I'm not embarrassed.
I have a great body. Look.
Oh, oh, oh!
Are you okay?
I have great reflexes.
You think you can do this?
Ask him what he did.
Stay out of it, mom.
Don't abuse my son!
He's going to become the president of Korea!
I was never going to see you,
but I just couldn't let it slide.
What are you two doing?
I heard what happened last night.
Learn to control your husband.
How dare he?
If I were there, I would've kicked his butt.
A son in law yelling at his mother in law?
Who does that?
Did you put him to it?
Subak.
You think I'm a nobody now that I'm poor,
but I'm still standing.
I'm still the eldest daughter.
I'm telling you, if he or you make one wrong move, I'll kill you both.
Just who does Sedal think he is?
Tell Sedal to come and apologize to mom.
Understand?
Yeah.
Even if Sedal went wild,
you should've stopped him.
You're older than him.
Get up.
Go apologize to mom.
She's at my place.
At your place?
She had a fight with father.
Look what you did to our family.
Don't mess things up again.
I asked to see you today because...
I know, Mr. Wang.
Don't call me that.
Force of habit.
You used to be my teacher.
What do you think about last night?
Excuse me?
You feel sorry about it, don't you?
I'm sorry,
but I don't think what I did was wrong.
The problem is not what but how you said it.
You were at your in laws house.
Yelling and screaming there was okay?
I'm sorry about that part.
But Don's sister in law was mean, too.
I actually thought Hobak was adopted.
Stop calling her Don's sister in law.
I've been calling her that since forever...
I won't do that again.
I'm actually relieved because now I know how you feel about Hobak.
You've always been so immature.
She's my wife.
Shall we order some beer, Mr. Wang?
I have to go back to school after lunch.
Be kind to Hobak.
After being married for 10 years,
you don't live on sparks.
You live on compassion for each other.
I'm relieved now that you're growing up.
I'm not the growing up type,
but I'll work hard on it.
Apologize to my wife in a few days.
Yes, Mr. Wang.
I mean, father.
Mom, Hobak's here.
Mom,
I'm sorry about last night.
Sedal was drunk.
He said he was sorry this morning.
Why doesn't he just kill me?
He has no respect for his mother in law.
Put yourself in my shoes.
This is wrong.
Have you forgotten our family motto?
This will never happen again.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I know you were in on it.
In on what?
That didn't come from Sedal's head.
You were behind it.
That's not true.
I didn't know about it.
Anyway, mom, don't be so mad.
And Hobak, I'm sorry.
Daebak, don't worry.
She's probably went to the sauna.
No, she didn't.
She went to Subak's place.
That's strange.
I heard women go to the sauna after a fight.
Your mom is extremely unique.
Everything's a mess at home.
Do you know how to cook?
I can make spicy rice cake.
You want some?
It's okay.
How do I bring mom home?
Your father will take care of it.
A couple must work on their issues together because meddling can escalate things.
- Understand?
- Yes.
- Should I go get her number?
- Stop that.
- Yes.
Why did you do that?
I should've asked Hobak to clean it.
I can't stay longer because of the bathroom.
Little girl!
- Me?
- Can you help me?
Do you know where this is?
Oh, over there.
It's on the 3rd floor.
The sign is hard to see.
Oh.
I don't give directions, but since you look kind, I made an exception.
Huh?
Mom told me to watch out for strangers.
Right. You should.
Watch out for kind looking people too.
Mom told me that too.
Smart girl! You must get good grades.
I do pretty well.
I'm sure you're a top student.
I've heard that before.
They say I should become a lawyer,
but I'm going to be a good wife.
Thanks, little girl.
Aeji!
Dad!
- Dad!
- Oh!
Aeji, did you miss me?
Yes.
How much?
Lots and lots.
Dad missed Aeji lots and lots too.
I want to live with you, dad.
Dad, why won't you come visit me?
Sorry.
Let's go to grandfather's house later.
Okay.
Mom, mom.
I gave directions to a man earlier.
I told you not to talk to strangers.
He was nice, a parcel service man.
He told me I look like a smart girl.
A parcel service man?
What did he look like?
Like other men his age.
What did he say?
She's comfortable with her lifestyle.
What if Sangnam gets married?
Right now, Sangnam's living with you,
but when he moves out, people will talk.
You're her brother in law.
And you won't be able to remarry.
But I can't force her to get married.
She hasn't gotten over her first love.
He must have a family of his own.
Probably.
I'm sure he's forgotten all about her.
She can't seem to get over it.
I think she feels guilty.
When I think about that,
I can't bring myself to forgive that woman.
You should tell your mom to go home,
not let her stay here!
You should've dragged her home.
Why are you yelling at her?
It was my choice.
Get up.
No.
I'm not scared.
Help your mom get up.
Why don't you make me get up?
You get up on your own then.
I'm too weak to get up.
You're strong enough to yell at me.
Help her get up, hurry.
Father coming here means he's surrendering.
I'm not really surrendering.
He's not really surrendering.
Hurry! He'll get mad at me.
Go home.
I'm going because of the darn bathroom.
Hurry up and come inside!
Silly old woman.
How can you be so childish?
How could you run away to Subak's place?
They only have one room!
Minjung didn't come home.
I didn't even see him.
He doesn't come home?
He didn't, when I was there.
I talked to him, but it didn't work.
I told him you said so, and that did no good.
What's the problem with our son in laws?
They have no respect for any of us.
Are they plotting against us?
Plotting against us?
Are you mad?
This is all your fault.
You always scold me and that's why.
What?
There you go again with "what."
Why did I come back to this hell?
You won't earn any points that way.
Go and beg.
What's more important?
My pride or money?
Money.
Give me a harder question.
I shouldn't have asked.
Just hear me out.
The manager was really getting on my nerves.
Nobody has any respect for me.
He said you got me the job.
He's correct.
Speaking of the devil.
Is it the manager?
Hey, hurry up and answer it.
I don't want to.
Come on!
Hello?
Why did you call?
This late?
I have to go to bed.
Fine.
Did he ask you to come in?
He said to come quick.
He did?
Is he giving you your job back?
No way.
Then why would he be calling you this late?
How did he sound?
I don't care about that.
He said he'll pay for the cab.
Hurry up and go then.
Don't get your hopes up.
You can't go to a hotel wearing that.
Drive.
Excuse me?
You know how to drive, right?
Yes, I was a driver in the army.
I was under the commander.
Now you're under me.
She's in our board of directors.
Director Eun Miran.
Do whatever she tells you to do, got it?
Oh!
Wow, this is so cool.
I'm sorry.
Don't get scared.
Pretend this is your car.
This is my car. This is my car.
Step on it.
We'll get a speeding ticket.
Don't worry about it.
Seriously?
Ma'am, may I scream?
Go ahead.
Yay!
This is nutty, nutty, nuts!
- Tada!
- Whoa!
Isn't this perfect as a late night snack?
Did you make it?
This is my specialty.
Oh, it's amazing. Try it.
This tastes better than I remember.
What is it?
It brings back memories.
How hard it was when you were growing up.
We've been through a lot.
It wasn't hard for me.
It was hard for you, though.
When you cried, I cried,
and when I cried you cried.
She was in and out when you were a baby,
and when you were in the third grade,
she left for good.
Though she wasn't good to you,
you cried everyday for her.
And I'd make you these noodles,
and you'd stop crying.
To make you fall asleep,
I used to put you in the driver's seat of my truck and drive around the neighborhood.
That was the only method that worked.
I was a really nasty kid.
No, you were an amazing kid.
And now you're a good man.
Why didn't you wake me up?
I just nodded off.
No, this is actually fun.
I'm good at this.
Would you like a taste?
It's okay.
I'll clean up. Go to bed.
Just leave them in the sink.
Good night, Daese.
Good night.
I hope she meets someone nice.
Right, father?
Yes, but I don't know what she wants.
Call your wife.
Tell her you won't come home for 3 days.
Excuse me?
I can't. We're moving tomorrow.
Don't worry, Ms. Director.
She can handle the move by herself.
It's me.
So? Did you get your job back?
Of course!
Really? That's great!
I'm out of Seoul with the director.
I don't think I can come home tonight.
It's okay. I'll take care of the move.
You're with the director?
- Yes.
- Hurry up and hang up.
It's okay. We can talk.
No! Remember how you got that job?
Just work really hard from now on, okay?
Even if you have to beg, don't get fired.
But I won't be home for about three days.
It's okay. Don't come home!
Even three months is okay, too.
Don't call and suck up to the director.
That's what I'm doing.
Don't pretend you're working hard.
Just do as you're told.
If he tells you to lick, lick.
What?
Lick his feet if you have to, I mean.
Keeping a job isn't easy!
Fine. How about tomorrow?
What about tomorrow?
Aren't we moving tomorrow?
As if you ever helped before.
What I want most is for you to make money.
So don't lose this job, okay?
Bye.
Hello? Hell...
It's always money, money.
Wow...
Man...
Hobak!
Scrooge. How can we move by ourselves?
There isn't much.
You have to pay me.
I'll buy you black bean noodles.
Plus sweet and sour pork.
Where's goof-off?
He's on a three day business trip.
How long is he going to keep that job?
Traitor.
Don't be like that.
You're single but he has a family.
He has to make money.
Ugh! Stop arguing and start working!
Be careful.
Oh!
Out of my way!
Be careful.
- Hey, hey!
- Ugh, uncle!
- Careful, careful.
- Where is this going?
- This way, this way.
- Uncle, a step!
Be careful!
No! This was expensive.
- Why aren't you lifting?
- Ugh, uncle!
Try this on.
Me?
Oh...
What are you doing?
That has wheels.
They are all yours.
Excuse me?
I hate monotony.
Change your suits often.
Do it for me.
She's coming.
- Hi! It's been so long.
- Hello.
I'm the last one.
I took a cab because my car's being fixed.
I had a little accident coming out of the department store last week.
They offered a rental car but I said no.
Let's order.
What would you like?
Should we have a big lunch?
Let's keep it simple.
Why?
Uh...
This looks good.
It's a lunch course.
Let's order something cheap.
Your husband must be having a hard time as a delivery man.
I heard you moved into a basement efficiency.
You should save money when you can.
I didn't tell them.
They already knew.
It's all over town.
Be honest.
What is?
Secrets don't exist.
I heard you lost your house, car, your handbags and clothes.
All you have left is that handbag.
I heard they let you have it out of pity.
Isn't this a small world?
My relative was the collection agent.
No way.
Why would people say that?
Why would people make up stuff?
Sometimes they do.
Order whatever you like. My treat.
We can't let you treat us.
And let's pick a new manager.
What do you mean?
I still have 4 more months.
Your hands must be full with the girls.
You can't take care of the money.
Right.
You think I'm going to dip into our account?
It's not that.
To be honest, I couldn't be sure.
If there's money, I'd use it.
Even if it's someone else's money.
Hand over the money and the book.
It's better to be safe than sorry.
Hey!
I can't believe what you just said!
Who here hasn't benefited from me?
You'd all run over whenever I called and tried to kiss up.
And now look at you!
I'll spend the membership fees? Me?
I was in the Miss Korea pageant!
You were all my minions before.
How dare you?
You think I'd take your money?
Crazy.
I can't believe I thought of you as friends.
Here!
Take them!
You disloyal bitches.
[Apartment Purchase Contract]
There, there.
No, a little to the right.
Oh, does this have to go here?
It's beautiful.
Beautiful my butt.
My arms are killing me.
Hurry up.
There, there!
A little lower.
Like this? Good?
Okay.
Don't move. Let me mark it.
How's Hobak's move going?
I'm sure they're doing fine.
You didn't go?
Where are you?
Uncle and Gwangbak went.
My back hurts so I can't move anything.
You should've gone.
I can't go because of a meeting.
You should drop by later.
She's having a house warming party tonight.
I'll deal with it so don't be concerned.
As if you ever paid any attention to us.
Hang up. It's time for my medicine.
Oh, boy.
I think you're the only one who has the purchase contract framed and hung.
Doesn't it look like an artwork?
And the handwriting is pretty.
The realtor has beautiful penmanship.
I don't believe this.
I think we're done.
Let's eat something.
I'm starving.
What should we order?
Hold on. I have to see who to order for.
Mother, when are you coming?
I'm ordering Chinese food.
Please come and bring Yeongdal.
Yeongdal has a date?
With that man she met before?
Okay.
She can't come and Yeongdal has a date.
So it's the three of us, Sintong, Bangtong, grandmother, mom, Hobak.
Father's at the Office of Education.
Haebak's at school, Daebak's at the academy.
That means eight people.
Hobak, take me off the list.
Why?
I have plans.
I just remembered.
You should eat!
You did all that work.
It's okay. I have to get going.
Oh, but you worked so hard.
Then come visit another time.
Okay.
- Uncle, I'm leaving.
- Yes, I will.
Hey, I have to go to work.
But I'm starving.
Oh, no! I'm so sorry.
I'll come another day.
- Bye.
- Oh, boy.
Thank you.
- Bye, Hobak.
- Bye.
You're really going to be a dating expert!
Sangnam, I have a problem.
What is it?
I'm teaching someone and it's so hard.
The sixth grader?
She's 29 years old.
Huh?
A 29 year old woman is learning from you?
She's never really dated anyone before.
She always got dumped.
I'm trying to teach her how it's done.
Oh, boy.
I feel bad for her, whoever she is,
but I'm sure you'll do a great job.
I'll see you later.
Where are you going?
I have a date.
Be careful of gold diggers!
Yeongdal has a date?
With that man she met before?
You're going home?
Daebak's not home, so I'm leaving.
Goodbye, Gwangbak.
Uh, Miho, wait.
What's the problem?
She says a powerful rival appeared.
Is she pretty?
She has had a lot of work done.
She's not naturally pretty.
It doesn't matter if she's had work done because men love pretty women.
I know.
You know how cool men who can park well are?
You wouldn't know.
I know about the men who can park well.
Women just love them.
Especially when they back up real fast with only one hand on the wheel.
Oh, you could write a book.
They already have those books.
Why haven't you read them?
I know.
I read useless books and became a teacher.
Dating is hard.
I can't control my heart,
so how can you control another's heart?
World domination would be easier.
Dating is a game where the one who loves more loses.
I think so, too.
To beat the rival,
you must get to the next stage.
Physical contact.
Physical contact?
Kissing.
I kiss him first?
No, your friend.
Oh, right. It's not me.
Tell my friend to kiss him first?
No, men don't like forward women.
You must make him want to kiss you.
How?
The scary part is over.
Oh...
If you can't watch scary movies,
why did you pick this?
It's exciting.
It feels like I'm losing weight.
I like your perfume.
It's my shampoo.
She has a date.
It must be going well with that man from the blind date.
Ugh!
Ouch! Ouch...
Stop doing stuff like that.
Hey! Where were you?
My bat's been crying out your name!
As if I'm not mad enough already.
What are you doing this weekend?
I have a business trip to China.
Is it a long trip?
About 3 days?
You want a present, don't you?
Wrong.
But I won't refuse it if you bring me one.
Can I tell you what I want?
Sure.
Huh? Me?
Yes.
Come back safely.
That'll be the best present.
Let's hurry up.
I have a curfew.
You have a curfew?
How old are you?
My mom is really strict because she had to raise me on her own.
She said a woman must be very careful.
It used to be 9 but now its 10 pm.
And on special occasions it's midnight.
And tonight's a special occasion?
Yes.
Ugh! That hit the spot.
Trying to act demure was hard, mom.
Did he fall for you?
I told you.
Nobody can escape from me.
He'll fall for me hard.
Oh, I feel bad for him.
Yeongdal, how do you do it?
Teach me how you do it.
But what would you do with that?
Everything you learn will come in handy someday, except for how to rob a house.
I'm just saying.
Listen carefully.
You must use different techniques.
Men in their 20s fall for your looks.
Men in their 30s fall for your money.
Men look at women's money?
Then again, it's a difficult time.
Both women and men are money crazy.
With him, I can't be money crazy.
I must pretend to be humble and naive.
It's my dream to become a good wife.
And that works?
Oh, well, a rich man wouldn't need to make his wife work.
I'm answering my own question.
Oh, I can't drink.
It's my first time.
I have a curfew, so I must go home.
My mom is very strict.
This is what I do.
You got awful grades at school,
but you're really good at things like this.
It's because you took after me.
Oh, he's going on a business trip.
Did you ask him to bring a present?
That's what the dumb girls do.
I'm different.
Have a safe trip.
That'll be the best present.
Oh, you're crafty.
Dumb girls get greedy about little things and end up losing what's important.
You have to look ahead.
Way ahead.
Way into the future so I can milk him.
Oh, you're such a smart girl!
Why do you think I dated all those men?
I learned how to pick the best man.
Experience is knowledge.
Just wait, mom.
He'll buy me a luxury brand handbag and propose to me in a month.
Please make that happen.
Don't be sad about not moving with Sedal.
I'll make sure we live in a great big house.
Just hearing that makes me happy.
Find a good husband.
I'm going to crush Anggeum.
Though she's halfway there already.
Oh...
Mom, can't we eat first?
Hold on.
Grandmother, great grandmother and aunt are coming.
Oh... This is torture.
Slow down.
You'll get a stomachache.
Mom, it's good even when it's soggy.
Mom, you eat too.
I'll eat later with your grandmother.
Mom, can I have just one piece of pork?
You shouldn't touch it before the adults eat.
Just one!
We should be grateful about the noodles.
This is nuts.
The only time I ate out was when I had black bean noodles on my painful anniversary.
Painful anniversary?
Yes.
Painful days come right after your wedding.
Only those who've done it can understand.
My wife would go nuts if she came here.
This is like straight out of a movie.
I'm the male star and you are...
Enough.
- Let's drink.
- Okay.
Sintong!
Bangtong!
Sintong, wake up. Wake up.
Bangtong, have some sweet and sour pork.
Get up and eat sweet and sour pork.
Eat. You said you wanted it. Eat.
It doesn't taste good.
Why didn't you give it to us before?
Mom, I'm full.
I'm sleepy.
Go to bed.
Wow...
Dad, I told you to leave me alone.
What am I supposed to do with a man who hasn't called me since I came back?
It's over between us!
Subtitles by KBS World
What are you doing here?
To say goodbye?
I've been waiting here for an hour.
Incredible. I'm touched.
Please come with us.
Check what?
Oh, that woman must be crazy.
Do you know her?
No way.
Say you're sorry about treating me differently!
How could you say that?
That's what I get for raising you?
Come out.
Why can't you see how I feel? Why?