Subtitles by KBS World
Where's your aunt?
I don't know.
She won't answer her phone.
Where did she go?
You raised your daughter really well.
We all welcome her into our family.
I liked her the moment I saw her.
This must be meant to be.
It was the same for us, too.
Sangnam is not like other young men.
I love how honest and hard working he is.
And he's so handsome, he could be an actor.
We want the wedding to be as soon as possible.
What do you think?
Since they like each other,
let's do it before the year is over.
Okay. Shall we order some food?
Okay.
Aunt.
Where were you?
I'm sorry.
Daese, I'm sorry.
Sangnam, can you come out?
She passed out?
Yes.
She didn't just pass out. It's serious.
I called 911,
and I took her to the emergency room.
My heart is still pounding.
I was so scared.
Are you sure you can go through with this?
Sangnam.
Let's go in, aunt.
She won't die.
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
Something urgent came up.
Okay. Sit down.
She's my sister in law.
Hello.
Think of her like Sangnam's mom.
We need to run more tests,
but it looks like anemia and malnutrition.
Malnutrition?
Yes.
She hasn't eaten or slept, father.
What if she dies?
It's because of him.
I know.
She worked at a cafe, trying to forget him.
She worked at a cafe?
Yes.
She hurt her arm and couldn't eat.
And she was working on top of that!
What did the doctor say?
They need to run more tests,
but it's malnutrition.
Malnutrition?
She hasn't eaten or slept.
How dare she!
Why didn't she tell us?
Oh!
The second floor is spacious,
but if you want, we can renovate it,
so Jihwa can feel comfortable.
I'm never going upstairs,
and I'm never going to bother her.
Sunjeong, you know how I am, right?
I would never bother Jihwa, right?
You wouldn't.
So when should the wedding be?
Let's set the date right here.
Okay.
How about on Christmas?
On Christmas?
That would be meaningful.
Sangnam, what do you think?
How about on Christmas? Good?
Aunt.
Yes?
Where is it?
Daehan Hospital.
Aunt,
please take care of this for me.
Father, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Please excuse me.
Sangnam!
Where were you?
Gwangbak is dying.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
You came!
How could you be so heartless?
She's dying!
What took you so long?
She's dying here.
What if she really dies?
She was thin to being with,
and look at her now.
She's skin and bones.
It's malnutrition. She hasn't eaten!
Who gets malnutrition these days?
Imagine how heartbroken she has been.
I'm sorry.
Gwangbak.
Oh, Gwangbak, it's mom!
Wake up. It's mom.
Oh, I know you're tired.
Can you see me?
I thought you were going to die.
I can't believe my eyes.
Mom.
Yes, mom is here.
There's someone she wants to see here.
Okay. I'll see you later.
Don't get up.
How did you know?
Why didn't you tell me, you fool.
Nothing's more important than your life.
Why would you stop eating?
Love isn't worth it.
It's for the birds.
I couldn't find any birds...
Aren't you meeting her parents?
I told them to wait.
You're awake, so I should get back.
I ran here because I didn't want to be blamed for your death.
Should I go back?
You're mean.
You're my sucker.
My precious sucker.
What is this?
You're too thin for me to hold you.
I'm afraid you'll break.
Why didn't you do as I say?
You're a bad girl.
I told you to eat well, but look at you.
How should I punish you?
Even if your family doesn't accept me,
I won't let you go.
If they beat me up, I'll take it.
If they yell at me, I'll listen.
I'm not letting you go.
That's why I came.
Don't let me go.
We're done here.
Is the barbecue ready?
I want to eat the moment they get here.
Mom!
Sedal! My Sedal!
Mom, where's the kimchi?
You like kimchi more than your mom?
I brought it.
Mom, don't you see me?
No.
I just need mom and kimchi.
Why did you come?
I can't believe you said that.
Mom, make me some kimchi stew.
I've been dying for your kimchi stew.
Oh, you live here?
Mom, look. This is amazing.
Oh, my...
This is incredible.
Mmm...
Yummy.
This is nuts.
Make me everything you can with kimchi.
Make stew, stir fry, steamed, what else?
Kimchi fried rice.
I'm making them all.
I missed kimchi so much.
Wow, how can you live without kimchi?
I never knew kimchi was so good.
But you didn't like it before.
Be honest with me.
Are you having an affair with the director?
An affair?
That's degrading.
You can't put a name on this.
It's a peculiar relationship.
Maybe soul mates?
What are you talking about?
Do, re, mi...
This is nutty, nutty, nuts!
I'm so happy.
Mom, cheers!
Cheers!
I can't believe my luck!
Look where I am, thanks to my son.
My life is pretty great.
I know.
Servants!
I'm having friends over...
I mean, I'm having a party, so get ready.
Make barbecue, some noodles and pancakes.
And get some sirloin.
Get the best kind.
The kind with something plus...
Get them.
Today's menu has been decided, madam.
For entrée, caviar and foie gras,
the main dishes are sautéed lamb and bass meunière.
For dessert, we have crème brûlée and macarons.
Oh, okay. That sounds fine.
Did you make my beauty salon appointment?
At the Park Salla Beauty Salon.
I made an appointment at the beauty salon
for the stars in Cheongdamdong, madam.
Oh, you did?
Right. I should go there.
And I don't like you calling me madam.
I never owned a bar.
These aren't new bags!
I'm sick and tired of them.
I never carry the same bag twice!
Call Paris.
Have them air deliver their newest bags.
Now!
They are on the plane over right now.
Oh, how amazing!
Just thinking about it is nutty nutty nuts!
You too?
Oh, man.
Huh? What's going on?
Why is she back so early?
Who are they?
Huh? Oh.
Say hello. My mom and my sister.
I don't want to meet anyone.
What's that smell?
Did someone bring kimchi?
Oh, how annoying!
Uh, hey...
What? She doesn't want to meet anyone?
We should be meeting her!
How can she be so rude?
Mom, destroy her when she marries Sedal.
Mom, you should go.
People who lived in America for a long time
hate it when people show up uninvited.
I'll invite you formally next time.
Baby.
What's wrong with you?
How could you tell outside people to come here without my permission?
This place is here for my privacy.
You need my permission to invite people.
She's not outside people.
She's my mom.
She's your mom, not mine.
Why did you call them over?
I haven't seen her in a while,
and I missed kimchi.
This won't ever happen again.
Forget it. I want to be alone.
The person you have called is unavailable...
How dare he...
How can he do this to me?
Sunjeong! Ice water!
I got it.
Here, Daese.
How could you do this to me? Huh?
What did you two do?
You made me look like a fool!
Because of me,
you must have been hurt.
When I think about it,
I'm not a good enough person.
I'm a teacher,
but I'm so narrow minded.
But because it was my daughter,
my view of things became very narrow.
I used to tell other teachers and students
that education level wasn't important,
but I'm very embarrassed to say that
I had a prejudice against you.
I understand.
Any parent would've reacted the same way.
I don't believe a degree is just a piece of
paper or that it's not worth anything.
It shows a side of one's character.
It shows how the person lived,
and if he went to a good college,
it means he was smart
and that he was a good student.
I have an accountant and a lawyer
who work for my company,
and it takes a lot of work to become that.
hey worked really hard to get there.
So I think education is important.
Are you saying you understand where I was coming from?
My daughter's far from perfect.
I think you're a better person than her.
You have
my blessings.
Father.
Thank you.
Thank you so much!
Why don't we
just make it happen as soon as possible?
Okay, father!
I won't ever hurt  Gwangbak again.
Thank you.
Daese!
Sangnam, are you hurt?
Let me see.
Get out!
Look at the blood!
You're not my son!
How dare you leave in the middle of dinner?
Did that rude girl call you?
Father, I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
You're sorry now?
You know how you humiliated me?
I've never been so humiliated in my life!
And I'm going to lose my business!
It was credibility that brought me here.
Because of you, I'll lose it all!
Get out!
Father, I'm sorry.
But...
I can't get married like this.
I want to marry someone I really love.
What?
Have you lost your mind?
I ought to...
Daese, don't do this.
Sunjeong, step aside.
Sangnam, run!
I said step aside!
Aunt, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Please don't do this, father.
This won't change my mind.
You're not my son!
Get out!
I will!
What?
If you want me gone, I will leave.
I'm not changing my mind.
Sangnam!
This is wrong.
How can you leave like this?
Aunt,
I'm pushed against the wall.
If I don't do this, I can't win.
Aunt, they gave me their blessings.
- They did?
- Yes.
So I need him to accept Gwangbak,
but it won't happen like this.
I'm leaving.
Where are you going?
Divorce!
Meet me at the courthouse tomorrow at noon,
before I go nuts.
How could you do that?
You said you'd work with us, but
not you're working with Daejin?
What happened to our agreement?
Hello? Hello...
I don't believe this!
Nothing's getting done.
Mr. Kim and Mr. Park didn't come to work!
What?
They stayed with us because of Sangnam,
and without them, it's a mess out there.
And Sangnam won't answer my calls.
Man.
You can't beat your son.
You're too weak for that.
Call Sangnam in.
What about the dinner the other night?
You should go and apologize to them.
People get divorced all the time,
and some people break up at the wedding.
It's not like they were engaged.
You're lucky it ended there.
I never lived like that, so I can't!
That dinner was a form of promise.
How can I break it so easily?
Look,
I never paid my employees late,
and I never fell behind on payments.
Even if it means financial damage for me,
I've always kept the promises I made.
But this is different from that.
That's your life and your business,
but this is your son's marriage.
How can he marry someone he doesn't love to keep your promise?
Let Sangnam marry whoever he wants.
She's going to be his wife, not yours!
I want you to stay out of this!
Sangnam, your father's furious.
Please hold on for a few more days.
I took care of Daejin.
And I'm working on Mr. Kim and Mr. Park.
Sunjeong,
where's Sangnam? I know you know.
I don't know.
You don't know?
No.
If something happens to my company,
I'm kicking you out.
Sangnam, your father's furious.
I'm not afraid of getting kicked out,
but what if you can never make up?
Why is getting married so hard for you?
Aunt, I'm sorry.
Just tell him you don't know anything.
And don't worry about me.
I'm eating well and sleeping well.
Just hold on for a few more days, aunt.
Gwangbak, mom wants you downstairs.
What's all this, mom?
It's for you.
Sit down and eat.
Why did you make so much food?
Oh, how can you have malnutrition?
In the old days many people got malnutrition,
but who gets that these days?
If you couldn't handle it anymore,
you should've talked to me about it.
Mom, thanks.
Take your time.
Your life is more important than love.
It's good, mom.
Eat all day, if you want.
Oh, you're skin and bones. Here.
My, sucker, I have homework for you.
Eat a lot and get chubby.
I don't want my bride to be boney. Kisses.
What smells so good?
Grandmother,
I'm eating pork belly, so I can get fat.
Girl, don't make your father all worried.
When you end up in the hospital,
it breaks your parents hearts.
The Korean War was nothing compared to it.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo.
I won't, grandmother. Have some.
I can't chew very well.
You're feasting now, aren't you?
I'm sorry for making father worry, grandma!
What's wrong?
It's my stomach.
It's because you haven't eaten for so long.
Chew thoroughly.
Who is it?
I don't know this number.
- Who is it?
- Maybe it's the magazine.
- Hel...
- I'm Sangnam's father.
- Fath...
How are you, father?
You know I'm not doing well.
I need to see you.
Okay, father. I'll see you there.
That was his father?
Yes, he wants to see me.
Your father in law to be called you?
When you haven't even met him?
I know.
Maybe he heard I was sick.
You should've said no.
You're not well.
How can I? He's Sangnam's father.
They are lucky.
I said yes because I thought you would die.
Just think about it.
You're so much better.
But you should wear something nice.
Oh, no!
Man.
Man...
I'm sorry I'm late.
Don't you have a watch?
How can you be 30 minutes late?
I'm sorry.
I left early,
but I got splashed by a car,
so I had to go home and change...
Stop. Sit down.
Okay.
You know why I asked to see you?
I'm so sorry.
I know I behaved really badly...
I don't want to hear you calling me father.
So don't.
Then I'll call you sir.
I don't like that either.
Then what should I...
Call me president.
I will.
President, I know things have been really
bad between us, and I want to erase it out.
I wish I could go back and cut it all out.
I'm so sorry.
I know I was really rude.
You know?
Yes.
But you were so weird to me back then...
And you asked for money, so I thought...
I'm so sorry, president.
You're apologizing because of Sangnam.
Otherwise, you wouldn't!
No!
Looking back, I was really ill mannered and really rude.
But I was like that only when I met you.
I think it's because we were supposed to meet.
I'm serious. Please believe me.
I'm sorry.
I really am not that girl.
Things between us went so awry,
and I don't know how to handle it.
That's why we weren't supposed to meet.
Things are complex because of that.
Why are you forcing yourself on my son?
Stop chasing after my son.
I didn't.
Stop talking back.
Okay.
You made him run out on us at dinner!
That alone shows me how rude you are!
How could you call him at a time like that?
Where is Sangnam?
Excuse me?
You must know where Sangnam is.
I don't understand...
You don't know?
He left the house after a fight.
He did?
Yes,
I think he was calling her.
Okay, aunt.
Sangnam has never gone against my wishes.
He never talked back to me.
But he changed after meeting you.
I know what's going to happen to you.
So I'm begging you.
He broke up with you and met another woman, so you should let him go.
Why would you hold on to him?
I'm sorry.
Think of this as a way of paying your dues
for acting so rude to me all this time and set Sangnam free.
Sangnam only knows how to more forward.
And he'll never get married without my
blessings, so don't get your hopes up.
He would've, if he really wanted to.
You're still young,
so you should make a U-turn.
You don't understand what I mean, don't you?
Why wouldn't you pick up the phone?
Sangnam.
I was worried to death.
You should at least answer your phone.
I was meeting someone. I put it on mute.
I heard you met my father.
How did you know?
You left your house?
Why would you do that?
That's not important.
What did he say?
You don't have to tell me.
Whatever he said, don't worry about it.
You only need to listen to me.
But...
He's not going to be your husband.
Never listen to anyone else.
Just listen to me.
And keep your eyes on me.
Do that, for the rest of your life.
But you shouldn't have left the house.
Why did you do that?
You've made him so mad.
This is the only way to solve this.
Where are you staying?
Are you eating okay?
Don't worry about it.
You know me.
I always eat on schedule.
Are you doing your homework?
Yes.
Let me see.
You haven't been doing it!
I should spank you!
This won't do.
Let's go and gain weight.
Why did you order so much?
Eat up.
I told you.
I don't want a boney bride.
What would you like to eat?
This? This?
I'll just put everything together.
I'm never going to let you go.
No matter how hard your father is on me,
I'll stick with you to the end.
I can take any heartache or difficulties.
I won't let another woman have such a good man.
You shouldn't reveal all of your feelings like that.
It's like going to war without any weapons.
A woman should know how to hide things.
Don't show so much love.
You don't like it?
I love it.
Can I ask you something?
Were you really going to marry that woman?
I thought
I could handle being married to her.
I was going to keep you in my heart
and go live with someone else.
But I don't like that.
Missing someone for the rest of your life.
If you're in love, you should be with him,
sleep in the same bed and have children.
Let's eat.
We need to have children.
Ah!
Ah.
Come right now.
I'm shivering in front of the court house.
Ugh!
Don't you know what time it is?
You think avoiding me will make this go away?
You're actually pushing me away.
I can be stubborn, too.
You'll have to sign the form!
I'm not changing my mind.
I'll be back.
See you later, manager.
Attacking?
Yes.
Let's say I ran into a mugger.
Teach me how to attack and subdue him.
Okay.
You have to attack first and catch him off guard.
And then...
And then, get on top of him,
oh, you should sit on him.
So he can't move.
And then, do this.
Oh, my...
And you attack like this.
Uh, let me...
Let's see, let's see.
Oh, no!
Hold on.
Oh, this won't do. Come here.
We'll leave everything up to you, then.
Of course.
Don't worry about a thing.
If things go well, I'll treat you to a drink somewhere really nice.
Of course. I'm looking forward to it.
Goodbye.
Oh, I'm exhausted.
I'm tired of making money.
But I love it.
Have your parents found out anything?
No.
I must return it before my father finds out.
Or he'll kill me.
Don't worry.
It'll only take a month.
It really is going to be doubled?
You're the best.
Subak,
you're lucky you found me again.
I know.
Who is it?
Hold on.
Yes, yes.
Tonight?
Okay. Wait for me there.
A present?
What would you like?
Okay. I'll stop by the department store.
I'll see you later.
Your ex-wife?
No.
You should break up with her.
It bothers me.
We're not in a relationship here.
You have a husband.
Don't be jealous.
That's funny.
- I'm home.
- Oh, hi.
You should try bringing some snacks home.
I feel like snacking.
Aeji, stop watching TV.
No! I want to watch more!
Grandmother, stop watching so much TV.
You're making Aeji watch TV.
What else can I do for fun but watch TV?
Stop bugging me about things like this.
Even your father doesn't say anything.
Whatever!
Mom, how can you let her watch TV all day?
I bought her books!
She can't even read yet.
That's why you need to read to her!
Why don't you just kill me right here?
I'm already exhausted because of Jungji.
How can I find time to read to her?
I don't even have time for a break.
But you can't let her watch TV all day!
What if she becomes stupid?
You're completely out of your mind.
She'll take after her parents.
If they're stupid, she'll be stupid.
Aeji's stupid because she takes after me?
Who else can she take after?
You thought you'd have a genius child?
Mom!
Don't start!
I had a crazy day, running over to the doctor's and the pharmacy.
Why? Is Jungji sick again?
He had a fever, so I got him some medicine,
but it wouldn't go down,
so I had to take him to the doctor's.
Why are you making him sick all the time?
I just can't believe my ears.
I'm making him sick?
Children get sick all the time.
Did I pray for him to get sick?
He's sick because he's a baby.
Anggeum, I heard something like that before.
You're hurting because you're young.
You're hurling because your young?
What's that?
What is that, uncle?
Pay better attention with Jungji!
Why is he getting hurt and sick so often?
That never happened before!
What's wrong with them?
Are they on something?
Who knows? Maybe they are.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
Egh, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo, hyo.
They used to get along great,
but now they're at each other's throats.
When your children get married,
you should see them only once an while.
What about me?
Not you.
I'm going to live with you.
I'm home.
Hello.
How's your father doing?
He's gotten much better.
What's wrong with you?
You're driving me crazy!
I'm relying on you to take care of my kids,
but if you're like this, how can I work?
Am I harming your kids?
You should just leave it to me!
But instead, you complain about everything I do, nagging about them.
I didn't feel this way raising my kids,
but I'm going crazy raising yours!
Why don't you raise them, then!
That's not what I'm saying!
Mother, I'm sorry.
Please calm down.
You go upstairs.
This is all your fault!
If you didn't wreck your business,
this wouldn't have happened
What are you up to these days?
If you hired a caregiver,
you should be taking care of your kids.
I'm sorry.
You're apologizing again.
We're always fighting because of you.
Don't you feel anything when you see us?
Why did I tell you to move in here?
If anyone wants to raise their grandkids,
I'd tell them not to even think about it.
Nobody should ever do this.
Stop this nonsense or move out!
I don't believe this.
I'm already furious,
but I get more annoyed when I come home.
What's wrong?
You're always mad.
Stop fighting with your mother.
She lashes out on me when you do.
She keeps telling us to move out.
It's really stressful for me.
Then why did you go bankrupt?
Just make more money.
I want to move out as soon as possible.
Don't start.
Your mother's already driving me crazy.
Don't pay attention to what my mom says.
Don't act like a girl.
- Like a girl?
- Yes.
I'll make money, so you raise the kids.
You're going out again?
I'm going to the gym.
Why are you exercising so hard?
Are you trying to beat someone up?
You've been acting suspicious.
What do you mean?
You're not doing anything fishy, are you?
Mother, I'm a human being.
And I behave like a human being.
What are you trying to say?
Who's not behaving like a human being?
Oh, she didn't even bother to answer.
I better destroy her.
Ice cream.
This late? It's cold.
You're supposed to eat it when it's cold.
There's none in the freezer.
Get me some.
Okay.
Who are you?
Wait, wait!
Please don't kill me.
I didn't do anything!
I have a wife and children.
Ouch! Blood! Blood! I'm bleeding!
Help...
You!
The house feels empty.
It's not. We're all here.
It feels like ten people are gone.
Doesn't it?
I feel really sad lately.
The house feels empty and so big.
Without Sangnam,
I don't want to come home anymore.
What's wrong with you?
Why don't you want to come home?
Miho, why are you talking like that?
What she said was right.
I think you have to let him win.
Why do you think Sangnam left?
He's rude, that's why.
They're both rude.
A match made in heaven!
You're going to lose your son.
If he was like other kids,
he'd already be married with kids.
I wouldn't let that happen!
You wouldn't?
I thought you wanted grandchildren.
Don't regret it later and let him do it.
That's what you should do.
They don't need your permission to marry.
You stay out of this.
Daese.
You stay out, too.
You're so mean.
Miho, you stay out!
Sunjeong,
call Sangnam and have him come home tonight.
Tell him I have something to say.
Okay.
I got you!
What are you doing?
Let me go! Let me go!
[Divorce Agreement]
What are you waiting for?
Look. Doctor's report.
I got 2 weeks.
Do you know what you did?
You didn't know this means divorce?
If you don't sign it, I'm going to sue.
Sue, okay?
I will.
You should've done it a long time ago.
Don't waste anymore time.
Stop leaking on it!
It should be clean.
If the judge saw that, he wouldn't like it!
I didn't know you were so strong.
Where did you learn to fight?
I can't believe this.
You're just unbelievable.
What little love I had left is now gone.
It was attempted murder, don't you know?
Oh, it hurts.
See you at noon tomorrow in front of the courthouse.
Hold on.
I'm sorry, Sedal.
I went too far, didn't I?
I'm really sorry.
And I want to thank you.
In the past 36 years,
the only good memories
are the ones with you in them.
You're the only good memory I have.
You made me smile and you made me happy.
It's the truth.
You gave me two sons whom I treasure.
To me you're essential.
If you're that grateful,
give me a present by divorcing me.
I'll see you tomorrow at the courthouse.
Is this what you really want?
I don't joke around.
Please reconsider this.
I'm done considering.
I'm only thirty five.
When will I get another chance like this?
I'll wait for you,
if you promise to come back to me.
Don't.
Why would you?
Let's end this.
Sedal,
we're not important here.
You should think about our sons.
They need their dad.
Sintong and Bangtong miss their dad.
This is what Bangtong said.
He said dad, mom, Sintong and him,
the four make up his family.
They'll understand when they're older.
We're over, so what good can they do?
Don't dwell on me and start a new life.
Being divorced isn't a problem now.
Lots of people get divorced and do well.
I don't think this is going to work.
Come with me.
To where?
Let's get a room near the court
and submit this first thing in the morning.
I'll be there.
I already signed it.
You better come.
Or I'm going to the police.
I'll see you tomorrow.
At the cafe before,
what did you tell the girl who works there?
She seemed pretty scared.
I gave her a piece of my mind.
She was mean to me when I worked there.
You should help the people you work with instead of trying to be their boss!
That's the ugliest thing in the world! Ugly!
What do you think?
It must have been hard for you.
It was,
but breaking up with you was harder.
But we never broke up.
You know exactly what to say.
You're right.
We never broke up.
Standing in front of your house reminds me of something.
Oh, no.
What?
I meant us talking on the phone all night.
How could you always think about that?
I don't know!
Good job.
You did really well.
She did well?
Yes. Law school won't be a problem.
She'll need a bit of luck, of course.
- Incredible.
- I know.
I haven't been this happy in a while.
Jayeong is taking the test again next year.
Her mom was crying so hard.
I bought everyone lunch, but I felt bad.
You bought them lunch already?
They called me a judge's mom, so I had to.
I bought them pizza.
Goof off went to law school, too.
How can you say that?
How dare you compare Haebak to Goof off?
You say the most inappropriate things.
Are you still going to the gym?
Yes.
You should travel with your friends before you start college.
- We're here.
- Hello.
- Hi!
- Welcome, welcome.
- Come in.
You look even more handsome.
Did you get a facial or something?
Thank you.
When will we meet your father?
Soon. Please pick a date.
When do you want the wedding to be?
After the winter. Like next spring.
I want to have it this year.
We have less than a month.
I'm not sure if that's possible.
Mom, we want a simple wedding.
Oh, look at her!
She's just dying to get married.
Grandmother!
You know me so well.
Oh, boy.
I want a simple but meaningful wedding.
Then talk to your father and pick a date.
I will.
What do we do about your father?
I'll take care of it.
Don't say anything to your parents.
I won't.
It's one obstacle after another.
Why is getting married so hard?
If it's easy, it won't be fun.
Father, I'm here.
I'm going to be stubborn, too.
I can't accept her as my daughter in law.
Instead,
let's have a daughter in law audition.
Excuse me?
A daughter in law audition?
They have lots of audition shows on TV.
If she passes the audition,
I'll accept her.
Can I ask you something?
Okay.
Is there a dry cleaner's near here?
A dry cleaner's?
Oh,
when you go out that way
and turn right...
What are you doing?
Where am I? Who are you?
Hey, hey!
What are you doing?
Let me go!
Why are you doing this to me? Hey!
Hey!
Let me go!
Why are you doing this to me?
Hey! Hey! Let me go! Let me go!
Uh... Hello?
Is anyone there?
Hey!
Is anyone there!
Subtitles by KBS World
Is something up?
Gwangbak! I've been kid...
How can a mom come home in the morning?
Are you sick or something?
Excuse me?
You should see a doctor.
What do you want?
Get me $100,000 by the end of today.
Where can I get that amount of money?
You better not call the police.
You cut your finger doing that? Man...
Hey! Time is crucial for a burn wound!
What if something goes wrong to my mother?
Forget about the mean mother in law.
Pretend you got a new mother.
I'll be good to you.