It's cold.
Where did you go?
Go back to sleep.
I didn't go out to meet women.
Don't worry.
Just try it.
Oppa, I want to go to the toilet.
Toilet?
Oppa, don't go.
Stay here.
Okay.
You must stay here.
Yeah.
Oppa!
Are you there?
Don't worry. Hurry up.
Oppa!
I said I'm here.
Don't go.
I'm scared.
Don't worry. I won't go.
I won't.
Scared me to death.
Brother-in-law.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
Yeong Dal said she's scared.
Wow. It's not a public toilet.
It's just in the yard.
What's so scary?
She doesn't know how to be embarrassed.
Oppa! Oppa, are you there?
Oppa!
I'm not oppa.
Is it ajubeonim?
(Elder brother-in-law)
I'm scared.
Wait there for me.
What?
Yes, yes, yes.
Ajubeonim!
Yeah.
I thought you left.
I won't leave.
Is someone in there?
Sister-in-law.
She's still in there?
How long has she been there?
Hey!
Hurry up and come out.
Consider the person waiting for you.
Leave her alone.
There are plenty of busy people.
She should hurry up.
She is like that occupying position how can?
Wait a while longer.
She's so tactless.
Hurry, come out.
Ajubeonim, are you there?
Yes, Sister-in-law.
There's no toilet paper here.
Please get one for me.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yah. Yah.
Sister-in-law, toilet paper.
Did you sleep well, Mother?
Perhaps because we changed house,
I kept having nightmares.
You can't rush me.
I'm already suffering from constipation.
Oh my.
Mo-Mo-Mother.
Don't do this.
Go and submit your application again, Judge.
Mom.
You saw how we are, right?
You're the only one who can save us.
We don't have money to apply again.
Even I starve myself to death,
I will support you.
Go and study again.
If you don't want to see me die.
It's too narrow, can't open my arms.
It's stuffy.
This reminds of the hardship
when I was a refugee.
Back then, there were no tables,
we just spread the newspapers and ate.
The bathroom is the problem.
My buttocks were freezing until
it felt like it was going to split.
I thought my buttocks were going to fall off.
My buttocks were freezing too.
Ajubeonim, your buttocks were freezing too?
What? Yeah.
Oh, yes. Since your an elder,
I should address it with a "Sir".
Buttocks, sir.
No?
We should set an order in using the bathroom.
This won't do.
I'm so busy in the morning.
And someone just hogged
the bathroom for a few hours.
Next time, those who are leaving
in the morning will use it first.
Those who are not going out will go later.
He ran all the way to school
just to use the toilet.
It's good exercise.
You ran all the way there because you had to go.
Is that what you call exercise?
Father, Uncle and Dae Bak
should use it earlier.
The rest of us can take it slowly.
Then she will use it in my stead.
I can endure it.
Sister-in-law is pregnant.
She will get all the convenience.
She's number 1, no matter what.
Ajubeonim is the best.
Hey, we're eating.
Let's stop talking about toilet.
Oh my god!
What's wrong? What's wrong?
I killed a few yesterday.
There's a lot of them.
You should practice to catch them.
What's so scary?
I can't do that.
Are you going to eat with that hand?
Go and wash it.
But Su Bak's not eating breakfast?
Is she on a diet?
Don't give her food.
Did she do something good?
Why feed her?
Look at her.
She's still sleeping.
She doesn't even show her face.
That girl has a long way to go before
she comes to her senses.
Maybe she's too shy to show her face
because she's sorry.
I'm going to wash my hands.
Hye Bak, bring this to her.
Give it to me.
Aunt will bring it to her.
Su Bak is not here.
No?
She's not here either.
Where did she go this early in the morning?
Come to think of it,
I don't think I saw her this morning.
Me, too.
We were sleeping together in one room last night.
Mom.
This.
Her bag is not around either.
Mom, sorry.
Father, forgive me.
I left because I just can't stay
at home any longer.
I will earn plenty of money then come back.
Mom, I'm a really disappointing daughter.
I'm really sorry.
Please take care of Ae Ji and Jung Ji.
No matter what happens,
I will definitely get back the house.
I won't come back before that happens.
Mom, sorry.
Father, please forgive me.
She's crazy, crazy.
This girl really always worries people.
Always.
Where did she go?
Where can she go?
She doesn't even wash her own underwear.
She can't even take care of herself.
Where is she going to earn money?
She doesn't even have 10 000 Won.
What are we going to do, Husband?
What if something bad happens to her?
Don't cry.
You're wasting tears.
She caused all this,
she should be punished.
She has to suffer somewhere
in order to wake up.
She'll be 40 in 2 years,
and she can't even wash her underwear.
Is that worth showing off?
She has 4 limbs.
Why can't she earn a living?
This is all because of you.
She was already trembling with fear
because of what she did.
You still reprimanded her.
Would she be able to take it?
If something happens to Su Bak,
it will be your fault.
What?
Stop it, Mom.
I hope Su Bak will be all right.
She's really immature,
for someone so old.
Are you leaving now?
Yes.
Let's talk for a moment.
I have to go to the construction site.
You went there at dawn, didn't you?
I still have to go.
Still must then go next transaction reside.
Sang Nam, sorry.
It was my fault.
I shouldn't treat Mother like that
but I unconsciously did it.
Sorry.
If I put myself in your shoes,
if you did that to my mom,
I would get mad.
I am really sorry.
Eonni.
Can you talk for a moment?
Yes, I'm in my room.
Su Bak eonni left from home.
What?
She left a letter.
Do you have any idea
where she might be??
I don't know either.
What's wrong with her?
I know.
What's going to happen to her
running away in the state she's in?
She even left the kids here.
Because she's depressed.
They moved to that kind of house
because of her.
Will she feel comfortable?
She didn't even consider our parents.
This is really driving me crazy.
Where can she go?
Think about it.
Okay, Eonni.
Imagine how sad she must be.
Imagine how depressed she must be
when she left the kids.
They say 'Hate the crime but not the sinner'.
I wanted to kill her, but doing that
will give me a heart ache.
Can you think of any places
Su Bak might go to?
I don't know either.
Can't you think of any place?
I can't think of any.
Su Bak doesn't have good friend?
I don't know.
You've been married for several years,
and you don't know anything.
That's right.
With her pride,
she won't go to her friend's place.
I don't think she keeps in touch
with any of her friends recently.
Where can she be?
I'm worried that she might get other ideas on her head.
When you went bankrupt,
she wanted to die back then.
According to the context of her letter,
I don't think she'll do that.
There are the children.
Trust her and just wait.
I'll come back after work.
Did Su Bak call you?
Don't worry too much.
Okay.
Hey, did you bring it?
Hey, I can't because of that old man.
They rummage bags at the school entrance.
Where can I hide it?
How frustrating.
That old man's not going to another school?
I don't want to come to school
because I hate that old man.
I just forced myself to come
because of assembly.
Hey, that old man should be retiring soon, right?
He's quite old.
Why is that old man still loitering here?
What did you say just now?
Nothing much.
We just said a few words about that old man.
Don't call him old man.
What about it?
You call him old man too.
Why?
You're siding with him just because
you share the same surname?
Really.
What are you doing?
Everyone can go except Wang Dae Bak.
Follow me.
Tell me the truth.
Why did you fight?
Just because.
Were you smoking?
You should also know...
That Father's really sad these days.
What am I going to do
if even you are like this?
You even fight now.
Do you have the strength
to take on 3 boys?
Do you think I'll be happy
to see you take a beating?
Wait till you have your own kids later.
See if you'll be happy seeing
your child being beaten up.
Did you do something wrong?
No.
What?
Even if I got beaten up,
I don't think I did anything wrong.
This child, till the end...
If they do that again,
I won't let them off.
What do you mean?
Please behave in school.
I'm already ashamed to face the other students.
I feel guilty to face the other teachers too.
If they found out that you were my son,
they'd say that I couldn't
even teach my own son.
How could I teach other students?
There'd be plenty of gossips.
If you keep doing this,
I'll tell them you're my son.
Don't do that, please.
So, listen to me.
Go.
Are you Yeong Dal?
Do you keep in touch with Wang Su Bak?
Okay.
Yeah.
Oppa, can you talk right now?
I'm busy right now,
I'll call you later.
Husband, didn't I give you 30 000 yesterday?
Gone already?
How many times are you going
to take that exam?
Just give up.
I'm already frustrated.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
Were you with that girl again?
If that happens, it's either you die or I die.
Let's talk later.
Hello, Team leader.
What's going on?
I thought about you while
I was passing by so I came.
As if I'd believe that.
Why?
Anything I can do for you?
You're really fast.
I want to work.
Is there any work you can give me?
I heard you got married.
Your husband's unemployed?
It's not like that.
You even said that I'm supporting
an unemployed husband.
I have an appointment.
See you later.
Team leader. Just this time.
I need work.
You never thought you'd come
and see me again?
You don't want to drink the water you spat.
Take that bread with you.
Just that much.
Why did you have to bother?
Hello.
Why are you here?
You came to see your husband?
Yes.
You don't visit us these days.
I'll just be a burden to you.
No.
Come and have dinner.
This is for you.
Thank you. I will eat properly.
Sang Nam.
I'll be back later.
I have a meeting with President Gim.
Bye.
What?
Can't we have lunch together?
I have a prior appointment.
How could you come out of the blue?
I'm working.
Sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Isn't she a college graduate?
Her dad is also a head teacher.
Is that how her family taught her?
I'll talk to her.
It won't happen again.
I was treated like that
by my daughter-in-law.
I was too upset, I couldn't sleep.
I am her mother-in-law.
How could she glare at me like I was a stranger?
If she really loves and respects you,
this wouldn't happen.
Isn't it?
Men these days are too giving to their women.
Don't be like that.
I'm really afraid how'd she'd treat
your father in the future.
She is not that kind of person.
Is that written on the face?
You dated for just a short while.
You don't know her.
I'm fine.
For both your father's sake and yours,
I hope we can settle this properly.
I'll make her apologize to you.
I don't really want her to apologize to me.
Where did you go?
There's no one at home.
Where did everyone go?
I thought Aunt was at home.
Don't you kow that she went to cooking school?
Sorry.
I don't want this house to be empty all the time.
I don't like it, ever since before.
If you have an appointment,
ask my permission first before you go.
Why did you leave on your own?
Brother-in-law. Sorry.
Sister-in-law, teach her well.
I have to scold her at each and everything.
It hurts my mouth.
Tell me if you're going to leave.
That way, I'll just stay at home.
I forgot.
I had something to do
and I wanted to reconcile with Sang Nam too.
Be careful next time.
Please don't cry again.
Crying is not a virtue.
Since you're already married,
it's not good to keep crying.
Yes.
You don't have experience and training.
There's nothing except for manual jobs.
What kind?
Cleaning or washing the dishes.
I can't also make introductions randomly for these.
You must confirm your identity
and a health certificate is needed.
Have you done any housekeeping or nannying jobs?
I'll do anything you want me to do.
If you don't do well,
we'll get criticized.
Since you're pretty, how about working in
a karaoke lounge or try waitressing?
I don't want to do those.
You wash dishes here,
and collect the bowls as soon as the customers leave.
You must be quick.
Welcome.
The kitchen is over there.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
Can't you be more careful?
Even if you cook and wash dishes at home,
you can't work outside.
Giving this to you is such a waste,
but I'm giving this to you
seeing how pitiful you are.
You're lucky that I didn't charge you
for those broken bowls.
It's so cold.
I'll sleep here for a while.
Oh my god!
I don't know where she's sleeping.
She's making her parents worry.
She'll come back if she can't endure it.
She's not my child, she's an enemy.
Is there anything I can help you with?
You see...
Go ahead.
Sorry, but can't I stay here until tomorrow morning?
Bounce...
From family inside came out renga all sing bad.
An ajumma used to work here.
because she's old,
she was a total mess.
She was fired in the end.
You must listen carefully
to everything I say.
You must always wipe the glass cleanly,
mop the floor well,
and clean the toilet.
Memorize the menu--
Memorize discount cards and VIP cards.
Don't forget to stamp on the coupons.
Don't panic when taking orders from customers.
Remember the customers' orders.
Enough?
Welcome.
What do you want to order?
Americano.
What size?
A small cup.
Did you bring your membership card?
I said, you can't.
You're still young.
I'm sure I'll do well.
You're really persistent.
How could you beg me for 2 hours?
I must earn money.
Can I?
Fine.
Ask your parents to sign this.
Since you're a minor,
you need your parents' consent.
Thank you.
Hot, hot.
Sorry. Sorry.
Sorry.
Is this your first time to do this?
No, I've done it plenty of times.
It's hot, so...
Sorry. Sorry.
What are you doing?
Clean it up quickly.
Yes. Yes.
Ajumma, please give us radish.
When they say ajumma,
it means you.
Do you understand?
Radish.
What radish?
Bring it to the customer.
Okay.
~ Bounce. Bounce.  ~
Hello, Ajussi.
Yes.
Grandmother!
Those are someone else's.
There's no such thing.
First come, first served.
I'll come again tomorrow.
Don't give it to anyone.
~ Bounce, bounce... ~
~ Looking at you. ~
Hey. There's nothing here.
Some grandmother took them away.
What? That son-of-a-gun.
For you.
Just this?
That's considered a lot.
I gave you a whole bundle.
But I still feel good.
Do you know what this house means to me?
What tired?
She does whatever she wants to do.
You have too much bad luck,
that was why Go son-in-law lost everything.
Just take a look.
After divorcing you,
everything went well again.
How could you do something so atrocious?
Are you human?
Sang Nam, I have an important appointment tonight.
Okay.
Please tell Father-in-law for me.
Boss...
Sorry, but can you give me 100 000 in advance?
You just started working and
you're asking for 100 000.
Do you do this at every restaurant?
Then, how about 50 000?
I have something urgent.
Please, Boss.
Gwang Bak, how are you doing
at your in-law's place?
Are you all right?
Of course, I'm fine.
Mom, I'll go there for dinner later.
Did you cook Father sea kelp soup this morning?
Kelp soup?
Oh my, I forgot.
I'm so forgetful.
I even forgot your father's birthday.
You forgot?
Oh no.
What's the use of living like this?
As your granny said,
"Old people should just drop dead."
2nd Eonni and I will bring food over.
Let's just have a party tonight.
Bye, Mom.
Daughter-in-law.
Today is Bong's birthday.
I just found out after Gwang Bak gave me a call.
What to do?
If you don't take good care of people,
it will surely be a big problem.
How could you forget his birthday?
You should have told me.
Blame this on Su Bak.
Just cook kelp soup tonight.
What else can we do?
The children said they're coming.
Stop talking about Su Bak.
I don't want to hear it.
You still have to listen even if you don't want to.
You are to blame for your child's wrongdoing.
What else can I do?
Just let Mom cook the kelp soup.
Let's do the rest.
What are you going to cook?
Beef short ribs?
You can do it?
Okay then.
You do that and the salad.
I'll do the cake, japchae and some sashimi.
See you later there tonight.
Eonni.
Eonni, what happened to you?
Geez.
Where's your bag?
You don't need to know that.
I was so worried about you.
You don't even answer your phone.
Don't be like this. It's cold.
Let's go somewhere.
No, I have to go back right away.
This.
What is this?
It's Father's birthday today.
You haven't forgotten?
How can I forget? That's not much.
You must give it to him.
Wish him a happy birthday for me.
Eonni, come home.
Everyone's worried about you.
I can't go back until I succeed.
No, I won't go back.
Ho Bak.
I'm really grateful to you and Gwang Bak.
You found them a house.
I didn't do my responsibility as the eldest.
I just cause trouble.
Eonni.
Just consider yourself the eldest
of our family from now on.
Just pretend that I'm not around.
How can you say that?
Eonni, where are you and
what are you doing?
Take good care of Mom and Father.
And our younger siblings,
I'll rely on you.
Ho Bak, sorry.
I'm going.
Eonni.
Eonni!
Eonni, wait!
Wait...
Eonni! Wait!
Wait, Eonni!
Eonni!
Wait!
Oh, no. Sorry.
Oh, no.
Eonni!
Eonni! Eonni!
What do I do?
Your sister is really hopeless.
She's really immature.
That's enough.
I was really crushed when I saw how she was.
She's the black sheep of your family.
The black sheep.
I'm the black sheep of our family.
Right?
- Dad!
That's right.
You're back from cram school?
Wash your hands and
prepare to do your homework.
Look at you guys.
As if you didn't see me.
Of course. I'm their mother.
You're not popular in this house anymore.
Sin Dong, Bang Dong,
can't you see Mom?
We saw you.
See?
This makes life fun.
Delicious smell.
What's this, Dad?
You're really...
Just one.
Don't touch.
That's for your grandmother.
Who did you take after?
Why are you so naughty?
If you join a 'naughty competition' somewhere,
I'm sure you'd get first place.
Our kids won't choke no matter how they eat.
I told you to wash your hands
after coming home.
Hurry, go wash and change
then do your homework.
Okay.
I hate you, Dad.
These little brats.
Who did you take after?
You're so disobedient.
Slackers.
Just like their father.
What's wrong?
Wait, are you like this everyday?
You're like a mother.
You're a total housewife.
Perfect.
Of course.
I do everything perfectly.
You hurry up too.
We don't have much time.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Oh my!
Did a man come here to visit you?
My brother's daughter-in-law gets shocked
all the time because she has a man.
What's that?
It smells good.
It's beef short ribs.
Are you giving it to someone?
Yes. That.
You take things from this house?
How could you say that?
Do you feel uncomfortable
because I was spot on?
A cup of tea please.
Please add egg yolk.
I don't know how to do that.
I already taught you.
Was it the sushi I ate yesterday
that's causing this indigestion?
Or, I was too ecstatic
because I ate with my son.
I won't get hungry even if I don't eat anything.
You ate sushi with Sang Nam?
Sang Nam didn't tell you?
We had lunch together yesterday.
Sang Nam was so apologetic because of you.
Ha said he married the wrong wife
so he begged me for forgiveness.
Be good to me.
If you want your husband to love you.
How could you not be aware of the basics?
You even went to uni.
Did you enter through the backdoor?
What?
No.
Forget it.
Whether you entered through the front door
or back door, that's not important.
You are my daughter-in-law
and I am your mother-in-law.
That is important.
Oh. That sounded so cool.
Right?
Are you ready?
Mother... I didn't say anything because
I don't want Sang Nam to get hurt.
What?
You know.
I say you...
Are you going to shift
the blame on me again?
The more you do this,
the more you need to give me something.
I'll just pretend I never heard that.
Even if I want to,
I don't have money to give you.
Wait! Ah, I'm thristy.
Give me a glass of fresh juice first.
Where are you going?
I just remembered that I have a prior appointment.
Cancel the juice.
I don't need to pay you, right?
What are you doing?
You need to mop the floor.
There's no time to sit down.
You think you can just slack off.
Do you want me to pay you
while you rest?
You're too much.
I've been working all the time,
this is my first time to sit.
Although I'm doing this because
I have some difficulties,
don't be too strict with me.
I was in the Miss Korea pageant.
Miss Korea?
Yes.
What about Miss Korea?
Can they clean and cook tofu soup?
I didn't want to say this but...
In our store, Miss Korea, super models
and actors all came to work here.
You don't even know.
Hurry, mop the floor.
Clean it till it shines.
Until you can see Miss Korea's face clearly.
It's too stuffy.
We're all squeezed in.
Who's crossing their legs?
Except Father.
Do it Father.
You're exempted today because it's your birthday.
We forgot the cake.
Go son-in-law will buy it.
You should've drank kelp soup this morning.
What to do?
Sorry, Son.
I forgot too.
I've never forgotten about it all these years.
Throw away this useless wife of yours.
What's a birthday?
Being together is enough.
Thank you.
Everyone gathered here to celebrate
this inept father's birthday.
I'm to blame for everything.
It's all my fault.
When will we laugh again?
Mom.
Father, it's your birthday today.
Why are you crying?
Just like Granny said,
A day will come when you will laugh again.
That's right, Hyeongnim.
Hurry, let's eat.
Congratulations for being born, Son.
Yes, Mother.
If you hate your in-laws,
they will also hate your daughter.
Wait and see, Beautician.
Like mother, like daughter.
I will surely make her cry.
My daughter's already married.
What can I do?
Yes, Mother-in-law.
You're here.
Hurry, go in.
Yes.
Yes, Mother-in-law.
We don't live there anymore.
That is because...
Hello.
Start.
- Hi.
Welcome.
Just squeeze in.
The house is going to explode.
This is the first time I've heard of that in my life.
Come and sit down, Brother-in-law.
The divorced Go son-in-law even came.
Where is Choe son-in-law?
He went to China on a business trip.
Father, I made this beef short ribs.
Sin Dong's dad made this.
You can also call him Sin Dong's mom now.
House chores is becoming more interesting.
I've finally become a cheapskate house husband.
That's right.
It gets interesting when you're used to it.
Dad, this too.
Is it money?
Eonni wanted me to give it to Father.
You met her? Where is she?
What is she doing?
How did you meet her?
She called me.
It's your birthday so she asked me
to pass that to you.
She asked you to pass that to him?
Where is she?
What is she doing?
She wouldn't tell me no matter how much I asked.
She said she'd come back after she succeeds.
You should find out no matter what happens.
I chased after her but couldn't catch her.
Is she doing well?
She lost a lot of weight.
She just cried.
What to do?
Don't feel sorry for her.
She should go out and suffer
to make her come to her senses.
She's so sly.
She left because she couldn't stomach
living in a house like this.
Do you think she really left because
the house has become like this?
She wrote in the letter that she's going
to earn money to get the house back.
You believe her?
When can she earn enough money
to buy the house back?
She ran away because of you.
What?
She wouldn't have left
if you didn't bully her.
She was already suffering.
You kept nagging her
ever since we moved here.
She was already in pins and needles.
She said she destroyed her father.
You kept rubbing it in,
how could she stay here?
Furthermore,
she didn't lose the house to loan sharks.
Go son-in-law's income wasn't enough,
so she just wanted to supplement it.
That happened because she met a swindler.
You berated her like that,
would she be able to take it?
You chased her away.
You must be out of your mind.
You kept babying Su Bak turning her like that.
You still can't differentiate shit from miso?
That's enough, Mother.
That's right.
Today is Father's birthday,
let's be happy.
Come, come, come.
Let's gather up all our energy
and sing happy birthday loudly.
Granny, Mother-in-law.
Use all your energy here
and sing loudly.
Come. Start.
Happy Birthday to you.
- To our beloved Father-in-law.
- To our beloved Father.
Happy birthday to you.
Blow the candles, Father-in-law.
Happy birthday.
Still far away?
We'll be there in a bit.
Is it still far?
We'll be there soon.
You kept saying that.
Where the heck is it?
That.
Here.
Mom, Hyeongnim...
Come out.
Bag.
=Bag and to poop have same sound=-
I already pooped.
I was first in line.
I told you to pack your bags.
I don't want to.
Pack your bags!
Don't yell.
What if something happens to the baby?
Is the baby the problem now?
My daughter is dying.
You're too much.
Your house became like this.
Why didn't you tell me?
How could you let my precious daughter
live in this kind of place?
Neighbours!
Don't yell, Mother.
Why are you calling the neighbours?
Butt out.
Mom.
You too, butt out!
You're both useless.
How could you be so treacherous?
In-law, please calm down.
Butt out too!
This woman's so arrogant.
Who the hell are you?
That's enough.
It was just a slip of the tongue.
Sorry.
There's no need to talk!
Pack your bags immediately!
I don't want to.
I don't want to pack my bags.
Oppa.
Come here.
Mother-in-law.
What mother-in-law?
Loser, does this make any sense?
What loser?
Wang son-in-law.
You don't even know how to address him.
Have you forgotten you call my son slip head?
Let's go.
He doesn't even have a house.
Suffering like this here, does it make sense?
How could you let a newly wed couple
sleep on the cold floor?
I said I want to sleep here.
That's why I said to let them use the bedroom.
I will sleep on the cold floor.
Ask any passerby,
does this make any sense?
Come with me!
Go with Mother-in-law.
No! I'm not going.
She doesn't want to go.
I can't let her go too, Mother-in-law.
What are you doing?
Mom, Mom...
Let's go.
Mom, let's go.
Let go.
Father! We're going.
Come here.
Let's go.
Oh my.
The Korean War was nothing compared to this.
What are you going to do later?
You seduced my daughter so you
should be responsible for her.
You're 35, no, you're 36 already, right?
You're already 36 years old.
You don't even have money to rent a house.
Does that make any sense?
Mother-in-law, if you wait a bit longer...
Wait for what?
What?
You should at least have a room.
When 2 doors open,
all eyes will be on you.
Furthermore, sleeping on the cold floor,
does it make sense?
It's winter.
I'll find a monthly rental house for you.
Move out.
I can't do that.
Why not?
I don't want to depend on you.
I'm just letting you know.
Se Dal and I are not the same.
What about Se Dal?
Did Se Dal want anything from your family?
Ho Bak's supporting him.
Hey!
He's right.
My wife, my child,
I will provide for them.
I won't rely on anyone.
How we live is our business.
I'm going.
Loser, you...
And I'm not loser.
Please call me Wang son-in-law.
If you keep calling me loser,
I will also call you ajumma.
Oh my god, listen to what he said.
Did you hear it?
He didn't say anything wrong.
You are wrong.
Since your family lost everything,
you should have at least told me.
Bring her back here!
She likes it there.
How can I drag her back?
Let's wait till she can't take it any longer,
then I'll take her home.
I think it's better to let her stay there for now.
Ditto.
What?
I share the same opinion.
Mom, don't worry about her.
Whether she's rich or poor,
let her take care of it.
When she married me a long time ago,
we had nothing and we used to live in
a basement room too.
Did her family drag her away?
Are they the same?
Exactly the same.
Carbon copies.
Your children are exactly alike.
Just treat it as fate.
I'm really going crazy.
Ouch, it hurts.
I can't afford it.
Uncle has to go to college,
Su Bak is studying far away,
she needs living expenses.
Ho Bak, give it up.
She is your sister.
The eldest of this family.
Father.
You're too much.
I am better at studies.
I need to graduate from university.
I can't quit midway.
I want to be an announcer.
You really are...
I told you many times.
The eldest has to graduate from university.
You keep saying 'Eldest, eldest'.
You just care about the eldest.
It's really unfair.
Su Bak.
Yes, Father.
Study hard.
Just think of it as studying for
Ho Bak's part too.
You are the eldest of our family.
My eldest child.
Understand?
Oppa?
There's a registered letter for Go Min Jeong.
Yes. Thank you.
It's only our family here now.
I'm also part of our family too, right?
Of course, Sister-in-law.
Thanks for not going home with your mom.
I know.
Ajussi, wait a moment.
Ajubeonim.
I forgot.
I keep forgetting.
This is my salary.
Let us all gather our money together to buy a house.
If we unite together,
we can buy that house.
Take it back.
No, I'm also part of this family.
I have to contribute.
Just take it.
I'm just saying.
Did you think I would spend her salary?
Just take it as part of Uncle and Sister-in-law's living expenses.
You have to save money and rent a house immediately.
But it's also a problem.
You saw how your mother was earlier.
Son, I earned money too.
What did you do?
You don't need to know.
Did you pick up scraps?
How did you know?
It's obvious.
I collected a whole bag but
he just gave me that bit.
Mother, don't do that.
If you slip,
the medical fee will be more expensive.
I won't slip.
I walked very carefully.
Earning money is fun.
Father, I found a part-time job too.
In a cafe, taking orders and waitressing.
Be quiet!
I'm not nagging you because
it's a happy day today.
Go and apply to the review academy again.
Even if I starve to death,
I will send you to university.
Father, you need to sign this.
You're going to work?
Yes.
If you sign that.
Just forget about it.
What's the role of a student?
To study hard.
That's helping Father.
I'm also part of this family.
Aunt even gave her salary.
I want to help in buying a house too.
I'm the eldest son of this family.
I'll just work during winter break.
Dae Bak, you don't have to work.
Plenty of people will do that.
Whatever you want to do,
just wait till you're in high school.
I'm also against it.
Thank you, everyone.
I'm stronger now.
My legs have strength now.
It feels like I will stand up again soon.
Come. Come.
Ajubeonim will stand up very soon.
Yeong Dal will sing a song.
I will sing a song.
Because I know that feeling.
Bravo.
The atmosphere at home is so much better
because of Loser and Yeong Dal.
What would we do without them?
That's right.
Treat In-law better.
He treats her well,
that was why she came here to cause trouble.
It's your day today.
Sing a song.
Singer Wang.
You think I won't sing?
Singer Wang! Wow.
1, 2, 3, 4.
~ The hearts of parents in this world are the same. ~
~ They want their children to do well. ~
~ Must be happy. ~
Really good.
~ They cheer them on from behind. ~
Oh.
~ I am Wang son-in-law. ~
~ If people jeer at you,
don't get mad. ~
~ Don't look at me like this.
I'm still young. ~
Really great. Really great.
Wonderful. Wonderful.
~ Dad's youth. ~
Bravo.
~ Dad's life. ~
Really good.
Singer!
Now? Why?
You'll find out when you get here.
Did something happen at home?
Okay.
Hello.
Have a seat.
What is it, out of the blue...
I think this can't go on.
Apologize to my mother. Hurry.
I'm sorry about that day.
It was my fault.
I was really upset that day.
Since you've already apologized,
I feel better.
Let's get along.
Okay?
Sang Nam. Coffee.
Yes.
Did you see that?
My son is on my side.
Don't try to be naughty again.
Sorry. I have to go.
What are you doing?
There's no one at home.
Then...
This is all my fault.
Who else is to blame?
I can't get my daughter-in-law's respect.
She left already?
Leave her alone.
As long as she apologized.
Sang Nam.
Hot.
What are you doing?
Why are you crying?
You're mad because you apologized?
Don't you need to apologize if you
did something wrong to an elder?
I did it.
You can't be like this.
I hope you can apologize sincerely.
You let me apologize out of the blue.
I need to prepare first.
What preparation?
What preparation do you need
to apologize to an elder?
Sorry.
She's my mom.
She gave birth to me.
I can't forgive how you disregarded her.
You, for suddenly calling me over to apologize,
and I, for not apologizing sincerely,
we're even, so sorry.
Enough?
Let's stop.
Next Episode Preview.
Perhaps one day wife one day husband.
Just now hand over the material deal with.
Don't have. Haven't process.
Know that
today no process today just will not valid.
Brother-in-law is because do not know
know those who would does not matter?
Daughter-in-law how can like this?
You towards Sang Nam still use drive a wedge between calculate.
I also won't can have endured.
I always put up with you. You actually dare.
Sang Nam auntie come here doing what?
At here have a person I know.
Son-in-law Go hand over to before
you must certainly find him beg forgiveness.
Although won't let me know
but I really like like this the brother.
Unswerving from start to finish the man.
-=Episode 41=-
-=Bath house=-
-=Police officer=-
-=Wanted: Kitchen Hand. Free board and lodging.
Preferrably with experience.=-
-=House Foreclosure Notice=-
-=Seoul Civil Court=-
-=Mr. Go Min Jeong.=-
-=Employment Consent Form for a 15 year old.=-