Sister-in-law. Sister-in-law. Sang Nam.
What are you going to do about this?
This is all because of you.
If you didn't leave the house,
this would never have happened.
What happened?
Your father's gold key has been stolen.
What?
The tie clip he received as bridal gift and
and his gold cufflinks are also gone.
I told you not to leave the house,
but you wouldn't listen.
Was that an ordinary key?
Let's report this to the police, Father.
Yes, let's report it, quick.
Brother-in-law...
Reporting this to the police is a bit...
What's wrong?
It'll complicate things.
The police will have to come here and investigate.
You need to go to the police station too.
If it weren't for you,
this wouldn't have happened!
Did Eonni come here?
Yes.
She entered Brother-in-law's room, right?
No way.
That's impossible.
I'm sure of it.
It felt strange so I didn't
want to call the police.
What if the police says Sang Nam's mom is the culprit?
What embarrassment will that bring?
How about the hurt it will bring to Sang Nam?
She's really an enemy.
Really.
Aunt!
Wait.
Let me settle this problem.
Just pretend you don't know.
I have a plan.
Oppa, I left without waiting for you.
I couldn't reach you these days.
Hope there's no problem.
The court sent you a mail.
Re-heat the stew.
You must eat.
If you present it to the district office,
you'll be divorced right away.
If you don't present it,
the divorce will be considered null and void.
What are you doing?
You're not sleeping yet.
Why did you come out?
Bathroom.
Happy birthday, Husband.
I don't know where one of my child is.
Whether she's alive or dead.
Does it make sense for me to celebrate
my birthday as a father?
Don't worry.
She won't die.
She gave you 50 000 Won, didn't she?
So many things have happened,
if not for Hye Bak and Dae Bak,
I really want to give up.
Don't say that.
Mother is still here.
Don is also married now.
I can say whatever I want.
How can you do that?
Even if you want to abandon your kids,
you can't abandon Mother.
Without you, Mother will collapse immediately.
What about you?
What do you think?
You'd surely be happy... celebrating.
Of course. If you don't want me to get mad,
stop saying nonsense. Stay alive.
Don't go, Oppa.
I'm scared.
What did you say?
Uncle stays outside the toilet
to protect Sister-in-law.
Do that for me too.
I will never do that.
I might as well run away from home.
How cold-blooded.
Dae Bak. Dae Bak.
Didn't you ask me to wake you up?
What are you doing?
Nothing, Hyeongnim.
Go back to sleep.
But the floor is too cold.
Your knees must be cold.
Sleep in the room.
Sorry. I should sleep here instead.
If I let you sleep here,
In-law will kill me.
Hyeongnim, not there.
Mother, it's me.
Hurry, lie down beside me.
Oh, you must be freezing.
No.
It's cold.
There's hot water in the kitchen.
I've already boiled some.
Is that so?
There was none.
None?
This angle.
One more.
Did you finish all the hot water in the kitchen?
Yes, I washed my hair.
How could you finish it?
I boiled that for people leaving in the morning.
What happened to ranking?
Stop scolding her.
She's our family's treasure.
This is the first time I've ever
heard that in my life.
She's not our treasure,
she's a troublemaker.
Then what are you?
Kimchi jar.
Right?
Right! Kimchi jar.
I think my stomach's getting bigger each day.
How big can your stomach grow?
It looks different every time I take a photo.
Have a look.
Forget it.
How can that be possible?
It will only grow big on the 5th month.
Let me see that.
It's true.
Right?
It looks bigger than yesterday.
Ajubeonim, look at my stomach.
Stop showing off.
Be more sensible.
You don't show that to your brother-in-law.
- Son, it seems like you're not eating much.
- I don't have an appetite.
How can he have an appetite?
Sleeping on cold floors in winter,
he can't use the toilet in the morning,
he has to run all the way to school just to poop.
The hot water was also stolen by Sister-in-law in the morning,
he had to use cold water to wash his face.
At his old age,
what strength does he have?
Can he eat sumptuously?
Of course, he won't have an appetite.
It's because he's full.
Try and starve him,
he will surely eat--
Yes, Sister-in-law.
It's probably because I'm full.
If I get hungry,
I will surely eat ravenously.
For me, it's really fun to eat here.
The whole family eats together so I have to eat fast
otherwise there'll be nothing left to eat.
It makes it so much fun.
I'm really going crazy.
Eat more.
Don't be afaid.
Will I let you starve?
If only you can contribute
more to living expense.
There are several meals in a day.
If you don't exercise and just eat,
the baby will become very big.
We have a kimchi jar in our house
so food is really delicious.
Hey, but we're missing a person.
Dae Bak.
Dae Bak ran away from home, too?
He's studying.
Dae Bak?
Hurry up.
The lunch time customers will be here soon.
Is earning money easy?
Other ladies finish it in 30 minutes.
It takes you an hour.
Only I can endure you.
Try and go somewhere else.
You're almost out the door.
I was already chased away.
Thank you, Boss.
You will be blessed.
You participated in Miss Korea.
What happened to you?
It's a long story.
Life has no answer.
Looks like you have a bundle of stories to tell.
What's a bundle?
It's a truckload.
It's me, Mother-in-law.
I want to see you for a moment.
I have something to say.
I want to see you too.
Your call came just in time.
When can you come?
- Now.
- Now?
Turn around.
Why are you so surprised?
Your family gets shocked whenever they see me.
I came just in time right?
I locked the gate.
How did you come in?
This.
If I have this, there's no door that I can't unlock.
You didn't apologize to me sincerely,
so I couldn't sleep.
Have a seat.
I'll prepare some tea.
Mother-in-law.
What did you say?
The gold key.
Give it back.
Including tie clip and gold cufflinks too.
Are you dreaming?
I know you took them.
Oh my god.
Who the hell are you?
I took them away?
You dare accuse your mother-in-law of stealing?
This won't do.
I need to call Sang Nam.
Call him.
What?
Do you want to call Sang Nam and
go to the police station together?
How dare you?
Hey!
I'm not 'Hey'.
I won't give up until you give them back.
That's not an ordinary key.
That's a gift given to him by his staff to commemorate
10 years of his hard work at the company.
It 's an evidence of Father-in-law's hard work.
How could you steal that?
That's not just gold.
Give it back while I'm talking nicely.
This matter will get bigger
if I call the cops.
Are you really going to do this?
Did you see me take it?
You entered his room that day.
You accuse me of being a thief
just because I entered his room?
You're really hopeless.
How could you report your mother-in-law to the police?
Fine! Let's go to the police station. Let's go!
You really want to go?
Yes, let's go!
Who's afraid?
Fine, since you're like this,
I have no choice.
I'll buy that.
What?
You won't get much money
if you sell those.
I'll pay double the market price.
Do-double?
Yes.
I won't tell anyone.
Just pretend I caught you.
Sell it to me.
You won't lose anything.
I will keep my promise.
I'll keep this a secret from Sang Nam and Father.
Re-really?
Of course.
It's troublesome to report this to the police.
Then, give me triple.
That's too much.
How could you ask for triple?
Instead, the tie clip and cuff... that thing.
I'll give them to you.
I won't get much money if I sell those.
Fine.
I have to give you money anyway.
I'll give you triple.
In cash.
Give them to me.
I can't now.
They're at home.
Come by tomorrow.
When there's no one around.
Don't regret it.
Don't worry.
This.
What are you doing?
These are good clothes.
Can I take these?
You can't.
I'll let you off this time.
Take those other good ones too.
It's coffee time now.
Do you want to come?
The pretty ajummas are all
gathering together.
I'm not interested in those ladies.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
I'm really going crazy!
Hey, hey, hey!
This is our new member, No. 505.
- Hi.
Hello.
I'm Heo-Heo Se dal.
We don't need names here.
Numbers will do.
I am No. 505.
How handsome.
Oh, there's no need to be shy.
We're all the same.
Come and have a seat.
Yes.
So... What happened?
What else?
She searched his cellphone.
Then caught him right away,
then she splashed it with water immediately.
Well done.
She must have felt
so much better after that.
Nowadays, you can catch an affair
by searching the cellphone.
You can't leave men alone.
Once outside, they will roll
their eyes here and there.
No. 505. Try it.
Roll your eyes around.
You'll be good at it.
Your eyes are so protruded.
- That's right.
- That's right. He can surely do it.
Like this? Roll here. Roll there.
Well done.
You passed.
But which family are you talking about?
We're talking about a drama.
Ah, everyone was so serious,
I thought it was real.
Nowadays, women are also like that.
You know that No. 103 is having an affair, right?
The guard was the first one to find out.
He saw how she was dressed.
The in thing nowadays is
"Office wife and office husband".
What is that?
They act like husband and wife at work.
Is to get engage in affair use English have said
seems like how about it the same?
Oh...
It's me.
Are you going to be late tonight?
I have a company dinner tonight.
Around what time will it end?
I don't know.
Will there be drinking?
There will be since it's a company gathering.
Who will go?
Why are you asking those questions?
So what if there's drinking?
Why do you want to know who's going?
You have nothing to do at home.
Sin Dong's mom!
Really.
It suits you.
Newly wed's memoir.
How about it?
Newly wed's memoir?
You can interview other people
or base it from your experience.
The topic is,
"Things we don't know about married life."
Let's reveal the true facets of marriage.
What do you think?
This will make all the old maids happy.
But you just got married,
I don't think you qualify.
No, I think I have plenty to say.
I'm giving you work since I feel bad for you.
Do it well.
Thank you, Team Leader.
Bread?
I ate it.
I'll buy you another one
after I get my pay.
Mom.
Mi Ho.
Oh, you're back.
How was it? Did you have fun?
You didn't get hurt, did you?
I'm going to see Oppa first.
Geez. Children are useless.
Oppa, what happened to you?
I kept calling you but I couldn't reach you.
Are you having an affair?
I don't even have time to have an affair.
What have you been up to these days?
You saw any pretty girls?
You'll get it from me
if I catch you.
I don't have time to look at pretty girls.
We moved house.
You moved?
When?
It's too long to talk about it.
I need to go in and study.
Studying is the only path I can take.
Are you sure you're all right?
Did you get beaten up?
I'm perfectly fine.
My family is totally bankrupt.
What?
Mom, Mom.
Really?
Dae Bak's family lost everything and
they moved to another place.
Is it going well?
No.
Eat this while you write.
Thank you, Aunt.
What topic are you writing about?
Nothing.
It's just, I write whatever's asked of me.
Why didn't you tell me?
I just heard from Mi Ho.
I heard your family's having a hard time.
You heard?
It must be very hard on you.
You just got married and this thing happened.
What to do?
Even if you're married now,
with what happened to your family,
you must be really worried.
I know how you feel.
It was my father's birthday yesterday.
If I told him,
he might have come with me.
I couldn't tell him.
You should have told me.
Please keep this a secret from Sang Nam.
Don't tell Father-in-law either.
I don't want them to find out
about what happened to my family.
I know.
It hurts the pride and
you'll feel dejected too.
I know how it feels since I've
experienced it from my sister.
No wonder you don't look good these days.
I thought you were having a hard time here.
Who knew it was like this?
Please don't tell Sang Nam.
I'll find a chance to tell him.
Please give me 2 hoteoks.
~ Pretty princess. ~
Is it delicious?
Yes, delicious.
Rotten brat.
Who did he take after?
So stingy!
He only bought 2 hoteoks?
That's discrimination.
I'm not eating this.
It's our Wang Dal that's eating this.
Who's Wang Dal?
My baby's nickname is Wang Dal.
Are nicknames still popular?
Is there honey inside?
I don't know.
I think it's just sugar.
It's sugar.
Is there pine nut as well?
I think so.
I can't let you try it though.
It must be delicious.
Watching other people eat is
the most annoying thing to do.
Don't look.
I can't help it,
my eyes keeps lingering there.
I have bad luck today.
I wanted to share this actually
but this is not enough.
I wasn't like this before. Ever since I have Wang Dal,
I really don't know why I keep thinking about food.
I'll eat this inside.
I'll annoy you if I stay here.
See, Mother?
Babying your youngest is useless.
Since he's buying,
why not buy a few more to let you try.
I'm not saying this because I want to eat.
You told me to love your children in your heart.
But you're being totally ignored now.
It's going to happen more often next time.
That kid, really...
Give me your baby.
I'll take care of him.
- Thank you.
- It's nothing.
Just give me 10 minutes.
10 minutes is enough.
This kid.
Take care of the baby.
Yes.
You don't miss the children?
Take care of your kids.
The kids like my mother more.
I can't attend Ae Ji's program today.
I regret marrying you.
I also regret having the children.
Good enough?
Red light, green light, white light.
Where the heck were you?
You're too much.
I pay you on time every week.
The customers are coming
and the vegies are not cut yet.
The bowls are not washed yet.
You said you'd come back in an hour.
What time is it now?
Sorry.
I'll do it right away.
Do you think it's easy to earn money?
I know.
I know it very well.
~ Go to sleep.
My Jung Ji is really obedient. ~
I wonder where your mom is
and what she's doing.
Is she eating properly?
Is she sleeping well?
Jung Ji.
Ask your mom to come back soon.
Say, "Hurry, come back, Mom."
"Hurry, come back, Mom."
Nuna!
She has a heart too.
Just to give her child food to eat,
she left this milk at the entrance and left.
Imagine how heartbroken she must have felt.
She must be having a hard time
living alone.
Only people who have experienced work should work.
She has never even washed her own underwear.
Where is she and what is she doing
to buy her child this powdered milk?
This girl, really...
I feel bad for Su Bak.
I used to hate her before.
Why did you stop chasing her?
I was yelling "Nuna, Nuna" while running,
but it was so dark and I couldn't see clearly.
Husband, let's find Su Bak.
Let's go to the police.
Just wait.
She'll come home when it's time.
Since she already came,
we know she's alive so there's no need to worry.
Come, let's go to sleep.
Why isn't Mom back yet?
She'll come.
Dad, be careful. Mom is pretty.
What if other men like her?
Mom is not pretty at all.
She is.
Other men are all looking at her.
Mom might get stolen away.
Right?
Come, let's have a toast.
For the sake of our success.
Cheers. Cheers. Cheers.
Manager.
- Cheers.
=The number you dialed is unavailable.=
Oh, come on.
Why didn't you pick up?
Where are you?
Who are you with?
Did you drink a lot?
Are you with another man?
Hey, hey. Wang Ho Bak!
I'm really going crazy.
What to do?
I had lots of fun today.
- I'm going.
- What the?
What are you doing?
Why did you come out?
Say hello.
He's my children's father.
Hello.
Although, I can't bear to part with her,
I'll leave Department Head with you.
Please take care of us, Department Head.
Fine. Take care.
See you tomorrow.
Department head.
You were great today.
Sweet dreams.
Okay.
Sin Dong mom. Hey.
Lie down.
Department head.
Did you get home safely?
You were awesome today.
Department head, you were so cool.
You were really sexy.
Did you get home safely?
My Department Head, I love you.
Fighting.
Are you crazy?
Ouch.
Open the door.
Why aren't you opening the door?
Open the door for me.
Why aren't you opening it?
Are you sleeping, Oppa?
Wang Dal wants to eat noodles.
Tell him to sleep.
He's not sleepy at all?
Are you going to do this?
Our Wang Dal wants to eat it.
Fine.
Sister-in-law!
Eat.
Hot, hot.
Drink slowly.
Mix some rice.
Well done. Good job.
A woman who drinks outside.
The husband who makes bean sprout soup.
This family is really something else.
How refreshing.
I can live now.
That punk who took you home last night,
who is he?
Someone took me home?
You don't know?
I don't remember.
This is a big problem.
You really don't remember?
This woman...
What if someone kidnaps you?
Who will kidnap me?
A young punk drove you home.
Who was it?
Oh, yes. My staff.
How could you call him young punk?
How mean.
Every time he opened his mouth,
he kept saying, "My Department Head."
I couldn't take it anymore.
Why am I so freaking mad
at that word, "My"?
I get mad everytime "My Go son-in-law" was mentioned too.
Don't tell me you two are playing
"Office wife, office husband"?
Where did you hear that from?
The ajummas told me.
They said it's the in-thing nowadays.
Don't bother about that.
You have nothing to do everyday,
you keep sticking to those ajummas.
Why did you say that?
There's plenty of things to do at home.
Don't talk like that.
It hurts my pride.
Text messages kept coming all night.
Ding dong, ding dong.
Why are you invading my privacy?
And also,
why did you keep calling me yesterday?
I told you I had a company dinner.
What exactly did you do on
your company dinner?
"Department head is sexy, cool, awesome."
You really want to know?
Yes, otherwise, do it in front of me again.
I will really do it.
How about it?
Oh, come on.
You... Don't do that despicable act of
peeking at my text messages again.
Despicable?
Yes, when have I ever done that despicable act?
I don't even have a cellphone.
Even dogs have cellphones now.
Only I don't have one.
So? Are you unhappy?
N-no.
Don't hang out with those ajummas.
They talk about nonsense all day long.
Which apartment's wife is doing what?
Which apartment's husband is doing what?
Don't do that.
Stop watching dramas too.
Read the newspaper.
You don't even read books?
If I don't watch drama,
I'll be isolated.
What?
I don't have a friend.
Good thing those ajummas
would hang out with me.
Are you an ajumma?
One half.
Eat.
Mom.
Let's go.
No, I'm working.
What work?
Let's go.
Mom, you can't do this.
Come with me.
It's still useless even if you do this.
It's useful.
Go to school right away.
With our family's situation,
can I still go to uni?
Even if I have to sell myself,
I will provide for you.
Don't worry.
Hurry, go in.
I can get a scholarship at marine university.
I can still attend university,
even if I don't have money.
Mom, I want to become a ship captain.
I don't want to be a judge.
You still don't understand me?
Just give in this time.
Can't you give in to me this time?
Listen to Mom's wish.
Do you want to see Mom live miserably
in that house forever?
Everything will be fine as long as you become a judge.
You alone can save the whole family.
Mom, being a judge is not some lottery ticket.
Even if I become a judge,
money won't rain on us at once.
Shut up!
Go home.
Oh my. Hey!
Father, sorry.
I didn't tell you earlier.
Do you know why your mom's like that?
Yes. If I if I knew that our family
would become like this,
even if being a ship captain was my dream,
I would have listened to Mom's wish.
But this is my future.
I've already decided.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
I want to become a ship captain but
Mom keeps stopping me.
I don't know if I should think
go back to review school again.
I'm worried.
Father, what should I do?
Life is long.
Look far ahead.
Choose the path you won't regret
10 or 20 years down the road.
Whatever you choose,
it's fine with me.
You can pursue your dream or
listen to Mom and become a judge.
Try and write these on a piece of paper.
Weigh the pros and cons of each path.
You will find the answer if you list it down like that.
You can only decide this yourself,
no one else can.
It's your life.
- Welcome. Sit over there.
- 2 bowls of tofu stew please.
- Yes. Boss, 2 bowls of tofu stew please.
Yes.
Hello.
It's me. Where are you now?
The court sent me the papers.
I think we need to meet one more time.
Ajumma, the tofu is ready.
What are you doing?
It's work hours.
Take care of it yourself.
These are the divorce papers.
Yes.
Have you submitted the papers
I gave to you already?
No, not yet.
When's the deadline?
Up to today.
If we don't process that today,
you know that it won't be valid anymore, right?
You won't be divorced.
No, Mom.
Eonni might do that.
But Brother-in-law won't do that.
What about your sister?
Go son-in-law is acting strange.
Otherwise, why does he want a divorce?
Find out what kind of woman she is.
What's the use of finding out?
They're over.
We can get compensation if they got
divorced because he had an affair.
To be honest, Eonni's not that honest either.
What do you mean she's not?
She just made a little mistake before marriage.
Was that a mistake?
If done at a marrying age,
perhaps it's okay with both sets of parents' consents.
Without any plans and thoughts,
a university student co-habitating without her parent's knowledge.
How can that be considered a mistake?
That was a huge blunder.
It's because he doesn't know.
Who will be happy if they hear that?
Whether male or female.
If Sin Dong's dad did that,
I would never forgive him.
Please receive this.
Okay.
The divorce papers is already received.
Then, am I considered divorced?
Yes.
Today is the last day.
You almost missed it.
I don't know whether it's a good thing
or a bad thing though.
Oppa.
Congratulate me.
I am finally divorced.
You submitted the documents?
Yes.
It was quite simple.
The decision before that was hard.
After you hand that in,
you're divorced right away.
How do you feel?
Strange?
Of course.
On one hand, I feel relieved,
and a little expectant.
I'm looking forward to a hot romantic love with you.
I don't believe you.
It's true.
Nothing can stand in our way now.
I think you're a bad man.
Although I am only saying this now,
do you know how sad I was before?
About what?
Once something happened,
you asked me to come.
Another thing happened,
and you broke up with me.
Me?
See?
You're the classic bad man.
You conveniently forgot.
When Father was in the hospital,
you wanted to save,
so you used me.
"Sun Jeong, can you help me for a few days?"
You asked me politely.
But after he left the hospital,
you kept avoiding me.
"I can't meet you again."
"I don't need you. Go."
I was also going crazy.
You asked me to come, I came.
You asked me to go, I left.
After hearing that,
I'm really such a bad man.
Then why did you keep following me?
I wasn't following you.
You appeared on your own.
You're that kind of person.
I like you like that.
You are loyal.
You always treasure your family.
Although you made me cry,
you're that kind of guy.
In our 7 years of dating,
you never looked at another woman.
You were loyal all through out.
That's what I like about you.
You're a faithful man.
Congratulations.
Yes.
If you weren't there,
I would be drinking soju at home alone.
Seeing you makes me feel more at ease.
Since it's already like this,
let's have a party.
Divorced man and divorced woman.
Be honest with me.
Were you waiting for it?
How could you say that?
You really know me.
Check how long my neck
has become from waiting.
See?
Was it really like that?
I told you already.
Excuse me.
It's me.
Go son-in-law, what are you doing?
I have an appointment outside.
Have you eaten dinner?
Yes.
Are you busy lately?
You don't visit.
Ae Ji and Jung Ji ae looking for their dad.
Oppa!
I'll go tomorrow.
Okay.
You must come tomorrow.
Don't you pity your children?
Their mother is not around.
You should come by often.
Then, let's hang up.
Don't call Go son-in-law often.
I'm just calling for the children's sake.
Don't call him using the children as excuse.
He will feel uncomfortable.
Why would he feel uncomfortable?
He stopped coming here.
I was just curious,
so I gave him a call.
He's living alone,
I wonder if he's eating on time.
He'll take care of it.
I know you why you're like that.
Don't do that.
They already handed their divorced papers.
It's not final yet.
What is this?
Divorce Confirmation papers.
I saw it when I went to get the mail.
Go son-in-law must have gotten his already.
They will be strangers already
if he submitted it.
Don't keep calling him,
it will make him uncomfortable.
The children are our grandchildren.
Of course, we should raise them.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
I'm thinking about it.
Maybe walk around.
I heard that you were in a bad mood today.
So I came to see you immediately.
Not only today.
Children are enemies.
Both my son and daughter.
It's really cold.
Where do you want to go?
Where there's plenty of people.
Crowded places.
What?
It's cold. We should go to a place
where there's plenty of people.
I will keep you warm.
Let's go where there's no one around.
It's boring if there's no one around.
How about it?
Not cold anymore?
Yes. I really love people hugging me.
Whether it's over the shoulders
or tight embrace.
There's no one around.
It's fun.
Am I right?
I forgot all about my problems.
Tell me if you're hungry.
I'm not hungry.
Let's walk some more.
Yes.
I feel at ease now.
The divorce papers came.
Before Go son-in-law submits it,
meet him and ask for forgiveness.
You have children, you must reconcile.
Sister-in-law, I'll go ahead.
Bye, Brother-in-law.
Goodbye, Father-in-law.
Aunt, I'm leaving.
I think I'll be going to China one of these days.
Yes.
Ask them what contracts we need
to prepare for signature.
I was thinking of doing that too.
Aunt. Now?
Okay.
Is that true?
Yes.
You wife asked me to keep it a secret from you.
But I just can't take it anymore.
How could such a thing like that happen?
They even moved house?
Yes. They moved to a house with only 2 rooms.
How could she not tell me?
Aunt, couples can't be like this.
Even so, she still has pride.
You just got married,
and her family went bankrupt.
It's embarrassing and hurts the pride.
Anyone will feel a sudden loss of self-confidence.
That happens.
How can that happen?
We are husband and wife.
She must be having a really hard time.
Don't tell Brother-in-law.
Just comfort her.
Hello, Mother-in-law.
Do you want some tea?
Before that, let's exchange what we need to exchange.
Yes.
Give that to me first.
You really won't tell them?
No.
This is our secret.
Of course.
Then, give it to me first.
You should give them to me first.
I've already taken the envelope out.
You should take them out too.
Open them.
Why should I?
Open it first.
I need to check first.
Then, let me see what's inside the envelope too.
You can't do this.
You're something else.
I went to university.
Then, I can't give this money to you.
We are really alike.
If we open a teahouse,
it will do really well.
Good enough?
Give that to me.
Let's exchange simultaneously.
1. 2. 3, then let go.
1... 2...
You're really something else.
How did you know that I'd snatch
it away at the count of 2?
I went to university and
I used to be a teacher.
What's this?
What did you do?
You deceived me.
I just took back what you stole.
I have no reason for giving you money.
I am your mother-in-law.
How could you do this to me?
How did you treat me?
I did everything I could for you.
I gave you 10 million Won behind Sang Nam's back.
Although Sang Nam was hurt when he was little,
do you know how happy he is to see you now?
As long as Sang Nam's wound can be healed,
I can bear the castigations.
But, you even stole Father's gold key,
and drove a wedge between
Sang Nam and me.
I can't endure it any longer.
What are you enduring?
I'm already indulging you and you dare...
Sang Nam. Sang Nam. Sang Nam.
Listen to me.
She is framing me.
Sang Nam, listen to me.
Sang Nam.
Get out.
I told you to leave!
I'm really embarrassed that I even
tried to treat you like a mom.
I really regret meeting you again.
I feel really wretched because
you gave birth to me!
I want to draw out all the blood in my body.
I even called a person like you mother.
I regret calling you mom.
Sang Nam.
Please leave.
Don't say anything.
Get out.
Sang Nam.
I'm really sorry that things ended up like this.
It would have been better
if only you and me know about this.
Later, after a long time has passed,
when Sang Nam's ready to accept you as mother again,
I will call you.
Then, goodbye.
Why did you come back?
I could have settled it.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm really speechless.
Sang Nam.
You must be really heartbroken, right?
It would have been better
if you didn't know.
No, I should know what I need to know.
But why didn't you tell me
about what happened to your family?
Why didn't you tell me?
We are husband and wife.
You heard from Aunt?
Yes.
How could you keep that a secret?
It must be very hard having to bear it alone.
Fool.
I'm really lacking compared to you.
I still have a long way to go
before I mature.
I'm not your husband.
Go Min Jeong and Wang Su Bak
are already divorced.
It's here.
Oppa.
Hello.
Yes.
What are you doing here?
I know someone here.
I came to see someone here too.
Is our Gwang Bak doing well?
Yes.
I'll rely on you.
As the middle person,
please help her.
Yes.
Then, go.
Bye.
I'm back.
Is it snowing?
Yes, it's snowing.
Really?
-=Next Episode Preview.=-
You know who the head of Dae Se Heavy Industries is, right?
Who are you to use informal language at me?
You actually dare.
I will make up for all the hurt you had before.
It feels like I'm falling in love with you again.
They said couples can still start again
after a divorce.
Mother-in-law, we've already...
You're making him feel uncomfortable.
Why do you keep doing that?
You have children.
Mom, please.
Just go.
Our destiny ends here.
It won't end here.
Although Go son-in-law didn't say anything.
He is definitely with another woman.
What face do I have to hold on to him?
Wake up.
Don't let another woman take him away.
-=Episode 42=-
-=Confirmation of Intention to Divorce Application Form=-
-=Marriage is...=-
-=Missed calls=-
-=Family Registry Application=-
-=Ae Ji father=-
-=Seoul Family Court=-
-=Confirmation of Intention to Divorce Application Form=-