Subtitles by DramaFever
Mr. Chairman... Please let me go.
What are you doing?
Get him to kneel down.
Honey!
Get up.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Gosh, why did you come here?
I'm not here to see you.
I came to see the chairman.
I'm glad you are here too, Gi Bum.
What brought you here?
I am here to show you something.
You know who that is, right?
They would risk their
lives for Director Baek.
Ah... I didn't do that intentionally.
It was an accident!
I was going to just scare him.
But he tripped over and died.
It's true, Tae Soo! It's true!
Dad, please believe me.
Do you know what kind of guy Mr. Son was?
He was a loser, swindler, and gambler!
He lost all of your three
billion won at the casino!
It says the borrower is my husband, huh?
If you and I were drowning in the water
Which of us do you think
Tae Soo would save first?
If this place is on fire
who would he save first?
He risked his life for you for 20 years.
But framing him for a
murder was not enough.
You had to make him sign an
IOU for three billion won?
Let's go, Honey.
Dad...
What an idiot.
Dummy!
[Episode 4]
Oh, gosh!
Ah...
Eun Ok!
You don't have to thank me.
The one who saved you is the lady in
charge of the neighborhood council.
Huh?
Kyung Mee.
Eun Ok, did you hear about Tae Soo's
IOU for three billion won?
Gosh...
Eun Ok, what brought you
here at this hour?
I'm sorry... but can I check
the black box footage from last week?
My husband said it got deleted
because it had a small memory card.
Tae Soo asked about it last night too.
Is something going on?
Am I fooling a ghost here?
I saw it with my own eyes.
You can't deny it!
You threw away trash here
at 11:40 PM last night.
Huh?
You did it at 11:13 PM the night before.
Should I say the seconds too?
It's not like you're poor.
Buy your own trash bags!
Chairwoman of the Neighborhood Council!
Seriously... Huh?
- Ma'am!
- You scared me!
Ma'am! How do you know that?
How you do you know they
threw away trash here?
How? Please answer me!
Over there.
What's wrong?
Where are you going?
I have to say what I couldn't
say to the chairman!
Are you crazy?
Why do you think I went to
him, not to the police?
That way, you could live and
it wouldn't get too big.
What is it that you want to do there?
Gosh.
Didn't you see how pale his face turned?
And Baek Gi Bum had the sorriest excuse!
They are that kind of people!
What will do you now?
We've seen everything about them.
You can't go back!
I, Yoon Tae Soo...!
I quit as of today!
Even if I make one million won a month
You will be able to sleep
well at night, Eun Ok!
Geez, I'm so glad to hear that!
You finally grew up!
Now that I decided to do that
it feels great!
Sure! Why not!
I'll make it work no matter how
little money you bring home.
We won't send the kids to
the afterschool programs.
Sung Min and Soo Min will dance
around because they're happy!
Ding Dong Dang!
Our house is the chairman's.
We can just live on the street!
Let's buy a tent!
There are many good ones!
Where should we put it up?
We need to use water and a restroom.
Maybe right next to a public restroom?
We can handle the smell...
And we can just eat
the free samples at the market!
Or we can get free meals
at Mom's senior center!
I love that!
We could even save some
money if we did that!
I'm still going to spend
5,000 won on Lotto tickets.
Of course.
Without that...
What hope would we have to hold on to?
Geez, why do you say that?
I'm losing my appetite for
alcohol over the word, hope.
Gosh.
Geez.
- I'm going to die.
What's going on here?
Oh?
Madam Lee Choon Boon!
What the heck is going on?
Hey, how much did you drink?
It just happened.
Oh, Mother!
Please don't be harsh.
Today, I did something amazing!
Today I saved your son, Yoon Tae Soo!
You should praise me for that, Mother.
If you praise me, I will forget
everything and forgive you!
What the heck is she talking about?
Get off me! You are stinky!
Give me a high five!
High five!
Geez, calm down!
Wow!
Gosh, go in the room.
The kids are watching.
Why? Go on, Mom!
Give me an interview!
Please make me look
beautiful like an actress.
My ugly, pretty daughter!
Drink some water, Mom.
Good.
My son was here too!
Did you cry? Why are your eyes so red?
Who cried?
Sung Min!
You're the best, my son!
You know what my wishes are.
No matter what, you must
go to a college in Seoul.
At least one of the top three schools!
If you go to Seoul University
I will dance in the middle
of a road in Seoul!
Seoul University! My son got
admitted to Seoul University!
My son goes to Seoul University!
Mom!
Mom...
Mom loves Seoul University!
I'm sorry, Mom. I'll take her.
Let's go, honey.
- Let's go.
- Love ya!
Mother! I love you!
- I love you, Soo Min!
- Let's go to sleep.
What a beautiful night!
Love you!
Oh, my blood pressure.
Oh, yes! I got you, Mom.
I love you!
Oh...
Geez.
Geez. Let me see.
Why is it that life sucks?
Do you remember this place?
How can I forget?
Without you, this would
have been my burial site.
Was it about 15 years ago?
You and I hid here and barely survived.
I made up my mind then.
From now on, Tae Soo is my son.
Tae Soo.
About Gi Bum...
I'll just think that he doesn't exist.
So do whatever you want with him.
I'll send him to the Philippines
if you say so.
Even if you turn him to the
police, I can't say much.
How will you live without Gi Bum?
Is he my only child?
I have you too, Tae Soo.
It's all my fault.
A horse running in the wild doesn't have
the time to take care of his stable.
That's how I spoiled Gi Bum.
Now that he's so immature
he's becoming a disgrace to me.
Mr. Chairman.
Will you do as I say?
What do you want?
Promise me first.
Gi Bum...
He's my dearest friend.
I'm the one who owes him.
Anyway, he took care of
someone who deserved to die.
And I'm proven innocent.
So I am the one who
owes him a drink.
Do you mean it?
Do you think you can
let go of everything?
Yes.
You always said if the result
is good, everything is good.
This is that kind of situation.
Then... what about the movie?
Of course I should make it.
I was even on TV as a movie maker.
Also, I should make sure you look good.
Tae Soo.
Geez, look at you.
You got so thin because
of all that stress.
Don't worry about the movie.
I will take care of it.
Why are you outside? It's cold!
Honey, are you really okay?
Of course I am.
Thank you for coming back safely.
Oh, man!
People might think we are
shooting a movie here.
You're frozen. Let's go in.
You might catch a cold.
Are you sober now?
I was all over the place
last night, right?
I don't know. I saw nothing.
Soo Min took a video of it.
- It's cold!
- Why is it so cold?
You just recovered from a cold.
Are you up?
You haven't slept much
since you came home late.
Is something going on?
Director Baek didn't come home
last night.
I can't really talk about it.
Just pretend you don't know.
I'm disappointed if you do this.
I can't blame anyone.
He's like money bouncing
around, not doing anything good.
It's my fault. I'm always on his case.
It feels like I lost two sons
at the same time.
How about making him a family?
He's lost because he has
no family to take care of.
That's why he keeps causing
trouble for you.
You know his ex-wife and
daughter came back to Daejeon?
Don't even mention them.
I have no business with them.
Oh...
I used less whipped cream
and put lots of fruits.
Was it obvious I was on a diet?
Why don't you sit if you aren't too busy?
Should I?
I know I might be rude to say this...
But I know about you and Director Baek.
It's all in the past.
Perhaps...
The chairman doesn't like me
coming back here...
Are you here to tell me that?
Oh, no. Please don't misunderstand.
Then... why?
Well.... let's say I'm just
curious about you, Do Kyung.
It's like, you are attracted
to certain people.
You're someone I can relate to.
Wow, you and I are definitely
thinking the same thing!
You felt so familiar from the beginning.
Where did you live in Seoul?
Seoul...? Mostly... in Gangnam...
But...
You wouldn't have seen me
because I lived abroad mostly.
Well...
Could it be the Indian consul's
party last summer?
Didn't you come to the party?
Not at all.
Well, maybe because you are so beautiful
I might have thought you
were an actress I knew.
Oh, please...!
I would like to treat you like
my own sister from now on.
If that's okay with you.
Thank you.
Please have some, Sister.
[Missing Person]
What the heck! What is this, Boss?
Gosh.
What are you doing? Take it off!
Take it off?
I said take them off!
Hey.
Did you see them, honey?
Where the heck are you?
Ma'am...
You can't report a missing person
until it's been five years.
For now, you can report a runaway.
I said it's an accident, not a runaway.
You can't insist that
when there's no evidence.
There's an order of business
in everything.
My goodness, you are so dense.
That's why you are still
in that position.
Were you born in August?
Year of Dog?
How do you know...?
What's the date of your birth?
It's eighth.
Oh... geez.
It's one of the hottest days of the year.
Gosh.
You went through a lot, right?
The spirit says a good thing
will happen in the new year.
Yeah?
She says watch your steps.
She says dig with your front legs.
Please help me find him.
My son is missing.
Please help me find my son.
Please help!
He talks like a Seoulite.
Gosh, we're going to die from running!
Honey, are we having a punishment?
What are you doing? Take them off!
They are all over the town!
Someone's there!
It could have been bad.
- Are they gone?
- Really?
Yeah.
Be careful! We almost got caught!
I was so focused I didn't see them!
It drives me nuts! When are we
going to take them all off?
Are we going to be okay?
What do you mean?
Did we do something?
Just focus! Okay?
Over there! It's totally covered!
Be natural. Be natural.
Be natural...
Oh...
What are the bags for?
Oh... it's nothing.
Say hello. She's my friend.
- Oh, hello.
- Hello.
You must be her son.
And you are her daughter in-law.
Yes.
I'll bring something to eat.
Okay.
Sit over here.
Sure.
Oh, Tae Soo!
This is an amazing coincidence!
How could I run into the
Shaman of Mia-ri there like that!
Shaman of what?
She says she's a famous shaman in Seoul.
She has hundreds of regulars!
You know what's even more interesting?
What is it?
She's the mother of the man.
Who is that man?
The man you're making a movie with!
I told him he had a lucky face.
What?
Why are you so surprised?
We were just worried about him.
Because his business partner
has been out of touch.
I see a knife in your physiognomy.
Pardon?
What does that mean?
Actually he's well-known
for his fist in Daejeon.
- Mom...
- Yeah?
Okay.
Why did you have one child?
You didn't want a son?
It's not true.
We have a son. My oldest is a son.
Well... he doesn't look like you at all!
That's why he's a good student at school.
He ranks first in his class.
Gosh, this isn't the time for
me to tell others' fortunes.
My son is missing!
Okay.
Anyway she'll stay with us
until she finds her son.
Just know that, okay?
Sure...
Get him! Get him!
Get him!
Hey, beat him!
Stop!
You!
Step aside.
Huh?
Mr. Son, are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Huh?
A dead body doesn't hurt.
Oh... oh...
Ah!
See you soon.
What's wrong?
No... it was a dream.
I had a nightmare.
Could it be that... she knows something?
You saw her scary eyes, right?
Yeah.
Well, it can't be.
If she knew something
she would've reported it.
Sleep now.
I have something to do.
Okay.
You scared me!
What are you doing here?
I'm praying!
My goodness!
What are you doing?
You totally scared me!
Geez.
Did you have a nightmare?
Pardon?
No...
I came out to go to the bathroom.
Please answer me!
My poor son, Se Yoon!
Just like that, that feeling!
Pavane!
Cry if you want to cry.
Don't save your tears if it's for an art!
Should I make you shed tears and blood?
Pardon?
Huh?
I have no comments on that.
Is this all you can do, huh?
That's the most expensive item here.
You can break anything except for that!
It's the most expensive here!
Oh!
Luckily, Mr. Yoon is here!
Oh, what brought you here?
She wanted to see where her son worked.
So we came.
Excuse me.
Huh?
Are you the director?
You work for Se Yoon?
How do you know...
What happened to my son?
Why are you still here when my son isn't?
It wasn't me...
Oh...
What... what is it?
Hmm?
Perhaps this is...
That belongs to Mr. Son.
Oh... Se Yoon is asking
me to find him quickly.
He's shouting, "Mom, find me!"
Se Yoon!
Is this Choong Shin Construction
that invested in the movie?
Yes, it is.
Oh, he's coming here!
Gi Bum!
Oh!
What brought you here?
This is the man, who I told you
was really close to your son!
Who is she?
She's Mr. Son's mother.
What?
Something happened between
you and my son, right?
What do you mean? It's just
that things went wrong...
He did it first... I didn't
do that intentionally...
Just tell her the truth.
You spilled hot soup over his pants.
His thigh was burned a little.
Yes, it was my fault... hot soup...
his thigh...
Is that all?
Well... that's...
Gi Bum, you always did that.
You still do that?
You should be more careful.
Oh, yes.
I am going to pray in
Gyeryong Mountain tonight.
I am sure... I will get an answer.
Did you buy whipped cream
and condensed milk?
Okay, I got it.
Come on in!
I'll close the store for a moment.
Why did you come back?
My contract didn't say I couldn't
come back to my hometown.
You are still arrogant.
You didn't change a bit.
Don't even think about
ruining my son's life.
Just go back while I'm still nice.
Do you still think
I ruined Gi Bum's life?
You should be thankful that I let
you keep the money and your child!
What the heck are you trying
to do, using your child?
Is it money?
Think what you like.
Aren't you embarrassed to your child?
No, I have nothing to be
ashamed of or afraid of.
You're doing this for your child, right?
It's likewise.
I won't let you kick me out like before!
How dare!
You kicked out all the
customers, and now it's us?
Hyun Jee!
What have we done so wrong?
I asked her to move down here.
Don't do this to my mom!
Hyun Jee! Hyun Jee!
Hyun Jee!
Well, do you have an upbeat song?
I'm totally gloomy today.
Gosh.
You're ignoring me again? Hey.
Don't pretend to be so chic.
I remember how dumb you
were when you were little.
Hey!
Stop bothering me!
I'm not interested in you!
We are lovers from now on.
It means I'm your owner
and you are my servant.
If you understand, say yes.
Yes, Hyun Jee.
Do you remember it now?
It's not enough pretending
to be a singer?
Now you're making a movie?
Is she your girlfriend?
Wow, she's...
Cute!
Let's go.
Bastard! You ignore us again?
Hey!
You better just go your way.
I'm not in a good mood today.
Bitch!
You!
Hey!
I can't see!
Cops!
Oh, Sung Min! Sung Min!
What?
What happened to your face?
What on earth happened?
I'm fine, Mom.
You are not fine at all!
You should've been at cram school!
Why are you here?
Hyun Jee!
Hyun Jee?
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Aren't you hurt?
Man!
It seems that those kids bothered them.
We already got the story.
Please sign here and you can go home.
You can take them.
Guys, next time...
Have a date in a bright
spot, not in the dark alley.
Got it?
Wait a minute, Officer.
Oh... no.
What do you mean by date?
How could you say that?
My child isn't that kind of boy.
Even though slutty girls
keep bothering him
he never pays attention to them.
He only studies...
Watch your mouth.
Are you saying Hyun Jee tried to
seduce him when he didn't do anything?
And what do you mean by slutty girls?
Oh, my. Did it sound like that?
Your ears must be broken. I meant
my child wouldn't do that.
You're being oversensitive.
Let's say they did have a date.
When you raise a kid
all sorts of things can happen.
It's not like we are strangers.
Why do you make a big deal out of it?
Make a big deal?
Wow, you are so calm!
How can you say that when they
were brought to the police station?
How did you raise her in Seoul?
I raised her at ease,
not hovering over her.
I didn't raise him to be a brat!
Please stop.
You should stop too.
Sung Min, tell me the truth.
Why were you at the park and
not at cram school?
Did you really have a date with her?
Answer me. Why were you there with her?
It's my fault.
He tried to help me when those
kids were bothering me.
Sung Min did nothing wrong.
Did you hear that?
My son saved your daughter.
And it was definitely not a date.
Aren't you cold?
Thank you, Mom.
Tell me the truth.
Is it really true that
Sung Min saved you?
And you ran into him coincidentally?
Is that important?
By the way, his mom doesn't
seem to like you that much.
Was she like that before?
I guess she's guarded
because I'm too pretty.
Gosh.
Why isn't there anyone
here who welcomes us?
Like Grandpa...
Everyone hates me.
Don't say that.
You're making me feel bad.
Is that so?
By the way, I was totally
rude to Grandpa, right?
Don't worry. That felt good!
But don't do that again. Okay?
Since we feel gloomy,
should I sing a song, Mom?
Good!
Okay!
Okay.
What's wrong with you?
You never did this kind of thing.
Did you have to be like that?
It was embarrassing.
Embarrassing?
How can you say that in this situation?
Why did you skip your cram school?
What did you do?
You don't go to Seoul University
for free.
You've worked hard. But why
are you doing this now?
If you go to a good college, there
will be lots of nice girls.
Much nicer girls!
I'm tired. I'll go rest.
Hey, Yoon Sung Min!
Oh! Did you cause trouble?
Wow, you're a human! So cool!
Nice!
Soo Min causes enough trouble for me!
Do you have to add more trouble?
I just finished my homework!
Why do you treat me like that?
So annoying!
What? Hey, you!
I can't live like this!
Why did that fox come back?
She's making me upset!
Why the daughter of
Lee Do Kyung and Baek Gi Bum?
My head is already about to explode!
Please calm down. Do you want water?
By the way...
The shaman won't get answers
at Gyeryong Mountain, right?
I'm nervous, and your
mom is driving me nuts!
You're right.
Mom is being ridiculous!
Gosh.
It was my fault.
He was just trying to help me when
those kids were bothering me.
Sung Min did nothing wrong.
My name is Baek Hyun Jee.
I was a slacker in Seoul.
That's all.
So refreshing!
That's all. Go sit by Si Yeon.
Okay, let's have a good day!
Hyun Jee, I'm Young Jae.
Chang Young Jae.
From Love Preschool.
Oh, Young Jae!
Young Jae, can we trade seats?
Huh?
Thanks, Young Jae.
It's so nice to see you again.
It's been 10 years!
Hey, what are you doing?
I've been looking for you.
It seems that your mom
doesn't like me at all.
Sorry.
And thanks for keeping my secret.
Do you study music composition?
What about harmony?
It's also helpful to know keyboards.
Right!
We took piano lessons
together back in preschool.
What's up with you?
Were you a singer in
training back in Seoul?
It's a secret.
I've gone to see fortune tellers before.
But I've never seen such a
powerful one like that before.
The shaman of Mia-ri took
a quick look at my face.
She found out I was born on
August 8, in the year of dog.
Man, she said something good
would happen in the new year.
Maybe I'll get a promotion
after I resolve this case!
What is it that you wanted to tell me?
Oh, man... are you serious?
Both of us are pros.
Of course I know you've been
busy looking for that man.
Share some information with me.
What information?
Don't you see I'm empty-handed now?
Don't be a wuss.
The shaman said...
I should dig with my front legs.
Could it be...
He's buried somewhere?
That's nonsense!
If you have no more to say, I'll just go.
It's the weather forecast for Daejeon.
There will be heavy rain at night.
It's going to rain, 100 liters per hour
accompanied by lightning and thunder.
There are chances of landslides
in the Bong Gal mountain area.
Please be prepared for that.
Bong Gal Mountain?
It's going to be colder tomorrow.
From high 12 to high 19
degrees in Celsius...
Come on in... Oh, my!
You scared me.
Where are you going in a hurry?
It's raining outside.
It's just... over there...
Tae Soo, you won't believe this.
She got her answer!
What? What... answer?
She heard... she'll meet
her son within a few days.
Huh?
That bastard... bastard!
Ah!
Tae... Tae Soo!
You were worried that he might get
washed away in a landslide, right?
I was trying to bury him deep,
to be sure!
Heart to heart!
We are friends after all, right, Tae Soo?
Shut up. Just dig!
Oh...
Mr. Son's mother has a scary stare.
Should we do something about
her before it gets bad?
Heavens will punish you!
You are all about saving your life!
You are hopeless!
Tae Soo, I'm sorry. I was wrong.
Why, are you afraid you might
get struck by a lightning?
Are you afraid I might kill you?
subtitles ripped by riri13
I deserve to die. But please forgive me!
How can you say the word
'forgive' that easily?
Oh, Tae Soo! Tae Soo!
Tae Soo! Don't do that!
Don't do that!
Oh... oh...
I won't waste a shovel on a guy like you!
Hide!
Huh? Oh, my.
Oh... what are you doing here?
You didn't hear about the landslides?
Well, we just checked our
father's burial site.
Yeah, in case of landslides...
There isn't a burial site around here.
Have you seen one?
It's over there, but we got
lost and ended up here.
Where are you going?
Someone reported a collapsed bearing.
Then there's no time for this.
Where is it? Show me.
No, just go down. It's dangerous here.
It's good to have more hands.
Okay, let's go.
Show me. Where is it?
Is it that way? Let's go.
Hurry up.
Oh, come on in, Director Baek.
Geez.
People might think
two spies are meeting.
My goodness!
What happened to your face?
Gosh, did you get into a fight again?
Just say what you want to say.
Do you know the chairman
went to see Lee Do Kyung?
He did? What did he say?
I don't know exactly, but
obviously nothing pleasant.
I heard he yelled and
pointed his finger at her.
I guess he really hates Lee Do Kyung.
What is it that you want?
Gosh, don't make it all
about give and take.
I know how dear your ex-wife
and your daughter are to you.
I felt bad and just wanted to help.
Why don't we have lunch together
and talk about what's on our minds?
Accept a new member?
I just want to raise our
bar a little higher.
She went to Le Cordon Bleu.
She's also a certified barista.
If she joins us, One Heart
will shine brighter!
What do you think, Kyung Mee?
Pardon?
Oh, of course!
I think we can get
a lot of help from her!
Do you agree?
Yes, we like that, Madam!
Oh, it's good timing!
It seems like everyone is welcoming you!
Really?
I'm relieved.
I worried that someone might oppose.
It's a brilliant idea, Madam.
We are all for change and innovation.
One Heart needs a change too!
That's right.
However!
There's a rule about
accepting new members.
The majority of the members must agree.
Yeah, that's right.
I was hasty. I made a mistake.
Then let's vote by raising hands.
Anyone who opposes to
Lee Do Kyung's joining the team?
Does this mean everyone agrees then?
Since we are all here, should we hold a
ceremony to accept her as a new member?
That's great!
Thank you.
This is... a bit awkward...
I don't want to do this either.
So be quiet.
Do Kyung.
Do you know how special this
feet washing ceremony is?
It's about respecting and
loving our new members.
Madam Oh started this tradition.
I see.
Oh... Mother!
Mother!
How on earth are you here?
I just followed her.
She said she was spoken to.
I think she's going to do something.
What? Do what?
My feet just lead me here.
First...
May I ask you to do me a favor?
Well...
What... what kind of...?
Audrey Hepburn said this.
'Everyone must be saved from pain.'
'You must not abandon anyone!'
Please!
Please understand the desperation
a mom feels
when she's looking for her lost son!
We need your help and participation!
Has anyone...
seen this person?
His name is Son Se Yoon...
It's nice to volunteer.
But we could look a bit
all over the place.
We are doing this with a pure intention.
There will be a lot of these things.
I hope you're not regretting.
Hello. Please read this.
What am I supposed to do?
Even Madam Oh is involved.
Come quickly. I'm worried
what might happen.
Where are you?
She's doing exorcism so
she can find Mr. Son.
Really?
I heard she's a famous shaman
from Mia-ri.
What's all this?
How would I know?
Gosh.
This is such nonsense!
Is this a show or what?
Let's play a round!
Oh, my!
Why is she doing that?
I don't know.
I guess a spirit is upon her.
Honey.
What's going on?
My son has come!
My son! My poor child!
Come to your mom's arms!
My poor child!
Come to my arms!
Oh, Gi Bum!
Gi Bum! What's wrong?
Gi Bum!
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
Gi Bum! What's wrong?
Are you Se Yoon?
Yes, Mom.
My poor child!
Welcome back!
Welcome back, my child!
Mom!
My child!
What's wrong with him?
Director Bong.
Yes.
It must be hard on you.
Because of me...
Not at all, Mr. Son.
Producer Lee.
Yeah?
Mr. Yoon.
How could you... out of all...
It's not a mistake...
Wake up, Gi Bum! You aren't Mr. Son!
Wake up! Wake up!
My poor child.
Who did this to you?
Mom...
It's one of them here.
Who?
That person is...
What...
I, Yoon Tae Soo, will take care
of Kim Eun Ok until my death.
I don't need this.
Don't you hate me?
I'm like a worm.
Go, just go.
Go. Just go!
Tae Soo! I'm so sorry!
Tae Soo! I'm sorry!
Tae Soo, come down!
I am sorry!
Please get down!
I did wrong.
Tae Soo! Tae Soo!
Tae Soo, get down!
Tae Soo!
You are in here.
My child!
Where are you now?
Half way up Bong Gal Mountain.
Where exactly?
In the back of the pine tree forest.
Bong Gal Mountain?
Stay focused.
Bong Gal Mountain!
Don't worry.
To Bong Gal Mountain!
What do we do now?
Don't lose your focus.
We sink or swim!
Is he possessed or something?
Cross! Do you have a cross or garlic?
They are useless.
Just knock him out!
Ah!
It's here! Right here!
Right here?
Right here!
Would it be true?
Over here! There's something here!
Something's in here.
Take it out!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Sweet Savage Family]
The police station is upside down now.
Someone reported about that case.
Tae Soo's jealous of me
but I'm jealous of him.
It's for Eun Ok?
That's too much.
Go all the way.
It was then. I made you mine then.
It's not Sung Min, right?
Eun Ok will be furious.
He risked his life for movies.
But his scenario tells me
he's about to die.
I'll do it!
Enjoy now.
You never know how long it'll last.
Wait and see.