Subtitles by DramaFever
We can't do that.
Flying kick!
[Episode 2]
Huh? Where is everyone?
What the heck...
Subtitles by DramaFever
Boss. There's nothing here.
It's all empty.
What's going on?
The number you dialed does not exist.
Please confirm and try again...
What the heck? Did they run away?
Boss?
Didn't you say the chairman
deposited three billion won?
Rats...
Get out and find him!
Run!
Geez!
Is this the right place?
Yes, he was living off of his friend.
Search thoroughly.
It seems like he knew we were
coming and ran away quickly.
Catch him!
Stop right there!
Get him!
Hey!
Stop right there!
Hey! Stop there!
Hey!
Get him!
What's this?
- Congratulations!
- Thank you, Sun Young.
They're beautiful.
Do you like what I picked for you?
Oh, I knew it!
It's definitely your taste!
You never change.
Graceful and sophisticated.
Sit down, sit down, everyone.
Yes, ma'am.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Let's toast to One Heart!
One Heart!
Ma'am, don't bother yourself.
I'll cut it for you.
You might hurt your wrist.
Thank you.
- Please have some wine.
- Thanks.
Eun Ok.
I guess you can sleep well now.
You wished your husband
had a different job.
Please don't say that.
I just hoped he would do a variety
of things within the group.
As an advocate of art, I look forward
to watching Mr. Yoon's movie.
You should support him well.
Yes, ma'am. I will do my best.
Young Il told me that
if the movie does well
Tae Soo will continue
to work as an investor.
Of course that's a possibility.
You never know what could happen in life.
It's not easy to make a big hit movie.
Life doesn't change that easily.
If it was that easy,
we wouldn't be wives of thugs.
Hey.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Should I stitch up my lips?
Yes, you should.
Yes, ma'am.
- That's pretty.
- Yeah.
- So many pretty things.
- I know.
Excuse me.
Do you have time?
- It was me.
- It was me!
- Don't argue. You better back down.
Be a little modest, Mom.
And think about your age.
You lost to me many times!
Don't make me a bad mother.
We are pretty even so far.
Should we find out?
- Sure!
Excuse me.
Oh, you mean me?
Which of us were you talking to just now?
Were you interested in me or was it...
this old lady?
- I was--
- For your information...
We are not really interested in you.
So would you please
just tell us the truth?
Both of you have good
energy in your faces.
Pardon me?
If you get training,
you can dispel all bad luck.
Perhaps, you are interested
in finding the way to do so?
Hey!
Stop right there!
Geez.
Oh!
I finally got you, little rat!
Geez! Please!
Geez!
Come over here, you little rat!
- Hey!
- Geez!
Stop right there!
Geez!
- Geez!
- Hey!
Stop right there!
You're dead...
You are...
Stop please...
You come here.
- Come on.
- Geez!
Don't even try.
It's not me!
Come here!
Hey!
I won't beat you. Let's talk outside.
You're dead.
Hey!
Easy! Easy!
Boss! Boss!
Ugh.
What's this?
Get up.
What a mess.
What's this stuff? What...
Oh.
Oh... Lee Do Kyung.
Long time no see.
Oh, man.
Well.
I'm sorry but...
I'm in a hurry. But I'll be back.
Hey.
How did it go?
Huh?
He says Mr. Son even stole
his money and ran away.
He ran because he was afraid.
That's a lie, right?
Where is that bastard?
I really don't know. I don't know!
Get this.
Geez.
I'm very sorry about that.
I'll clean all of this up.
Don't worry.
That's not right.
I should pay for all of this.
You haven't changed one bit, Tae Soo.
Geez.
It's been ten years.
And this is what you had to see.
I live like this.
Ouch.
What's wrong?
I guess I twisted it when
I used the fire extinguisher.
Let me see.
Oh, luckily your bones seem fine.
It's hasn't been a month
since she came to Daejeon.
She opened her store last weekend.
And Tae Soo stopped by
the store just now.
Hey.
Did you just come home?
Looks like you had a drink.
Is it the movie or Tae Soo?
On which did you spend three billion won?
On both.
Honestly, I wanted to
give Tae Soo a chance.
He's worked hard all of these years.
And he's never caused trouble.
You mean whereas I failed many times?
It's time for him to do
something different.
He can't just do the clubs.
The clubs are our source of income.
Who can run them other than Tae Soo?
Do you trust anyone other than Tae Soo?
You can’t make someone keep shoveling
just because he's good at shoveling.
People work harder when there's a reward.
He's a muscle man.
He doesn't have the brains.
Someone like me, who does have
the brains, should do the thinking!
But he has the heart.
There's no one as responsible,
or as loyal, as Tae Soo.
He's a person I need the most,
and you know that!
Then make him your son.
Okay?
How did it go? Did you find out?
We checked all the CCTV
footage we could get.
But we found nothing.
What the hell...
I'm totally screwed!
What have I done, huh?
So why did you get into
the movie business?
Just make up some excuses,
like Gi Bum does.
You'd just get scolded,
but that would be it.
I'm not Gi Bum!
Would I be like this if
the chairman was my father?
I'm doing this because I trust you.
Tae Soo, this can change our lives.
Work to death.
Your life depends on it.
He's been a bit edgy since
he invested in the movie.
He spent three billion won all at once.
Yoon Tae Soo! Yoon Tae Soo!
Now that I'm looking at this,
my husband looks so handsome!
Why are you doing that?
What do you mean?
Of course I should clip these.
This is our family's treasure to pass on!
Not anyone can be a movie investor.
Geez.
One Heart threw a surprise party
for me today.
Madam Oh came to congratulate us.
The ladies are so jealous of me.
I heard some movies
make 10 billion won!
Let's buy a house in Seoul first.
We need to do that when
Sung Min goes to college anyway.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
You have to succeed.
Everyone knows about it now.
If you fail...
We won't be able to lift our heads up.
Okay?
Stop it! My head is about to explode!
Did you just yell at me?
No... it's not that...
You're already like this?
Will you hit me if the film is a success?
Go ahead. Hit me.
Hit me.
- Hit me!
- Geez!
There's so much on my mind.
My tongue just slipped.
Come to your senses, jerk!
Come to your senses.
Enough. Just take out the trash.
It's overflowing.
Ugh...
Yeah.
Boss, we got him for real!
What?
Where is Mr. Son?
Geez.
You must know where he is.
They say they don't know.
No worries. I can beat them to a pulp.
Please... please, please.
There must be a misunderstanding.
We just did what Mr. Son told us to do.
He told us to lay low. So we did.
What about the money? Where is it?
What money?
We didn't see even a penny.
We're victims here too.
- Yes.
- What?
Do you look down on me
because I'm an uneducated boor?
- Huh?
- No.
What is it?
What did you do with the trash?
The town councilman came to see me.
I was going to toss it
and got sidetracked.
She totally blew up on me.
My ears still hurt!
Boss...
I got it.
- Talk to you at home.
- Honey!
What time are you coming home?
I'll be home as soon as I'm done.
Stop by the market on your way.
I forgot to get milk.
Trash bags too. 10-liter ones.
Please!
Don't get 20-liter ones like last time!
Okay.
10-liter trash bags.
And two cartons of milk.
I got it. See you later.
You rats! Do you think I'm nobody? Huh?
Do you know what
that three billion won means?
Geez!
Please just report it to the police.
Then we can get our money back
and be proven innocent.
The police? Great idea!
Call the TV station too!
You give them an interview on TV!
How great!
Our chairman will be dancing around!
Mr. Yoon.
We don't know anything! We know nothing!
Yeah?
If words don't work, use something else.
Go ahead.
What is this?
My phone is on fire...
Brother!
Man!
I'm sorry I'm late.
Don't worry.
Why did you come so fast?
You should have taken your time.
I'm sorry for making you wait.
You're a busy man.
That's all right.
I have no home and no money.
All I have is time.
I have nothing.
Would a busy policeman
run errands for a gangster?
What's wrong, Brother?
What do you mean?
I'm just speaking the truth.
Well, did you look into it?
Do you know what kind of guy
Son Se Yoon is?
Yeah?
This isn't right.
It's a violation of human rights.
I may be running errands
for a gangster...
But as a policeman,
I do have a conscience.
Let's say there was nothing.
Hey, Bro!
You scared me!
Do you want to see me die?
I can just--!
Okay. I got it!
Son Se Yoon is a rock bed.
Yeah?
He has five stars!
Fraud, gambling...
Violations of the
Foreign Exchange Control Law...
He goes to Las Vegas and
Macao as if he lives there.
Is that true?
Where is this bastard now?
Tae Soo.
I am a policeman.
I don't work for the CIA.
My God!
Why do you yell at me?
Judging by the given situation
he probably already
went overseas with the money.
Give me some tea.
Go somewhere else.
I need to clean the store first.
It'll be a while.
If you had told me
I would have helped you
to find a home and a store.
Do I have to report to my ex-husband
when I come to my hometown?
"Why did you come?" "Do you need help?"
"What do you need?"
If that's what you're
going to say, I will get up.
I was surprised that you came so quickly.
I was going to come see
you when I was ready.
Ready for what?
You hated me when you lived with me.
But you hated being
a gangster's wife even more.
Since it happened this way
it'll be good to show you
how I've become a different person.
Are you saying you're
becoming a new person... for me?
I know you won't believe me
no matter what I say.
But I mean it.
I'm trying very hard
these days, Do Kyung.
Aren't you curious about Hyun Jee?
Isn't asking about her
the first thing to do?
I have no right to say her name.
How funny.
But she says she misses her daddy.
Leave.
My first customer was bad.
My day isn't off to a good start.
Honey, it's a scoop!
Director Baek met his ex!
She opened a cafe
in Eunhaeng-dong called La Mer!
One, two, three!
Lee Do Kyung's back.
- She came back to Daejeon!
- What?
My goodness.
I'm very sorry.
Really?
You should have told us.
I feel a bit disappointed.
I'm sorry.
I was too busy opening the store.
I haven't seen you on TV for a while.
You don't act anymore?
I quit acting long time ago.
Everyone knows except for you, I suppose.
Were you an actress?
- Actress?
- Yes.
You were Lady 3 in Farm Diary.
You were in a movie too.
Her Fight?
Right. I played a bitch who
seduces a married man.
Right. Your acting was amazing!
Right?
I baked it myself.
How do you like it?
Wait a minute.
Perhaps... La Mer from Samchung-dong?
Some people recognize it.
I used to go there often
when I lived in Seoul.
When I feel gloomy...
Drip coffee and a waffle...
That was like food for my soul.
By the way...
I guess you came from Seoul?
Yes. But my hometown is Daejeon.
Hmm.
Do Kyung, Eun Ok, and Me.
The three of us were like the
Charlie's Angels of Ho Soo High.
Eun Ok was the smart one.
Do Kyung was the pretty one.
And I was...
The slutty one!
You're laughing too loud.
Sorry, sorry.
Actually the slutty one was Eun Ok.
Ah...
what the heck are you talking about?
You were good at that kind of stuff.
In the end you married the man
you loved unrequitedly.
Our handmade cookies are good.
Would you like to try some?
Bub Kyu.
Yes, Boss.
We have to succeed with this one.
I really want to succeed.
Yes, of course you will.
I heard you like soccer, Chairman Wang.
Soccer is all about
the center of the field.
Chungcheong-do is the center of Korea.
And I'm the midfielder.
You can't go to Seoul, Jeolla-do or
Gyeongsang-do without going through here.
A thematic park in the middle
of the transportation hub.
You will see.
Not only foreigners
but also Koreans will come here
from all over the country.
I understand what you are saying.
Haste makes waste.
I will get it all ready.
Please wait patiently until then.
And enjoy looking around.
Okay.
I trust you, Director Baek.
But don't make me wait too long.
Don't worry. Thank you.
Thank you, Director Baek.
Thank you!
- Thank you.
Thank you.
What do you think? Was I good?
Yes. You should be a politician.
I'll do it if I have the chance.
Of course!
Huh?
Isn't he the CEO of the
movie production company?
I think so.
What is he here for?
Find out what he's up to.
Yes, Boss.
Boss, this is big!
What is?
They say Mr. Son is a
regular at this casino.
He's staying in a VIP room.
Only foreigners can come here.
It seems that he has a fake passport.
What's that... Do...
He has the passport from
the Dominican Republic.
Oh, he has some guts.
That bastard lost a ton
of money since yesterday.
Is that true?
Card for player, card for banker.
Player's, banker's.
Player's card.
Banker. Natural nine.
Geez.
You should have rubbed your nose.
You're losing lots of money here.
Does Mr. Yoon know this?
Gi Bum.
My friend, I have big news.
Want a drink?
Here.
How's the movie going?
What do you mean?
It's just starting now.
What's the big news?
You know Mr. Son...
Yeah.
What is his personality like?
I want to get to know him,
but I haven't had the chance.
Can you set something up?
Sure. Another time...
I heard your family is excited
about your doing that movie.
You wife and kids are excited to death!
What's the big news?
I discovered something about Mr. Son...
No, never mind.
I'll tell you another time.
What is it?
Huh? What was that?
Are you upset?
Are you on your period?
Don't joke around.
I'm sorry.
Why are you so worked up?
Oh.
I just found out
Mr. Son...
He's our high school senior!
Isn't that big news?
Thanks, Tae Soo.
What the heck are you talking about?
It's been a while since
my dad smiled like that.
You're like a good son to him.
So I'm thankful.
He's crazy.
All he talks about these days
is movies, actors...
I can't believe it.
My friend.
Do it right.
Make a good movie.
I want to see...
how big his smile can get.
Oh my god! Oh my god!
Oh my! My goodness!
Let me ask you for the last time.
Where is Mr. Son?
Don't do it again!
I really don't know.
Save me!
I told you we are the victims here!
Put them in.
Don't let go!
Wait!
I will make the movie!
That way we get to live.
And you get to live too!
With one billion won!
We can make a movie that's
worth three billion won!
Back in college, my nickname was...
Low Budget, High Quality!
- That's right!
- Yes!
- You don't make a movie just with money.
- Right!
Low-budget movies!
Yes, low-budget!
Everyone dies. I'm not afraid to die!
But we can't die like this!
I can't die like this!
I'll make the movie!
Please?
How can I trust you?
How?
You know what...
Since I was eight years old
my dream has been to make movies.
If you give me one last chance
I will put my life on it.
I'll make the movie!
If we can have one billion won
we will make the movie, no matter what!
One billion won! Save us!
Are you crazy?
Stop talking nonsense.
You have no money.
If I don't make the movie,
I'll have to put up my head.
I have no choice.
Mom! Mom!
What's going on?
Oh my goodness!
- Hey...
- Grab his leg.
How much did you drink?
I can't live like this!
- Geez!
- It hurts!
- It hurts.
- Are you okay?
Just get up.
Are you making a movie or something?
Yoon Soo Min!
Stop that. Help!
You didn't wash your face.
You look like a puppy.
Put that away!
Give me that!
Mom! Help.
- I don't want to be late for school.
- Okay. Open the door.
Honey! My goodness!
Look at your belly button! You stink!
I can't live like this!
He stinks!
This is worth 50,000 won at least.
Geez!
- Take his clothes off.
- Let go!
You jerks!
Am I number two?
You want to die?
You are dead.
I won't leave you alone.
Get my fist.
Hi!
I'm sorry for having you come out.
Why did you want to see me?
I remember the day you
first came to our house.
I thought my husband finally
found someone he could trust.
I was very pleased.
If it hadn't been for him,
I would not be alive now.
Please tell me the truth.
Something happened to Tae Soo, right?
Well.
Nothing is going on.
I'm going crazy here.
Please don't do this.
Tae Soo will beat me up for this.
It's bad enough for him
to lose his life, right?
Look here.
I've been married to
a gangster for 18 years.
I can tell something is up.
I'm not sick anymore. Why did you come?
I have something to discuss with you.
With me?
Yes...
Geez.
I can't handle this on my own.
What is it?
It's Soo Min.
Soo Min doesn't listen to me.
I'm dying here!
What's wrong with my puppy?
Did she get in trouble again?
It's not like that.
She never listens to me.
She's good with you.
Of course, I raised her with love!
Don't be hard on her.
These days parents
have no control over their kids.
The only thing you can
control is your food.
That brings up my point.
I want you to come back.
For Soo Min!
I know things are still
awkward between you and me.
No need to say more.
It's for my puppy.
Mother.
I'll come right now.
Oh, my.
I had no idea what was going on.
I slept well without knowing anything.
What's all this?
I took out all of my savings.
I broke our savings.
Your mom is coming back,
so we sold her place too.
This is all I can do.
You take care of the rest.
- How did you--
- I've lived anxiously for 18 years.
I can tell by just looking at you.
If you fail,
our entire family will suffer.
You saw how excited the kids
were about your movie business.
I'll go. Soo Min will be home soon.
The room looks bigger with
everything organized.
It looks bigger because of that tiny TV.
Pardon me?
I have bad sight, and the TV is tiny.
I guess I'll just listen.
It's practically a radio.
A 32-inch TV isn't small.
It's perfect for this room.
Okay. My eyes are the problem.
Why do you have to take away
my joy of watching TV?
The TV in the living room is yours.
So I can't touch that.
Others think I have a good life.
But my life is miserable.
My friend left behind a 42-inch TV
when she left the country.
I'll bring that.
A used one?
No, it's only been used for two years.
It's practically new.
My goodness.
It's used when you open the box.
How much longer will I live?
If I buy a new one now,
I'll use it for the rest of my life.
I shouldn't have said anything to you.
Tae Soo would buy one
for me if I asked him.
Your son is in a bad situation now.
He has no money.
Huh? What do you mean?
Do you know how many clubs he manages?
Grandma!
Oh, my puppy!
Are you going to live with us?
Of course.
Now I'm in charge of you, puppy!
Yay!
I love it.
My precious granddaughter!
I bought them!
Air spray, apples, orange juice...
Toast for breakfast...
Oh, no. I forgot squid legs. Sorry, Mom!
Okay. I'll pay attention.
Come home early. Bye!
Oh?
Is he a singer or something?
Who said you could sing here?
He sang in the park last time.
It's him.
Hey, it's you, right?
He ignored us last time,
and he is doing that now!
Hey! Hey!
Who said you could sing here and there?
Huh?
Stop it. I don't want to fight.
- He said stop.
- What a cutie.
Are you leaving?
You should pay the rent.
I don't like this guy.
Hey, can't you hear me?
You can't hear me?
You want to die?
What's this?
Guys, run!
You improved a lot.
What?
Let me see.
You didn't grow much.
I kind of like your chin, and your style.
I'll forgive you for your shortness.
You don't recognize me?
Geez!
It's not easy to forget me.
I've been well known for
my beauty since I was little.
All right.
You'll have to remember who I am
by the next time we see each other.
Bye then.
When did he toughen up?
He's making my heart flutter.
Hey! Your vocalization is awful!
If you sing like that,
you'll hurt your throat!
Producing Mr. Son's script
will cost us a lot.
So I modified my script around the one
for which I was highly praised in Poland.
I want to use that.
Did you read it all?
I can't understand any of this!
I don't understand what
is hard to understand.
Mr. Lee, do you understand this script?
Honestly, it's not a commercial piece.
This is a bit lacking...
These gangsters don't fight.
They talk funny.
There should be some order!
Like One, Two, Three, A, B, C.
It has no story, it's no fun!
What do you think movies are?
Movies are movies!
What else are they?
Do you know the director Otani Iosselian?
- Otani what?
- My--
He made
"The Favorites of the Moon" and said this
"A movie is to weaving our daily lives
that are like dust, in an artistic way."
Those are the kinds of movies
I want to make!
I feel like dying from running.
What the heck are you talking about?
I told you many times that we're making a
movie about the fists in Chungcheong-do!
That's just a motive.
What TV?
Motive... I mean.
The main thought.
- I'm an educated man.
- I don't give a shit about that!
Talk about gangsters.
You don't know gangsters?
Should I call my underlings?
Huh?
This is our asset! Stop!
What's going on?
Did something happen?
Oh.
It's not that.
We are having a meeting.
Having a meeting without the CEO?
Where is Mr. Son?
Oh, well...
He went to Seoul for business.
Hmm.
My dad is about to die from anxiety.
I guess Mr. Son has a lot of time.
What are you here for?
I just wanted to see
how things were going.
"The Pavane of the Fist Emperor"?
Wasn't it Hot Brothers?
Did the title change?
We are just reviewing some other things.
We haven't decided anything.
A bad movie can be made
with a good script.
But a good movie can't be
made with a bad script.
I am so curious as to what kind of
script you're thinking of, Tae Soo.
Did you come here to spoil it?
Why are you upset?
You're making it awkward.
You are scary.
Oh, my!
Why do you treat an
important person like this?
Are you a gangster?
I told you not to act like Tae Soo.
I'm sorry, Boss.
Where... where am I?
Why do you want to know?
Tae Soo was having a meeting
with the director and producer.
I guess they're going
to make a hit movie.
Jian Carlos Jackson?
What a name!
I know.
Did you make the name or
did your broker do that?
What is it that you want from me?
I've seen a movie
where they put two hungry
beasts up for a fight.
I'm making Tae Soo starve now
until his eyes are rolling back.
You said you had one billion won left.
Where did you hide it?
If you give me that, I might let you go.
There's nothing left.
I've lost it all.
Look here, Mr. Son.
I'm different than Tae Soo.
He uses his fists.
And I use this.
You better punch your numbers again.
Got it?
Boss! Are you okay?
Hey, where are you going?
Where are you going?
Where?
What will you do?
Where will you go?
What are you good at, Mr. Son?
You're bad at gambling
and you're bad at escaping.
I feel sorry for you.
How do you like it?
Wow, it has an amazing aroma.
- What kind of tea is it?
- Oriental miracle...
Oriental beauty tea.
Is there such a thing?
This is my favorite tea.
It's the top class among Oolong tea.
It's made out of leaves eaten by bugs.
Bugs?
Because of some kind of
chemical reaction they cause
it has a honey-like scent.
Wow.
It's good.
Is there anything you don't know?
Please don't say that.
I'm lacking in many areas.
What do you lack?
Let me know if you lack clothes or bags.
Oh, my.
If you really want to buy me something...
would you buy
the entire Dostoevsky collection?
I feel like reading
classics when it's cold.
You got it!
I'll buy you a library before I die.
Do you mean it?
You promised.
Of course!
Oh.
Are you going to work?
It's early.
Father, I went to
the movie production company.
What about Tae Soo?
He's working really hard.
I was surprised.
Speaking of that
for the success of the movie and Tae Soo
should we call a shaman
to hold a ceremony?
Shaman?
Yes.
You spent the money but you were
a bit indifferent to him.
You should drop in sometimes
and encourage them.
When was the last time you saw Mr. Son?
Well, it's been a while.
Geez.
What do you think, Madam Oh?
Actually, I thought about that.
But I wasn't sure how you feel
about a shamanistic ceremony.
So I didn't ask.
You should have asked me.
Do it tonight.
Let the people know.
I will.
Oh, my goodness!
Look!
Take a look, Mr. Lee.
What's this?
Oh, geez!
Ahh!
Put it away!
It did? It came sooner than I thought.
Is it smiling?
I see.
Father asked me to do that,
and he wants to see Mr. Son.
Don't worry about the ceremony.
Just tell Mr. Son to
come down from Seoul.
See you later, my friend!
Okay.
Mr. Son.
There will be a shamanistic ceremony
for the movie tonight.
Don't you need to go to bow down to
the pig head and pray for a blessing?
Huh?
Please save me.
[Hot Brothers! May it be a big hit!]
November 19th, 2015.
Gods of the heavens and Earth...
Who rules all things in the world!
We pray to you!
Thank you, Tae Soo.
Make a good movie.
I'll help you as best as a I can.
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
Oh, man! The order was wrong.
The CEO of the company
should have bowed first.
Mr. Son!
Mr. Son Se Yoon, please come out!
Tae Soo! What are you doing?
Bring Mr. Son!
Where is the CEO of
the movie production company?
Mr. Son, please come out!
Where is the CEO?
Well...
Then One Heart can do it now.
Members, please come forward.
The CEO should go first.
Good to see you!
Mr. Chairman, you look amazing!
May it a big hit!
What happened to Mr. Son?
Oh, that's...
- He had an urgent matter in Seoul--
- Even so, he can't do this!
If he doesn't come, I'll look funny.
It takes only one hour
to get here by train.
Is someone dying or something?
- He said he was busy--
- So, what is it that he's busy with?
Actually...
He's meeting with someone from
Hollywood about a remake.
Do you think we're idiots?
The movie isn't even made yet.
What remake?
If the concept is good,
they often make a deal before it's made.
Many of my seniors in Poland
had those kind of deals.
- That doesn't make sense.
- Be quiet.
So he's meeting with an American?
Yes, Hollywood.
- To me--
- What do you know?
If you know nothing, just don't ruin it.
Okay. I know nothing.
We will see what kind of
movie we end up with.
Tae Soo, why are you sweating so much?
Oh?
Oh... I'm not.
Oh, pack some rice cakes
from the ceremony for me.
There's someone who has
really has to try the rice cakes.
Okay.
Geez.
Jian Carlos!
- What's his name?
- Jackson.
CEO Jian Carlos Jackson!
Have some rice cakes from the ceremony!
Carlos! The ceremony went well!
I didn't get the pig head meat.
Just eat the rice cakes.
Where is that bastard?
Hey!
I'll find him.
Geez! What a resilient Korean!
Geez!
Stop right there!
CEO Son! Hey!
Get him!
Hey! Stop!
Let go!
- Bastard!
- I'm sorry!
Come on!
Your feet hurt! Stop right there!
Hey, Mr. Son!
You're going to hurt your feet!
Hey!
Man! What a way to sleep!
Go wash up. Let's go to the market.
Do I have to go?
Then should I carry everything
all by myself?
Now!
Hurry up.
Geez.
Did you wake me up
that early just for this?
Your mom's at home.
I should pay more attention.
Open it.
What was that?
I don't know.
Who knows if you don't know?
Oh, man.
I feel like dying from running.
Check again.
Okay.
What the heck is going on?
My goodness.
Did you do that?
Am I crazy?
Then why is his dead body in there?
I really don't know.
It's your car. How can you not know?
I don't know because I don't know!
That's right!
The black box!
Let's check it.
We turned it off at night.
The battery was low.
Then what are you going to do?
Are you trying to kill me too?
Over... there.
Turn around.
What do we do?
What's that?
Is he looking at us?
Be calm.
Excuse me. I'm going to check your car.
Oh, you're working hard!
Is something going on?
An armed soldier
deserted the base nearby.
Oh.
Oh, man.
We went to the market.
Right.
Please open the trunk.
Please open the trunk!
What are you doing?
Excuse me.
Please come here.
Just a minute.
Please.
I asked you to open the trunk.
What are you doing?
It's okay. Just buy something to eat.
Look carefully.
It's not a 5,000 won bill.
Keep up the good work.
Over here!
Please come over here.
Honey.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Sweet Savage Family]
Movie maker? Civic hero?
But he's nothing.
He's finished!
Being a gangster isn't enough.
You're a criminal now!
My son is not like that.
He never pays attention to girls.
He only knows how to study.
What are you saying?
Gi Bum, you are the only one I can trust.
What should I do?
Making a movie with one billion won.
What?
Tae Soo could get us!
Gi Bum, we aren't just friends.
Mr. Chairman, you don't trust me?