Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 7]
Where's Soo Min?
Where's my daughter?
How would I know?
You had me followed.
You have the wrong guy!
Your guy fessed up!
I don't know what you're talking about!
How dare you, Gi Bum?
Where's Soo Min? Where is she?
Is this what you meant when
you said I'd come to regret it?
Is this what you plotted
with that swindler?
What are you talking about?
Try to help me understand.
Gi Bum! How can you do this to me?
We may be in a dirty line of work,
but we've got rules here.
That bottom line is that we don't
mess with each others' families...
You want to know what happens
when you don't follow that rule?
All of you are pieces of garbage!
What the heck are you doing?
Stop acting like a crazy person!
Soo Min disappeared!
And he had me followed.
If it were you, what would you do? Huh?
But you shouldn't suspect me.
Am I someone who would kidnap
your daughter, and then enjoy my drink?
Be honest. Did you do something
to his daughter?
No, I didn't. I mean it.
Why would do such thing?
If that's a lie, my fist will be
the last thing that you see.
Honestly, many people are
holding grudges against you.
Don't bark at the wrong guy.
Check everyone on your list.
If it turns out to be you guys,
you better be ready for what's coming.
You better be ready for what's coming
if it turns out that it isn't us.
Got that?
Thank you, Brother. You saved me.
Did you send a guy
to take care of Tae Soo?
Do you know that my wife
got hurt because of him?
You said it wasn't you.
You said you would cut off your hand!
Brother... that was really
an accident. An accident!
Tae Soo's daughter...
You didn't do that, right?
It's not me. I swear! If I'm lying,
I'll cut off all my own limbs!
Bro...
Please find my daughter! Please!
Please!
This is serious.
Can you think of anyone
who would do this?
I can't. I'm totally clueless.
I can't live without my daughter.
Please! Please find her!
Please?
Where on earth did she go?
Hello?
Soo Min did?
- It hurts!
- You should have called us!
Soo Min!
Oh my! Are you okay?
You're not hurt?
I think Mom cracked some of my bones!
Why are you hitting me?
What happened?
Don't even get me started! She--
Let me explain.
Let me say hello first.
How have you been, my brother in-law?
What happened?
I had concert tickets,
so I called Soo Min.
But she came to Seoul without
telling you. That's what happened.
What? Why didn't you say anything?
My phone died! How many
times do I have to say that?
You call that an excuse?
You need a beating!
- Mom!
- Teach her!
She needs to learn!
I almost had a heart attack!
- Auntie!
- Get over here!
This is exactly what she ran away from!
She begged to not go home.
Can't you be like Scandinavian parents?
- She's right!
- What?
Geez.
You went through a lot, Dad.
Sung Min, you're looking more and
more like your dad as you get older.
You didn't look anything like
your dad when you were little.
That's interesting.
Who else would I look like?
What?
Yeah, you're right.
We can't reach Soo Min.
I understand how desperate you are.
But how dare you suspect me!
Mr. Chairman!
Dad.
Is it true that Tae Soo
came here to question you?
Geez, that's insane.
He suspected me too!
I had a guest, and he showed up
and caused a scene.
A guest? Who?
Does that matter?
Dad, a dog can bite its owner.
You can't let Tae Soo be
a loose cannon like this.
I already told you.
It's just a matter of time
before Tae Soo gets to us.
See how he accused us,
without even having any evidence?
If he finds anything noteworthy,
he'll chew us up instantly.
Geez... where is everyone?
Mom! Honey!
Geez.
Hello. We are from the realty office.
The reality office? For what?
The owner of the house
put the house up for sale.
- What?
- Please let us take a look.
- Excuse me.
- Wait.
The owner of the house is the chairman
of Choong Shim Construction.
He really built a nice house here.
Mr. Chairman.
It's true. I deserve to die.
I was wrong for having
doubted you like that.
But where would we go during this
cold winter if you sold our house?
Tae Soo.
A food farmer is more diligent
when it isn't farming season.
It forces him to show his heart,
as opposed to just his skills.
The way you're behaving these days...
Are you really the Tae Soo that I know?
That bastard, Cho.
He was hanging around Gi Bum,
so I called the guys from Cheongjoo.
You did?
The Cheongjoo guys didn't want
to be involved, and they went back.
So, you should take care of Cho now.
Unless you want your family to suffer in
the cold winter, you should do it right.
Hello! How are you?
Mr. Yoon! I didn't kidnap your daughter!
Sit down.
Black noodles aren't good when bloated.
So listen and eat at the same time.
I said eat.
I heard that you're selling loans
to college kids these days.
One million won loans,
or something like that?
How do you know that?
Man, you need to live like a person.
You're ruining their lives
over a measly one million won?
I know a detective who desperately
needs to break open a case.
Should I introduce you to him?
Listen carefully.
From this point forward,
you don't know Baek Gi Bum.
You don't call him.
You don't answer his calls.
Erase any memory of
Baek Gi Bum from your head!
Got that?
Keep what I told you in mind, okay?
The ballot box will be opened at 7 p.m.
How can you wait that long?
How? Calmly and humbly, like I have to.
It doesn't look good, Eun Ok.
You never know until
the results come out.
Man, what kind of guy are you?
You even questioned my father?
You think we're the kind of people
who would kidnap your daughter?
Don't put it that way.
Be quiet!
You may look loyal, but come crunch time,
you don't trust a damn soul but your own!
I'm not sure how I should
deal with you now! Geez...
You're not entirely innocent.
You hang out with the man
who had me followed.
Is that a problem?
Don't try to change the subject!
Enough.
Don't hang out with Cho.
The chairman is about to explode.
What?
If you see him again, my family
will be kicked out of our home.
Oh! My dad told you to leave the house?
He must have been really upset.
He was agonizing all night.
He couldn't even sleep.
It's all your fault!
Anyway, look, I warned you about Cho.
Why would I hang out
with a guy that hurt Do Kyung?
I'm more worried about
constantly seeing you!
Director Bong.
Geez, what happened to him?
He hasn't been able to sleep for
a few nights because of the script.
How hard can writing be?
More action, more romance!
I told you, that will do!
Stop it with the nonsense.
A good house is built
on a good foundation.
You are the one who
is spewing nonsense.
I'm the CEO here. I'm your boss.
What more is there to say?
You have no respect for your elders.
Stop! Please stop it! Stop!
- What's wrong?
- Crazy?
Writing a script is already hard enough.
You two are always fighting.
He can't relax.
We're begging you, please
communicate with us as a unit.
Geez...
Geez... geez... it feels good.
It feels good!
How is Tae Soo doing?
Is he trying at least?
He took his underlings
with him and warned Cho.
Geez, humans are sly.
They don't recognize it when
someone is being good to them.
They only realize how well they had it
when they're falling off the edge.
By the way, about One Heart...
What about it?
Lee Do Kyung is running for
the chairwomanship of One Heart.
What?
Let's count the votes.
Kyung Mee, please open them.
Yes, Ma'am.
Lee Do Kyung.
Kim Eun Ok.
Lee Do Kyung!
Lee Do Kyung. Kim Eun Ok.
Fifteen people voted.
There is one vote left.
Yes, there's one left.
Please open it.
Sure.
My goodness!
How dare you step foot in here?
What brings you here at
this hour, Mr. Chairman?
What the heck are you doing now?
We're electing a new chairwoman.
To change things up.
To change things up?
Who told you to do this?
You better do it right.
What the heck is this?
Get out. Everyone, get out!
I told you to disappear quietly.
Yes, you did.
Did you think that I was just
another old fart, nagging away?
What right do you have
to be so greedy like this?
I'm sorry if I was too greedy.
But please stop telling me
what rights I have.
What?
I used to be a part of this
"great" Choong Shim family.
As long as I have Hyun Jee,
I do have a right to be here.
Anyway, since the election was
canceled, I have no reason to be here.
I'll leave now, Ma'am.
Look at that...
She can never hide what she is.
Mr. Chairman!
I am so... so disappointed in you.
I never... never imagined you
to be this kind of person.
I trusted you. I depended on you.
And I respected you.
But what happened to you?
Madam Oh!
Thanks to you, I have been...
I have been humiliated and disgraced
in front of all of the members.
How can I face them again?
So humiliating... terrifying... oh...
What are you saying?
My husband is home.
Sit down.
You're drinking?
Oh, what happened with your election?
"How dare you step foot in here?"
"Who said you could
play this kind of stuff?"
"Get out right now!"
The chairman broke it up when
we were opening the ballot box.
Man, what the heck...
Anyway, you worked so hard.
How disappointing.
No, no, no.
Now I can say this.
I was not confident.
She has more money.
She has better qualifications.
I'm lucky that we tied.
At least I was able to save my pride.
I'm sorry.
You had so much going on
and I wasn't being helpful.
I'm not really disappointed
about the chairwoman position.
But I'm worried about Sung Min.
I don't know what to do.
What are you doing?
I'm organizing my composition notebook.
Wow, composition notebook?
It's not that different from
playing games in my spare time
You were bragged just moments ago.
When did I do that?
You said that was
your number-one treasure.
Is it more important than me?
Let's stop here.
Geez.
Stop what?
Get over here with your notebook
within thirty minutes.
Well, can't we just support him?
He's never been a troublemaker before.
He's working so hard because he
found something that he really likes.
He's just a kid.
He'll regret it someday.
We have to stop him now.
As his parents, that is our duty.
Geez, hey!
We're talking about
Sung Min, not Soo Min.
He can take care of himself!
Do you really wish for him to stop
studying and become a singer?
He said he would keep studying too!
That doesn't make sense!
You should be on my side
when it comes to their studies.
Now, you make me look bad!
I'm not taking anyone's side here!
I know what's going on.
You don't want any conflicts with him.
You just want to play Nice Dad.
What?
But all you do with them is fight.
It's much better for us to
support him, so we can get along!
If he were your own son, you would
make him study, no matter what!
How can you say that?
It's true.
If he were your own flesh and blood,
would you still be so lenient with him?
Eun Ok!
I want to repay you for what you've done.
I want to raise him well,
so he can make you proud.
That boy is--
Oh, Mom.
Yeah? Oh, I need to go to the bathroom.
My stomach hurts.
Oh... my... oh...
Go to sleep.
Come on.
If he were your own son, you would
make him study, no matter what.
If he were your own flesh and blood,
would you still be so lenient with him?
Sung Min, you're looking more and
more like your dad as you get older.
You didn't look anything like
him when you were little.
That's interesting.
Whose son are you?
You're so smart and handsome!
You're perfect!
[Baek Hyun Jee]
Where have you been?
Right outside.
Don't go out too late at night.
Mom gets worried.
Hey, look at this.
Mom said she forgot
to do it. So I ironed it.
I'm not very good at this.
Just wear it tomorrow and take it
to the dry cleaner on Saturday.
Take it. My arm hurts.
Good night!
Good night.
Okay.
Why is he being so formal...
Have as much as you want.
So this is what it's like to
cook for your own family.
You didn't even cook.
You know what I mean. Geez...
Ma'am, what do you think?
I eat whatever is offered to me.
I eat when there's food.
I starve when there's no food.
Oh, that's bread!
My bread girl is here.
What about Sung Min?
He's gone. He must have left early,
so as to not see Mom.
Geez, how much did you torture him?
He went to school without eating!
Mom, is he a terrorist?
Why would she torture him?
Should I beat your first?
Geez, what's wrong with you?
You made me wait for two hours!
Sorry.
Did something happen?
It did, right? It did!
Were you embarrassed about your notebook?
Were you afraid I might tease you?
Hey, man! Everyone is like that.
No one is good right from
the start, except for me!
Hey!
Do you have time?
Be careful.
You must not have slept well last night.
Actually, I slept very well.
I have a strong mind.
You were amazing, Eun Ok.
You led us to a tie with those
pathetic promises of yours.
Don't say that.
You were amazing enough to earn 7 votes
as a hugely unproven candidate.
Oh, you have a good supporter behind you.
We need a real battle,
rather than this kind of quarrel.
I agree.
The only thing both of us hate
more than losing, is tying.
- Oh, Ma'am!
- Ma'am, you're here!
Unfortunately, yesterday's
election was called off.
The chairman had a minor
misunderstanding, but all is well now.
I hope that you won't hold bias
against him after that.
Are we going to resume the election then?
No, we are not. The chairwoman's
position will be vacant for a while.
Then, how are we going to
handle volunteer work?
Since you handled it previously,
you should take care of it for now.
The holiday events and marketing too?
About that...
Do Kyung should take care of those.
Eun Ok does all the dirty work,
and Do Kyung gets all the glory.
Good. I ask you to carry out
your respective duties
faithfully and diligently. Okay?
Yes, Ma'am.
Are you crazy? Crazy?
This is the last vote.
Seven to seven. And this one that we
couldn't open because of the chairman.
[Kim Eun Ok]
If Dad hadn't showed up,
Do Kyung would have lost.
Our efforts weren't enough to
change the hearts of the members.
Do you have any ideas
as to what we can do?
Why do you ask me that?
Isn't this what you're supposed to do?
What I'm saying is since we are in the
same boat, we should help each other--
You were so sure of it before.
Now that you're stuck,
you want me to get you out?
Madam. Madam Oh Sook Ja.
It's Oh Joo Ran.
Oh Joo Ran!
If you want to be called by that name,
do your job, Madam Oh Sook Ja!
Paternity test?
Are you sure? Really?
Yes, I want to know.
Show me your test sample.
Why?
I just want to see it!
Are you crazy?
Why did you throw that away?
What will you do after
you take that test?
What?
What will you do after you find out?
What if it is true?
What if it's not true?
I'm sorry about last night.
I said the wrong things.
I wasn't good either.
I am always on your side, no matter what.
I'll bring you a stick.
If Sung Min doesn't study,
you can beat him with it.
You don't really mean that!
What? Are you worried I might run away?
Don't worry. I go this way too.
I'm fine. You should go home.
Are you thinking for me?
Anyway, about today...
Don't worry.
I, Baek Hyun Jee, have zipped my mouth.
Yoon Sung Min!
Go now.
Okay.
Wait.
Hyun Jee.
I have a favor to ask you.
Please stop hanging out with Sung Min.
Mom!
What are you doing,
saying that to a child?
Your parents would not like
for you to see him either.
You understand what I'm saying, right?
What are you doing?
I should ask you the same thing!
Hyun Jee, go home safely.
See you again.
Yes, Sir.
What makes you so confident?
Aren't you embarrassed?
You don't feel ashamed?
I'm not embarrassed or ashamed about
anything concerning your studies.
I'm sure.
That way you don't feel as guilty.
What are you talking about?
Let's talk.
Don't touch me.
And leave me alone.
What?
You stay here. I'll go beat him up!
Want some chicken?
Dad!
It's okay. You're an adult now.
You should learn how to
drink from your dad.
Toast! Man to man!
Okay!
One coke please!
Wow, my son really is
a good student, huh?
Say what you want to say.
I have nothing to say.
Wow, this is good!
I get to have drinks with my son!
I did that earlier...
because Mom was harsh on Hyun Jee.
I know.
A real man knows how
to protect his woman.
Dad.
Why did you marry Mom?
Huh?
Who proposed? Mom did?
Geez, why do you say that?
You can't say no if someone asks.
Hey!
I'm the one who's drinking.
But you're talking drunk.
Dad.
Why are you good to me?
Why do you always side with me?
I side with my child, of course.
Honestly, there were a lot of times
you didn't like me, right?
Don't even get me started.
I didn't like you long before
you were born!
Your mom had really bad morning sickness.
The labor process was horrible
when you were coming out.
My wife was hurting!
Of course I was upset.
"What kind of baby is this?
Come on out!"
But then you came out,
and when you saw me...
You smiled so brightly!
Geez, you were definitely my son.
You had striking facial features.
You had a big penis!
Dad...
"This boy will be someone great!"
"This boy will make lots of girls cry!"
I need to go to the bathroom.
Eat up!
I was so upset that Father ruined the
election that you would have won.
Take this. "Congratulations,"
and "Cheer Up."
I have no reason to take this.
Honestly, I didn't win the election.
You aren't hurt because
of what happened, are you?
I'll resolve it with Dad soon.
Soon? When?
You said you wanted to show me
how you could change, right?
You haven't changed a bit.
No change, no growth!
When I see how you do things, I don't
feel Hyun Jee and I can depend on you.
Does that mean...
there's a small part of you
that wants to get back together?
Mom!
Hyun Jee!
Hi, Dad.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
No.
I don't think that's the case.
What happened?
I said nothing.
- Go home.
- Okay.
Baek Gi Bum!
How dare you insult me...
Oh Sook Ja?
It's clear now,
why I can't write.
I'm bad at writing scripts.
I have no talent!
Why do you say that?
Director Bong from Poland!
Hey, I'm serious.
Okay, okay.
I surrender!
You and I are going to be
killed by those gangsters.
Even if we're going to die,
let's order another bottle of wine.
This is an expensive bar.
You have the company
credit card. Use it.
What if they say something?
I'll take care of it.
Anyway, this is red wine.
And my blood is red too.
I'll pay with my blood!
What's the point of living
if I can't even write a script?
Order.
Geez, kill those gangsters.
Kill...
Wow.
- Oh, my!
- I'm sorry. I apologize.
I was not careful. I'm sorry.
Perhaps... you are the movie director?
Wow, you know?
You're Madam Oh,
from One Heart, next door?
By the way, what were you doing here?
I felt I needed to suddenly stop here.
The painting that I fell in love with
in Europe is hanging on the wall.
Oh! Jan Van Dyke?
The Arnolfini Marriage!
Crazy!
You know this painting?
- Sure!
- Sure?
This painting!
There's a secret hidden in it.
Hidden secret!
You knew that?
The secret in the mirror!
Huh?
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Who are you? Huh?
Hello, Madam Oh.
But what have you done to me?
Oh, no! What's going on?
Calm down! What happened,
already happened.
Happened? What happened? Huh?
Nothing happened between us.
I drank so much last night,
I can't remember anything.
And... I... I am an educated man.
Calm down!
What you need to do now, is go to the
bathroom, and turn on the shower.
When you come to your senses, try to
remember what happened last night.
And see if you can still say
those irresponsible words!
Do you know what I'm saying?
Yes, I do.
Okay. Turn around and go to the bathroom.
Hurry up!
Go now. Go.
Go now.
Oh, my God! I'm crazy!
Geez.
Josephine was a great politician's
woman, and she was older!
But Napoleon loved all of her,
even her soul!
He must have known what would
happen to him if he loved her!
Please finish me today!
There's nothing to be afraid of
when you risk your life for something!
This is my first time. Please kill me!
I think it was then!
My mind woke up!
So fresh, like mint candy!
I had an overflowing inspiration
for my script!
Okay... Okay... Okay...
That's right.
"What were you doing here?"
"I felt I needed to suddenly stop here."
And then I pushed her to the wall...
Geez!
Mr... Chairman...
Well... you haven't gone to work yet?
Don't tell me...
You stayed up all night like that.
Mr. Chairman...
As a matter of fact, I...
You're home, Madam Oh!
I was so worried that
you might have left me!
Thank you for coming back!
I was wrong.
Wait a moment.
Geez, please stop, Mr. Chairman.
Last night, I...
I left the man who couldn't trust me.
But today, like a boomerang...
I came back here.
Therefore, let's forget...
Our mistakes yesterday.
Thank you, Honey!
Madam Oh!
Mr. Chairman.
I missed you.
I have to go.
I have a marketing meeting.
Oh, okay. Did Director Bong go somewhere?
He's going crazy over the script.
He disappeared at the bar. I'm worried.
I see.
Did you buy that?
No. This is my son's.
Bye.
Bye. Keep up the good work!
Thanks.
[Paternity Test]
What makes you so confident, Mom?
Aren't you embarrassed?
You don't feel ashamed?
Why are you good to me?
Honestly, there were a lot of times
you didn't like me, right?
I happened to see you.
I just wanted to apologize for my mom.
You don't have to.
I understand why she said those words.
Is something wrong?
Are you sick?
Well, I guess you can say I'm sick.
But it's really nothing.
I'll tell you if you can stay calm.
Want to know?
You're scared.
Then pretend you didn't see it.
I'll telling you this just
in case you imagine things.
I'm not like a sad dying heroine
in a movie.
So don't go there.
Anyway, did you sort out your thoughts?
Looks like you aren't there yet.
See you later.
Okay. Hang in there.
We only have a few boxes to go.
Oh man!
Do Kyung didn't come.
Geez, she was so eager
during the election.
Isn't she being a bit negligent?
Everyone else is working hard.
Why don't you call her, Kyung Mee?
Should I?
I'm late.
Oh, Do Kyung!
Hey...
Did you have a good time?
What do you mean?
Director Baek asked my husband to buy
flowers for him so he could cheer you up.
He was worried you might have
been hurt because of the election.
Maybe the two of you
will get back together.
Tell me the truth. Is there a possibility
you'll get back together with him?
Why are you hesitating?
If you become his wife
you'll become the chairwoman
without any need for an election.
You don't want that?
Eun Ok, you're really old-fashioned.
You should live your own life.
Why do you keep trying to
piggyback off of your man?
Is that what you want from Tae Soo?
Anyway, are you looking
for a place to live yet?
Do you even have time
to be here right now?
What do you mean?
What is she saying?
- Kyung Mee!
- Oh, my.
Tell me.
I'm not sure if it's accurate.
But my husband said...
The chairman told Tae Soo
to leave the house.
Are you okay?
Well... I need to get going.
Sun Young, please take care o
the rest for me.
Do Kyung...
Why did you say that?
I don't know.
Yes, the owner put it up for rent.
Did the chairman come
speak to you, himself?
His secretary came.
He said the chairman would
like to have a new renter.
Have you gotten many inquiries?
This neighborhood is popular these days.
I think it will be rented out
before springtime.
You will need to look for a new place.
Why are you outside? It's cold!
Why didn't you tell me?
Huh?
Oh... it's just that...
The chairman told us to leave the house?
What do we do now?
Geez, I'm dying from running!
You're worried we're going to
freeze to death on the street?
I thought you came out
because you missed me.
What? It's not true?
Do you not know that he
thinks of me as his own son?
No father would kick out his own son.
He was just upset with me because
of what happened with Soo Min.
I was rude to him.
I went to see the realtor.
Secretary Ma told him to
take care of it soon.
The secretary was exaggerating!
He only knows how to look serious.
He can't take a joke.
The realtor must be disappointed.
Are you sure?
Are you sure that that's the case?
Geez, how many times
do you want me to tell you?
Do you want to talk to the chairman?
Do you want to ask him yourself?
Forget it.
Do you know how scared I was?
I was worried to death!
Renting a house is expensive.
Let's go in. It's cold.
Did the kids come home?
What about Sung Min?
I don't know. He won't
come out of his room.
What about Soo Min?
Sung Min.
What?
I have a lot to do.
You asked me why I married your mom.
As a matter of fact...
I held onto her and begged.
That's how I married her.
If I hadn't done that
how else would I be able to marry a woman
as beautiful and smart as your mom?
You wouldn't agree?
Sung Min...
No matter what you may know,
or what you might have heard...
Nothing changes.
I am your father, and you are my son.
The 16th generation of
the Yoon family from Pal Bong.
Yoon Sung Min.
It's not good to hurt
your mom because of that...
Let me tell you something.
A man should remain calm in any
situation he may find himself in.
You know what I'm saying, right?
Okay. Eat some. I peeled them.
[Keep us safe today.]
Wow!
This is it! It has it all!
It's so good!
[A Man of Two Faces]
- You mean it?
- Would I be celebrating if I didn't?
Fists, Napoleon, Josephine?
It's a love story.
But it's so refreshing!
Big time! It sounds great!
Promise me an autograph when you
become director beloved by the nation.
I was right! Please,
from now on, trust him.
Good job, Director.
Thank you!
I... I went through a lot.
Until I could write this story--
Is this your story?
Huh?
The dialogues and the situations...
they're so real!
You must have a lot of
experience with women!
Fess up!
Director Bong, congratulations!
Good job!
Tae Soo!
Things started working out
ever since I became CEO, right?
Sister, I'm going to have
dinner with a friend.
Aren't you going back to Seoul?
What now? Tae Soo said
I can stay as long as I want.
Be quiet! Go back to
Seoul tomorrow. Okay?
I'll be back, Ma'am.
Your face is pretty and
your clothes are pretty.
That looks nice. It looks warm.
Enjoy your dinner.
She must be cooking deodeok.
It's been so long since we had deodeok.
My mouth is getting watery
just looking at them.
Mother, this is for the chairman.
I'll make some for you tomorrow.
Forget it.
I don't deserve to eat deodeok.
I can eat rice with water.
Do you have something to say?
No, of course not.
Just say it. It's better
that way for the both of us.
I'm not going to the senior center
until springtime.
- Do you want to go somewhere else?
- Go where?
I just want to stay home.
Yeah? Why?
It's cold...
And I don't like how Hye Sook's
mom brags about everything.
Brags about what?
Don't get me started!
She's a mean old hag!
She's boasts and boasts.
Her son bought her a mink coat.
When she wears that mink coat,
she has this strange look in her eyes.
She wags her bottom,
this way, and that way.
She won't take off her coat
while she's eating, or in class.
She's the only one
sweating in her seat.
What a scene!
So what can I do? I should stay
home if I don't want to see her.
I wish I could buy you a mink coat!
I'd like one too.
Don't misunderstand!
I'm not asking for one.
I guess the prices went down.
I see your sister has one too.
Geez, my body feels cold.
My heart feels cold.
Geez, when is Spring coming?
Geez.
Yes, Teacher?
Blank paper?
What do you mean?
Why would Sung Min
turn in a blank paper?
What's on your mind
that you don't even know I'm here?
Oh... you are here.
It's been a while.
You called me out here for a drink.
It's nothing. Take this.
Is it about your family?
Drink it first.
Geez, why am I feeling so sad
all of a sudden?
You're worried your family
might lose the house.
Tae Soo The Great had to call me
out here to buy me a drink.
You know the situation I'm in currently.
I'm living month to month.
I would be in big trouble if I didn't
hit the earnings quota for the month.
If I lose my home, we'll definitely
be living on the street.
Gi Bum, please speak
to the chairman for me.
Please?
You were all over me last time,
and now, now what's this?
Don't worry. I'll talked to my father.
Gi Bum, thank you!
But I'm not sure...
if my father will listen to me.
The whole world knows that he
likes you more than he likes me.
He already disowned me.
What should I do?
Like you say, I feel like
dying from running.
By the way, Tae Soo...
You've worked for over twenty years.
You must have some savings to your name.
You should have owned a house by now.
Did you spend it all?
I have two children and my mother.
It's expensive to raise kids!
Don't yell at me. Did I give them to you?
With my salary, it would take over ten
years to save enough to buy a house.
That's not my business.
There are so many condos everywhere.
I don't understand why more
people don't own homes.
I hear tons of units remain unsold.
It's a mystery.
How unfair is that, right?
Don't you agree?
Yoon Sung Min!
You turned in a blank test paper
turned off your phone,
and skipped cram school!
How dare you come home?
Should I leave?
You've gone insane!
What's wrong with you?
Aren't you going to college?
I'll take care of it. You leave me alone.
I'm your mom.
That's why I can't leave you alone.
I can't forgive you this time.
Forgive?
Do you have the right to say that?
I have the right because I'm your mother.
I gave birth to you, and I raised you!
Only an innocent mother can say that.
Honey!
How dare you! Did I ask you not to?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Sweet Savage Family]
You need to tell me first.
Tell me who my birth father is.
I don't want Dad to find out.
What's wrong? What did you do?
This is my fault.
This isn't realistic! How can he
run away with a gangster’s wife?
He promised to give him the house
if he kicked Lee Do Kyung out of Daejeon.
Tae Soo!