Subtitles by DramaFever
We need a new venture.
I will support you. Just
find a new business item.
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
Hanbat Pictures!
The chairman likes to do things big.
He deposited three billion
dollars right away.
Is it Tae Soo or the movie
that you're investing in?
He's been edgy since he
invested in the movie.
Did they run away?
Didn't the chairman deposit
three billion won?
Get out and find him.
Run!
Stop right there!
Do you know what money you stole?
Do it right.
I want to see how big his smile can get.
I'm doing this because I trust you.
It can change our lives!
Where is that bastard now?
Did you do that?
Then why is his dead body in your trunk?
Ouch!
Over there...
[Sweet Savage Family]
[Episode 3]
Excuse me. I need to inspect your car.
Ah...
Oh, you are working hard.
Is something going on?
An armed soldier deserted
the base nearby.
Oh... Geez.
We got grocery at the market.
Right.
Please open the trunk.
Honey...
What are you doing now?
Excuse me.
Can I see you for a second?
Just for a moment... Yeah.
Well, here.
I asked you to open
the trunk, but what is this?
Well, it's okay. Please get
yourself something to eat.
Look carefully.
It's not a 5,000 won bill.
Keep up the good work.
Over here.
Please come over here.
Honey.
Honey!
What was that?
What the heck is going on? Huh?
Huh? What is this sound?
Honey!
Huh? What the heck!
I'm scared!
- What...
- I'm scared?
- What the heck is going on?
- I'm scared!
What the heck?
Oh my goodness!
Please chase that vehicle!
What?
We don't know what will
happen if we don't stop him!
Hurry!
Why do you ask me that?
Get out now.
It'll take a few minutes until
the special team gets here.
It's not my business.
Go to the Ace Department Store.
His ex-girlfriend works there.
- That's close to Soo Min's school!
- What?
He even has a rifle and grenades.
Grenades?
Yes.
If he holds someone hostage
it can get really serious.
Sir, I am begging you.
Many people's lives are depending on you.
Gosh, I'm going to die from running.
My goodness!
What's happening here!
Gosh!
I can't believe this.
Oh, it's that vehicle!
Oh? Yeah!
Ah! Honey!
Oh my goodness!
Oh, gosh!
Honey, get off right up there.
Why?
There's a short cut. I know it
because I take Soo Min to school.
Right now!
Okay, I got it.
Hold tight!
I said hold tight!
We got ahead of him.
Get close and stop the vehicle.
What? You can't do that!
We are buckled up.
We won't get hurt.
In the worst case, the trunk
might suffer some damages.
Not the trunk!
Don't worry. You'll get compensated.
Ah!
What are you doing?
He might get ahead of you!
Be quiet!
Honey!
Duck and cover!
Oh, man. What just happened?
Are you okay?
My neck!
What the heck?
What on earth just happened? Huh?
Gosh!
Around 11 AM today
an armed solider deserted the base nearby
with a grenade and 30 bullets.
He was arrested around 1 PM right here.
The officials said that he was headed
toward a department store in Daejeon
where his ex-girlfriend who
had left him was working.
According to the military and
police joint investigation
his arrest was made possible
thanks to one brave citizen.
Right here, we have the hero who risked
his life and saved many people's lives.
Hello.
Oh, hello.
You did an amazing thing today.
Aren't you hurt?
Well, my neck is a bit... but I'm fine.
I see.
Judging from the damages in your car
I can imagine how serious
the situation was. How was it?
I just did what I was supposed to do.
It would've been bad if he
had held a hostage downtown.
My daughter’s school is really
close to that department store.
Oh, I see. Well...
I heard it was almost like in a movie.
Interestingly, you are making
a movie now.
Oh, yes...
It's a movie about gangsters in Daejeon.
- Gangster movie?
- Yes.
Wow. I wish you good luck on your movie!
Ah!
Oh! Are you okay?
Are you okay?
The police department decided to give the
Brave Citizen Award to Mr. Yoon Tae Soo
for his courageous action, which
helped resolve the situation.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Don't touch me.
- I got it.
This afternoon, an armed deserter
was arrested after a long car chase
thanks to a brave citizen who
risked his life to save others.
This citizen is making
a movie based on Daejeon
which became an instant top news.
Now from Reporter Ma Bong Choon.
The military and police
joint investigation team...
What the heck!
Grandma, Dad is on TV!
- Hello.
- Oh... well...
Hello.
You did an amazing thing today.
Aren't you hurt?
Well, my neck is a bit... but I'm fine.
I was on TV just now.
If I turned myself in,
it should've been then.
It's too late now.
We can't delay it any longer.
If we told them there's
a corpse in my trunk
would they thank us for telling them?
They would suspect us and
wouldn't let us go home.
And what about the kids?
Really?
Ms. Kim Eun Ok?
It's you, right?
From the Neighborhood Watch Team?
Oh! Sir!
How have you been?
- Have you been well?
- Of course.
Aren't you the man who
got the deserter, Mr. Yoon Tae Soo?
Oh... Yes.
This is my husband.
Wow, it's nice to meet you.
Oh, yes.
You are an exemplary couple.
We are planning to hold
a ceremony next week
to give you a Brave Citizen
award medal and a plate.
Will you be able to attend?
Oh... sure.
By the way, what brought
you to the police station?
Well...
That is...
We were just wondering
if we should give them more
details about the incident today.
Wow, you are such law-abiding citizens!
If everyone were like you
our country would be
a much better place to live!
Oh...
Oh, thank you.
Dig deep!
Do it faster!
Geez, I'm working on it.
Oh, man! There are so many rocks!
Geez!
Why does she keep calling me?
Hi, Kyung Mee!
Congratulate me?
Please don't say that.
Right now?
Thanks a lot.
Of course, we are having a good time.
Okay, talk to you later!
Gosh.
What are you doing?
Waiting for snacks?
Do it faster. I'm scared
to death right now.
You know I hurt my back earlier.
It must be bad.
My goodness.
Give me that. Step aside.
You dug this spot forever!
Oh my back.
- It's killing me.
- Get out.
Okay. What am I going to do?
Is there anything you do right?
You can't do well at night.
You can't dig.
How could your back give out already?
Gosh, your back is useless!
Gosh!
Oh, my!
What do we do now?
I'm scared.
Gosh.
Shut your mouth!
Put.... put him away.
You do it. I'm scared.
My goodness.
Mr. Son!
Your feet must hurt. Stop!
Hey, Mr. Son!
You will hurt your feet!
Hey!
Geez! Geez!
You are a rat!
Bastard! Wake up!
Huh? Hey?
Wake up!
Wake up, bastard...
No!
Shit.
Should we call 911?
Are you crazy?
Then what should we do?
Give me a minute.
I need to think.
I'm sorry. We are closed--
I don't like how you
show up without notice.
Stop doing that.
You hate seeing me that much?
What a strange question.
We are already divorced.
Get to the point. I need to go home.
Hyun Jee...
I wondered if I could see her.
Do you mean it
or are you just saying that?
It's better to keep it the way it is
if you're going to only hurt her.
You said she missed me.
I'm curious too.
I will ask Hyun Jee then.
What did you talk about with Tae Soo?
It seemed nice.
I didn't want to believe it.
But you were really spying on me?
And you came here to ask me that?
Just answer me.
I don't know why I have to answer that.
But it is as you saw.
If I was smiling, it means
I was happy to see him.
If I looked upset just like now
I was probably angry.
Need more explanation?
Are you defending Tae Soo too?
A movie-maker? Heroic citizen?
He must look amazing.
But he's nothing.
It's going to be over for him soon!
Why are we here...?
Well, what about it?
How can you think of that
in this kind of situation?
What the heck are you thinking about?
You're covered with dirt.
Should I wash first?
Yes, you wash first.
'Should I wash first?'
'You go first.'
Who would say those words
in this kind of context?
Why do you say that?
What's going to happen to us?
I looked it up online.
You get seven years for
throwing away a dead body.
How are we going to send
Sung Min to college?
Soo Min is so sensitive.
She could go astray.
What's going to happen to our kids?
Eun Ok.
Having a gangster father wasn't enough.
Now both of their parents are criminals.
Listen to me.
Please listen to me.
You know nothing about this.
You didn't see anything.
You didn't do anything.
You eat and send the kids
like you always did.
Wipe this from your memory!
Does it solve anything?
There's no secret in this world.
Someday everything will be revealed.
What if we get the blame?
Honey...
Let's go tell the police.
You didn't kill him.
We buried his body because
we were out of our minds.
If we tell them the truth, they'll
take that into consideration.
Honey, please?
Please? Honey...
Please... let's do that.
Let's do that.
You!
- What are you doing?
- You!
You, bastard!
As a gangster wife, I couldn't
sleep well for 18 years!
How could you do this to me?
Did I ask you to make me rich?
Did I ask you to serve me like queen?
How could you do this to me?
I want my life back!
Bring my life back, you bastard!
Asshole!
You are a bastard!
Bastard! Bastard!
Bastard.
You are bad! Bad!
Oh, man!
The heroic citizen, Yoon Tae Soo is home!
You look different!
My son, I'm so proud of you!
I am still alive because
I had to see this!
Mom, you were on TV too.
That's right!
What's wrong with her on this joyful day?
Just leave her alone. She must be tired
because it was pretty traumatic.
Dad, what happened to your face?
Huh?
Oh, no!
What happened to your face, my child?
It must have happened during the chase.
It's nothing.
Glorious bruises!
Look here and tell me more details.
Let's do it another time. I'm tired too.
Do it now. I promised to
send a video to my friends.
Just do it.
You are strong enough to
catch an armed soldier.
Then show only this side.
All right!
Go, go!
I hurt my back.
subtitles synced by riri13
How hard did you work your back
that it's already giving out?
[Tree-planting ceremony for
righteous Yoon Tae Soo]
- It's a good day!
- Yes, it is.
This is big!
Congratulations!
This is a righteous tree!
It's going to bring blessings!
Plant it well.
To Yoon Tae Soo!
Toast!
What if that deserter had thrown
a grenade at the department store?
It would have been bad!
Tae Soo saved hundreds of lives!
Yes, he did!
Mr. Yoon Tae Soo did an amazing thing!
Please don't say that.
It's not enough that
I'm buying him a drink.
He should get a purple
medal at the Blue House!
The movie, and now the medal...
You hit many home runs.
You'll hit a grand slam home run soon.
Something big is going to happen.
Gosh, what are you talking about?
Sir, did you hear that?
What he did was worth one billion
won in advertising for the movie.
Wow, is that so?
Congratulations, Chairman Baek.
Gosh, Mr. Son is missing again
on this joyful day.
I told the assemblyman I would
bring Mr. Son this weekend.
What? You mean Mr. Son?
Yes, he has something
important to talk about.
Make sure to bring Mr. Son tomorrow.
We have to make sure we are
on the same page, okay?
Well... sure.
The movie is finally getting made!
Wait and see.
You will make it big! Okay?
Hey, why did you want to see me here?
Gi Bum, I need your help.
Did something happen?
You know the chairman told me
to bring Mr. Son tomorrow.
Then you should do that.
I can't. He's dead.
What? Are you crazy?
It wasn't me.
Someone killed him and put
his body in my trunk.
Who did that?
Anyone who might have done that?
I don't know. I have no clue.
This is bad.
If Dad finds out, he'll be really upset.
Gi Bum, you are the only
person I can depend on.
I'm standing on the edge
of a cliff right now.
I'm in total darkness.
Okay, what should I do then?
Can you hold off the chairman
for a while?
I need to find out who did it.
I don't want to disappoint the chairman.
Would I be your friend
if I couldn't do that much?
Thank you, Gi Bum.
Mr. Son...?
How could you and your wife do that...
Are you out of your mind?
What matters is now.
I need to find out who killed Mr. Son.
Wait.
Isn't it strange?
That person is trying to frame you.
But why is he not doing anything?
Since you were on TV just now
this is a perfect time to hit you.
The chairman wants to see Mr. Son.
That's the real problem.
What kind of women is our One
Heart trying to produce?
Kim Eun Ok...
I am sorry.
Our team leader, Kim Eun Ok
was the example.
I want you to learn from her.
That's why I invited all of you here.
One Heart!
You didn't have to do this.
I have done nothing.
Did you see that?
She's humble.
That is the beginning of
being a good wife.
Eun Ok, your husband is
doing really well.
Mine doesn't catch a deserter,
but only gets traffic tickets.
Young Jae's dad is doing well too.
Are you serious?
He came home drunk last night, saying
he wants to quit and run away.
I'm so sick of him! He's like a ghost!
The members of One Heart don't
speak ill of their husbands.
I am sorry, Madam.
Oh, wow!
What's all this?
I can't just do nothing when
something good happened to my friend.
Congrats, Eun Ok.
You don't have to do this.
I was so happy to see Tae Soo on TV.
When he came here last time
we couldn't talk much.
Tae Soo came here?
You didn't know that?
What? Did the two of you
already saw each other?
You guys were first loves to each other.
How long has it been?
How was it, huh?
Please.
What? I was just joking.
Kyung Mee is right.
There's nothing. That's why
I'm joking around too.
You aren't upset, right?
Well... of course not.
That's right.
A relationship between a man and
a woman isn't always about romance.
We need to be gracious about
others' past romantic relationships.
That's the first step to
become a mature person.
Madam, you and I are like-minded people.
Is that so?
This weekend the chairman
is meeting an assemblyman
with Mr. Son.
You know that right?
With Mr. Son?
Of course, because it's about
investing in the movie.
That's great! Now you have
a politician on board!
Mr. Yoon's movie will
have a lot of support!
Yeah, right.
Wow! Wow!
That's Chungcheong-do's famous kimchi!
You love our herb kimchi, Mr. Chairman.
I tried to be here right
before your dinner time.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
Nope. I can finish a bowl
of rice quickly with this.
- Well, Mr. Chairman.
- Yeah?
Gosh, did you forget your doctor
ordered a low-sodium diet?
Please think about your blood pressure.
Yeah, right.
Of course!
Being healthy is the most important.
Please have a small bite when
you don't have an appetite.
I'll let your housemaid know.
Tell me now.
Pardon?
I know the kimchi is just an excuse.
Now get to the point.
Well... it's not quite like that.
I heard you are going to see
an assemblyman this weekend.
And?
Of course it's great to have a powerful
support like that for the movie.
However, I wonder if it's
giving you too much burden.
Not only Tae Soo...
But also Mr. Son and everyone else
should show how they do it on their own!
I think that's the right thing.
You're saying...
I should let them do it on their own
without others' help?
Is that it?
It's rude to turn it down
when the elders want to help.
Pardon?
Well, Mr. Chairman made that arrangement
because he had a plan.
Also, it's good to help out
one another in the local community.
Isn't that right, Mr. Chairman?
Of course it's right.
Madam Oh is right about that.
I want to show Tae Soo and Mr. Son
how I get Assemblyman Kim
on board for the movie!
This is why I adore you, Eun Ok.
Others are busy bribing.
But you worry that your husband
might lose his independence.
She knows how to support her husband.
That's why she's the leader of One Heart.
I know that.
Tae Soo is so lucky!
He's blessed with you and
good people around him!
He's one lucky guy!
What will you do?
The chairman told you to
bring Mr. Son tomorrow.
Don't worry.
I have known him for years.
I will take care of it.
You just take care of the kids.
Are you sure?
You are sure nothing will happen?
Geez, don't you worry!
Come here.
It's been a while. Should
I put you to bed tonight?
Geez! Just sleep!
Geez! What timing!
- Gosh, you're dense.
- Why do you always hit me?
My goodness!
He couldn't come again?
I'm sorry.
Did I ask him to come play with me?
I'm trying to get a golden
badge on board for the movie!
He didn't even come to the
blessing ceremony. What's wrong?
I gave you a new arena.
So you should do better.
Do you want to go back to the clubs?
No, it's not that.
Then what is it?
Why are you acting so timidly
like a different person?
Did something happen?
I'm just being concerned.
I know you will do well, Tae Soo.
But make sure to bring Mr. Son when
I see the assemblyman this weekend.
Yes, Sir.
Okay. You can leave now.
Did you want to see me?
You are here. Sit down.
How are things? Are you busy?
I could have been busy. You know.
Did you hear anything about
the movie from Tae Soo?
No. Why?
Nothing. I was just curious.
Where the heck is Mr. Son?
Ask Tae Soo.
You should find out.
Don't say anything to Tae Soo.
Did something happen?
Sir, I brought him.
Director, I'm sorry for asking
you to come, when you are busy.
Don't worry.
You must be disappointed
I didn't pay much attention.
No, Sir. I am not disappointed at all.
By the way, why did you want to see me?
Let's just talk.
When was the last time you saw Mr. Son?
The day we had a ceremony
for your investment.
I haven't seen him since then.
You mean he disappeared the
day after he got the money.
Did Mr. Son say anything?
He told me to stay in Seoul because
it could be dangerous here.
He said he'd contact me.
You mean he felt in danger, right?
In danger...? I mean...
Your investment...
You mean he was threatened
by someone, right?
- That's not it...
- Be quiet.
Go on.
Mr. Yoon took me and
Producer Lee to a lake...
And he would put me in the water...
He told us to make a movie that's worth
three billion won for only one billion.
A low-budget high-quality movie...
he said I should make that...
What?
He's saying... someone
took two billion won.
What happened to Mr. Son?
I don't know that much.
If you don't, who does?
I think there's only one
person who would know that.
The one who stole the two billion won.
Who took Director Bong?
The secretary of Choong Shin
Construction was here.
When?
It's been a few hours.
You should have told me!
I didn't know it would take this long.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Director Bong!
Yeah.
Are you okay?
I am fine.
Where were you?
I went to see the chairman.
What?
What did he say?
He asked where Mr. Son was.
And what?
I told him he disappeared.
I'm sorry.
I felt my life was in danger.
The chairman found out then!
[Dad, bring ice cream
when you come home!]
Dad!
My ice cream!
Thank you!
- You're home.
- Thanks!
I'm home.
The people at the senior center are
demanding that I should treat them!
Are you busy tomorrow?
Mom... let's do it another time.
Another time? When?
Mom... Do I have to do that?
Dad, when are they giving you the medal?
They'll do that when it's time.
I became a star at school because of you!
That's nice, but the teachers
always make me do things now.
Gosh!
Stop talking about that.
Is something going?
No.
Then don't make that face.
You are someone who will
do great things. Smile.
Your facial expressions
can change your fate.
I got it.
Tae Soo, speaking of
facial expressions...
The man with good facial expressions...
why is he siding with Gi Bum?
What do you mean?
You know the man.
You showed him on the phone when
you tried to catch the swindler.
He thanked me for saying he'd succeed.
Things will go well for you, Sir.
Thank you, Ma'am.
You mean, he was with Gi Bum?
When? Where?
When was that?
I had seafood stew with
a friend at a restaurant.
I saw the man talking with Gi Bum.
Gi Bum went to Pyungchang that day?
I got it.
Could it be the casino in Gwangwon-do?
Fraud, gambling, violations of
Foreign Currency Control Law...
He goes to Las Vegas and
Macao as if he lives there.
I said let go!
I just need to see who came here.
Let go!
We have no choice, Sir.
Hey!
Geez.
Gosh.
Oh.
It's me.
Really?
Okay. I'll be there within two hours.
- Is it here?
- Yes, Boss.
Gi Bum tortures guys here.
He probably worked on Mr. Son here
and put him in your trunk when he died.
Gi Bum wouldn't do that.
Boss, look at this.
What's this?
His hands were probably
tied up with that.
Looks like he used all of
his strength to escape.
Why, you can't still believe it?
Gi Bum is the one who killed Mr. Son!
You're being too quick to say that.
Gosh, Gi Bum has a real good friend here.
Bub Gyu may fess up if we beat him.
If that's not enough, just get Gi Bum!
You can't do that.
Is there anything we
can't do at this point?
Be quiet.
I'll take care of it.
You better seal your mouth.
Say something.
I heard you wanted to see me.
I almost couldn't recognize you.
Why? Because I became too pretty?
Because you look like a grown-up.
True. I saw you at the
zoo for the last time.
It's been 9 years and 3 months.
Why did you come here?
You were an actress in training.
I quit. It was boring.
Why suddenly?
You were about to debut.
You worked hard.
Why did you age so much?
Do you have a girlfriend?
I heard Grandpa set you up
for blind dates.
Who said that? Your mom?
I guess it's true.
You are embarrassed.
Anyway, I'll be disappointed
if you meet just anyone.
She better be prettier, cooler...
and better than Mom.
I'm not sure such woman really exists.
Hyun Jee.
I am really sorry.
- About what?
- Huh?
About everything... everything.
Next time when you come, write
down what you're going to say.
Or record it and just play it.
I don't want to see you
babbling like that.
Bye.
What's up?
What is it this time?
Gi Bum.
Back in high school...
We got caught smoking by the chairman.
We were scolded big time.
Do you remember?
Of course I do. Only I got beaten up.
Actually I was jealous of you.
You have a father who could beat you up.
What the heck are you trying to say?
Now that I think about it, we
had the most fun back then.
We had no worries.
Every day was fun and exciting.
But now... My wife, mom, and kids...
I feel such a burden on my shoulders.
It's hard to make it every day.
But that's what I guess I live for.
Tae Soo...
- I wouldn't have been alive without you.
- What?
Gi Bum.
We aren't just friends.
Aren't we like brothers?
Was it fun to watch me
suffering all this time?
Your prank was over the line.
You spill soup and I get messy.
It happens all the time
so I'm fine by that.
But if it involves my family
it's a different story!
You should have cleaned that up
even though you were in a hurry.
What if someone else found it?
Explain it well to the chairman.
You know I consider him my own father.
I may not get his love
but I don't want him to hate me.
Oh, man. I'm tired.
Mr. Chairman.
Say something.
It's true that Mr. Son is dead.
He was in my trunk, and I buried him.
Is it because of the money?
Do you really doubt me?
Oh, Tae Soo.
Just tell him the truth.
You know my dad hates lies.
I was shocked to see the pictures.
Gi Bum... Why are you doing this?
I've done enough. You should
do as much for me too.
Isn't spilling soup enough? Now
you want to turn over the table?
What are you talking about?
Mr. Chairman. It's me, Tae Soo.
You don't trust me?
Then who did it?
The one who killed him should know.
Dad, the game is over.
It's pointless to ask him.
Be quiet!
Tell me who did it.
Sir...
Just say it.
If it's not you, who did it?
Who did it?
That is...
Enough!
What are you doing between friends?
You guys, is this all you are?
- Sir...
- Stop!
Get out.
Why did you do that?
Why did you let Tae Soo go like that?
He wouldn't do that.
There's evidence. What else do you need?
If so, is it right to doubt him first?
Was your relationship trivial like that?
Gosh, I'm dying here.
Are you Tae Soo's lawyer or something?
Mr. Son died and
three billion won disappeared.
You can't just let it slide!
You prescribe medicine
without a diagnosis?
There's an order of
business for everything.
I'll take care of it. You just stay put.
Can I believe what you just said?
Tae Soo has nothing to do with it?
Yes, Sir.
Your name is Young Il?
Yes, Song Young Il.
How long have you been under Tae Soo?
It's been five years.
Did you do a sport?
I did Taekwondo.
I made the national team, but
I quit due to an injury.
Did you enter college as a special scout?
No, I studied hard.
Wow.
You were smart and athletic.
I didn't know I had such
a talented guy on the team.
Let go. Let go!
Guys, stay outside.
Is it you or Gi Bum?
What are you talking about?
Fess up while I'm nice.
Who killed Mr. Son?
What?
You don't remember because I'm too nice?
I need to go escort Boss.
Stop talking nonsense!
What nonsense?
I asked you a question, asshole!
Fess up.
Do you want to end up being like Mr. Son?
I said I don't know.
Bastard!
Boss, I feel so wronged!
How dare he do this to me!
Bub Gyu, I mean, Assistant Manager Chang.
As of tomorrow, you are Manager Chang.
What?
Even though you are upset
you better watch your mouth.
Only the two of us know
what happened until we die.
Understand?
This is upsetting.
Kyung Mee, you must have been shocked.
Of course I was. He's just a driver
and came home like that.
Watch the tone of your voice.
What? Am I wrong?
Rest. I'll call you.
Bye.
Well...
How could you talk to him like that?
What?
Want me to repeat it?
Tae Soo sent his guys to beat up my guys!
They threatened that they
should say I killed Mr. Son.
You don't get it?
If we don't do anything
Tae Soo will hit us too!
You... really don't know
who Tae Soo is.
Dad...
Dummy!
Idiot!
What are you talking about?
I'll take care of it.
Don't do anything hasty.
Just stay put.
Honey... Eun Ok.
I'm home. Go sleep in the bed.
Honey.
Are you really okay?
Of course. Don't worry.
Everything will be okay.
What about dinner?
I already ate.
Go to sleep.
You only have a few hours to sleep before
you have to send the kids to school.
Okay, I'll go to sleep then.
Yeah.
[Keep us safe today.]
Have a good day. And be careful.
Okay. Go in.
Mr. Yoon, the chairman wants to see you.
He could just summon me.
How nice he sent a car for me!
Honey.
Don't worry. Just go in.
Sit down.
Have some tea.
Yes, Sir.
It's been over 20 years since
you first got on my boat.
Yes.
No matter what, I trust you, Tae Soo.
It's not important how
Mr. Son disappeared.
As for me, I have nothing to
worry about, because I have you.
You are reliable.
I trust you and I'm grateful to you.
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
As for me...
Trust is the most important thing
in life.
I know that very well.
You know...
I invested three billion won
because I trusted you.
Pardon?
Didn't I say that?
I invested in the movie
trusting you, not Mr. Son.
What?
Mr. Chairman!
[IOU]
[Borrower: Yoon Tae Soo]
What is this?
Mr. Son is dead, and we
have things to sort out.
Sir...
I didn't even see this money.
What the heck are you talking about now?
Just get this done quickly and move on.
Tae Soo, Dad is being nice
because it's you, Tae Soo.
You know well what could have
happened if it had been someone else.
Well... Sir!
You said this before.
Even a cow plowing a rocky field
can't work harder than I do.
All these years, I served
you with all my heart.
Please reconsider.
Are you... disobeying me?
Mr. Chairman. Please let me go.
What are you doing?
Get him to kneel down.
Honey!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Sweet Savage Family]
Let's go, honey.
We hit rock bottom.
We can't go back!
It feels like I lost my own son.
Heavens will punish you!
You're hopeless!
Why Lee Do Kyung's daughter?
Are you making a movie?
How did you raise your daughter?
What do you mean?
He didn't run away. It's an accident.
Please understand how she feels
looking for her lost son!
We ask for your support!
She's asking to find her quickly.
What do we do now?