[REGISTRATION CERTIFICATE]
From now on, I'll work
my absolute hardest for you.
I don't want Lee Do Kyung here.
I want her gone from Daejeon.
What?
I'm at the movie production office.
Can you come see me here for a moment?
We came here with evidence.
All of my guys were arrested
because of you!
Bastard!
Tae Soo.
Oh, Do Kyung.
Tae Soo!
Tae Soo.
If you want to save this woman,
then you better kneel.
Kneel down, bastard!
You bastard!
How dare you?
Kneel down!
Tae Soo...
Subtitles by DramaFever
[SWEET SAVAGE FAMILY]
Do Kyung!
What happened?
I did this, Gi Bum.
What?
He came for me.
But he saw her and took her hostage.
Bastard!
Honey!
- What happened?
- Eun Ok!
Oh, my!
Oh my...
He's not breathing.
Could he be...
What have you done?
Move over.
What are you looking at?
We have to perform CPR!
Tae Soo! What are you doing?
Perform CPR!
What? Me?
Now!
Hurry up!
Geez! I'll do it!
Geez, Do Kyung! I'll do it.
- Now!
[Episode 9]
He's breathing. He'll be okay, right?
We'll know once we get him examined.
How did this happen?
Why were you at the office, Do Kyung?
And why did Cho show up
at the tiger's den?
Now is not the time to get upset.
Let's save him first. Then we can talk.
Everything always turns to crap
because of this guy.
Hey, buddy, wake up!
Hey! Hey!
Ugh! Geez!
Geez!
You invited Do Kyung over
and she hit him so she could save you.
You're responsible for all of it!
Do you understand?
Shut up. Just find a nurse or a doctor!
We have a patient here!
This way, please.
Geez! What was that?
Geez!
What did the doctor say?
He said that he'll be fine.
He has a minor concussion.
They'll do more tests when he wakes up.
Don't worry.
His head is made of rock.
He'll survive anything.
Gi Bum and I will stay here.
The two of you should go home.
No, I can't just leave after what I did.
I'll stay until he wakes up.
I'll take care of it here.
You should go home and rest.
Hyun Jee must be waiting for you.
You should go too, honey.
The kids have school tomorrow.
Okay then.
- Go home.
Go home. Don't worry about this.
What was that?
I don't want to take
my dirt into the house.
I don't want to pass any bad luck
on to you or the kids.
Let's go in.
Really? He regained consciousness?
Yes.
He's awake. He eats.
He goes to the bathroom.
He doesn't have any brain damage, right?
That's right.
You should relax now.
Get yourself back to normal.
I'll take care of everything.
Don't worry yourself!
Okay?
Why did you say he woke up?
Should I tell her that we still
don't know when he'll wake up?
Plus, the doctor said there isn't any
brain damage, so he should be fine.
Still, you shouldn't have said that.
To be honest, I wish he would
just never wake up.
You feel the same way, right?
I'm not you! You're evil!
What the...
What?
What the hell is this?
He was here when
we went to see the doctor.
Oh, no... Did he wake up and run away?
He could have it out for us.
The police could get him too!
No way! We have to find him!
You're a writer?
But... Madam...
Shouldn't that be a decision for
the executive producer to make?
The chairman gave his okay.
And the director and producer
also gave their okay's.
Is there more to this
decision-making process?
Wow! Then from now on...
We should call you
Writer Oh, not Madam Oh.
I can tell this movie is going to be big!
At least ten million viewers!
Now that I have become one of the writers.
The movie, "The Man of Two Faces"
is going to be the pride of One Heart.
And everyone in the Choong Shim clan
should work on it.
Everyone, do we understand?
- Of course!
- Yes, we do.
Great.
Oh, Do Kyung.
How is your character analysis going?
Pardon me?
Oh... that. Not yet.
Wait a little bit.
I'll inject some soul
into that character.
There's this character...
who will play opposite you.
It'll be a minor role but...
She's a powerful character who
is supposed to provoke you.
Using film terms, she's a scene-stealer.
That brings me to my point.
To freshen things up a bit
I want to pick one of you
for that character.
Are you saying you want to
cast someone from this group?
Bingo!
Everyone here seems to be interested.
Why don't we hold an audition tonight
instead of our regular book club meeting?
What do you think?
That sounds great!
That sounds like fun!
Great!
What? She's holding an audition?
Yes, that's what I said.
The ladies are super excited.
Are you going to let them do this?
A film is a director's work of art.
Yet, you have no power over it.
I'm not even a director. I'm a failure.
What are you talking about?
This is the time for you
to be strong and focused!
Honestly, in this gang's den...
You and I have been through
all of this hardship to get here.
Right, Director Bong?
In times like these, I really wish
we had Mr. Son. Don't you agree?
Why are you bringing up the man
who deserted us and ran away?
I wonder how he's doing.
I wonder if he's alive.
Stop talking about Mr. Son!
It makes me even more upset.
Geez!
You're so loud! I can't sleep!
Geez, where is Tae Soo anyway?
Is Mr. Yoon Tae Soo here?
What brings you here?
Hello.
I'm Kim Eun Sil,
Mr. Yoon's sister-in-law.
He's not here.
I know.
You're the director, right?
You look just like a movie director.
I have a good eye, you know.
I'm a producer.
He is the director.
Yes.
Oh, I knew it.
You look very educated.
I know. Anyway, how can I help you?
My brother-in-law said he needed
a female assistant for the office.
So I thought I could help.
No, thank you.
We aren't hiring any
female assistants. I'm sorry.
Geez, it's all men here!
The office needs cleaning.
Oh, my. Look at this dust.
Do you know where
the cleaning supplies are?
I think I saw them somewhere.
Wait!
Thank you.
- You're here!
- Geez!
What are you doing in my office?
I came to see you.
I was resting for a bit.
I don't want to die
from working too hard.
I swear...
Why are you here?
You know Cho Dong Choon.
Where do you think he's hiding?
Geez, why did you lose him?
If you had caught him,
nothing would have happened!
I'm sorry...
I have flat feet, so I can't run fast.
I got it, that's fine. So go catch him!
Wait, wait, wait!
Mr. Son contacted me.
So I went to see him.
What?
But he stood me up.
He didn't show up.
Bro!
I wonder if someone got to him first.
What is Baek Gi Bum up to these days?
I do not know!
Why don't you go ask him?
My advice is that you confess to
your sins in hopes of being freed!
Tae Soo, you should listen to me!
Since he's awake,
should I bring him some oatmeal?
No, don't do that.
Just in case, I'll say this.
Don't take the blame
like you did with Mr. Son.
Report it to the police, okay?
This isn't the same situation.
We're in an entirely
different predicament now.
Are you worried about Do Kyung?
Are you worried that your first love
will go to jail or something?
You're really talking nonsense.
Then, what is it?
Why are you being indecisive?
It happened because I asked her
to come to the office.
So, was anything even
resolved because of it?
In the end, the issue with the
house still hasn't been solved.
How does her being there
make it your fault?
Nothing ever works out
because of Do Kyung!
You fox!
Get out.
I told you to get out.
You fox.
You fox!
I'm sorry, Madam. I can't do it.
Next!
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Next.
Get out!
I said, get out!
You fox!
My life is in shambles because of you!
Grab her hair violently!
- Violently?
- That's right! Violently!
Grab her hair violently! Violently!
My life is a disaster!
Violently! Violently!
Is that really okay?
Director Baek would be furious.
I know. And she's a strong candidate
for the chairwoman position.
Violently! Violently!
My life is a disaster!
Are you going to do it or not?
Make up your mind!
My life is a disaster!
I am a disaster!
I can't do it.
I am both frustrated and disappointed.
My goodness.
Is there no one here who
can play this vibrant role?
Oh my God...
Eun Ok.
Do you want to give it a try?
Oh, no! I'm not interested in acting.
This is one effective way
to help your husband.
You are the wife of
the investor of the film!
Whether the role is
a grandmother or a traitor
you should be able to play it.
Try it. Try it!
You fox!
Because of you, my life is a disaster!
You are the nuclear bomb in my life!
You are a tsunami!
I will reveal all of your
most shameful secrets!
Ha!
I'll crush you before you get the chance!
- You!
That's it! Forcefully!
That's it! Great!
Okay! Oh my God! Wow!
That was soulful acting!
I did my best.
- She's good! Wonderful!
- Wonderful!
It looks pretty good.
The code progression is a bit too simple.
Change it here a bit.
It just needs reharmonization.
How is it?
I'm thinking of using
this piece in a movie.
In a movie?
Yes, I need to make a score for a movie.
So, let's say... you've proven
yourself with your solo work.
And your music composition is good.
You passed!
So...
Are you saying you want to
make film scores with me?
We might not make it big.
But it won't be as embarrassing
if we do together, right?
So you have to do with me, okay?
You think about how to arrange it. Okay?
Hey, I didn't say I would do it.
Oh! So good.
Oh, what brings you here, Dad?
Why do you come home so late?
I was worried, Hyun Jee.
I usually come home around this hour.
Why are you overreacting?
It's cold. Let's go inside.
What are you doing?
It's cold.
Why are you here?
Oh... I ran into her nearby,
so we came together.
It's so cold! My goodness.
People could think that we live together.
I know, he was so casual
that he caught me by surprise.
I'll go change.
Are you here to talk about that man?
Does he remember how I hit him?
He was wrong to begin with.
So there isn't much for him to say.
Well, nothing happened today, right?
Yes, something big happened today.
Huh?
I haven't even decided to be in the film.
But Madam Oh just created this new role.
It was quite a scene.
Geez, she was using so much strength
from her arms to grab my hair.
What do you mean?
Just go home.
It's stressful to talk about.
I heard that there have been a lot of
burglaries because it's the end of year.
I'm a bit concerned for your safety.
Can I sleep here tonight?
Mom, don't fall for that.
He's an expert in getting his way.
That's a classic example.
You heard what she said.
Good night, Do Kyung, Hyun Jee.
I will protect you.
Geez, why is it so cold?
Why did Cho run away?
When I catch you, you're finished.
Producer Lee, please go with me.
I told you, I'm busy.
I need to work on the budget,
and hire people. I have so much to do.
I can't believe it... Hey!
Attending a scene meeting is within
the responsibilities of the producer!
Director! What is really going on?
I'm scared to go to that house.
Huh?
The chairman adores you!
What's scary about going there?
Perhaps... is there some
problem with Madam Oh?
Are you crazy?
What the heck are you thinking?
I'm just irritated.
I already finished the script.
Why do we need a new writer?
Honestly, it's good to have her.
She's not just a writer.
She's the perfect model for this story.
She's a head gangster's woman.
I like the move because
she'll make the story feel more real!
Hey, what do you think death is?
Is a movie more important
than a person's life?
Stop saying strange things. Just go.
- Strange? Strange how?
- Just go!
Oh.
Welcome! Welcome, Director Bong!
- Where is the chairman?
- He went to a funeral, so relax.
Okay! Should we start writing then?
Come this way.
Why are you doing this?
This is about our script.
Napoleon went to see Beauharnais.
But he wasn't there, and he was
left alone with Josephine.
Just the two of them.
Imagine that.
Madam...
Madam, you shouldn't do this anymore.
I'm not inspired, but rather,
I'm terrified to death!
Fear is another source of creativity!
- Please, Madam!
- No...
Wait.
I just heard a noise.
"The only thing I can hear now
is the sound of your beating heart."
What movie is that line from?
Say what comes next.
"The only thing I can
see now is your lips."
What? What is it?
Over there!
Is it... the chairman?
Mr. Chairman!
Madam Oh! What's wrong?
Over there... over there.
The man over there.
Cho Dong Choon!
How dare you come into this house?
This feels nice.
Now my body feels relaxed.
Now, I feel much better.
Now is not the time for you
to be having fun like this.
Have fun?
I guarded Do Kyung's house
all night last night.
Where is that crazy guy hiding?
Hi, Dad.
What?
Tae Soo, hurry!
Dad!
Young Master!
What the heck are you trying to do?
Where's my dad? Huh?
What's wrong, Young Master?
Did I do something wrong?
Tae Soo, you came too. It's cold outside.
Father!
What's wrong with this guy?
You think he lost his memory?
Does that make sense?
How would I know?
He showed up, out of the blue,
holding an ax over his shoulder.
And he said, "Mr. Chairman!"
And then he bowed to me!
I almost had a heart attack!
You know what he said then?
He asked where the yard dog went.
The yard dog? The Jindo
we had twenty years ago?
Yes.
I don't know what's going on.
But he seems to think that
he's still the butler of the house.
Butler?
Maybe he hurt his brain, and he lost his
memory up until some point in the past.
Maybe up to the
happiest moment in his life.
Would feeding a dog
be your happiest memory?
I can't trust him.
He acted so loyal to Dad.
But then he stole the money
out of his safe and ran away.
What?
There's no reason to discuss that.
Do you know why he might
have lost his memory?
Call the police
so they can take him away.
The police?
For starters, he trespassed in my home.
They're sure to find even more than that.
He deserves jail time.
Well... the truth is...
He and I had an argument,
and it got physical.
He hit his head against a wall,
and got this way.
What?
It wasn't serious!
He didn't get hurt.
He probably just lost his memory.
I'll take care of him.
Don't worry.
Among all of the ladies that
I have served in this house...
You are the oldest.
It seems that the chairman's taste
in women changed while I wasn't around.
Please...
So you're saying... you didn't
see anything earlier, right?
Can I have more soup?
Sit down.
Thank you, Ma'am. Thank you.
Look here. Eat as much as you want.
Mr. Butler.
I came here for a meeting.
And nothing else happened.
I swear.
I didn't ask.
Geez.
What do they only eat peppers
and tomatoes here?
You know what a butler
is supposed to do, right?
Of course, Ma'am.
I know nothing. I saw nothing.
I...
I covered up...
for many ladies here.
What can we do?
He's like an innocent lamb now.
Just watch him.
If he isn't faking it, it's only a matter
of time before he gets his memory back.
Are you telling me
to watch a ticking time bomb?
You're doing this for Do Kyung.
What else can you do?
Tae Soo... can't you take him with you?
Drop the nonsense.
I'm leaving.
Tae Soo! Hey! Hey!
Geez.
What is this?
Why did you have all of
your stuff sent here?
Sister, please let it go this one time.
I'm not good at working at a big company.
If Tae Soo gives me
a small role in the movie
I'll give my very best...
What?
Are you trying to live off of us?
Tell me the truth.
Is this why you asked
Soo Min out for the concert?
I'm sorry.
Wow, I'm speechless.
You wench! Do you know what
has happened because of you?
I'll kill you right now! Come here!
- Come here!
- I'm sorry!
Hey! You!
Go back to Seoul!
You're a burden to everyone!
Oh, a war between two sisters!
I have no place to go.
I have no money.
What happened to your money?
What about your rent deposit?
Tae Soo took out a loan for that!
Oh, that... I paid off
my credit card with that.
What? You did what?
You wench! You!
What's wrong now?
Dad, she spent all of her money
and used me so she could live here.
She wants to be in your movie.
What?
You'll help me right? Even a small role...
You haven't learned a damn thing!
Calm down.
Geez.
Mom.
Did you come back from collecting
spring water? What's wrong?
Why are you all out here?
Ma'am, isn't that my mink coat?
Why are you wearing my coat?
What's wrong, Grandma?
Ah!
What's wrong?
Wow, you are awesome!
No!
Well...
Didn't you say that it cost you
12 million won?
And that you bought it
in 36 monthly installments?
Mom!
Why did you wear someone else's coat?
Hye Sook's mom wanted to buy me lunch!
But I had nothing to wear!
I don't have a coat.
I'm going to die from running.
Oh, Tae Soo...
Please buy her a new coat with the
money you would spend on my coffin.
Oh, Honey...
Please come get me.
You! Are you out of your mind?
How could you buy that
expensive mink coat?
My goodness!
She's done nothing wrong. Just beat me!
Just beat me.
Okay then.
Mr. Chairman.
Well, do you have anything
you would like me to do?
I don't... I don't.
Have a good night, Mr. Chairman.
Hey!
You scared me.
You really don't remember anything?
It's okay. Tell me the truth.
What do you mean?
Man... you're driving me nuts.
Have a good night, Young Master.
Have breakfast, everyone!
Come on! Sit down!
Eun Sil made breakfast!
Don't even try. Go back.
We have no room for you.
She's going to share her room with me.
They came to an agreement.
Grandma let her use her room
in exchange for the damaged coat.
Mother, why are you doing this?
That's not the only reason.
In this house, no one pays any
attention to me the way she does.
She'll have a place to stay.
And I won't be as lonely.
It's good for both of us.
Catch two birds with one stone.
- You!
- Stop, stop, stop.
Soo Min is still growing,
but her face looks pale.
Can I help you with anything?
Geez, everyone teases me for being short.
That's why you should listen to me.
You should take this every day.
It's good for you.
Here.
Okay. I'll grow to be tall
like Miss Korea!
You're the best!
What? One Heart does what?
It wasn't an official audition.
Madam Oh created a nemesis
for Lee Do Kyung's character.
It was just a trial audition
for that role.
Now it's Madam Oh too?
No one is helping me.
Mr. Chairman! Mr. Chairman!
This is serious!
What is it, that you can't breathe?
My safe is gone!
The gold ax you bought me,
and my cash, and my jewelry!
They are all gone! Oh my goodness!
- Find Cho Dong Choon!
- Yes, Sir.
Okay, I see.
What did they say?
He got on an airplane
to China one hour ago.
He didn't lose his memory at all.
He was pretending, for the money.
What a wretched piece of garbage!
He showed up again 20 years later
and played me the same exact way!
Is it true? Did he really run away?
What an idiot...
What are you?
Is there anything you do properly?
I'm sorry about him, but I'm doing
a good job with the movie.
Doing a good job?
Is making a film child's play?
Why are you involving your ex-wife?
Do Kyung used to be an actress.
There's no reason she can't succeed.
And she's perfect for this role.
You don't have other motives?
I heard that you take your kid
to a mental hospital.
Dad.
It's not a mental hospital.
It's a mental health clinic.
A mental health clinic!
You have no remorse for your sick
granddaughter who lives fatherless?
I know you have no affection for her.
But how can you say something like that?
Then see her, and only her.
Don't try to involve that fox!
And what if I can't?
Since it was brought up, I better say it.
I will get back together with Do Kyung.
What did you say?
I didn't expect you to approve it.
Just pretend you don't know.
I was an idiot who couldn't decide
on my own marriage, or remarriage.
I don't want to live like that anymore.
Can you handle the consequences?
Have you ever seen me consider
the consequences when taking action?
You!
What? The butler ran away?
He ran away with all of my money!
He won't show up here again.
So don't worry about that.
Are you sure that I don't need to worry?
Regardless, absurd things
like this keep happening.
My soul is stricken with fear!
I am disappointed.
I didn't think you were a weak man.
Look here, Madam.
If the chairman finds out
about us, we will both die!
Both you, and me!
I can't succumb to that death
before even making my movie!
Secretary Ma, what brings you
to the production office?
The chairman wants to see both of you.
For what?
I can't say it myself.
You will know when you get there.
Why did you want to see us, Mr. Chairman?
Are you busy these days?
Well...
Of course.
We're really busy trying to
bring the script to perfection.
You already know that.
Geez.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
Oh... well...
He's stressed out with the script.
Right.
It's not an easy thing
to create a work of art.
I am a bit upset with the two of you.
Mr. Chairman! I was in the wrong!
Please forgive me!
If you really think that you did wrong...
Then you should recast.
Pardon me?
Director Yoon is here.
Oh, Tae Soo!
The new captain of Choong Shim Pictures!
Pardon me?
Sit down, sit down.
Sit down and let's talk.
Okay.
I called the three of you here
because we are in an awful situation.
How could all of you
be played by that idiot?
What do you mean?
You had a good script
and everything was going well.
But why did you let Gi Bum
run the whole show
when he had his own vested interest?
Oh...
Recast, and this time,
keep things fair and square.
That's how you can save the movie
and that's what I want.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Okay? Writer Oh? Director Bong?
And our new captain too!
Okay.
I see.
[OPEN AUDITION]
What's that?
What is this? An open audition?
Wow, it says anyone can apply!
Yes! Madam Jung is mine!
Brother, why are you smiling like that?
Smile?
I always smile!
I've never seen him smile like that.
Just like we said in the announcement
fairness is key, okay?
No favoritism, no nepotism, okay?
Finally, I feel like we can
make this movie the right way.
I'm so glad you came back
as our new captain.
What is that thing you posted outside?
Who said you could recast?
Mr. Yoon made the decision.
That's bullshit.
I'm the legal owner of this company!
The chairman ordered it himself.
Gi Bum, sit down. Let's talk.
You were sucking up to my father
about your house until a few days ago.
So this is what you got out of it?
Sucking up?
He got upset because
you practically cast anybody.
Do Kyung isn't just anyone!
Are you really going to be like this?
That's too bad, Do Kyung.
You won't be able to play that
cafe owner character, right?
It's too early to say that.
Do Kyung is the top candidate
for that role.
She'll just have to audition,
fair and square, like everybody else.
Still, you must feel like you lost
a fish you had already reeled in.
Well, I kind of feel that way.
But this is an opportunity
for me to show my true value.
I feel motivated.
That's great, Do Kyung.
Nothing is free in this world.
It's right to earn it with fair play.
Madam Oh, for the sake of
everyone at Choong Shim
I wholeheartedly welcome
the open audition.
Eun Ok, are you going to audition too?
You were totally into it when you
grabbed Do Kyung's hair last time.
You must have gained some
confidence in your acting, right?
I was just saying I support it.
I won't audition...
Okay, whether anyone
here auditions or not
this audition is very important
for our Choong Shim family.
So please encourage and
support one another. Okay?
Yes.
- Of course.
- Yes, Ma'am.
One Heart!
- Why did you...
- Madam Oh Sook Ja!
It's Oh Joo Ran!
You went as far as
becoming a screenwriter!
- Yet, you ruin everything.
- What?
I'm talking about Do Kyung.
I already cast her.
But what's with this open audition?
You know that it's the chairman
who wanted that.
You said he would listen to you.
That was the leverage you used
at the negotiating table.
Are you trying to destroy me,
rather than help me?
Of course not.
If you keep this up, you won't be able
to register your marriage to my father.
You know, give and take.
I really want that marriage registered
so I can call you Mother. Understood?
Please understand how I feel,
Madam Oh Sook Ja!
Oh, Writer Oh! Welcome home!
I ordered a new gold ax. A big one!
Why do you look so tired?
Because of you.
What?
The open audition.
The movie production company
is in chaos because of that.
Oh.
I'm trying to make a good movie
by discovering new talents!
Speaking of which,
I have something to show you.
What is it?
You fox!
Because of you, my life is a disaster!
You are the nuclear bomb in my life!
You are a tsunami!
What do you think?
They're pretty good!
She's definitely a former actress!
She seems solid,
and she looks good on screen.
As a screenwriter, I really like her!
There is no one who can play this role
as well as Lee Do Kyung.
What? You want me to act?
What are you talking about, Mr. Chairman?
I came here because
you wanted to eat my kimchi.
Wow.
I thought you were just a good cook.
But you're a hell of an actor too!
Pardon me?
You are much better than someone
I know who used to be an actress.
Oh...
I want you to play that role!
Even so, there's an open audition.
That's what I'm saying.
You should audition, and get that role!
Is it because you don't
want Do Kyung to do it?
I just want someone better to do it.
Someone that's good for the movie.
It's the movie Tae Soo is making.
That's why I shouldn't.
Enjoy the kimchi.
I'll bring you more next time.
There's someone who wants to
move into your house this month.
Excuse me?
Everyone heard that
the house was built very well.
Many people want to buy that house.
Some people want to pay
above market price.
Do you know how I feel now?
I feel like a dog, a dog whose owner
just strapped on my leash.
You'll just tighten my leash even more.
I guess I better listen to you now.
In return, please let us live in that
house until Sung Min goes to college.
Is that all you need?
If you win that role, I'll put your name
on the title of the house.
Do you mean it?
But you have to keep it a secret.
Sir, I am calling you because
I see many good candidates here.
We are having an open audition this time.
Why would you bringing gangsters?
This is a movie!
We are not recruiting gangsters.
We're recruiting actors!
Hang up!
We need top actors. Someone new! Yes.
Thank you, Eun Sil.
There may be bad actors,
but there aren't bad roles.
I want to be salt and light...
Excuse me. I don't want this.
Why? I like it.
This is a bribe!
Tae Soo!
Please tell Producer Lee not to hate me.
Now you're soliciting.
That's enough.
We called a lot of places.
You'll be hearing back soon.
Be ready for the audition, okay?
You fox! You are a disaster in my life!
You're a nuclear bomb in my life!
You're a tsunami!
I will reveal all of
your most shameful secrets!
I'll crush you before you get the chance!
Geez!
Why are you fighting again?
Dad, you ruined their acting practice!
Acting practice?
Yes, Mom and Auntie are auditioning.
What?
What do you mean?
You're going to audition?
Why? Can't I do that?
Are you crazy? Do you remember
what you said to your sister?
You told her that it wasn't a joke,
and that she shouldn't bother me!
Do you have to dance to her tune?
It's not that!
I just want to give it a try!
Your sister is giving me enough trouble.
If you do this, you're putting me
in an awkward position.
You shouldn't do this.
You know how I got this opportunity back.
Is a housekeeper all that I can be?
Back in school, I was a much
better actor than Do Kyung.
Let's go, everyone.
Please, give me my coat back.
I will sit here for just one more minute.
I feel like...
I don't remember at all
what the walls or the ceiling
in this house really look like.
That's why I keep looking at them.
I'm looking very eagerly.
I remember too.
It was when I was six years old,
at a church event.
I was sitting on this windowsill.
I saw my father walking down the street.
When we leave, there won't
be anyone left here.
Ha ha ha! It's going to be
like that until the spring.
Now... get in the wagon.
It's time.
My beautiful house,
those beautiful hills.
My life, my youth!
My happiness!
Goodbye, my house.
Goodbye, my old life.
God bless my new life!
Hooray!
Bravo! Bravo! Bravo!
Eun Ok! You are an amazing actress!
You have to be the protagonist!
Thank you, Teacher.
Do Kyung...
If anyone wanted to cast you for a movie
that person would be a swindler.
Pardon me?
Didn't I do pretty well today?
I thought I did well.
Well, you would be good at
playing a narcissistic role.
Eun Ok, don't you want to act?
Not at all.
I want to be a good wife.
I'll marry a civil servant, have lots of
children, and live with my mother-in-law.
Are you crazy? Why would you
want to live with your mother-in-law?
Be careful what you wish for!
I feel like I'll have
a nice mother-in-law.
She'll be someone warm and sophisticated.
Do I look prettier?
Ma'am, the mole on your nose is gone.
Oh, my.
I drew it. It's supposed to be pretty.
All beautiful women have
a mole on their noses.
It's right there.
Oh, don't tell the kids.
What's the matter?
Do we need a reason to drink?
Let me pour one for our new captain.
Geez, what are you talking about?
My dad said you were
the new captain of the movie.
That's how it should be.
An idiot like me can't make a movie.
Don't be pitiful. It doesn't suit you.
Tae Soo.
Please do a favor for this poor guy.
What is it?
Do Kyung... has to play that role.
You know that.
You know I'm not into making movies.
I'm doing this for Do Kyung.
Gi Bum...
I want to make her a lead actress,
and I want to get back together with her.
You are the only one who
can grant me this wish.
I'm a poor man.
Tae Soo.
I'm the poorest guy here!
You know my situation!
What about it?
I'm standing on the edge of a cliff!
There's no place for me to go!
And I'm begging a guy like that!
I'm the poor guy!
I envy your life!
I don't even have a wife!
I don't have a house to live in!
You are blessed to have a mother!
You are blessed to have a father!
Tae Soo, please!
Gi Bum, please!
- Ah! I got cramps! Cramps!
- Cramps, cramps.
- Cramps...
What is this?
- Ouch!
- Geez, I'm stuck!
What are you doing?
My wife!
Ex.
My ex-wife!
What are you doing here?
Why did you call me?
Come on, sit down! Do Kyung too.
The four of us used to
hang out together all the time.
We remembered that, so we called you.
He missed those days.
Why do you miss that?
- How long ago was that?
- 25 years ago.
Wow, time flies!
Oh, right here!
I envy Do Kyung.
Did you wait a long time?
No, I didn't.
You got a new scarf?
- Is it good?
- Yes.
Eun Ok!
Long time no see.
Yes, it's been a while.
Hi.
What's your name?
Choi Kyung Mee!
How many times have I told you?
I've seen you many times,
but I can't remember you.
Unlike Do Kyung.
I'm here too. Have you been well?
Yeah.
I'll go then. Have fun.
Hey...
Kyung Mee!
What?
What? Should I hang with
you guys too? I'm free.
No, I wanted to say bye. Bye.
Okay. Bye then.
Bye then.
If you leave, we'll be an odd number.
How about karaoke? I'll pay for it!
I don't know where or when
but love always...
Can't you make a place
for me in your heart?
You're the one and only
beautiful woman in this world!
On this sad day.
You, on this day the fig ripens.
You and I hid under
the fig tree that day.
Whenever I think about those days.
I want to tell that story.
A girl secretly in love
and a boy who's secretly in love.
One day under this sky...
One swallowtail butterfly
was sitting on a petal.
What's wrong with me,
swallowtail butterfly.
Fly up high into the sky.
Swallowtail butterfly, fly!
- Fly into the clouds!
- Oh yeah!
- All right!
- Swallowtail butterfly!
Swallowtail butterfly, fly!
Stop it already!
If you don't stop, we'll leave.
Should we all go drink more?
Yeah!
Enough. Nothing is open
at this hour. Let's go.
Let's go home.
Wait, wait.
Let's get some alcohol
and go drink at my office!
You are the captain, indeed! Let's go!
Swallowtail butterfly, fly!
Hey! A swallowtail butterfly!
Gi Bum, what is that singer,
Kim Hong Gook, doing these days?
I'm sure he's doing okay.
Hey, who are you?
Hey, why are you standing
in front of my office?
Hey, you!
Who are you?
Standing there like that...
How have you been?
You didn't miss me?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[SWEET SAVAGE FAMILY]
What? Who's here?
Mr. Yoon!
I came to say goodbye.
Do you know what happens next on a date?
Show me your best and make me happy.
Self-realization! Starting a new life!
Can't married women do that?
He slept in that house? Stop all of that.
It's not working? No way.
Where can I get 20 billion won?
It's all your fault.
I have no place to go.
I can't just let that happen!
My goodness! I can't die like this!
I will take the worst guy with me.
What's going on?
Huh?