Subtitles by DramaFever
I had met many people
while following you around
carrying bagfuls of money
earned from all of those clubs.
National assembly members,
civil servants, prosecutors and police!
When those bastards were
greeting us with smiles...
You told me this.
"They've fallen into our traps."
But...
I thought about it the other way.
And the person in the worst position
is you, Mr. Chairman.
Tae Soo, you punk!
Compare that to the original
that you have.
As for the German tape recorder
you put in my pocket...
I'll be taking good care of it.
Don't you worry.
Why you...
Just like I learned from you...
I am trying to survive from you.
Now, let's cut our ties completely!
I am leaving you, Mr. Chairman.
As of today, it seems
that I am no longer your dog.
Still, we share a long history together.
You don't want this to get dirty, do you?
There's nothing I want from you either.
I do have one shield
to protect my family.
And that's what I came to show you today.
Mr. Chairman.
I wish you... a long, healthy life.
[EPISODE 12]
What did you just say to my father?
What kind of crap were you just saying?
If you don't know anything,
then move over.
Why are you acting like this?
Why are you acting out,
being angry like some little girl...
I said move!
My dad spent so much money
on you, and invested in this movie.
You created this mess.
Now you're going to pull out?
For the past 20 years,
I managed places with neon signs.
Why aren't you considering those
bags full of cash that I brought in?
You little...
Don't treat me without care.
I simply won't take it anymore.
Geez, Soo Min, hurry and load it up.
What is this? Some sort of cart?
Stop complaining and load everything up.
My knees hurt and I can't walk properly.
Mom, just sit over here.
Dad, where are we going now?
We're going to
a warm country in the south.
Geez... It's a mountain I need to climb
at some point anyway.
Just let it out and tell them.
Get your clean slate. Start over.
Oh my, oh my!
What do I do about my money?
What is it, Mother?
Dad, Grandma lost money. 20 million won.
What happened?
Mother, please get up.
This won't bring your money back.
Just leave me alone!
I'm just going to go die!
Why did you deal with those
financing groups?
How many times is this now?
I didn't do it for my own good!
I wanted to help with Sung Min's
college tuition later.
How else can I get my hands on big money?
Goodness, I'm going to die.
Tae Soo, find the woman
who took my money.
Get the people who work
under you to go find her.
Tae Soo!
Geez, that old lady upsets me so much.
By the way, Honey.
I have something to tell you.
If it's about your mother,
I don't want to talk.
That's not it.
What?
The thing is...
Well, actually...
Is it about the house?
Then I don't want to talk even more.
Hey, Eun Ok.
I'm going to read the script
and sleep in Soo Min's room.
Just like I learned from you...
I am trying to survive you.
Now, let's cut our ties completely.
I am leaving you, Mr. Chairman.
Come in.
Yes, come in.
- Sit down.
- Yes, Mr. Chairman.
You ought to be with your pregnant wife.
I'm sorry to call you out
at this hour. It's late.
It's not a problem, Mr. Chairman.
I'm ready to come running,
whenever you call for me.
Since you say that,
I'll get straight to the point.
Tae Soo has turned
his back on me and left.
What? Tae Soo?
I wanted us both to live
and I made us a hiding spot.
But he wants to ruin me
and live happily on his own.
No good will come from
bothering him any further.
I want to end this by getting
my hands on something covert.
I was hoping you would
do it for me, Manager Song.
Manager?
Let's try to work together.
Manager Song.
Are you good at treasure hunting?
Do you know what Do Kyung said to me?
She felt that I was genuine
in my efforts towards her.
But she said to give up on her,
because she can't endure my father.
What have you been doing,
that things turned out this way?
Don't speak that way, Director Baek.
Even with the audition and the scene
I did the best that I could.
The Chairman dislikes
Lee Do Kyung that much.
How could I have possibly known that?
I need to go head-to-head
with my father immediately.
You're going to pour gas on a fire?
The chairman is very traumatized
because of Director Yoon.
Don't make this into a bigger issue.
Wait a little longer until
things get a bit better.
Okay?
By the way, Director Baek...
I noticed that there is a CCTV
in the chairman's office.
Do you know anything about that?
Why do you ask?
Have you done something wrong?
What kind of question is that?
If that wasn't the case, why would
you care if there was or wasn't?
I'm trying to protect my privacy.
Everything is being
recorded all of the time.
Doesn't that make you feel
a little strange, just sitting there?
You are very suspicious.
You have the expression of a thief
that has been caught in the act.
You are the one who has been
very suspicious lately.
What?
From what I know, the chairman
is no longer giving you any money.
But your spending habits haven't changed.
Did you, by chance,
empty a safe or something?
Why are you saying such nonsense?
Geez... I was only joking!
There's no need to get so upset.
My goodness.
This is truly good news.
A spot investment during times like this,
when making films is so difficult.
Though he could not be with us today,
to Director Byung Nam...
I mean Director William.
Let's give him another hand.
Director, we should announce
the news about the scene revision.
You...
Well, it's nothing really.
We asked Senior Ahn
to monitor the scene.
How do I say this?
We were told that the new character
was slightly problematic.
This makes me very upset!
Using investment as bait...
I will not let a foreigner
control our project.
This is the authority of the writer.
I feel the same way.
I believe we need
to respect the creative work.
They just want the film to be better.
I don't think the intent
is to look down on the writer.
Nevertheless, isn't it wrong
to put down the writers' morale?
We don't have the luxury
of discussing morale.
First and foremost,
the film has to succeed.
Now that you brought it up...
Kim Eun Ok, I'm not sure you have
the luxury to sit here like this.
What? What does that mean?
Last night...
Your husband cut ties with the chairman
and left, after 20 years together.
Didn't you hear about it?
What do you mean, cut ties?
Let me phrase this differently.
Should I say... betrayal?
[RESIGNATION]
Resignation?
I heard about you cutting ties
with the chairman.
It's true, isn't it?
I was going to tell you myself.
I guess you heard elsewhere.
It just worked out that way.
Honey.
I'm glad you quit.
For years, I haven't been able to sleep
until you arrived at home safely.
But, I don't think this is a decision
you should make without preparation.
I waited as long as I could,
and endured as much as I could.
I thought hundreds and thousands of times
before I making my decision.
Still, how could you make a decision
like this without talking to me first?
Don't you know what I've done
in order to protect that house?
I'm doing this because I do know.
I don't want you to get pushed
around by the chairman either.
Honey, think carefully.
This isn't about pride.
It's about living and surviving.
We give up the house
and our value is gone.
There are loans and interest rates.
We have nothing saved. How will we live?
Have you forgotten that you're
the head of a family of five?
I held on this long because
I'm the head of a household.
I had fingers pointed at me because
of what I did but I had my family.
You think I don't know
about your hardships?
I'm asking for time to prepare!
At least until Sung Min goes to college.
If it's about money, don't worry.
No matter what I have to do, I'll keep on
earning what I've been earning.
Honey!
You should go. I'm busy.
Sister-in-law.
Hello. Are you going to work?
Yes, I heard about Tae Soo.
It was so sudden for me too.
Yes, I know.
I'm worried that things might
become dangerous for him.
I've heard that the chairman has called
on people from other districts.
People from other districts?
With the way things are right now,
I think you should get prepared.
I know Tae Soo is not a weak person,
so I'm sure he's getting prepared.
Is there anything he has
told you, in particular?
Or something he gave you, in secret?
There's nothing like that.
But why are you suddenly
asking me questions like that?
Because I want to help you.
He's always confided in me,
all of this time.
Anyway, please take care of Tae Soo
and call me if you need anything.
Bye then.
I said I don't want to meet up.
Why did you call me?
I couldn't sleep for a second
last night, Do Kyung.
Don't bother me then,
and go back to sleep.
I won't be able to sleep tonight either.
- Why not?
- You won't let me sleep.
Are you playing around?
Do Kyung, you didn't mean
what you said to me, right?
Please say you didn't mean it.
That's the only way
I can eat or sleep, Do Kyung.
Stop acting like a child.
I meant what I said yesterday,
and I can't forgive the chairman either.
And if you continue with this behavior,
I might stop living here altogether.
I'll move away with Hyun Jee.
Do you really want to see me die?
Give me a chance, and trust me!
I'll cut all my ties with my father.
Cut your ties?
Then he'll bother me even more
absurdly than he did before.
Please think about the consequences
before you take any actions.
Did you find out where the CCTV's are?
I tried to find out from Director Baek,
but he was suspicious of me.
So I gave up.
The server was in the basement,
so where could it be?
Lower your voice.
We're being filmed right now.
Geez.
Madam, only the video gets filmed.
The sound doesn't get recorded.
I made a mistake for a moment.
Are you really
going to revise the script?
Are you not going to stick by my side?
Madam, this is not about
whose side I take.
We're shooting a film here.
A film with common sense.
What common sense?
Why do you enter without knocking?
I did knock, but I don't think you heard.
Mr. Chairman is not feeling well,
so he told me to bring you a snack.
By the way, Mr. Ma...
Yes, Madam.
Do you know anything about
the CCTV system in this house?
I need to know for the script.
Do you anything about
the server location, or anything similar?
After the Director Cho incident,
we installed them in the rooms.
But due to a scheduling issue,
the servers haven't been installed.
What?
I'm sorry I couldn't
be more helpful. Goodbye.
Director.
Madam.
We must make sure that the light are off.
Let's get out of here for now.
Oh, we're free now!
We no longer need to live in terror!
Let's be careful now.
Let's look for another location now.
- So cute, cute!
- Cute!
Don't come any closer!
Are you okay?
Well... I didn't see anything.
I didn't see a thing.
You saw everything!
Producer Kim! Come back!
Nothing about you needs to be erased.
Do you know how I feel?
I call after you...
It's finally the concert tomorrow.
I assume you're very well prepared.
Just don't be totally shocked
when you see me tomorrow.
I'll be looking forward to it.
Bye for now.
What are you doing, Daughter?
Just sitting here.
How about a date with your mom tomorrow?
I planned a full-course meal.
We can watch a movie in the morning,
then brunch, then go shopping!
I've run out face cream.
You need gloves too.
You can get a massage at
the nail shop in the evening.
What do you think?
The day will be over so fast.
Mom.
I have plans tomorrow.
Plans? With who?
I'm not going to be depressed
at home on Christmas anymore.
So don't worry, Mom.
Are you really okay?
I am.
Geez, I'm worried about you.
You'll be bored alone.
Why not go on a date with Dad?
What? Forget it. What date?
Why not? He's cute in his own way.
I feel bad for him too.
So just accept him already.
Anyway, I don't know
what your plans are.
But don't come home too late.
I'll make you pasta.
Pasta?
Yeah!
Hyun Jee.
Wait. I miss you.
Let's have a fun Christmas tomorrow.
I deserve to be left alone
to die in an open tomb.
Yet, here I am,
getting all of my meals in a warm room.
I don't know if I deserve this.
You need to eat to get strong.
You're right.
Mother.
Actually, I have something to tell you.
Don't even mention the money that I
brought you without letting Tae Soo know.
I have no money to give you and
I just want to jump into a lake.
Mother... Tae Soo is quitting his job.
You need to stop him.
He can't do that so suddenly.
What do you mean, he can't?
Are you saying Tae Soo will be in danger?
No, I'm not saying something
will happen to him.
It will be hard for us to make ends meet.
You know how things are for us.
We have nothing planned.
We have to give up this house.
Oh my, this house is the problem.
Oh, is everyone sleeping?
Tae Soo, see me for a moment.
What are you doing here alone?
Sit for a moment.
Geez.
I can't catch that person
who took your money.
I'm not the police.
How can I catch someone who
made plans to run like that?
Just give up on it.
I heard that you're quitting.
My resignation will be processed soon.
I'm sorry that I couldn't
tell you beforehand.
Okay.
You're past the age to be doing that.
You didn't have parents
who could send you to college.
You go around taking care of all
of the problems in this household.
You've suffered so many hardships.
You have enough money saved up
to buy a house like this, right?
What?
Since we're going to move,
let's just move into an apartment.
Hae Sook's Mom's apartment
looks pretty nice.
This house has high
heating costs, after all.
Mom, we don't have enough for that.
We have just enough for us
to avoid rainy wind.
Enough for us to get cozy
and sleep comfortably.
The body needs to be comfortable
for the heart to at ease.
Do you think we will happy sleeping
comfortably in a tiny house?
Mother.
Didn't you start working there in order
to not live like your father?
So we lived well until now.
I'm not saying this so that
we can continue to live well.
Even when you go to the mineral spring,
you have do to warm up exercises first.
Even when you get a shot at the doctor,
you need to prepare your heart first.
You're starting a brand new life.
Don't you need to prepare?
Mom, I'm not a child.
Don't you think I've thought about it?
I even found a job.
Your son is very competent.
I'm the Home Mart delivery man.
Are you home right now?
Yes, I'll be right there.
Wallpapering? Yes, I have experience.
Yes, please call me.
I'll only be driving
on the weekends, right?
Yes, of course it's possible.
Yes.
Collecting on loans?
Geez, it's just that I have a soft heart.
Yes, sorry about that.
[HEALTH CLUB CENTER]
Hey Mister, what are you doing
on another person's building?
[THE TWO FELL MADLY IN LOVE.]
Do Kyung and Hyun Jee,
this is how I feel for you.
Please accept it.
Are you going somewhere?
I have plans.
You shouldn't go out on days like today.
Have dinner at home.
It's busy because of the script at home.
It feels empty at home.
You should have been good to your
daughter-in-law and grandchild then.
Christmas should be spent with family.
Don't you know that?
I'll be going now.
Why, that little...
Mr. Chairman, I'm here.
Yes, Manager Song.
Have you done your treasure hunt?
I think Tae Soo has hid it very well.
His wife has no idea about it.
For now, I've just dropped hints.
It would have been good
to end it quietly.
He just has to create a confrontation.
- Yes?
- Delivery from Home Mart.
Okay.
Tae Soo.
You live here?
Oh, it's nice here.
Where should I put this?
- Just give it to me.
- Oh, no, no! It's heavy.
Where do you want it?
- The kitchen.
- Okay.
I'll be going then.
Tae Soo.
I heard.
The chairman's people
eventually leave this way.
It seems like Gi Bum
is making a lot of efforts.
Do Kyung, you should think positively,
with Hyun Jee in mind.
I'll be going then.
Bye then.
What are you doing here?
I came to deliver stuff.
Don't get the wrong idea.
You made such a fuss
and this is what you're doing?
Gi Bum!
I'll be going then.
When, exactly, are you going to grow up?
I'll be embarrassed for Hyun Jee
if you keep hanging around, so leave.
Wait, Do Kyung! Look at this, Do Kyung!
I wrote it all and made it myself.
Geez, Tae Soo ruined my plans.
Tae Soo, you have a knack for
involving yourself in my life's affairs.
- What?
- My Christmas plans were ruined by you.
- What are you going to do about it?
- Just move.
I have no time for you.
Hey, you were a guy who controlled
Daejeon with your fists.
Now you've turned over a new leaf
and you're working hard.
It looks like fake marketing
for others to see.
It brings tears to my eyes.
Then cry on my behalf.
What does your family say?
Hey, do you have a new house?
It must be tearing your wife up inside.
What are you doing, Little Missy?
I told you not to call me that.
Don't talk to me.
I'm really zoned in right now.
Stop trying so hard to do
things you can't do, Little Missy.
Seriously, I'm annoyed enough
that I can't do it.
You'll see. I'll get it soon.
I don't know about other things,
but you can't look as good as I do.
What? I've seen you without makeup.
I was totally shocked.
Hey.
If you have nothing to do,
let's go to Sung Min's concert.
- Sung Min has a concert?
- Yeah, with his girlfriend.
It's secret from Mom.
There's no need for that
because she's not home.
I was sad because I had nothing
to do on Christmas Eve.
Now, I get to see a concert,
thanks to my niece.
I'm the best, right?
So, stop calling me names.
Just make sure to eat it diligently.
We'll be late. Let's go.
Uncle Song, are you sure
you saw him here?
I'm looking for him,
but he's not here.
Let's talk later.
And please look into what I asked about.
[CHINESE LANGUAGE ACADEMY]
I'm worried that things might
become dangerous for him.
I've heard that the chairman has called
on people from other districts.
Chinese Academy!
Chinese Language Academy!
Honey!
Do you even know that the chairman
is having you followed?
You came because you
were worried about that?
Wow, you really are the best.
Walking away is good
and earning money is important too.
But your safety is the most important.
If you are in danger,
I'm going to tell you to not walk away.
Isn't it dangerous to do that work too?
Don't worry. I have everything prepared.
What is it that you prepared that
you're so confident like this?
Geez, I'm busy, so go.
I'm busy. Just go on now.
Chinese Language Academy!
Chinese Academy!
How's the concert preparation going?
Yeah, I'm on my way now.
Hey, what color do you like?
Just tell me quickly.
Okay, I'll be there in ten minutes.
- Please give me two of these.
- Okay.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Sell lots today.
One of those scarves is mine, right?
I missed you, Hyun Jee.
[A SMALL CHRISTMAS CONCERT]
Sung Min, what about Hyun Jee?
She's on her way. I just spoke to her.
Hi, Sung Min.
Oh Nephew, you look very good today.
You guys should eat something.
It'll start very soon.
Geez, I feel bad for you.
I'm hungry. Should we eat?
Sung Min, isn't it getting late?
People are waiting for the concert.
Oh, we'll start soon.
You must be waiting for Hyun Jee,
but I think you should end it with her.
What do you mean?
I saw with her with some guy
at the park on the way here.
The guy was holding her hand.
What? What guy was this?
Forget about him.
You're much better than him.
He was so slimy,
with yellow bleached hair.
Yellow hair?
What's your relationship with
that female student?
You're just friends, right?
You're not her boyfriend?
Why do you ask something like that?
I just thought I would.
Please let go of me.
What's wrong Hyun Jee?
I know you missed me.
Don't you remember that
we first met on Christmas?
That's why I came here on Christmas.
Don't you remember
that restraining order?
You're breaking the law.
Breaking the law?
How could you do that to me?
You liked me. You always smiled at me.
You practiced dance
until late all the time.
I even praised you to the chairman
so that you'd debut faster.
Are you crazy?
Hey, Baek Hyun Jee!
Hyun Jee, Hyun Jee!
Hyun Jee, Baek Hyun Jee!
Baek Hyun Jee?
Are you going to be like this?
Why are you making things so difficult?
Hyun Jee!
Sung Min.
- Who are you, Mister?
- Me?
- I'm Hyun Jee's boyfriend.
- No, he's not!
He's a crazy stalker.
Seriously, Hyun Jee. Come here!
Let go of her!
What's with you, punk?
Sung Min!
Hyun Jee, let's talk.
You little punk!
Let go of me!
Sung Min!
Hyun Jee, just talk to me.
- Hyun Jee, hurry! Get out of here.
- Sung Min.
You jerk.
Hyun Jee... Hyun Jee.
Please get out of here, Hyun Jee.
- Let go of me.
- Hyun Jee, hurry!
- Hyun Jee, hurry up and go.
- Let go of me.
Hyun Jee, Hyun Jee!
- Sung Min.
- Hurry!
Hello, Yoon Tae Soo.
- Mister, this is Hyun Jee.
- Who?
Hyun Jee.
- Mister!
- Where, where?
Over there.
Get over here, you punk.
What's with you?
You dare lay a hand on my son?
Who the heck are you?
I'm Santa, you punk.
Santa?
Chinese language academy?
Dad, this guy has been stalking
Hyun Jee since Seoul.
What? You piece of garbage!
You're going to have to
get a beating from Santa today.
Get up. Get up now.
Get over here.
Come on.
Come get a beating from Santa.
How dare you touch my son?
How dare you think you can lay
a hand on my son, you little punk?
Get up now!
You're dead.
You think you can bother my son?
You can taste my fist tonight.
I really didn't do anything wrong.
I just wanted a quiet conversation
with my girlfriend.
This man appeared
and suddenly started attacking me.
May I make one phone call?
My uncle is a prosecutor.
What is this? What the heck?
- Die, die, die you punk!
- Wait, Mister.
Die you jerk!
You dare stalk my daughter?
You're dead!
You're totally dead!
Die, die, die!
- Die, die!
- Wait, Mister!
- Calm down.
- That's enough now.
That's enough.
You better get over here now.
How could you do that to my Hyun Jee?
Get over here now!
You're dead you punk!
You little punk.
Get over here now!
Anyone who bothers my daughter is dead,
and I'm going to die too.
Get over here right now!
Father, Hyun Jee liked me a lot
when she was a trainee.
She likes me too.
What did you say?
You must really want to die.
Please give us your blessings.
We're in love with each other.
You're going all out, aren't you?
This is a police station. Just calm down.
If you keep this up, I'll arrest you
for obstruction of justice, okay?
Policeman, get me a phone.
My uncle is a district prosecutor.
You guys are all dead.
I'm going to put you all in jail.
I'm going to sue you!
Shut your mouth!
I told you I'd kill you
with my own hands if you showed up again.
How dare you show up again.
Do Kyung, Do Kyung.
Who are you to show up here!
- Do Kyung, Do Kyung.
- You garbage.
I'm going to kill you myself.
- Do Kyung.
- You can't let that guy go.
He can't be showing up here.
You punk!
- Calm down.
- Mom!
Hyun Jee!
- Hyun Jee.
- Mom is here.
It's okay now.
Are you all right?
It's all right.
We'll need the statement,
so please follow me.
- Okay, let's go.
- Yes.
Dad.
Sung Min, are you hurt at all?
I'm all right. How about you?
I'm just fine.
Geez, what a relief!
- Honey.
- Mom.
You make me worry all by myself.
Is this what you wanted?
I really don't like this.
Mom.
It's all right. It's over now.
For real?
He's not going to come back again?
Of course, you saw what your dad did.
He won't even try anymore.
Maybe I should have told Dad
earlier and given him an SOS.
He would've caused an incident
and created complications.
I suppose.
But I did feel
more protected when I saw Dad.
Did you?
What is this anyways?
Dad left this here earlier today.
I guess he got the idea from somewhere.
Look through it. I'll make warm tea.
There was a man and a woman.
They fell madly into a hot,
passionate love.
Like this.
However, the man was stupid and
the woman ended up leaving him.
But the woman returned.
Bringing with her a beautiful jewel,
that is.
The man made a vow to protect these
two women.
Even if they both become like this.
It must have been so hard
for that young thing.
I'm sorry, Hyun Jee.
It's all your dad's fault.
Sorry, Hyun Jee.
It will be okay now.
He's in jail now.
I'm just trash.
My daughter was getting stalked.
And she came here because
of her emotional trauma.
But I couldn't even protect her.
I have no right to be a father.
I should just bang my head
on the wall and die right here.
All you need to do
is take care of her from now on.
But I have no right to face Do Kyung.
How much did she not trust me?
That she didn't even
say a word after coming to Daejeon.
I didn't even know anything.
Once I get out of this place,
I'm going to get back together with her.
I really am.
Wipe up, would you? Wipe your face.
Thanks, Tae Soo.
If it weren't for you,
Hyun Jee could have been in trouble.
How did you know to run over?
I was working when I got a call.
What work?
Wearing that?
You're doing something else
besides delivery work.
Do you have to do this?
Isn't it hard?
If you think about it,
I've been living too comfortably.
Isn't it just better
to come back to my father?
I saw your wife back there.
I've never seen such a cold look
on her face before.
All you know is your family.
How much can you really make
wearing this and working?
Think of your family and come back.
Dad would take you back.
You're probably tired. You should sleep.
Yeah, I am pretty tired.
Geez, I'm so sorry Hyun Jee.
I've heard that the chairman has called
on people from other districts.
You came because
you were worried about that?
You really are the best.
What? My son is at the police station?
Oh my, I'm embarrassed Chief.
Please send him home in the morning.
What?
He had a friend with him
when he was arrested?
Who? Yoon Tae Soo?
Baek Gi Bum.
- Baek Gi Bum!
- Yes.
Oh me?
Yeah, come on out.
Geez, it's cold.
Hey now.
What is it?
Not you, Yoon Tae Soo.
What do you mean?
We came in together.
Those were the orders
that came down. Go inside.
I have to go out. I have work to do.
Hey, Gi Bum. Gi Bum! What is this?
You'll be out soon.
- Hey, Gi Bum.
- Let's go.
Hey, Gi Bum! Gi Bum!
Dad, where's my present?
You said you'd buy me shoes.
Yeah, where is your dad?
He had business to take care of.
What is this? He didn't give me
my Christmas present and left?
Just go upstairs.
Why are you getting mad at me?
Did Tae Soo not come in?
Dad.
Why did you bother coming at all?
Hyun Jee's dad is out.
Why aren't you out?
Oh, that's because I have a harder
fist than her dad.
When are you coming out?
Don't worry. I'll be out tonight.
For sure, right?
You're coming out tonight?
Then should I live here or something?
Or do you want to come in too?
Don't worry about a thing and
you go about your business.
Console Hyun Jee, as well.
Oh, Sister-in-law.
What's going on?
Your feeling was correct.
The chairman is planning
something against Tae Soo.
I hear he's setting Tae Soo up
to take the fall.
Take the fall for what?
Everything that the chairman got
Tae Soo to do on his behalf...
he is trying to make is look as if
Tae Soo did it all on his own.
I knew it when the chairman
called in Young Il.
What do you mean?
What about Uncle Young Il?
Young Il has completely betrayed Tae Soo.
He has stuck onto Chairman's side.
Like Tae Soo said,
it's the last stop of the last bus.
- I have to do something now.
- No.
You stay put.
I'll do it.
As for Tae Soo suddenly leaving you...
I don't it was proper and I know
the rights steps weren't taken.
Chairman.
It still doesn't call for you
to run him down in this manner.
You come to me out of nowhere.
What are you saying?
He served you for 20 years.
He isn't asking for anything.
Can't you let him go quietly?
Why are you going so far?
Do you think I wanted to go this far?
Tae Soo came after me.
I want to let Tae Soo go too.
Why would I hold onto someone whose
heart isn't in it?
He was half like a son to me.
It's good to end things
and tie things up.
So what is it that you want?
A recorder.
It looks like a pen and you can wear it.
If you bring that to me,
Tae Soo lives and everyone lives.
Everything is put back into place.
You're smart so you know what I mean.
What is this? What are you doing?
The moving truck is downstairs
and movers will come.
Just put the important things
in here for now.
I'll tell them to move the rest.
- Gi Bum.
- Move into the house.
I can move you in half a day.
Why do you do whatever you want?
Why would I go into that house?
I can't live apart from you two
because of my anxiety.
Is there another way? I have to
have you with me to protect you.
So you do this without a word to me?
Do you think your dad will welcome me
if I go into that house?
Even you will get kicked out.
Leave that to me.
Madam Oh will help us too.
Those are your thoughts.
I think I'll suffocate just from thoughts
of seeing your dad's face.
I'm not going and neither will Hyun Jee.
Are you going to make me out to
be a bad father right until the end?
I can't ever give up so just know that.
Me?
The star has finally arrived.
To my friend who manages to stay
pretty even after a difficult time...
I stayed up two nights so I could
dedicate this song.
I'm not sure if she'll like it.
It was a little bit cheesy.
But I totally liked it.
Are you feeling okay now?
You must have been quite shocked too.
You even have a cut on your face.
Are you hurting anywhere?
It wasn't a big deal. I'm all better.
Can you tell your
mother and father that I'm sorry?
Because of me,
their Christmas was ruined.
Especially your dad,
I'm apologetic and thankful.
I will.
Ah, I have something for you.
Christmas present.
Yup, it is a matching couple scarf.
I have something for you too.
Wasn't the song from
before your gift to me?
Merry Christmas.
Mom, can you come here? Hurry!
What happened?
Dad must have stayed like this overnight.
He's completely frozen.
Seriously, do you want
to die or something?
Why are you acting this way?
Even if I freeze to death
I'm going to stay
next to my wife and kid.
I won't ever be separated.
Stop saying nonsense and go home now.
At this rate, you'll seriously get ill.
I'm not going! I won't go.
I can't... I can't go.
- Oh my! Dad! Dad, are you okay?
- Gi Bum!
Dad! Are you all right?
Gi Bum! Wake up!
- Dad!
- Gi Bum!
It's a recorder.
It looks like a pen that
you can put on your clothes.
If you can bring it to me,
Tae Soo can live and everyone else too.
Everything will be resolved.
I'll get released soon.
Why did you bother coming?
You won't be able to come out.
What?
I met with Chairman.
Give it to me. The recorder.
Only if you do, you can come out.
Does it make sense to give up
your weapon during a war?
That's only when you're up against
an opponent you can handle.
This isn't one of those times.
What happens if I lose my weapon against
someone who's stronger than me?
Living as a wife of a gangster...
I longed and waited for the day
I would be free from all these things.
But when that day actually came...
I didn't welcome it.
I found myself pushing you back into it.
I hated the person I had become.
I felt like I became a really bad person.
But Honey, I'm doing this because I can't
watch you be in danger anymore.
What exactly did you hear?
Why are you acting this way?
You will end up losing a lot.
I hear Young Il is gone too.
I'd been preparing for it.
I'm prepared to sacrifice
whatever I need to.
Are you awake now?
I can't even die.
I just create heartaches for others.
I can't even protect my wife and my kid.
What would I be good for?
Enough already.
I'll do what you want.
Are you being serious?
Are you coming home with Hyun Jee?
Nope. You come here.
- What?
- Didn't you say you'll protect us?
Come live with us, Dad.
Yeah! No more sufferings.
This is the start of happiness!
All right, Hyun Jee.
Your Dad will protect you!
I'll protect you!
Prepared to sacrifice
whatever you need to?
If I can't get free this time,
I'll be tied down forever.
I'll be living as their dog.
To become human,
I have to pay whatever the price.
Even if I'm the price?
What?
Honey.
I don't think I can do this anymore.
I think I'm going to die. My heart
is torn into pieces because of you.
"After this time, it'll get better.
After that passes, it'll be okay."
I lived like that for 20 years.
I don't have enough heart left to
feel anxious anymore.
I can't live like this.
Come on. Why are you doing this?
Why are you acting
like a different person?
What I said wasn't
in the heat of the moment.
I thought about it a lot.
If you keep this up, it's obvious that
our kids and I will be covered in wounds.
Everything will be ruined.
If that's the alternative, I'd rather
that we get separated.
Eun Ok! Eun Ok! Hey, Eun Ok.
Eun Ok! Eun Ok! Eun Ok!
Eun Ok!
Subtitles by DramaFever