Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 8]
Yoon Sung Min!
You turned in a blank test paper
turned off your phone,
and skipped cram school.
How dare you come home?
Should I leave?
You've gone insane!
What's wrong with you?
Aren't you going to college?
I'll take care of it.
Leave me alone.
I'm your mom.
That's why I can't leave you alone.
I can't forgive you this time!
Forgive me?
Do you have the right to say that?
I have the right because I'm your mother.
I gave birth to you, and I raised you!
Only an innocent mom can say that.
Honey!
How dare you? Did I not
ask you not to do this?
Is this all you are?
Why are you crying, like a baby?
Are you doing this for me to see? Huh?
Answer me!
Sung Min!
Oh, my...
What was that noise?
Are they fighting?
You didn't hear the shocking news?
Yoon Sung Min, our family's pride,
turned in a blank test paper.
What? Is that true?
Ma'am, it's going to fall off!
Ah...
Why the heck did he do that?
Any sign of Sung Min?
What's gotten into him?
Well... actually...
Somehow, Sung Min found out.
It turns out, he wanted
to have a paternity test.
What?
Oh, no...
Honey, hurry up.
We need to find Sung Min!
Okay.
The customer's phone has been turned off.
Please leave a voice message.
His cell phone is off.
How could he be so immature?
Hello?
- Sir, this is Hyun Jee.
- Who?
Hyun Jee, Sung Min's friend.
Hyun Jee?
Yes.
Wait a second.
I'll put my mom on the phone.
It's Sung Min's dad.
It's me, Tae Soo.
Hyun Jee was talking to
Sung Min on the phone.
He didn't sound good,
so she went over to see him.
And he was in really rough shape.
He took an Advil and fell asleep.
Let Eun Ok know.
So he's at your place?
Okay, I'll be there soon.
Why don't you let him sleep here tonight?
He finally just fell asleep.
He's sick, let him sleep.
Okay.
I'm sorry for imposing on you.
But yes, please, let him stay there.
Okay then.
What's going on?
Why should Sung Min stay at her house?
Bring him home right now!
He has a fever. He took some
medicine and just fell asleep.
Let him stay there for tonight.
Honey!
Nothing good will come out of it
if you two see each other now anyway.
If my mom finds out,
the whole family will be in turmoil.
Stay strong. You need
to pull yourself together.
That's the first step in this process.
Okay?
Oh, man.
Oh! You're up?
Good. Now you have the temperature
of a normal human being.
Are you feeling okay?
Do you remember how you got here?
What was that medicine?
Why do you take it so often?
We were talking about you.
Drink some water.
Mom said you should
drink water to keep hydrated.
Come on!
Geez, who knew my first love
would be such an pathetic man?
So...
Do you feel better, now that you've
hurt your parents and ran away?
I'm not in the mood to joke around.
I'm being serious.
My dad is not my birth father.
Mom deceived me for 18 years.
But you're telling me to act cool?
Now that you say it like that,
I guess it makes sense.
Listen.
This has helped me get through
tough times in the past.
As you know, this test was very
important for his transcript.
Turning in a blank test
is really damaging.
Sometimes particularly exemplary students
rebel like this due to stress.
The way you take action,
as his mother, will be very important.
Do Kyung.
It's me.
Can you do me a favor?
Let's just talk, without causing a scene.
It won't take long.
I understand why you are upset.
Regardless of whether or not you can
forgive me, there isn't much I can say.
That being said, are you going to let all
of the effort you've put in, go to waste?
What benefit did you gain from
turning in a blank test paper?
Sung Min, let's be reasonable here, okay?
All you care about is my grades.
Wouldn't it be right for you
to give me an explanation first?
Don't you think that you should tell me
who my birth father is, or what happened?
I know you're upset.
I know you're confused.
But can't you understand that I had
my reasons for keeping this from you?
That's your business.
You don't care about my feelings.
Yoon Sung Min!
Hey!
Is this really how you're going to act?
I'm having a hard time
keeping up with you!
Hey! Ah--
That's why I told you not to follow me.
How much more time are you going
to waste acting like a child?
Whether he's your birth father
or not, you live with him.
Since you were born,
he's protected you and loved you.
You've had a good life!
Do you know how secure
that should make you feel?
Can't you just let it go
and only think about that?
I'm about to go crazy because I can't!
Then what was the point
of telling me all of that?
You should have agonized all by yourself!
You're right.
I'm regretting that now!
I told you everything about me
while you can't even tell me
about your secret medicine.
Hyun Jee!
Hyun Jee! Baek Hyun Jee!
What happened?
What's wrong with her?
Out of nowhere, she just
started having trouble breathing.
I turned around for a moment,
and she was on the ground.
What did the doctor say?
He said that she's stabilized,
and that she'll be okay.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
You. What did you do to Hyun Jee?
Don't do that. It's not his fault.
He just said that it is!
Say something.
What did you do, that she had
to go to the emergency room?
Gi Bum! It's not his fault. Let him go.
Sung Min!
What happened?
Is Hyun Jee okay?
She's okay. Take Sung Min home now.
No, you can't!
Hey, how did you raise your boy, huh?
Don't make a scene!
If you don't want to know the issue,
then you can keep acting that way.
The doctor said she'd be okay.
Her mom said it wasn't your fault.
If anyone is at fault...
it's me.
As for me...
If my children suffer...
All the blame falls on me.
Because I didn't lead a proper life,
my children are getting punished.
Even though I know that,
I still don't live the right way.
That's why I feel ashamed,
and that's why I'm sorry.
Dad...
They say blood is thicker than water.
But do you know what's
even thicker than blood?
When I think about you, Sung Min...
I feel something overflowing,
deep down and through my heart.
To me, whatever that is,
it feels thicker than blood.
That's the truth.
Dad...
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
That's not true.
Geez.
You're still a baby.
When will you grow up? Huh?
She's taking psychiatric medication?
For what? Why?
Calm down. You'll wake Hyun Jee up.
So hurry up and tell me.
You know she's been
training to be a singer.
I was told she did since sixth grade.
The competitive environment
was too much for that little thing.
She didn't even say anything about it.
Eventually, she began
suffering from anxiety disorder.
Don't worry too much.
She's taking medicine.
She's getting treated.
And she's been much better
since we came here.
What dosage did they give her?
What's the company? What's the name?
Who's the CEO?
I'll take my guys
and teach them a lesson!
You are hopeless.
Why do you think I kept this from you?
What do you think Hyun Jee
needs the most during this time?
Rest! And parents on whom she can rely.
But see what you're trying to do.
What can you achieve with your fists?
A father like you can't help.
I was just... upset to hear
Hyun Jee was sick.
Can I ride along when Hyun Jee
goes to see her doctor?
I would like to give her a ride at least.
Let me know when she goes.
When did you wake up?
Did you fight with Dad?
No.
I was just trying to calm him down.
He was very upset to hear about you.
He has to be upset.
You didn't tell him everything, right?
No, I just told him it was due to stress.
Mom, I just...
I don't want him to ever
know what happened.
Okay.
Lord, if you ask me...
what sin have I committed...
My biggest sin is that even though
I loved Do Kyung and Hyun Jee
I let them leave. I didn't protect them.
Oh, how I hate myself so much.
But...
I want to change my ways...
so that I can get
Do Kyung and Hyun Jee back.
If you ask me again,
what my biggest sin is...
What you are doing now is a sin.
Pardon?
You should keep it quiet in the church.
Okay.
Welcome back!
My grandchild!
Look how thin you are!
Welcome back! All is good,
as long as you're back.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
Don't say that!
You must have been really stressed out!
You turned in a blank paper and ran
away from home? You're pathetic!
I told your mom to not stress you out.
So take it easy! Come here!
What's all this? Is this a party?
Sung Min,
I made spicy rice cakes for you!
And Grandma and I bought the pizza!
It must be nice!
Everyone worried about you!
Eat up before the food gets cold!
You should sit down too.
Grandma, the way you
pronounce "stress" is wrong.
Who cares? Just eat up!
This is all mine!
- Okay. Eat up.
- Looks yummy!
I didn't think that I could
keep it a secret forever.
I was going to tell you...
Right around the time you got married.
Everything you want to know is in here.
Good night.
Not that... two red bagels
and two Americanos.
Boss, you look tired.
I couldn't sleep at all
last night. I was so upset.
Did something happen?
How can I sleep well when I can't
protect my wife and daughter?
Bub Gyu, I will get back
together with Do Kyung.
Geez, the chairman won't leave you alone.
I have to face him someday.
I'll have a good plan.
He won't be able to say much.
I'm going to die from running!
I said he wouldn't sell the house.
Why are you still sending people over?
I don't care. Bye!
Is your house still up for sale?
The chairman is too much!
He's trying to control you with that!
Boss, you said that you
were meeting him today.
Don't beat around the bush.
Be frank with him!
It'll backfire for sure!
You know how he is.
It's better to kneel down and beg--
Hey! Boss doesn’t deserve
that kind of humiliation!
- That's not important at this point.
- Then what?
Be quiet.
I'll take care of it.
Cheers!
Your script was so good,
I wanted to treat you to dinner.
But then, Director Baek
said that I should do it right.
That's why I prepared this.
I wanted to brag about
your grilling expertise.
Isn't this nice, Madam Oh?
It was a great idea, Mr. Chairman.
I was going to invite the
hard-working staff over anyway.
What do you think, Dad?
Since I became the CEO,
the script got so much better!
You don't worry about a thing,
and just enjoy the show.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
We finally have a good script,
all thanks to the chairman.
We couldn't have even started this
movie without you, Mr. Chairman.
We came this far because of your support.
Truly, we need someone
like you to support us!
I didn't do anything,
but I feel good, huh?
I haven't seen a script
as good as this one
since Moon Hee's Black Stream.
Our hero, Director Bong! Eat up!
Thank you. It looks good.
Oh!
Why? Is the meat bad?
No. It's so delicious,
I was caught off-guard.
As for me, the ending was a bit crazy.
Is it right that a guy who ran away with
a gangster's wife gets to live happily?
What about it?
I thought that was the best part!
What do you call that...
fantasy! It's got fantasy!
Director Yoon has an
eye for good scripts.
The victory of a man
who risked his life for love!
That is so touching!
Don't you agree?
Yes... ah. Ah, ah.
Yes... ah. Yes.
It can happen in a movie.
But not in real life.
What would happen
if it were a real story?
Dad, what about these?
Geez, aren't they so plump?
Oh, geez, Director Bong!
I'm sorry. I was too worked up.
He'd be lucky to have his life spared.
Here!
We are out of alcohol.
I'll bring some from your study.
I'll go with you.
I'm a bit curious.
I'd love to take a look
at your book collection.
Man, he's definitely a writer.
Seriously! Why did you
do that to me, Madam?
What? You came here following me.
I came here to tell you to stop.
Didn't you see him?
He cut it off... and then...
The sacrifice of the green pepper and the
tomatoes made me realize something...
Which is... life is valuable.
Do you really want me to die?
Then... what about the Napoleon and
Josephine analogies in the script?
That was exactly our story!
Of course, you inspire me!
That's why I was able to
complete the script in the first place!
However, this isn't the time...
to follow our impulsive emotions.
It's time to be reasonable!
You completed a script because
of the inspirations I gave you.
Are you saying you don't need me anymore?
That's not what I'm saying.
I don't even know what I'm feeling!
Mr. Chairman, please take this.
Huh?
I put the meat, the sauce,
and my respect together in the wrap!
You worked hard grilling the meat.
I can't eat it, I have indigestion.
Oh...
Tae Soo, you're being so obvious.
What?
Dad, let him live in that house.
I can't watch this. It's so sad.
You really suck at sucking up!
By the way, you should
come downtown sometime.
There's a new restaurant
that you'll really like.
I want to take you there.
What do you want?
It's not like that.
Let's have dinner with Do Kyung.
Speak Korean when you're supposed to.
Worry about those calculations later.
Don't be like that.
You've been like that long enough!
Be quiet. Stop drinking.
There's nothing to drink!
Are you distilling your own liquor?
Where the hell are they?
Producer Lee, go check the study.
Sure.
Really, why are they taking so long?
Director Bong!
Oh, Producer Lee.
What are you reading?
I showed him a very good book.
We'll be there soon.
Can you take the drinks?
Why don't we all go together?
They're waiting.
No, you go first. We'll be there soon.
Okay. Come soon.
What should we take?
Hey... that one.
Okay.
Oh my...
Please stop! We almost got caught!
You started, Director Bong!
Who did? I did?
Geez, I'm sorry.
I'm the emotional type.
I tend to get excited.
What should we do now?
Oh geez.
I have no idea. What I do know,
is that we shouldn't do this.
You're so interested in
other people's business.
But you're so indifferent
to your own granddaughter!
Do you know why
Hyun Jee came back? Do you?
If you're drunk, then go to sleep!
I'm not saying this because I'm drunk.
I can't hold it in anymore!
- What's wrong?
- You stay out!
I will get back together with Do Kyung.
I will live with Do Kyung and Hyun Jee.
Gi Bum, stop it.
You stop talking about the
house already! I'm sick of it!
What? Why didn't you read it?
Aren't you curious as to
who your real father is?
I am curious... very much so.
And?
Mom's diary will be like Pandora’s box.
I wish I never found out
in the first place.
Even that was too much for me.
If I open her diary,
I don't think I'll handle it well.
And the bottom line is...
I only have one father.
Oh, Yoon Sung Min.
You're cool as a cucumber.
You've become mature overnight!
Just a few days ago, you were a crybaby!
I got it.
Anyway, let's not feel
sorry for each other.
For what?
You know my secret.
I know your secret.
We're even.
I'm not sure if you know this.
My nickname is,
"Handsome man with good looks."
I will help you.
I won't make you upset,
and I will help you feel at ease.
So what's your point?
Are you apologizing, or are you saying
you'll stay with me as my wonderful man?
What?
Tell me. Is this the first time you’re
telling a girl that you like her?
What are you talking about?
You paid extra attention to
your clothes and your hair today.
You came here before me
and set the table with sweets.
More importantly, you are babbling--
Not true.
This isn't my first time.
Are you telling me you like me then?
I have to go somewhere.
You stay here and think about it.
Geez.
In a movie?
Yes, I think you are
perfect for the character.
"A mysterious cafe owner."
It's one of the lead roles.
Dad, it's a mistake.
I watched her movies. She's really bad.
Hey... my daughter?
You are hurting my feelings.
I guess I was too honest, huh?
Yes, that was mean.
Regardless, you should star in the movie.
Hyun Jee, you make music for the movie.
What music?
The original soundtrack!
I look forward to it.
Really?
Do you think the CEO of a movie company
is just joking around with his daughter?
I'll make your dreams come true!
Just tell me what you want!
The Sun? The Moon?
I'll get them for you! Just tell me.
You don't seem to believe me.
Should I get the moon?
What?
He took her to the hospital
for her treatment today.
I don't think Lee Do Kyung
accepted his offer for the role yet.
I was nervous about this...
What an idiot!
Yes, Mr. Chairman?
Sure. I'll call you later.
Yes.
Would you take a look at this.
Director Yoon!
What brings you here, Officer Seo?
Who were you talking to?
You never answer my calls.
I was worried about your daughter.
I called you many times.
A woman answered.
"The customer cannot answer his phone.
Please leave your message."
Don't worry about my daughter.
Nothing happened.
Really? That's a relief.
A father who worries about
his daughter coming home late
is either a policeman or a gangster.
They both have many enemies.
That's why I'm not married.
I want to focus on my police work.
Bro... I'm a bit busy. I have to go.
I wish I were busy too!
I'm jealous of these
busy guys, running around!
By the way, you know what?
A guy called me and said he was
Mr. Son from the movie company.
Do you know what Son Se Woon said?
He said he would bring me
a big blessing next week.
He told me to wait until then.
Okay! Then you should wait, right?
Keep on waiting!
Do you think that I'm joking?
He asked me for the new address
of the production company.
If he calls you, let me know.
Don't go alone.
Of course. How will he come?
Will he fall through the clouds,
or blow in with the wind?
Geez, are you saying he'll show up
like Son Oh Kong, because he's Son?
Isn't that Yoon Tae Soo?
Who's the guy next to him?
He looks familiar.
I think that's Officer Seo.
That's right.
Why are they talking?
I don't like it!
Get struck by lightning!
What is this?
Open it, first.
Mr. Chairman, isn't this
the title to the house?
I know how you feel, Tae Soo.
Honestly, compared to what you've done
for me all these years, this isn't much.
You must have been worried a lot.
I had no idea how much
you were thinking about me.
I'll work even harder for you
from now on, Mr. Chairman.
You're already doing a good job.
Don't say that.
You're giving me a house.
There's nothing I can't do for you.
If you need anything done,
please, just give me your orders.
Actually, there is one thing.
What is it? Consider it done!
It's not a big thing. There won't be
any blood on your hands for this one.
There's someone I need to send far away.
I don't want Lee Do Kyung to live here.
Pardon?
I want her to be gone from Daejeon.
As soon as possible.
Do Kyung, are you going back to acting?
I told you. I haven't decided yet.
Look at her. She won't budge.
You're making us jealous.
Okay!
"You mind your business."
"You humiliated me."
"I'll take it off if you tell me to."
"Bok Gil!"
"Bok Gil's Mama! He's eating
stuff off of the ground!"
"Bok Gil's Mama!"
That's right!
Can you get me a role too?
Back in school, I was in an acting club.
Make my dreams come true!
Huh? Huh?
Okay, I will ask him.
Nice!
Everyone in One Heart
could be in the movie!
That's great!
Hey.
Doesn't the director decide the cast?
He may be the CEO,
but he's a bit out of line.
He's not a tyrant.
You don't know this field.
The CEO has a lot of
control over the movie.
Tae Soo, who is the film's
primary investor, didn't say anything.
That's because Gi Bum has all
the power to make decisions.
I heard that they are
equals in what they do.
Well, Gi Bum has someone
who has his back.
You mean the chairman?
Speaking of him,
does he know what's going on?
Won't he be upset when he finds out,
just like he was regarding the election?
Is that what you want?
It's not that. I just don't you
to spill cold water all over it.
Cold water?
Do you hate me being in
the movie that much?
Why are you fighting again?
We have yummy chicken here.
Please just enjoy the chicken.
Try the drumstick.
- Get that out of my face.
- Okay.
Oh?
Ladies of One Heart,
please come tonight at 7 p.m.
Choong Shim Pictures and
One Heart will have a joint gathering.
Baek Gi Bum from Choong Shim Pictures.
Welcome, everyone!
We are here today
to announce Choong Shim Pictures'
first movie, "The Man with Two Faces"
and to congratulate
Lee Do Kyung on her lead role!
I'm paying for everything at this party!
Please enjoy the food and drinks,
and everyone have a great time!
Thank you!
Put your hands together!
Casting?
I'm not sure. Let's wait and see.
Nothing is confirmed yet.
Thank you.
We're going to start the night
with Do Kyung's song.
Actress Lee Do Kyung!
Don't do that!
Please come up to the stage!
Don't be shy. You're going to
be in a movie soon! Come on!
I said I didn't decide yet.
It's decided! Come to the stage! Come on!
Wow!
Kyung Mee, should we do it together?
Go ahead.
Shall we?
Then how about the three of us?
Eun Ok, come out!
- I don't want to.
- Hey!
Eun Ok, please help her!
I said I don't want to!
- Ho Soo High!
- I don't want to!
I don't want to!
Please help Do Kyung!
Kim Eun Ok! Kim Eun Ok!
Kim Eun Ok!
This woman...
Geez, it hurts!
Lee Do Kyung has incredible
passion and amazing talents!
I look forward to your movie!
Wow!
- Good job.
- Let's toast!
To our new movie, and to
Lee Do Kyung's success!
Cheers!
You were awesome.
You're making me blush.
Who's blushing?
You're going to be in a movie soon!
Don't you need to discuss
casting with the director?
Geez, I'm the CEO here.
This is what I'm supposed to do.
Do you know a good salon?
Should I look around for you?
You need a new car. Oh, no...
You need a manager.
No, should you sign the contract first?
Geez, casting you has
given me a lot of work.
I dedicate this song to you!
My dear, Do Kyung, whom I adore the most!
There isn't anything
I can't do, if you want it.
I'll get the stars from the sky for you.
Can I see you outside really quick?
What's up? Do you have something to say?
Boss will be mad if he
finds out I told you this.
But I can't hold it inside anymore!
Why? Did something happen
to Tae Soo again?
The chairman presented the papers
to your house to Tae Soo.
He said he'd give it to him if Tae Soo
kicked Lee Do Kyung out of Daejeon.
What?
He said the house issue was resolved.
This is so damn frustrating.
He gets calls from
the realtor all the time
warning that he's sending
people over to look at the house.
My dearest, Do Kyung!
Mr. Chairman! Mr. Chairman!
Your daughter in-law is here!
What brings you here?
I heard your housekeeper quit.
So I brought you some side dishes.
You didn't hear that a new
housekeeper is coming tomorrow?
Oh...
This big house needs help every day.
We can't ask Madam Oh to suffer this way.
Should I fix your lunch?
No, thanks. Madam Oh isn't here.
And I'm not hungry.
I talked to her on the phone.
She won't be happy if
you start skipping meals.
Give me ten minutes.
I made nutritious rice too.
There's a fire in their house.
Both the husband and
the wife are going crazy.
[To Director Bong: I'm thinking...]
Miss, please bring me
two glasses of wine.
Let me see.
Nice.
What's going on?
Mr. Chairman, what brings you here?
You humiliated me!
Oh, man! Did you have a nightmare again?
No...
What's wrong?
What are you doing this to me?
I don't want to die!
Life is valuable.
Huh?
I need to go. I need to run away.
I need to write a new one! This is trash!
Burn it! Burn it!
What? Are you kidding me?
The story is not realistic!
Does it make sense that he runs away
with the wife of the head of a gang?
The first thing he should do
is run away from that woman!
I'll lock myself up in my house
for a week to rewrite the script.
If anyone asks, tell them I'm not here.
Please do that, Joon Seok, okay?
Thanks.
You better come to work tomorrow!
I won't!
Oh, Madam Oh!
Welcome home!
I told you not to come.
But you're still here?
I was going to leave after I fixed dinner
for the chairman and finished cleaning.
How was your book club meeting?
You said there was an artist guest today.
I used to do that kind
of thing in college.
A guy I liked wanted to
be a movie director.
It's all in the past.
Did you eat dinner? I brought eel--
Are you kidding me?
Do you know what time it is? Dinner?
Eel? I don't hate anything in life
as much as I hate eel.
Oh?
Huh?
You're still here? You said you
would leave after you set the table.
I was just about to finish up cleaning.
What are you doing here?
Why are you here getting scolded?
It's not that--
Oh! Did Tae Soo send you?
He's worried he might lose the house.
But he's using his wife?
Shame on him!
I'm not here because of that.
Leave immediately. I want to rest!
Don't do this. Please go home.
Tae Soo, you should come get your wife.
Eun Ok.
I'm sorry.
That was an idiotic decision.
Don't say that.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Geez, who are the people
living in these condos?
They look even taller today.
I got 30 college kids to open
bank accounts within a week.
One million won is too much.
Just give them 800,000 won.
If one of them argues,
then give them one million won.
You should be fair to everyone.
Okay. Then give them your money.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Stand up! We're here to make money, okay?
- Yes, Boss!
- Sit.
- Cheers!
Who are you?
You can't see? We are the police.
What brings you here, Officer?
Would I be here to pick up those dishes?
I heard you were selling ghost
bank accounts to college kids.
You give them one million won?
What do you mean? I didn't hear anything
about that. Do you guys know anything?
I don't.
Geez, your hearts are darker
than those black noodles.
We're here because someone reported you.
Arrest them.
Hey, stop there!
Don't do that!
Geez...
What's the matter?
You couldn't sleep at all last night.
It's nothing.
I'm doing my best for you.
But I'm sure I'm lacking in many ways.
If you hate me or resent me,
don't forgive me! Just hit me.
With this.
My goodness! A gold ax?
It's pure gold. So don't
hit me too hard, okay?
You totally scared me! You're naughty!
Was I naughty? Then I'm bad!
Okay, you can hit me.
Oh, my goodness! Stop it.
Mr. Chairman, I have something
I want to do for you.
The script needs changing.
The chairman wants to see you.
Sir, Director Bong is here.
Okay, sit down.
Mr. Chairman, why did you want to see me?
Please save me! Mr. Chairman! I--
You save me.
Pardon?
Well, it's important
that the movie succeeds.
But the success of my personal life
is important as well.
What do you mean?
There's a writer who can
help you with your script.
A writer?
She's a genius writer, who loves books.
Madam Oh.
What's wrong?
Wow, Director Bong,
you came here yourself?
Mr. Chairman, why did you do that?
I just wanted to give him my opinion.
Oh, no. Words can change when
they pass through many mouths.
You should tell him in person,
so that your words don't get twisted.
Don't you agree?
Of course I do.
Mr. Chairman, you are the man
who makes things happen!
I'll get back to what I was doing.
Call me if you need me.
Please take me with you, Sir.
Please take me!
I'm trying to help you make a good movie.
Listen to the writer, and work hard.
Please think again! Please!
Why are you doing this to me?
With one word, I can make
your movie, or your life...
disappear like smoke.
Do you want me?
It's rude to ask a question
when you know the answer.
Director Bong, you found your
creative energy because of me, right?
Yes, that's true.
Do you know how amazing it is
to find someone you can talk to?
I'm not saying that we
should have a romance.
I'm simply saying we should help
with each others' intellectual needs.
Monday, Wednesday, Friday at 3 p.m.
Meet me right here.
Right here?
The chairman is literally holding
a sword, just outside that door!
It's quiet inside the eye of the storm.
This thrill will give you
even more creative energy!
Your movie, and you and I,
need a perfect scenario!
I don't want Lee Do Kyung to live here.
I want her to be gone from Daejeon.
I'm at the movie production office.
Can I see you here for a moment?
Do Kyung!
Do Kyung?
I am Cho Dong Chool, you bastard!
How dare you act that way here?
Bastard!
What have I done so wrong to you, huh?
You can't get enough of me, huh?
You bastard!
What are you talking about?
You!
I know you told the police everything!
Because of you, all of
my guys got arrested!
Bastard!
I won't leave you alone anymore.
A mouse can bite through
a cast if he's cornered!
Geez.
Tae Soo.
Oh, Do Kyung.
She has nothing to do with me.
Let her go and talk to me.
Don't make me laugh.
If you want to save her, kneel.
Kneel!
Now!
Tae Soo.
I'll do it.
I'll do it. So you let her go now.
Let her go.
Hey, hey! Do it again! Kneel down again!
Do it again! Now!
You bastard!
He's nothing! How dare he?
Kneel down again!
What was that?
Tae Soo.
What have I done?
Do Kyung!
What happened?
I did that, Gi Bum.
What?
He came for me and then held her hostage.
Bastard!
Honey!
What happened?
Eun Ok!
Honey!
No!
He's not breathing.
Could it be...
What have you done?
Let me see.
What are you looking at? CPR!
Tae Soo, do the CPR!
Me?
- Now!
Hurry up!
Geez, I'll do it!
Do Kyung, I will do it.
- Now!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Sweet Savage Family]
Let's save him first.
Nothing works out because of you!
You fox!
Who are you?
Why are you standing
in front of my office?
How have you been?