[Episode 11]
Tae Soo, are you okay?
- We're over here!
- Save us, Officer Seo!
Over here!
- Officer Seo!
- Over here! Over here!
Don't move.
There are real bullets in my gun.
Thank you so much for coming, Bro!
I texted him earlier.
I told him to track us down with the GPS.
Good job! You did a good job, Tae Soo!
Are you okay?
Yes, Bro!
How about you, Director Baek?
I'm fine, I'm fine!
What were you even doing?
They're still saying that they're fine.
Bro!
What the heck are you doing?
You're a police officer!
I told you yesterday,
when I bought you farewell drinks.
Life is about making it,
or not making it.
If you're unlucky, things get
taken away from you.
Bro!
Oh my, oh my!
I forgot to introduce him.
My savior, Officer Seo Chul Joong!
I did what I had to do.
As a policeman,
I had to save a dying man.
What does that mean?
You killed me.
You buried me.
When I woke up,
I couldn't move my body.
I thought to myself,
"I'm going to die here."
But then, Officer Seo appeared!
And he saved me!
I went to the mountains.
I saw something moving in the ground.
So I started to dig into the ground.
The shaman from Miari was right.
If she hadn't told me that
I should dig with my front paws
I wouldn't have done that.
I love you, Mother.
What is it that you want?
You're asking that again?
How many times have I told you?
I want to take your life!
If they get annoying, just use this.
What?
It's quick and easy.
Subtitles by DramaFever
Which one should I shoot first? Huh?
You?
Now, on to the final round.
This time, we'll do freestyle acting.
Wait.
Since it's the final,
let's make it a bit more difficult.
A comet is on its way to Earth.
It will collide with the Earth
in five minutes.
Everyone is about to die.
Now, you're going to say
your farewell before you die.
What will you say,
and to whom will you say it?
Let's start with Lee Do Kyung.
You don't have much time.
The comet will hit Earth in five minutes.
Now, cue!
My dear daughter, Hyun Jee.
Thank you so much for being my daughter.
I...
I will only cherish good memories of you.
I will protect you from Heaven...
so that you won't have to cry again.
You wanted a happy family so badly.
And I really wanted
to make that happen for you.
I am so sorry for not
being able to do that for you.
Hyun Jee!
I am so sorry.
Mommy...
Mommy loves you so much.
Honey.
Sung Min's dad...
They say I'll die in five minutes.
Well... I'm glad.
Finally, I don't have to be
a gangster's wife anymore.
I'll make this short,
since there isn't much time.
Sung Min and Soo Min...
If you raise them as if
they didn't have a mom
you know what I'll do to you, right?
Let your mother be sometimes, too.
About you and me...
I do not want to meet you
in our next lives.
"Let's have a happier life
in our next lives."
That's something only those who
didn't try hard enough would say.
But we did our best.
You and I did.
Yoon Tae Soo...
You are the best.
You are the best husband.
You are the best father.
If I could wish for only one thing...
I would wish that in our next lives
we would be born with
golden spoons in our mouths.
I mean it.
Okay. Now...
I will announce the winner.
The winner is...
Dad, save me...
Oh, hello, Mr. Chairman!
This is Son Se Woon.
Who?
It's Son Se Woon,
the CEO of the movie production company.
You invested
three billion won into my movie.
What? How did you...
Oh...
You must be surprised that I'm alive.
Everyone is surprised.
I can give you more details later.
You saw the photos I sent you, right?
Don't you think
those photos are worth as much
as you invested in the movie?
Are you threatening me
with my son's life?
How did you figure that out?
You're a quick one.
I think I deserve the right to do this,
since I almost died.
Your son...
He's still too young to accompany
me into the Underworld.
You can keep him!
Hello?
What did he say?
Ha!
Suddenly...
I'm thirsty!
Well...
Let me have a sip.
Let me have a sip too.
Oh, okay.
Wait.
It's not fun if you just give it to them.
Give me that.
Which one should I give water to first?
How about here?
Here? Here?
Here?
How about the middle?
Oh, you got it.
You guys are so inconsiderate.
That's why you're both losers, gosh.
That was all we had.
Keep eating, please.
You're sure that I won the role?
It's not a mistake, right?
I can't believe this is really happening.
I know how you feel.
Congratulations.
Thank you so much!
Thank you. Thank you!
You don't need to thank me.
Everyone was horrible.
So I picked the least horrible one.
From now on,
you need to do a good job.
I see.
I have a question.
- I forgot.
- You know.
Oh, in the emotional scene...
Everyone tried very hard to shed tears.
But you didn't shed a tear.
Are you a bit dry?
I guess I am.
I'd prefer to laugh until I die.
Because I have already shed
too many tears in my lifetime.
Yes, I picked the right one!
She's definitely an unfortunate woman.
What? An unfortunate woman?
Yes, an unfortunate woman.
The best actors are those who have
had many hardships in their lives.
It's like... through hardships,
they head for the stars!
For the stars.
Huh? Stars?
Anyway, I'm proud of myself
for finding a treasure!
I'll give you a big hug.
No, thanks.
You will regret...
- I'll just regret it then.
- She's stubborn! I love that!
Anyway, can you invest in my movie?
I'm William.
William. William.
William, William... okay?
I need to go to a sauna.
I need to sober up.
Then let's drink at the sauna.
Okay.
Mr. Chairman.
I'll just go to the police
station with your son.
Well...
If you sin, you should
receive punishment, right?
You can see your son's face
when it's all over the newspapers.
I kind of think you'll just
give me a lot of money.
Oh, I almost forgot. Mr. Chairman!
Eat good food and live a long life, okay?
Live long enough to see
your son coming out of prison.
I'm busy, so I'm going to hang up...
Pardon me?
Excuse me...
Do you have more to say?
Then do that.
He has a burner phone,
so it's hard to track him down.
What should we do?
Send the money.
Wow, the chairman is a big man!
He sent the money right away.
Really?
Then is it over now?
Yes, Officer Seo.
You worked hard.
Wow, did you save the country
in your previous life?
You're so lucky that
you have a rich father.
You! You think I'll just let you be?
If you want to.
Don't do that, don't do that.
Don't do that!
It hurts, right?
I said stop!
Do you want to try?
It's kind of fun.
Tae Soo.
Bro, why are you doing something
that you're going to regret later?
I think I'll regret it if I don't.
It hurts. Stop.
I know what we're doing is bad.
But Chairman Baek isn't someone
that you want to hang out with!
I'll send my last gift to you.
So think it through.
Let's go.
There's a good soup spot nearby.
Should we go?
Of course!
I should go back!
This place isn't good for me!
In the lavish temptations.
I stand, smiling.
But everything feels unfamiliar.
You always choose
between the two.
You will lose everything here.
Geez.
Now you're acting as an idiotic duo?
Say something with that mouth of yours!
Why didn't you just let me die?
What?
Gi Bum!
You were going to spend the money anyway.
Why did you take so long?
You have no idea what he did to me.
That bastard!
I'll kill him when I catch him.
Wait and see.
Look at him!
The arrogance...
I... I am very sorry.
It all happened so quickly.
Do you think that
you and Gi Bum are equals?
Pardon me?
Do you think that you're actually my son?
Well... Mr. Chairman.
Why do you think I had you stay close
to Gi Bum all of these years?
So you could be a duo
and have fun together?
I did that so you could calm
him when he lost control.
Save him when he's drowning.
And take beatings for him.
That's why I took care of you
and supported you.
Tae Soo.
You are the one who introduced Son to me.
And you are the one who maintained
a close relationship with Officer Seo.
Don't you think this is a bit strange?
Mr. Chairman.
Geez.
Do you think that
you and Gi Bum are equals?
I had you stay close to Gi Bum.
I did that so you could calm
him when he lost control.
Save him if he's drowning.
And take beatings for him.
That's why I took care of you.
But Chairman Baek isn't someone
that you want to hang out with!
I will send my last gift to you.
So think it through.
[OFFICER SEO]
Let's talk.
Do you have more to say?
I only have half the money.
So save just one of them.
You'd like to only save your son?
Then what about Yoon Tae Soo?
He's the one who buried you.
Regardless, no one
would say anything.
You said you had all the evidence.
If you take care of everything
regarding my son with the police
I'll send you more money.
Oh...
I thought he was your adopted son.
What adopted son?
It would be better if he didn't exist.
I'm cleaning all kinds of messes for him,
but he doesn't even thank me.
His wife is even a bigger joke.
Mom, can't you just be the protagonist?
You only won a supporting role.
Not anyone can be a protagonist.
You mom did very well for a rookie!
Congratulations, Mom!
Thanks.
Wow, I never knew that
my daughter-in-law was so talented!
I'll buy you a nice outfit.
Just wait and see.
You have no money.
I have money. I have a lot.
Then buy me one! I would love that.
It's really great that
I've become an actress!
I get nice gifts from my mother-in-law.
Geez!
Dad!
Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad!
Mom won a role. She'll be in the movie!
What?
Mom, I'm a bit tired.
I'm going to go rest.
Why is he acting like that
when his wife just did so well?
Please eat some cake.
I'll go check on him.
Go ahead.
Honey.
Aren't you going to congratulate me
on winning the role?
Aren't you curious what role I got?
There was an amazing twist at the end.
You're being pathetic.
How much longer will you be like this?
I got it. Please stop.
It's not because of you.
Then what's wrong?
Your phone was turned off all day.
I'm really tired.
Let's talk later.
Honey.
I want you to know one thing.
I'm not doing this because I wanted
to be an actress or be in this movie.
I don't know how much help
I can actually give you.
But I'm proud of myself because I feel
like I can relieve your burden a bit.
I'll get your bath ready.
Soak yourself in hot water before bed.
You smell sweaty.
William? Whoever that is...
Because of that strange man,
everything is ruined.
Even our sweet director
was swayed by him.
It's my fault.
You did your best to support me.
But my acting wasn't good enough.
I thought that I did my best.
Oh...
There's no point in saying that now.
I never thought I would
need to use this card.
But I think it's time
to implement Plan B.
Plan B?
How are you?
Director Bong, did you
really write this script?
What happened to the story?
Well, that's... because of Writer Oh...
Are you blaming your writer now?
Aren't you the director here?
I know. I'm really confused these days.
You either fix the script,
or find a different actress.
I can't let my wife act out
this kind of crazy character.
And not because she's my wife.
No one should act out this
kind of wretched character.
Don't you want to make a movie?
Tae Soo, you can't do that.
What do you mean?
Eun Ok has to be in the movie.
Eun Sil, do you really want your
sister to do this kind of stuff?
Of course I don't like it!
But...
She has a reason.
What reason?
Please don't ask me that.
Please!
She'll kill me if I tell you this.
I won the role, just like you asked me.
Good job, good job!
I knew you would be amazing!
I told you.
You would be better than
someone who has acted before.
You're being kind.
Since you got the role,
you should perform well.
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
And... about what you promised last time.
I hope you'll keep your promise.
Huh?
I mean the title to the house.
Oh, that!
Of course I should keep my promise.
After the movie is finished
I'll give that to you.
After it's finished?
Well, do you win a marathon medal
when you start running a race?
Mr. Chairman...
Eun Ok.
In reality, I should have
sent you an invoice.
Tae Soo got kidnapped by
Mr. Son, like an idiot.
I paid a ransom and saved him.
What? Mr. Son did?
He's the worst kind of swindler!
This time, I'll let it go for you.
Don't worry. Just do what I say.
Then you will get what you want.
Get up.
- I said get up!
- Honey!
What the heck are you doing?
Mr. Chairman.
Is it true that you had her audition,
using the title to the house as bait?
Is it true that you pushed her,
so you could ruin Lee Do Kyung's life?
- Tae Soo!
- I...
It's true, I'm your dog.
I bark, I bite, as you say.
I don't know when I'll be killed,
but I always wag my tail.
I became your dog...
So that my family could
live like human beings.
Mr. Chairman,
you can keep me as your dog.
But leave my wife alone!
Let's go.
Let go of my hand! It hurts!
What's wrong with you? Are you crazy?
Are you insane?
I was insane, and now I'm back to normal.
- Huh?
- Finally!
I see yellow as yellow and red as red!
I got it. But what happened with Mr. Son?
I thought everything was
taken care of that night.
You should have told me what happened!
What about you? You went along
with that old man's scheme?
Did you really have to crush your friend?
What about me?
Don't say it like that!
Would I do that, just because I hate her?
I was just that desperate.
Yes, I got greedy.
If I was capable of being a mean person,
just this once
he would give me a house that I could
never dream of buying on my own.
Eun Ok!
You said you didn't want
to live like a dog.
But if you are a dog...
Then I am a dog too.
Where's the owner?
Did he go out to play?
Please let me pass you.
Hey, Number One!
- Oh, Bro!
- Yeah.
Wait. Let me get the burner first.
Okay, go ahead.
- Have you been well?
- Yes, how are you?
It's always the same for me.
Excuse me. Two orders of pork, please.
Two orders? Coming right up!
Bro, did you come alone?
I didn't come to eat.
I was passing by, so I came to say hello.
I see.
Can we have the check, please?
Okay!
I'm sorry, but can you set
that table over there?
Huh? Okay.
- Bye!
- Thank you!
Where are your servers?
Why are you working alone?
This time of day, I work alone.
I have part-timers for when it gets busy.
You have no workers?
I have no money.
It costs a lot to hire help.
By the way... how much does it cost
to start a restaurant like this?
Why? Are you interested?
Oh... I was just curious.
About 300 million won,
after the rent deposit.
300 million won?
Hey, Number Two!
Huh? Brother Tae Soo!
Wait one second.
What happened to your foot?
Are you hurt?
I tripped yesterday while
I was out on a delivery.
Did you go see a doctor?
Making a living is hard enough.
How could I afford that?
I have to save up
so I can pay the rent, at least.
Stay right here.
I'll be right back.
Oh... okay, okay.
I want some pastries.
Sure!
Huh?
Hey!
You're Number Three!
Right! Tae Soo!
You used to live next door!
That's right!
What are you doing here?
You used to work at a bank in Seoul.
Why are you doing this?
I retired a long time ago.
I lost all my stocks. So here I am.
I see.
Do Number One and Number Two
know you came back?
Don't tell them!
I'm sure they're having a hard time too.
I see.
Oh, well, how's business?
Well, fish-shaped pastries
are supposed to be the easiest.
When people lose a job, the first thing
they try is selling fish-shaped pastries!
That's why I started doing this too.
Well... making a living is so hard.
Yeah...
Geez! It's the police!
Help me push the cart! Hurry!
It's the police! Hurry!
Or they'll take it away!
Hurry up!
Geez, faster!
Oh, Do Kyung.
Are you just getting home now?
What brought you here?
Well, I wanted to see if you were okay.
What do you mean?
Your audition.
I heard a strange
guest judge ruined it all.
Geez, I should have been there.
I'm sure that I didn't get it simply
because I wasn't good enough.
Did you just come to ask about that?
Well...
It's Christmas soon.
How about taking a family trip?
Just to freshen things up.
Your cards are closed and your car
has been taken away. But a family trip?
Just go home and sleep.
You better watch where you're going.
I'm sorry.
Look at his hair...
Let me see.
Geez.
You, and I, are destined for each other.
Destined for each other!
It's done!
I want to brag to Yoon Sung Min!
Finally it's complete!
Memorize it so you don't make
any mistakes at the concert.
Are you working on my Christmas gift?
Geez, did he forget?
Did you forget?
Of course not.
I'm so tired from all of this work!
I'm going to sleep!
Picking a gift for a girl
is harder than math!
It's strange.
He even became stylish.
Are you picking a gift
for your girlfriend, instead of studying?
Let me give you a tip.
Girls like expensive gifts,
but they love romantic boys!
Romantic!
Kiss? Something like that?
What are you talking about?
It's not like that. Just get out.
It's not?
Your notebook is completely covered with
Hyun Jee's name! Hyun Jee! Hyun Jee!
When did you take that?
Do you want to die?
You should be more careful to
keep that relationship secret.
If Mom finds out, he'll be dead.
I can look the other way,
depending on what you do for me.
What do you want?
Say it!
That one.
Take it.
We're good now, right? Don't tell Mom.
The two of you, please leave my room.
Please get out.
Ah.
Do you know what
the next step in dating is?
I look forward to my Christmas gift.
What am I thinking?
Geez.
Wake up. What are you thinking?
Oh.
Wow.
Wow, cool!
Wow, this is so cool!
- Let me try too.
- No way, it's mine.
You're stingy...
Why are you drinking alone?
- Oh, Sung Goo.
- Yeah.
You look handsome today!
You're a handsome guy!
Boss, what's the matter?
Sung Goo.
What do you think...
we could do...
if we weren't gangsters?
Say what?
As for me...
I don't have 300 million won.
I don't know how to make a fire.
I don't know how to ride a motorcycle.
If your leg gets hurt,
you should go see a doctor.
I can't live my life afraid to get
caught by the police forever.
Say it so I can understand
what you want to say.
Huh?
Yeah...
I'm just babbling.
Hey.
Ask them how much I owe.
Ask them how much I should pay.
And ask them how much this bar costs.
Why should I ask that?
You know what?
I'm more jealous of the owner of this bar
than of anyone else in the world.
- Sung Goo.
- Yeah?
Let's go sing.
Geez! Boss!
You're really drunk. Sit down. Geez!
Geez.
Hey, call a driver.
You didn't bring your car.
Why do you need a driver?
Hey, if I said do it, just do it.
Call them.
And find out how much a driver makes.
Tell them I'll work hard.
You know what?
I can only drive an automatic.
I can't drive a manual.
I have a regular,
Type 2 driver's license.
You...
You know I have no sense of direction.
I can't go anywhere without a GPS.
I can't.
I have no idea where I'm going.
Geez... Boss.
Sung Goo.
Is the world so harsh?
Or am I that stupid?
I thought...
I thought I had the hardest life.
But if you look around,
so many people are suffering.
I never felt this way before.
But I'm frightened.
I don't know what kind of life
I've been living so far.
I...
This is the kind of life I've lived.
Honey! Honey!
Honey!
I don't have 300 million won.
I don't know how to ride a motorcycle.
Just run away. Run away.
Go.
Geez...
You're here!
Why did the string break?
I don't know. When I saw it
this morning, it was cut.
Let's go in.
We checked the guitar and the amplifier.
The composition is finished too.
We're ready to go, aren't we?
I'm a bit nervous.
You're nervous?
You've been performing in the streets!
We'll be fantastic!
Go!
Come to the cafe to rehearse.
I'll get it ready.
Okay. See you then.
Do you live around here?
Excuse me?
What's your relationship with that girl?
You're just a friend, right?
Not her boyfriend.
Why do you ask?
Oh...
I thought I should.
Never mind.
Office job...
Two million won.
Storage...
Age limit...
Oh.
Boss, I need to know.
Know what?
Why are you dragging this on so long?
I need to know.
It's nothing.
Oh, man. I am really disappointed.
Wow, Yoon Tae Soo.
You lead a good life.
What are you talking about?
Those two guys must be sitting
the way you are, in first class seats.
Flying over the clouds.
Huh?
Mr. Son and Officer Seo...
They left the country.
Is that true?
Geez, I'm about to explode!
I wasn't going to let them live.
But they had a plan, and they ran away.
Did you really not know that
Officer Seo was working with him?
The two of you call each other brothers.
What is it exactly, that you want to say?
If I had known, would I have been
stabbed in the back like that?
I'm about to explode too!
Do you know how much
money my dad blew?
He was all about you,
and then ended up losing money.
At least I'm his own blood.
But you, you're a money drainer.
A money drainer.
Yoon Tae Soo is looking for a job.
Man, after the huge mess
that he's made...
He's going to leave me?
That seems to be the case.
Bring me all of the books
for the bars that he manages.
Pardon me? You mean, all of the bars?
When my dog betrays me
I have to tighten his leash.
Oh, no, don't do that, dear actress!
- Are you crazy?
- I'll do it.
You are an actress. Please!
You didn't have to do this yourself!
Please just give us your orders.
We, your servants, will do everything.
Geez, you guys are overreacting.
Can you please recommend
Kyung Mee for a small role?
Otherwise, she'll keep
bothering you like this.
I have no power over that.
Don't say that.
You won your role because
Director William loved you.
And Director Bong drools all over him.
Why do you say that you have no power?
You're big stuff now!
Geez, have you changed already,
just because you're doing well?
How could our friendship change?
Sister! This is bad! This is bad!
Look at this.
What?
What is it?
Madam Oh!
Why did you suddenly change the script?
What are you talking about?
There's a bed scene
that was not there before.
And Mee Mee turned into a pervert?
Geez.
Mee Mee is dealing with extreme
loneliness and pain right now.
She was a gang leader's woman.
But she lost that title because
of Sunny's appearance.
I wrote it that way, to show
Mee Mee's desperation and humiliation.
She is feeling some complicated emotions.
I guess you don't
understand that, do you?
It's not that.
But then who is Sunny?
That character came out of nowhere.
That's me.
You are that Sunny who
is innocent and fragile?
Yes. Madam Oh thought I was perfect
for that role, so offered it to me.
I can't make the story
any sadder than this.
I told you, Ma'am.
Eun Ok is so prideful that
she likely won't take this with grace.
What? What's wrong?
Are my edits to the script too intense?
Geez! What were you thinking, Ma'am?
Director Bong!
Mee Mee turned into a pervert,
due to her stress?
Now she's disguised as a man?
Why didn't you just say she
was the boss' daughter?
Oh! That's a great twist!
Madam, please!
I can't let you ruin the script anymore.
Your job is done.
I'll take care of the rest.
Are you telling me that I'm fired?
It's not that. I'm saying you
should come to your senses!
Okay, I got it. Please calm down.
Let's drink this, okay?
Geez!
Okay.
Uh?
Why did you do that?
Over there...
There's a CCTV on the ceiling.
Where?
No! Don't look.
Then... are you saying...
Our previous times in this room
were all recorded?
Okay! Great!
So there's an unused company car?
- Yes.
- What kind of car?
It's a one-ton truck.
We just need to unload the cement.
Should I get it ready now?
Are you saying... I should take
my wife and Hyun Jee in that truck?
Yes, it seats three people.
All of you can ride in it comfortably.
Get out! Get out!
And how about using
the production company's credit card?
Are you trying to make me
look like a fool? Get out!
This is hard!
Geez! What should we do now?
The chairman must be spying on us!
We're dead!
Please, please, calm down.
We need to think calmly.
Why did this happen to us?
How can I think calmly now?
I'll get killed before
I can even make my movie!
You told me to be rational.
And now you're going to act like this?
I'm finished!
Please, stop!
- Huh?
- Stop.
Stop? Okay, I got it! I got it!
In my opinion...
It was most likely installed
for home security, not to spy on us.
Home security?
Remember the old butler...
the one who ran away?
He stole all of my money and jewelry.
The chairman ordered them
to reinforce home security.
So it must have been
installed pretty recently.
And I'm still alive, which means
the chairman hasn't seen it yet.
Let's go back.
What? Why... why go back?
We need to take care of that
footage before he sees it!
That's right. That's right,
that's right. Let's go!
- Is this the right place?
- Yes.
This is the only part of the house
that I have never seen before.
This is not the time to be doing that.
Okay.
Geez.
By the way, what are we looking for?
The computer that is connected
to all of the security cameras.
It must be here.
So then we just find it
and crush it, right?
You don't need to crush it.
We'll just delete it.
- Please...
- Save me!
I told you! This is not the time!
Okay.
Oh! Over there!
Over there! Isn't that it?
Oh! Okay!
What? Why isn't it turning on?
Is it broken? Huh?
Please! Please! Geez.
Hide! Hide!
Would I die if you
canceled all of my cards?
How have you been?
What?
Gold.
Dad, you cut off my money line.
I had to do this.
Do Kyung and Hyun Jee, just wait.
I checked all of the books that
Secretary Ma brought from the bars.
I found something strange
at Tae Soo's bars.
That's why I had you come.
What's strange, Sir?
Since the beginning of the year
the numbers haven't matched at all.
What's happening here?
Did Tae Soo steal the money?
No, definitely not.
He would never do that.
Then what's wrong with the numbers?
Who did this?
Actually what happened was...
Director Baek...
Tae Soo tried to stop him, but
Director Baek said he'd tell you later.
Be quiet!
You're not a smart guy.
In times like these, what you
need is politics, not honesty.
Pardon me?
I heard that you're
becoming a father soon.
How will you take care of your
family if you lose your job?
What? Eun Ok auditioned
to save her house?
The chairman said she could stay
in the house if she won Mee Mee's role.
That's why she worked so hard.
I feel bad for my sister.
Why does the chairman
hate Do Kyung so much?
That's a mystery.
If Director Baek finds out,
he'll be furious.
Keep it a secret from Do Kyung.
What is it that you need to say,
that you need to say it in private?
Is it true, about Do Kyung?
What?
About your house.
Geez, that was too much.
You guys are still friends.
Kyung Mee, can you leave us alone?
Okay, I should get out.
Speak calmly.
Did you want to kick me out
like that too?
Do Kyung...
Were you trying to make me leave
just like the chairman wanted?
I know you think it's just an excuse.
But I did that because I was afraid
to get kicked out of my house.
If you were in my shoes...
I don't care. I don't even want to know.
Aren't you the same, anyway?
You sided with Madam Oh
and tried to kick me out.
You...
You don't know why I came
back to Daejeon, do you?
It's obvious.
You wanted to get back
together with Gi Bum.
No, it was because of Hyun Jee.
Eun Ok.
Is it true?
If you are here about your father,
don't say anything. I already did.
Is that all?
I'm really disappointed.
How could you do that to a friend?
I said to not say anything!
I can't hold my anger back!
I see that you were desperate about
your house. But to do this to a friend!
- Gi Bum.
- Yes.
It was all my fault.
I regret that I accepted the chairman's
offer without thinking about it.
What? Is that an apology?
Was she always so blunt?
Don't be harsh on her.
The real problem is your father.
I knew you were making real efforts.
So I thought about getting
back together with you.
But I can not and do not want
to stand your father anymore.
Just let me go.
Don't say that. We should
focus at a time like this.
Don't you have self-pride?
Self-pride?
I lost that ten years ago.
And I endured that loss
with my competitive spirit.
But I'm not sure
I have that anymore either.
Just give up.
Do Kyung. Do Kyung! Do Kyung!
That old fart!
Boss!
What are you here, Young Il?
Geez, you smell like alcohol!
I only had one pint.
But suddenly, I missed you,
so I came.
Huh?
Did something happen?
Boss.
Sun Young is pregnant.
Really?
Congratulations!
You're going to be a father soon?
But I'm confused.
When I think about being
a father, I feel scared.
And I'm not sure how
I can be a good father.
I see.
From now on, you should only
think about your family.
That's all you need to do.
Oh, my. Congratulations!
What? Is something wrong?
Boss.
Go ahead. Tell me.
I am sorry.
I am really sorry.
Are you a human?
How can you call yourself
a human after doing that?
You destroyed any and all evidence
that exposed Gi Bum misusing the money.
Don't you know that Boss
has to take the heat now?
Yes!
I know what I did was wrong.
I know I shouldn't have
done that to Tae Soo.
But I had no choice,
when I thought about my family.
How can you say that?
You...
Do you know how hard it's been on Boss?
Who helped you get this far?
You got married thanks to Eun Ok!
How could you stab Boss in the back?
I will be a father soon.
But I have no savings.
I couldn't see my future.
It's okay. These things happen.
I told you. All you need to
think about is your family.
Boss!
And...
This isn't much.
But you should buy a cake
and some flowers for your wife.
Boss.
Here.
I have some business to attend to.
Finish up here and go home.
Mr. Chairman, I'm here.
Oh.
Finally, we seem to be in sync.
I was going to tell you to come.
But you came all on your own!
Sit down.
What are you working on so hard?
Well...
One of my dogs is acting out.
So I'm getting ready to beat him up,
to teach him a lesson.
Is it that the dog is smart,
or that the owner is stupid?
Just to get the dog,
you use his wife and his underlings.
How dare you?
There are dogs that
are better than humans.
Also, there are humans
that are worse than dogs.
- What?
- Watch your mouth.
You be quiet!
This isn't the time
for a little mouse to barge in.
Stay out.
Mr. Chairman...
Are you trying to tie me up
and choke me to death, with that?
You won't be able to do it this time.
You always said, it's about the people.
It's the people who do the work.
You said, make good connections.
You said, find flaws in them.
How dare you act so rudely like this?
I had met many people
following you around
while carrying bagfuls of money
earned from all those clubs.
National assembly members,
civil servants, prosecutors and police!
When those bastards were
greeting us with smiles...
You told me this.
"They've fallen into our traps."
But...
I thought about it the other way.
And the person in the worst position
is you, Chairman.
Tae Soo, you punk!
Compare that to the original
that you have.
As for the German tape recorder
you put in my pocket!
I'll be taking good care of it.
Don't you worry.
Why you...
Just like I learned from you...
I'm trying to survive from you!
Now, let's cut our ties completely.
I am leaving you, Mr. Chairman.
As of today, it seems
that I am no longer your dog.
Still, we share a long history together.
You don't want this to get dirty, do you?
There's nothing I want from you either.
I do have one shield
to protect my family.
And that's what I came to show you today.
Mr. Chairman.
I wish you... a long, healthy life.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[SWEET SAVAGE FAMILY]
Why are you acting like a little girl?
Do not treat me rudely anymore.
I'm trying to find something important.
Are you good at hunting a treasure?
This isn't a matter of pride.
It's about making a living!
Do you know
the chairman had you followed?
Let me go! You have a restriction order!
This is a crime!
Crime?
Who are you?
You will lose a lot.
I'm putting my life on this!
Even if that's me?
Eun Ok! Eun Ok!
Eun Ok!