Subtitles by DramaFever
[My Sweet Family]
Final Episode 16
It's so hard to get away with my fate...
of being a gangster's wife.
I was finally looking forward
to ending it after 18 years...
so that I can live a normal life.
I guess I am not lucky enough for that.
I can't stop if I go now.
I'll just have to keep going.
You think I don't know that?
Go.
Go and either save a country...
or some people.
- Honey.
- Go!
Go before I change my mind.
Wait.
What...
What happened?
Where is Chul?
His father got hurt so he
took him to the hospital.
Did he get hurt badly?
Those gangsters pushed him and he fell.
It didn't seem too serious.
We're just worried that they might
not be able to open the store.
The place is totally ruined.
By any chance,
was it the same guys that came before?
No.
They were new faces.
They must've hired professionals.
That way it won't leave any evidence...
and they'll be able to end things.
Will they come back?
Just think of this...
as a taster.
Next time, it's going to be the dry
cleaner's and the other stores.
They are going to slowly
take over the place.
So?
You want us to back off
before it gets worse?
We are tired of those lame advises.
So please leave.
No.
I came to tell you that
I will fight with you.
Well, it may not be an easy fight.
We can put ourselves into a
more dangerous situation.
Then...
how do you plan to help us?
I've been with Choongshim
for over 20 years.
I know them inside and out.
And I can clearly see what
they're thinking right now.
Isn't that a big weapon in itself?
Even if we will have a bloody fight later,
we need to first declare
a war against them...
in a gentlemanly manner.
Okay. Make sure you end things properly.
Hey.
Why do you keep coming here?
Is this your house or what?
How is it different from my house?
I worked here for 20 years...
and it's your room. We've
been friends for 25 years.
Don't I have the right to come in here?
Why are you here?
Drop the lawsuit against Manbok Shophouse.
- What?
- Drop the case and...
promise them that you will
redevelop it in a fair way.
Also, compensate them for making
the gangsters trash the snack bar.
Have you gone mad?
What's gotten into you? Did you get bribed?
That's your dirty trick.
Watch your mouth, my friend.
What if I say no?
Then you will end up in jail.
Why would you bother doing this for them?
Who do you think you are
to help someone else?
Those people are suffering because of...
Choongshim, but you and I are
equally responsibly for it.
We've done so many bad things
in the past 20 years and...
I am trying to make up for it.
I want to make an apology by doing this.
Only then will I get to live the
rest of my life without guilt.
Gosh, aren't you the hero?
Let them die like that.
You should get your life sorted out first!
You listen to me.
Being born rich doesn't give you
the right to step over the weak.
Ms Oh, why don't we go to a
hot springs this weekend?
You want to go on a trip?
But you just got out of the hospital.
It's for you.
You like going to hot springs
around this time of the year.
Don't worry about me.
You need to get better first.
Okay.
Let's go on a cruise trip in spring.
We can get on the cruise
and go all around...
the world.
Do you want to do that?
What do you mean?
You don't know what a mess our company is.
You don't even know what I
had to hear from Tae Soo.
And yet you are just so happy.
Ki Beom, don't do this.
Just think of it as a tough lesson
for you to become the president.
Do you think it's easy
to get to that position?
Right. Yes.
Have a good time, you two.
What's wrong with you?
You agreed to be nice to them.
He's with the woman who cheated on him.
How can I not get mad?
Then what if he finds out
about Ms Oh and Mr Bong...
and passes out again?
The doctor warned us, remember?
How do we know if he knows or not?
Honestly, I feel like...
Dad is just putting on a show.
So you think he's pretending
that he doesn't know anything...
when he actually knows everything?
Otherwise,
does it make sense for
him to forget just that?
Anyway,
please keep an eye on Dad.
There has to be something more.
We're eating kimchi fried rice again?
Just eat it. It's simple
and nice for breakfast.
My friends tell me that I
smell like fried kimchi.
They also tease me about my
name being on the truck!
Mum,
you added chicken breast today.
How is it?
It's more filling and more nutritious.
I'm thinking of adding it to the menu.
You should make anchovy
kimchi fried rice, too.
These days, female office workers...
lack iron because they
always go on poor diets.
I was already thinking about that.
Gosh,
my puppy and I will be fed...
only kimchi fried rice,
and we will die shouting
"kimchi fried rice".
Gosh, Mum.
By the way,
we're going to need everyone's help...
with the food truck for a while.
Especially you, Eun Shil.
Why? Are you getting another job?
No, that's not it.
I need to help someone.
I think I am going to be
busy with that for a while.
What?
How can you push aside making a living...
and help someone else?
Tae Soo,
don't tell me you stuck your nose
in someone else's business...
and caused trouble again.
What's wrong with him helping other people?
You can't live this life
alone anyway, you know?
What are you doing? Hurry up and eat.
Father,
you know that you have a doctor's
appointment tomorrow, right?
It's at 3pm.
Don't worry about it. I will go with Ms Oh.
Father,
are you having trouble
with anything else...
after your brain surgery?
Perhaps your memory has gone fuzzy.
Or you remember some new things?
Why? Are you worried that
I might have dementia?
Of course not. Why would
I be worried about that?
It's just that your doctor asked me...
to take a good care of you.
Just focus on taking care of Ki Beom.
- Pardon?
- He treats Ms Oh very badly.
You saw him yesterday.
He was so rude to her.
Yes.
I will tell him to be more carful.
You have to learn how to
control your husband.
Just think of it as practising
to become the president's wife.
Okay, Father.
- We're in trouble.
- What?
- What is it?
Attorney Park called and
said he's resigning.
- What's wrong with him?
- What?
What's the reason? Why is he
taking his hands off the case?
Choongshim people must've done this.
This is what they always do.
It's all your fault.
What do you mean?
It doesn't feel right.
Our lawyer just quit!
Ever since you got involved,
they've become more fierce.
- He's actually right.
- He's right.
I heard you betrayed Choongshim.
That's why we are going
through this hassle.
I can't trust you any more!
Did he pay you to say that?
- What?
- It sounds like...
one of Choongshim's favourite move.
What are you talking about?
Did they promise you to give you
a nice spot to open a store?
Or did they promise you to
triple your compensation?
- What is he talking about?
- What is this?
Wait. You ran into me the
day before yesterday...
when you were coming out of Choongshim.
- What?
- He went there?
He went there.
Well why did you have to
make this fight so big?
Do you think you have the
slightest chance of winning?
You're just wasting time.
Gosh.
- What's wrong with him?
- Let him be.
This is not the end.
They will visit you all of you...
and try to persuade you one by one.
If you want to win, you
really have to toughen up.
We'll lose if we fall apart.
What kind of person did you send for
Tae Soo to find out so quickly?
Tae Soo seemed like he had a hunch.
It's what we've always been doing
so it's not hard to guess anyway.
Tae Soo is always the problem.
Why did he have to get involved
in this and create this mess?
It's annoying...
to see Tae Soo act as if...
as if he represents justice.
Keep a close eye on him and
report to me if anything happens.
- Yes, Sir.
(SOO MIN'S KIMCHI FRIED RICE)
- Here you go. Enjoy.
- Come again.
- Good-bye.
It's cold. You should go home.
It's not like we have a lot of customers.
I got this.
I'm just worried that you might get bored.
Don't you like spending
quality time with your son?
Well, you should go home after an hour.
Aunt Eun Shil is coming.
Okay.
By the way, what's going on with Dad?
- What?
- You said he's helping someone.
I'm not a kid any more. Tell me.
It has something to do with
Choongshim, doesn't it?
Yes.
They are trying to redevelop
a nearby building...
and he decided to help the tenants there.
It seems like Choongshim is
giving them a hard time.
Wouldn't it be dangerous for him?
Does he have to do it?
Sung Min, your dad gave
a lot of thought to it.
He thinks he's going to regret
it if he doesn't help them out.
I don't like the idea myself,
but I decided to trust him.
So let's give him our support.
Did you talk to Choongshim by any chance?
Well, there's nothing we can do.
You're scared of the gangsters.
Gosh.
I'm worried. How can we
fight without a lawyer?
I think we contacted almost
every lawyer in this town.
How come everyone says the same thing?
Why are they so terrified of Choongshim?
They are just worried
that they will be harmed.
Gosh, cheer up.
If we can't find one here, we can
go to Seoul or Busan to find one.
I am sure we can find at least one
lawyer who's willing to help us.
Gosh.
Dad.
- Hello.
- Sung Min.
How did you come here?
Mum said you must've missed your meal.
I'm such a lucky man, aren't I?
I'll take it.
He's my son.
He's a good student and
he sings really well.
And he's sweet too.
Dad, I will go now. Mum's alone.
Okay.
Thank you and sorry.
Go now.
Good-bye.
(STOP THE REDEVELOPMENT!)
I will wait for you in front
of the terminal at 12pm.
No, don't wait for me.
I won't go there.
I will wait until you come.
I'll be there every day.
Gosh, how can she do this?
How can she not turn up...
and make me a homeless man?
Mr Bong!
Mr Bong, I'm here!
Mr Bong! I'm here!
I'm here!
Oh gosh!
You're still here?
Mr Lee!
You stink!
Now, you're not just
frustrating and pathetic.
I now pity you and you also make me mad.
What's the use of waiting for
someone who won't turn up?
Why don't you just go to
her and bring her out?
I heard both the father and son are...
searching me desperately.
They're going to kill me.
So let's leave Daejeon now.
The only way you and I can
survive is to leave this city.
Are you going to quit making films?
We went through so much.
We have to toughen up
and give it another go.
You are Mr Bong Jin Wook, right?
Run!
- Run!
- Oh, no.
Oh my gosh!
Ouch. My goodness.
You missed him?
Is it that hard to catch him?
Keep an eye on him.
Make sure he doesn't set
a foot in this area.
Completely shut him off from Ms Oh.
- Father.
- You heard it?
I... I wasn't trying to eavesdrop.
Please don't say anything to Ms Oh.
I'm doing this because I
can't live without her.
But still, how can you put on such an act?
This is wrong for everyone.
It's not just about Ki Beom,
but if Ms Oh finds out about this later,
she will be embarrassed and shocked.
But what else can I do?
If I don't do this,
I know am going to regret it later.
After I Inherit the company to Ki Beom,
my wish is to grow old...
happily with Ms Oh...
until I die.
I didn't know things
would turn out this way.
What happened between her and Mr Bong...
is something I'll never think about.
Eun Ok!
We came to visit you.
Why did you come?
I told you that you didn't have to come.
What good are friends for?
Of course we should come.
We didn't know what to get you
as a congratulatory gift,
so we got you a small heater.
Thank you.
I'm sorry about everything.
After you left One Mind,
I didn't get the chance to give you a call.
And especially after what
happened with Young Il.
Why are you talking about that here?
I told you we should talk
about it over drinks.
Right.
I'm sorry about my husband.
I heard he was quite mean to Tae Soo.
I don't know the details, but
I can assume what happened.
No.
There's no need to feel bad.
That's the life of a
gangster's wife anyway.
And I'm here working so that I can...
escape from all of that.
If you feel so bad about it,
help us promote the business.
You should buy some and share it
with your friends. It's cheap, too.
Should we? We should.
Then give me 10.
Me too. I'll take 10, too.
Okay, 20 kimchi fried
rice, coming right up.
I'll make it really delicious.
- Okay - Okay.
Give me a lot.
Give me some ham, too.
Okay, more toppings.
You used to hate the cold.
It's not like you to want to go for a walk.
Although, I'm happy to.
Do you remember?
We first met...
at a park.
Of course I remember.
It wasn't as cold, though.
It was on a warm spring day.
You were sitting on a bench reading a book.
And I went up to talk to you.
- Excuse me, are you an actress?
Life was so meaningless...
and boring.
I'd take a walk without
knowing where to go...
and I would eat only to live.
But then, that's when I saw you...
and I wondered how an actress
showed up in our neighbourhood.
Like what the kids say nowadays,
I fell for you the moment
I laid my eyes on you.
Ever since then,
you've been more than caring to me.
I'm sure...
no one else could have done it like you.
It's because you're special.
The last three years...
were full of happiness.
I'm so thankful.
Although, I feel...
more sorry than thankful.
Ms Oh.
What are you trying to say?
Remember when you asked me...
what I wanted?
You said you wanted to
do everything for me.
President.
Will you..
Just let me go?
Ms Oh.
I don't deserve your love.
If I stay here,
your relationship with
your son will be ruined.
And that'll make me feel worse.
This is not what I want.
You understand...
what I mean, right?
Well?
I really...
want to be...
remembered as a good person...
to you.
All right.
I know.
Yes, this is Tae Soo.
Who?
Attorney Kim Min Ho?
How did you...
What?
Sung Min!
Have you eaten?
Honey, that's not the problem.
Where's Sung Min?
In his room, why?
We'll talk later.
Hey.
What have you done?
- What?
- What did you say to...
persuade a great lawyer like Mr Kim?
What? He called?
- He really said he'd help?
- What are you talking about?
Sung Min talked to someone
really famous from Seoul to...
help with the Manbok Shophouse.
On top of that, he also said that
he couldn't turn down our son...
and that he won't even take money for it.
How did you do it?
Well,
should I say it's the
power of social media?
Just listening to his voice
made me feel at ease.
I feel like we've already won.
What a great news.
I should work even harder...
for you, Sung Min.
Is that really him?
Yes, right here.
He even won an award as
a human rights lawyer.
I can't believe it.
What do you think? Isn't my son great?
- He looks like a good person.
- Look. Scroll down.
A friend of the evicted...
- He helped out.
- I see.
He gave up his prosecutor
position to stand on the side...
of the weak. Attorney Kim Min Ho.
Excuse me.
What?
You're attorney Kim, right?
Yes. Are you Mr Yoon Tae Soo?
Yes, it's nice to meet you.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Nice to meet you.
You must be tired from
travelling all this way.
Not at all.
It's only an hour on the bullet train.
Well, Sir...
- you're a very handsome man.
- Thank you.
Yes.
Since we don't have much time,
let's listen to your story first.
It's a hard fight, but
not an impossible one.
You must know this already, but
collecting evidence is the key.
It's good to have as much evidence
as possible that proves...
Choongshim was disquieting
you or trying to harm you.
Evidence?
Look at this.
We took some photos.
And this is where my dad got hit.
This and...
(POOR APPRAISAL, POOR COMPENSATION)
This.
Don't you have anything else so
that they can't get out of this?
Hi, I'm Choongshim's Yoon Tae Soo.
It was your boys who were
hired yesterday to disturb...
the tenants at Manbok Shophouse, right?
What do you mean, why?
We just want to hire them one more time.
Was it your boys?
Okay, I got it.
You want me to come in for a questioning?
Why should I?
What did I do to Manbok shophouse?
What?
Tae Soo, you little...
Tae Soo! Are you crazy?
How dare you sue me?
That's why...
I told you to compensate the
owner of the snack bar.
You really want to play this game, do you?
Should I send the boys again?
Why are you screaming?
I thought you said you didn't do it.
You jerk.
Do you want to die?
Come on, who would want to die?
By the way, Ki Beom.
Do you know that all of
this is being recorded?
My gosh.
My goodness.
What's wrong with you?
You couldn't take care of this on your own?
I'm sorry, Sir!
It's my wish to never hear
those words from you.
Get out, I don't want to see you.
Sir...
I told you to get out!
You should let it all go.
I'm sure that's what Ms
Oh would want as well.
She left only with what she came in with.
All the bags, shoes and jewellery
that I bought for her...
were all left behind.
That woman...
She received a lot of your love.
It must mean that your
love was enough for her.
You're home late.
Where's your beloved Ms Oh?
Why are you all alone?
Your wish has come true. She left.
Are you happy now?
- Pardon me?
- She left early in the morning.
I don't even want to see you.
Let's try our best to avoid
each other for a little while.
I'll be happier if you don't come home.
Is it my fault that Ms Oh left?
She left because she feels guilty.
Why are you blaming it all on me?
Goodness. How rude...
Dad. Do you have any idea about
what happened to me today?
Tae Soo reported me to the
police so they interrogated me.
While you were talking about your love,
I had to go through all
kinds of crazy things.
- You were at the police station?
- Forget it.
Just continue to think about Ms Oh
and suffer through your heartache.
Did you say you were interrogated
by the police? What do you mean?
Tae Soo filed a complaint against me...
on behalf of the tenants.
Really?
Does he think he's the warrior of justice?
Why is he always getting in the
way of what Choongshim does?
He makes me so mad.
Are you doing your job properly?
Tae Soo won't do such a
thing for no good reason.
Whose side are you on?
I just got home from being
interrogated by the police.
I'm not taking his side.
I'm just worried about you and the company.
There was no problem like this
when President was in charge.
Why are these things happening as
soon as you take over the company?
Preventing trouble from the
start is important, too.
It only turned into trouble because
that jerk, Tae Soo, got involved.
My brain is about to explode
because I'm trying beyond my best!
Out of everyone, you should
try to understand me.
Anyway, I won't forgive Tae
Soo for what he's done.
- I will...
- What will you do then?
Are you going to threaten him
with his house like your father?
If not, are you going to risk
putting someone's life on the line?
Dad!
I told you this before.
If you can't make me proud, at
least don't make me embarrassed.
Do you remember me telling you this?
- Hyun Ji.
- Why are you doing this, Hyun Ji?
I want to know what kind
of person you really are.
No, I'm scared of you.
You and Sung Min's dad are friends.
How can you treat him like this?
Have you forgotten about how he saved me?
Hyun Ji, that's...
Mum. Let's move back to our old place.
As soon as possible.
I asked you...
to be a good dad at least to Hyun Ji.
Is it that difficult?
I'm not sure if reuniting with you...
was the right thing to do.
Do Kyung.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why does everyone do this to me?
Am I the only one to blame?
Why does everyone hate me so much?
The number you have dialled
cannot be reached at the moment.
Please try again later.
- Hello?
- Yes. Is this Sung Min?
I'm Hyun Ji's mum.
Yes. Hello.
Sung Min. By any chance, are
you with Hyun Ji right now?
No, I'm not.
Why are you asking?
Well, Hyun Ji hasn't come home yet.
She's not answering my calls either.
Can you call me right away...
if you hear from Hyun Ji?
Sure, I will.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
(MISSED CALLS)
Baek Hyun Ji. Are you trying
to make me worry about you?
Hyun Ji, where are you? Did
something happen to you?
I'll come and get you right now.
(YOON SUNG MIN)
What happened? Do you not know that
your parents are looking for you?
I know.
Don't look at me like that. I'm
already stressed out as it is.
What?
I'll apologise to you on my dad's behalf.
I can't list everything and I'm
sure there's more than what I know.
But I know that my dad has caused
pain for your dad and your family.
I'm sorry.
I totally understand why you've been upset.
And when you told me that you
wanted to break up with me,
I couldn't accept it because I was
angry and I couldn't believe it.
But I've pulled myself together now.
Let's break up.
- Baek Hyun Ji.
- I won't bother you any more.
Good-bye.
I didn't mean to break your heart.
I know.
And I know that you're probably
more stressed than I am, right now.
Sung Min. Promise me one thing, though.
Don't throw out the ring.
This matching scarf, too.
I'll do the same.
You can promise me this, right?
- Hyun Ji!
- Baek Hyun Ji!
You've never done anything like this!
Do you know how worried I was?
Mum. When are we moving?
Hyun Ji.
Ki Beom, you wanted to see me?
Yes, Beob Kyu!
Yes, Ki Beom.
- Beob Kyu, what am I to you?
- Pardon?
You're my boss and the
president of this company.
To me, you're like the Almighty...
- So what can you do for me?
- Pardon me?
Can you die for me?
Can you do everything I tell you to do?
I'm asking you if you can
kill a person for me.
Can you do it or not? Why
aren't you answering!
Yes. I can do it.
Good.
If that's the case, you should...
Stop it!
Boss!
What brings you here, Dad?
Are you bored because Ms Oh isn't around?
You're so dumb. You're such an idiot.
That's right! I'm dumb. I'm an idiot.
Get your hands off everything.
I'm going to take over.
I will finish this.
So you stay quiet.
How come nobody is here?
It's weird.
Nobody is answering their phones.
What?
Welcome.
Have a seat.
Take a seat.
Have a seat. Gosh. Go on and take a seat.
My apologies for introducing
myself so late.
I am Baek Man Bo, the president
of Choongshim Construction.
Sir,
- please take a seat.
- You sit first. Gosh.
Actually,
Manbok Shophouse is like my first love.
I used to go there for nearly 30 years.
It's gone now, but...
there used to be a small
dumpling place there.
I used to be a regular customer there.
Gosh, I got so nostalgic and
bored you with my story.
I let my son take charge...
and I heard he had disrespected everyone.
Why...
did you want to see us?
I hate beating around the bush.
So I will be frank.
Does anyone of you think...
you can compete with Choongshim and win?
As you know, it's like beating
your head against a brick wall.
I recalculated the compensation...
and it seems like you should be
getting twice the initial price.
I will only apply that price...
to the people who are here today.
So please promise me one thing.
Gosh.
Where have you all been?
Is something wrong?
We need to talk.
We've discussed it ourselves...
and we think it's best that you
stay out of this, Mr Yoon.
- What?
- Hey.
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
No matter how hard we think,
we have no chance to win this.
We need someone who will put out the fire,
not someone who will start one.
Don't you agree, guys?
- We agree with him.
Sir,
why are you acting like
this all of a sudden?
The same goes for you, Sir.
We want you to stay out of
this along with Mr Yoon.
Why are you doing this? You
act like a different person.
Stay out of it, Chul.
This is for the good of everyone.
If this goes wrong, you won't be
able to support your sick father.
After all, it's good for everyone.
Why should we refuse it when
they're doing us a favour?
I guess you met someone in a
high position at Choongshim?
I know what you've been told
and how you've been treated...
even without having to hear it from you.
When I first came to help
you, I told you that...
I worked at Choongshim for 20 years
and that I know it inside and out.
You all are...
getting fooled right now.
We already made a decision.
So please leave us alone.
Please.
- Yes. Please leave.
- Please leave.
- We already made the decision.
- Leave now.
What's wrong with all of you?
When they build a mall here, all the
shops on the small streets will die.
That's why we decided to protect it
on our own. Isn't that why we began?
We promised to fight until the end.
Why are you doing this now?
We didn't begin this fight for money.
I am very disappointed.
Hey, Baek Ki Beom!
Ki Beom.
- Boss!
- Look who it is!
My son, Tae Soo!
You saved me last time.
And I didn't get to thank you properly.
I am still alive like this...
because you took me to
the hospital right away.
Don't change the subject.
Do you really have to do this?
Do you really have to...
kick the tenants out of Manbok Shophouse?
Watch your mouth.
We are simply following the procedure.
Boss!
Did you think you could help them?
What did you learn from
me in the last 20 years?
I am just very frustrated, you know?
Nobody is strong in front
of money and power.
We're signing the papers tomorrow.
So you should stop and leave.
If you can't manage to go alone,
I will call people to take you home.
I am sorry.
I apologise on behalf of them.
Why would you apologise? I
should be the one to apologise.
If I hadn't done that five years
ago, this wouldn't have happened.
When I look at you, Chul,
I feel sorry and thankful at the same time.
I'm thankful that you
grew up as a strong man.
Now Manbok Shophouse is doomed, right?
The tenants already
turned their backs on us.
What do you think is going to
be Choongshim's next move?
It's to sign a memorandum.
It seemed like the leader
of the tenants group...
is most likely to sign it.
What would be the memorandum about?
Is it going to be a legal disclaimer...
which states that you
give up all your rights?
- Yes.
- My goodness.
This is like the modern version of
the Korea-Japan Treaty of 1905.
After a public hearing tomorrow,
it's going to be really the end.
I invited some journalists...
to the public hearing tomorrow.
I am going to make it official.
The leader of the tenants...
will wag his tail and bring the memorandum.
That then will be it.
Tell them to do whatever they want.
They will just make
themselves look like a fool.
Are you just too good or
am I just plain stupid?
Why would you say that?
When we build a mall,
it will run by it itself.
You will get paid for breathing!
I heard Tae Soo visited you.
Yes. He was busy going
around and wasting his time.
He's so naive.
He can never be successful.
He will always live his life
looking down at the ground.
Ki Beom.
President Baek.
You'll only have to look
at the sky from now on.
Dad.
They already discharged you?
I just got discharged a while ago.
What are you doing here?
I am...
How dare you come here?
Get out you scum!
What's wrong, Dad?
He's been helping us.
He's not a gangster now.
Get back to your senses, Chul! You
can never trust a guy like him!
What's this, Dad?
(LETTER OF CONFIRMATION)
You already signed it?
A while ago, Doo Seok came
and stamped my seal on it.
He said all the tenants...
from Manbok Shophouse decided to do it.
We got attacked twice in one day.
Chul, can I meet the leader?
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I heard you made my dad sign a memorandum.
You told me to fight instead of my dad.
And you use me to get
him to sign the paper.
You weren't like this before.
Chul.
It's not what we originally wanted,
but this is the best
decision we can make now.
This is the best decision?
Surrendering for a couple more
dollars what you call best?
You really don't know who's
getting all the benefits?
I don't want to talk to you guys.
I will go now.
Gosh.
It feels so good.
What?
You're still up?
I'm about to go to bed now.
Is the thing with Manbok
Shophouse going well, Dad?
You even got us a lawyer.
I should do better.
Is it really tough?
Not particularly.
But nothing is easy, right?
Cheer up, Dad. Okay?
- I'm going to bed now.
- Okay.
Have a good sleep.
(PUBLIC HEARING ON THE REDEVELOPMENT
PLAN FOR MANBOK SHOPHOUSE)
The president, Mr Baek Man Bo, is here.
- Yes. Hello.
- They're taking photos already?
Don't frown. These photos
will be posted on the news.
Yes! Mr Noh. Long time no see.
Mr Baek, please say a few words.
- Have you found a solution?
- Please tell us.
(BAEK KI BEOM)
Oh? He's the leader of the tenant union.
Have you been able to come to an agreement?
- What is the current situation?
- Please say a few words.
The public hearing on the
redevelopment plan for...
Manbok Shophouse will begin now.
First, Mr Baek Ki Beom
will say a few words.
We, at Choongshim Construction,
will do our very best to contribute...
to the economic growth of our region...
through redeveloping Manbok Shophouse.
President, please say a few words, too.
I know how busy all of
you are as reporters.
Thank you for making the
time to join us here today.
When it comes to redeveloping
a commercial property...
like this shophouse, the
most important thing is...
the opinion of the tenants who are
currently occupying the property.
We will respect their opinion...
and find a solution that
benefits both parties.
Now, the leader of the tenants'
union will share his thoughts.
We, the tenants of Manbok Shophouse,
are very grateful for all of...
Choongshim Construction's hard
work and consideration...
that went into actualising
this redevelopment plan.
He's lying!
We're grateful? For their
hard work and consideration?
Have you forgotten the oppressive
and unfair treatments...
Choongshim Construction has put us through?
Hey. Come with us.
Leave him alone.
- Stay out of this, Yoon Tae Soo.
- Get out of here!
Calm down. Let's have the leader
of the union finish his talk.
Let's go.
Among the total of 60 tenants,
over 90 percent wants...
the redevelopment plan to be...
- executed as soon as...
- Hey!
I really can't do this.
To be frank, I've done...
something that I shouldn't have.
The president of Choongshim
approached me with a proposal.
Thinking that I probably won't
win against them in this battle,
I sold my conscience.
I lied to the tenants and made
them to sign a memorandum.
I gave Choongshim the list of
tenants who weren't cooperating...
and ended up putting them
through severe harassments.
I am very sorry.
- What did the memorandum say?
- Why did you sign the memorandum?
Did it include any unfair provisions?
I can tell you more about it.
I'm the lawyer, Kim Min Ho.
Choongshim Construction...
made Manbok Shophouse tenants
sign this memorandum.
By signing this memorandum, the
tenants agree to not exercise...
any of their rights and will not be
able to sue the company, either.
It was made to make them
give up their rights.
It's like the modern version of
the Japan-Korea Treaty of 1905.
- Did you hear that?
- What's going on?
Goodness.
I don't know about any of this.
It looks like it needs to be investigated.
If the police wants to
investigate this matter,
I'll be more than happy to cooperate.
Last but not least, I think that...
the issue of the Manbok
Shophouse redevelopment plan...
and compensating the tenants
must go back to square one.
The plan must be executed in a
fair and transparent manner...
by a different company, not by Choongshim.
That is what we want.
Are you really not going
to regret this decision?
They'll ask you to speak at
the public hearing tomorrow.
Then you'll show them this memorandum...
and say that all tenants who signed it...
have agreed and that you want the plan...
to be executed as soon as possible, right?
And when a shopping complex
gets built right here,
they'll give you a store space...
at a high-traffic area to thank
you for your contribution.
I've seen union leaders like you
during my 20 years at Choongshim.
And a lot of them end up
avoiding to meet people.
They've betrayed everyone whom
they were once close with.
They can't even hold their
heads up and make eye contact.
Many are still living in fear.
Wrong decisions make you
pay a bigger price later.
Just like me.
Did Mr Baek Ki Beom send
gangsters to harass the tenants?
Is it really true that there's a
politician affiliated with this?
Mr Baek Man Bo. Please say a few words.
Has the entire process for
this project been transparent?
You know that you can't write your
stories based on something...
that hasn't been proven as a fact, right?
I'm just saying that...
you should write informative
stories based on facts.
As a resident of this district...
and as someone who loves Manbok Shophouse,
I will make sure to correct any mistakes...
and resolve all issues related
to this redevelopment project.
If it is necessary,
we are even willing to take
our hands off the project.
We'll make sure that all
is taken care of...
so I hope you don't write stories
that are unfavourable to us.
Mum! Mum!
- Have you heard the news?
- What news?
(CHOONGSHIM CONSTRUCTION WILL
RECONSIDER ITS PLAN TO REDEVELOP.)
I don't even want to see them in photos.
What is it about?
Their redevelopment plan is
going back to square one.
- Really?
- This means that Dad won! My dad!
Goodness. Sung Min, I'm so happy.
This is such good news.
Isn't it such great news? I'm so happy.
It's not over yet.
Going through ups and downs
is unavoidable in business.
Don't forget that the end
result is all that matters.
Start fresh again.
You have to stay focused
at times like this.
Remember what your father told you.
By the way, you're not photogenic at all.
Don't tease me. I'm not
in the mood for a joke.
Hyun Ji, is there anything
you want to say to your dad?
Dad. Next time, I hope the
article will be a better one.
And I hope you look better
in the photo next time.
Honey!
Sung Min! Soo Min! Dad is back.
- Dad!
- You did such a great job.
Yes.
My daughter is all grown up.
Good job, Dad.
I know.
It was a huge job.
It's not like you got into Harvard.
Do you know how much each one of us...
had to fill in while you were away?
Of course I know.
I'll do everything from now on.
What should I start with?
Dad.
You should give Mum a hug to start with.
Good idea.
Forget it!
It's broad daylight. It's
not romantic at all.
Is that so?
We'll leave that for the evening then.
It makes me so happy to be with my family.
Me too.
- Are you happy?
- Yes!
(FIVE YEARS LATER)
You want to open the seventh
Soo Min Food Truck?
Yes, just trust us.
This work isn't easy.
You might not be able to do it.
Come on Tae Soo, don't worry.
With my beauty and the
little one on the way,
I'm going to work really hard.
I tried to stop you, but I
guess you take after me.
What is it?
Right now?
- Honey, let's go.
- What is it?
We'll talk on our way. Eun Shil,
can you look after the truck?
Let's go, honey.
Eun Shil, look after the truck, will you?
- Okay.
- What's going on?
Mum, Dad.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Please, take a seat.
- Okay.
What is it that you want
to talk to us about?
Why are you calling us out?
We need to hear an answer from you today.
We booked our flights.
- Hyun Ji!
- You two...
We're not asking for your help.
We'll support ourselves for our education.
Why won't you let us?
- Because you're going together.
Isn't it better than for her to go alone?
I'll make sure to protect her.
It's you I don't trust.
Ki Beom.
What did our son do?
Come on, let's sit down and talk.
If this is about you going abroad again,
this is a waste of time.
All of us are against it.
Hyun Ji.
I already begged you, why do...
Eun Ok.
You should get your facts straight.
If Hyun Ji changes her mind,
will it solve everything?
- What about Sung Min?
- You must not know,
but Hyun Ji is the one who
lured Sung Min into this.
No, that's not true.
I asked her first.
That's not what you said before.
See, Eun Ok? He says he asked her first.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but we'll be leaving in
two weeks as we planned.
- What?
- Oh gosh.
There's something more important.
Before we go,
we decided to have a
small wedding with you.
- What?
Going abroad is not enough?
Now, it's marriage?
You just graduated! It's
too early to get married.
Hyun Ji, please come to your senses.
Think about who will
become your mother-in-law.
And what about you?
Eun Ok.
Compared to you,
we're rather wealthy.
Money isn't everything.
Gosh, this is crazy.
Do you really have to do this?
Can't we do this step by step?
Dad.
We already registered today
as husband and wife.
Goodness!
We'll be living together
when we go study anyway.
We decided to exchange
rings as wedding gifts.
Goodness.
Honey!
- Do Kyung! Hey!
- Gosh.
- It's okay, breathe.
- Oh, my.
What are we going to do?
- What use is it to raise kids?
- Hey.
- You little...
- My...
After finally escaping from
being a gangster's wife,
I thought there will only
be good days ahead of me.
And now, the Baek's are our in-laws.
Why can't we escape from them?
What can we do? They already
registered their marriage.
You sure seem calm after
all that's happened.
Anyway, this is the worst thing
that's happened in my life.
Just wait it out.
Your spring will come.
Let's go on a national tour...
with our food truck this spring.
We can work and travel at the
same time, what do you think?
I don't care, that doesn't
make me feel any better.
I'm just going to think that
we don't have any children.
I'll live just for Kim Eun Ok.
You only have me too, right?
Even if I'm born again,
all I want is Kim Eun Ok!
I already told you that I
don't feel the same way.
I don't mind.
As long as I have my beautiful wife,
my life is like a garden of roses.
Stop that, you're so sly.
I'm so upset.
What would you like to eat,
my lovely Eun Ok?
Seriously.
Do you want me to cook
you something delicious?
How is kimchi fried rice?
Are you crazy?
I like cheese.
Do you?
Then, fried rice with cheese!
That sounds good. We should
add that to the menu.
Then we'd have cheese with fried egg,
cheese with cutlet, cheese fried rice.
Stop that.
(THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
SWEET AND SCARY FAMILY.)
We'll become rich!
I'm hungry.
Let's go eat something delicious.
- Would you marry me?
- Absolutely.
Dear god, please let me meet...
the man of my life at today's meeting.
Is being married fun?
He wants to go to trial for our divorce.
I'm sorry, my heart is too
passionate to love only you...
for the rest of my life.
(THEIR BEGINNING WAS BRAVE.)
Seriously, just stay right there!
Why did you go in?
From now, you must only
look at me and no one else.
Keep going! Step on it!
AND IT WILL ALL END IN HAPPINESS.
I think I'll have to get remarried...
with this man.
"HAPPY ENDING ONCE AGAIN"