Subtitles by DramaFever
Swallowtail butterfly, fly!
Gi Bum, I wonder what that singer,
Kim Hong Gook, is doing these days.
I'm sure he's living well.
Hey, Sir. Who are you?
Who are you? Why are you
standing in front of my office?
- Hey, over there. Geez.
- Geez.
What the heck...
Have you been well?
Didn't you miss me?
Honey, what was that noise?
- Gi Bum!
- Ah!
What happened?
Gi Bum!
Geez! Get up!
What's wrong with them today?
- My goodness!
- How much did you drink?
- Geez.
- Go this way.
You drank too much!
Wake up, please!
No!
Go! Go!
Oh my--
See you again soon...
[Episode 10]
My goodness...
I can't believe you.
Drink this, wake up.
Okay.
"Swallowtail Butterfly"?
That's an old song.
Change up your repertoire
and stop getting wasted.
You're not young anymore.
Think about your age.
Well... Honey.
You didn't see anyone
last night, did you?
Who?
Well... that is... I mean...
Geez, never mind.
Finish what you were going to say.
- Did you see a ghost?
- Don't say that!
What? You're the one who brought it up!
Sorry. I must have been so drunk
that I was being delusional.
You must be proud.
Oh, by the way...
What did you decide about the audition?
You won't audition, right?
I'm going to submit my application today.
Are you really going to do that?
It'll be trouble,
whether you get it or not.
Why do you insist on doing it?
Honey, just know that I have
a good reason to do this.
Can't you just try to understand me?
Tell me what your reason is, then!
What's your reason for being so stubborn?
That's... I mean...
It's my dream! I want a new life!
What? Married women aren't allowed
to challenge themselves?
Anyway, I'm auditioning, no matter what.
If you can't support me,
then just don't try to ruin it.
Geez! I'm going to die
from running! Geez!
Man!
Oh, my head...
Your snoring was awful!
You have awful manners!
Eat before you leave!
Wow.
What? He slept at their house?
It looks like he got drunk
last night and called Do Kyung.
I bet that fox called him first.
He's an idiot.
I warned him so many times,
but he doesn't listen.
- Stop them all.
- Huh?
You don't get it?
Void all of his credit cards.
Come this way.
Are you treating us today?
Wait, wait!
Why are you buying us dinner?
I imposed on you guys
last night, big time.
Hyun Jee, you couldn't even sleep well
last night because of me.
You annoyed me to death!
Is there a motor running in your nose?
I'm sorry. I won't do that next time.
What is this? Who said that
there will be a next time?
I'm just saying.
What should we order?
- I already ordered.
- Ordered what?
I told them to bring out
the most expensive dishes here.
Did I do well?
Here.
You ladies, don't get your hands dirty.
You just eat.
I'll get the meat out for you.
So, how's it going with the score?
It's going okay.
By the way, if your mom gets the role,
we'll be a movie family!
A beautiful actress
and the youngest film composer!
Don't get ahead of yourself.
I'm so excited that I'm proud
even just thinking about it.
Waiter! Wine, please!
Bring the most expensive one
you have, of course.
What? The card is not working?
Well, that must be a mistake.
Please try this one then.
This one is also not working.
Why don't they work?
Please put it on this.
The total is 650,000 won.
Is he home already?
Gi Bum and I bought drinks
from the convenience store...
And then we were going to the office,
singing "Swallowtail Butterfly".
From this side...
Have you been well?
Didn't you miss me, the two of you?
- What are you doing?
- My goodness!
Why are you scared?
I'm the one who should be scared.
What's your problem?
Geez, my dad voided
all of my credit cards.
I was completely humiliated when I took
Do Kyung and Hyun Jee out to dinner.
I see... by the way.
Gi Bum... you know...
Last night, here.
Didn't you see something too?
See what?
I think...
I saw Mr. Son.
I see him every day.
What?
He shows up in my dreams every night.
I'm about to go crazy.
I've been sleeping with
my lights on, since that night.
Geez!
What? Who is here?
Mr. Yoon!
What the heck is going on?
I don't know.
I almost fainted when I saw him.
Go talk to him. You go.
Geez...
Why is a dead man still walking?
How have you been?
Ah...
Oh, Tae Soo!
What a relief!
I knew this day would come,
just like the shaman said.
Well, Mr. Son.
What's going on?
What do you mean?
I came to say hello, of course.
My mother told me
how great you were to her.
She told me to come and thank you.
Of course, it's my duty to come here
and say hello to you, Mr. Yoon.
Mr. Son, you have good manners!
Oh, you are being so kind!
You are so sweet.
Ma'am, should I give you
a piggy back ride?
No! Don't do that!
Please get on my back.
How do you like it?
I love it!
It's great! As if a dead son
came back to life!
- Come on out!
- Let's play!
Come on out! Let's play!
What's going on?
Shaman from Miari?
It's me, Lee Choon Boon.
Your son brought red ginseng for me!
I was sad when you left
like that last time.
You can sleep well from now on!
I'm so happy for you!
How long has it been since
we last sat together like this?
Oh, it was at my movie production office.
We were having some coffee.
You said, "Let's go drink more!"
This is the first time since then, right?
Oh, yes.
Well... anyway, what happened to you?
Let's get to that later.
I came here out of the blue,
not only because my mother asked me to.
I came here to say my farewells.
Farewells?
I'm sure that you have found out
what kind of person I was.
I'm in no position to be
raising my head around you.
I'm sorry for losing
all of your investment money.
What? You spent all of it?
Every penny of it?
No...
Everyone thought you were dead.
Can you please tell us
what really happened?
A person's life depends on God.
I am alive!
That's what I'm saying.
So what happened--
You... This is the first time
I've met you, right?
Yes, this is the first time
that we've met in person...
Wow...
Wow... you are really beautiful.
My mother couldn't have said enough...
about your kind heart.
She said that she wasn't jealous
about her friend's son.
But she was very jealous
about her daughter-in-law.
Oh... please...
Anyway, I am really sorry
and really thankful to both of you.
Mr. Son--
Toast! Let's toast!
Oh, that one is empty.
Please.
Drink it.
Okay... please.
Mr. Yoon.
I hope you make a great movie
and become a successful film investor.
I'll get going now.
Now? Already?
You should tell us what
really happened before you go.
Yes, tell us everything.
I have a lot to do
before I leave for good.
I am a thorough person.
So, I prepare very
thoroughly for everything.
Anyway, I owe you a lot.
Please wait!
Let me go with you.
I'll call you a taxi.
Oh my...
Geez.
- Did he leave?
- Yeah, I got him a taxi.
Geez. It feels like
a ghost is fooling us.
Was that really Mr. Son?
He's definitely not a ghost.
But he's scarier than a ghost!
How did he come back alive?
Does he know what we did to him or not?
There's no way to know,
since he wouldn't talk!
That's what I'm saying.
Wait. If you think about it,
isn't this a good thing?
Huh?
Think about it.
We thought he was dead. But he's alive!
Then, what we buried was not a dead body.
That means Gi Bum didn't kill anyone.
Isn't this a good thing for everyone?
That's true, but...
But what we did was still bad.
Of course I know that.
We can try to only do good things
from now on, to repent for our sins.
I'm definitely happy about this,
in terms of our kids.
I was so scared that we would
ruin their lives by being criminals.
Geez, what the heck is going on?
K, it's time for me to let you go.
What do you mean, Nana?
I think the boss has found out about us.
You could die without anyone knowing.
If you left, I would be like
a dead man anyway.
No matter what, I will never leave you--
Not this. Not this.
This part is not realistic at all.
Huh?
His life is at risk.
He can't just be all about
romance in this situation.
As a human, he has to go
through emotional struggles!
This is how people act
when they are in love!
And that's K's real charm.
Just like you and me.
You're a piece of garbage!
Why do you make it so hard on me?
Please save me!
I don't deserve to live!
Oh. Mr. Chairman, you're here.
Go on, go on! Wow!
I was just going to leave
this here and rush out.
But it was so fun to watch.
Mr. Chairman, I have a favor to ask.
What is it? Tell me, tell me.
When you barge in like that
while we're focused on the scene
it makes Director Bong a little upset.
Is that true, Director Bong?
Well... it's not that... but yes.
I'm sorry, Director Bong.
I won't barge in like that anymore.
I'll head out to the orchard.
Then the house will be really quiet.
So don't worry, okay?
Thank you.
Why did you use me for your excuse?
I did that because you're so scared
of the chairman! You're so nervous!
Let's get into the story. Relax, okay?
What? Mr. Son came to see you?
That's nonsense.
He even brought red ginseng for my mom,
and he gave her a piggyback ride too!
Are you being haunted by
a ghost or something?
You're rambling nonsense.
Director Baek Gi Bum.
Long time, no see.
That feels good.
Nice!
I feel rejuvenated!
You... you are...
If you are a human, stay!
If you are a ghost, get lost!
I am a human.
Get lost! Get lost!
What are you doing?
You're waving dust in my face.
Mr. Yoon...
I saw you yesterday.
Now I see you again.
We run into each other quite often.
Mr. Son... why are you here?
I have something to resolve
with the owner of this room.
Huh?
Isn't that right, Director Baek?
This is bullshit. You are dead!
Yes, you are right.
I returned, alive,
from the gates of Hell.
I ran through the death hills
and crossed the Jordan River.
I walked through the narrow tracks.
And finally I stood in front of
the King of the Underworld!
Ah!
I felt so wronged.
So I said
"Oh, King of the Underworld!"
"I can't die like this!"
And then he told me to bring to him,
the most wicked man in the world.
Are you talking about... me?
Director Baek! This is Officer Seo.
I'm going to come in.
I said, freeze!
Is that what you're doing?
Why were you standing like that?
What brings you here, Bro?
Oh! Well...
We heard that Mr. Son
appeared in Daejeon.
Someone saw him going into this building.
So I stopped by Tae Soo's office,
and then I came here.
Have you seen Mr. Son?
- Huh?
- Huh? We have no idea.
Since he contacted you,
you should wait for him.
Why are you running around
impatiently, looking for him?
Running around impatiently?
I bear the lightest responsibility
among my peers.
The other guys are now higher ranks
and shoulder a fair burden.
Whereas the lightest wind
could carry me away.
My nickname is Cotton.
My peers are moving up the ranks
at the speed of a bullet train.
But I'm on the slowest train.
Stopping at every station...
taking forever to get anywhere.
My life is like a slow motion picture.
That's why I'm impatient.
I want to catch him
so I can be promoted!
What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Are you hiding something?
- Ha!
Ha.
- Hiding what?
- Hiding?
You're talking nonsense.
You guys look extremely
nervous right now.
What is it?
Hey, the chairman is about to be here.
You should leave before
he sees you and gets upset.
- He's coming here?
- Yes.
- Then I should go.
- Yeah!
Geez, why are you so
obsessed with Mr. Son?
There are so many criminals in the world.
He was going to turn himself in
and tell me who tried to kill him.
He said that there was evidence.
Kill two birds with one stone!
Buy one, get one free.
Just wait and see.
Everything will be revealed soon enough!
Go! Get home safely!
Geez!
Bastard!
What? You want to kill me again?
Go ahead.
You think I came into
a tiger's den without a plan?
I didn't kill you. You tripped
on your own and killed yourself!
Please.
Who drove me to that point? Huh?
Oh, I should ask that detective.
Officer?
What is it that you want from me?
Sir?
One billion won.
What?
You blew my three billion won!
He should be still close. Officer!
Why are you doing this?
Do you really have to do this?
You gangsters.
You can't do anything for a man
who came back from the dead?
What will happen if I tell
the police everything?
You will rot in prison!
You'll get even heavier punishment
because you're gangsters!
First, you should thank me for
coming back alive, bastards!
Did you forget that I am
your high school senior?
Attention.
Let's talk about our business.
If you give me that money,
I will disappear quietly.
I don't like drama.
I enjoy meditating.
I listen to classical music a lot.
Anyway, Mr. Yoon,
you're involved in this too.
So you should guide him well, so that
he doesn't think of anything foolish.
Okay.
Get it done by tomorrow.
By tomorrow.
What? Really?
Thank you! I love you!
You are the best director in Korea!
I'll never forget what
you've done for me!
Wow! Listen!
Director William said he would
be a judge for the audition!
Really? Really?
Oh, my!
Everyone looked down on our movie
because it's being funded by a gang!
But this will bring so many actors!
High-quality actors!
That's right! High-quality!
What are you doing right now?
What are you doing?
What? They say joy is halved
when you share it.
- You mean doubled?
- That's about the same.
Big news!
Will... Will... Will...
What's wrong?
Director William is coming!
What do you mean?
Director William is going to be a special
guest judge for the upcoming audition.
William? Who's that?
You know, the man who directed
"Kind Ms. Taeng Ja".
And "Gold Boy".
- Director An Byuk Nam.
- Really? That's him?
He's going to Hollywood and will
become famous internationally.
So he needs an English name.
The name, An Byuk Nam,
isn't very Hollywood.
I heard that he's handsome,
and he has good manners.
He's even a great singer!
It'll be an honor to just audition.
How could people like us ever stand
in front of Director William?
Madam Oh! No, I mean Writer Oh.
Writer Oh.
Thank you so much.
It's my honor!
I was going to break the news later.
Anyway, you should prepare well
for your auditions, okay?
Everyone, give her a round of applause!
Excuse me.
This is on the house.
What's up with you?
As you can see, I'm working.
Are you working part-time?
Yes, I am.
Don't tell my mom.
Sung Min, you're here.
Hello.
I heard you guys are
making music for a movie.
I'm planning on having
a small holiday concert here.
Do you want to join in?
Holiday concert?
I haven't finished arranging this yet.
You should hurry up.
Ma'am, he's already excited.
He'll do it.
I look forward to it.
Hey! Why do you always drop bombs on me?
Last time it was a film score,
now it's a holiday concert?
What's next?
Go on a date?
I just spent a half of our monthly
living expenses because of you!
A first impression is really important.
How can you audition when
you have no decent clothes?
I'll totally transform you! Wait and see.
Sister, sister! We forgot
to buy this. Eye shadow!
- Eye shadow?
- Yes.
I said I would use what I have.
Your eyes need to pop!
Good eye shadow is a must!
This color is perfect for you.
Well, use what you
already have. You're poor.
Yes, let's get going.
Sung Min should be home soon.
Hurry up!
I'm out of breath.
What's up with that hand?
What is it? We even kissed!
Stop talking nonsense.
About earlier...
Because my mom was there,
I was trying to not get caught.
You...
Do you know what
the next step on a date is?
What is it?
You have to show me
something amazing and wonderful.
I look forward to your
Christmas gift for me.
Oh, what should we do next?
Hey, wait for me.
I just received the list
of audition applicants.
Many members of One Heart applied.
I won't be greedy.
I applied for a very small role.
I know myself, so I didn't even try.
Then you should usher people
on the day of the audition, Sun Young.
Yes, Ma'am.
Everyone here was aware of her own
capabilities and made wise choices.
Except for one.
She has no acting experience.
But she aimed very high!
There are no qualifications required.
It's true I'm auditioning for Mee Mee.
If I'm good, I'll get it.
If I'm bad, I won't get it.
I don't even know why I have
to defend myself about this.
That's just it. You feel the need to be
defensive because something isn't right.
Well, for example...
Your intention of taking advantage
of your husband's position?
Take advantage of my husband?
I have no intention of doing that.
I just want to play fairly--
The chairman said this.
No outside influences on casting.
Keep it fair and square.
That's how this movie can succeed.
And that's what he wants.
But you are going against
his grand vision.
You are a housekeeper
with no acting experience.
Simply relying on your husband,
you applied for a major supporting role.
Does that make sense?
Lady! How can you say that?
Hey!
My sister won a lot of awards
for acting back in her school days.
And she was always a star
in Christmas plays at church!
And she has good looks.
She has a clear loud voice!
She's not like what you think, lady!
And she's not a selfish woman
who takes advantage of her husband!
Hey, are you crazy?
This lady pissed me off!
Ma'am, are you okay?
- Oh, no!
- Oh!
Come with me!
Get out!
Don't live your life like that!
Come with me!
Wait! What was that just now?
Have I just been terrorized?
Do you have any sedatives?
Call 911!
Sis... are you upset?
Sis...
Are you crazy?
How dare you speak to her that way?
How could I, your sister, just watch
you being treated that way?
What's wrong with you?
Who is that fox? Why can't
you say one word back to her?
She's the chairman's woman.
What?
She's also the screenwriter,
and a judge for the audition.
Do you think I'm doing this
because I want to be in a movie?
Our house depends on it.
We could lose the house because of you!
What? What does that mean?
Never mind. You didn't hear anything.
What is it? Just tell me.
I said never mind!
I should ask Tae Soo.
Hey!
Don't even think about it.
So you should tell me.
Geez.
You know the chairman owns this house.
And you know he hates Do Kyung.
He said he would give us the house
if I beat Do Kyung and get the role.
Really?
Tae Soo doesn't know.
You must not tell him!
We have no time to kill. Let's go.
Where?
I know an amazing acting coach.
I arranged a lesson for me,
but you take it.
From now on, I'll help you.
- Geez.
- Let's go.
Where are you going? Hey, hey!
My goodness.
Are you feeling better now?
That was so awful...
I guess I got worked up
because I felt humiliated.
That's what I'm saying.
I was totally baffled.
Why did she bring her sister here?
It's better this way.
Because of today's occurrence,
I'm more convinced of my idea than ever.
What do you mean by that?
Mee Mee, the cafe owner,
is a spirited, mysterious character.
A blatant, rude tiring woman like Eun Ok
can't be an inspiration of my writing!
Do Kyung.
For the sake of our movie,
please win Mee Mee's role.
You know, Do Kyung...
I adore you, not only as an actress,
but as someone on my side.
And I totally support you.
To be honest, I am a bit confused.
You're such an amazing supporter of mine.
But the chairman is trying
to cut me off from Gi Bum.
He even voided all of his credit cards.
He voided Director Baek's credit cards?
He treated me to an expensive dinner
but I ended up paying for it!
Oh, my!
Gi Bum is trying so hard to
get back together with me.
I'm not know if I can
endure this for much longer.
There are people who are incapable.
There are people who are careless.
There are people who make mistakes.
There are people like that.
But my people can't be like that.
Why did you lie?
Pardon me?
You said you have no acting experience.
That's the truth.
I don't usually praise people.
But I can't help
but praise you, Kim Eun Ok.
You are really amazing.
I swear, on my name, that you
can go to Hollywood right now.
Sister!
He said I'm good!
Did you order a taxi?
Yes, I called you last night
from my house too.
Do you remember me?
Yes, I do remember your face.
Then, please take me where you
dropped off my guest last night.
Well, Attorney Kim?
The stocks and the land are in my name.
But why can't I sell them?
It can't be done unless
the chairman allows it.
I'm sure there's a way.
Attorney Kim.
You've worked for my father so far,
but soon you'll be working for me.
Try to be flexible.
Then... should I talk to the chairman?
Forget it, forget it.
What was so urgent, that you
wanted to see me right away?
Madam Oh, please sit down first.
Would you like some tea?
No, thank you.
I have been thinking...
It's time for you
and my father to get married.
Surely, and definitely!
You're a capricious man.
I'm not sure whether I should
take your words literally or not.
Of course you should.
If you help me this time around,
I'll make that happen right away.
What is it?
Get me one billion won.
Do you need that kind of money
because your cards were canceled?
How do you know that?
I heard that from Do Kyung.
We're pretty close like that.
Perhaps... you're planning on
moving into your own place?
Don't ask too many questions.
Just do something about my father.
If he doesn't let his own son
touch his money, then how can I?
If I were legally married to him,
this could be really easy.
I wish I could help you, but I can't.
Hi, Tae Soo.
What?
Oh, Tae Soo.
I felt unsure, so I did some digging.
Look what I found.
It seems like he came back
with a deliberate purpose.
What the heck is he?
He's a swindler and a gambler.
He's no Average Joe.
Geez!
We should have taken
care of him yesterday!
Who is this?
Hey, you gangster bastards!
Why did you break into my room?
What the heck are you up to?
Where are you?
Where am I?
I'm inside your heart.
What?
I was going to leave with
the money, nice and quiet.
But you're making it difficult for me.
Double double.
- What?
- You don't know double double?
I want twice as much.
If you don't send me
two billion won by tomorrow
I'll send those pictures to Lee Do Kyung.
Via a quick delivery service!
No! You can't do that!
I don't want to do that either.
So don't overreact.
You should get back
together with her soon.
Think about your daughter.
Anyway, enough of that.
Put Mr. Yoon on the phone.
Well... Mr. Son.
Do you really have to do this?
Tae Soo, I know you're totally broke.
So you should talk to Gi Bum,
and you guys should work as a team.
Finish it quickly and cleanly, okay?
Oh, my phone is about to die!
It's shutting off!
My Bal Gwang High alumni, go, go!
Geez!
Bastard! Crazy bastard!
Really? You got praised for your acting?
It's true.
He's really picky and particular.
But he praised her after her first scene!
She really has potential!
Really? Am I supposed to believe that?
I said it's true!
Are you sure he isn't full of hot air
and fooling your family?
Don't think that way, Ma'am.
Imagine that your daughter-in-law
was an actress.
More money and new cosmetics for you!
That would be wonderful!
Really?
Then could we have
drumsticks every night?
That's not all.
You said your friends were jealous
of your dad being a movie investor.
Imagine your mom was an actress.
Mom... becomes an actress?
[Korea's actress, Kim Eun Ok,
goes to Cannes.]
This is for you.
Ta-da.
What is it?
Taffy?
Yes, so you can score the audition!
I wanted to get you a rice cake,
but I have no money.
If you become an actress,
give me lots of money, please!
Lady, just eat the taffy and shut up.
From now on, I'll take care of the house!
You just focus on acting!
Mother, I haven't been picked yet.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
It's time to give a massage
to our actress, Kim Eun Ok!
Don't call me that yet.
I'm embarrassed.
What's wrong with it?
I'm calling you that from now on.
Get used to it.
That's right! Actress Kim!
- Actress Mom!
Yes, Actress Kim!
Don't say that!
You're making me blush.
I'm shy.
I don't even have 20,000 won.
But two billion won? Geez!
I thought about it. This isn't
something he can do by himself.
There is something else.
He said he has the
"King of the Underworld" on his side.
Stop messing around.
It's all your fault.
You are the one who
proposed the movie business.
That doesn't matter now.
Could it be...
He already sent the pictures to Do Kyung?
Do Kyung, it's me.
Is everything okay?
Yes, everything's fine.
Okay. If anything happens,
call me right away.
Okay. I'm busy now. Hang up.
Good luck with your audition.
Thanks.
Well... how was my acting?
I don't usually praise people.
But I can't help
but praise you, Lee Do Kyung.
You are really amazing!
I swear, on my name, that you
can go to Hollywood right now.
You're much better than I am.
How so?
You know what...
I couldn't wish my wife
good luck with her audition.
You don't need to say that when you
live with her. She must already know.
Is that so?
Why do you guys look so down?
You scared me! Geez!
Don't ask me what brought me here.
I'm a regular here.
Then go over there and drink.
I came alone. Can I join you guys?
It's on me.
What's gotten into you?
What? I can buy you drinks too.
Judging by the look on your face,
there must be a problem.
Drink over there, will you?
I know. Sometimes, in life,
unexplainable things happen.
Geez, it's so hard to live in this world.
That's what I'm saying.
But what can you do?
That's how people live.
Life is like that. When you're
unlucky, nothing works out.
Things only get worse.
Excuse me! Please make way!
Please get out of the way!
Please, no photography! No pictures!
Have they never seen
a celebrity? So tacky.
No pictures! Give me that camera!
Oh my goodness!
Are you the Kyung Mee that I know?
The Kyung Mee you know died yesterday.
Please cheer on the new Kyung Mee!
Manager Chang, let's go.
Yes, Ma'am.
Can you see well?
Yes!
Get out of the way! You!
No pictures! Get out of the way!
Did she pour hot sauce all over her?
What's all that?
By the way, Honey.
Why aren't Mr. Yoon
and Mr. Baek here yet?
They made all of you do the dirty work.
They said that they were
going somewhere on business.
They're really busy these days.
Oh!
You're crazy!
Welcome to the open audition
for The Man Of Two Faces
the very first film by
Choong Shim Pictures.
First, let me introduce
our special guest judges.
Korea's pride! Asia's star, who has
been discovered by Hollywood as well!
Please welcome Director William!
Welcome him with a round of applause.
Byuk Nam! Bro!
Thank you! I love you.
My baby, baby. Baby. Baby.
What's with the hair and the clothes?
Excuse me. I'm Oh Joo Ran,
the screenwriter.
Do you want one? She's funny.
Let's get started.
I'm not sober yet.
Applicants in Group One,
please come forward.
Why did you put a hold on my properties?
Call Attorney Kim, please?
Dad, please! Please?
Why do you need one billion won?
It's not easy to find
investors for the movie.
The money we have now
can afford us one actor.
The audition has begun.
We need more fuel, now! More fuel!
Tae Soo is the new captain.
Whatever it is, you stay out of it.
I know you're doing this
because of Do Kyung.
No matter what,
I won't back down on that.
You fox!
You are the disaster in my life!
That was a disaster.
You're a tsunami and a nuclear bomb!
Yes, you are.
I'll reveal your dirtiest secrets!
I'll crush you before you can do that!
All I can hear is your beating heart.
All I can see is your lips...
That was the man's line.
I'll do it again.
Pass.
What just happened?
Does anyone have any special talents?
- Me!
- You.
Oh, Gi Bum! How did it go?
He won't budge. He's determined
to control my life with his money.
Geez.
It's already 2 p.m.
Wow, it's like he's psychic.
[Mr. Son]
Hello, Mr. Son?
Hello, Mr. Golden Spoon!
I just checked my bank account.
Are you going to stab me
in the back like this?
Mr. Son, that is--
Never mind.
Give me the number for
the quick delivery service.
I'll send some pictures to Lee Do Kyung.
You bastard!
Mr. Son, this is Yoon Tae Soo.
Oh, Mr. Yoon... geez.
I told you to work with him as a team.
I'm disappointed.
Well, it's too early
for you to be disappointed.
I have the money, all in cash.
All of it? In cash?
All in cash?
Yes, we borrowed it from a loan shark.
It won't look good if we deposit it
into a bank account.
That's why we couldn't
send the money yet.
Wow, I totally misjudged you.
You are so bad at lying.
Do you really think I believe that?
Well, since you're a filmmaker...
You should find out like
you would in a movie.
Where should I leave the bag of money?
This concludes the first round.
We have two candidates competing
for the role of cafe owner, Mee Mee.
The next round is scene number 74--
That's enough.
I'm sure they've practiced hard.
They'll be good, of course.
Okay... why don't you try...
Try to make me laugh.
Are you going to do it?
Are you shy?
In my opinion...
Actors must know how to appeal
to people in any given situation.
Director! Look at me!
It's raining cats and dogs!
Wow, that's a lot.
Batman!
Young Gu is here!
La-la-la.
"Dashing through the snow,
in a one-horse open sleigh."
"Over the hills we go,
or not? Go or not?"
I don't know!
"Did you season bean sprouts?"
Soo ri... Soo ri...
Isn't it fun?
Isn't it funny?
Aren't I funny?
Excuse me.
Bravo! Bravo!
Bravo!
In this awkward situation, you put
in everything, and you did your best!
They are amazing actresses! Bravo!
This is annoying. I'm torn. I'm torn!
What do you think?
- I'm torn too.
- I know.
I don't feel that way at all!
From the beginning, I knew which
one would be perfect for Mee Mee!
Right there, the one
who did the "Soo ri Soo ri" line.
Can we really do this?
What if Mr. Son finds out
that that's an empty bag--
We are standing on the edge of a cliff.
We can't just let him dupe us.
Whatever comes out of this,
we have to meet him.
Do you have a plan?
Just wing it.
I'm going crazy here.
Anyway, why did he ask us
to come to a place like this?
Let's wait calmly.
What's wrong with the water?
Water is water.
We'll move on to the next round,
which is situational acting.
I will give you a scenario.
Two women are fighting over a man.
He's Lee Do Kyung's man,
and Kim Eun Ok is interested in him.
Lee Do Kyung feels
betrayed by her friend.
That's the scenario.
Is he a movie director
or a fortune teller?
Crazy...
That's a bit of a cliche.
But life is kind of like that.
So give it a try.
Get in the mood.
Go.
How could you do that to me?
He was my man!
You're the one balancing two men.
A diamond or a pure heart?
Whatever it is, just make your choice!
Whoever I choose,
I won't let you have him!
What a fox.
You're making that man miserable.
That's what you want to think.
That way you can steal him from me!
You're using him
for the way that he loves.
No, he loves me!
Love can change.
Wow! Wow!
That was so real!
That gave me goosebumps.
Their acting was neither excessive,
nor was it lacking.
That was good acting.
Lee Do Kyung, you are full of energy.
Thank you.
You felt it, right?
Yes, I got an idea of it.
- What about you?
- I did too.
Let's move on to the final round.
Huh?
What's going on here?
Geez!
Who did this?
Geez.
Huh?
What the heck?
Mr. Son?
You're asking because you don't know?
Look here.
Man...
The two of you, keep me company
on my way to the Underworld.
Mr. Son, please don't do this.
Let's talk. Talk!
Talk?
Talking is good.
All in cash?
Is this cash? Huh?
Cash? Is this cash? Huh?
You're trying to swindle a swindler?
My father will never leave you alone
if he finds out that you kidnapped me!
You dare touch me?
How scary.
Ouch.
Hurts?
- Hurts?
- Ouch!
I touched you, so now what?
I'm just repaying you
for what you did to me.
Let's go.
Untie it.
It's loose!
- Come on!
- Wow.
Come on!
You!
Hey.
Let me do it.
Geez.
Stay away.
Okay, okay.
Why I ought to...
Tae Soo, are you okay?
Huh? Oh!
Over here! Over here!
Save us!
Don't move!
I have real bullets in my gun.
Thank you for coming, Bro!
I texted him earlier.
I told him to come.
You did a good job, Tae Soo!
Are you okay, Tae Soo?
Yes, Bro!
How about you, Director Baek?
I'm fine!
What have you done so far?
They're saying they're fine.
Are you going to stay up all night?
- Huh?
I feel so bad,
I can't be rough with them.
Bro!
What the heck are you doing?
You're a policeman!
Officer Seo!
I told you yesterday,
when I bought you a farewell drink.
Life is all about making it,
or not making it.
And if you don't make it,
things only gets worse.
Bro!
Subtitles by DramaFever