Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 5]
What do we do now?
Just stay focused.
We sink or swim!
Should we spray water over him?
He's possessed.
How about a cross, or garlic?
Do you have anything like that?
It's useless!
It's best to just knock him out!
Ah...
It's here...
Here... here!
It's here?
It's here!
Right here!
Huh?
Something is here!
Looks like something is here.
Take it out.
Be careful.
These are sandbags.
- Did... did you move it?
- Why would I do that?
What?
Then where the heck did it go?
Oh no...
My poor child...
Look at me.
Who are you?
Where am I?
Se Woon!
I'm your mom!
Are you crazy?
You're not my mom.
Go away!
Gi Bum, are you okay?
Are you back, Gi Bum?
- Tae Soo...
- Yeah?
Why am I here? Why am I...
Gi Bum!
I was possessed by Mr. Son's ghost?
Don't even get me started.
I still have goosebumps.
So what happened?
Did it come out?
If it had come out,
you and I wouldn't be here now.
Then where did it go?
You and I fixed it on the stormy night.
Geez, lower your voice.
You scared me!
What is it that you have
to discuss so quietly?
By the way,
what brings you here, Officer Seo?
The Shaman of Miari stirred up a big
commotion at the police station.
I'm in charge of that case, you know.
I heard you were at the shamanic ritual.
I need to ask you a few things.
What is it?
You know the other night,
we had thunder and lightning...
Well, I guess
something happened that night.
What do you mean?
Someone reported something to the police.
Someone saw a guy in a raincoat
going somewhere with a shovel.
Perhaps...
You guys...
What the heck are you doing?
Mr. Chairman...
How can you do this to patients?
What station are you at?
What's your name?
Go catch North Korean spies.
Don't ever come back!
What an idiot.
Are you trying to disgrace
your family name?
You always do the dumbest things!
Because I'm a dummy.
I ordered herbal tonic.
You need to restore your energy.
Let's have dinner together later.
Bring your wife with you.
Pardon?
We have good meat!
And I have something to say to you.
I got it wrong because
my prayers were lacking.
But I'll find my son, no matter what.
Se Woon, please wait for me.
Mommy won't give up!
Of course you won't.
Don't ever give up.
Mother, didn't you say
your train comes at five?
Is it already five?
Let's get up.
You said a rich client was coming.
Thank you for helping me as if
it were your own business.
I'll find my son and come back
to see you again.
Ma'am, please don't worry.
You'll find your son.
Of course! You will find him.
- Take care. Bye.
- Okay. Thanks.
I don't think Mr. Son is alive.
What does it mean to be possessed?
It means you are possessed by a spirit.
Mr. Son's wandering spirit...
Director Baek's...
Ah!
Oh my...
His spirit went into him.
My goodness...
But listen.
Why is it that Mr. Son's spirit
possessed Director Baek, of all people?
That part really bothers me.
All of you saw it.
Mother...
I'm in here, Mother...
Oh... Mother...
Stop it! You're making everyone scared!
Don't go overboard!
Geez! You're the one going overboard.
Why did you slap the possessed man?
For a moment,
I thought you were an exorcist.
It wasn't a mistake...
Wake up, Gi Bum!
You're not Mr. Son!
I did that for Gi Bum--
I thought it was too much.
I know they're friends,
but he's still your husband's boss.
You have manners.
You should apologize to him.
Hyun Jee would be upset
if she heard about it.
He's still her father.
Hi, Honey.
Mr. Chairman invited us to dinner?
He doesn't need to do that.
His hands are so full at the moment.
Okay. I won't be late.
Wow, Eun Ok.
Mr. Chairman really treats you
like his own daughter in-law.
He's a bit harsh on Do Kyung, you know.
He's not being harsh.
He just ignores me.
I'm leaving.
She's being jealous.
And she just sided with Director Baek.
I bet it must be
pretty upsetting and disturbing.
It's her ex-husband who
was possessed. Mother...
I said stop it!
Geez!
Please!
Stop it!
Why do you keep doing that?
Don't do that!
- You scared me!
- Be quiet!
Oh my--
Don't be scared. It's me.
What are you so scared?
I thought you were at the hospital.
I left. It's not like I'm sick.
You saw it all, right?
Yes. It was a bit scary.
Geez.
It's hard to impress you anyway.
But that was awful for you to see.
Please don't tell Hyun Jee.
I came to say that.
Does your father know what happened?
He called me dummy... idiot.. Oh, man!
How much longer will you live like that?
You're over 40, and you have a daughter.
Why are you so intimidated
by your father?
You don't even have the power to
protect me and your daughter.
Do Kyung, I--
You said you wanted to impress us, right?
Then do that with your actions.
Okay... Try it.
It's going to melt in your mouth.
You said you have something to say.
That shaman was powerful...
How did she find out the location?
Thank goodness! The body wasn't there.
But where on earth did it go?
If it shows up somewhere,
you'll be in big trouble.
It's a good thing that it disappeared!
That's why we are eating meat now!
Please talk about something else.
Huh? Okay, okay, I got it.
Tae Soo, how is it going with the movie?
Is there anything I can help with?
Oh... there's nothing.
Can you put it in writing?
What are you doing?
What?
I heard that you promised to
help him with the movie.
If we have something in writing
it'll make us feel much better.
Special tea is here.
Wow.
What's going on?
Are you discussing a secret?
No, no.
I was waiting for our drinks.
Is today a special day?
You've never done this for anyone.
Does it have to be a special day?
My son is worth more than this drink!
Oh... your son?
Mr. Chairman... I mean, Father.
Then I trust that you'll grant my wish.
Please let me pour for you.
Huh?
I'll be sad if you drink alone.
Love shot!
What are you doing?
What? She's being nice!
- Love shot.
Oh, Director Baek!
Director Baek.
Wow, did I just spoil the mood?
What's the meat party for?
You shouldn't drink, for your health.
You haven't learned anything?
Either way, I'm never in my right mind.
Gi Bum, don't say that.
Come join us.
You eat it all.
The uninvited guest will leave you alone.
Leave you alone...
Geez.
Please leave me alone!
How old are you?
Why do you always do
the opposite of what I say?
Do it... don't do it.
You can do it... you can't...
Am I a kindergartner?
I'm over 40 now.
What are you trying to do with me?
Do you really acknowledge me
as the CEO of Choong Shin Construction?
Tae Soo says he's jealous of me.
But I'm jealous of him to death.
It's hard for him to support his family,
but he owns his life.
But what about me?
Am I living my life or your life?
Am I your enemy's son?
Did you keep me to torture me?
Don't act up just because you're drunk!
You didn't even let me
be there when Mom died.
You didn't let me cry,
because I'm a man.
Because of you... my eyes don't tear up,
even when I yawn.
That wasn't enough for you.
You kicked out my wife and daughter!
But you're so good
to someone else's wife.
Honey... where on earth did it go?
I can't sleep when I think about it.
This is why you can't live well
when you commit sin.
If it weren't for Soo Min
and Sung Min, I would...
Geez, why are you
saying things like that?
Honey, I can't just go home like this.
Mr. Son, please go to a nice place.
We wish you happiness in heaven.
I am so sorry.
I'm sorry.
My wife has done nothing wrong.
It's all my fault.
If you have to punish someone,
please punish me.
Why do you say that?
It's not true. I'm a sinner too.
I'll make a good movie.
And I'll dedicate it to you.
That's all I can do.
Please forgive me.
No, please don't forgive us.
It's true.
Don't forgive us.
I am sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- I am sorry.
Wow, your head is always bright.
Welcome, Brother.
Well, you didn't need to bring anything.
You must be feeling okay.
You're exercising.
Of course! I'm going home tomorrow.
My body is all well now.
Well...
I understand that
Mr. Chairman doesn't like me.
But I'm disappointed that he never
even came to see me at the hospital.
Geez. Is that why you told me to come?
Is Tae Soo doing well?
It's too bad that he is doing well.
Do you know how I got through it,
being at the hospital?
"What should I do with Tae Soo?
Chew him up? Fry him up? Bake him up?"
Those thoughts kept me going.
So... what's your conclusion?
My conclusion is...
I will eat him up, no matter what.
I will eat him up without failing.
I will absolutely...eat him up.
How do you like this room?
I want to hand it over to
Yoon Tae Soon when I leave.
Oh, man.
Mr. Cho has become a real man now.
Right?
You definitely understand me.
Oh, my son! Sit down.
What brings you here at this hour?
I know you're busy,
so I prepared this for you.
Investment Confirmation...
Well, you promised my wife.
Huh?
Oh...
You're really prepared.
I consulted with other
filmmakers and a lawyer.
You really hate being sloppy.
That's right. Good job.
It's good to be thorough.
I already got my stamp out
for Secretary Ma.
Did you take care of him?
Yes. I put him in the river.
A policeman is digging into it.
You better watch them.
Yes, Sir.
What should I do with Yoon Tae Soo?
I guess I'm not good at farming.
I thought I was taking care of my field.
But shoots are still coming up.
Should I call Cheongjoo?
What is your wife like?
Well... she's pretty innocent.
She has an amazing body.
How about this one?
It's easy to wash and practical.
Are those for Eun Ok?
Yeah...
You buy your wife underwear?
You're a good husband.
I'm not, really.
Did you see Gi Bum?
Yeah.
Eun Ok wears an A-cup.
That's too big for her.
Since you're buying for them her,
go a little wild.
As they get older,
women like more colorful underwear.
I'll get this one.
Where is he?
Okay, to the left.
Keep going.
Keep going...
And stop.
Take a deep breath.
Tada!
Honey, what on earth--
Don't say a word.
Tada!
What is this?
One billion won?
I thought the chairman might
not do it... but he signed!
Honey!
Yoon Tae Soo, your husband,
is no scarecrow.
After all of these years,
you don't know that?
Geez, you're finally living up to
your good looks?
You're way too handsome.
Oh... I forgot something
really important.
Well, please come this way, Madam.
Come over here.
- What is it?
- Sit here.
What is this?
Open it, and then you'll know.
Oh, my!
Oh, my! Wow! What is this?
Only three women in Korea
can handle that one.
Kim Tae Hee, Jeon Jee Hyun,
and Kim Eun Ok!
My goodness!
People might speak badly of me!
It's so pretty! How's this look?
How do I look?
There's always a way.
After we went through all that,
we found a way.
Is it really over?
Can we really do this?
It's been really quiet.
I'm sure it's over now.
Let's start fresh.
- Okay.
- A toast!
Love shot.
Oh, do you remember you were
going to kill me here last time?
Geez, I really felt like
killing you then.
Tonight, I'll kill you.
Your back is broken,
but your mouth talks a big game!
Do you want to see what else is big, huh?
Oh, my! Oh, my!
Oh, my back! Geez!
Roar!
Well... go inside.
Have a good day.
Wow, what a nice day!
I love you! Have a good day!
Bye!
I love you! Bye!
Oh, my heart is running toward you!
I found a new side of me!
If things are always like this...
It won't be too bad to
live in this harsh world.
It won't be too hard!
Mr. Yoon! Please!
Please! Please don't do this!
We beg you!
Why are you doing this, all of a sudden?
If you fall, you'll die!
You'll die!
I'm risking my life for this movie.
But this script tells me
that I'm already dead.
Don't stop me.
See you in hell.
I'll rewrite it! I'll rewrite it!
I can feel it now! I know now!
I know now.
Well, I am sorry.
I just put on a show to
spark us to do a better job.
We went through a lot.
But now we have one billion won.
We can do it.
Let's write a new script.
Okay.
You can't do this to artists.
More than anything,
we need democracy first.
Okay, from now on,
I'll pay attention to what you say.
So let's work well together, okay?
Sung Goo, you take care of
the clubs from now on.
Young Il, you're in charge of
keeping the books.
Okay?
Then what about you?
From now on,
I'm devoting myself to the movie!
My Hyun Jee, the most beautiful girl
in the universe!
I have a lot of time these days.
When can I buy you something yummy?
- Hey!
- Shh.
This is my favorite part.
I knew it. This song is boring
every time I listen to it.
Here.
What kind of music did you do?
You said you were a singer in training.
What was your genre?
Acoustic... modern funk, hip hop, rock.
And etc.
Is it music, or me,
that you're interested in?
Could it be... me?
Stop it.
Oh?
Strange. Your face turned red.
Did I see it wrong?
Or did I hit the nail on the head?
Should I pretend I didn't see it?
Enough is enough.
Let's go together.
You play the guitar, and I will sing.
How's that?
You worked hard. You're the best!
Wow.
Did you guys
call each other this morning?
Was that a gift from your husband?
How do you know that?
Never mind. Sorry.
Why don't you just say it?
What is it?
You're making me upset.
Well, I ran into him at
an underwear store yesterday.
I gave him a tip. I guess he picked
the same one as mine.
My goodness...
Mr. Yoon really has no sense.
I know. They have such different styles.
That's not true.
They aren't that different.
They even have the same taste in men.
Huh? What's this?
Isn't that Sung Min and Hyun Jee?
- What?
- It's them.
- Right?
Did Young Jae send these?
Don't worry too much.
Even pre-schoolers date these days.
Hey!
You scared me!
I wasn't going to say this but...
- Do Kyung, talk to your daughter.
- What?
Since the incident at the police station,
I've been worried.
You're saying it's
Hyun Jee's fault again?
Daughters learn from their mothers.
I don't like how flirty she is.
You're upset, aren't you?
Because Tae Soo bought you
the same thing I bought?
What?
You should thank me.
You could have gotten
yourself granny panties.
You should have seen what he was holding.
I would like anything my husband buys me.
That's what I'm saying.
You shouldn't do this to me.
You got your husband, thanks to me.
Hey! Watch your mouth!
You're a fox, like always!
You are the real fox here.
You play innocent all along,
yet you took my man away.
Is that not a fact?
Lee Do Kyung!
Ahh!
Oh, no!
What did you do just now?
I didn't see it wrong, did I?
I said to not to kill a flower.
I said to make a peaceful world.
I didn't hear her, Ma'am.
Then what was it?
It's still violence,
even if you don't break arms or legs.
My goodness.
Then... is this how you've
been controlling the members?
Do Kyung... are you crying?
No... I'm sorry, Ma'am.
Well... Park Sun Young.
Yes... yes?
Tell me.
Was Eun Ok always violent and
controlling to you like this?
You can tell me the truth.
Oh, no. Eun Ok was never--
It's all my fault!
I shouldn't have joined One Heart.
I was too excited about
volunteering with nice people.
I knew someone here didn't
want me to join, but...
It's all my fault!
Why do you think I started
the feet-washing tradition?
Why do you think I had you
wash a new member's feet?
It was to prevent
incidents like this one.
This kind of thing happens when
the leader is not mature enough.
What? I'm controlling?
She only scolded me...
being deceived by that fox!
Stop. Blow your nose, blow your nose.
Everything has been going wrong
ever since that vixen came back!
I was upset about Sung Min,
and now it's Madam Oh!
Geez, please stop it.
Why do you guys fight amongst friends?
Be quiet! You have no right to say that.
Geez. I feel like dying from running.
Why are you taking your anger out on me?
You are an idiot.
You know nothing about women.
What have I done so wrong?
Here.
Forget it.
Geez. I'm going to die from running.
Geez.
Oh, my.
Black tea and waffles
are a perfect combination!
It's like Do Kyung and One Heart.
Pardon?
I was a bit surprised at your wits.
You are definitely a good actress.
And you make me curious
about what's next to come.
In fact, I'm also curious
about something.
Oh.
From One Heart to Eun Ok...
You're helping me left and right.
What is your reason?
Oh, didn't I tell you? My goodness!
Director Baek really wishes
to get back together with you.
I just want to help you.
The chairman is stubborn now.
But he would try to move a mountain
if I asked him to do so.
In addition, Director Bae
is depending on me these days.
Madam Oh.
Do you think I came back
to get back together with Director Baek?
Of course, my daughter wants her father.
But I don't really like the man,
Baek Gi Bum.
Maybe if he becomes
independent from the chairman.
Huh?
What my daughter needs is her father,
not a son of her grandfather.
Oh...
I knew it! I knew it!
I was right about you.
You are really an
independent and wise woman!
That's exactly what One Heart is about.
I'm so glad you joined One Heart!
You are amazing!
Your cup is empty.
Oh?
Oh... it's empty.
Mom, hurry up!
The noodles are getting soggy.
Do you have to do that at this hour?
I ate a lot.
If you don't want it, I'll eat it all...
Don't do that. Let's eat together.
Okay.
It looks yummy!
Good.
Mom, I want to do music again.
I'll take it easy.
And I have a partner to do it with me.
He's a bit dense, but it's not too bad.
You're not talking about
Sung Min, are you?
Keep it a secret from his mom.
Yoon Sung Min wants to study music.
Eun Ok will be furious if she finds out.
She'll blame you for this. She's vicious.
Are you two really friends?
What? Did something happen again?
You don't need to know.
Does your father talk to you?
He sends me childish texts.
He wants to see me.
He's bothersome!
You wanted to live close to your dad.
Hyun Jee...
I'll make sure you live a good life here.
Erase all the bad memories
you had back in Seoul.
No one can touch us.
Okay.
Oh, are you taking your medicine on time?
Oh, I forgot!
Wow... did you get a new car?
It's my company car.
You have a nice job.
You just sit around...
and money just rolls in your hands.
Why did you want to see me here?
When you come, you're a regular customer.
When you don't come, you're a stranger.
This song suddenly came to my mind.
You asked to see me last time.
But you are acting like a stranger now.
What's wrong with you, Brother?
What about what?
I'm just speaking the truth.
Get to the point.
That stormy night...
Director Baek was caught
on camera, speeding.
It was near Bong Gal Mountain.
The road must have been really slippery.
I wonder where he was going
at 110 kilometers per hour.
I heard the chairman
turned down Director Baek.
And then he raised your hand.
So Director Baek lost his business
chance and you got to make a movie.
So Director Baek got really angry...
and took care of him.
What do you think?
Do you see the picture?
Draw your picture on a paper!
You said to help each other when in need!
It's your turn to help me, Tae Soo.
Please! Gi Bum isn't that kind of man!
- Thank you.
- You're welcome. Bye.
Tae Soo, watch your back!
What are you, huh?
Hey!
Do Kyung!
Open your eyes! Wake up!
It was like being in a movie.
What? How can you laugh?
You were lucky.
It could have been bad.
Anyway, it seems that we run
into each other too often.
I don't want any misunderstandings.
Don't worry.
Honey! Tae Soo!
Oh...
Oh! Do Kyung!
Do Kyung...
What happened?
Someone was trying to hit me.
Do Kyung happened to see it
and saved me.
Save you?
That's a bit of an exaggeration.
Someone suspicious was
following him so I let him know.
I didn't get hurt badly.
I just need a cast for a while.
Geez. Unbelievable...
How could you not notice him?
Eun Ok, don't be too harsh.
I'm sure he was shocked too.
I wasn't talking to you.
What's wrong with you?
Do Kyung got hurt because of me.
How long has it been since
the four of us got together?
We all met for
the first time at a hospital.
Stop making that face.
We were good back then.
Why do you bring that up?
Why not?
If hadn't saved me,
then we wouldn't have known one another.
We'd be living different lives right now.
Tae Soo, you don't regret it?
Why would I?
I feel regretful sometimes.
I regret that I turned your
patient room into a love room.
I'll stay. You should go home.
You will?
I don't need that.
As the leader of One Heart,
I can't let my member suffer.
Don't worry. Go back to work.
Okay then. Please take care of her.
I'll call you.
You regret that you turned
his room into a love room?
Why? Because I met him there?
There you go again.
I meant that it would impose
on the other patients.
Oh... that's why you went on a date
with the patient's friend?
And you made me take care of Tae Soo.
You don't remember how you kicked us out
so you could be alone with Tae Soo?
And you don't remember how desperately
you wanted to get out with Gi Bum?
You never saw him before?
Can you think of anything?
How would I know the man
who wanted to whack you?
You really don't know, right?
What do you mean?
I'm already upset about Do Kyung.
Don't do this to me.
I'm going to crush him when I find him...
What is it? What? What?
You're having fun after
hitting the wrong person?
What's wrong, Brother?
Do you know who was hurt
instead of Tae Soo?
You hurt someone who must not be hurt!
What are you talking about?
It wasn't me!
What?
We haven't even gotten started.
Look. We're having a party celebrating me
getting discharged from the hospital!
Then who was it?
Think about it.
Tae Soo has lots of enemies.
It's not me! I swear!
You can cut my hand off if I'm lying.
Are you proud that you did nothing?
Do it right. Okay?
Boss! How much longer
will you let him be like that?
Have you ever seen a fisherman...
who wastes his bait?
I need Back Gi Bum to get Yoon Tae Soo...
and the old man, Baek Man Bo.
That was amazing.
One Heart is all about
sacrificing yourself for others.
Do Kyung showed us exactly what
that is like, with her actions.
Oh my God.
I can't express the way my heart feels
right now with any words.
Do Kyung, you are a heroine.
How could you think of jumping in
to help in that situation?
Could you do that?
We could never do that.
Please stop it.
I told her, my action was just
following my innocent heart.
You're being too kind.
Geez, you are being modest.
Eun Ok.
You should erect a statue of her,
out of your own pocket.
She saved your dear husband's life.
That's enough.
Leader Kim Eun Ok,
what do you mean by that?
I know she deserves a compliment.
And I'm thankful to her.
However, what matters is that
someone tried to hurt Tae Soo.
And even the others at Choong Shim
could be in danger.
This isn't the time for us to laugh,
going ha ha, ho ho.
Well, you have a point.
I guess I'll go home...
And contemplate what you said, Eun Ok.
Ha ha, ho ho?
Follow her!
Madam!
It's good that you spoke your mind,
but that was too much!
How will you fix this? I'm going.
How many songs will you do?
About six songs?
That's not enough.
Short, but impactful!
You need at least ten songs
to make an impact.
What if someone calls for an encore?
Is that right?
What is this? I can't stop eating it.
Isn't the gratin really good?
Sweet and spicy.
"Slunch" is popular these days.
Oh...
So are you going to do it or not?
I'm still thinking.
Are you playing hard to get?
That's mean.
My motto is "Think deeply
and prepare thoroughly."
What is it now?
When we were in pre-school...
You peed on your pants so often!
Geez, that little boy grew up so fast!
It's amazing.
What about you?
You used to fart in others' faces,
and make them cry.
You were the first student
to get kicked out of the school!
It was then.
What?
I picked you right then... as mine!
Hyun Jee!
Hyun Jee...
You brat!
Hello, Mr. Baek.
Oh, it's you, Sung Min!
I wondered who the heck this was.
- I'll go.
- Okay.
Okay, bye.
Why did you come here?
What is that?
Oh... I recorded what I
couldn't say last time--
Don't you think I'm too old
to be happy about that?
Huh?
Mom's not here.
She'll be back from Seoul tomorrow.
If you are done, I'll go inside.
Well... Okay.
It's cold. Go inside.
I'll take it since you brought it here.
Hyun Jee,
call me if you're scared to sleep alone!
I'll put my phone by my bed!
Call me!
It was then.
I picked you right then... as mine!
You must be tired, deprived of sleep.
A little.
Do you have something to say?
Well... Sung Min...
I guess I was a bit edgy these past
few days, because your grades fell.
You must have been even more upset.
No... don't worry about that.
Sung Min,
let's just endure one more year.
What's wrong, Mom?
I don't want you to do anything that
would distract you from studying.
You'll have good friends
when you go to college.
Much better than Hyun Jee.
Mom.
Who is that from, at this hour?
If you're done, please leave.
I have a lot to do.
I trust you, Sung Min. Okay?
Will you do it or not?
If you don't answer within three seconds,
I'll take it as a no.
Give it a try.
Dad.
Madam Oh insisted on it,
so I made a big decision.
I'll go to the orchard.
Yes, see you later.
How is it?
Do you like that?
Why are you doing this?
For you to get close to Do Kyung,
that will be the best way.
Let me make this clear.
Only after I get back together
with Do Kyung, can you marry Dad.
Do you know that
Do Kyung joined One Heart?
What do you think that means?
It means she's kind of
a part of Choong Shim now.
Then it's time to make her an official
member of the Choong Shim family.
Tae Soo and Eun Ok were the central axes
of Choong Shim and One Heart until now.
But from now on...
Baek Gi Bum and Lee Do Kyung...
The two of you can start a new era.
Thanks to you, I was discharged
from the hospital with no problem.
And I'm very sorry for
making you worry, Madam Oh.
You don't need to be sorry to me.
You should be sorry to Eun Ok.
I thought about it a lot,
and Eun Ok was right.
I didn't think about the real issue,
and I was not responsible.
I am very regretful about that.
I thought we should take this chance
for One Heart to be reborn.
Therefore...
I've decided to resign from my position
as Honorary Chairwoman.
What do you think, Eun Ok?
Of course, I won't force you.
Pardon? What do you mean by that?
Will you support One Heart's reform?
Or will you hold on to your position?
That's my question.
The movie production company
is moving in next door.
What?
Where are you?
I'm at the production company, of course.
What are you talking about?
They just moved into
the Choong Shim building.
What?
Okay, this is the new beginning.
I will show you my power.
Okay.
You suffered a lot under Tae Soo.
Your pain is over.
Happiness is on the way!
How do you like the office?
Do you like it?
I'm a businessman.
This movie is not art, it's business.
I'll make a movie that makes money.
Can you please, first,
explain why this is happening?
Just be quiet, Producer Lee.
Why are you always timid like that?
Did we do something wrong?
Are you a robot that just follows orders?
Please understand. He's a bit stubborn.
You couldn't talk back to Tae Soo,
but now you're raising your voice to me?
Why? Do I look that easy to you?
Gi Bum, what are you doing here?
Can't you see? I'm talking to my staff.
What right do you have to do that?
[Business License]
- What is this?
- As you see...
The director of Choong Shin Construction
is a better fit than a mere gangster.
That's Dad's grand idea.
What?
There's no point
in talking to a guy like you.
I invested one billion won, as promised.
What's the problem?
Well, I'm not talking about that.
Do I have boatloads of money?
Is one billion won a small amount?
Because you kept asking,
I used the company's money.
Since I did that, the director
of the company is put in charge.
But you promised to put me in
charge of making the movie.
I know, I did.
You are still making the movie.
Having two heads,
is better than having one.
It's a good thing if the movie
does well with Gi Bum's help.
Do Kyung!
Do you know that I'm the owner
of a movie production company?
Movie production company?
I'm the CEO of Choong Shim Pictures.
I'm also the Director of
Choong Shim Construction.
Tell Hyun Jee to look for
my name in movie credits.
No, let's all have dinner
together to celebrate!
Oh...
How did it go?
What did the chairman say?
He took your movie away.
And Madam Oh wants my position.
How badly do they want
to walk all over us?
We were too naive.
Geez. I can't do this anymore.
It's so dirty and unfair!
I want to quit it all!
Let's go. You are freezing.
Let's go.
Honey... over there.
What is it?
Sung Min!
What are you doing here?
Mom.
You should be at cram school.
Bu why are you here?
- Ma'am... that is..
- You stay out.
Don't touch my daughter!
What are you doing?
I warned you. I told you,
keep your girl away from my son!
What are you talking about?
Your son was already doing music.
You didn't know that, as his mother?
Okay, bring it on!
Your ex-husband and your daughter
are crapping all over us anyway.
What?
Crapping on you?
Sure, bring it on! I'm not scared!
Okay, bring it on!
You!
Stop!
You are dead!
Let go!
What's wrong with you?
Do Kyung!
I said let go!
You let go first!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Sweet Savage Family]
Have you ever asked me what my dream was?
Did Hyun Jee talk you into it?
Dad said he'd support me no
matter what I decide to do.
I will resign.
Let's vote on the Chairwoman position.
Are you all together now?
I'm sorry.
Don't trust them!
The chairman called
the guys at Cheongjoo.
Are they those guys then?
The skies are falling down on us!
Where is my daughter?
Are you questioning me now?
Mr. Chairman!