Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 1]
The sun is going to set! Hurry up!
Okay!
- Oh!
- Hey!
My goodness!
I almost died, running like that...
Take it easy.
You're already tired,
from such little work?
Sir, I'm just worried about you
working too hard.
Look at how much you're sweating!
No pain, no gain.
Speed it up.
There's no time to kill.
- Is there anything else I should do?
- Well...
You can finish those.
And now...
These branches need trimming.
I thought they would be okay
but they grew too fast.
There are a ton of twigs
sprouting everywhere.
It's quite a mess.
It's going to ruin my crops.
No worries.
Spray some chemicals.
Then everything will be fine.
Chairman Geo, who knew
we would run into each other here?
Tae Soo! What brought you here?
I came to take a piss.
Next time, our chairman
will let you have it.
Ha... Hey.
There's no such thing as next time
in the world of business.
I heard Yoo Du Ri was good
at doing business.
But I guess that's not true.
Look at you, you little brat.
The way you talk...
Huh? Huh?
Oh man...
You'll sign it now, right?
What did you say?
That old geezer,
Baek Man Bo, must be senile.
How dare he order me around?
Huh?
Old geezer? Senile?
You must respect the elders.
You don't fear anything
just because you're doing well?
I'll kill you today.
[Sweet Savage Family]
Hi.
[Chairman Baek Man Bo!
We wish you a long life!]
Come on, hurry up.
Why are you so late?
I told you to pay extra attention!
I'm not the guest of honor.
Oh?
You did something to your face?
If I didn't look nice today,
I'd be a disgrace to you.
Is that so?
I'll get compliments for
you looking so sparkly.
Enough.
How much are you
going to give for the gift?
Why do you ask? I'll give just enough.
So how much?
Just one.
One million won?
Are you crazy?
We can't afford
a 10 million won gift!
Hey! Who's helping us make a living?
We worked to death to earn that money!
We worked because the chairman
gave us that work!
Man...
People might think you do
some kind of important work.
Are you saving the country?
Ugh...
Gi Bum! Director Baek!
Where are you going?
I'm not done!
You came!
Hello.
What's wrong? It's a good day.
What's all this?
It would have been classier
if it were at a hotel.
He's so tacky!
They're serving noodles!
Is this a folk village?
It's nice! It's festive!
- Honey, I need to talk.
- Chairman Baek is here.
- Mr. Chairman!
- Congratulations!
How did it go?
It's done.
Good job.
Mr. Chairman!
Congratulations!
Thanks.
Wow.
You always look great,
but you look even better today.
You look like the guest of honor today.
Isn't that true, honey?
Of course! Since you're so young
you still look good,
even without doing much.
Well, Mr. Chairman.
The members of One Heart prepared for
your 70th birthday for a month.
You know that, right?
Eun Ok made it possible
as the head of the group.
Oh, wow.
Please don't say that.
We were obliged to do it.
Don't be nervous. Just smile.
One Heart! Don't be nervous. Smile.
One Heart, One Heart, One Heart!
One Heart.
Mr. Chairman, we wish you
a long, healthy life!
All I think about is you...
When I think about you
I can't help stop thinking about you.
Hooray, Chairman Baek Man Bo!
I begged you so much...
but you left heartlessly.
No matter how hard I cry...
it's all pointless.
All I think about is you...
When I think about you...
my heart can't stop beating for you.
The angel of smile, Baek Man Bo!
We love you, Baek Man Bo!
My goodness!
We love you!
That was great!
Go, honey!
Great!
The lady in red is my wife!
The one in the red dress!
Great! Great!
Hello?
What did you say?
What?
- My goodness!
- Be careful.
We're late.
Wait. I can't walk fast in this!
My shoe!
Why didn't you tell me?
It's not a good thing to talk about.
Wait until we get home.
You're dead today!
Be quiet.
I'm the assistant principal
at Bal Gwang Middle School
in charge of the
Anti School-Violence Committee.
We are here today to address
Yoon Sung Min's misconduct,
as she cyber-bullied Nam Mee Ae.
First, let us hear from
the victim's parents.
She constantly harassed and threatened
my daughter with texts and e-mails.
Mee Ae was so traumatized, that now
she almost has a heart attack
whenever her phone rings.
I'm not saying this just
because I'm a lawyer.
I must say, this is a serious crime.
I'm confident the committee will
deal prudently with this matter.
But I reaffirm that I hope there
will be severe punishment handed down.
That's all.
When a child does something wrong,
it is her parents who did wrong.
As her father, I apologize.
I ask for your mercy.
Soo Min, you were usually
good friends with Mee Ae.
Can you tell us why you did this?
She harassed my classmates.
When did I do that? I never did that.
Oh, so I'm going crazy?
- I saw it!
- Hey, hey hey!
Did you see that?
She shows no signs of remorse!
Even if she knelt down and started
begging, that wouldn't be enough.
A thief of a needle
becomes a thief of a cow.
A kid like that will cause
serious problems as an adult.
Wait a minute.
You don't know her well at all.
Why do you curse her future?
And it sounds like my daughter
isn't the only one at fault.
- Be quiet.
- Let go...
Soo Min, tell them how she
harassed other kids.
- I will complain to the committee too!
- What?
How dare you yell!
You're the parent of the aggressor!
You want a fight?
I can sue you for
making false accusations!
Like mother, like daughter!
Hey! Do you know me?
Why are you talking to me that way?
Is being a lawyer that great?
Watch your steps at night!
What?
Are you threatening me?
I'll sue you for making threats!
Sue me for assault too!
Sue me for assault, okay?
- This lady...
- Do it!
You're asking for trouble!
Oh, it hurts... it hurts...
You are a person who
knows the law very well.
It's inappropriate to act like this here.
I am very sorry.
We all learn from our mistakes.
I’ll teach her well at home.
I'll discipline her
and make sure she behaves well.
Please have mercy on her.
Please.
Watch your steps at night?
I was upset.
Is being a lawyer that great?
I'm so embarrassed because of you...
Be quiet!
I will deal with you at home.
Soo Min, you shouldn't
fight with your friends.
Try to get along.
I must be like someone here.
Let's go eat something since we're out.
When I'm stressed, I like to eat meat!
Steak!
Steak? My butt!
If you open your mouth again,
I'll confiscate your cell phone.
Ugh.
We haven't eaten out
together for so long.
Let's go!
It's the perfect day to do that.
Hey!
Whose genes do you have
to be so smart and handsome, huh?
If you don't answer correctly,
I'll cut your head off!
You, Dad!
That's right.
He's going to do well as an adult.
He's perfect! Sit down.
Eat up.
I spoke to your teacher on the phone.
You missed a question.
Yes. It was a mistake.
Not making that mistake is a skill.
That one question can change
your ranking at school.
By the way...
Strangely, your outfit fits
this place pretty well.
Don't change the subject.
What question was it?
Algebra? Geometry?
Stop it!
He's going to get indigestion.
Who will you go with when you
go to the workshop in Seoul?
Seoul?
He'll waste too much travel time!
There are good places here too.
On weekends, taking the train
is better than the express bus.
Why aren't you eating? Eat up.
Eat up.
Yes, Mr. Chairman?
Right now?
Yes, sir.
I got full just from
watching you guys eat.
This is what I live for, right?
Honey, order whatever you want to eat.
Do you want more steak?
You like the one with cheese.
Yoon Soo Min!
I told you not to use
your cell phone at the table.
Should I take it away?
Why do you take your
frustrations out on me?
Go.
No.
I can stay a little longer.
Go when I allow you to.
Go save the country.
Okay.
Stop right there!
Those rats!
Kill them all!
I almost died from running.
Were you on the track team?
Get them all!
Come here!
Stop right there!
Stop!
Hey.
Ugh...
Sir! Sir!
I returned the written contract.
Please save me.
I don't even know who you are.
I've never seen the written contract,
or whatever you're talking about.
Of course we never saw it.
That's because we never came here.
Boss.
Let's feed him to the fish
and go get some soju.
Save me!
Please save me, sir!
Forgive me! I did wrong!
Forgive?
What a swindler...
Do you know how many people's
lives you've ruined?
I can't live like a normal human
being because of jerks like you.
Go to hell and repent for your sins.
Let him go.
Okay!
Stop! I... I...
I... I...
In fact... In fact...
I have a house.
I hid it away secretly!
I'll give it to you!
Go ahead.
Two! I will give you two houses!
Two! That's all I have.
I promise.
As for me
I hate backstabbers more than
anything in the entire world.
Do you want to live?
That's entirely up to you.
Understood?
Eun Ok.
I'm home. Go sleep in the bedroom.
Oh.
You're home.
Did you eat?
I ate. Go get comfortable.
I'll go to sleep then.
Good night.
Egg tart! Egg tart!
Where is my egg tart?
Just eat a fried egg with rice today.
I'll go buy more.
I don't want to! I want to eat it now!
Yoon Soo Min.
What's wrong with you?
I was saving the last one!
You should take care of this!
How did I know this would happen?
Did I eat that?
I didn't say you ate it.
Don't eat anything then!
Why are you yelling at me?
Someone else is responsible.
You're going to be late.
Give me money then
so I can buy something to eat.
You just wanted to get money, right?
What did I do wrong?
- My goodness!
- Stop!
I am sorry.
The singer of the next generation!
Today's guest singer, Hong Jin Young!
Charge me up with love.
My love battery must've run out.
I can't live with you,
I really, really can't.
You are my battery.
I like you even though
you're not a pretty face.
I like you!
I like you even though
you don't have a great body.
I like you...
If you only look to me
then I'd consider you the best.
Everyone went crazy when
Hong Jin Young came out.
You are so adorable!
Thank you, sir.
Thanks to your support, I became
the MC of a variety show.
Really?
That's great!
Congratulations!
I knew you would be happy for me.
Of course I am.
I'll tell everyone about you.
When do you start?
Next month.
So speaking of that...
- Yeah?
- Actually...
I don't think I can make time.
What do I do?
Oh, well.
Some people work really hard.
But is she already out of battery?
It's just that her
main MC role is really big.
Please understand.
Is she quitting just here, or everywhere?
Well, that's...
All the clubs in the country.
Yes.
What about Busan?
Except that place.
Okay then.
Just stop by when
you're on the way there.
1.5 million people in
Daejeon love Hong Jin Young!
We've known each other so long.
We need to stick together all the way.
All the way.
This is Yoon Tae Soo,
Hong Jin Young's fan!
Pay your respects.
Hwang So.
Slow down, please.
Leave me alone.
It's not just anyone. It's Hwang So.
They said he hung himself
because he had no money.
Without knowing that,
I threw myself a birthday party.
He took good care of his underlings.
But what's this? No one showed up.
What's happening to this line of work?
At least Dal Shik should've been here.
I know he made a boatload of money.
But how dare he ignores his seniors!
This is not right.
You didn't know that
he went to prison last year?
His business failed.
He opened a business?
He invested in stocks.
His story was all over
the news at the time.
He made good money.
He started buying buildings and stocks
and then he lost them all at once!
That's why we are like a sand castle.
You may start your own business.
But once they get you,
you just go to jail.
Honestly...
How could you escape them if the
prosecutors wanted to get you?
Yeah.
It's time for us to find a new business.
Yes, sir.
Yes, Father.
Don't worry.
Chairman Wang.
Shall we get to our casino business now?
Did your chairman approve it?
Of course.
The Chinese will love Daejeon
even more from now on.
Man, it's so dry.
Hot! Hot!
Black noodles are the best
to eat quickly!
What's up with this leafy stuff?
Are we goats?
The chairman told us not to eat black
noodles in the office due to the smell.
We need to refresh the place first
if we want to have a fresh start.
What are you saying?
When an educated man looks
so serious like that
can he come up with good ideas?
Hey, Sung Goo!
A man must think with an open mind.
Who knows, maybe,
if you keep thinking and thinking...
you'll come up with
some good ideas too?
Geez.
Yes, Boss?
What did you say?
Oh, Tae Soo.
I think I'm going to die.
Just cremate me and scatter
my ashes somewhere.
And don't even hold a memorial ceremony.
Anyway, your wife is sick
of her mother-in-law.
She won't even have the desire
to hold a memorial ceremony.
Mom, why are you saying that?
I've lived long enough. It'd be
a good death if I died today.
Isn't it true?
Who says you're going to die?
Stop the nonsense. Tell me now.
I came here in the middle of my lunch.
It must be nice. You can eat.
I can't even dream of eating.
So what is this about?
Gosh, it's embarrassing to say...
But it's wrong not to say it.
Please, Mom!
Okay.
Since you are asking,
I guess I have to say it before I die.
Geez... geez.
Geez.
What's this?
I bought it because they were
giving away free toilet paper.
I ate it because it's supposed
to be good for my health.
But I have no strength,
like a baby's penis.
I've had diarrhea for three days!
I'm even wearing a diaper now.
My goodness...
How much did you pay?
2.8 million won.
What?
2.8 million won?
Are you out of your mind?
Did they say this would
give you eternal life?
Did I buy it for me?
I bought it for you, Tae Soo!
What the heck are you talking about?
Think about it.
Who suffers if I get sick?
It's you, Tae Soo!
If you got sad because
of your pathetic mother
how would I feel?
When I'm healthy, you're happy too!
Isn't that right?
Where did you buy this?
Where?
Well...
Is it here?
Go.
Hey. Open the door!
Open the door.
Come on!
Were you already packing up
so you could run away?
What's this about?
- Lock the door.
- Yes, sir!
Who are you?
You guys sold this to old people
for 2.8 million won!
- What is it?
- My mother had diarrhea for three days!
What will you do about that?
There must be a misunderstanding.
We are not those kinds of people.
What kind of people are you then?
As you see, we just moved in today.
This is a movie production company.
You are such a liar.
Is this made in Japan or America?
That's a camera. Don't touch it.
Hey, what are you? What do you do?
I am an educated man.
An educated man?
- Then am I an uneducated man?
- Stop.
I am telling you the truth.
I studied film abroad
and I'm a movie director.
We really make movies.
Why are you doing this? Please leave.
Don't even try.
You ripped off old people,
and now what are you up to?
- Guys, start it.
- Yes, sir!
Please stop it!
Please!
What's going on?
Should we call the police?
I shouldn't have come back.
If you don't stop, we'll call the police.
Hold it. We don't need to do that.
They'll leave when they see the truth.
What's this?
Hanbat Pictures?
That's the brochure about
our movie company.
- Movie company?
- Yes.
Look at the first page.
This is me. I'm the CEO.
Stanford?
Yes, and I went to Poland.
And I also went to
the Cannes Film Festival.
He's a famous movie director.
Yes... I'm pretty educated.
Oh, man.
Well...
Oh, wow.
I feel like dying from
all of this running.
Mom, it's me.
Can you see me?
Yes.
I will show you some faces.
See if any of them is the swindler.
Okay.
Is he this man?
I've never seen him before.
Yeah?
What about him?
Hello.
It's not him.
The last one. What about him?
What's going on?
Is something in your eye?
Look up.
What about this man?
He's the last one. Look carefully.
Turn him around. Let me see his ear.
His ear?
He'll do well in his later years.
I see wealth in his future.
You will succeed!
Thank you, ma'am.
Why are you reading his fortune?
I asked you to find the swindler.
That's why you don't have
good people around you.
You don't know how to see good people.
Enough. Just hang up.
Oh well.
I didn't do this intentionally.
Okay, anyway.
Keep up the good work, okay?
Sorry about that.
What are you doing?
It's not here.
Yes, sir.
What happened?
Luckily, I got him even though he moved.
I got the money back.
Plus free red ginseng.
This is real stuff, so you can eat it.
My goodness! What a relief!
What would I do without you?
Mom...
Please don't be so stubborn.
Come back and live with us.
We left your room just like it is.
Don't say that.
No one welcomes me.
I'm worried about you!
Don't worry about me!
A social worker comes to see me
since I'm a senior living alone.
You're not a senior living alone.
You can live with us.
Don't you miss the kids?
Please acknowledge your daughter-in-law.
And let go of things.
Can't we just live together happily?
You have no idea.
She's wonderfully sweet to you.
But she and I are like oil and water.
Geez...
Have a good day.
[My honey]
He calls me when I'm busy.
Go to the math class
right after the English class.
Okay.
Sung Min!
Why don't you take a grammar class too?
I don't have the time.
I'll work it out for you, okay?
Do it then.
Bye.
Go, go, my son!
Honey, it's me.
I get treated so nicely when I'm sick.
How are you feeling?
I've lived long enough.
It'd be a good death if I died now.
But I guess it's not the time yet.
Your son hates it when you
say things like that.
Are you siding with your husband?
I'm worried about your son.
You sure can talk like an angel.
I'll put the side dishes
in the refrigerator.
Okay.
We still have your room.
You can come back anytime.
Let's live comfortably.
It's good for both of us.
I'm saying this because you don't seem
to live comfortably and I don't either.
What about you?
Is something going on at home?
Did Soo Min get in trouble again?
Tae Soo and I had to go to the school.
Stop favoring Sung Min.
Kids are all born differently!
[Wives can help their husbands succeed!]
You have nothing to worry about,
except for your mother-in-law.
Your son is smart, your husband
does well, and you live in a nice house.
I feel suffocated when I think
about the two men in my home.
I heard Sung Min placed
first at school again.
He will definitely go
to Seoul University.
Don't say that.
He could lose his place if he
lets his guards down for a second.
He's barely holding that place.
Oh, don't whine.
That doesn't make any of us feel good.
Please.
- Oh, ma'am!
- Ma'am!
Welcome!
You worked really hard.
Didn't you get sick after that?
Wow! It's so beautiful!
It's silk!
It's so soft! I love it!
Do you like them?
Yes!
Everyone did a great job.
Thanks to you, the chairman had
a wonderful 70th birthday.
More than anything
I had a chance to witness the
power of One Heart once again.
I was very pleased.
In particular, our leader, Kim Eun Ok,
worked very hard.
Please don't say that.
It was like preparing for
my own father's birthday.
All I could think about was
how I could help more.
It's nice that you are busy
volunteering and working for One Heart.
But I wonder if you are neglecting
something important internally.
What's our motto?
- I know.
Loyal wives with intelligence,
grace, and healthy bodies.
I've stressed this many times before.
To me, intelligence is the
most important of the three.
Oh, wait a minute.
I want to recommend this
book to all of you.
Why don't you read it and
discuss the book together?
Justice.
That's a bestseller.
The title is very intriguing.
You have an eye for books!
Isn't that right?
Of course!
Enjoy reading it.
Did the news reach that far?
Okay.
Let me know if there's anything
the chairman would like.
Come see me at the nightclub.
Okay. Bye.
Huh?
Let's go up.
Thank you so much for
taking the time to come.
She could have picked
a different color for each one.
Is this a uniform or something?
This is a knock-off, right?
In my opinion, her life,
in and of itself, is a knock-off.
She's not even legally married.
But she acts like queen.
I wonder what's in her past.
I heard she and the chairman
use different beds.
Really?
Is it platonic love?
Or is she just torturing him?
- The chairman must be desperate.
- Crazy!
You're writing a novel.
You're having fun too.
Did you hear that the chairman
gave all the men serious homework?
Yes. "Power for a new growth."
Power for a new growth? What's that?
Movies are a cultural industry.
Gangster movies, specifically,
are a symbol of power.
Friends for Busan.
The Glory of Family for Leo Soo.
Silla’s Night for Gyeongju.
Mokpo is the Port for Mokpo
Let me ask you something.
What is there for Chungcheong-do?
What do we have?
This is the current situation
of our Chungcheong-do!
Oh...
- The movie, Hot Brothers!
- That's right.
It's a black and white action film
about gangsters in Daejeon.
Many cities in Korea became famous
because of the movies about them.
Now, the time has come
for Chungcheong-do!
I am saying this with confidence.
The movie industry is
a high value-added industry.
You may not know exactly what that means.
Let me make it easier
for you to understand.
Korea's big companies could not sell
enough cars or cell phones
to earn half the profits
that the movie Avatar made.
That is the power of culture!
The power of movies!
Well said! Well said! Well said!
Thank you! Come in!
Come in, sir! Come in!
Come on in! Thank you!
You remember Yoo Sung Special District.
Everyone wanted to go there.
I'm saying we should revive that again.
A hotel, a shopping mall,
an amusement park.
And a casino.
A paradise on Earth!
This is... Yoo Sung Multi-Thematic Park.
We have a Chinese investor
who wants to invest 10 billion won.
They wanted Busan or Incheon.
But just barely, I convinced them
to pick Daejeon, the transportation hub.
Tell me how.
Give me details.
You don't see it?
I'm saying bulldoze it and rebuild it.
If we can do this, everyone will see us
as a legitimate corporate group.
Tae Soo.
- Yes, it sounds great.
- What does?
Gi Bum's idea.
Not that.
I'm asking if you have something.
I see.
- That is--
- Did you not hear my words?
You didn't hear me?
It's not that. I mean...
Well.
That is...
How about movies?
What?
The fists in Chungcheong-do.
You know in Daejeon...
It's called Hot Brothers.
That is...
Stop stuttering. Just say it.
I mean, the movie, Friends,
is based in Busan.
"The Glory of Family" is about Yeosu.
"Mok Po is the Port" is about Mokpo.
Silla's Night is based in Gyeongju.
But what about us? Nothing!
Are our fists like water?
There are many movies about other cities.
But why is it, that there
are no movies about us?
Don't you agree?
Movies are great.
They could make a movie
based on your life!
So they're making a movie?
Of course.
I went to the promotional meeting.
Look at this. This is the brochure.
What are you doing, Father?
You're here.
Why are you looking at
something like this?
I'm a bit curious.
Movies can't compare to a casino.
You should think big.
They don't raise pearls in a small creek.
You do nightclubs and a movie. Fine.
But you still remain a gangster.
It's like a gangster
investing in a movie.
But a multi-thematic park
is a different story.
You'll become a businessman
that revives the entire city.
Because of the casino?
Please stop.
You need to see the forest,
not the trees.
Is that all you can see?
What about the hotel, or the mall?
And casinos aren't always run by gangs.
A casino is a legitimate
leisure business venture.
Chinese tourists will come
like bees looking for honey!
This isn't a small business!
So it's risky.
Don't underestimate the Chinese.
Father.
China is the big thing now.
You have to get the Chinese to succeed!
This kind of opportunity
will never come again!
It's like a pumpkin rolling
in your hands by itself!
This isn't something you can pull off.
Please!
No father stops his son from getting
a pumpkin instead of an acorn!
Try this.
- This is a special dish.
- Thank you.
Our chairman doesn't
bring just anyone here.
I see. I received a very
special invitation then.
My mother loves acorn tofu rice,
so I had it a lot when I was little.
Oh.
Wow, it's delicious!
Delicious? It's bitter.
Mr. Chairman, I am from Daejeon too.
Please speak casually to me.
Oh!
Is that so?
You're my local then.
Yes.
And I heard you are my
senior in the film industry.
Mr. Yoon,
you didn't need to tell him that.
It's all in the past.
When I first went to Seoul
I worked briefly as
a production manager
for someone I knew that
owned a film company.
Moon Hee's debut film was a hit then.
You mean Black Stream?
Wow.
I've met my senior, who even
took a path before me!
It's my honor to meet you!
Don't say that.
There is a movie about
gangsters in Chungcheong-do.
The City of Violence.
The City of Violence!
It's directed by Ryu Seung Wan.
Actually, I'm the person who got
him to start making movies.
The name of the city in
that movie is Onsung.
It should be either Onyang, or Yoosung.
What's the reason to invent
a city that doesn't exist?
It doesn't exist!
That's why I'm making
a movie about Daejeon.
I want to make a good movie
about gangsters in Daejeon!
That's what interested our chairman.
I really want this movie to make
people be proud of our Chungcheong-do!
Many people in this country
look down on Chungcheong-do!
- Isn't that true?
- Yes.
You know what I'm most upset about?
They said it was the era of three Kims.
Both YS and DJ became President.
But why not JP?
It's all because they think of
Chungcheong-do as a joke!
That's right!
Don't ever underestimate Chungcheong-do!
When the Pope came to Korea
He didn't go to
Jeolla-do or Gyeongsang-do.
- He only visited Chungcheong-do!
- Right!
No need to say more!
UN Secretary General, Ban Ki Moon!
He's also from Chungcheong-do!
Right.
When I hear them say,
"idiotic Chungcheong-do"
my head opens!
They say we are slow.
That's bullshit.
Is Park Chan Ho slow?
Is Park Se Ri slow?
That's right.
The people of Chungcheong-do
are not slow!
Go, Hot Brothers!
May it be a big hit!
A big hit!
What made you want
to invest in the movie?
Movies are a cultural industry.
Hot Brothers is about Chungcheong-do.
I wanted to make a good movie
about our hometown!
That's why I'm investing in the movie.
May it be a big hit!
Big hit! Big hit!
I never could've dreamed of
getting it done so fast.
It's all thanks to you.
Let's go toast to it then!
I'll buy you a drink!
I have more money than you do!
I have 3 billion won in my bank account.
What?
The chairman does things big.
He already deposited all of the money.
I see. That's why all the lawmakers are
treating him like their big brother.
I see.
Do you remember what your mom
said when you first met me?
Of course I do.
She said that in your fortune
she sees wealth and success.
Does that mean I'll be blessed
with good people from now on?
I should be that blessing to you.
Thank you for your kind words.
You are from Daejeon.
Where did you go to high school?
I went to Bal Gwang High.
- You went to Bal Gwang?
- Yes.
I did too! What year?
I was in the 17th year.
Speak casually to me, Brother.
You are my senior by one year.
I was in the 18th year.
- The 18th year?
- Yes!
Oh, my!
But we didn't know each other back then.
We just met as adults.
I can't speak casually to you.
This is why they say the people of
Chungcheong-do are called gentlemen.
I'm so happy to have met you.
I'm going to get really busy soon.
I will need your help.
Gosh, I know nothing.
You'll be the one to
help me out, older brother.
Please don't call me older brother.
I'm so glad to meet you.
Who knew we would meet like this?
I hate you. You totally
messed up my office before!
- I thought it was a machine gun.
- How on earth--
- I'm so ignorant.
- This is a camera.
- It's expensive.
- I got it.
Excuse me, Big Boss.
Chairman Wang wants you to call him back.
What are you?
Are you working for Tae Soo?
Of course not!
You planned this all along, didn't you?
I didn't!
I would never do that.
Tae Soo. Wait and see.
I won't leave you alone.
What's all this?
I can't even eat a cake!
Don't be like that.
I respect and love you so much, my dear!
You're being cheesy.
Dad, you look great in the picture.
Wow.
Can I tell my friends that
you are a movie investor?
Of course!
Wait. If the movie becomes a hit,
do we get to go to award ceremonies?
I guess the director gets to go.
I think the investor receives
the award for the best picture.
What? Then are you going to be TV?
I felt something right here. Feel it.
What are you doing in
front of the teenagers?
What's wrong with that?
- Give your speech! Practice.
- Great!
We didn't even start
making the movie yet!
Yoon Tae Soo! Yoon Tae Soo!
Stop it.
Yoon Tae Soo!
Okay.
Let us hear from Yoon Tae Soo,
who just won the award for best picture.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Ladies...
Gentlemen?
It's a beautiful night.
Actually, there were so many good movies.
I thought we had no chance.
They say a pheasant catches an eagle.
I can't believe I'm receiving this award.
Actually, I am nothing.
I am just a gangster.
The director set the table.
All I did was sit at the table
and eat with my spoon.
Lastly, I have some people
I want to thank.
My wife, whom I love dearly.
She is...
What's your name?
Kim Eun Ok!
And my puppies, Sung Min and Soo Min!
I want to give my glory to all of them!
Hey!
Stop!
You are a rat! Rat!
How dare you steal my money?
What was it, just over 10 million won
that he stole more than three years ago?
Yes. You know he doesn't
forget when it comes to money.
He's been a bit edgy since
he invested in that movie.
He spent 3 billion won, all at once.
Now that I'm old,
my heart has become tender.
I would have done more if I were younger.
He ran away with my money. How dare he...
Should I deal with him?
Leave it.
You shouldn't do this kind of thing.
You're meant to be big.
Mr. Son was quick to take that money.
He said he wanted us, not because of me,
but because of you.
He's just saying that.
I'm doing this because I trust you.
Tae Soo, this can change our lives.
Work to death.
Your life depends on it.
Yes, sir.
The chairman is really
putting his trust in you.
Oh, man! I feel burdened.
But Boss, will our names
be in the credits?
How hard can that be?
Mr. Son is my school senior!
Really? Everything is going so well!
- I know.
- Should I be an extra in the movie?
I can be an actor!
Then go to talk to him!
What about me?
If you do it, I'll do it too!
I can't!
Why don't all of us do it?
That's great! Okay!
No way.
I don't think we can.
Let's go.
We can't.
Flying kick!
Huh?
Where is everyone?
Boss, there's nothing here.
It's all empty.
What?
The number you called does not exist.
What? Did they run away?
Boss.
Didn't the chairman
deposit three billion won?
I'll kill them all...
Go find him!
Now!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Sweet Savage Family]
Do you know what kind of money that was?
You can live too if we make a movie.
What did you talk about with Tae Soo?
I've been married to a gangster
for 18 years. I can tell.
I like his style and his chin.
You're ignoring us again?
You don't recognize me?
Does Mr. Yoon know you're slacking here?
My friend, I have big news for you.
Where is the CEO?
What have I done wrong?
My friend, good luck.