- What are you doing?
- What about you?
I warned you. I told you to keep
your daughter away from my son.
What are you talking about you?
Your son was already doing music.
You didn't know that, as his mother?
Okay, bring it on!
Your ex-husband and your daughter
are crapping all over us!
Crapping all over you?
Okay, bring it on!
I'm not scared!
Bring it on!
You!
Stop!
Let go of my hair!
You let go!
What's wrong with you?
Do Kyung!
Hey! Let go!
Subtitles by DramaFever
Honey!
Are you okay, Honey?
Calm down, Honey!
Let go!
I said let go!
You let go first.
Let go, both of you! Calm down!
Let go on the count of three!
One, two, three!
Three!
You!
What's wrong with you?
This is embarrassing!
She won't let go!
What about you?
Eun Ok, please stop.
Do Kyung is a patient!
Oh, Gi Bum!
Your nose, your nose!
My nose? What about it? Huh?
Ah!
Blood! From both my nostrils!
Geez!
Let go!
Oh, my nose! My nose!
Gi Bum! Oh, no!
Gi Bum, don't die! Don't die, Gi Bum!
This is bad! What should we do?
- Ah!
- My goodness!
Don't die!
Gi Bum!
My nose is bleeding!
Louder...
Oh no!
It finally stopped.
Why did you try to stop us?
I was going to battle it out this time.
How dare she hit my precious daughter?
If only my arm was in shape...
That's right. Is your arm okay?
Huh?
I guess it got better after
I warmed up my body a bit.
Were you just pretending?
Stay still. I need to wipe your face off.
Geez. Your face is covered with blood!
Geez.
Blow.
Oh, Hyun Jee.
Oh... where have you been?
I was with Sung Min.
All of this happened because of me.
I'm sorry, Mom, Dad.
Don't say that.
You did nothing wrong.
Right. The adults were wrong.
We ruined your show.
Offering a show to
the public is a great thing!
Your singing totally mesmerized me.
By the way, Hyun Jee...
Do you want to do music for film?
Why music for film, specifically?
Oh... you didn't know that I became the
CEO of a movie production company.
Never mind.
You are a beauty just like your mom.
Do you want to be
in a movie with your mom?
No, thank you. I retired a long time ago.
Why not? You'd be good in action movies.
You can fight.
Let go! Let go! Ah!
It's going to be a hit!
Stop it already.
You should go home.
I'm good. I can go later.
I meant she and I need to go home.
I see...
That's right.
Since when?
Let's talk later.
No. Answer me now.
Mom...
Did Hyun Jee talk you
into doing it together?
It's not like that.
It has nothing to do with her.
You were a good student. Why are
you suddenly doing strange things?
Do you know how I feel now?
It feels like the sky is falling down.
This is big.
Well... calm down.
Let's hear what he has to say first.
I don't want to hear it.
Stop that strange stuff
and focus on studying.
If you study hard for just one more
year, you'll go to Seoul University--
Stop talking about Seoul University!
I won't go to Seoul University.
I don't want to.
You have no interest in what
I like, or what I want to do.
You always talk about Seoul University.
Have you ever asked me about my dreams?
I kept it a secret all this time,
but I won't do that anymore.
I will keep doing music.
You've gone insane.
Okay, I'll help you come to your senses.
Honey!
- Mom...
- Step aside!
Mom.
I said, step aside.
Please don't do this.
Stay away. You'll get hurt!
- Mom!
- Go!
No, don't do that!
Tae Soo! Tae Soo!
Oh no!
I said step aside!
What are you doing?
Give me that.
I don't want to.
I don't want to!
You don't see what's going on here?
My cell phone!
I'll call the police!
Soo Min, go to your room!
Why are you doing this to me?
You pay for it!
Stop it! What are you all
doing to your own family?
Mom, can you stay out of it?
Am I not allowed to talk?
You don't respect your mother?
It's not that!
You stay out of it!
What about my phone?
It's all your fault!
You made it worse!
Calm down!
How can I calm down?
Stop, stop! Geez!
Do you really have to
do this in front of me?
I won't live much longer!
Geez, where is the Grim Reaper?
Please come get me!
Just in case, here's a
song to cheer you up.
Geez, you are handsome and smart...
And you are good at music!
Who's your dad?
Just scold me like Mom did.
Why would I scold you?
I totally understand you, Sung Min.
You are not allowed to
do what you want to do.
And you have to study,
which is not what you want.
It must be really hard.
However... I understand what
Mom is going through too.
Now I understand what it means to
say that everything has its own time.
Your life can get hard if you don't
study when it's time to study.
Give me some time to think.
Okay.
I will let Mom know.
Cheer up! Up here.
Sugar is the best thing
when you are stressed out.
The song you sent me was pretty good.
Just pretty good?
Not amazingly good or shockingly good?
Yes, it was amazing, shockingly great!
It comforted me.
But I'm not sure.
When I think about myself,
I just can't give up music.
But for my mom,
and the rest of my family...
I feel like I should focus wholeheartedly
on studying for one more year.
Then do that. You won't lose music
just because you stopped for one year.
But without music, I don't feel
like studying, or even eating.
Everything I see or hear is meaningless!
Then do what you want to do!
Why do you agonize when you've
already made your decision?
Did you know Sung Min was
doing music, Director?
Pardon me?
He often skipped cram school
to perform on the street.
Did you know that?
That was...
Sung Min promised to keep his rank so...
Director!
You asked for his picture so you
could put it on a plank card.
You promised to teach him
as if you were his parent.
Parents wouldn't do that.
You can't do that when he's only one year
away from his college entrance exam.
I'm very sorry.
I'll make it short.
I cannot allow him to
skip cram school again.
Don't tell Sung Min that I was here.
And tell the front desk to text
me every time Sun Min comes here.
I'm sorry if was rude.
Kyung Mee, I can't come
to One Heart today--
What?
Ladies dog fight! That's funny!
I've seen her before.
Isn't she an actress?
Isn't she the chairwoman of One Heart?
One Heart? What's that?
It's a volunteer organization, but
it's just a bunch of gangsters' wives.
You know...
One Heart's reputation, for which
we have worked very hard, was ruined...
By violence.
The chairman would be very proud
of you if he found out, right?
Ma'am, please calm down and sit...
Put it down!
Sure.
I have no right to drink this water.
This kind of incident happened
as soon as I resigned.
Absence of discipline!
Absence of leadership!
That's the only conclusion I can come to!
Please don't say that, Madam.
We were impulsive.
No, it's all my fault.
Yes, it is.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's my fault that I didn't do anything
about what you did to Do Kyung.
If I had corrected the problem then,
this wouldn't have happened.
How will you
take responsibility for this?
I've already resigned from my
honorary chairwoman's position.
Now it's your turn to decide.
Will you choose the
big cause for One Heart?
Will you hold onto your
position for your own glory?
You choose.
Right. It is all my fault.
And I understand what you're saying.
I will...
I will resign from the One Heart
chairwoman position.
Oh... I see.
Okay then... As of now...
Both positions, Honorary Chairwoman,
and Chairwoman, are vacant.
We will elect a new chairwoman right now,
as this is an urgent situation.
All of you are eligible
to run in the election.
And also...
You will choose your next
chairwoman all on your own!
What the heck is going on?
Are we really having an election?
We only have 20 members. But now we
have an emergency planning committee.
My goodness!
I understand how you feel,
but you should have held it together.
It's okay. I don't have the time
to work for One Heart now anyway.
You can have the chairwoman title.
But you're basically a
servant, just doing chores.
Do you really mean it?
What do you mean?
It sounds like you have
no desire for the title.
And how does that interest you?
I'm thinking of running.
You better do something about your wife.
She's totally marred the
company reputation.
Did she fight alone?
Enough.
What about your smart boy?
Hyun Jee wants to be a singer anyway.
But Sung Min was your only hope.
He's the bookworm!
Good morning.
Oh, sit down.
Did you read the script? How was it?
Oh... that is...
Polish it up a little.
Make it a bit more dramatic and sensual.
Wouldn't that be enough?
Just a bit?
You can't turn a watermelon
into a pumpkin by fixing it up a bit.
Why don't you totally change it?
Don't just work on the surface.
A gangster movie is about action anyway.
There's no point in delaying it.
Just worry about whom to cast.
You can't move into
a house if isn't built well.
Tae Soo, I'm the CEO here.
Listen to your boss.
Don't take your stress out on them.
What did you say?
I've had enough of you.
Are we here to discuss the script?
What's wrong with you?
Whether it's criticism or blame,
let's talk about the real issue here.
How can you make a movie when you just
waste your time arguing over nothing?
Yes.
Okay.
Everyone, follow me.
Geez, we are all dead because of you.
What did I do? Was I wrong?
This car is for you to use.
Are you really giving it to us?
Have you always been
fooled by people throughout life?
You're going to get big.
You better travel safely.
I'm not a stingy man, like someone
who might have always criticized you.
Bub Gyu, give it to them.
Yes, Boss.
Here.
What is this?
You need money.
You don't need to watch your spending.
But watch your mouth.
You don't need to
always speak up, okay?
Don't spend more than 7,000 won per meal.
You could get billed.
Hey, don't be pathetic.
What does a CEO do?
Isn't this something you do as the CEO?
We need to talk.
Come here.
Why do we have to come here?
I told you, I'm risking
my life for this movie.
But why are you doing this?
You want to take it away from me
because it's something I'm doing?
I was the one who got into movies.
Who showed you
"A Better Tomorrow" and "The Killer"?
You watched them because of me.
Stop talking nonsense.
What's the real reason?
You know Do Kyung used to be an
actress, and that acting was her dream.
I want to make her dream
come true with this movie...
And get back together with her.
We're not making a home video!
Even famous filmmakers fail all the time.
If you put you life down on this movie,
it still will not be enough.
You can't use this for
personal goals.
Stop saying you put
your life down for it. That bothers me!
Then you put down your life for it too!
Geez!
What's this talk about life? Is someone's
life in trouble or something?
Brother.
Why do you always scare people
by showing up out of the blue?
Your staff said you would be up here.
I have big news.
You better take
your heart medication first.
I don't want to hear it. Just go.
You don't want to hear about Mr. Son?
That man...
Someone saw him.
What?
Why are you overreacting?
Well...
Director Baek was possessed by
Mr. Son's spirit, you know.
Well... keep going then.
That swindler came back to life,
and he's running around now.
What...
He came back to life?
He wasn't dead. He's alive.
Geez, what does that mean?
Wait and see.
I will catch him, and I'll twist his neck
and put a handcuff on his hand.
You better not think about
catching him on your own.
If anything happened to him,
you'd be my first suspects.
I will catch him!
It's really good.
It's melting in my mouth!
I know.
- It's good we came.
- I know.
Kyung Mee, can we really do this?
What if Eun Ok finds out?
Did we commit a sin?
We were invited here.
It would be strange if we came,
having not been invited over.
Think about your husband's future.
You need this.
Eat. It's good.
So good.
I have a red from a 1999 vintage!
Wow...
Do you like the casual
Cheongdam-dong style party?
How is it, Kyung Mee?
I love it! Cordon...
Whatever it is you went to...
Your food is on a whole different level.
Thank you.
By the way, why did you invite us here?
Well... so I can impress you?
You've only tried to control your son.
You haven't tried to understand him.
Are you really his mother?
What did Sung Min say?
Tae Soo talked to him...
He said he needed time to think.
I can hear my grandson's heart hurting.
My heart is hurting too.
What will you do about my screen?
It's not working.
Soo Min.
I was left out in my class chat.
Stop it already!
Sung Min caused the problem,
but why are you upset with me?
- Don't be rude!
- Whatever! Why me?
It's annoying!
Look at that.
My goodness. We spoiled her...
Please eat more.
Can you really swallow
food in this situation?
You're carefree.
You were all about your son's schooling.
But what came out of that?
Geez. It's frustrating.
I have never been so
frustrated before!
Geez.
Sun Young.
I can't talk to you right now.
I'm in the middle of something.
That's okay.
I just wanted to see if I
could have a drink with you.
I'm so sorry. I'll buy drinks next time!
You had a dream like that?
Kyung Mee! Be quiet...
Is Kyung Mee there too?
If it's Eun Ok, tell her to come.
Let's drink some wine together.
Wasn't that Do Kyung's voice?
Are you all together now?
I'm sorry. I'll explain
everything tomorrow.
Geez, my hands are shaking.
Why didn't you tell her to come?
This is great!
Hello, everyone!
Oh!
What brings you here, Director Baek?
Manager Chang told me you were
all here, so I came to say hello.
Manager Chang, let's take them out.
Yes.
Take one please.
It's a special gift from Director Baek.
Please sit down. Please.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
I heard about the election.
I thought you could use my help.
Director Baek, isn't this cheating?
You're causing trouble for us.
Don't worry about that.
The ladies of One Heart are
representatives of Choong Shim.
As the CEO of Choong Shim Pictures,
and Choong Shim Construction
I must take care of our ladies!
You're the best!
I feel good.
Thank you, Director Baek!
You're welcome! I'll take care
of your skin from now on!
Take care!
Bye! One Heart!
Great. Let's go in.
Oh!
Oh, man! You're drunk!
I thought you were fine. Is there any
medicine that will make you sober?
Just sit down. Stop being dramatic.
Okay.
Unexpectedly enough, you made me proud.
I didn't even ask you to do that.
You told me to prove myself with actions.
This is just the beginning.
You should have done that sooner.
When I heard Hyun Jee singing the
other night, I thought of our old days.
The swap song.
Do you still remember that?
Let's go through the jungle.
Let's crawl through the jungle.
When we come across a "swap"
You'll see crocodiles!
Crocodiles!
Hyun Jee always said
swap instead of swamp.
Back then... the three
of us were pretty good.
We were.
Hyun Jee was...
always a fantastic dancer.
Do you remember this?
Hyun Jee's favorite dance.
Oola Oola... Oola Oola.
Oola Oola.
Isn't Dad dancing?
It's more fun dancing together.
I am. Of course I am.
Oola Oola.
You are cute!
Remember Hyun Jee's kiss massage?
Grab your cheeks like this...
and kiss ten times.
Yeah...
Are you okay?
I guess I'm drunk.
No, you aren't drunk!
You're totally sober!
I want to sit. My legs are giving out.
Okay...
Water.
Water!
By the way... the kiss massage.
How do you do it?
I can't remember very well.
How can you forget that?
Come over here.
Grab the cheeks...
Hey.
Do Kyung, what are you doing?
Are you sleeping?
Do Kyung? Do Kyung...
Do Kyung... please...
Do Kyung, please wake up! Do Kyung!
I don't even wish for ten kisses.
Just one...
Just once...
Honey!
Oh, my husband is here!
You're so handsome that I can
recognize you from a mile away!
I'll die from running.
Why did you drink so much?
Just...
Because I'm in a good mood!
What? Did something happen?
How's your work at the movie company?
Is Baek Gi Bum bearable?
It's true that life is in vain.
See how I got betrayed by my friends,
and tried to get comfort from alcohol?
When you proposed to me...
You said you'd be loyal, no matter what.
Do you remember that?
I loved how that sounded.
Loyalty is the best thing
for a gangster to have.
Of course it is!
Honey.
Thank you.
Thank you for accepting Sung Min
as your son and raising him.
No one else could compare to that.
- You really are amazing.
- Huh?
What are you talking about?
No matter what, Sung Min is my son!
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
If you say that again, I will...
Scold you.
Drink.
Okay. Here.
Okay! My amazing husband. Let's drink!
You need a cup.
Sir, bring us a cup--
I have this. Toast!
Oh, good!
Good, my husband.
You are on my side, no matter what.
That's needless to say.
You're not on someone else's side, right?
Well, I already told you.
I have your back.
So don't worry about anything.
If anyone bothers you,
I'll bite off his nose!
Wow, I feel stronger now.
Cheer up, Yoon Tae Soo!
Cheer up, Kim Eun Ok!
Let's go through the jungle.
Let's crawl through the jungle.
When you see a "swap"
You'll see crocodiles!
Crocodiles!
Smells good.
Cheer up!
What is it?
Oh... it's nothing.
Are we already home?
No. Sleep more.
I will close my speech with a proverb
that I've been cherishing in my heart.
Put it into action!
Your dream comes true when
you put them into action!
Gorgeous. Gorgeous.
That was an impressive candidacy speech.
Is there anyone else who wants
to run in the election?
I'm sure there isn't anyone.
Then...
Lee Do Kyung is the sole candidate
for the chairwoman position--
Wait a moment.
I would like to run for the election too.
You would, Eun Ok?
Then, why don't you give us a speech too?
For the past five years,
since the birth of One Heart...
I was the Chairwoman of One Heart.
I had praises. I also made many mistakes.
I know I'm lacking.
That's why I thought of stepping down.
However, after some serious thinking,
I came to a conclusion.
No parents would give up their children.
Just like that,
I can't give up One Heart.
More than anything, I believe...
The members of One Heart will not
be blown away by a cosmetics gift set.
That's what I want to prove.
Then... according to the order
of candidacy submission...
Candidate number one, Lee Do Kyung!
Number two, Kim Eun Ok.
The election is in three days.
We'll have a new chairwoman then.
Wow, Director Baek! Congratulations!
Wow, you came to visit us yourself.
I don't need that kind of thing.
Put it outside. Outside, outside!
Now you are the CEO of a
movie production company!
How can I just sit around doing nothing?
These are the people who will
make you a billionaire, like me!
Nice to meet you!
What are you doing here?
Hold on, Tae Soo.
Director Cho came to congratulate us.
He also introduced us to an investor.
Are you crazy?
How can you let just anyone in here?
Well, Director Yoon.
Long time, no see. I've missed you.
What did I say would happen
if we ever saw each other?
Huh?
Geez, I forgot.
Please understand. I'm an idiot.
This idiot is going home then.
What was that?
That was my guest.
He's a swindler, not a guest.
If he came to invest,
he's our guest, no matter what he is!
Be careful, Tae Soo.
You are going to be full of regret.
Who's that guy next to Gi Bum?
He's Director Cho Dong Choon,
from Gunseol Group.
What the heck...
Do you want to make a movie or not?
Questionable people come and go
all the time, and they say nonsense!
He looks like a gangster’s errand boy.
You were happy to death when he gave
you the car keys and the credit card.
Now you've come to your senses?
What brings you here, Mr. Chairman?
Why did Cho Dong Choon come here?
He came to see Gi Bum.
What are you doing, Tae Soo?
If Gi Bum does something wrong,
you should stop him!
How could you allow that?
Is this how you handle things?
How can I trust you with anything?
You didn't trust me with
the movie entirely.
Are you... blaming me now?
Tae Soo.
Now that I see you today,
you sit really tall, yeah?
You are even taller than I am!
Let's have an election that is
clean, honorable, and free of bribery.
Just like the color white,
which represents One Heart.
In particular, do not spread lies
about a candidate's past.
My strategy is to be mysterious.
Just like the color purple.
Candidates, your eyes
are quite scary right now.
A clean election starts with... a smile!
Oh, Madam asked me
to take pictures of you.
Please come forward and shake
hands with each other.
Okay.
Okay. Ready...
Please shake hands.
Shake hands.
Smile... one, two, three!
I'm over here.
What is this place?
Why do you ask when you already know?
By the way, did you clean
it up for a guest?
Or did you clean it up to hide something?
You may not know,
since it's Gi Bum's hideout.
Geez, there you go again.
Say it in a way that I can understand.
I believe there's something
between you, Gi Bum and Mr. Son.
Here, Baek Gi Bum was...
Someone reported that he
worked on Mr. Son here.
I should have had forensics work on it.
Then I would have
already gotten a gift box.
What do you think?
Think about what?
Then bring Baek Gi Bum here and ask him!
That brat has his almighty dad
in his back pocket. How can I do that?
What I need is a witness.
Bro, what am I, a woman's heart?
Stop trying to look into it.
You better bring me evidence!
Okay?
I'm a busy man.
Don't trust Baek Man Bo and Baek Gi Bum!
Lots of loyal dogs like you
have gone to jail for them.
I'm worried you might end up like that.
Dad!
What are you listening to?
Wow, what a beautiful voice.
Why don't you listen at home?
It's cold.
Is it because of Mom?
You haven't decided yet?
My head is spinning.
Geez.
My head is about to explode too.
Cold air is the best thing
at times like these.
Should we keep taking in this cold air
and just freeze to death?
Okay.
Nonprofit foundation?
Yes, a nonprofit foundation.
That's slight overkill.
We're just a group of volunteers--
That kind of mindset kept One Heart
from growing in the past five years.
What's your point?
Think about it.
It's hard to make a living these days.
We can help the members
buy a house with a loan.
And for families with kids in schools,
we can set up scholarship funds.
Helping others is all well and good.
However, the real growth should start
with benefiting our own members.
Wow, why haven't we ever thought of that?
Do Kyung, that is a great idea!
Ladies, you all agree, right?
Right?
Kyung Mee! Kyung Mee!
You're being too obvious.
What about your friendship with Eun Ok?
Geez, you have no idea.
I'm trying to survive, myself.
If only my husband were better...
Did Manager Change get in trouble again?
It's not like that.
I'm just saying life is hard...
Bye.
Okay.
Okay, what you said was
really intriguing to me too.
But can you keep all of your promises?
You won't be able to do those
things without the chairman's help.
I don't need him. I have Director Baek.
Hey, Lee Do Kyung!
It was just yesterday when we
shook hands on a clean election!
Do you really need to
involve your ex-husband?
Eun Ok, you're being old-fashioned.
Did I cheat? Did I speak badly about you?
In an election, I can use anyone
who will help me to win voters.
That's how elections work.
Fair play, okay?
Thank you.
I told you I didn't feel like eating.
You need to eat when it's time to eat,
even if you don't feel like it.
Okay.
Please sit here.
Okay, sit right here.
Did you wait long?
Are you hungry?
I already ordered.
The one with
lots of cheese, your favorite.
Oh, man! My son knows his manners!
See how sweet he is to you?
Let's eat. The food is getting cold.
In my opinion, I am the only one in
our family who needs to do better.
Everyone else is doing a good job.
Sung Min is good... you are good...
Just forget my mom.
And Soo Min will do better
when she gets older.
Oh, my! I forgot.
It's time to go pick up Soo Min.
Well... enjoy your date
with your son, okay?
I will be back soon.
I am sorry for having
disappointed you and Dad.
I'm sorry I didn't tell
you about me doing music.
I will study hard
during my last year as you wish.
I'll study hard for my goal.
Sung Min!
You made the right decision!
You are my son, indeed!
In return...
I want to major in music composition.
What?
I will go to Seoul University as
you wish, but as a music major.
Are you crazy?
Music can be your hobby!
After you get a good job and
make loads of money, buy a nice guitar!
You can do whatever you want.
I won't stop you then!
Mom...
I am serious.
This is the best scenario,
for both you and me.
Sung Min...
Think about your dad,
who loves you so dearly.
So he can be proud of raising you.
So he can be proud of you.
Dad said... he would support me
no matter what I choose to do.
Dad!
Are you done?
- Bye.
I'm a bit late. Let's go.
Man, kids have hard
lives these days, right?
They study until this late, and then
do homework when they get home.
You're right.
When we were little, we would just
play baseball and run around.
Yes, it was good back then.
Do you like baseball?
Baseball?
I'm sick and tired of it.
Dad!
Hey!
- I told you to speak English!
- Okay.
How was your class today?
Grammar was a bit difficult.
- Really?
- Yes.
Don't worry. I will teach you
some grammar when we get home.
- Okay.
- Okay?
How many words did you memorize?
What a bunch of bullshit.
Hey! Hey!
Hey, come on, baby! Come on!
Come on, baby!
Baby, come on!
What's wrong with him?
Ms. Yoon! Ms. Yoon!
Ms. Yoon! Hey!
Hey! Come on! Come on!
I was so embarrassed that
I couldn't take this out at cram school.
Look at this, Dad.
Mom didn't even apologize to me.
Does that make sense?
I know. Just let it go.
I have the worst phone
in the whole school.
My friends have the newest phones,
while mine has a broken screen!
It's super slow and the
touch screen doesn't work.
What should I do, Dad?
What's wrong?
Welcome!
Sit down here and have some chicken.
I'll be right back.
But I'm not hungry.
Well, I want to have some.
Don't come out at any cost.
If I don't come back within
20 minutes, call your mom.
Okay.
Who the heck are you?
What is this about?
My touch screen...
My cell phone...
[Keep us safe today.]
My goodness!
Geez.
Hey, kid.
He followed me from Soo Min's
cram school last night.
Boss, I dug into Manager Ma.
Sounds like the chairman called
the guys from Cheongjoo.
What? Cheongjoo?
Yes, what would he call them here for?
He would always call us,
dirty work or clean work.
Boss, I'm a bit suspicious
of the chairman.
If it's really those guys,
you never know what they'll do.
This is Yoon Tae Soo.
I'm calling from Soo Min's cram school.
Her mom isn't answering her phone.
Did Soo Min come home?
What do you mean?
What happened to that?
That's my question.
How did that happen?
I don't know!
It was already like that
when we came in.
Geez, when I saw that...
My heart is still beating so hard.
Are you okay, Madam?
Should I get you some medicine?
Please be honest, Eun Ok.
Did you want to win that much?
What are you talking about?
I really don't know anything.
Madam, please stop.
I don't want others to find out.
It's embarrassing.
I'm in charge of the election.
I'm the most embarrassed one here.
Not only the election, but also
One Heart has been disgraced.
Madam, what evidence do
you have against me?
Who else is there that would
do something like this?
Your phone is ringing.
I'm sorry, Honey--
What?
What is it now, Eun Ok?
I have to go now.
Explain it before you go.
Otherwise you're admitting you did this.
I have to go.
What happened to Soo Min?
She was going to see a movie
with a friend after cram school.
But she didn't come
and we can't reach her.
What?
Sung Min's thing was only a few days ago.
Now what's happening?
What about Sung Min?
He went to see Soo Min's friends.
Did you talk to them?
A friend of hers saw her talking
to a man at the bus station.
Man? What kind of man?
Calm down.
Honey, could it be those guys?
Soo Min!
Soo Min! Soo Min!
Soo Min! Yoon Soo Min!
Soo Min!
Sorry. I need to report a missing child.
I can't find my child!
Wait a moment.
- What?
- Where was it?
Well...
Excuse me! Please let me
report a missing child.
I can't find her. She's a sixth grader.
Soo Min! Soo Min!
Soo Min!
Tae Soo.
Now that I see you, you sit tall.
You look even taller than I am!
The chairman called
the guys from Cheongjoo.
What brings you here at this hour?
Mr. Chairman, I need to check something.
Check what?
We can't reach Soo Min.
Where did you daughter go?
Mr. Chairman!
Are you questioning me?
Is that why you came here?
Tae Soo, I know you are
desperate for your daughter.
But how can you doubt me?
Your daughter is like
my own granddaughter!
Yeah.
Boss, we found the guy who did it.
Where's Soo Min? Where's my daughter?
How would I know?
You had me followed.
You got the wrong person!
Your guy fessed up.
I really don't know!
How dare you! Where is Soo Min?
I asked you, where is she?
You said I would be full of regret.
Is this what you plotted
with that swindler?
What are you talking about?
Make it easy for me to understand.
Gi Bum, how can you do this to me?
We do dirty work but we also
have a rule we call the bottom line.
That bottom line is to
not touch our families!
You want to know what happens
when you don't follow the rule?
I will show you clearly! You bastards!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Sweet Savage Family]
He's gone mad!
It's only a matter of time
before Tae Soo gets to us!
He wants us out of this house.
What have you done to me?
Don't be upset. What's done is done.
No matter what, you are my
son and I'm your father.
- What makes you so confident?
- Let's talk.
- Don't touch me.
- Don't say that.