Subtitles by the DramaFever
If I can't free myself this time,
I'll be tied down forever.
I'll always be their dog!
Whatever price I have to pay
to become a human being, I'll pay it.
Honey.
I can't take this anymore.
I feel like I'm going to die.
You've broken my heart into pieces.
"After this time, it'll get better."
"After this passes, it'll be okay."
That's how I've lived for twenty years.
I have no heart left
with which to feel anxiety.
I can't live like this.
How can you lay down
your weapon during a war?
I've been preparing for this
from the very beginning.
I'll be out soon.
Why did you bother coming here?
You won't be able to get out.
I met with the chairman.
Give it to me. The recorder.
That's the only way you're getting out.
I've thought about this a lot.
If you keep this up, our kids' blood,
my blood... it'll all be on your hands.
If that's the only alternative
then I would rather live separately
from one another.
Eun Ok! Eun Ok! Eun Ok...
Eun Ok! Eun Ok! Eun Ok!
Eun Ok!
I've been preparing for this
from the very beginning.
I'm prepared to sacrifice
whatever I need to.
- Mother?
- Yeah?
What are you doing?
The exterminators are here.
They're spraying the second floor.
Exterminators?
I got chewed up by those red ants,
you know. I was suffering!
I had them spray every room!
They said it was free, so I let them in.
They came on their own?
Yeah!
But how could you just let
strangers into the house?
You should've watched them, at least.
He told me to stay away,
because the chemicals are toxic.
He locked the door.
He's been in there for quite some time.
It's a free service,
but he's really thorough supposedly.
What?
It's all done.
- You don't need to worry anymore.
- Thank you!
Bye.
Wait a second.
What's the name of your company?
Well, we're brand new.
You wouldn't have heard of us.
I'm sorry, but do you have any
identification I can take a look at?
I'm just trying to be cautious.
Oh... hold on.
Did I bring my card?
- Eun Ok!
- Hey!
- Eun Ok.
- Who are you?
Oh, my! What just happened?
Sung Goo, catch him!
You have to catch him!
Stop right there!
Geez...
Sung Goo, what happened?
Geez, I couldn't catch him.
Who were they, anyway?
They were exterminators, supposedly,
but they were very suspicious.
I think the chairman sent them.
He did?
This is serious.
Yoon Tae Soo, you have a visitor.
Geez, you look like
you're suffering, boss.
Are they feeding you all right in there?
This isn't the time
to worry about my meals.
The chairman must really
be pressuring Eun Ok.
It must be seriously bad
if she's asking for a divorce.
But maybe she's right.
Why not just give them
the recorder and be done with it?
Do you know what just happened?
Some guys came looking for the recorder.
They pretended to be exterminators.
I chased them off after Eun Ok
got suspicious. Your family is in shock.
What? Did anyone get hurt?
Luckily, no.
This is an endless battle!
Just give him the recorder
and be done with him!
You need to get out of here!
Boss, please!
Sung Goo.
I need you to do something for me.
Oh, how long has it been?
You've been well, right?
Is something wrong?
Why don't you sit down?
What is this?
That's what I would like to ask you!
[SEPTEMBER 10: 1.5 MILLION WON,
SEPTEMBER 13: 3 MILLION WON]
What are you trying to do?
Are you trying to ruin my election?
Of course not, Assemblyman.
There must have been a mistake.
You need to resolve this immediately.
Yes, Assemblyman.
I'll take care of this right away.
Congratulations on your election.
[FIVE YEARS AGO]
That should be enough
to buy a few buildings.
Buildings in this area,
or in Seoul, you mean?
You'll be working in the capital now.
Of course I mean Seoul.
Chairman Baek Man Bo.
You and I, Jang Gook Han,
are now in the same boat.
From now on,
I will take care of Choong Shim.
Tae Soo! You piece of...
Tae Soo.
Why are you still here?
Well, fortunately, you came
before I could send out the recording.
Tae Soo, what's wrong with you?
Let's talk it out. Talk.
You and I, we go way back.
I'm a stupid guy.
If had used this weapon of mine sooner
you would not have sent
visitors to my house.
What are you talking about?
Make it easy for me to understand.
Mr. Chairman.
From now on, think of me as a mine.
And I'm a mine
in the center of a mine field.
You really better
stay away from that mine.
If you don't step towards the mine,
you have no chance of striking anything.
Let us go our separate ways.
Then, no one will get hurt.
Mr. Chairman, first, I need to get out.
What?
If I don't get out,
you're coming in here too.
Honey, I'm back.
How did you get out?
How? I walked right out, of course.
Do we have any tofu?
To cast away bad luck!
Let's talk in the room.
Soo Min will be home soon.
Tell me the truth.
How did you get out?
Who helped you get out?
The chairman came and got me out himself.
He did?
Why did he do that?
It all worked out, and I got out.
Your husband is a capable man!
You can't see that I'm not
in the joking mood?
I'm not either!
I heard that strange
people came to our home.
I warned him of the consequences,
and so it won't happen again.
You don't need to worry about a thing.
No.
Give it to me first.
Give me the recorder.
Honey!
I can't live with a ticking time bomb
in my home! Give it to me!
I got out because I had that recorder!
That's why I can't give it to you.
Are you going to put us in danger again?
I wasn't joking when I said
that we should get a divorce.
Yes.
It was a warning, partially.
I felt the need to do it.
But...
Have I ever been like this before?
Geez, I know. I know this!
You were always on my side,
no matter what I did.
That's why you should listen to me!
This isn't just about trying
to break a rock with an egg.
Please, honey?
Just give him the recorder
and be done with him. Please?
Geez, I'm sorry, Eun Ok.
Eun Ok, please!
Geez.
Where are you going?
I'm moving in with Do Kyung.
I'll come back
for the rest of my stuff.
Aren't you past the age
of running away for a girl?
Do you know what I just went through?
Do you know what your
granddaughter went through?
She was stalked by some creep, for years,
and she came to Daejeon to avoid him!
She wanted my protection!
As her father, I had no idea.
I lived without worry for
all of these years.
I won't do that anymore.
She will be by my side!
I will protect her!
The moment you leave this house
you will be giving up
your title, and your wealth.
What an idiot...
Without money and power,
you aren't a father, or a man.
Without money,
you're just their burden.
You better realize that
before you make any decisions!
Dad, is that really the only leverage
you choose to use to keep your son?
Right.
That's all you have.
You wanted to see me, Sir?
Mr. Hong.
What's wrong with you?
I told you to conduct a treasure hunt,
not a game of hide and seek.
This is all you got, huh?
I'm sorry, Mr. Chairman.
I'm bleeding from Tae Soo's whip.
I thought you'd be a good fit to replace
Tae Soo, but I guess I was wrong.
I'm not sure if you've had
any real chances so far.
But this, here, is definitely
a once-in-a-lifetime chance for you.
I can guarantee it. Understand?
Yes, Sir.
This is making me go crazy.
Pee sitting down.
What? Why?
For hygiene, and for good health.
For heath?
Listen, that's our house rule.
And don't forget to wash your hands
before you leave the bathroom.
Oh, Dad's snoring is really bad.
That can't be controlled.
Give the guy a break.
Okay.
I cook. Hyun Jee washes the dishes.
I need you to be in charge
of the grocery shopping.
Sure, sure. I love shopping.
Oh, the most important thing.
- Huh?
- You barged into my room earlier.
I hope that won't happen again.
Good manners, please.
Hyun Jee, I'm a gentleman.
Gentleman!
While you're here,
please maintain proper etiquette.
Respect one another's privacy.
And don't come into my room
if you don't have a good reason to do so.
What? Then where will I sleep?
- Here.
In the living room? By myself?
You better not have
any expectations set for me!
I'm letting you stay here
because you want to protect us.
I have no other intentions.
If you change your mind,
you can leave at any moment.
No, no, no! Of course not!
Well, I'll just be sleeping here then.
It's great!
What is this?
Who knew that I would
be sleeping alone, even here?
Geez!
I miss my king size bed!
Geez.
Our whole family is here!
This feels wonderful!
Don't get me started.
We were invaded by thieves
while you were gone.
Thieves are getting smarter these days.
They fooled me!
They told me it was a free service!
So, now, hopefully you'll remember
to not let any strangers into the house!
Everyone should remember that.
Everyone should be careful.
By the way, you didn't
get us any Christmas gifts.
Christmas passed a long time ago!
That's why he should speed it up!
I have no shoes to wear!
Geez, that's my daughter.
Be patient. I'll keep my promise.
Well...
Listen.
I have something to tell you.
You would've found out eventually anyway.
So, I thought I should tell you
when we all gathered as a family.
You already know, Mom.
Sung Min, Soo Min.
And you, Eun Sil. Listen carefully.
I...
I left Choong Shim.
Then... what will you do now?
Are you unemployed now?
Unemployed? Of course not!
Have you ever seen me slack off?
Then?
I do promotions and deliveries.
I have multiple jobs.
Wow. Then you must
make more money, right?
Well, that's great.
I was always worried sick about you.
I bet you left Choong Shim
so you could do great things!
Then what about the movie?
You'll keep working on it, right?
I won't be involved in anything
related to Choong Shim.
Also, we have to leave this house.
Well...
We'll move out soon.
We'll move into a small house for now.
But I'll make sure that
we buy a big house soon!
It may be a bit inconvenient.
But please, be understanding.
Okay?
How embarrassing!
He should just stick
to the movie business!
Be quiet.
You'll hurt his feelings.
I don't care! I won't have my own room
if we live in a small house.
My goodness! Tae Soo!
How can I mooch off of you now?
You'll have to work yourself to death!
What are you doing, Grim Reaper?
Come and get me, please!
Please calm down.
I'm more worried about my sister.
What about her?
A wife suffers when her husband suffers.
My goodness...
Ta-da!
Wow, it's so pretty!
Do we really have to do this?
Matching scarves would be enough.
Of course! We have to!
We kiss! Couples rings are a must!
Please.
You're blushing. Now you look
like the real Yoon Sung Min.
You know how long it's been since
you've acted like your real self?
What?
You've been so distracted lately.
You were really worried about your dad.
My dad came home.
What? Really?
Why are you just telling me this now?
I forgot about it.
What a relief.
It must have been hard on you.
I felt really bad.
I felt responsible for
what happened to him.
Oh, I wrote a new song.
Do you want to check it out inside?
Where?
Your house?
It's too cold.
Let's go inside. It's cold.
- But...
- It's cold! So cold!
Do you like that
new famous British singer?
Hyun Jee!
Dad!
You're home?
Aren't you going to work?
Huh? I took the day off.
What brings you here, Sung Min?
Do you come here often?
There are only women in this house.
No, it's not like that.
I invited him over because
I had something to show him.
You should behave respectfully,
like a gentleman, Sung Min.
You know how precious she is to me.
If you get caught
doing anything funny...
Sung Min isn't you! He's not like that.
And don't you remember
how he saved my life?
You should thank him
instead of being like this.
Let's go, Sung Min.
Hyun Jee, would you like some snacks?
What should I make?
"I can't lie. I want to hold you."
I've been wanting to finish
this song, but it's hard.
Give me that. I'll try.
"I'm holding myself for you, but..."
I've never seen this before. Is it new?
My dad gave it to me.
Oh, it looks nice.
- It suits you.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
Dad!
I wasn't peeking.
I brought you fruits.
You should knock on the door, then!
Why were you just staring at us?
That was just...
Sung Min.
Yes?
Be good to Hyun Jee.
Yes.
What were you doing?
Go!
Go! Get out! Get out. Get out.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
What is it now?
Just leave it open. Okay.
Geez.
Hello!
Did the assemblyman calm down a bit?
What do you want?
Oh... well...
I would like to make
a donation to his office.
That won't work.
The assemblyman told me to keep
my distance from Choong Shim.
Sir?
Madam Oh!
What?
He's been missing this entire time?
Yes! He hasn't come home.
And his phone is off.
Think. Can you think of anything?
I wonder... if he went back to Seoul?
I tried calling his home in Seoul.
They said he didn't come there either.
Producer Lee wouldn't have met
with the chairman, right?
The chairman doesn't know anything.
There's no sign of that yet.
Right. If he had found out,
we wouldn't be alive right now.
That's why I told you to be careful.
You kissed me first,
then you hugged me... oh, forget it.
By the way, is it okay for you
to be out at this hour?
Stop using the script as an excuse!
He'll get suspicious of you.
I was so anxious.
I had to get out of the house.
Please get up, now.
Okay? I think it'll be best for us
to not see each other for a while.
Let's go.
Oh, my!
Madam Oh!
Mr. Chairman!
What's the matter?
Oh... I feel dizzy.
Oh no!
Madam Oh.
Where were you, so late at night?
Were you working on the script?
Don't talk. I'm worried your
blood pressure might go up again.
I'm fine now, now that you're here.
Please don't say that.
It's not like I'm a doctor.
Dr. Kim will be here soon.
To me, you're the doctor
and the medicine.
Mr. Chairman...
Madam Oh.
Do you know what I thought about
while I was collapsing earlier?
I thought I was about to die,
lonely, without anyone.
What?
You weren't here.
Gi Bum wasn't here either.
The thought that I was alone in this
big house made me feel so lonely.
That's why you really need
a family as you get older.
You don't have Tae Soo now.
If you lose Gi Bum,
you will be really alone.
I have you, Madam Oh.
Of course, I'm here with you.
But he's still your blood.
You'll feel real security
from having your son right beside you.
He left the house on his own.
He chose the difficult path, himself!
Why would you make your son suffer?
What if he never comes back?
He won't even last a month.
Please don't be like that.
Give Do Kyung and her daughter a chance.
Isn't it much better to take in
a daughter in-law and a granddaughter,
than to lose a son?
Mr. Chairman, in this house...
you are too lonely.
Geez.
When I'm feeling sick and weak...
What is my son doing?
Oh, man!
Are you okay?
Huh? Oh, kitchen towels! Kitchen towels!
Ah... oh, hot! Hot!
They didn't burn.
You must be tired.
Drink this, rest a little bit.
Okay. Thanks.
Tell me the truth.
You regret it, right?
What do you mean?
Looking at you these days...
I wonder if I've made you suffer
by allowing you to stay with us.
You can go back if you want.
No, no! I really like it now.
But I don't.
Huh?
I wanted a strong fortress for Hyun Jee.
Not a house maid.
Do Kyung, that's...
Gi Bum, I'm really curious
about your plans for the future.
I don't need your empty words,
that you'll protect Hyun Jee and I.
Show me more concrete,
realistic ways to do that.
Yeah... I...
Boss! Boss!
You should go home now.
Why should I?
I just moved out.
Well, the chairman is sick.
Well, then I really shouldn’t go.
He'll get sicker if he sees me.
Boss, he told me to bring you home.
I said forget it!
You should go.
Forget it. He's faking it.
Whether he's faking it or not,
he says he's sick.
Going is the right thing for you to do.
Hurry up.
Dad! Dad...
Dad.
Are you really sick?
Did you think I was faking it?
His blood pressure spiked up.
Why? What happened?
Tae Soo got me.
You got me.
An old man can't handle these things.
I collapsed from the stress,
and from high blood pressure.
But there was no one in the house.
What about Madam Oh?
You didn't come home last night?
Of course that's not what happened.
I went to the office
to work on the script...
Are you living for this movie?
Is the movie more
important than his life?
If I'm not home, you should
step up to the plate. Isn't that right?
What did the doctor say?
Are you okay now?
He told me to retire.
Huh?
He says, I should retire and rest.
I do listen to my doctor.
Your era has come, Gi Bum.
It's time for you to lead Choong Shim.
Can you do that?
Dad.
I can just sit back now
and be an old man.
I'd humiliate myself if I kept going.
Gi Bum.
Do you know that Tae Soo is trying
to corner me with the recorder?
Recorder?
Whenever he would accompany me
to meetings with old guys and bosses
he would record everything for evidence.
He's trying to destroy
Choong Shim with it.
What?
What's on it?
This, and that.
But the biggest issue
is Assemblyman Jang.
You mean Assemblyman Jang,
who is running for Presidency?
He changed the status
of our company land for us!
Geez, this is serious.
You mean...
Tae Soo has evidence that you
gave bribery money to Assemblyman Jang?
That's right.
Why did you leave that
important thing with Tae Soo?
Back then I couldn't trust
Assemblyman Jang.
But I thought of Tae Soo as my own son!
You brought this upon yourself.
You reap what you sow!
Who will own all of this when I die?
You could lose all of
the wealth you're worth!
Gi Bum, get that recorder from Tae Soo.
It looks like a pen that
you can wear on your clothes.
If you do that...
I'll adjust my thought process about
you getting back together with Do Kyung.
What's there to think about?
I'm already living with her!
How long will you be able
to live with them with no money?
They won't like you very much
if you have no money!
Now that you put it that way...
I can finally see my plans
for the future!
Boss! Did you hear about the bars?
Geez, do I really have to
worry about them, at my rank?
Talk to Tae Soo. He's in charge...
Oh, he left.
Everything is a huge mess now.
Since Tae Soo left,
all of the bars are out of control.
One bar in Eunhaeng-dong
hasn't paid us in months!
What?
You take care of the bars for now.
Pardon? Me?
Do it right.
Do it right so that no one
asks for Tae Soo again, okay?
Yes! Thank you!
Thank you, Boss!
I will do a good job!
Wow!
The medicine my son
bought for me tastes so sweet!
You deliver milk in the morning.
You hand out flyers and do deliveries
for a supermarket in the afternoon.
And you clean a spa at dawn.
When do you sleep then?
What's the point of sleeping more?
You'll sleep forever when you die.
It's hard, right?
Don't look at me like that.
You know what?
I really like it now.
Even though it's hard,
and I'm hungry, I like it.
I just like how it is now.
Oh? What is that ring?
Huh?
- Oh...
- You!
Did you get rings with your girlfriend?
It's not like that.
I'm fine with it, but don't
let your mom see that.
Also, don't get distracted
from your school work, okay?
Of course not. I'm your son!
Oh, get out of here now.
You'll be late for cram school.
Okay.
Oh.
Here, Dad.
Don't work too hard. I'm going.
Okay. It's cold. Stay warm, okay?
Go!
Yes, Home Mart Deliveries?
Okay, yes, I'll be there within the hour.
Come on in, Tae Soo.
Hey, what's up?
Do Kyung let me live with them.
Oh, I see.
Congratulations.
It's cold outside. Have some tea.
I got it ready for you.
You drink the tea.
Tae Soo, just five minutes.
I'm a busy man. Can't you see that?
Then three minutes. One minute!
Okay, what is it?
Tae Soo, our era has finally come!
My dad wants to hand it over
to me, and sit down for good.
The dream we had at 20
is about to come true!
Choong Shim's twin towers!
The two pillars of Choong Shim!
The two of us will lead Choong Shim!
- Really?
- Yes!
That's great! I feel like dancing now!
Did you think I would say that?
I left Choong Shim,
and I'm living just fine.
But you enjoy the throne!
If this is about the recorder,
don't even think about it.
I told him, all he needs to do is leave
us alone, and nothing will happen.
Don't you know what my dad is like?
He makes anything happen
once he puts his mind to it.
The recorder will fall into
my father's hands eventually.
Don't waste your energy!
Pass it over while you have the chance!
I'm saying this as your friend.
Dad was eating cold bread and milk
in the car without the heater on.
Mom, I don't know what's
going on between you and Dad.
But I just wish you would
make him feel at ease.
What is it? I'm busy now.
Don't be like that.
I came to say thank you.
Because you chose to pursue a new life,
I got all of the good positions you had.
I guess I shouldn't
call you boss anymore.
Anyway, call me the Knight of Nights!
Man, don't laugh like that.
You're making me upset.
I would let it go, if you
were my boss. But not now.
Don't you think so, Yoon Tae Soo?
Bub Gyu, I'm saying nicely, just go.
Oh! How scary!
You look scary!
Listen to what this
delivery boy is saying!
"I'm saying nicely, just go."
You sound more like a gangster
than a delivery boy!
I know you're just trying to
provoke me so that I use my fists.
But it won't work. Just go.
Don't be like that, huh?
It's no fun when you're like this.
Maybe...
It's a lie that you beat up
18 guys at once, right?
Stop it. I'm busy.
I'm busy too!
Who isn't busy in Korea, right?
What's up with you, huh?
What are you doing?
Come here!
You really want me to let him go?
Do I look like a saint?
You don't know why he's doing that?
Yoon Tae Soo!
I won't leave you guys alone!
- What?
- I said, stop!
Boss!
If you act this way,
you're no different from him, okay?
You said you left Choong Shim.
You said you aren't a gangster!
You think everything is over
just because you said you quit?
Whether we break, or they break...
one of us is going to break!
They're not the kinds of people
who just let things go!
What's going on?
What's the matter, Mr. Chairman?
What... what brought you here?
You humiliated me!
Why do I keep having this dream?
It's driving me nuts!
You scared me!
Why? Are you scared
of the thought that you could die?
It's not that I'm scared...
Where have you been?
I was worried about you...
Don't do that!
You give me goosebumps!
Are you trying to get me killed too?
Madam Oh is the chairman's woman.
If you get caught, everything is over.
I won't be safe, just because
I know the truth. We'll all be dead.
I know.
I was struggling with the script so much
that I must have gone crazy.
Geez, I shouldn't have done that...
Are you saying now that you regret it?
I do! I regret it every waking day!
I regret it in the morning,
at night, and every minute of every day!
However!
What I regret the most, is that
I cannot escape Madam Oh's charm!
I thought you came to your senses!
Do you know how I agonized at the temple
after witnessing that shocking scene?
You were at a temple?
I went to a church too.
"Forget about the movie.
I have to run for my life."
Do you know why I came back,
even though I thought that many times?
It was for the movie.
I wanted to complete our movie.
Oh, Producer Lee.
So, you choose.
Madam Oh or the movie.
I can't choose!
Then, I have no choice.
I'll go tell the chairman.
Are you crazy? Are you trying
to save yourself by killing me?
Then you should choose.
Is it Madam Oh, or the movie?
Is it the woman or your life?
Ah!
Geez.
The movie director?
Wow!
Madam Oh from One Heart?
This painting has a hidden secret.
Secret!
Why did you ask me
to come here? It's cold!
That way, I can cherish
this moment later.
What is it that you want to say?
Say it quickly, so we can
go somewhere warm.
Let's break up.
What?
We have no choice.
We have to end it.
Is it because we got
caught by Producer Lee?
No. That can't be the true reason.
- It's because I want to survive!
- Like deer!
You said that's how we should live,
leaning on one another.
You said the kind of life one leads
outweighs the length of that life.
But there are too many days left to live.
I can't live, this young, without
being able to make a good movie.
At the very least,
I shouldn't die like a dog!
Please forgive my cowardice.
Forget me, Madam.
Okay.
Let's end it.
What?
It's the same for me.
I've felt so guilty, I haven't been able
to live with peace in my heart.
It's not that I wasn't
afraid of the chairman.
I just felt pathetic.
I'm everything to the chairman.
It wasn't right for me to do this to him.
Won't... won't you come to regret this?
I am sure...
I will regret it.
I will regret every day.
However...
Once I've left a man,
I never look back.
Goodbye, Mr. Director.
Bye.
Madam! Madam!
Madam!
Please don't forgive me!
Because of you, I was happy!
My Josephine!
Please be happy!
You have to be happy!
You didn't tell me you were coming.
Do I have to give you notice
before I come? Aren't we friends?
Do you want some tea?
Before that...
I want to give this to you.
What's this?
It's a gift from my pure, innocent heart.
What?
You know my husband
just on took an important job.
I thought about it,
and it was all thanks to you.
What do you mean?
Because of your support,
Director Baek came back to the company.
And because of that,
Bub Gyu got Tae Soo's job.
Do Kyung, thank you so much.
I told him, work hard! Work to death!
I didn't do anything.
You're being humble.
By the way, how was
your first night with him?
Well, actually, it isn't
the first night with him.
It's the second first night.
Don't be ridiculous.
It's not like that.
Gi Bum loves Hyun Jee so much,
he would give up everything for her.
So I took him in as her guardian.
Do Kyung.
That's what you think.
I bet Gi Bum doesn't think that.
He waited for you all this time.
You should accept him.
And, tell him good things
about my husband.
Open it.
Come on.
I'm here, Mr. Chairman.
Where the heck have you been?
I'm sorry. I couldn't face you
because I haven't succeeded.
I guess I've misjudged you.
How can you do great things
with that weak heart of yours?
You can do anything
for your family, can you?
Once you miss an opportunity,
you don't get it back!
I will succeed this time.
This is your last chance.
Yes.
Wow, what's this?
Mother, do you know how I feel now?
Let's say it's...
It's just amazing!
Get off now! Let me try it!
I don't want to. I won't.
What? Didn't you buy it for me?
I was kidding.
Mother, try it.
Sit on it?
Put your legs in there.
Both of them... like that.
And sit down.
Put your arms there. And...
Okay.
Wow, that feels great!
This is nice!
Mother, you're worried
about Tae Soo, right?
Yeah.
He quit his decent job,
during tough times like these.
What is he thinking?
I know.
We have to move into a tiny house.
Oh, my. That's why I came here.
You should talk to him, so that
he comes back to Choong Shim.
Are we strangers?
Why should we live like enemies?
Someone has to yield.
Gi Bum!
You're home, Eun Ok.
What are you doing here?
And what's that?
Eun Ok!
Gi Bum brought this as a gift!
Why did you do that?
That thing is a burden.
It's a New Year's gift.
And I thought of her.
Don't feel burdened.
I need to talk to you, Gi Bum.
- Mother, enjoy.
- Okay.
Did you come here about the recorder?
You're so straightforward.
I'm a bit appalled.
I'll be frank.
Eun Ok, just give it to me.
Don't make everyone suffer.
I don't even know where it is.
Don't be like that.
If you wouldn't know, who would?
Let me see what it looks like.
Well, it looks like a normal pen.
It's looks classy.
You put it on your clothes, like this.
See you later, Grandma.
It's cold outside. Stay warm.
I'm going out.
Hello.
Yeah...
"I can't lie. I want to hold you."
I've never seen this before. Is it new?
Dad gave it to me.
Oh... cool!
See you later.
Go on.
Huh?
What does it look like?
Eun Ok, I just realized I have
something very urgent to do.
I'll talk to you later.
Go on in.
Sir, I'm fine, really.
But it's not fine with me.
I didn't get to properly
thank you for saving Hyun Jee.
I just wanted to buy you
something nice, since I saw you today.
Give me two combos.
I'm a regular here.
Isn't it great?
Yes.
Well... do you have
something to say to me?
For now, eat.
Well, I have something to ask you.
Yeah?
How did you get out before my dad?
I mean at the police station.
Oh... That's right.
I wonder why that was...
Sung Min.
Your dad gave you a really nice gift.
Huh?
I mean the pen you carry
around with you. The classy one.
Can I take a look at it?
Why?
Hyun Jee seems
to want one just like yours.
But I can't find one
that nice in any store.
I see.
I'll be back.
Hello.
Eun Ok, I just realized I have
something very urgent to do.
Have some fruit.
Thank you.
Well, it looks like a normal pen.
It's looks classy.
You put it on your clothes, like this.
Here.
Oh.
Sir, excuse me for a moment.
Okay, take your call.
Mom.
Are you with Hyun Jee's dad now?
Yes, why?
Sung Min, don't give him your dad's pen!
Bring the pen home. Right now!
Okay.
Sung Min!
Mom, he took the pen with him.
What? Why did you give it to him?
I turned around while I was talking
to you. And he disappeared with the pen.
What is it?
What's so important about that pen?
I'll be back before 4 p.m.
Okay, don't worry.
Okay.
Oh, hey.
Where are you now?
I'm working. Why?
I have to see you now.
I have something to tell you.
I said I'm working.
Let's talk when I come home tonight.
Gi Bum took the recorder from Sung Min.
What?
What do we do now?
Let me park the truck.
What's wrong?
My brakes aren't working!
- Huh? No!
- Honey!
Honey!
Excuse me. Do you have
a patient named Yoon Tae Soo?
Yoon Tae Soo?
Eun Ok!
Sung Goo!
Luckily, it was a minor accident.
He tried to impress your mom with a gift.
He sent Mr. Chang to provoke you.
He met with Sung Min himself.
And he did this to you.
He got the recorder.
He must be dancing around now.
Dad! Dad!
What's all the noise? Calm down!
Is that it?
Yes, Dad!
I'm proud of you, Son!
Good job!
You did a good job!
So we lost.
No. Both sides lost.
What?
In this kind of war,
no one should win.
Honey, what do you mean by that?
How do you like it?
Does it write well?
Yes, I like it.
Dad, do you know Hyun Jee's dad
is living at her house now?
What?
I went earlier,
and he was wearing an apron.
Did he say anything to you?
Nope.
Well, let me borrow that pen for one day.
They say prevention
is the best remedy for disaster.
That really is true.
Did you...
You did a good job! I knew you would!
Go, go, Baek Man Bo!
What is this?
That's what I wanted to ask you.
What the heck did you bring me?
If you're listening to this now, it means
Gi Bum stole something from my son.
Shame on you!
You're listening too, Mr. Chairman?
I'm sorry for surprising you.
If you let me, I'd like
to end this, my way.
I should have done it sooner,
but I simply couldn't.
I wanted to take
the punishment and end it.
But I was worried
about you, and the kids.
But... it's time to do it.
This was something
I just could not avoid.
Are you sure...
you won't regret it?
Yes.
Mr. Chairman,
do you remember what I said?
I told you to keep
your feet out of the mine field.
You just struck a mine.
Now, I have no choice.
What the heck is he talking about?
Be quiet.
I realized a long time ago, that I should
pay the cost of living a brand new life.
It's my fault that I didn't
put that plan into action.
I'm taking the original
recordings to a reporter.
It'll be a big story in
tomorrow's newspaper.
It's time to end this ridicule.
Let's pay the prices for our sins.
Subtitles by the DramaFever
[SWEET SAVAGE FAMILY]
We came this far, risking our lives.
The whole nation will turn
upside down tomorrow.
What happened?
Why isn't it on the news?
I'm going to my grandpa's house.
My mom and Dad might get back together.
I'm sick and tired of them.
I can't stand the Baek family!
I can't see you anymore.
You have a real reason.
Is it about my parents and your parents?
Let's break up.
I was impulsive.
Say something.
Please kill me.
This is bad!
Director Oh, say something.
Director Oh will die! Please save him!
What?