I told you to keep your feet
out of the mine field.
You just struck a mine.
Now, I have no choice.
What the heck is he talking about?
Be quiet!
I realized a long time ago, that I should
pay the cost of living a brand new life.
It's my fault that I didn't
put that plan into action.
I'm taking the original
recordings to a reporter.
It'll be a big story in
tomorrow's newspaper.
It's time to end this ridicule.
Let's pay the prices for our sins.
You have to stop him now.
You need to find that reporter.
Check every newspaper.
How am I supposed to find him?
There are so many newspapers!
Are you going to just sit around
and let this happen then?
Tae Soo is trying to go to hell,
and he wants to take us there with him!
I got it.
Leave it to me for now.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 14]
Mr. Yoon?
Are you Reporter Kim Hyuk Soo?
- Yes.
- Hi.
What happened to your arm?
Oh, it's nothing.
Honey, give it to him.
We're depending on you for this.
We've come this far, risking our lives.
Here it is.
Of course, I know.
The country will be up in arms tomorrow.
I'll make sure that your courage
does not go wasted.
Please help us.
We're depending on you.
Honey, did we do the right thing?
I'm really nervous.
I feel uneasy.
It's only natural
for you to feel nervous.
In a few hours, our lives
will change completely.
But... no matter what,
let's not regret our decisions.
It's already out of our hands.
Geez.
Soon, my handsome husband
will be on TV once again.
It feels like yesterday, they coined you
a hero on TV for catching the deserter.
This time, you're the snitch.
You do lead a rough life.
Don't worry about me.
I've already been to jail.
Now that I think about it,
it was good practice for me.
The floor isn't that cold.
I don't even need this, honestly.
You must be proud.
But...
I'm worried about you.
You'll have to take care of
the family without me for a while.
I need to find a job.
I'll do anything.
I am sorry, Eun Ok.
Thank you for trusting me,
and for following me.
I really am sorry.
Make sure to explain the situation
to your mom and the kids
so they're not completely shocked.
And don't worry about me.
Okay.
Here. Drink up!
To my wife, whom I love
more than anything else in the world.
All right!
Even if the whole world turns upside down
tomorrow, I won't regret this.
Here.
Dad.
Hey.
You haven't gone to sleep yet?
You're still up.
Dad.
Can I talk to you?
Okay, I'll see you upstairs.
Let's get you into bed.
What's with this look on
my son's handsome face?
Is something wrong?
Dad.
I'm not a little boy.
Tell me the truth.
Was there a problem
because I lost the pen?
The pen that you gave me.
Geez, what are you talking about?
It's not like that.
Then what is it?
I need to know.
Okay.
You're not a child anymore.
You're an adult now.
You know that...
just like Hyun Jee's dad
my line of work
was not very reputable.
Shameful adults, we are...
I will pay the costs for my sins,
and I will start a new life.
Pay the costs?
It's something that I have to do.
So, for a while...
I won't be around.
Dad...
You and I are the only
two men in this family.
My son...
Please take care of...
your mom, and everyone else.
Okay?
[KEEP US SAFE TODAY.]
It's not here.
I don't see anything.
What's going on?
Why isn't the story here?
Is it going to be in tomorrow's paper?
No, he said it'll be printed right away.
Maybe he meant it'll be a TV story,
or he was going to publish it online.
No, I didn't see anything.
I already checked.
What the heck...
What?
He's on vacation?
He didn't mention that yesterday.
Why is he on vacation, all of a sudden?
Then give me his home phone number.
I need to talk to him!
But his cell phone is off!
Then give me his home address...
Hello? Hello?
What the heck?
Nice work, Director Baek!
I couldn't have imagined that you
would take care of it so quickly.
Well, this wasn't my doing.
With his knack for good judgment,
Reporter Kim is destined for success.
Oh, thank you.
I was listening to the recording
when Director Baek called me.
I knew, immediately, that this would be
very sensitive material to write about.
Director Baek, be sure to treat him well.
Of course.
We've already spoken.
Reporter Kim.
What are you doing?
Are you really a reporter?
Are you threatening him?
- You stay out of it.
- Huh?
You're a journalist. How could you
stab someone in the back like this?
You're no different than a gangster!
A journalist's conscience?
That's a good argument.
However, when I thought
about my family...
It didn't matter that much.
Also, nothing would change anyway.
Reporter Kim!
It's best to avoid a fight that
you have no chance of winning.
At your age, you can't
run on passion.
Tae Soo, did you hear that?
No matter how hard you try,
you can't escape our grip.
My dad is furious.
You're in big trouble.
Please go inside.
The editor-in-chief is waiting for you.
This is Yoon Tae Soo.
Manager, what do you mean?
I don't have to come anymore?
You missed several days' work.
We already found someone.
You should go home.
I'll mail you your last check.
You told me you would excuse my absence!
Why are you doing this, all of a sudden?
Is there a real reason
you're not telling me?
Geez, I'm a really busy man!
Manager!
Mr. Yoon Tae Soo.
Why didn't you tell me
you worked for Choong Shim?
They keep sending people
here to bother me.
We really don't want to get
involved with Choong Shim.
Well...
Nice!
Did something good happen?
It seems that Gi Bum
is finally displaying his worth.
Come again?
He tamed a crazy horse
with just one hard grip!
If you want to praise
Director Baek, do it properly.
Not just with your words.
What do you mean?
Please grant his wish.
Why don't you meet with Lee Do Kyung?
Please?
Hyun Jee! Hyun Jee!
Dad! What are you so excited about?
Hyun Jee, your grandpa invited you
and your mom to his house for dinner!
What are you talking about?
Oh, Do Kyung.
My dad wants to see you.
I know it's awkward for you.
But please, do it for me.
Why bother?
It's going to be really awkward.
Hyun Jee and I won't go.
I'm going.
I want to see Grandpa's house again.
Just like the old days.
Dad, tell Grandpa that
I'll be there, no matter what.
Hyun Jee.
Really?
Definitely.
Honey.
How did it go? Did you see Reporter Kim?
Yes.
What? Is it what we thought?
Seriously?
Geez, I ask to be punished,
but they won't help.
What kind of a world do we live in?
We risked our lives for that!
I'm going to protest in front of
Choong Shim, or the newspaper offices.
I can't let it end like this!
Calm down.
How can I calm down?
Even if they destroy me because of it,
I have to do something.
All I'm saying,
is that now is not the time.
They have every intention
of destroying us.
I already know.
That you got fired from Home Mart.
Geez. I'm so sick and tired of them!
What did we ever do to them?
I'm sick and tired of the Baek family!
I already know.
That you got fired from Home Mart.
Geez. I'm sick and tired of them.
What did we ever do to them?
I'm sick and tired of the Baek family!
Even if you get a new job,
you'll get fired almost right away.
Also, they'll try to kick us
out of the house soon.
What do we do now?
I'll get a job.
They won't do that to me.
I know how you feel.
But you should take care of the kids.
No matter the situation,
I'll bring home money.
Honey, you can't just say that.
We're in deep trouble right now.
I'll do my best to not
spend money from now on.
The kids should stop
going to cram school.
You can't do that!
You said that since they wont be getting
any inheritance, you need to study.
But we are in a different situation now.
Do you know what our cost of living is,
on a monthly basis?
Bills, groceries,
your mom needs money...
The kids' cram school fees
and their allowances...
The minimum is two million won per month.
I can't go to a hair salon or buy clothes
for myself without worrying about money.
When we move out of this house,
where can we really go?
We need at least two or three billion won
to put down a deposit on rent.
You have no job
and nothing to use as collateral.
We can't even get a loan!
Sometimes, I even contemplate
borrowing money from a loan shark.
This is not the time to worry
about the kids' cram school.
You often say we're standing
on the edge of a cliff, right?
Right now, that's exactly how I feel.
Sung Min.
I'm a pathetic father.
I feel ashamed, and I am sorry.
It's all so absurd...
yet, I can do nothing about it.
Sung Min, I wish...
I wish that you
will be different than me.
You can do the right thing
when you have power.
Only when you have power,
can you protect your family.
Sung Min, you're studying so hard.
So, you will do well.
You always have.
What are you doing up?
Eun Sil, your friend's father
owns a food company, right?
Do you still talk to her?
Yes, why?
Find out if they have any open positions.
They hire a lot of married women.
Eun Ok.
Young people who just graduated
from college can't find a job.
It won't be easy to find a job after
spending 20 years tidying up the house.
You're talking nonsense.
Either way, find out for me.
Why?
Are you nervous because
Tae Soo quit Choong Shim?
Then get into business.
Starting your own business
is the way to go.
Hi. I'm interested in getting a loan.
I'm a stay-at-home mom.
Collateral?
I have nothing.
I see.
I'm too old, I'm too inexperienced.
Geez, I can't find a job,
I can't get a loan...
Geez.
Mom!
Oh, Soo Min! How was school?
Good.
I saw her on the way.
She gave me a free one.
You didn't have to do that.
Give me this week's special.
Sure.
Soo Min must be happy.
Her mom is taking care of her at home.
Ma'am, how do you like your job?
I like it. It's pretty good to me.
I'm sorry to ask you this,
but how much do you make?
If I apply, can I start right away?
Why don't you ask the company?
Oh, of course. I'm sorry.
What was that? You want to work?
Well, I was just curious...
Hurry up. I'm really hungry.
What do we have at home?
I didn't go grocery shopping.
How about kimchi fried rice?
Yes! Your kimchi fried rice is the best!
It's way better than
anywhere around here.
- Really?
- Yes.
You'd make big money in front
of a cram school. Just not mine.
I said I would do it!
Geez! Boss!
Can you really support
your family by doing that?
I need to do what I need to do.
Boss, let's go to Seoul together.
What? Seoul?
Someone I know just
opened a club in Gangnam.
But he hasn't hired a manager yet.
He's offering twice as much as
what you made at Choong Shim.
Sung Goo!
I know. It's a fancy neighborhood.
It's a bit intimidating.
But you won't need to
worry about your family.
Do you want to be a gangster again?
What was the point
of leaving Choong Shim?
Don't come to me
offering things like that!
Boss!
Geez... I can't believe him.
"I love you!" "Thank you!"
Learn Chinese at
Mr. Wang's Chinese School!
"I love you!" "Thank you!"
Huh? What are you doing?
Director Bong. Producer Lee.
How did you find me?
You can't do this to us.
You threatened us into making this movie.
And then you left us, just like that?
I had no choice.
I understand why you did it.
But even your wife quit.
What are we supposed to do?
She did?
Our movie is falling apart.
Please help us, Mr. Yoon!
I'm really sorry, guys.
I'm no longer a part of Choong Shim.
You already know that.
Someday, I'll pay back
what I owe you guys.
Making a movie isn't child's play.
You guys are too much!
You are too much!
Mr. Lee, Mr. Lee!
How can you just leave us like that?
Director Bong!
Geez...
Hey, Sung Min!
What's up with you?
You don't take my calls,
you ignore my texts...
We just started dating.
But you're already ignoring me?
Oh, man! You're not even
going to try to give me an excuse?
Okay.
Since something wonderful
happened to me today
I will let it go, just this once.
Aren't you going to ask me what happened?
What is it?
I'm going to my grandpa's house.
He invited me and my mom to dinner.
If it goes well, my parents
might get back together.
I wanted to tell you
before anyone else!
I am sorry... but I have to go.
I'm not feeling well.
Are you sick?
Do you have a cold?
I don't think you have a fever.
Then, I'll take you home.
No, thanks. It's not that bad.
Okay then. Rest well at home.
Call me when you feel better.
Honey, I'm home.
Oh, you're home!
Welcome home.
You must be hungry.
Well, I was so busy that
I didn't have the time to eat.
Go wash your hands.
I'll get your dinner ready.
Ta-da!
Oh, it's kimchi fried rice!
You must be hungry. Eat up.
Oh, it looks good.
How is it?
It goes without saying
that I would not notice if someone
was dying right next to me.
This is a little taste of heaven!
Yeah?
Oh, by the way...
I heard you quit acting.
Oh? How did you know?
Well...
Director Bong and Producer Lee
came to see me earlier.
You're not going to regret it?
You really wanted to do it.
There's nothing to regret.
It's not like acting was my dream.
I did that to keep the house.
That's that.
So, there is something that
I want to do more than acting.
Huh?
Honey, why don't you quit your gig,
and start a business with me?
We have no money
with which to start a business.
Not too big. We can start small.
How about a food truck?
We can start with kimchi fried rice.
A food truck?
All you know is housekeeping.
How are you going to run a business?
I'm being serious.
Look at this.
I compiled this scrap book.
Huh?
I'm worried about you working
out in the cold all day.
Soo Min says mine is better than
the restaurant in front of her school.
I thought about it, and it's the perfect
thing that we can actually manage to do!
It's cheaper to buy a food truck
than it is to rent a store.
I have plenty of kimchi!
Wow, when did you make all of of this?
I'm worried about the table.
It might fall into the ground!
I tried. For someone
with culinary training
this isn't much, right?
Now that we're all sitting together...
we look like a true family!
What kind of family?
A quiet family.
Do Kyung, how is it?
Do you like the food?
Yes, Madam.
Do you like the food, Mr. Chairman?
Yep.
- Dad.
- Yeah?
Can you pass me the fish?
Huh? Oh, the fish! This fish!
Oh, here, eat the fish!
Grandpa, please.
Huh?
It used to be your job.
Hyun Jee...
Hyun Jee, I'll do that for you.
No, I don't want you to.
You always left bones. I only ever ate
the ones Grandpa would fix for me!
Grandpa, won't you do it for me?
I knew it. You're the best!
By the way, this house
hasn't changed one bit.
This table... and the cabinet over there.
You really remember all of that?
Yes. I think about
this place all the time.
That way, I won't forget.
With Do Kyung and Hyun Jee here...
This big house actually feels full.
It's like... finally,
our family is complete.
I need to talk to you.
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
Not you.
Sit down.
Do you have something
you want to say to me?
You raised your daughter well.
She grew up on her own.
I just cheered her on.
Move in here with Hyun Jee.
Pardon me?
It's better to gain a daughter in-law and
a granddaughter than it is to lose a son.
I will think about it.
And I'll let you know.
Okay. I hope you'll do it.
What I said last time...
I said that amidst my worries for my son.
Please erase that from your head.
If you live here, it will be pretty
uncomfortable for both of us.
But...
Let's try not to ruin it
like we did ten years ago.
I understand.
More than anything,
we need the lady of Choong Shim.
You should prepare for that,
starting tomorrow.
But you have Madam Oh.
If I suddenly emerge, wouldn't that
trigger some sour feedback?
I'll go with the flow.
That will be the best way to go about it.
In the end, it's all Gi Bum's.
So you should help him along.
He's still lacking.
I think Gi Bum goes underestimated.
He's a real, hidden gem.
He didn't receive
a lot of love and trust.
So he made a few mistakes.
But it seems, from now on,
he's going to be different.
I will help him with all of my might.
How is it? Does it look decent?
After all this cleaning, it's spotless.
Sung Goo spent big money to help us out.
Boss, am I a stranger to you?
He might have spent everything
he saved to get married one day.
Really?
Sung Goo, you might not
be able to get married then.
What are you saying?
I saved so much money that
I don't even know where to put it.
If I can't get married just
because I spent some money
then I must be pretty pathetic!
- Really?
- Yes!
Sung Goo must be a pretty capable man.
Wait, honey.
I think something is missing.
Huh?
Right! It's the name!
We don't have a name for the truck!
That's right! We forgot
the most important thing!
Wait a second.
Oh!
How about Gyeryong Mountain Fried Rice?
What is that? It sounds like
a place to get your fortune told.
How about Fry Fry?
Fry Fry?
Well, it's not bad.
But it sounds like a hair salon.
Does it?
Boss!
How about Gangster Fried Rice?
Yes! That sounds good!
Are you kidding me?
You can keep that name.
How about Tae Soo and Eun Ok's?
So annoying! Annoying! Annoying!
Who said you could use my name?
That's so embarrassing!
Change it! Change it!
You aren't the only Soo Min in Korea.
You should know that
it's quite honorable.
Geez! Never, ever!
Change it! Change it to Sung Min's!
Eun Ok, just change it to
Little Kiddo's Fried Rice.
I told you not to call me Little Kiddo!
Oh, my! What's wrong, my little puppy?
I love that name!
By the way...
Will this type of business work?
Of course!
Food trucks are popular these days.
If the food is good,
people will hear about it.
And the line will be miles long!
Trust me.
Really?
Then we'll get rich really soon, right?
We'll have to see.
You're getting ahead of yourself again.
It's Eun Ok's kimchi fried rice!
I can set my sights high!
Am I wrong?
Now that you started the business...
Do your best, so that you
won't miss Choong Shim!
You know what I mean, right?
Yes, Mom.
It's cold. Let's go inside.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
Soo Min, don't be upset.
I'm glad that it will do well.
We'll see, we'll see!
Dad, this is bad!
What do you mean?
Huh? Huh?
Oh, my!
Where did the truck go?
I don't know. I came out to
take a photo but it was gone.
Could someone have stolen the truck?
Who would steal a used truck?
Honey... perhaps...
I can't believe it.
Did the chairman order you to do it?
What are you talking about?
Did he tell you to steal my truck?
You've got the wrong person!
What would I do with that used truck?
How did you know it was a used truck?
Well... that's...
Well... you can't buy a new truck...
Geez, let go!
This is ridiculous!
Why are you treating me like a thief?
What did you say?
Look here, Mr. Yoon.
I'm not your underling.
Why are you treating me
like I'm your underling?
You brat!
Okay, go ahead. Hit me.
Hit me, hit me. Huh? Huh?
You...
Hey.
Bring me evidence. Real evidence.
Hyun Jee, Do Kyung!
All together in this house...
Let's live happily ever after!
You're in a good mood.
Can I help you with anything?
Not really.
It's so great that the two
of you got back together.
I am so happy for you.
Now, it's time to take
care of our business.
What business?
What do you mean?
You know, the chairman and I getting
married officially and reporting it.
You didn't forget that, did you?
Oh, that's right! My little brain!
I didn't know how brazen-faced
you actually were, Madam Oh.
Come again?
Think about it.
I bribed the reporter,
and therefore, I stopped Tae Soo.
That's how I earned this.
And it was Hyun Jee
who melted Dad's icy heart.
Honestly, what have you done, Madam Oh?
What? How can you say that?
I drove Kim Eun Ok out from One Heart,
so Do Kyung could become chairwoman.
You know that!
So, did she become chairwoman?
Director Baek!
Please get out.
Dad might see you.
Now, it's time to take
care of our business.
What business?
What do you mean?
You know, the chairman and I getting
married officially and reporting it.
You didn't forget that, did you?
Oh... what are you
doing here, Mr. Chairman?
Madam Oh...
Are you feeling all right?
You look pale...
Is it because of Gi Bum and Do Kyung?
Well...
That's been bothering me too.
Yeah?
I thought it would be good for Gi Bum
to get back together with Do Kyung.
That's why I was so insistent on it.
But now that I think about it...
I feel like it's a bit rushed.
You might not be ready for that yet.
But I really rushed you.
I'm afraid I might have
made it hard on you.
Madam Oh.
Yes, Mr. Chairman?
You always think about me first.
But I haven't been
very considerate of you.
Is there anything you want from me?
I told you many times.
As long as you stay healthy...
That's enough for me.
Gi Bum finally got the family he wanted.
Now, you and I should live
happily, traveling together.
Of course, we should do that.
[DIRECTOR BONG JIN WOOK]
If you're done, then I will...
Okay. Go take care of your business.
Okay.
I told you to stop calling me.
We shouldn't do this.
Why isn't he coming back?
It's so late.
I wonder if it's gone forever.
Don't say that.
Why don't you call your dad?
Sure, Grandma.
- Honey!
- Dad!
Did you find the truck?
What happened?
I haven't found it yet.
Who the heck did this?
Does he even know what
that truck means to us?
Oh my goodness!
Don't worry, Mom.
I said I would find it,
and I will find it!
Wait and see.
Give me three days. I'll find it.
Are you feeling better?
Something big happened at my grandpa's.
Aren't you curious?
Yoon Sung Min, I don't like
how you are these days!
You're ignoring my texts!
Okay, keep it up!
When I'm upset, you won't
be able to handle me!
[TURN OFF]
Why isn't he calling me?
Are you sleeping?
Come in.
Well...
Tonight is our last night
living together, just the two of us.
So, I want to sleep with you tonight.
Shall we?
Okay.
Dad is going to be so happy tomorrow.
Finally, the day he's been anxiously
awaiting, for you and him, is here!
Don't tease me. I'm moving in
there because you wanted to!
If you keep that up,
I'll cancel the move tomorrow!
No...
I think I put it somewhere here.
Please handle with care!
These are the ladies' belongings.
Be gentle with them.
This one! This one!
This one goes to that room over there.
Hyun Jee, that box is yours, right?
- Well, wait. Mom?
- Do Kyung?
- What?
- See that box?
Don't carry that. It's heavy.
Is that box mine or yours?
Yours are all in your room.
I already organized it.
- Thank you, Mom!
- You're welcome!
Madam Oh.
What are you doing in here all alone?
I just wanted to stay out of their way.
Oh, are you going out?
Did you forget?
I told you, it's the couples party!
Oh... no.
Get ready quickly.
Since we're going out, we could do
some shopping at a department store.
Or we could go to a book store
and get you some books.
Let's make it a date.
Oh... but...
I'm sorry, Mr. Chairman.
I'm not feeling well.
Can't you just go by yourself?
It's New Year's Eve.
I told you it was a New Year's party.
I would go if I didn't feel like this.
Please understand.
I want to rest.
I guess I have no choice then.
I'll be late.
Okay. Have a good time.
What? Someone stole the truck?
Geez, I'm about to go crazy!
I'm really upset and sad too.
But I have no one to talk to.
I thought you might have a solution,
so I asked you to come meet me.
Well, I'll try.
But if they stole it to get rid of it...
then there's nothing
that can be done now.
What are my sister
and Tae Soo going to do?
We bought that truck with
all the money we could find.
Can't you do something, Sung Goo?
Tae Soo lost his job
and we need to move out soon.
If we don't find that truck, all five
of us will be stuck sucking our fingers.
I'm living off of them right now.
So I'll have to go back to Seoul.
That can't happen!
Pardon me?
I mean...
Tae Soo's family of five shouldn't be...
stuck sucking their fingers.
Eun Sil!
I need you to come with me.
We need to talk.
Do you still have something to say?
We need to close our deal
about the marriage license.
Of course, I will report it.
Do Kyung and I will
report our marriage soon.
Please!
If you keep this up,
I will not simply sit back.
Then what will you do?
Are you threatening me?
Director Baek!
Madam Oh Sook Ja.
What would happen...
if my father found out the real reason
for why you're staying with him?
You should thank me for
keeping that secret of yours.
- Dad!
- Oh!
Let's go. What do you want to eat?
Mom and I want rice noodles.
Why don't you come with us,
since the chairman isn't home?
No, she's not feeling well.
Let's go, let's go.
What? I haven't done anything?
Now that you've gotten
what you want, you ignore me?
How dare you...
How dare you treat me this way!
Find the third volume of Dostoevsky’s
Crime and Punishment, page 69.
My dearest Madam.
While you are reading this letter...
I'm probably lying, broken-hearted,
not able to eat anything.
Madam, you were
my savior, and my Messiah.
Had it not been for you, I couldn't have
overcome the pain of artistic creation.
I would have ran away like a coward.
It's true though,
I'm in much greater pain right now.
But no matter what, I won't regret
my sweet memories with you.
You are my muse,
my persona, and my soul.
Madam, I have a favor to
ask of you, for one final time.
Please meet me one last time.
I'll live the rest of my life, cherishing
the moment we shared for the last time.
I am waiting to hear from you.
Director Bong, come right now!
At the very place where we first met...
Let's have our final moment together!
Madam Oh!
Director Bong!
I wasn't going to see you again.
However...
I couldn't say no to your
beautiful, hand-written letter.
What about the chairman?
Everyone is out.
We have a few hours.
Oh! Madam!
Director Bong.
How are you, Mr. Chairman?
Why are you here?
Didn't I tell you that
we had a script meeting?
The ending needs revision.
You came home early.
I think I have a cold.
I wanted to drink your herbal tea.
I guess I can't.
Why can't you? Should I make the tea now?
No, continue your meeting.
It seems that I interrupted you.
I can't go back and forth like this.
It's wrong of me to do this to everyone.
I'm sorry. I was impulsive.
No, I was the one
who was impulsive.
When the chairman and I
officially report our marriage
I will be his woman for life.
I can't see you ever again.
I know.
That's why...
I am trying to make one unforgettable
memory with you for the last time.
Director.
Madam.
You're still up?
It's past 3 a.m.
I can't sleep.
Alcohol only makes it harder
for you to fall asleep.
Madam Oh.
Are you happy?
Huh?
I am happy because of you.
But I wonder if you are happy at all.
What kind of question is that?
I have the joy of life because of you.
But you, I wonder if you would
rather wish for your own death.
You're being strange.
Are you drunk?
I am drunk.
I've lived my entire life drunk.
Go to sleep.
I'll be in the study.
I'll sleep when I feel sleepy.
What's this?
I bought you a scarf.
Why aren't you wearing it?
You're not wearing your ring either.
Why are you acting this way?
You ignore my calls and my texts.
I have something to say.
What is it? Say it.
Let me hear it.
I'm going to focus on studying.
In college, music will just be a hobby
I pursue in my spare time.
Okay, do that.
Having a job that is your passion
doesn't always make you happy.
Do it as a hobby.
I'll help you.
No.
I can't see you anymore.
What?
I'm going to study, only.
I have no time to see you.
Yoon Sung Min!
I understand that you want to focus on
your studies and that you can't do music.
But do you really have to do this?
I'm trying to have
enough time just to study.
Honestly, I've been too
distracted since I met you.
I regret it.
Tell me. What's the real reason?
Is this about our parents' relationship?
Bye.
Yoon Sung Min!
I said, leave me alone!
Sung Min!
Yoon Sung Min!
Come to your senses already!
You promised not to do this anymore.
I know. I know.
But I can't control my own heart!
You need to review these.
Who's calling at this hour?
Hello?
Who is it?
Chairman Baek Man Bo?
Yes, Mr. Chairman!
What is this about?
Yes, I understand. I will do that.
What did he say?
He has something to discuss
with me about investing in films.
What?
Is that it?
He didn't say anything else?
Do you wish that there was something?
I'm just a bit nervous for you.
When you go there,
don't even look at Madam Oh, okay?
You promised to move on.
You better only think about the movie.
Okay. I got it. I know that.
Madam!
Oh?
How could you come here without notice?
The chairman is here.
It's not like that!
The chairman told me to come.
The chairman called you? For what?
He said that he wanted to discuss
something about investing in films.
Wait, why are you here?
He told me to stay here.
He said he has something to show me.
Oh, no!
Say something.
I will decide what to do
with you after I hear it.
Open your mouth!
When it was just the two of you,
you were busy smooching!
Did you make a promise to not
open your mouths in front of me?
Mr. Chairman, please kill me.
Even though he threatened me,
using the movie...
I am worse than him!
I felt ashamed. I was afraid.
So I couldn't tell you. It's my fault.
I deserve to die.
Director Bong.
Yes?
Say something.
Mr. Chairman... it's...
It's not like that...
I just...
Is love...
Is love a sin?
What the heck...
Why is she asking us
to wait outside in the blistering cold?
Boss! Boss!
Geez.
What's this hunk of junk?
Boss, let's start with this.
Sung Goo, this truck is a bit...
You can't be picky.
Still, how can we sell
food in this truck?
Just trust us, Eun Ok.
- Fist bump!
Mr. Yoon!
Something bad has happened!
What's the matter?
Director Bong...
He's going to be killed!
You have to help save him.
Huh? What do you mean?
He said the chairman
was dragging him somewhere.
And then I heard a scream,
and the phone got disconnected.
Mr. Chairman... I did the wrong thing!
Please let me go!
You know what?
I haven't been fortunate
with women in my life.
I must have been cursed
when I kicked out my first wife.
When I liked someone,
Gi Bum didn't like her.
When he approved,
I got sick of her.
Some women even ran away with my money.
Young women, pretty women,
educated women, successful women!
I can't count how many women I've had!
Half of the people on Earth are women,
but I couldn't find anyone to love.
And then I met Madam Oh.
"She's the one!"
I knew that right away.
I never felt that way before!
"I can spend the rest
of my life with her."
"I'll laugh for her.
I'll cry for her."
That's how I wanted to live.
But... I wasn't the only one...
Who told you that you
could steal her heart?
That's your sin!
I don't care if she
likes me for my money.
I don't even care if she has a plot to
marry me, with my son as her accomplice!
Why would an amazing woman
like her live with an old man like me?
Do you know why I didn't
legally marry her yet?
I was afraid she might change.
I was afraid, once married, she might
divorce me and demand her alimony!
And recently, I decided...
"Okay, I'll give her a chance!
I'll give her what she wants!"
That's what I was going to do.
But you came out of nowhere!
How dare you?
I won't forgive you!
Wait!
Wait for me in hell.
I will join you later!
Mr. Chairman!
Mr. Chairman, please don't!
Subtitles by DramaFever