you
hell what are you stopping for I'm
stopping for a rest really so if you
can't stop here what did he say guy
doesn't want to go back you can't expect
me to spend the night like a hospital in
a mountainside better to stop and drive
the car gently over a cliff isn't it
wasn't helping losing your temper I've
never been in a better temple in my life
I love driving a hundred miles through
the dark practically without headlights
I love the trickle of ice-cold water
pouring down my neck this is one of the
happiest moments of my life would you
like me to drive for a bit yes I was
expecting that
I shall be glad when we get to
Shrewsbury if we get the job Rick you
haven't have any idea where we are I
haven't the least idea in the world
that's very complicated URI tendril fine
where are we we don't know we've lost
our way with somewhere in the wels mouth
the top
very solid today and the one we don't
see shows through the night oh well bye
Oh mr. way button what shall I do I
wanted to go to Shrewsbury but than just
me on the crew as a matter of fact maybe
one thing with another I'm not really
sure that I want Paris rose red
cause that goes I don't think they want
to go anywhere something might happen
here but now they ever have a control
for it something definitely might happen
here well I think of something
don't want to frighten music wave of
them come on and I'm not easily strike
Roger
just might say
you
don't stop how can I help stopping you
think we're in the motor boat that's all
the night
all the nine please sorry
do it I really don't know for my eyes
now for heaven's sake stop looking for
something my own view is we're not on a
man oh you look Phillip I can't see
anything it's all a stupid puddle seems
to represent this country very well
everything here is under water or just
drive on will arrive somewhere sometime
that's all
his life rifle in there
widened to push off well I'm staying
here
there you are the holy Hilltoppers far
we've fallen on
knock again louder I just thought that
was loud enough to wake the dead that's
an idea what is wouldn't it be dramatic
supposing the people inside where
they're all stretched out to the lights
quietly burning about them I'm sure it
would be very amusing I'm sure I could
do with a drink the people have to be
selfish to be soaked inside not out what
I heard
good evening we come to us for shelter
we lost our way we're absolutely cut off
don't you understand we can't go forward
we can't go back the roads blocked on
both sides landslides even well short
not sound like that
my name is him Horace Tim how do you do
I'm very sorry to break in on you like
this my name is waiver may I introduce
my wife how do you do Kendra charmed I'm
sure how do you do won't you sit down
thank you
my sister was on the point of arranging
these flower
I don't know your man explained the
situation to you he did his best I'm
afraid I couldn't understand him you see
Morgan is dumb oh I see you of course I
didn't realize we saw your lights and
wondered if you'd be kind enough to give
a shelter for the night you see it's
quite impossible to go on I see now only
a very old Lee what is it what do they
want now that you use my sister it
should become what did he say what did
he want what are you doing here what's
all the fuss about what you must excuse
my sister she's a little dip in fact
sometimes quite death they want to know
if they can stay here for the night
shelter they've been caught in the storm
of course it counts takes the content
him here we only hearing not tada go on
you see that the landslide half the
mountain seems to be crumbling it only
just missed it the road block behind us
and I'm pretty sure as block in front as
well we hate to intrude but what else
can we do you see there isn't anywhere
else we can go even the road below is
under water and for that matter this
place itself may be underwater pretty
soon or even bury what's the matter you
hear what he said there's a landslide in
floods the nick has burst expects
retract protect we've gotta go you here
we've got to go you're afraid hugs
you're afraid aren't you we don't
believe in God and yet you're afraid to
die you've seen his anger in the sky and
you've heard him in the night and you're
afraid afraid afraid but you're lucky
now you might well be afraid your time
will come but it hasn't come yet this
hodges's I know it better new
you remember the pics 1 years ago would
be the cutoff under the landslides
floods in the road to washed away
Morgan remembers he needs his house is
safe because it's built on rock
you will have to stay here the
misfortune is yours not ours no big i
can type in that's my sister hints that
I'm afraid no big that's quite all right
if we can just sit around the fire that
will be fine by all me I'm not very sure
that I want to go to bed myself tonight
mogan attend to the file is there any
place like with the car of the rain
there are some stables round the corner
to the right Logan will show you thank
you very much I'll come along get bag
right no big the contact page
what the storm we're well out of it I
hope you're right though this house
gives me the creeps not to mention its
inmates well it's better than driving
along roads that aren't there at least
as a roof and a fire yeah
now dependable you think that you could
join me in a drink mr. Pham I honestly
believe I could join you in a drink it's
only gingival only gin I like shit this
is waverton thanks very much mr. Pender
oh I will give you a toast that you will
not appreciate being young I give you
illusion illusion huh I'm precisely the
right age for that toast mr. fame hello
I presume you are one of the gentlemen
slightly should we say bettered by the
war correct mr. damn war generation
slightly soiled a study in the
bittersweet the man with a twisted smile
and this mr. Pham is exceedingly good
gin it's used to forget him worse yes it
is pretty bad but evidently there's no
danger here your sister was quite
definite about there but splitting their
cut off shut up in here well it would be
rather a nuisance for you having us
billeted on you like this but it's all
for how can you be so calm you don't
seem to understand we may be cut off
shut up in this house I'm free I'm
rather nervous I am rather a nervous man
but the fact is Morgan is an uncivilized
brute sometimes he drinks heavily a
night like this would set him going once
he's drunk he's rather dangerous I don't
wish to alarm you mrs. waverton but I
don't quite know what we should do I
know what I'm going to do that isn't mr.
me what I'm gradually wet night will be
so glad if I could go and change my
clothes what I wanted to find my change
my thing we look wait nobody can change
your things cool thank you a good idea
is that a bedroom or something I say you
are very I'm none of this electric life
I won't have it
thanks very much I can manage quite well
now my sister Rachel had this room one
she died when she was 21 she was a
wicked one and someone wild as a whole
all the young men use to follow her
about with her red lips not big eyes now
what Nick but they didn't save her she
fell off her horse hunting hurt us fine
on this big chill a month after month
many of the time i SAT here listening to
her screaming oh she used to cry out to
me to kill her but I tell her to turn to
the Lord she didn't she was Douglas to
the last well I'd better change my rep
thing they were all bogus here I used to
bring gavin india Bray's lulling
creatures in soups and seconds they fill
the house with luck to us in laughter a
sin if i ever went down among them my
own father and brothers they would tell
me to go away and pray they wouldn't
tell rachel to go away and pray and I
pray that unless them with our lustful
they don't white women my father still
alive he's upstairs he's very old or if
he he's a hundred me too very old isn't
it he's a wicked blasphemous old name
y'all ready to young and handsome silly
and wicked you think of nothing but your
long straight legs and your white body
and how to please your man you revel in
the joys of freshly love don't you let's
find stuff and it'll rot let's find us
tough still but the rock to entitled
but for you mrs. waverton you make it
look like a party thank you you must
have thought I was a long time matter of
fact I thought you were quicker than
usual oh I just thought I'd be another
long
hice what are you doing not all heathens
oh I had forgotten my sister strange
tribal habits the beef lo seamless stuff
when she has invoked a blessing upon him
Hollis fem I can't hear i can see your
best feeling undercuffler an idea
Rebecca I was merely telling you're
wondering guests that you were about to
thank your gods for their bounty how do
I know you're mocking lying tongue to
thank them for the health and prosperity
and happiness granted to this family for
his years of peace and pinky to thank
them for having created Rebecca them and
Roderick him and so have a good teacher
thank you
well it is a storm and a half yes
appetito thank you I should love updater
vinegar miss fame
it's simply coming down in buckets Bulls
outside thank you mrs. waverton that's
the phrase I've been searching for all
evening no no pickled onions thank you
whose life they gave me quite a storm I
suppose at the store on the contrary we
got an electric lights here and we are
not really good at it trickle be alarmed
if a girls all together
someone outside the company what surely
they must come in it's probably
dangerous up there now
they're probably half down you know
really we ought to keep him waiting no
I'm praying should have to let them in
Morgan open the door come on Morgan nixa
mean I thought you are never gonna open
that door bye there must have been a
reservoir boost assuming any I before
when you well we wear something had
fallen down and smut the caring hahaha
it's a wonder in smash horse
incidentally the causal probably be
washed away in diminished
that's a girl on fire I'm sorry to barge
in on you like this but needs must when
the devil drives well who's your air
mattress choice Fiona missed em how you
do miss him my name is porterhouse Sir
William taught our house and this lady
is Miss Gladys Duquesne a friend of mine
glad to know you nice weather product
allow me to introduce you this is mrs.
Waverton how do you do mr. Pinder oh how
do you do sir william and mr. David how
do you do sir william porter house are
you there never seen such a knock in all
my born national tickets going down in
boy fools pretty well soaked we were at
oakmont elegant i should be surprised if
we got our debt you better not put those
wet shoes on again or I so will you
point out you'll probably catch your
death here you are these may not be
exactly your size
are you brothers the mom Judy be coming
out some agreed oh now you're talking
Morgan bring up some chairs Oh roast big
hey nothing back roast beef with a man's
only be holding leg how does that go do
you remember that mister abbadon was
that before your time penrose our song
extrait oh so your music liar well ha
benefit of an average ever have a potato
Morgan bring a glass of water person
take ourselves for instance here we are
six people sitting around and we've been
talking now for nearly two hours what do
we know about each other not a thing how
are you sure I agree with the William at
best we only make guesses you were a
woman you wouldn't talk about only
guesses ah the famous old feminine
intuition let's never tell you which
horse is going to win the Derby no but
it tells me quite a lot about you and
one day mrs. ray Burton whether it
happens to tell you time wanted by the
police I know mrs. Emma tells me nothing
so romantic I'm sure can you conceive of
anybody living in a house like this if
they didn't have to well there's no
accounting for taste you know haha no
mr. Kay yes what does your intuition
tell you about me I don't know hmm that
frightens me a good deal what does it
tell you it tells me well it's not very
interesting anyway hey let's have it
well it sounds silly but I think he
doesn't quite fit into these time you
know fact risen cheap advertising money
grubbing well what I mean is bill here's
all right with these things but they
make mr. pendril a kind of fish out of
water you should be flattered mr.
pendril no I'm not flattered you see
I've not much sympathy with fish out of
water although I happen to be one myself
my trouble is I don't think enough
things are worth while now so William
here would put tremendous energy into
anything to make even a few pounds now I
don't think it's worth it no doubts will
be covered if I hated my own friends
but maybe I can see through things of it
further than you suppose that was a very
fine speech of yours but I know as well
as everybody else here but you really
only getting at me but honestly I wasn't
doing anything of the kind I envy you i
admire you oh yes you in with me all
right but you don't admire me yeah well
I don't admire myself so much I know
that money-making isn't everything but
let me tell you something I'm a young
man see married to a Manchester girl
prettiest paint the only thing in the
world are cared about well she dies it's
this way my directions give a party they
are sauce red letter day for us i can
tell you i buy me for stress suit and
lucy as a new prop up cotton from it
seems that Lucy didn't go too well at
that party especially with the women
they snubbed at nothing definite you
know just didn't think the cotton frock
was good enough Oh Lucy what is about it
gets into her head that she's gonna hold
me back well you may not believe it but
I know that's what killed her that's
what started me making money I swore I'd
smash those fellows and their wives it
wouldn't give my Lucy a kind word and I
had smashed them at least most of them
when you started making money it's hard
to stop especially if you like me it
isn't much else she good at but what
plan is here us mr. period I don't know
miss Duquesne why don't you tell me a
real name my real name is Perkins and a
very nice name too I may not be this now
may not be that if you don't catch me
pretending to be what I'm not I think
I'm finding you a little bit offensive
that's all right Sandra I can take care
of myself
least if account but now I never will be
able to I wasn't trying to put anything
across you bill I don't pretend to be
what I'm not either I'm not as dumb as
that these people here know chorus girl
when they see one incident did not a
very good core of scared of death if I
would desert my job I probably wouldn't
be weak ending with you no I take that
back I probably would you're nice enough
we get on but
bottles of the bottle again I'm Uli's
bikini game tonight when you get it home
you didn't get it from me can't you stop
him it is the kitchen uh from my trunk
ohs morgan is either fella that waited
on us a table yes Morgan is that the
buffler looks to me in the bigger deal
with a shave oh hello hello well have
you come over to help me gaze upon the
wrath of garden no I came to say thank
you for trying to take my part just now
charmed I'm sure mr. Kent Perkins to you
nice person I say I'd mortgage the old
homestead for a drink mmm Sarah died and
we have one I've got some whiskey in the
car I'd forgotten all about it you stay
here and I'll go get it no
you better stay here on the cover the
cars in the stables you get so oh my god
I
Oh what are you doing you're just coming
thank you hey hey what's the matter
what's happening nothing nothing really
I've bit scared that's all somebody sat
on the door in my face probably the wind
no it wasn't I know when when I see it
it doesn't sound much but well you know
it gave me a bit of a turn yes I bet it
did yeah what you want to drink of this
thanks little bit more human now this
certainly is a benighted household you
were right it is look at those
come on take them off I seem to spend
most of the evening changing your shoes
you want to be a nursery maid yes except
that the best nursery maids don't break
whiskey off the bottle don't just as bad
as ever listed done it the night's gone
out it I supposing stared this time now
we should be miserable all the evening
that's all right sure there's some
candles somewhere answers I do anything
about the lifeless them no nobody
understands our lights except Morgan and
as an electrician Morgan is temporal
disqualified you haven't got enough any
chance of you no no you haven't got a
limp what did they say nothing nothing
important huh not important there's
happened I heard that time they want to
lend give them a large run bizarrely
need we use it the last time I like
something wrong on hottie sure you know
the one I don't remember where it is
suppose you get in Tribeca it's too big
for me if you don't know what it is I'll
tell you you know as well as I do it's
on the top lending I'm a little table
you know where the top lending is how
least you might believe that is a tough
landing or you don't believe in so
little it's a fair Horace affair next
roof if across I remember but I think
it's a little too hit it for me I don't
think I could carry it down all those
stairs why don't you say what you mean
hotties you mean you got afraid to go
there alone you'll go with him yeah take
this no no why bother myself do you ever
go to sit in the dark
we'd better go up a tree yes I suppose
he had we won't be long that's all right
this is where it can see that I don't
get nanny you better leave the word this
is my room huh there are one or two
things that I should very much like for
you to see I should like to very much
but you will show me some other time
we've got to get that lamp you
listen why should we bother about the
damn letter Shwayze after a few minutes
and then go back and since we couldn't
find it all the did spoken by Garth it
apart yes the vice should we trouble
about the netbook we don't want to but
said we get it so I should forget it if
it why should we if we don't phunk to an
ideal farm too but this is absurd did
you hear that I did you hear something
what was it it must have been Morgan
he's drunk you know he's probably making
a disturbance downstairs in the kitchen
I thought that noise came from upstairs
anyway what about this lamb I wondered
whether you'd excuse me from coming with
you I'm not very strong there are rather
a lot of stairs I really should have
told you before but the manatee rage you
know you'll find it on the little table
at the end of the landing two floors
above I suppose it's not too heavy for
me to carry oh no rush at all it's quite
late really antsy thank you thank you
very much
you are potential well now you can
demonstrate it come on shut it I can't
burn short one the rains pouring in the
floods rising whatever be drenched if
you don't come quickly she means the
window in her room I'm afraid I open ah
you won't forget you can shoot each box
all right miss filmer oh come on shut it
it's a good know everything breathing
from here he's only stunned you'll be
conscious in the minute the will
probably fall asleep again is very drunk
Oh Philip this is an awful house it
isn't very nice is it
listen Margaret something happened
upstairs just now Oh Phillip not
something else horrible no this was
nothing horrible it was a voice calling
from behind a door tiny voice rather
like a child I think I ought to go and
see what it is you'll have to come with
me I'm not going to leave you alone
again he'll be all right take my hand
darling what is it sit down here when
darling
Thanks well what happened then well then
the war ended what about the girls oh
the girl I left behind me girl you were
in love with when she got married gladys
what Abby's no on the contrary a lady
rather good judgment now let's talk
about you for a bit I know what you're
going to say you're going to ask me
about veal porterhouse claro miss Birkin
I don't mind telling you I'd rather like
two bills all right really of course I
don't love him and of course gives me
money I'm not very much just enough to
keep me going you probably won't believe
me but no doesn't he doesn't expect
anything do you know what i mean by
anything yes I know what you mean by
anything he likes to think he's ever so
gay you see for all his money he's a bit
lonely yes I spotted that when he told
us the story of the cotton dress I think
he's in love with that little dead wife
still I'm sure he is I suppose it why
here he wants me well for company last
person am i dead at night and boast to
me about the things he's done during the
day well that's harmless enough mind you
I'm not pretending to be any better than
I am you're a nice creature our job I
like you often
and are you what are you thinking of you
may not be very pleased risky
i was thinking i'd like to pretend that
I was your lover and that you were mine
glad his body and soul I'd like to take
you in my arms and hold you and press
you to me very gently very tight I'd
like it too would you blend is Perkins
why then let's pretend
mission
Gladys Perkins has an idea I think she
must have gone man she she she wants to
live with you I'm just flinging myself
with your head I've got a crazy idea
that I might help him to be a useful
person darling virgins
you think I'm mad quite made my darling
and thank God free well what you say
that's what I say Perkins are darling
but I've got a better idea than yours an
improvement on it what is it wait just
this no I won't tell you here there's
magic here I'll tell you later on in the
house preps even in the cold light of
morning tell me now come on let's go
back no let's stay here you're cold now
it's just the idea of going back to that
house at mag me shiver I've got a funny
feeling something dreadful might happen
to us if we go back to that house
Perkins Perkins you've my strong right
arm him Joe all right come on
no you copied on those wet shoes I'm
going to try to carry you I'm a definite
of a wait well if you're too heavy for
me I shall drop you in the modern go on
alone
hello where are you been I went out to
the car to get a drink and I went with
him she got her feet wet all she got a
fake wet yes she got her feet wet I
thought the devil's been happening here
I don't know what the devil's been up in
the air Oh anyway I'll sign in or three
not me anywhere I went into the old gal
zoom to close a window and candor
confound this where all the other I
don't know no more than you mr. where
vision went upstairs would sing a
retired to fetch a lamp I suppose his
wife joined him I've been a slave so you
got your faith wait yes bill that wasn't
all I'd yes I didn't suppose it was
quite know how you'll take this but well
I've got to get it off my chest come on
let's have it I fall in love them oh
you're out of here with him yeah with
him dance pole probably but we don't
choose these things has he gotten him
money not a penny but you're going up
with him yes are you angry I think
you're a lunatic but I'm not angry he
took it pretty well didn't he break in I
told you bills all right he is indeed
what do i do this can be
listen bill she hasn't told you
everything and k why not because she
doesn't know everything herself we're
going to be married oh oh yeah at least
if she'll have me I'm going to ask her
tomorrow in the cold light of morning
will you come to the wedding I think
you're off your name do you know I don't
I think it's probably the best days work
you've ever done in your life ah bill
bill hotel judging you could call me
Bill will you try and stop me not okay
come and make yourself useful and put
this tag on it chief that's no way to
change roast beef mr. came to roast beef
then if you sell show you feel better
yes I'm all right well let's go on
this is the doll
you
who are you i miss Layton this is my
husband I used to Roderick then we we
came in because we thought we heard you
call him can we get you anything
can you take it yourself or shall I give
it to you I can take it my soup
what was that noise what it p market yes
Morgan is a savage aria I must apologize
but we have to keep him here you
shouldn't have come here I'm very sorry
but really we couldn't help it oh I
don't mean that I was never in
hospitable yes this house was always
filled with gates once upon a time when
you came or did they carry you why they
told us you were an endless what's that
ah yes you've seen my son Horus and he's
just a Rebecca yes and Morgan
I would like to tell you all about it
but there may not be time you see even
your at all that i am at any minute you
may just die oh please don't party the
tires you this is an anarchy house two
of my children died when they were 20
and then about things happened Magnus
came we had our touch to eat a little
Lucy except me at least I I don't think
I am would you like to go to cook now no
not just yet you see it maybe it maybe
what dangerous you mean Morgan no not
Morgan I mean from my eldest son soul so
they didn't tell you about soy no they
didn't sorry it's the rest you know we
have to watch him because you teased
even he just wants to destroy to kill
poor sigh where is he I know really is
he's upstairs behind that bolted door
isn't it yes knocking sorry why we have
to keep Morgan but if it did you know
soil quite certainly would set fire to
the house he tried to once before he
wanted he said to to make this house a
burnt offering but isn't this a falafel
yes but you see if Morgan his bed I yeah
I think he might open the door
yeah what are they come to wait here
God says I heard you you don't will it's
all out week fine downstairs and killing
what are we to do can't we stay in here
no suppose he said fired at the place
come on master Radley we must lock the
door fabric I'm gonna lock you in listen
there's a madman upstairs Morgan's let
him out in these dangerous we've got to
do something good Josh where are they
may come down any minute all right my
dear I knew I felt something dreadful
was going to happen hadn't we better get
out of the way no we can't do that you
might set fire to the place he's tried
it once before wouldn't let him let the
rotten old place burn I wish it would
that's all right what about the bends
what did he your brother's out of his
room what
welcome you hear me taking back
sins of the father the sins of the
father
miss regular trouble come on coming here
yeah I don't want to be shut up for
heaven's sake come in here mark you're
like this
oh I love in the truth I just love him
please please don't touch me what is it
listen don't put me back don't happen to
me back I'm not mad I swear more hidden
I'm not mad it's just that they locked
me up here they're all wicked why should
i lock you are but they're frightened of
me I know something about them years ago
they killed their sister Rachel but I
wouldn't tell I promised I'd never tell
and they've kept you here all that time
for that then Morgan I tell you sit have
a bit Morgan don't leave me stay with me
that's all right you sit here and wait
I'll be back
but our love the spin must about it it's
not digit yes I'm glad then you can't
leave me listen we got off the others
with Logan isn't there some way of
getting through no no way but there must
be a back entrance into the house stop
I want Kelly restore it who's in there
nobody friends of yours I tell you
nobody shall we invite them out you you
don't tell me something yes so I won't
you won't you tell me that story yes
shall we sit down yes let's
who's in that covered nobody tell me
what you were going to save me
are you interested in flame why yes yes
i am robert i made a study of flame have
you what happens to be very interesting
I know things about flames but nobody
else in the world knows won't you tell
me I'd like very much to know why did I
tell you you wouldn't tell me who is in
that cupboard what I did tell you is
how'd you know it isn't fair to make me
curious and then just not say anything
you'd like me to tell you all about
firewood you yes I wish you would well
in first of all they learnt it flames
are really nice they're cold my friend
sharp and cold ass no they burn like
nice
oh it certainly is very very interesting
so they're really like knives are they
will do go on tell me what else you
found out a lot of things my friends sit
down
so you thought you could cheat me to do
you thought you could leave me sitting
here and I wouldn't notice but you see I
am a clever man also that is why we
understand one another that is why you
understood so quickly that I wanted to
kill you we understand each other so
well don't we my friend yes isn't he
with you from the start somehow I I
liked you and I I thought you liked me
like you my friend I love you did you
know my name is Saul Saul my friend and
so long did he did he did that saw was
afraid of David because the Lord was
with him and was departed from Seoul and
it came to pass on the morrow that the
evil still it came upon soul and he
prophesied in the midst of the house and
David played upon the heart with his
hand and there was a javelin in Souls
and and soul cast the gem limb and he
said I will smite David even to the wall
with him and David avoided out of his
presence twice twice much begging the
third time third time you must be
careful listen I'm your friend I'm on
your side it's silly to lose me if you
lose me look there's Morgan he's come
for your mother stop don't move
ah
let's go cloud you see his central let
me go to him go on let me go by oh but
I'm not afraid of you I'm going to him
you here Oh could you listen you gotta
let me alone you here I gotta go to
Pendrell he's hurt oh oh can I made you
understand he's hurt I got to look up to
him in the other man to Seoul there
Bofur
you all right Margaret yes I'm all right
darling gladness it's all right come on
yeah okay if you didn't better yes I'm
not so bad what happened do you
I'm all right now West Pendrell I've got
the craft in Morocco over there come
with me
good morning good morning good morning
mr. Edison good morning
the plans have subsided considerably
forgiven for that I think it really
possible phone to send for an ambulance
now you mean we can go yes I'm sure we
can go now come on darling want me to
stay here with Dennis aren't you I am
don't belong we won't do be as quick as
we can
five beside so happy to admit you swine
really dead and gone to heaven now it's
morning we've only just a tail behind
morning yes cold light of day one or
something you're going to tell me in the
cold light of day come to think that
that was Perkins would you marry me
you