there are images around us everything we
see some more real and some more fantasy
to the water sees his vision
to the child it's his dreams you're the
one to decide that you gonna D so give
it your best and don't worry about what
some may say follow your dream that's
all that you can do get a job as and
remember the knife is what you choose
there are phases you
and time to miracle face is that
repression
Martina + 58 email box will will in
finishing this puzzle now ready for
boarding you're the one to decide the
tuna
John if I wanted you to smile I'd ask
you to smile right I can't help it move
it reflex
think about accidents hundreds of us is
stalled at the state lines and all your
schedules rendered useless forever
wonderful give it your best don't worry
about what some may say follow your
dream that's all that you can do give it
your best and remember the life is what
you Jesus resending loved you
hi Parker are you back for good oh yeah
you don't know how happy you just made
her she's Crowder's up sleep every night
since you lay out damn give it your best
don't worry about what some may say
follow your dreams
get a job best friend aroma the
cantilever cream is wrong with you all
my to run you down yeah well if you had
I would have too soon the park case
would have dragged on for years Marianne
Taylor she look different I do not I'm
exactly the same mind if I smoke Oh what
is it you call that set doing shuffle
boom talk Parker it's a half
never used to wear stuff like that
before well yes you're back clunk out
did not just quit oh can you give me a
ride home I got a bunch of stuff to do I
gotta find a place to live come on
Parker I'll take a picture come on tell
what you do with that thing mm-hmm come
on Park I'm not asking you to marry me
just give me ride home ah give the car
well thanks for the ride maybe I'll to
go in there and order something
hamburger something oh no you don't have
to bother I mean you'd only be doing it
cuz you've discovered how wonderful I am
I mean wouldn't blame me if you wanted
to see me again you know call me might
find out what you've been missing all
these years
you sure took your time about you think
I've ruined my chance making this hard
for you know I've correspondents who we
can have any operator you want it's true
Bishop one Jim's been waiting down here
for a half an hour i'll see you tomorrow
Stan ya see sorry I'm late daddy
Shelley's one of the nervous I don't
mind me saying there's somebody gonna
take my order hold on what would you
like shortstack shortstack college
mama what are you doing out here honey I
just wanted to get some air I'm not dead
yet mama you should be wearing a sweater
did you get the mail today yes there was
nothing well is still time I may not
even hear anything till sep tember I
know you're gonna get in that art school
is gonna snap you up right away I don't
have a chance oh you used to be so wild
wow thank any girl who painted toenails
it's wild not while that's not the word
spirit he used to say any school that
didn't take you as crazy that's any
school around here it's different in
California they got standards I know
you're gonna get in I can picture you in
Los Angeles you'll be going all over
with that camera of yours you're gonna
live in one of those apartments that has
a pool a garden apartment around a big
blue pool
I like house oh well now it's just a
small one of course with the pool I can
picture you there you know if I close my
eyes I can see you there can you
hey you doing hey oh goodness well yeah
I've grown up on y'all keep playing ball
up and see what your mom's done oh so
glad you're back this one he said you
warm up to you Charlie over the grocery
told me you were back oh you can't keep
us say you're in this thing but wait it
supposed to be secret Lord no Jack I
want this to be a nice dinner how could
it not be with me home I've been wishing
you come back don't worry
played perfectly in the sixth inning at
the time there was no score Baker was at
first Garvey kept fouling off Nolan Ryan
pitches in the 22 damn horizontals out
the right of Dickie thon into left field
tip TV names it's a vacation sit in sun
somewhere bringing a pitcher of martinis
got tribe huh y'all want to create
screws teach engineering cuz when they
go to let guys off engineers are the
last go we always need one I tried
you're thinking narration weren't you
thinking about that goddamn car decided
against it that's all he's ready thank
you honey less honey dinner's ready Hey
look I gotta go face it you're a loser
hey Jack welcome home page in all right
hey come on you give it your best shot
good up there next to mine um Jan okay
you don't get any change anything oh
Jesus Christ Nancy would you put him
down how you treat him under goddamn
baby going to a convention in Las Vegas
no kidding all expenses paid they got a
Cadillac taken aim at the airport you
got a failed you got it made now I want
to have to tell you again you're ruining
him now put him down now everything's
getting cold let's eat huh no wonder he
acts like a baby all the time cuz that's
how you treat him really is still a baby
I'll show you how to tough on that for
help yeah
oh you're gonna show somebody how to
treat kids big one damn thing for sure I
failed with you I've been harder on you
you wouldn't end up that service station
dad please where you are right yes where
I you wouldn't come back after a year
without like a tree like a tree yeah he
loves it that's enough who do you think
you are boy you'd better not leave this
goddamn house after she cut up his body
she stuffed him into jars mason jars
then she tickled him and she left him in
those jars all separated into pieces on
her own kitchen shelf for 20 years Jesus
what some women won't do shit the
mercury county sheriff said it was a
case of jealousy plain and simple mrs.
McPhee is now 82 years old and the
mercury County Sheriff plants to see
that everything could be done to avoid
upsetting mrs. McPhee as she has a bad
heart has been suffering from angina
angina shit what about the old man's
heart she's like to pickle that too Evan
I can't concentrate what are you worried
about you're gonna win Bearsville again
oh yeah that's right you got what it
takes
you got luck oh I see you're predicting
now well I told you I psychic you're a
lucky guy look you can't afford to new
rear tires that's what I call her
good-looking gal I just think how pretty
you was why sorry you got something to
show you these last week I don't look
like that hello wish you did I didn't
SPECT you to come around here well I
figured if I ways for you to ask me out
i might just lined up waiting forever
well see ya
you better pick me up my house tonight
Jack Parker you may never get another
chance like this again
told you you were lucky
well we probably won't even show up I
don't care if he does he's here where
well of course he is behave yourself
well what are you doing out there Jack
Parker I don't have time to wait for any
man I don't care who he is
you look beautiful don't be ridiculous
oh I'm Vince better any girl in mercury
better any girl I ever saw before think
so I do wish I'd run into you before I
always wanted to be the prettiest girl
in town I think you are never let you
meet twice hey Barbra when we gonna go
out on that date you promised this isn't
haven't told my name was Barbara like
privacy hey Julie I I just took this
picture that's all you've got a nice
profile well I'll have a birthday water
my friend park will help what do you
have the coke huh oh that's are you
me
this isn't really my kind of place well
I come here a lot like to get out of
town you know some people might say that
girl who comes here alone is cheap but
until a new I think anybody who says
that I'll be shot straight through the
heart well I never said anything about
you come in here you know what Entre
Nous means it means Cheers just between
you and me oh yeah no I remember you
real well from high school yeah what do
you remember you got suspended three
times in our senior year what just
reminiscing that's not reminisce okay
you just talk about now well what is it
you do for fun now cars that's what you
do for a living myself I never saw
another apron again as long as I live
I'll be thrilled I think always just
sawdust it
special wait just look down
your meals served by little robots
human beings anywhere you were mind if
we leave
we're almost to Jessup where do you
think you're taking me well I know what
you got in mind Jack Parker and you can
just forget it wait no guys like you
come out here for one of two reasons to
get laid or howl at the moon you don't
look like a howler to me well there
might be other reasons for bringing you
out here oh yeah like what if I keep
driving we'll find out now do I turn
around or keep driving keep driving
so this is what you like to do
okay hold imagine
let's see it shut her off
I know this place is here that's
better'n howl at the moon last minute
Mac the car views must be pretty rusty
Parker oh yeah probably is you want stay
for a race yeah uh no I'm it you could
watch them over there oh but they're all
lovely you what are they talking about
over there mascara oh no no they're
comparing hairstyles look it's not you
it's just dangerous race for the
passenger well I'm not scared yeah well
I am would you bring me up here for
watch exciting
hey are you here with Jack I guess so
you're lucky I'm Jenny Caroline Caroline
you know what's going now oh yeah I got
the breakfast shift in the morning he
had a terrible time no no not terrible
was trying to impress you I know it
worked
starting to what do you mean keep trying
honey you got any salt on the counter
right in front of you well what do you
know girls close to my daddy gets back
can you a cup of coffee how you be
working thought I'd take lunch early
inconvinience see you I'm here
resistible I love this book read Malone
took all these when he was teaching in
Paris these aren't by red Malone you
know what I think what
thank you better than he is well has a
stupidest thing I ever heard of me read
Malone is a great photographer he's the
only reason I'm going to Los Angeles Los
Angeles wanna go there get in on Lord
why don't want you to get to race with
me on the fourth of July not you only
race alone today all right sure it's a
date I stopped and got those magazines
your mama won thanks for taking over for
me daddy you remember Jack Parker why
sure you're the fellow with a fancy car
it's the man I love you don't say might
be so I'm just easily loading been out a
few times you better watch out for it
she usually gets what she wants
maybe you'll leave town with me yeah
maybe you'll stay listen
let's go over my place right now
here it is I haven't much time to fix it
up I'll say de corps and the Camaro tops
this here well I just want you to know
I've been with a lot of guys love before
same thing about that cuz you have a
little know rod yeah that's what you say
now good Oh Gary you've been worked
before now and you're gonna be with me
just what makes you so sure that's what
I want why are we talking so much you
don't even know me
I know you
maybe I'll break your heart
I
Wow a letter from the admissions
department today they have 700
applicants and they're only accepting 25
and they don't even mention anything
about a scholarship you're gonna be one
of those 25 uh-huh don't have chance I
don't care you know I never dead
Marianne
so what if i don't get in
check what a nice surprise Nessie why do
you keep opening the goddamn door also
use a pan for air conditioner keep
opening the goddamn door two men honey
that piece here Oh Jack I know is you
come on hmm get him a coke or something
yeah it is a great game on right here
it's the Dodgers oh yeah I've been doing
a lot of work on that Camaro well that's
good trying to get it ready for
bearsville god damn if the Dodgers don't
win tonight that's it they fucking had
it hey yeah I'm gonna get these out of
your way
less I'd like to ask a favor of you
shoot well it bar some money oh shit
I'll pay you back I everybody I know
wants to borrow money from me what gave
everybody this idea that I had all this
dough that's just three hundred dollars
are you in some kind of trouble oh no no
I just need to new rear tires before the
race Jesus Christ jack are you ever
gonna grow up it's just a loan yeah but
I don't get in the interest you would
yeah what do I get in return I could
work on your car for you for nothing see
they take care of my car already real
nicely at the plant
listen
how about your undying loyalty sure hows
Yusei 300 yeah thanks thanks a lot well
you know if you really want to thank me
you could keep an eye on Nancy while I'm
in Las Vegas next week she can be
staying with your folks will be fine
right here well I'm sure you'll be all
right here you just love to be here all
alone with me out of town wouldn't you
know no yeah you Rick some stranger back
here the first night I'm gone hey I know
what you're planning I can see right
through you you want to get a little
action
probably have somebody in mind already
anybody I know hey yes I didn't hear
your answer I don't have anybody in mind
don't lie to me I know you've been
thinking about it I know what a fucking
liar you are are you talking about hi
there look at her she's not even
listening to me well I know how to wake
her up hey what are you doing no there's
just a little game we play she likes it
oh yeah well I don't like it yeah well
Nancy does tell him tell him I would you
like quit it tell him to mind his own
business mind your own business Jeff no
luckily stops you heard your sister oh
please
I'll see you soon go on
and I could stay asleep while the man
was awake in the same room aren't you
gonna ask me how many times I've been in
a situation like that you think many
women get beat up I am not that kind of
girl so don't get any ideas
happens all the time Barker
I can't be the one was gonna put up with
getting beat she wouldn't stay with a
man like that you just get up and walk
out the door go where who are you
talking about well happens all the time
how do you know you write a college
paper on the subject it's a fact alive
Parker you are wrong no woman is gonna
stay with a man like that
classic Ryan those kids do not hear a
word you say they're all right you know
I wish less wasn't coming home tonight
it's just kind of like it was for you
got married
you
that's it honey where are you going had
some errands to do it's almost dinner
time I wanted to get a cake for dessert
I've already got dessert oh I thought
maybe we could talk I can't talk all
right I just can't talk I don't like the
way you've been looking you look tired
you keep an eye on the boys
hello
okay all right all right I'll be there
in five minutes well where the hell were
you oh she drove her car into the garage
and she closed the dope she forgot to
turn it but er I mean forgot ha yeah I
tell you to watch I told me to keep a
goddamn mahan ornatus what did I tell
you the water back door him listen to me
if you hurt her Oh break your fucking
neck ok for your own sake I'm just gonna
forget all of that ever happening where
you see county hospital psychiatric hey
come on come on I wasn't even here I
mean how the hell was I supposed to know
she were gonna drive into the fucking
garage and leave the engine on it was an
accident that's right it was an accident
how are you me everyone in the hospital
all right I wonder if they have vases in
here they must Nancy what happened I
know you're so unhappy everybody in here
want cigarettes you'd have any no mom
you think cigarettes were golden here is
it less yeah they hurt you I'm pregnant
oh that's great hidden it
listen I think I can get you out of here
I I'm a relative unbelieving sign you
out I want to stay what about that baby
what about the baby I have too many
children already what am I gonna do with
another baby we don't even have talked
about it night here you have to think
about it we'll cross that bridge when we
get to it I don't know what I want you
could leave him he'd find me change your
name yeah go on pick one pick a new name
pick a name any name but Laura Oh God
hey what's wrong with your name it's
beautiful just like you okay it's time
for her to go back to her room
communis nami listen if you don't want
me to lead you to say the word and I'll
stay right here with you hear me Nancy
let's say goodbye here then we'll go
back to your room
how's dad sister do they still I ever
locked up well what are you asking me
for pardon me jack says she's coming
home on Friday
oh I'm not just what you need how are
you jack hard yeah well you better go
home and get some rest tomorrow
I don't think I'm gonna mom what do you
mean let's don't feel like well to hell
with that Jack Parker you promised me we
were gonna race together on the fourth
of July we are going on your mark get
set we've got bills in the seventh
annual fourth of July decoration the
love octopus are in the lead fellas
beauty shop and right behind you Devon
shamrock station
get happened away
followed by skeleton shop and the
barbell now I call that a race
congratulations
you
mom
Oh
go home we just got here maybe she
doesn't want any company maybe she's
crazy well she could be she not I just
want to know what to do she serves a
live chicken for dinner that's not funny
sorry let's go home she invited us Jesus
look she wouldn't have invited Chad want
to cover well that just shows how much
you know people invite you for dinner
all the time doesn't mean they want you
here we are oh can I have some more of
those potatoes please babe hmm thank you
don't you look great great I do not you
do I'm telling you ever since you got
back from the hospital he looks just
like a movie star you really think so
really do know jack last time I saw you
we were both pretty upset yeah what's
wrong well you say we just forget all
about that forgotten good good cuz you
got that race years to concentrate on
right so little will I wouldn't be
lending three hundred dollars to a loser
Jeff shock therapy oh no you will we
don't talk about that stuff here not
right
I'm sorry I just never met anyone who
had it just wondered what it was like
that's all right in the hospital though
they just gave me Thorazine and know
that i'm home i just take valium cut it
out would you like some of us be no
thanks don't you do with rise no no luck
huh no well I'm I don't really think
it's a night in the hospital need me so
much for as long as you as much goddamn
money my mother takes temel all the
facts does it makes him feel like she's
asleep I why did she starred in the Dean
use chest to take it huh it's too bad
hmm cancer I'm sorry hey come on come on
what you talk about disease disease is a
fact of life bakra me pardon me if I
talk about reality brothers very
unrealistic he's a dreamer so listen
what's with you two anyway I mean are
you gonna make it legal and get married
or what ya know
well it's something we still have to
discuss you finished yeah delicious
portlet sure would make your mother
happy inhale there's nothing to discuss
wouldn't talk about it my first smoke me
no I am mine I'm a bit we are not going
to get married you know no no how can i
come going to Los Angeles Angeles yeah
your brother just does not understand
how much I want to leave mercury oh no
deep in his heart he thinks I'm staying
yeah don't let him talk you into stay
and if that's not what you want don't
let Jack make you forget what you really
want no you sure are different than I
thought you'd be I mean I thought you'd
be sort of crazy yeah but you're not I
love it you just can't see it I hide it
you get me the coffee cups there in that
covered what no same crazy to me no I
think I'll come back and see you okay
strange as you have tired all the time
what's the value yeah no sir it's a
different sort of tired its own inside
my bones yes Rudy just sighed my bone
she's gonna do it again
it might have been an accident Nancy
didn't know a thing about cars she might
have pulled in the garage and closed the
door by accident she said she was tired
and her bones
hell he wouldn't be tired for what she's
been through yeah you're right probably
right
you know I am
have you heard anything from Los Angeles
no I stopped thinking about it you can't
fool me you're as sure as I am that
you're gonna get in maybe I am today I
am yeah I'm getting so good at this I
should open a laundromat Carla call the
doc
can we see her now I'm sorry you just
have to wait she's resting right now but
these collapses are going to take more
and more out of her
you
she'll be home in a week that's great
go look in on her during my break
Miriam is that you well of course it's
me who else would it be hui expecting an
old boyfriend oh I'm sorry I I didn't
know we had company well it's nice to
meet you nice to meet you well she were
told me we had company i mean at least i
could have done was combing my hair tell
you food management jobs or hell living
hell of course we weren't expecting it
we weren't expecting anyone we are busy
over at the diner i can tell you can
drive you crazy i mean if the hamburger
meat isn't rotten there's bugs in the
coffee beans you know this little grave
bugs with wings how they manage to fly
around in those bags of coffee is beyond
me well I'm glad I drink tea oh I'll bet
you are but I didn't just come here to
drink tea I came here to see you
Marianne this is mr. Malone oh no you're
not red Malone after i saw your
photographs i had to meet you well i got
in i wanted to see if those photographs
you sent me were real or if mercury was
just some town you dreamed up Oh mercury
is no dream that's for sure well she
wasn't supposed to find out till the
first of sep tember but I didn't want to
wait you have a scholarship full tuition
the disgusting truth is she's better
than I was at her age she's going to be
one of the best students i have had
nor won't be no false modesty it turns
my stomach it always has mr. melona I'm
real flattered you drove all the way
here to tell me this oh hell don't be
flattered I had a goddamn gallery
opening to go to in Santa Fe and I hate
openings they always serve white wine
which I've always hated you know in
those little paper cups mr. Malone
excuse me this is real nice you but I'm
not going I've changed my mind she talks
about you all the time I'm sorry what do
you mean you've changed your mind you'll
never get another chance like this again
not like this Marianne Marianne I know
you think you're good now but when I get
through with you you'll want to be
incredibly good I'm sorry I wasted your
time there'll be a place waiting for you
on the fifteenth whether you like it or
not don't you believe a word she just
told you I wish I could stay longer talk
some sense into her is she really that
good that good
he's gone
I just changed my mind that's all huh
are you worried about money are you
afraid that scholarship won't them huh
it's not just the money come with me
right now um just be quiet and follow me