also we celebrate in da Street be
rushing things but we can hardly wait
are these
right this very minute Hamilton
Carol's at the spinet yes vee
right this very minute it hasn't sold a
single hurry Bobby we're all in guys
this is the best idea we've had in years
Christmas at my mother's farm sounds
great party but don't you think we could
have called your mother to let her know
we were coming oh how little you
understand bears trimming my mother
loves surprises good then she's in for
beauty the bride to bride you see I know
what she is doing this very second there
she is in the old farmhouse on the snowy
hill nice and cozy by a roaring fire all
the Christmas decorations will be up and
mall being a rocking chair knitted and
feeling just a little sad and she's all
alone for the holidays hello plane
leaves for California in three hours of
o Christmas in Malibu poof I'm going to
lie on the beach and catch some rays
waka waka oh this is going to be such a
surprise
Oh
the fruit cake
e
well I think I have everything yes the
airline ticket my suntan lotion come in
hello it is this grizzly farm oh you
must be the winter come in come in yes
yes I'm darker are you my landlady whoa
no sprocket I didn't know I was renting
from a bear Oh mind your step be careful
there's an icy patch there oh I'm just
so glad that someone going to be staying
in the house while I'm gone yes flow
sprocket and I he's my dog orthogonal
we're certainly delighted to be renting
the place we've been wanting to spend a
nice quiet Christmas in the country
you've come to the right place now put
your things in the bedroom at the top of
the stairs hmm now who could that be
better Merry Christmas son ah hard
something to citywalk well what the a
surprise oh no the real surprise is I
brought all my friend Whitney
aren't you glad to see so well I should
say me miss Barrett remember me I rented
this place to have a nice quiet Chris
designer gave me Bradley careful rocket
these could be from some foreign planet
actually they're from television I
recognize fuzzies weirdo friends yeah
boy might hear thee Tavis properties
anything like this psychos you keep
telling me about I'm on my mom I want
you to meet someone this is my boss my
friend my inspiration or the one who
gave me my big break into show business
coming oh yeah the lizard all right well
frog actually listen mrs. Barry you know
I know they're an awful lot of us here
oh I did you worry about it there's
plenty of room for everybody excuse me
you promised me a nice quiet curses you
think you're disappointed I just took
three months of surfing lessons for hip
califone telephone and that's just
animal hell I'll I'll give me presents
Oh dig up
hello piggy kiss me my dear shoot it's
you oh yes baby it's me hey listen where
are you you were supposed to come up to
the farmhouse with us oh I know cami but
I forgot about the Dead Sea reads a
photo session I just scheduled okay now
give me more over the shoulder honey
hold it Donal it will hurry up do not
worry so many the green hunk oh yeah oh
yeah couldn't be nice thank you I'm my
chauffeur to wrong is it ready to whisk
me way into your arms to the farmhouse
Oh Oh beautiful beautiful I must go non
rather busy trim you see you soon hmm ok
boy kisses Bob oh oh oh oh no do that
pony thing who's a pony thing Oh up the
skin those are our bedrooms we rented
this place not more fuzzy get that door
okay mom swedish chef lil are you
chopping up icy patch they're your
biggest burger be go go go blue go blue
go blue tour I mean you're here to cook
the Christmas where did my little chicky
poo Camilla get 20 I'll get it yes idea
how can your a turkey of course Oh God
come on outside we gotta talk yeah sure
that they're rats and chickens here we
always have rested kitchens listen
you're in the wrong place at the wrong
time now take a walk fly south for the
winter anything I was invited for
Christmas by some guy who spoke Swedish
brought a white chef's head on sounds
like a nice vacation mmm-hmm listen that
guy is a chef don't you realize it could
be very dangerous for turkeys around
here not to worry I'm a survivor now
where's my room
traffic will be in the oven so long
bucco shorter no it seemed to be the
trouble fuzzy only to come and fish FS a
little bit angry because of our ration
chicken with ketchup oh well how about
we you send them to his bedroom instead
Cujo chicken rugby in the books come on
school hooray let's go come on okay come
together i'm up to the bedroom here we
go guys another crisis solved weather
sure are a lot of us here Wow whole
family is starting to come together we
always come together at Christmas yeah
wife we just passed in a blur for work
for times like this hmm jingle bells
jingle bells jingle all the way oh what
fun it is to ride in a one-horse open
sleigh jingle bell jingle bell Jingle
Bell Rock jingle bell swing and
when I blow it up so fun now the jingle
hop has begun jingle bell jingle bell
Jingle Bell Rock jingle bells chime in
jingle bell time dancing and prancing in
jingle bell square we're in the process
what a break time is the right time to
rock the night away I waggle Bell time
well time to go grab me in a one-horse
sleigh hideous kinghorn pick up your
feet jingle around the bar mixed and
England England me that's the Jingle
Bell Rock
so
horn they gotta be jingle around the bar
single
Jingle Bell Rock
oh that's gonna be a terrific Christmas
tree just bring it inside guys thanks yo
fuzzy you finally made it hey Ralph wat
can reuse 8 yeah I've been chasing the
truck all the way and boy am i exhausted
yeah I get track exhaust that's funny
yeah that's dog joke Oh go inside and
come on that gosh you she loves canine
humor okay boys put it over there in the
corner hi doc let's get this Holly up
here Oh mrs. bear I've been chasing the
truck and boy whip oh my i guess Fozzie
didn't tell you about the icy patch oh
yeah I guess he didn't anyhow my name's
Ralph a dog I come for the holidays more
more people who I'll go out and see if
there's a spare pillow in the kennel
yeah don't you just hate it when you can
speak the language uh-huh just what I
was looking for look at this little
beauty the boys is being attitude I love
on two pianos
we just hear those sleigh bells you're
doing
oh dear it's lovely weather for a bear
and a snowman like you up here the snow
is falling and friends are calling you
boo come on it's lovely weather for a
bear and a snowman like you and that's
pretty good harmony for a snowman I'm
Troy i'm a snowman what's this new man
nothing's us no man what's a snoo of the
old bear it'll be a perfect party with
my friends oh there will be singing the
songs we love to sing Brad a single star
at firebase while we watch that chestnut
but seriously funny what do you think of
the weather we're having it's so cold
how cold is it it's so cold that when i
open my refrigerator this morning there
was a polar bear inside trying to keep
warm that's always cold christmas
christmas time for Santa Claus and his
eight prancing rain bear that's reindeer
no that's snow darling
dearest always funny friends are coming
too it's lovely weather for Christmas
together with
funniest comedy teams in the business
stay right the way you are come on where
are you in the kitchen Fozzie oh I get
some wonderful nose Oh current kind of
coming let me tell you about this new
Act I found aye aye mr. dis time Leslie
yeah I was outside building a strong
against a second and Oh Trevor wait wait
wait commencing hello Emily beers
residents this is Kermit the Frog oh hi
piggy sure you know welcome me I just
wanted to tell you i haven't spits of
christmas shopping to do before i come
out but piggy tonight's Christmas Eve oh
never you fear dear i should be there
sir Tata Oh green fuzzy flipper slippers
o divine having different huh turmeric
from it and I'm not gonna tell you about
my new Act I'm all ears oh wow what can
that be our policies our ears frogs
don't even have yours look my daughter
rocket he is not a Christmas turkey this
meka go blue go blue fearful news I
don't care if the turkey says the dog is
a turkey the dog is not the turkey the
turkeys the turkey you turkey on target
Oh Nicola gobbling goofy Ruthie this
it's time to be fun whoa speaking of fun
hey mom are you doing it Kermit look
what I have it's home movies I found
this old film in the closet it's the
very first Christmas the Muppets ever
spent together greet I haven't seen that
film in years turn off the lights and
roll the film
it's miss ham hocks when she was just a
little sausage roll that's why you were
still in diapers in those days oh this
is Ralph what he was a wee puppy not so
we I was paper-trained that's a little
devil I was animal yep some things never
change oh that was fun even we're
doesn't cute when they're babies I knew
you learn to love us I didn't say that I
tell you Chicken Little you're my kind
of poultry ah more what's going on here
you got some drumsticks here my fine
feathered mama Camilla's my girlfriend
you've gotta be kidding you're not even
a bird roof nobody's perfect come on any
penny lets me and you go out to the farm
yard for a little friendly scratching
and squawk all right that does it let me
at him I'm gonna rip off his wattle you
and what other news on put up your wings
turn told why you're pulling my leg oh
no your wishbone banbury bro yeah
work what do I hear you hear me about to
make some turkey hash no no listen
methinks me here's carolers give on the
camera link among the lead sorry my one
green so fair to DC love enjoy come to
you until you glad tidings to I god
bless you exert you a happy new year
it's a Sesame Street gang merry
Christmas from Sesame
the halls with boughs of holly tis the
city's on dope a jolly Don we now our
gay apparel falala lalala troll the
ancient Yuletide Carol bahahaha ok Arnie
you're next see the blazing you'll be
for us strike the harp and join the
chorus I will not sing this song by like
how do you buy pleasure your turn hairy
monster that's the lady oh dear passes
he'll knew ye lads and lasses
haha Sankey joyous all together the holy
boughs of holly tis the season to be
jolly
Oh
it's nice to have everyone here you can
feel the peace of the holiday season
knock you know what this means sprocket
and I will have to give up our hammock
in the Attic right either that or build
by failing the brim posit fucker go get
me a hammer will you uh-huh oh hi there
hey we're Ernie and burger well hi there
yourself I'm doc did you know where the
doc starts with the letter D why yes yes
yes starts with a letter wide true and
true sir to the letter D hey what is
this where we come from this is small
talk whatever you say well it's nice to
meet you but I've got to go and build
some bunk beds bye bye dad see words aah
hey no no you got me wrong I'm a dairy
cow no no no do this boy be all right
okay mother I'm a birdie I'm a birdie
I'm a seagull right don't know golf no
gardeners okay all right I admit it I a
minute the jig is up here i am the
Christmas turkey you told Chris new oh
hey watch it there will you yeah no uh
oh yeah yeah I recognize it now this is
thick this is the traditional fitting
right to see if the roasting pan is big
enough for a nice fat bird yoyoyo goblet
goblet or keep its key whiskey of course
uh before we go any further uh there is
one thing I think you should see new
miss gusta score plug of this news if
you think I'm a nice fat bird look at
this
who's the hoopla w moodle beneath the
truth hey everyone quiet down there's a
bulletin on TV and now for this news
flash the worst blizzard in 50 years is
approaching us at a great rate The
Weather Service reports that barometers
are falling sharply oh he's right look
at the snow one snowflake to snowflake
police no Miss Piggy's out there in that
storm
right the huge canary sleeps in the
Attic with the cookie eater Chuck the
blue monster said he'd sleep in the
bathtub Chuck and Ernie and Bert will
bunk out with a lizard here uh uh frog
our Kermit the Frog well what about
Oscar no I'll be nicely miserable my
trash can here hey maybe I could bunk
out here with you yeah I never had a rat
in my trash can before that might be
nice hey everybody look what I've got
Christmas cookies okay um oh don't thank
you Tom mummy who was that streams blue
creature got my kind of fella ah hey
everybody it's time to rehearse our
sesame street pageant it's call was the
night before Christmas come on Albert I
won't come on Bert hi please don't make
me Oh Bert listen everybody's waiting
Ernie why must you always humiliate me
come on Bert somebody has to play mama
and you lost the toss all right we'll
just get it over with okay hmm twas the
night before Christmas by Clement more
hit it Rolfe was the night before
Christmas and all through the house not
a creature was stirring not even a mouse
kill the mouse I'm here I'm here
this year what's a ball four oh so you
can see that I am NOT stirring note how
the hand never touches the spoon oh hey
Dorothy no way hey don't encourage them
but a milk mammalian her kerchief that's
you Bert I know I know and I in my cap
had just settled our brains for a long
winters nap went out on the lawn there
arose such a clatter I sprang from my
bed to see what was the matter over the
garden
Monsters is a reindeer this is crazy and
what was Santa Claus but don't worry
Burt we're getting to him with a little
old driver so lively and quick I knew in
a moment it must be st. Nick there's
nothing sacred oh wait a minute now who
let the two-headed monster be Santa
Claus when birdie said he'd ever been in
a plane before I mean they said it I
both of them said it I could just throw
to the Big Finish will you please okay
but I heard him exclaim ere he drove out
of sight
sorry to break up your fun in here we'll
have you folks in the winner as a real
storm out there whoa lordy I haven't
seen a sky like that since a blizzard of
41 I tell you mr. lizard it's a good
thing all your friends are safe and warm
inside the farmhouse yeah but all my
friends are not safe and warm sorry to
hear that it's cold enough out there to
freeze your Winnebago hello did you
wrong got the demo stuck in the snow
bank so i'll just have to catch a taxi
to the farmhouse listen piggy there's a
terrible storm outside and i really
think it's too dangerous to travel so
why don't you wait for the storm to end
before you join us not since and miss my
Christmas Eve with fool it's just a
little bit of snow see you soon
Oh
I'm sure miss piggy will be all right Oh
coming cometh d you look worried yeah I
know exactly what you need comedy right
yeah come on now's the time for you to
meet my new partner well who's your new
partner a snowman the heck you say Yeah
Yeah come on outside of your door act
for you outside bazi it's too cold to go
outside it's not cold it is Cole's not
cold can I come in and warm up ok so
it's cold uh I'm Kermit the Frog you
must be fozzies do partners I'll say
we're terrific yeah yeah come on you are
coming in a snowman but you are going
out a star hey hey hey everybody would
you like to see I knew act we'd love to
see her act in fact we'd hate to miss
your act in fact we'd love to hate you
right stab her what would you guys come
from they're friends of mine fuzzy they
come visit me every Christmas my mom
mother is friends with you guys these
two comics are made for each other the
snowman is ice cold and the Bears not so
hard oh please after all there's no
business like snow business come on
ignore him I smell and do a straight
line here okay hey father yes mr. snow
me you hear about that church that
burned down holy smokes our best joke oh
that does it fuzzy forget the act I'm
stored in the mouth it's too hot in here
well you know what they say if you can't
stand the heat get out of the farmhouse
bo can the back porch boy that storm is
really getting worse yeah i hope miss
piggy is okay there is one great frog ah
that's wrong won't worried frog he's not
the only one that's two to worry throat
uh uh uh huh search me horse all talk I
think I better go up get some firewood
hi there did you wish to talk to me
about something mr. go yo yo yo bigger
coolers a nice kitchen hey are you gonna
have cranberry sauce and mashed potatoes
y'all and spearing and burn yeah coclico
please I just wanna I just want to hear
about the whole meal young Emma but
first I want to give this little present
to you you been huh it's it's chocolate
covered birdseed I made it myself
remember the more I wanted to give it to
you because well I know that you're from
Sweden and it must be hard for you
because you're away from your family and
loved ones during the holidays and
Christmas there are places and people
and things that become very very special
chestnuts roasting on an open fire Jack
Frost nipping at your nose even spoken a
single neighbor Eskimos everybody knows
a turkey and some mistletoe
they're calling stir big though it's
been said many times many ways Merry
Christmas Merry Christmas
now there mr. cook just tell me exactly
what are you going to fix for Christmas
dinner Oh Oh scraper vehicle crannon
bucher shredded wheat and cranberry
sauce my absolute favorite going to be
lots of snow for me to shovel tomorrow
oh it's getting worse and worse out
there aren't you glad you're in here all
warm and toasty I just wish Miss Piggy
you were okay one two
really worried about your friend Ike
occur hmm oh well uh yeah yeah oh I'll
tell you what I'll go out looking for
really but but you've never even met
Miss Piggy well we we never met any of
you on a little while ago and now we're
friends well she's freaky and I were
gonna spend Christmas alone but this is
better now what your friend look like oh
well our to begin with them she's a pig
well up to a short while ago I would
have thought that strange I'll give it a
try gee thanks dark
you'll be sorry it's cold enough to
freeze your Winnebago what a sweet guy
uncle Kermit Robin where are you in the
cellar what are you doing down there I
made a discovery whoo what are you what
are you talking about you're never
telling me about Fraggle holes uh yeah
so now if I ever found one that we could
go into Fraggle Rock and maybe meet some
Fraggles ah so is that one who look at
that well it certainly looks like one
you never know where you're gonna find
these things can we go we're not go
Kermit well maybe maybe just a little
ways see if we can meet anyone mind is
Gary these are beautiful caves gee
niggas just really Fraggle Rock well I
don't know but if I were a Fraggle I
think this is the kind of place I'd hang
out wait a second I thought I heard
something it's not
oh well uh uh hi there hi yourself I
your Fraggles say but you're not I'll
see I know I I'm Kermit this is Robin
we're frogs whoa what's a frog I'll say
don't touch him frogs are probably noted
German carriers oh well actually we just
came down here to wish you all a Merry
Christmas what's Christmas soon oh don't
you have Christmas no well that's when
you gather together with the people you
love and you wish each other peace on
earth oh we have a time like that yes we
do have a matter of fact we're
celebrating it right now see we give
each other little presents I'm getting
Boober this nice yellow pepper and I
gave whoopee that pebble last year and I
gave it to read here before that i'll
give it to you Wembley the year before
that that pebbles been a gift 37 x 37
times yeah la la la la la la
la la la la la la la pass it on when
it's nice and frightened and it brings
me like let your heart choose right
gotta based on when it feels real good
like a feeling should when it's
understood gotta pass it on when you're
giving lova wait love will come again
tuesday what you give is what you gain
when you cap it off when i give a gift
to you I know you're gonna get it too
that's like isn't what we do
rip off all the good things that you do
pass it on
grannies gone it will bring good luck to
you when you're giving love away club
will come again to say what you get it
what you get when you and I give a gift
you know they're gonna give if you
that's why givings what we do and that's
the way dragon presents oooh I love it I
almost forgot I want you Thank You mokey
hey listen Fraggles this has all been
great but we got to be going oh she sing
the wait wait wait wait wait Robin
before you go I'd like you to have this
pebble oh wow gee well Merry Christmas
freckles dash that was fun yeah well
it's nice to be with friends at
Christmas Kermit we hear shouting
outside it could be Miss Piggy oh oh
let's go anyone see her out there well
at least the storm has eased up a bit
all right chef why don't you make some
hot soup and mrs. beer would you put
some extra blankets on a bed wait a
minute there she is what
yeah and she don't look bad for pig
Oh Merry Christmas kami am i late I I
don't know how to explain this curve but
I was searching through the snow and
suddenly there was Miss Piggy with this
costume for me you don't have to explain
doc if there's one thing Piggy knows
it's how to make an entrance you are
when you
for the holidays you can be all
okay mom everybody commandos here buddy
everybody request my mother has an
announcement Thank You favi I'd like to
welcome you all here you are all here
aren't you good because I'm afraid we're
running out of room two of you will have
to sleep hung on hangers on a hook on
the wall what a fabulous idea love hang
love hang it ah that's the only way
animal ever sleeps man hey mom I told
you be easy they're weirdos fuzzy yeah
but they're nice weirdos yeah well
everybody is Christmas Eve and the tree
is trimmed so it's time for our annual
Carol thing take it Rolf happy holiday
hey happy holiday happy holiday happy
holidays
everybody stop ding dong merrily on high
in heaven the bells are ringing ding
dong merrily the sky is rip with angel
sing
what's there it's free let's go see a
deer I saw three ships come sailing in
on Christmas Day on Christmas Day I saw
three ships come sailing linnean on
Christmas Day in a morning what was in
the ships of me Christmas Day honest
mistake what was in those shits off me
on Christmas Day in the morning Good
King Wenceslas looked down on the feast
of Stephen when the snow lay round about
deep and crisp and even brightly shone
the home at night Oh Ross was cruel well
maintained inside during winter
Holly and the ivy when they are both
full-grown of all the trees that are in
the wood the Holly
I'll be home for Christmas you can count
on me
you have no present
happy holiday hey happy holiday holiday
calendar keep bringing Happy Holidays to
you
as in all the days happy golden days
of your
faithful Friends who are dear to us
gather near to us once cool piggy
yourself a merry little Christmas eat
your heart now on our troubles will be
out of sight
the years we all will be together hang a
shining star upon the highest
I have yourself a merry little green
dismiss bells are ringing girlie
gir-leeeeee due to snow christmas bells
are ringing joyous voices weed and clear
thing the side of our two tier in gone
down christmas balls are heavily turning
gear upon following our yonder star
mark UL the song we sing webs and items
now we bring
Christmas bells are
I heard the bells on Christmas a their
own familiar carols play and wild and
sweet the words repeat of peace on earth
goodwill to men it's in
every one of us
movie
wise
I
Oh
all
oh why
Oh friends new friends along with my
family will be together at christmas
snowflakes sleigh bells ringing back
memories will be too
something's changed with passing years
what does feel instead
new friends Oh me
Oh
together
you know Miss Piggy I think it's time I
gave you your prison well your present
is a mink Oh a Marine hi I'm moving the
me what she said hi I'm Laureen the main
harder harder oh this is this is a mink
I make worse oh I've seen everything
you've done I'm your biggest fan I wish
if the ground you walk on speaking of
presents Grover I'd like you to have
this Fraggle pebble ah did this Fraggle
pebble here is for me oh I just love
Christmas
merry Christmas everyone well he
certainly seems to be having a good time
out there sprocket yeah I like it when
they have a good time if I tell you what
somebody's gonna do something about
these dishes rocket come on I'll wash
and you dry mistletoe every Christmas
killed
Merry Christmas
merry Christmas everyone
you
Oh