yeah
michela dr. Watson what is keeping mr.
Holmes too long
reassuring boy yourself sisters you
don't really like will be with you
momentarily any which we have been
waiting almost one hour mr. all this is
a very pretty man sister just be Oh mr.
owns an arm plays ocupe sister but
tomorrow is the festival of st. better
already thousands of blind Clippers are
flocking to the chapel hoping to kiss
the relic in the name of all the
flocking blind cripples teaching house
ey know that God
yeah
homes are you there
no 1 i'm in Budapest sorry Holmes I'm
forward your mail and some very
disappointing news for leaders
apparently shown up arms in broader past
this is to look for coffee Watson i'm
now he's back
oh good of you to come home you remember
these three nuns from monty can or their
only request all and all the other case
of the engineers tumbles it no no no the
the other it's not no no house and
panels elbow elbows feet thumbs with all
these cases i'll never get any of this
now the ladies mr. Holmes
what do you think may have perpetrated
this offer crime
well to put it by simply in layman's
terms easily understandable to nuns I
believe this to be the work of thieves
all patent is very reminiscent to pass
blocking is where i found thieves to be
involved the tell-tale loss of property
the snatching away of substances it all
points to slaves but how can you find
such a person
well i'm using a wonderful new system
not even going to Scotland Yard i'll
call it picture fit
oh yes that's when you piece together
the face of the criminal isn't it unless
know i can only piece together the
appearance of the face of the terminal i
cannot piece together the actual face
shot good because of course once you
catch the criminal face the other
criminal parts are not hard to find the
criminal body being situated directly
beneath the criminal face join of course
but the criminal Nick so the relic is
lost forever on the country you have fun
did you miss your arms of course
starting bond of your congregation
triples are they not really you know Sam
amazing arse with a simple Watson our
spot which cripple it was immediately
the one launching around the shrine with
the
protruding from his waistcoat MSC
Monsieur merci
yeah
I
ha
yeah
the mouth
Lord
really
yeah
look let me I'd say it was a middle-aged
dr. hearing from dartmoor named probably
Mortimer LG deduce that Watson that's
what he told me when he made an
appointment this morning and if i'm not
mistaken that's him again
what's and i'm exhausted for all these
cases them without saying but i might no
guarantees or identity alright alright
precisely and sorry about that come on
in
thank you yes dr. was yes indeed yes
going through and arms
this is dr. modern man another
modernization of warms you don't get up
mr. I've no intention of doing so what's
the fetchers gentlemen the chair alright
because made it to do something you have
to be all my goodness why don't you take
a seat come tomorrow man
take yourself down yeah thank you oh
thank you oh yeah now I tell you mr.
Holmes how much how that my dude over
the years
well that's really dr. Mortimer please
get on with it I let me explain first of
all that I am the executor of the
Baskervilles estate valued at over a
million pounds
almost all in property a vast expanse of
gasoline more about the challenges dozen
times natural causes was it not all
levels for the public but it is in my
opinion that's a chance was murdered
mother by supernatural means like yeah
hello we are living in the 20th century
at me
we'll be that as it may local legend has
it that a monstrous boot available Hound
of Hell has been the death of every
single master of Baskerville Hall
how dr. Mortimer just what were the
circumstances of Sir Charles's death
well sir charles basketball was my
patient for a great number of years
during which time he was complete the
same but as the years went by he became
somewhat of a rituals really leaving his
estate and building a huge fence around
the whole of the property he became
completely and madly obsessed with the
idea that the legendary Hound of the
Baskervilles was going to return to
destroy him
how extraordinary see nothing unusual
and the numbers are my thoughts exactly
home
oh yes i was called the house in my
official capacity is kana to investigate
the extraordinary circumstances in which
is Charles body was found to go on and
spare no detail however small get it
over with
ya got it shot on his face was food in
the look of such extraordinary terror
that it was almost impossible to
recognize him
there was no sign of physical violence
on the body whatsoever but close by
footprints enormous and next and well
let's have it mr. Holmes they were the
footprints of a gigantic home doesn't
have a huge dripping jars and and and
great closing eyes and enormous private
parts
no but how do you know what I used to
have a little Pekinese like that you
know it's just a bleep up on the bad and
bad its friends and then when I was mr.
Watson in love straightforward to me
absolutely couldn't write in that didn't
would be able to meet the air and myself
. until ten o'clock tomorrow morning or
what you think God should we meet the
area the hair yeah the air here all the
air there there tomorrow 10 hear ya
there
yeah
may I introduce young Henry Baskerville
add a possible hole and 2,000 acres of
swamp
I can't thank you enough mr. Holmes for
coming here this morning I mean what
with you being dropped wonderful sleuth
you must help us mr. Holmes a sinister
incident good last night killings and
yes
will I would be there because you see
I've no not be him
oh yes okie dokie i went to bed early
last night because I felt a bit under
the weather touch of Dickie Tommy 10
runs in the family get wet anyway I put
my boots out to be shy and when I got up
in the morning I opened the door and
would you believe it
one of them with meeting to think on the
way smart time combing the streets of
London for some old boot this is a job
for an embassy or quite right on let me
deal with this scenario the book your
lunch was tall and what color was it
blackburn your prior a problem here from
exactly the same color as this boat the
one we have in front of us
of course i always try to get to the
same color too much of a coincidence
homes
I don't like this man of this the smell
exactly what better way to entice a
hound and to give it some personal
object from me she can derive the center
of the intended victim
yes sir henry is in great
ginger I'm sorry gentlemen I'm not
available to take this case Doctor
Watson will handle the matter
Oh are no I've never done anything on my
own me far I think you have what are you
sure you won't change your mind mr.
Hellman on side of the Mortimer on very
t'adore have another cases being the
world's greatest detective is no better
of roses i'll leave you in good hands
goodbye gentlemen I'll find my own way
out yeah he probably well yeah this is a
bitter disappointment to me
uh-huh uh-huh let's get down to business
ah there are one or two things have been
bothering me about this kiss ah oh
first-year this stick with you are you
dr. more than I see by this hair that
you are . fancier spaniel retriever
labrador how perhaps no it's a special
dog bed by a friend of mine on the moors
it's mexican they call it a chiuaua they
have get everywhere nature wise i have
this beach dr mortimer not on the moor
dr watson naturally adopt you about
Norma and where and at what time does
the train leave for basketball tomorrow
have a truck Victoria don't know you can
call me John we will recognize each
other by wearing pink carnations in
other pills or I like you
yes . yes I do
you dr. Morgan man dr. Watson cosine dr.
Mortimer unit we're like dr. Mortimer
well then where's your carnation AMV
wouldn't even be spoiling espero que yo
parte para o caves by the window
good thinking
a passing yourself dr. Martin a lot of
neighbors and basketball along well is
this chap steep and he's the champion
that you're wise and his sister a
strange couple in this Franklin man was
obsessed with catching the pound and his
mistress strange couple in this mr. and
mrs. Patmore been at the hall for
generations a strange couple in this
Marcia the scullery maid and package the
groom has changed couple what on earth
made you think that that a charming
there just aren't you
I really exhausted all his traveler oh
did you enjoy your boy over from Canada
know it was 10 I happen to be our first
rule of the dick when a storm came up
gale winds ports me to hang onto the
rail for dear life
black hold on no longer yeah
suddenly this great wave keep crashing
over the boat and washed me overboard
just go over to keep our heads about war
truck it was horrible horrible did you
manage to drag us out on deck where I
just dress casual
yeah
you seem to be taking a devil of a time
to get the whole yes I thought I'd take
a pretty way sir
here stop danger he won't and we only
married a month for good job he's
wearing the appliance yeah
ah dr. ma trigger
yes we're still searching for Seldon
ambitious expedition no oh yeah oh yeah
I don't matter he's the man who escaped
just before Charles was found dead
ah that awful man around hacking people
to pieces and sending the bit to his MP
extra ones her and you'd better watch
out because they've seen quite a bit of
American best get all recently and you'd
better tell your and there they better
bigger 05 on talking cbourgin prime
targets right even drive on Tarkin's to
even Bergen
good idea and attachment feed strange
couple what you stop animals and
compacted to be written as a child I ate
the difference will rise elderly people
in fact tried everything
Thank called you arrived I thought you'd
never get here mr. Barrymore I want to
use the you ask Henry basketball and his
friend dr. Watson there until saturday
for the reading of the will
dr. no tumor who had devil do you think
you are getting me not this mama died
happy me was fast asleep i want you to
choose the enemy and he's gonna take
defend the usual basketball hospitality
mr. Barrymore will relieve you
you're clever and
mrs. Patmore i would like to get started
right away I'm perhaps you would be so
kind as to show me show me to my my my
clothes you bought make lose
oh well let me see what can I show you
this of course his best of it all is
ethically and for you that's cup and all
yes yes it is yes indeed but forgive me
this is just the the whole of basketball
is Matt oh yes everything points to that
yes that's right this is grab our would
you get us something to eat we're
absolutely if damaged my stomach's
chattering a rare i didn't know really
some people barrel where you got there
out there cheese a Down oh cheese my
word we are being indulged to not be you
that's better than cocoa bean name
County utilize your circulation within
in no tang shodeh adjourn to the dining
room sudden me we have to see the
diagram the ballroom everything think
all this is going to be mine
no you don't want to see the dining room
down and I'm not having you checking all
that food out of the house
I'm telling event and I think I'm not
wasting my John cleaning up our to the
two of you this time and not can mom ate
up this compose
there you are God God I could have put
you in the master bedroom of course but
you'd have been overhauled wouldn't you
are you would I know your tent you like
to live casual you detectives but I'm
not a detective
of course you're not done you ever said
you was I want to explain the rules of
the outs for you are you yeah sorry my
husband that we like to get about five
o'clock in the afternoon but we're not
getting any younger you know least
office kitchen on the base or rather
he's not getting on as much as act like
him too if you catch my drift
anyway we like to get out at about two
o'clock in the afternoon but then of
course we have our own details to attend
yeah right from four o'clock 415 all
yours any think your heart disease as
you ever need to ask and of course you
know i have to get all of us if you want
it in don't you know new good that's
what I love your jim-jams watching that
it's smart
thanks very much family i think actually
want to get some sleep because we got a
very hot here to model
well if you want to anything tonight
hospital
I've got ya like ya had a very light
sleeper
yes me too good God
excuse me is this the pic of early
health and relaxation as part of the
pelle that's right i'm gonna be possible
for me to Hawaii
yeah massage scheduled this device
services thank you
yes but what I get for the gentleman's
half-hour lunch spot on with pressure
five shillings you get a basic rubdown
with flour and water
most of our clients finding ceases
special one of the more stimulating and
stop the more expensive that the
pendulums sanken bar to good lad master
and course a complimentary Green not
white this bold white with the dog of
the choices light is from our selection
of delectable damsels weights you behind
the bead cap one Guinea
with evening the ladies I have a ticket
for the better no boudoir we kept
walking workout hack for I was just
looking out of the window
I think someone signaling her body Bar I
see you are flashing the winds make all
across the old reflect our light
throughout the night I saw someone else
signaling across the Lord it's more
school I've learned that I think two
gentlemen had better go to your room
it's way past your bedtime known about
him or got some investigations to go
outside to see you always doing night
gentlemen
well no that's what it that we have that
sir yes indeed all that fashion practice
area clashing make Erica
yeah
what what what do you go dear over dr.
don't want to be a doctor he's tracking
down the jump
yeah you gotta come you know shop you
give him a few price
oh really oh don't want to do now
operations on not that he's quite way to
stop time noticing you know restart ever
so klever me the other day I said I the
code turn back time we can you call it
the bacchanal ha ha here the medieval
torture chamber huge impact on elephant
oh I know that without shame shy slow
your it's okay you're gonna be my I'm
again yes
yeah you don't feel much like your room
you will you three ladies about exactly
what I'd expected
Oh No
yeah
yeah help you doing a shiny cry with you
scared country girls also you know it's
coming from downstairs
it's been going on like that for the
last three hours why didn't you wake me
sooner than we think about it right
there will be so don't you just stop
that I'm warning years a bit of
fundraiser I never had that i lo
what's going on you're in my dining room
revenue time to get together next what
mr. Barrymore sister fold up to the side
hey fellow know about so we decided to
make it a crime anyway why I don't seem
to remember in Virginia you dr. Watson
know you sir h excuse us I'm not for
everybody bottom or don't need to have
some bricks to fall on me how mean all
that who I know
did you notice that woman with a loud
voice and enormous weapon
yes you think she's held and the axe
murderer
no no no so then we show you saw the
amazing resemblance between her and mr.
body more say my name nor same as god
that's his system
yeah yes we have to do know when you see
I'm a detective I'm clean today on
I hope it's a nice day tomorrow oh yeah
I
four-seam I more ghastly with spray i
don't think the spirits will be two
places happens great
yeah hand on table fingers tap Jade are
you think are you there was the time all
week
whoever you are you know heard of
comfort from his 20 via my beloved
husband is enjoying his tennis and says
to keep using the mouse wash be guided
by happy
yes I where the probability of the rest
was in the room is a potato make your
presence held rise up eyeball time even
to stop enjoying a spy school rise up
top right that work table this table
doesn't here to will
excuse me while i deal with this
malignant spirits please don't leave
this room except by the door show you my
son a common faith mother I'll just
party bar called up in my Lord and get
the party going to be asleep sleep you
know very well I haven't script writing
and that wasn't your beloved father died
bringing up father mother all why not
why not you drove him to his stare
oh my god that's dripping into other
people's business for detecting for
detecting detecting pesticide I'm some
guilty of pissed atty papasan mother
oh so you admit then do you never change
now you treated him as badly as you
treat party
what's this perfectly all I've mother
perfectly alright mother indeed oh I'm
sure no don't tell me you and want to
have a quarrel and he's walked out on
you and frankly I don't blame and and
then got nobody to cook for you maybe to
do your laundry come snooping around
here to steal a lonely old ones pork pie
I've got mrs. mark tells me that you
into that disgusting problems down the
road a woman tries my own fingering and
family my boy I think it's just got
thing this guy thing and what people
have been doing my work out tell me oh
my god i see it clearly
I volcana palm trees at the island
mother wish you'd give up his psychic
oaks a good land as both in trouble
don't have to answer that show or maybe
are under arrest for your crimes mother
god please have something to eat
you can have anything you like for me my
diamont iris and I are here to help you
remember i received my link with the
spirit well
oh yes mother I like to strike a happy
medium
I know my business thinking show by the
way that mentioned death in front of you
would you like to make my little pony
cup of tea iris
oh yeah yeah stupid care now then shall
mother please I'm call me girl I've
always called you sure and I always will
owe you for the city was a little girl
iris I'll never was a little girl mother
up a little golden curls in percents of
fun
oh I should put you in the loveliest
stresses you were the prettiest girl on
the blog gunma you he'll come anyway let
me bring you up-to-date all the
wonderful things have been happening
here iíve read to you about my stroke
and yes mother yes let's get these
clothes if any smelly come on the
climate mother
yes I think it was a combination of
things you know my brother came around
my brother Bernat was drunk as a lord it
was so rude to me I said I said burn
after don't be so rude
don't be so damn road to me I was so
upset about what shops shops to get some
fish for Sparky I always walk there and
back you know on the right back mrs.
prayer he said to me mrs. Holmes said I
have been talking about my choice again
nothing what you mean what you mean your
choice
she said about her having a baby and not
being married I said mrs. bread I said
excuse me I said I don't talk about your
choice acts I've got better things to do
with my time upset i came home i would
like to bed and then that he came to me
at the bottom of the bay
it to me come either Carly he said
you're tired
come with me that's enough that's it no
matter
that's it no I've got to wait here on
this earth until nice am my little baby
is happily married anyway I woke up in
the morning did not back up in the
morning and i thought i had around you
because you know the windows I'm is
virtually when coming through and the
doctor came came to me and said I have a
strong because my face my face was all
outside about it but that of course but
it's all come down now
artis family I was for out face down in
the toilet
anybody ever back what about what i
expect you bring one of your regulars
haven't you
mother please don't interfere in my
business hey thank you tell me don't you
tell me when to interfere when not to
interfere
I'm your mother wanted to be when
opening want and what he you know he
can't handle assignment on his own
mother if he's in any danger haha
another inventor all like are also go
down to the balls myself yes I hope her
because if not if not down in myself and
all i've got him at all will be well I'm
sure you'll never regret this you never
dies
why don't interact iris
oh what a terrible morning little frog
want a bocce there are you what'd he
make watching morning looks like a
really time to make day-to-day and that
if I know my hair will be in this so you
stay here and I'll go to the telegraph
office and cables about barrymore sister
i love with you I very world selling we
are totally we can't risk that used a
year and get on with your new good
morning gentlemen money mr. bad at all .
b day is great I've never seen fog this
bad and all my life must be absolutely
all right I'm gonna be able to
investigate anything know what is clear
is the barrel outside
what do you mean you're going to save
fucking the more glass case and dogs
fucking the our sons out for field house
and never that far
alright see for yourself it is that
family morning you'll be able to lock
your doors after all
yes gonna walk that you'll be able to
show me the exact place where as a child
yes I remember the night clearly my way
it would not allow such a chance to use
these indoor bathroom very big about to
this one that AC this is mrs starr
balding sitting tenant
been squatting there for years or meet
my podcast which i'm closer child lost
his life trying to reach this thread for
toilet is this is the very spot
oh how all oh no no what we gotta have
any God God if I not be sticking these
are the plants of a drag can't account
for UCB anymore they never poke menos
into other people's business
be that as it made I have to talk to the
neighbors whether the students live
forever in me repeat or on the moors mm
it's very dangerous there you might get
sucked top by good input Maya very
Christian nevertheless I have a job
article mr. battle then dream I want to
stay in your room and not been get out
here on the more you see how close to
help came to get a child I won't leave
my room
yeah
honey what can I do you do you work here
yes but would you mind keeping your
voice down there was another
confidential message I wish to technical
after London thinking channel fair whole
phone so far style farted investor
vacation stuff up right that seems
simple enough sir your home stop-start
investigation stop stop the
investigation today stop working on stop
stop
good god man you broke the cold yeah we
don't use this one anymore so been out
of date easy
oh if you want a really undecipherable
code you'll never wear my cleanness Oh
Land gentleman air needs a cow
oh come on face and child stops a crack
should be right here sir
bad night madam but she's illustrating
the culture she's always talked like
that
i I don't understand it's the cold of
opposite sir everything she say is the
reverse of what she means
good morning sorry dad night nothing wow
you give this a worldliness and your
life had as a good girl
dear Holmes stop hurried home start/stop
investigations
start restarting investigations
yesterday start not working nonstop
start
yeah i got much better one no one's ever
cracked
yeah mrs. Granger she got Beauty you
show this gentleman years sausage and
mash Daphne I love it like the last one
actually know your waiter you wear this
every where to begin with an ass Aaron M
we substitute sausage or mash go on
Thanksgiving around in our own sausage
sausage investigation sausage sausage
investiga wait a moment there's
something I gotta have at the end of the
school bad anymore
has a very peculiar sister barrymore
alfalfa belfry perfect yourself mr.
anymore as a very normal brother anymore
I peculiar a sausage I'm getting a bit
confused on your way sir i'll combine
all three codes and send it in
yeah
hello dr. once dr. modern man how good
the investigations
Oh slowly but surely
oh yes by the way I yeah I wonder if you
could help me with something
certainly what I don't suppose it means
anything but as I was crossing the more
i checked through an entire side of beef
at me
it's a local custom oh no you never
spanked him he's out on the moors
everything they throwing up meters be
for the Hound all obsessed by the brute
or do you think I ought to have a word
with then yes I would
yes i have my own suspicions ever since
he expressed enormous grudge against the
child all DNE yeah what was that about
you ever found out i have you can either
have something here
yeah he lives up by Grimpen beautiful
some animals for me i can never sleep
with me tonight
oh it's this one good luck with all of
this
yeah
don't pull the hell are you today
that's my meet you mr. Franklin the
expert on the Hound of the Baskervilles
so maybe I'm maybe I'm not and you that
make it to Detective come down from
London
yes the very same where you step inside
last so many trophies
mr. cranky if you did enjoy the
excitement of the hunted of you who
killed an element i don't remember
oh nothing
ok I I heard of your reputation with
outcome yea years I've been doing this
one for the left talkin to Phil Spector
dump came here to find a time that we
don't take have you seen him know what's
best friends
Oh exclaims many years he would now what
happened that empty hate to make me rich
friends the world in one night how you
slide without haha yeah what a monster
would do ours victims and go whoop
yes cost make sure yeah
it did you did you know the late Sir
Charles next class back dad
o.o you you didn't like such as then
write him hate him he tightens use
painted community have poor help
President man right here huh
and maybe even hear them dr. Watson nice
to meet you and your husband was I never
talk
oh god you're like I was telling me how
are ye his friends were massacred by the
house race right we did it happen I
don't know exempted all of our Insano
drank anhui you seem to be a very
rational and yeah I am rockin out on the
ground in 20 minutes later the better
meet house I random biker
remaining ought to be
coming because I thought of you to come
along with us all the mothers might miss
the bigger than it not yes because
tonight detection is a bigger than I am
and detection is the guy god you're
right mr. spiggott is not there the
plate tag powerfully my thinking like a
nothing the least that you just settle
down for one moment please mr. spiggott
there you are applying why you not for
the job on the walls as a loner right
mr. spiggott Oh you don't noticing
almost immediately
well that you are a one Liddy domain
how are you at United's camp when you've
been in the business as long as I have
mr. spiggott you get to notice these
little things almost instinctively yeah
well your parenting children never
suspect that you a one-legged man are
applying for the job of the sauna and I
a job
traditionally associated with a
two-legged man
yes and yet you a you Dexter applying
for the job I have a job for which two
legs would seem to be the minimum
requirement
well mr. spiggott need I point out to
you with overmuch emphasis where your
deficiency lies as the gods landing the
job can't make your 10 is perhaps oil
need also you with too much stress that
it is
the labor division that you are
deficient the leg division the leg
division mr. spiggott you are deficient
in the leg division to the tune of one
your light leg I like it's a lovely leg
for the job as soon as i saw it coming
on sat alone
what a lovely leg for the job
I've got nothing against you lightly the
trouble is neither have you
you fall down on the left our meaning
and click it seeing as that's what mr.
spiggott study and in my view the site
of a one-legged wanna hopping across the
malls might draw unwanted attention but
the despair mr. spiggott I mean after
all you score over a man with no legs at
all but one hundred percent uh yeah I
got twice as many exactly so that's no
help
of course there is still hope mr.
spiggott I mean if i get no two-legged
runners in here with inside the next 18
months there is every chance that you a
uni Dexter will be the very type of
person I should be attempted to contact
these RVs the job
wow I'm just sorry I can't be more
definite at this stage but you must
understand that the description exactly
is very precise work that and I'll call
the court but like any of this
whatsoever you misfigured oh one thing
mr. speaker
oh good what I scared i could be with
the out I is contrary to my talk don't
pay for next year when your time I I'm
just walking across the Moors from
basketball and best people how you know
you must be ahead rare happy fall be
ready to meet you
you can't imagine how pleased we are
that you about you have finally arrived
oh I happen when I'm and you are your
name is it your name
no staples unstable just kept and I was
just on my way to see you about this
mysterious sound that it's supposed to
have Carter child his death supposed to
be with other boys that I could only
have been the federal have lives to
wreak vengeance on the cursing
basketball family
uh-huh you shouldn't be out here sir
henry are not say that once you just
like the rest well so far i seem to have
been in more danger from your laptop
right come on huh
I don't just say was your uncle's a
child how do you mean comes and we must
know why uncle despise my Chihuahua's
the accused of founding up the volume of
fifties this will be taking them onto
his property and little darlings intro
it was much lighter now so that a Pascal
we're quite so casually interested in
woodstock aside after 10
not that you see is my baby is look at
you and he just wanted to make Britain
book eat your pocket and be your friend
Connor didn't know her there and we
don't have laptop
oh it's you i love you down yeah a
little dark help got him excited you're
not sure if you mean what do we write
forever
you don't understand it just wants to be
friends there yeah well thanks very much
yep look no thanks very much and want to
meet my sister and have a cup of tea
yeah well I'd been very interested in
making out of Kleenex we got way to beat
you leave just over there
yeah you couldn't put you couldn't put
your dog down could you thought heavens
and the rest of them fully into the
swamps don't take long for little log
like this together okay I'm sorry yes I
got apologizing to people
alright i'm sorry that i'm sorry i
didn't mean I didn't mean to say sorry
and pay and got me all my not imposing
on you but he must be a one-minute home
she's a little under the weather I
nothing serious i tire just a little
something she picked up more and hope
you get better soon when you know how
we've been to exaggerate yeah they're
all for their names on the nights of
Charles died she encounter at the house
broker past career since we're just be
confined to her bed does get his little
daughter but if it were a kid up Papa
gave it to give a personal question mr.
Bolton but damn it why how you can find
a bed and doctors orders i'm afraid i've
been a little rundown we yeah yeah we
are
I hope it's not too strong no not and is
not am your brother informs me that you
actually have seen this legendary how
that
is this true true are you another two
about my word another to call me mad I
tell you I saw this house is clearly as
I see you now and I'm over here
statement pokey
well actually I got enough it when
you're nothing
Thank You mr. find yours I got enough
tea i was out on the more than not your
uncle guy I felt this string this need
wonder over the basketball escape
I'm think about the meaning of my life
such as it wore such as you could be
yeah yes i know the feeling but he won't
miss table Tanya who I was overwhelmed
by the beauty of the night the more for
it was a dream to breathe eyepiece were
shot by we're on the moss
yes oh so terrifying that govern himself
loose around swirling mist depth of huge
hideous creature with that dripping and
glowing whatnot made 3k anything from
its nostrils
did you notice anything unusual about it
no it was on me in a flash I swore I
think you're doing things to me on and
on through the night
got it never stop it was insane
our reporter who their yourself any
further payments Stapleton really I
quite understand why knew you would I
felt at the moment I saw you all someone
I could trust you must give me whatever
you feel like they are before you me you
like me I'm please fuck up a favor and
try us out
ok
yeah
Watsky one after you doing with my
patient you mean you're not saying
really not inform anyone know you can
find she got me like this . also i think
would never leave I'll let myself out
I now me
I know what knock at the prong suite
door when i come home at night my number
23 that thousand worried I'm always
right
I don't walk it my goodness you with all
her heart must have had a good day
yeah it's not bad yeah all by yourself
right to definitely killed me i stayed
here all the time I being as good as
gold anyway starting we can't be too
careful right away anymore told me his
wife put some food out there for us for
the only thing she left here all day was
a little cold lamb that's wonderful i'm
famished wear that with their God God
good morning dr. Watson if you'd like
one of our options and expense auction
option it's the contents and furniture
basketball only possessions later
Charles that's very hard
the wheel has made me wretched good god
must get a little shallow homes
immediately about this is not a
telephone in this godforsaken town
shoulder is so down in the post office
I homes it's what's on ya son
it's funny I did you come down
immediately on the next plane to
basketball 12 noon train you'll be in
disguise
well I'm gonna recognize your and what I
do every time you can
alright then they didn't gentlemen get
around if you please
what he will be buried more than telling
everything you must do without being no
body suddenly I don't I look into this
yeah dr. Martin map
dr. Martin I hard to watch
nice to see you again yes very puzzled I
mean why this sale
Charlie the contents of basketball long
out of a different part of southern
region and advanced afraid not
she's a child's wanted the animals they
have the contents of all in view of the
wages that here they stink
I don't think it's very unfair earlier
an animal could live in our first night
I mean that be no place to sit darling
sleep who misses daddy Moses will fight
for company out there in the loss
oh yeah one more day and that's why we
didn't your area here in the nice have
webbed feet
yeah
which one Easter that one who the tall
funny looking one
he's a stranger that must be where I
can't see him and he's the one picking
you know which one I'm thinking is that
why he actually behind
ah the tall one yeah that must be him
now gentlemen we come to the next
festival victim 18 sir llew reporting
very is clean can only do I want young
radish what you might be not with this
video kinda might you be someone to whom
I can trust message concerning the
safety of saying in romesco unlikely i
knew any vegetable heirloom I've got to
talk
I know about this hound and your family
you're not going to escape the curse
unless I can talk tonight matter who on
earth are you I'm little Stapleton i
live on the more i was expecting me
is there any further bid you don't want
to make city that would give you
management for that bit of rubbish
so tonight to clean this country stop
York's and save my professor and I can
certainly and then I find all homes yeah
i'm not aware you hearing this case and
nobody must know ready which one is it i
might now be alright
unlike your guard you want to rush God
God harms home my favorite traveling
coat has been stolen first job now your
coat
it's a little pattern know it was there
playing cotton so mr. Hanley what did
your uncle see fit to himself painted in
such a novelistic style that's not a
charge we come to the last of the series
of the best bills
what is he it's an interesting piece of
work
painted by the name that Charles in the
last days of his life his old self
portrait much how goal of geraniums I'd
say and i'm going to loosening thank you
dr. multimatic charge 32 is 32 is 331
right right right i have three four five
six seven eight knowledge I have nine
chili the gentleman in the back to is 10
who is that derelict so it would say
Henry and invited him to dinner tonight
wha so the gentleman now see what you
made me do i've missed a bit
no nevermind see that you invite the
right man to dinner this time I think
Arielle definitely need know I know I
know what to keep the oil we want to i
think that woman has designs on him
oh yes indeed
you were seven and its temperature
what shall i wear just be there
I think she likes I get over you bought
this arms are gonna where I'm going to
hang it in Baker Street I got exactly
what some a perfect likeness of the
Hound of the Baskervilles hiding father
writes the Charles and hung upside down
by Glynis who used to work in the hole
and as you know get everything backwards
exactly sure that means such as actually
saw the help and the painting and far is
that
yes sire think he did find that the boys
their pots
I don't think he painted afterwards so
that means that it's actually a huge got
around that on the Mars precisely what
we can't possibly next time we go out
and have dinner with battle tonight on
the country and the Henry will not
benefit whole display these backup axons
of who's on the painting i am
yeah
i know i could come on all the time
what
that's why traveling cute
Oh turtle environment barrymore sister
Ethel the flasher who is in reality none
other than souls and the vicious
ex-mother and why was the allocation him
because he thought it was the heavenly
having been given the scent for your
boot the blood stolen from the hotel get
back into your coats and leap after
watching was terribly i wouldn't be seen
getting that Kurt that remains to be
seen
God homes are suspects animals out here
not a word about cell than the Hound to
come in fight with her side few much
safer if you repair its in Watsons hands
now isn't he mastered yet
bahar God saying we weren't expecting
you but you invited me here but we still
weren't expecting you
you had no trouble on the more already
far from it actually mr. Don here we had
I know it was everything pleasant where
you might as well come in thank you let
me take your coat sir henry i would test
the late 70s where I didn't mean to be
exact date it's just when we were
crossing memorize there's no need to
explain
so Emily what is more important is that
I have reason to believe that are
terrible crime is about to take place
here who don't tell me you're going to
play to take to begin dr. Watson you're
hardly qualified really dr. Mortimer on
it takes to be a detective is courage
intelligence press of your nose and
again it
oh and i I've got the gun
I want you intend to do with the dr
watson ball
what indeed miss Stapleton expect you're
all wondering why I've gathered you at a
light and that we invited you dr. Watson
I want you to know that I suspect
everyone of you accept this little girl
Leah you think of the board of my being
generous cut round yellow alcohol
you must be hungry after your long walk
and chew one sit-down had something to
eat
thank you i am feeling a bit peckish
actually a little bit is nothing yet
order sorry about that i mean it's a
thrilling meeting or all know that my
sister can find you something now very
kind before you arrived and we were just
discussing your uncle's Willie up with
as you know he's been red tomorrow
career finally longing
they're watching it yes as neighbors we
all share your interest in the
disposition of the Prophet here said he
was gonna happen to that bloody fence
restrict me and him don't you come out
of there with your hands in the air and
why is that silly thing at my shell for
God's sake mother what are you doing
here forgot slight matter what you don't
tell you my but nothing was watching
this volcano who mr. paramount another
time it's about the Raptor is no volcano
mother why did you lie to me then where
is what I he's in their mother told
myself what a dreadful lot of people
he's with that man sitting on his right
it's not completely generate that's not
client mother
what about the rest of them the
continentals aren't they yes Jews I'm
going in
mother you're losing everything come
he's not safe in there fell
we're here to help you show on the Irish
yes mrs. Holden to wrap their don't
mention dance in front of pirates I can
you that changes coming down with you
like it or not you see I'm for my uncle
had very good reason for putting it up
yes 2/2 waters of the chance to relieve
themselves where they like on fish
driving a different pace little darlings
you know what he can do to the soul of
an animal doing the step King every day
in this same pace as part of I'm
confirmed where your little dog isn't
relieved themselves is entirely in your
hands on the moors don't take kindly to
into general from outside US
you'll come around I think it needs
something I'm sure certainly will
cooperate to the fullest glue don't you
whoo well I don't want the state to be
told what to do with my hair property
and other hand he's guaranteed or we
gotta . ass and then stop dating his
side water you let me know when you're
upsetting my patient it's not my fault
you feel this come up
yeah
hair
yes I think we had better go sir henry
sure you keep it on
otherwise you might get with the dog
them like this
that's what I will see you all tomorrow
for the reading of the wheel and then we
repeated what offenses to be taken down
and walk out of Kane up
goodbye miss table-turning you all
should it be our of wha
maybe see you LOL oh look out of La
would buy a simple new surprised
yeah
I have signed by and watch you let the
outcome that's as maybe wants the nurse
let's go down here and wait for the
others that we ought to get a doctor for
some every you are dr. Watson rep
because they can't be good
you could dr. Martin map the idea
yeah if the naughty hounds killed Henry
sad loss on the country dr mortimer
Henry is very much alive and very much
in love
nice car who
I think I never get alone and we all
cared and brother 15 engagements what
happened at the time
looks like you know I smell that
look they're getting away from me fun of
him but he wants the real Slim get the
ball back in the water got incarnate a
falling Clinton is brilliant idea to
check cycles around almost goodbye
ladies and gentlemen mr. Holmes I'm
sinking help me out and I'll put in a
good word for your children struggle
with dr. Mortimer stop him thinking oh I
knew your friends with the cameras show
but I didn't live in for this sort of
thing
don't look iris hermaphrodite mr. home I
see your managed to pull one up just as
I thought
now all in it together who very funny
then the others are just in time for the
reading of the world
awesome if you become enough to find
your way into dr. Mortimer's right
entrails of pocket you'll find just what
we've been looking for him on my team
and all that
Thank You industry finds that the true
heir the best gorillas state is a child
is gone and those whole dog the helm
himself
you mean the end was his friend after
Donn exactly in the event of the hounds
death the estate would have reverted to
Sir Henry and shuts the Headley had I'd
gone to his neighbor's these muddy
DeGeneres are invited dr. Mortimer hole
in you detective he knew that you had
the culinary complaints a disease
traditionally associated with rising
damp and alopecia
yeah all the basket of her party do
Dickie Hart any his plane was for the
hounds to go berserk with delight at the
center of the basketball and chase you
oh and of course sir henry said with the
false rumors would drop down dead of
heart failure is Astley and Mortimer
plans for us to witness this event
and shoot the house oh what a rotten
load of robbers I get into the festival
police patrol for him and thoroughly
these people can scarcely sink in love
i'm really going to America this place
would seem the same without you being so
card
yes when I know but since the demise of
sweet brother the expo this place
who's too many pan young members for us
what are you going to do mrs. who has
read our palm it's almost warm isn't
that law
my mother is mad watch your model said
made sense she saw chickens in my life
lately chickens and fried potatoes in
mine we are going to carve out a new
life in a brave new world but what are
you gonna do with all those chickens and
fried potatoes put them in little
cardboard boxes and cover them with a
special thought it was send your first
card from Kentucky to be happy all
yes your case oh I'm but goodbye good
hack minutes
yeah yeah yeah
isn't he lovely talk show the think of
all those people wanting to make
something really scared of them
what a wicked world we live in my
darling oh yes yes to stop chattering
iris so you're looking at my breasts
one thing puzzles me alms obviously the
late Sir Charles was not killed by the
hound
so what did kill him he was on his way
to the outside bathroom
obviously I fatal attack of acid
indigestion the Barrymore's cooking will
be the death of anybody and I've lost
the media malaria in a world where the
stakes are high mother she was not a
psychic
I wish you'd give the whole thing up if
it wasn't for iris and mr. taramosalata
we would never have known about the
volcano for the last time mother the is
no volcano
yeah