- Please call heads or tails...
- Tails.
Alice!
I'm exhausted.
You've no idea the day I've had.
Hell on earth.
On top of it all they wanted me to lug
the Japanese to the Lido cabaret
It didn't take long,
I sent them on a walk.
Anyway, they shouldn't push it,
we're not animals.
Yep.
But that other bastard...
you know, the one who's always
making my life hell.
If I'm not careful, one of these
days, he's going to get me fired.
He's a nutcase, a real pain in the ass.
For a bit of trickery,
you can always count on him.
He's the master.
That's why, as soon as I knew
he'd be there to take the Japanese,
I backed out of it, said I'd sort
things for tonight, no problem.
Then he got in a sulk.
I was loving it.
- E
- Vowel
- Consonant
The old man even smiled
as he was thanking me.
He apologized for putting it on me.
Well, Alice, I swear...
I never do a thing!
So, I told him, it's no trouble.
I tell him, no bother at all, never is.
And that I'm always free...
and that it's perfectly normal...
because I'm a company man!
I really pulled one over on those two.
Bastards.
Well, whatever...
I'm fetching them from the hotel at 10.
And then we'll go and eat at the Lido.
Oh, hey, I forgot-
they invited you, to this dinner...
No thanks.
Have it your way.
Oh, did you go to the doctor?
What did he say, was it nothing?
No, it's fine.
I knew it.
Women, always worrying about nothing.
I'm going now, Bernard.
Going where?
I'm leaving, far, far away from you.
Are you mad?
What's going on?
Honey?
I'm going, now.
Why?
I don't understand.
Is there some guy?
Alice, come here.
7, 9, 1, 75, 10, 100
ALI CE
or the Last Escapade
You're mad, don't do this, not tonight.
I can't stand you any more.
No, I won't let you go.
Please don't touch me.
I'm sorry. I'm an idiot.
I'm begging you, please be reasonable.
We can't wipe out 5 years like this,
we just can't.
We loved each other, Alice.
You haven't always been unhappy.
I can't stand you any more.
And where will you go?
I'm not telling you.
The weather's awful.
And I'm not letting you
leave in your state.
Forgive me?
For whatever I've done, I'm sorry.
Please, don't leave tonight,
you can't drive in this state.
You could leave tomorrow morning.
Rest tonight and leave tomorrow morning,
you'll be calmer and you'll
know what you're doing.
I can't stand you one second longer.
Listen Alice, if you want...
I'll sleep in a hotel.
Don't leave tonight,
I'm sure something will happen to you.
Something's already happened to me.
- I'm sorry, my car broke down...
- Come in, come in.
What's going on, Colas?
A young woman in a predicament, sir.
Please, come in, madam,
the weather's awful.
Your hair's all wet,
rivers running down your cheeks...
Come and get warmed up in here.
Colas, go and find something
to help get her dry.
Have a seat, relax, and
make yourself at home!
Thank you.
My name is Henri Vergennes.
You're a lifesaver!
It's my great pleasure.
Thank you.
My name is Alice Carol.
I'm really sorry to be
bothering you like this.
Oh, it's no bother at all.
Sit near the fire, you'll feel better.
There! The fire is our friend.
Would you like something to drink?
I'd love that... a whisky, please?
Oh. I don't have any whisky.
But I can offer you an excellent Port.
Ok, that's perfect.
I take it you haven't eaten yet.
Colas will whip something up for you.
- Really? That's not necessary.
- Oh, just an omelette or something.
It looks delicious!
Colas cooks it the traditional way.
Whites and yolks separate.
Absolutely. Why would two
different substances
require the same cooking time?
I can tell now, I was very hungry.
But I'll never eat all this.
No matter at all.
Maybe I should explain
why I'm out here tonight.
No need. You're a charming guest
and I'm having a wonderful evening.
Ah! The rain never stops!
And I don't think it will stop.
There's no way you can drive tonight,
especially with a damaged car.
I'd like you to accept my hospitality.
You look scared.
There's no need to worry, my dear.
The real dangers
are never those we imagine,
and never turn up
in the places we expect them.
You know that, don't you?
Colas will bring your luggage in, and
you'll get an excellent night's sleep.
Tomorrow the rain will have stopped,
your windscreen will be repaired...
and you'll be relaxed,
your spirit will be free to roam.
Don't you think?
I'm sorry I hesitated before.
Please...
You're exhausted, my dear child.
Go and get some rest.
Good night.
Thank you, with all my heart.
No, don't thank me,
I'm only doing my duty.
It's fine like that, don't you think?
I lit a small fire for you.
Thank you.
What a shame this pendulum's stopped.
It's broken, madam.
We don't care too much about time, here.
Have a good night, madam.
Is there anybody there?
Thank you very much. A.
This is impossible...
You must be exhausted.
There there, calm down.
Please, help me.
I don't think I'm able to.
Are you trying to leave?
I've walked the whole length
of this wall,
and I can't find the gate.
There's no gate.
But yesterday night when I came in...
Yesterday night, maybe.
This is absurd,
I need to get out of here!
No can do. You can get in here
but you can't get out.
Make of it what you will.
Where are Mr Vergennes and his butler?
I don't know.
Don't ask me any questions,
I can't answer them.
Who are you?
No questions.
But I want to get out of here.
Not possible. For the moment...
When will it be possible?
No questions.
I accept the game. This wall has
no openings, but it's not sky-high.
If I stand on my suitcase, I can
reach the top, and climb over.
That'll be a wasted effort.
Why wasted?
Help me.
No. I don't want to do you a bad turn.
Listen. I've decided to
get out of here.
If I need to get over
this wall, I'll do it.
So, be a gentleman, and help me.
No, you listen to me.
Don't try to use your
logical arguments in here.
They're worthless.
And no sentimental arguments either.
You'll soon see how misplaced they are.
I'm refusing to help you because
I don't want you to feel hopeless.
I don't need your concern.
Just help me, that's all.
As you wish, but it's a foolish idea.
Hey, don't touch me.
Don't try to touch me,
I'll hold the suitcase, that's all,
but don't try to touch me.
There, you see now?
There goes your last hope,
jump over the wall, simple isn't it?
Is that your problem solved?
There's no other side, Alice.
And you need to save your strength,
the nightmare hasn't begun yet.
How do you know my name?
No questions, I told you.
Come on, don't push it, come down.
No. I will get over the wall.
This is just a nightmare.
I'll get to the other side.
Don't try to get out.
Don't try to understand, not yet.
You'll have to live in the dark
for a while.
Make the most of it.
Accept it.
Don't think.
Trust us.
Trust yourself.
Live inside of what you're given.
You're very beautiful.
Where are you?
Too easy...
You're starting to feel at home, I see.
Who are you?
No questions.
You know the rules of the game now.
Questions are useless...
when there are no answers.
Fine.
I won't ask you who you are...
nor how to leave here,
nor what you want.
Wonderful.
However... I'd like you to
make the record play.
With pleasure.
We're sorry, it's an old record.
You're a very interesting case.
Brave, and flexible...
really quite flexible.
You accepted it.
You got into the swing of things.
Did what was necessary.
It's rare. And very good.
Most of those who found themselves in
your situation weren't so well-behaved.
They argued, screamed, yelled... begged.
They suffered, poor things.
And all for nothing, of course.
But for us... well, it was very amusing.
We played pranks on them.
See, just thinking about it
still makes me laugh.
You're made of much stronger stuff.
And that's great.
In fact, women tend to be
a lot hardier, I think...
But you, well out of all the women
you're quite remarkable.
Nothing to say?
It's just that I'd only have
questions to ask...
Remarkable, yes, you really are.
Ok, well I think everything should go
quickly, you won't stay here too long.
Careful though, don't think we won't
have a bit of fun at your expense.
But, you're not too badly off here.
You might even admit it yourself.
Don't go anywhere.
Read, listen to some music.
And wait. We'll make sure you
have everything you need.
Well, the essentials at least.
Don't be impatient.
You understand your situation, correct?
You won't do anything stupid?
I'm not answering any questions either.
I might have known...
What's your name?
I get it. You don't answer
questions either.
That's right.
It's not easy having a
conversation with no questions.
You get used to it.
You just have that impression
because you think...
I can tell you more
than you can tell me.
Anyway, grown-ups think
the only way to talk to children...
is by asking questions.
- You're not a child.
- Well spotted.
You don't speak like a child.
You're just being flattering because
you think boys of my age
like to feel like men.
That's not true.
Here, look.
Birds are stupid.
They don't realize the moment when the
door opens and they could get out.
If I understand rightly, you're the
reason the birds are singing today.
Yes. They thought you might like it.
I don't know them.
That's not entirely true.
And you know more than you think.
In any case, they know you.
I'll go and find some more if you want.
Of course. Where do you get them?
Hello, who's there?
My name is Alice Carol.
Oh I see. I'm talking to myself.
Alice, look.
50 Francs' worth of Super, please.
Where can I wash my hands?
Shall I check your oil and water?
Yes.
What's your name?
Front left tire was a bit flat.
Rest's ok.
I topped up the water.
Thanks for that.
Hey, I saw I little girl. Is she yours?
It's not a girl, it's a boy.
Oh. He had a doll.
His slut of a mother managed to
pop out a boy who looks like a girl.
And when she realized,
you know what she did to me?
She took off, the bitch.
The world's a real shit-hole.
Don't talk like that.
Don't get me started.
Thanks.
- Are you going a long way like this?
- Why?
The steering's a bit funny,
y'know, be careful.
Have a good trip!
Hello, can I eat here?
Have a seat.
Are you having a banquet?
I'll have an omelette aux fines herbes.
Ok. And what would you like
to drink with that? Red wine?
No thanks, a black coffee please.
Wouldn't you rather have tea?
The coffee machine's broken.
I can only give you American-style.
Ok, tea then.
One omelette aux fines herbes!
- Hey honey, come back... champagne!
- No listen, s'not worth it I swear-
Leave me alone!
When we sing in cherry season
The gay nightingale and mockingbird
Will join the fun!
Fair lasses' heads
will fill with folly
And lovers' hearts with sun!
My sister died. We buried her this
morning. Do you want to dance?
Ok, maybe later.
What's that, tea?
Here, I've brought you a drink.
Well? Drink! Or don't, whatever.
- What's that?
- An omelette.
I can't breathe!
Piss off, Pepe!
Come in, come in.
My dear friend,
I'm so glad to see you again.
I hope you enjoyed your little walk.
I don't suppose you've eaten yet?
Come...
Let's get this sorted out.
Come and sit down.
While Colas is preparing dinner,
how about an aperitif?
I've got whisky!
You haven't said a word.
I've nothing to say.
Such wisdom.
I don't have any soda,
you must forgive me.
Oh absolutely.
Have you begun to understand yet?
I'm playing the same game
as you and your friends.
I'm not answering questions.
Would you like me to explain?
Bravo.
You have remarkable willpower.
Well, in any case, you need to know.
Where you are, why.
I hope you're not mad about
the little jokes we've played.
It's the only fun we ever have!
Right. Where to start?
You must understand that the
explanations I'm about to give you...
are not going to satisfy
your love for logic.
Because that logic doesn't comply...
with the laws you know of.
This house, this estate,
my own self and Colas are just...
representations drawn out for you.
Do you understand?
We're apparitions.
Apparitions, that can be changed...
according to your needs.
But we're not just apparitions,
we also have our own reality,
which is... transformable,
that's the word.
Now, how can I make you feel
this reality, to give you...
a clear idea?
Because ultimately, you realize,
it will soon be yours.
Let's say that this point is the spot...
where souls rise up from hell...
to take on human forms.
You understand?
Funny, isn't it?
Here, drink this.
That little wooden door over there,
which you found so intriguing...
even tried to open, well, it's
through that door that sometimes...
well, sorry to use
such an ugly expression...
but it's through that little door
that souls, all bloated with evil,
come back up from hell
to escape into your dear world.
Dinner is served.
Thank you, Colas.
If you'd like to come with me
my dear friend,
we can continue this interesting
conversation during dinner. Ok?
But please, finish your drink.
Omelette aux fines herbes.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Please, take a bigger portion!
It's a real omelette.
I'm fine, thanks.
No thank you Colas, I'm not hungry.
Oh, don't look so worried.
I'm sure the omelette is excellent.
Colas!
Has that convinced you? Reassured you?
Right... I'll carry on where I left off.
As you've deduced,
it's impossible to escape fate.
For example, you certainly
can't get out of here.
You believe it now, surely?
Answer me, please.
You believe it don't you?
Yes.
Well you're wrong!
You'll soon be able to get back to...
your reality, your civilization...
that you seem to be so attached to.
Well, isn't that good news?
It's excellent news.
That little door. It's the alpha
and the omega of your adventure.
I haven't told you
the full story about it yet.
If it allows creatures from down below
to escape into the world,
it allows you, and all those
in your situation,
to find out all the things
they're attached to.
You just have to go down.
Into hell, right?
Yes, hell! Don't be frightened of it!
You've no other option,
so let's not get scared about it.
Er, down there, from time to time...
hopefully not too long...
you'll experience certain moral,
physical transformations...
call it what you will.
And after, you can get out
of here, my dear Alice.
Do you like Mozart?
My dear Alice, tomorrow morning
you'll be woken by a ray of sunlight.
The little wooden door will open up,
and it will be the end of this torment.
Now that you know everything,
take my advice:
Go and get some rest, try to sleep.
Goodbye, my dear child.
Why are you laughing?
I'm going to answer that.
When you tried to get over the wall,
you could have made it.
You should have trusted your instinct,
followed through with your decision.
I can always start over, you know.
Nope. Now there's no more wall.
Goodnight Alicccce.
Goodnight Colassss.
We thought you'd be asleep.
You need to sleep.
We'll take care of it.
Don't move or fight. It's useless.
Be quiet, be still.
You won't feel a thing,
and you'll sleep.
There's a good girl.
Subtitles: M. Nicholson