yeah
what
and tennis
hey what gives
you're being paid to work around here
not to sit around it last year and jobs
hey take it easy I can't go
hello hello
didn't try the following link
no I did they've already hung up
well then it could have been too
important don't you have any sense of
responsibility
I could have been a very important call
at this hour in the future
just answer the phone no matter what our
it is and not make your own decisions
about what's important and what isn't
Yeah Yeah right right it's time for our
rounds
yeah
ok
it was like
she is not some time
really driving the tropicals now
you were waiting with oh it's just
there's nothing would give a welcome to
get anything
I'm telling you it's nothing down and
I'm not going to waste my time checking
it out
what is it well I had finished and
remember application it would have been
safe
yeah
ok
what took you so long i made it as
quickly as I could I was clear across
the lot
you're not as young as you used to be I
tried calling you at the main gate
before
why didn't you answer the phone I must
have caught it just as you hung up
let's be a little more efficient from
now on
how's the new boy doing fine fine but I
really need to get back there just a
minute
I want to talk to you about these beer
Chan's I found in the front gate
so there's nothing down
yeah
but they keep your sister
there
yeah
I give you a report in the morning
and another one
quit what was the problem this time I'm
not sure what the problem was it wasn't
something you said to him was it could
have been
I'm holding you responsible for this -
treaty every time we hire a new guard he
only last for a couple of weeks then
he's gone
how many is it now three or its three
and i really don't think you need to
hire anyone else I can run the post
myself
look you've been here for a long time
you know as well as I do that we need to
have a second guard ready so he can fill
in for you if you can't make it here
some night time ever mr. night since
I've been here
you're not as young as you used to be we
need to be prepared
do you know that if something would
happen to this studio while no one was
on duty
our insurance is boiled this place has
been deserted for almost 30 years
stop making excuses I want you to hire a
new guard and this time hire one who
will stick around for a while or else
I'll hire -
so Kevin is this the first time that
you've worked as a security guard
yes sir but I'm a very fast learn and I
promise to try extra hard and I really
need the job
sound very mature for your age
you don't own one of those portable
radios with headphones do you know sir
and that's good I think we'll get along
just fine now
are you ready for your first tour the
not oh oh yes sir
even prepared to take notes it's not
that complicated
yeah
you've never been before it's not that
difficult to keep track
there isn't much goes on how long you
been working there
whoa about to you
never missed a million years
the main not really you know time
becomes a look sometime I'll tell you
what this place was like when it was
still functioning distribute I'd like to
hear about that
haven't I told you that was very
important
there is a part is not want you to stay
away from
I don't want to have to explain all the
details
- I just want you to promise you I am
now this is the part i was telling you
yeah
what sound it's just about dangerous
machine
don't go in there and take a chance do
you understand that
yeah good now I don't want to have to
remind
the second time just a area
so is there anything else i need to be
made aware there is
this is what I was telling you about
but don't worry i I've never had to use
it
really that's right all the years I've
been here
i would like to show you how to use it
sometimes you never know when you might
need it
yeah
ok
hi not now your friends are here
hey how's it going
which brings in the music no i just read
that a videotape that Amy and I were
gonna watch
no it's very nine let's see what you got
what don't you ever give me teens from
the adult section
my boyfriend would never bring me a tape
it didn't have at least a single X
rating
well Kevin isn't like that he would
never want me to see anything that was
rated x
would you know I wouldn't
all right man
I recognize that horny where that's my
nick back from two months of army
training and you know what a man wants
to he's been away for two months know
what does he want
whoa everybody have sex tonight wish
that were up
did you say something no no
I wanna hear about everything you did in
basic training
well we could get any more about 40 and
you know it sounds like loads of fun and
there's calisthenics daily life six
months I think you got really swing
no I did after that very true gasps
training in the deal
I have access to a gun where I work it's
a big difference between having
something knowing how to use
I would be okay if I use your phone yes
sure
are you gonna call my girlfriend and
we're gonna get a chance to meet this
girl
I don't think so she's kind of shy
what else did you do with the gun well I
haven't actually had a chance to fire
yet
I was talking to Nick
that we have target practice actually
chance to shoot you
yeah shooting someone that really
important to you
yeah
hi
thanks for calling I'm going to see a
movie today if you are you ready
ug I want you to show created a unique
in the rear door and when the lights go
down
drop your wave that memory block the
projection
next pull me down and roll me on the
sticky Lord like that artificial butter
flavor off my body
then take my clothes and leave me making
your life come up
sure that's not long
no it's not it's good because I have to
keep calling the phone company every
month because of all these sex line
calls being built in my number
really that's too bad
thanks Holly
and you adventure awaits tomorrow
oh yeah
no it's been all of you to come back I
know about the techniques you have your
hands tell us about something else
yeah can we change the subject already
did you pay attention and maybe older
something
nick is protecting our country and
you're just guarding some rundown desert
and dump
what did you say to be nice maybe he
teaches something you can control about
heading and pull that
no problem yeah go on I know you can do
it
look I said I wasn't interested okay
come on
not that I hold like this
you can watch every move that I make for
watching
where are you
ok
yeah
my hero
really what I didn't even want to do
this was your idea i don't care what i
wanted to
how was I supposed to win a me I've
never even done this before
it's an unfair match
what do you want me to do I want you to
make me proud
yeah
systematic
it's really a long story
I've got all the time in the world
what do you do about someone who you can
never make out
is this your girlfriend we're talking
about
I don't want to tell you what's the
exact problem
well we've got this friend who's in the
army and my girlfriend's upset because I
couldn't do all the things that he can I
see
did I ever tell you what i did when i
was in the army
no it's also a long story but looks like
we've got company
wait it
I for you
mr. McCready I said
we
yeah
get away from cancer is my part I said
get away from what are you kidding you
don't have to use it
are you okay
you want me to call an ambulance no no
I'm fine
damn the matter I just wish amy could
have been here to see what I just did
it's still what do we do now i'm going
to call the police
I locate where he is but keep a distance
problem
don't try to be a hero
yeah
screaming
he went to have their going in for a
closer look
before
good
stop whatever you're doing that you want
to do
yeah
ok
too late
why don't you listen to me
yeah
what's going on
thank you
yeah
oh if you only knew what you just did
I don't understand what just happened
the wall I tried to warn you those
creatures fault
a tried all my work
30 years I've been trying to prevent
this from happening to prevent one from
happening
those creatures why do you think i spent
the last 30 years of my life here
I was keeping them from escaping and i
was young i began to work here in the
studio was busy and prosperous
but always remember the night that it
happened
yeah
sleep
it was having anyone around
did you know it was first
it's all so fast
flashing light and some explosion
stepped out to see what it was
one else there except for me
it was right in the middle of the line
- daytime
it probably would have been questioned
all the traffic
I just stared at it for a long time
I didn't know what to make of it
and then suddenly
and I'll top the district in this swim
creature government
I looked around
stared right at me
imagine
just give watching
first
for me I'd known what lay ahead
but I still don't understand
I let the creatures live on a lot
it was my secret and then I learned of
the power they had I still don't know of
a fever
doing good for people or not they slowly
began to destroy everyone a lot
they would find a person tap into his
brain and create his wildest fantasy
it seemed harmless at first I mean
watching everyone around me becoming
rich famous but the most people what
they really want in life can be very
dangerous
in fact the creatures want up destroying
everyone everyone who came in contact
with the loose in the city now but you
could warn everyone did listen to your
story
what no one will give me 30 years ago I
went straight to the head of the studio
and try to explain it
he didn't believe me no one did
just watched helplessly as people around
me were destroyed one by one and what
can we do
I to order to catch up with him now but
you might still have a chance
there aren't very many of them but they
move quickly
just remember they're attracted to
bright lights
that's how you can find them watch
everyone around you in person begins to
back strangely it means that one of the
creatures have attacked into his mind
when this happens the creature is never
far away
find it and kill it before it's too late
because when the creature dies the
fantasy ends in the victim is safe now
remember they're only attracted to
bright light
that's how you find them but you must
destroy them or before dawn because once
it's daylight it's too late
but you'll never be able to stop them
yeah
what
here
maybe circling the block
I thought you might be told up thanks a
lot
I thought I heard this one before
so did I
maybe you should wait in five
he's just looking for a place to park
don't you go back in the house there's
plenty of parking in front
maybe it wasn't his . look I'm positive
it was maybe the police just pulled them
over for all this warrant or something
no just go back in the house fine i get
the medicine is just take this stupid
jacket with you
damn it Nick with hell are you
just go back in the house and leave me
alone
breathing all right
yeah
I'll
how do you
kids
happy
yeah
thank you
pretty
wait
yeah
like our new dance
pretty kink
yeah
and
you know
yeah
God
no doubt
- yeah I'm just peachy everything under
control
good and you can finish out
yeah
I don't understand what were those
things
it's a long story but they give your
body is nothing compared to what they
did your mind
I have to worry about that you sure
you're all okay and you don't feel
anything different to you
pants
I'm sorry kidding and none of you have a
desire to do anything you've never done
before
right don't think there's anything left
with Duncan how about you Amy
well actually I didn't want china the
chinese restaurant and I heard about
Kyle groans your telephone again I want
to call my girlfriend still haven't met
this mystery early years what kind of
relationship the two and you have I
guess you see it's a fantasy
relationship
yeah
hi it's me
plantation thanks for calling I need a
new house to impress my friends
now hurry before the zookeeper Congress
help me hide this iguana on my body
oh can I help you miss oh yes mr. peace
master
something just caught up my leg oh
see if you can find it I think you
better come back to my office with me
now wait a minute are you sure your
office in the baboon head
mr. keeper what do you think you're
doing isn't the children's petting
I have a new house yet for you
myth up Oh mr. zookeeper
I can never take a cottage at five
stop wasting your money calling me right
outside your door
don't keep me waiting
yeah
where's Kyle
did you guys see where he went
you do kiss on the first date
I go all the way first date
my kind of woman my place or yours
neither will go to reputation road I'll
Drive
up
do we have some time to get pop rocks
and whipped cream
just start the car reputation road here
we come
yeah
wait where's Jackie where refugees wrote
you about the industry
make a right go to track lighting up the
hill and there it is
so I've heard what's going on I don't
have time to explain about those
creatures
I've got to go across town and get Kyle
I want to rescue to stay here don't make
a move or do anything
and above all don't fantasize about
anything
no girls fantasy right now involved in
the number three
yeah
Fantasia you're my ideal woman you're
intelligent and a wonderful personality
I'll bet you're a great cook and I just
know my mom loved meeting you
will you marry me skip the ceremony
we're going straight to the honeymoon
how
Fantasia maybe I can watch you all night
long
not going faster we could be driving all
night long
now hurry I know a shortcut
yeah
huh don't Park here
why not you have to park near the edge
if you want to go all the way
oh yeah sure how's that perfect
there was some shortcut you about I
never knew there was a road through the
children's playground there in vent
well what are you waiting for the
teacher where you going
I wanted a better view of the city you
can see it all from here
now isn't that I love leave you
oh it sure is
where are you going no you have to wait
a second
you just keep watching the view just
hold tight and get ready for the ride of
your life
do it to me
yeah
people
help
but you'll get back into signing away
from me this time John move
much they're just think nasty thoughts
while you wait
yeah
ok
do it to me baby
damn
hey what are you doing here I want to be
my girlfriend huh
when you see here Fantasia honey Kyle
there's no girl she was a figment of
your imagination
no she's not she's just hiding somewhere
I told her she's a shy girl sweety my
girl that bleach blonde which almost
killed you
she was back there trying to push your
car and when
thank you
yeah
ok
whoa
now do you believe me
yeah
I'll discuss my phone bill with you
later on
no they're gone
yeah
the creatures broke loose are you guys
okay we're doing just fine
what about Amy where she is she was
looking kinda strange
what where is she she said you want to
go to club scum
what why didn't you try to stop her
what's the big deal i've been there
before
you guys don't you understand its
creatures have a power they can tap into
your brain
since the things that you really want to
do what's wrong with that
they also tried to kill you i justjust
call across town and pull them out of
his car right before rolled over clip
and blew up it's still burning now you
see what I'm trying to tell you guys now
what could happen at that nightclub
well there's a lot of bikers and people
fighting everywhere and I've seen people
dealing drugs and knife fight
oh no we're gonna go arrest people there
all the time for god knows what
I think you got this all wrong
you would never come to
place like this she won't even go
through the ballpark yourself
you guys have got to start and added to
the party
look like you belong
but would you just listen
yeah
nothing
where you think you're going
looking for a girl and you
here
the string
understatement particular
tonight
yeah what is it working here tonight
pretty stupid
cross on working it
No
working
what I want me tonight
what you .
read my lips
for a friend of ours
machine look anything like fixing it
give you anything
ten percent of what
I didn't see you guys around
and
see you back there
yeah
bond
I'm sorry here but your boyfriend
back from the Army
it is
because your friend of Daphne's
you're not yourself
yeah
just sit down
oh you must be here for the wet t-shirt
contest tonight
teacher contest donkey mud wrestling
donkey my breath get lucky night
no oh I'm sorry
the donkey mud wrestlers are supposed to
use the rear entrance
like this
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
guys it's just the tonic oh really
always just shut up okay and you guys
are much about help you know supposed to
look at brain
why don't you try looking under the
table your daddy next we have been out
of the tables here because the rugs
yeah
same color of the carpet burns on my
knees niche
greetings life and welcome to get off
this thing
yeah
ok
you guys something to drink yeah maybe
is a two drink minimum here look we're
all under age
ok haha well grass can be a quick
yeah yeah yeah what is it kid 21
all right a fake ID
ok
this is a 40 and handicapped so what you
got a problem with that jr. no call them
now
Thomas proud to present you emit light
appearing usually and nicely
miss any
yeah
oh my god
Amy
yeah
show me
where
you
yeah
stop interrupting the show
where and when
yeah
she's just too long she doesn't even
know what she's saying she's never been
on the back
Michael she's terrified of him
riding a motor
like
sitting on the world Ron vibrator
yeah
sincere
you're my kind of woman
Amy sincere is only my stage name do you
want to know my real name
tell it to me on your knees baby break
it up you two
I'm not into the number three
get out
which guy stop sitting there and help me
when you're home gasps II never would
have met
this place
what are you doing here private
I'm out of the way get pass your Pixies
working tonight
you go out in public in full uniform a
real soldier died with his boots are
going on just prompting some small
better certain
I see
sort of the writing attack yes sir I
believe that we need to stage diversion
project is a command here
you're certain and I'll make the
decisions we need to stage a diversion
and I have just what you need
yeah
I
tonight
yeah
see
tell you that
a talent scout for major motion picture
studio
I've always been attracted to men of
yours
watch it
Oh
yeah
I don't want to mix white one
do it to me
yeah
shot
faking right
for you
yeah
they say
come back
yeah
still fake your orgasm
take this
he looked there's a me
yeah
pay me oh ok
not sure what am I trust like a fuck
videos lat
it's a long story i'll explain later you
there
name rank serial number don't use me
I'm just an employee I don't even put
the talent here start you can't stop
why this is the best training has ever
had never get this boot tab all that
training you could kill somebody
war isn't pretty Daphne maker still
inside we gotta try to help him
wait i have a special mission for you
you too
this
you ever consider joining
the USO us oh yes make of it
entertaining the troops doing your part
for our country
a small but big gesture that would be
appreciated by our boys are fighting
around the world
I'll do it good start right away
I've got a truckload of soldiers have
the parking lot
if you start now you can be finished
within my morning breath
Nick do something sergeant after me show
him one more time being
here
stop wasting time maybe I should send
Nick up to some third world
great give you all the time and you need
like ramen and you can pick up
picture altogether this is your second
speaking
yeah
the trunk of soldiers is waiting outside
a dream
yeah
my dream right now
I got the last ,
yeah
mr. bender rally crowd tonight
hey mrs. here
no I really like that Joe you're doing
it tonight
base from ball the show is over when I
just climb back under your rock
daddy I could have done that oh sorry
mhm I want you to know that I'll always
be there for you
well you know no it's never really
noticed me before like that
I mean I've always just been thought of
his daddy's friend
this is the first time somebody came up
to me like that
I kind of like that Amy I meant what I
said I'm going to prove it to you
yeah
where is it
mr. Comstock
I wasn't sure you'd still be here this
late and i'm on my way out the door what
do you want now
the creatures brokenness get the same
ones I tried to warn you about when I
first got my job
are you going to try to tell me that
same story about the hobgoblins again
yes sir I'm glad you still remember
about how could i forget that nonsense
then get out of here and get back to
work
but you don't understand a pro loose
tonight out there somewhere in the city
I already sent the other guard out to
try to find them
what you mean this there's no one
Manning the front gate right now
no sir this is preposterous you do know
that if something would have happened at
the studio while no one was on duty our
insurance will refuse to pay off
yes sir well then get back on your post
you're not listening I want to go out
and find him
you must need my help by now you I'm not
going to leave your job to go out and
chase some foolishness
if you want off this lot you are fired
good saves me the trouble
great
yeah
pretty
miss Morrison
this time I'm gonna make you proud
yeah
I think of food
maybe you would
we killed it
ok
with
yeah
I'm sorry for sending you out on your
own
should have known creatures would try to
destroy walls where they going back to
walk
sorry there isn't much time left
yeah
I'll be waiting
let's go alone
yeah
I was right about back inside
maybe we should get closer locking back
inside again
no spent 30 years guiding them that was
fired from my job tonight I will be
around here to keep an eye on
you're fired well
maybe I could get them from no I don't
want you to throw your life away that
way i had there is a better way
did you find him yeah they're back
inside the ball
what are you gonna do to them I don't
know Kevin and I ever tell you what i
did in the war
no not you nisshin's
yeah
isn't it ironic that they should be
completely studio tool and that's the
figure dick resolved in a dream fact
you are my hero tonight
are you sure yeah I'm sure
yeah
Daphne this is for you
really no one's ever given me flowers
before but there's lots of things I can
show you for the first time
Nick yeah I told you guys I had
everything under control
stephanie mckee
hello mr. Comstock
yes I I realize what time it is
I'm sorry doing buddy it's been an
accident in the studio
the film vault you up yes it
the building is still smoldering oh yes
i realize about the insurance but you
fire
there was no one on duty when it
happened
excuse me sir Christ your phone
the back
God
yeah
just remember the next time you feel
be rated G I want you to make a rating