As far as I can remember,
I've hated Christmas.
What does it say, Christian?
Gimme my car!
Christmas 1960
It should work.
Stop picking your nose.
It's working!
There we go.
Mine's not moving.
Gervais!
Han?
How are you feeling?
He's so cute!
Look, kids.
It's your little brother!
- Baby Jesus!
- Let me hold him.
Here you go.
He's beautiful.
Let me see!
Christmas 1966
Not only would my birthday
always go unnoticed,
but it had to start
with midnight mass.
Midnight mass is too long!
Go home and open your presents!
On the contrary, you're lucky
to share his birthday.
That doesn't happen
to just anyone.
It's special.
Hence the birthmark
on your scalp. Hmm?
It's a sign of being gifted,
you know.
At least, after mass,
there was the Christmas Eve party
at Grandma's.
Hello, my beautiful Zac.
The only advantage to having
one's birthday on Christmas
was getting a bigger present
than everyone else.
He likes it, huh?
But I especially hated Christmas
because I never got what I wanted.
Dammit.
It's what he wanted.
So? It's not up to him.
You want to turn him into a fairy?
- Stop it. He's only five!
- He's almost six and looks seven.
- Oh, come on!
- Never mind "come on."
Now return it. Go on.
It would make you
a laughingstock, son.
Daddy doesn't want that.
Daddy isn't trying to upset you.
He loves you far too much.
Hence the hockey game.
So he can play with you.
Go to sleep.
Mommy will have a nice surprise
for you soon.
- For my birthday?
- No, after. You'll see.
Go to sleep.
What's a fairy?
Nothing.
Hogwash.
Go to sleep.
Idiot.
I knew very well
what a fairy was.
I especially knew...
I didn't want to be one.
Want to play, Zac?
No.
Unlike my friends' fathers,
all of whom
were ordinary and uninteresting,
mine was the best in the world.
He has Patsy Cline's,
Buddy Rich's
and Aznavour's
entire collections.
He fired a machine gun
in the army.
Our secret side trips
to Norm The King Of Fries
made me deliriously happy.
For a few precious moments,
I was his favorite.
Take me
To the ends of the earth
To Wonderland
It seems to me
That misery
Would be borne more easily
under the sun
Hi!
Hello.
- You didn't bring any back?
- What?
Fries, you moron.
You can smell it a mile away.
We didn't have any fries.
Did we?
My three brothers were morons.
Starting with Christian,
the egghead,
who read constantly -
anything, anytime, anywhere;
Antoine, the sports nut,
a walking stinkbomb;
- What're you looking at?
- And Raymond,
my sworn enemy.
Get lost, you pisser.
Dad, Raymond called me
a pussy!
Not a pussy, a pisser.
Kitchen.
I could understand him
being proud of Christian,
or Antoine.
But Raymond?
Aren't you going to introduce us?
My dad.
- You're going out, Raymond?
- The little bastard's a Casanova.
But he asked
for more ironed toast!
Hi, pretty baby.
After nine months of prayer...
and superhuman feats...
the good Lord
would finally give me...
Another boy?
What kind of lead you got
in your pencil, Beaulieu?
What can I say?
I have a surplus of male hormones.
- A surplus of hormones!
- That's irrelevant.
He has to change positions
once in a while.
Yeah, well, I've tried that.
What can I say? Five boys -
you take what you can get.
Come on, Zac.
You like my surprise?
Christmas 1967
Take me
To the ends of the earth
To Wonderland
It seems to me that misery
Would be borne more easily
under the sun
Drop by sometime.
See? Look. Again.
Zac has a gift.
I'm sure of it.
His colic stops
whenever Zac holds him.
I'll go see Mrs. What's-her-name,
the Tupperware lady.
She, too, has a gift.
She can staunch bleeding,
heal burns and everything.
She'll tell us if he's gifted.
No. You've seen
how he plays the drums.
A regular little Buddy Rich.
Music runs in his blood,
I'm telling you. That's his gift.
He gets that from his old man.
Hi, pretty baby.
Mommy's little darling.
I can still remember the snow
slowly melting on his face.
I had just turned seven
and, unwittingly,
declared war to my father.
Are you crazy,
dammit?!
What are you doing?!
Roll that window back up,
you nitwit!
Do we have to tie you up?
Here, buckle up!
Christ.
Use your head, you nitwit.
Stop slurping, you pig!
Don't be such a sissy!
Eleven bucks!
An imported collector's record.
You'll each reimburse me
if the guilty party
doesn't come forward.
I'm warning you.
I'll teach you to take
responsibility for your actions,
dammit!
- Gervais!
I didn't do it.
It was an accident.
Scoot, you three.
You'll not only pay for the record,
but your lies, too.
I'll teach you, you'll see.
Go to your room!
He said it was an accident.
What in heaven's name
did you do to him?
Zac. He's changed.
He's a crybaby, he dresses
like a girl. It's not normal.
Get over it.
It's you who's not normal.
He's a child, for God's sake.
Let him be.
"What did I do to him"!
- The others weren't like that.
- Each of them is different.
Zac is more gentle, that's all.
More sensitive.
He's not gentler, he's softer.
God, please don't let me be soft.
And return my dad
to his old self.
Shut up.
Use your head, you nitwit!
Don't be such a sissy!
I did it on purpose.
I'll tell Dad, you pisser.
When will I stop wetting the bed?
I've been asking him a long time.
Never mind - no harm done.
Hmm?
You're not alone.
It'll stop eventually.
Keep praying. You'll see,
Baby Jesus will hear you.
Especially you.
You were born on the same day.
Sweet dreams.
Big chimneys, huh?
Where are we going?
You'll see.
Careful.
Mrs. What's-her-name,
the Tupperware lady,
had realized my mother's dream:
she had walked
in Christ's footsteps.
Try to trust your feelings.
You can feel things others can't.
You mustn't fear it.
He's been blessed
from on high, Mrs. Beaulieu.
The good Lord chose him
knowing he was strong enough
for what's expected of him.
But give him a chance
to grow up a bit. Hmm?
So he better understands.
He's a good-looking boy.
He'll go far.
Christ...mas, I'm bushed!
I've got news for you.
Your son has a gift.
A family's seventh child
of the same sex is gifted.
With my three miscarriages,
that makes Zac seventh.
Who says your miscarriages
were boys?
They must've been.
That's all you can do.
We knew he could stop colic,
but he's otherwise gifted.
Gifted people
can pass their gift on to others,
if they're of the opposite sex
and not related.
Mrs. What's-her-name
passed all of hers on to him.
Oh, Jesus.
How much Tupperware
did that cost you?
None.
She didn't try selling me any.
I bought some.
It's different.
This is no joke.
He's truly gifted!
Can your gift cure my headache?
There.
What's this?
Look.
It's not my birthday,
as far as I know.
Your record's unfindable.
We bought another.
It's the same thing!
I know.
I already have this one.
The sound's not the same.
An imported collector's record
isn't the same.
It's the thought that counts.
I'll just return it, then.
Raymond, Antoine!
That's enough!
Christian! Supper's ready.
Come on, boys. Let's eat.
- Coming.
Gifted...
What do you think about that?
What did Mrs. What's-her-name
tell you?
I'm not allowed to say.
But she told Mom that if
the good Lord gave me a gift,
I had to use it.
That I could help a lot of people,
even save them.
Tell him to think of him.
Think of Uncle Lucien.
He cut himself eating steak.
They're not going to start calling
for every little booboo?
Turn that music down.
All I had to do
was silently recite the secret
little prayers imparted to me
by Mrs. What's-her-name,
which consisted not of asking,
but of commanding God to heal.
Remember, you can't use
your gift for personal gain.
Or to harm others.
What a shame.
What's he saying?
He's not allowed to say.
Stop it, will you?
From now on, it'll cost a dime
every time you pick your nose.
You'll be rich.
You must know
how ketchup's made by now,
you've been reading the damn label
for half an hour.
Another pest
who just cut himself shaving.
Okay, I'll tell him.
Uncle Lucien's bleeding
has stopped.
Yes?
Well, I'll be damned.
Great. He'll be thrilled.
Yes. Thank you.
What is it?
Your lucky brother
is going to summer camp.
- What?!
I wasn't allowed to go at his age!
You got yours.
Stop complaining.
We've never sent our children
to camp.
He'll sleep there?
Of course. He'll make friends,
have lots of fun...
It'll be a good experience
for him.
- He'll always remember it.
- I don't wanna go.
Oh, come on.
I don't wanna go.
I don't wanna go!!!
God, please don't let it happen.
Go to sleep.
God, please,
don't let it show.
I'll never miss mass again.
Midnight mass
was so short and sweet
now that I'd become an atheist.
I'd kept my promise, though.
I'd never missed mass...
midnight mass.
Once a year.
It made her happy.
It kept his mouth shut.
You dragging your trash around,
brother-in-law?
It's your present.
Well, if it isn't Zac!
What, no girlfriend yet?
Christmas 1975
Nice paper.
Every year, I told them:
No Christmas wrapping paper
for my birthday presents, okay?
That's not what matters.
After the drum set, accordion,
guitar and violin...
a banjo.
You said to surprise you.
It's so hard to know
what teenagers want nowadays.
You try to please them...
Some fantasies
are worth keeping.
Merry Christmas!
Happy New Year!
You know what time it is,
Raymond?
You're late.
I was starting to worry.
- Hi. I'm Doris.
- Good evening.
- Merry Christmas.
- Take off your boots.
- How are you?
- Hi, Dad.
- Merry Christmas.
- Pleased to meet you.
I'm Raymond's mother.
My family always
appreciated gourmet food.
Did you at least make a wish?
It won't come true,
he can't get it up yet.
My brothers
hadn't changed a bit.
Dad, Zac gave him the finger!
- Except my darling Yvan.
- Such brotherly love!
And how polite
they are in public.
Turn that music down.
Every Christmas,
the bastard barely stayed an hour.
Just long enough
to stuff himself...
and to piss me off.
Here, buy whatever you want.
Happy birthday.
Wait.
I loved daydreaming
about my mother.
Picturing myself wealthy,
so that, one day,
I could spoil her.
Merry Christmas!
It's beautiful. Thank you.
Oh, what a lovely dress.
My cousin Brigitte
had just dropped out of school
to devote herself
to social dancing full-time.
At the age of 15.
I can dance too, you know!
But it's not my specialty.
Back by popular request...
No getting around it.
It's your birthday!
- You've really changed.
- Yeah, you too.
This is my boyfriend, Paul.
My cousin, Zac.
He has his driver's license!
I'm stealing one.
- You don't smoke?
- Never touch the stuff.
Good thing. If it was up to him,
he'd be smoking nonstop.
We go to the movies,
he wants to smoke;
we go skating,
he wants to smoke...
You skate? Roller-skate?
The guys' turn, full blast,
music blaring, really stoned -
you let yourself go...
you can hear everything,
and feel like everything around you
is moving in slow-motion,
like in a movie.
A stoner movie, yeah.
Try it.
Give me a shotgun.
No way.
Are you nuts?
I burned my tongue last time.
I thought of you
and it stopped burning.
He has a gift
for healing burns.
- What?
- And staunching blood.
It's true! Tell him!
My mother got that
into the whole family's head.
You stop your girlfriend's
monthly bleeding, too?
Idiot.
That's it, make a fool of me.
I don't believe in that anymore.
Sorry.
That doesn't mean
you've lost your blessing.
You blessed fool!
You want a shotgun?
Boy, have you changed!
Well, well...
if it isn't the lovely Michelle.
- Hi, Mr. Beaulieu.
- Hi.
I'll finish up later.
No problem.
- Is she really on the pill?
- Enough about my cousin.
I'm not the one
who wants to sleep with her.
That's the last time
I confide in you.
Why are the prettiest girls
always the dumbest?
You've never seen her.
I've seen her picture.
Enough said.
Don't be jealous.
You're dumb too.
I see her once a year. How am
I supposed to sleep with her?
Anyway, she's got a boyfriend.
Older. As dumb as she is.
Not as dumb as you?
Don't.
It'll ruin our friendship.
That's not what you said
last week.
Stop it.
See what happens?
Absolutely nothing!
Don't tell me he groped her.
You done imitating
that fucking fag?
Huh?! You're making us
look like a bunch of idiots!
Get outta here!
It's my room too!
C'mon, Toto,
ask him for an autograph.
Got a problem?
No.
Having a crazy brother
also had its advantages.
- Always ready to help...
- Pay up, you little bastard.
... for the modest sum of $2.
We were here first.
Shut up, faggot.
What did you call him?
Apologize.
Apologize
and switch back to his show.
Apologize, I said!!!
It's okay, Dad.
Go on!!
Sorry.
What's for dinner?
What happened to you?
Just a hockey fight.
- Didn't you have practice today?
- Yeah, yeah.
You fought with a teammate?
It was just a scuffle.
Didn't even drop my gloves.
- Who with?
- Tremblay.
You got beaten up
by Tremblay's little fag?
What, you four-eyed fag?
What's with you always
calling each other fags?
You'd swear we're nothing
but a bunch of fairies!
Please...
anything but that.
Sorry about last night.
You know I don't like you talking
to your brother that way.
Yeah...
Okay, see you at work.
Careful, now.
Please let me bump into them.
What're you doing here?
- Just in the neighborhood.
- God, you've changed.
What'd you do to your hair?
It's cool.
Thanks.
You alone?
- No, I'm with...
my new dance partner.
He's Italian.
Thank you.
This is my cousin, Zac.
Okay, well...
I'll be off.
Change... Change...
I would be cured of my asthma...
if I only managed to get through.
For the second time of my life...
I was declared clinically dead...
for three seconds.
Thank God you were dedicated
to Virgin Mary.
I can't believe it.
It's a miracle.
You know you made your father cry?
Don't ever scare us
like that again.
Feel like talking?
I'll come back later.
While my mother performed
charitable works daily...
her Baby Jesus
had only one thing on his mind.
You asshole!
What're you doing?!
Fucking liar.
The hottest was a black chick.
It was like
she'd never eaten before.
Mind you, they smoked a couple
of joints. Makes you hungry.
She sucked him like a Hoover!
He held her head,
thrusting as deep as he could.
The harder she sucked,
the more he screamed.
The more he screamed,
the harder she sucked.
Ever had a blow job?
What do you want?
I was wondering
where my shades went.
Going somewhere?
Boy, is this gonna cost me!
I didn't ask for nothing.
Your neck still sore?
We're out of HP Sauce.
You get a 2-for-1 special today.
You'll learn to drive properly
and how to make your father's
world-class spaghetti sauce.
Let's go,
before your mother catches us.
Go ahead. Turn the key,
put it on "D.”
Good. Slowly, now.
Go ahead.
- HP Sauce?
- That's my secret.
Watch where you're going
and shut up.
Lesson number one:
shut up and drive.
Go ahead.
Slow down!
What are you, nuts?
What are you doing?
The school principal just called.
Seems your son's been spreading
rumors about Raymond!
I won't stand for smut around here!
Much less drugs!
What?
If I have to call the police
to make Raymond understand,
I'll do it this time!
What's all this about?
Huh?!
What's this?
His little brothers live here!
Stay away from me, I said!
I didn't rat him out.
He's already gone.
I didn't even say goodbye.
Could be the wrong time,
but can I have his room?
- I want it!
- No one's taking his room.
Especially not you.
Does this mean
we're not just friends anymore?
I dunno.
What do you think?
What's he doing here?
Toto the Weirdo.
Forget him.
Peeping Tom.
What're you looking at?!
Fucker.
She's so excited.
I couldn't get a word in edgewise.
She went on and on about Brigitte.
We'll never hear the end of it.
Seems she's putting together
a big show with her boyfriend
this Christmas Eve.
- With the Italian?
- No, she's back with the other.
The mambo dancer?
He missed her big knockers.
Who's the pig
who ate all my lard spread?
Think of your little cousin Daniel;
he burned himself.
Too bad!
Rutting teenager
in his natural habitat.
Shut up!
What teenager?
You didn't come
just for my Tupperware?
How are you coping
with your gift?
Beautiful story.
A man dreamed he was walking
with Christ on the beach
while watching scenes of his life
flash across the sky.
Upon turning around,
he noticed that
throughout most of his life,
there were two sets
of footprints in the sand,
his and those of Christ.
Except during the worst times
of his life,
when there was only one set
of prints.
The man said to Jesus,
"You promised
you would walk with me always.
Why did you forsake me
when I needed you most?"
Jesus replied...
"There was only one set
of footprints in the sand
during the worst times
of your life,
because I carried you."
I want to be like everyone else.
Thank God, you never will.
What got into you?!
You have to learn
to control yourself!
I'm not going to the Christmas
party this year.
The guy was twice his size.
The little bastard's got nerve.
He gets that from his old man.
He's been doing well lately, huh?
You call that doing well?
A little fight's no big deal.
We should get him something special
this year, don't you think?
He just needed a girlfriend.
Michelle's a nice girl.
He said she invited him over
for Christmas Eve.
He'll be 16.
We can start
cutting him a little slack.
You didn't agree?
I said we'd discuss it.
She can join us, if she wants
to spend Christmas with him.
She can't take him away from us
on his birthday.
He can do whatever he wants
when he's older.
In the meantime, we celebrate
Christmas as a family.
What about a new stereo
for his room?
I can't believe
what a good ear he has.
He gets that from me, too.
- I didn't do anything.
- Don't take me for an idiot!
What you did was wrong!
I didn't do anything.
- A liar, too!
- Let him explain.
See what that pram business
and your mollycoddling does?
He's never to set foot here again!
Is that clear?!
If you can't choose the right
friends, we'll do it for you.
Fucking little faggot.
And you, you sap,
get dragged into it!
- Let him speak!
- Stop defending him!
I know what I saw!
What you did was wrong.
You don't do this.
We went in to warm up, that's all.
Did we ever beat you?
Do we have to start,
so you stop mocking us!
I'm sorry.
I don't understand.
After everything
we've done for him.
This shouldn't be happening to us.
It can happen to anyone.
It's no one's fault.
Father Carbonneau says
we mustn't seek to lay blame.
Father Carbonneau?
I had to talk to someone.
- What am I, chopped liver?
- You're impossible to talk to.
- The whole neighborhood will know.
- Of course not.
No one else is to know about this.
Is that clear?
This is strictly a family matter.
What did the priest
have to say?
It's a sin, yes, but not the end
of the world. He's not alone.
The sin is in the act,
not the inclination.
Look who's talking.
Him and his cassock!
Don't start.
He says he knows a priest
who's real good with teenagers.
Forget it.
It's not a priest he needs.
Sometimes I wonder
why we pray to a long-haired guy
who hangs out with a bunch of guys
in robes.
- It's fishy.
- Honestly!
Why are there
no female priests, then?
They're starting
to get on my nerves.
Anyway, we'll take care
of his problem immediately.
It's all in his head.
Abnormal people get treated.
People aren't born that way,
they become so.
It's up to us to make sure
that our son doesn't.
Nature doesn't make mistakes.
There's no in-between.
It's one or the other -
a boy or a girl.
I'm willing to pay for a shrink
if necessary.
Our boy is a boy.
No way I sired a fairy.
We'll wipe any such notions
right out of his head!
You have to be sick
to spend your life sticking
your pecker up someone's ass!
You've got a short memory.
That was different.
And we only tried it once.
Once?
Once or twice.
I don't remember.
Well, I do.
I'm not seeing a shrink.
I'm warning you.
I don't have a problem.
Understand?
He does take after his father.
He's freaking out over nothing.
Nothing happened.
We didn't touch each other.
We jerked off in the same car,
no big deal.
Why do it together,
then?
Watching him excited you?
I didn't watch him.
Do I look like a fag?
Do I talk with a lisp?
Strut like a peacock?
Nice idea of homosexuals
you've got there.
They're not all like that.
They all become that way.
Sooner or later.
This is a waste of time.
I'm not a fag.
I'd rather die.
It's just a figure of speech.
Isn't it obvious?
Being happy and healthy,
or miserable and fucked-up?
It's a no-brainer.
So?
A subconsciously deliberate
mistake.
What?
He says I deliberately did that
in your car so you'd catch me,
find out I was gay
and accept it so that I could.
Twenty-five bucks
for that hogwash?
You didn't buy it, I hope?
- 'Course not.
- Unbelievable.
"A subconsciously deliberate
mistake"!
He'll deliberately reimburse me,
believe me!
What do you want?!
You want to take this in to him?
He'll be glad to see you.
I'm sure he's forgiven you.
Dad!
How are you?
Come in, come in.
What're you doing?
Get out of here.
I don't have time.
Your brother's waiting in the car.
I'll take a rain check.
Hey, bro.
How you doing?
So, you take my room,
you little bastard?
Oh, Dad, I almost forgot.
Can you lend me a few bucks?
I couldn't cash my cheque.
I'll pay you back tomorrow.
Better than nothing.
See you.
I would be cured
if I could simply make it
through the storm.
Happy birthday.
Christmas 1980
Fall on your knees
O hear the angel voices
O night divine
The night...
When Christ was born
Yesterday when I was young
The taste of life was sweet
as rain upon my tongue
I teased at life
as if it were a foolish game
The way the evening breeze
may tease a candle flame
The thousand dreams I dreamed
the splendid things I planned
I always built alas
on weak and shifting sand
I lived by night and shunned
the naked light of the day
And only now I see how
the years ran away
So many drinking songs
were waiting to be sung
So many wayward pleasures
lay in store for me
And so much pain
my dazzled eyes refused to see
I ran so fast that time
and youth at last ran out
He wrote that for you, Zac.
Yesterday the moon was blue
And every crazy day brought
something new to do
I used my magic age
as if it were a wand
And never saw the waste
and emptiness beyond
The game of love I played
with arrogance and pride
And every flame I lit
too quickly quickly died
The friends I made all
seemed somehow to drift away
And only I am left on stage
to end the play
There are so many songs
in me that won't be sung
I feel the bitter taste of tears
upon my tongue
The time has come for me
to pay for yesterday
When I was young
Happy birthday, my man!
The old man's still got it, huh?
It's been a while since
I've seen him with an inhaler.
He got rid of it.
Since when?
- Almost a year, I think.
- He didn't tell us?
I said nothing, okay?
I don't know about cake.
I overate.
We've got news.
I don't want to steal your thunder,
bro, so I'll be quick.
We're getting married.
You hear that?!
They're getting married!
I'm very happy!
This calls for another bottle!
Congratulations.
How about a double wedding, honey?
Sit down and shut up.
You look like a damn fool.
What's the matter?
What's going on?
Tell him to go to hell.
Shut up, fag.
You shut up.
You seem to be sniffing a lot
for someone in detox.
Did I miss something?
Two subjects had become taboo
at home:
me,
and Raymond.
- Sucking cock's made you a prick?
That's enough!
Your ass must've been raw
after prison.
He'd done a year for beating up
a junkie who tried to steal his coke.
You'd have enjoyed that, huh?
That's quite enough!
It's Christmas!
Can't we eat in peace?!
Idiots!
How sweet life was
since I had become
so happy and fulfilled.
Aw, Mom!
Yeah, that's right.
Don't call me back
to say she's stopped bleeding.
She'll stop anyway,
whether or not I think of her.
If I truly had a gift,
by dint of being his instrument,
perhaps he would one day
answer my prayers.
Had I known,
I wouldn't have come today.
I think...
you won't come much anymore.
He says it's just
for a couple of weeks.
Just long enough
to get back on his feet.
To run through our savings,
you mean.
Anyway, he seems determined.
I've never seen him like that.
I think, this time, he really wants
to clean up his act.
Please, make an effort.
Your brother needs help.
So Michelle's well, then?
Yeah.
I brought your records back.
- Coffee?
- It's okay, Mom, I'll do it.
What's new?
Not much.
Classes, work.
So, were they a hit?
Your brother's playing
my old records at his club.
Can you believe it?
If that's the nutcase,
I'm not here.
No, he's busy.
Can he call you back?
That her?
It was for Yvan.
Is Doris the "nutcase"?
She was nuts to put up with you
for six years, that's for sure!
I'm sorry, Mom.
I'll be out of your hair soon.
I missed...
your delicious ironed toast.
I love you, Mom.
Any bacon left?
Well, I'll be going.
Already?
- Need a ride back?
- Never mind, Dad.
I'll go.
Coming?
It's disco?
Not just disco.
I play a bit of everything.
Anything unusual.
I'll come see you at some point.
I'll make an exception.
I don't drink anymore,
so I avoid bars.
I don't drink, smoke
or swear anymore.
Fuck, I left my bag of weed
at the pub.
You can drop me at the corner.
Listen...
I know I haven't always been
cool with you.
I need money.
I'll pay you back. I don't know
when, but I swear I will.
You're asking me?
The old man brags that his little
pet makes more than he does.
If he's got a pet,
it sure isn't me.
Don't be a prick, I'm in a jam.
Even if I was a millionaire,
I wouldn't lend you a dime.
Antoine and Christian did.
Even Fatty spotted me 20.
Come on!
Do I have to give you a blow job?
That's it, go kill yourself.
Aren't you in bed yet?
Here.
Someone left this for you tonight.
G'night.
You want to get things hopping,
give this tape to the DJ.
- Do I have to wear this?
- I want this off, too.
Bunch of nitwits. A tux
without a bow tie isn't a tux.
We're all dressed the same.
That's the beauty of it. Huh?
Very nice.
Where have you been?
Fatty.
- Goddammit, Raymond!
- I'll pay you back.
Congratulations.
Aren't you going to introduce us?
My mother.
My brothers.
My father. Min.
What's that?
Min.
He takes after his old man!
Is that idiot gonna play my tape
or what?
Not dancing?
I'm waiting for my song.
By popular request...
Shall we go smoke one outside?
Good idea.
You two go ahead.
Michelle and I will have girl talk.
What is it?
Your girlfriend's nice.
She's cute, too.
You want a shotgun?
A coke.
Same.
I'm very proud of you.
What's so funny?
Check those two out.
Little Zac sure seems
to like his cousin.
Talk about keeping it
in the family!
He's not after his cousin,
but her boyfriend.
I saw them French-kissing
in the parking lot earlier.
So it's true.
Junior's a fag.
Looks like it.
Ah, damn.
Don't touch me!
Are you okay?
Keep dancing.
Just a little misunderstanding.
The wedding goes on.
Keep dancing.
No, everything's okay.
Keep dancing!
Christian!
I'm sorry!
What's going on?!
Stop!
Give us a minute?
On your brother's wedding day!
Raymond causes trouble
and I get in shit?
What happened was your fault.
Your brother was defending you.
You were being called a fag!
They saw you in the parking lot
with your cousin's boyfriend!
What did they see?
It's not what you think.
We were smoking a joint.
We just gave each other a shotgun.
You're a born liar.
Nothing happened!
Be a man for once in your life
and tell the truth!
What do you want to hear?!
That I'm gay?!
A fag?!
That I suck cock?!
Yes, something happened,
but not with him!
You know with who.
Nothing happened earlier.
But I would've fucking loved it
if something had!
Fucking right!
Go.
Go away!
Forgive me, Mom.
I know you'll be sad I'm gone.
But I know you'll be glad
to know where I am.
Don't worry.
Your God is watching over me.
Raymond made me realize something
the other day:
I've never told you I love you.
This side trip to the Holy Land,
before Europe,
would make her ecstatic.
Walking in Christ's footsteps
certainly intrigued me...
but I hadn't crossed the Atlantic
out of Catholic faith.
Zac, are you there?
I love you, sweetheart!
God works in mysterious ways,
my mother always said.
The good Lord brought you back.
It's a sign.
You'll heal him.
Thanks for coming, Christian.
I'm so happy you're staying.
I want to know everything.
Dad coming down?
He's in bed already.
- Good night.
I found him lying there,
with a syringe in his arm.
I think it'll be a while
before I get that 20 back.
What?
You lost that 20 long ago.
If you ask me,
it was no accident.
He'll pull through.
He's tough.
I know I'm not a perfect father.
You certainly wouldn't have
the problems you do otherwise.
Raymond, either.
I'm trying to understand
what's happening to us now...
It's not easy.
I know I'm partly to blame.
I'd like to redeem myself,
but I don't know how.
I don't know what to tell you...
to make you understand
you're not what you think.
You can't forsake
life's greatest pleasure -
having children.
There's nothing more beautiful...
more powerful.
And that really hits home
when you come close...
to losing one.
Because...
there's no greater pain.
The good Lord must surely
be trying to tell me something.
If you think it's a lost cause...
that you can't change...
I can't accept that.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Speaking.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
Even in the face of death,
we have faith that life goes on,
for it comes from God.
It is to him
that we now turn in prayer.
Our Father
Who art in heaven
Hallowed be thy name
Thy kingdom come
They will be done
On earth as it is in heaven
Give us this day
Our daily bread
And forgive us our trespasses
As we forgive those
who trespass against us
And lead us not into temptation
But deliver us from evil
You spoke well.
I was deeply... touched.
Ciao, bro.
See ya, kid.
Mr. Beaulieu...
You'll come visit us, hmm?
Bye, Dad.
Take care of yourself.
Mom, too.
I don't know if it was Raymond's
passing, or if time heals all wounds,
but my father had become
my father once more.
Although it took him 10 years
to allow me into his home
with a lover.
And we've never mentioned
our differences since.
Nor Patsy Cline.
Subtitling and translation:
CNST, Montreal