yeah
ok
the
sweet
yeah
i'm sorry i wish there was more I could
do for her
surely there must be something doctor
she's still weak and so very very sick
we feel so helpless doctor I understand
be strong if she can make it to
Christmas
I think she'll be all right make it
oh if you'll excuse me later okay son
ok
yeah
the moment dad and realism it's going to
be all right
Landon your sister is very very sick
is it the same sickness that makes
you're not able to walk
yes son yes it is but she she's gonna be
okay
well Landon we're not going to lie to
you
Emery is very ill the doctor system
unless she gets better in a few days
by Christmas at the latest we may lose
her
what what will make her better the
doctor says she has to want to get
better
the trouble is she's been so weak for so
long that he's afraid she's given up but
isn't there some kind of medicine or
something we can give her the most
important medicine has to come from
inside Emily Elizabeth herself Landon
we've done all we can do the rest is up
to her
we need to stick together as a family
that's what matters thank you understand
you're brave boy land and we all have to
be brave
it might take a miracle for Emily
Elizabeth to get better but miracles can
happen any time especially at Christmas
that's right hold a good thought for
every Elizabeth
let's hope she finds a reason to fight
back
sure dad now why don't you try to get
some sleep all right
yeah
Emily Elizabeth
come on wake up there's someone here to
scene
why are you here to see a friend a
really cool friend
we're cool Frank
trust me this friend is about as cool as
a friend could be in fact he's still
cool she's freezing
what are you talking about
tena
see I told you he was cool oh man you
love
his name yes watching you kiss me
snowboarding noting smelling snow
listen and if you eat both open you I'll
tell you all about where Snowden comes
from and how we see Prince electron or
kingdom with a little help from his
friends
I mean yes tell me
maybe you need some oatmeal bread I'm
not hiding
come on landing I want to hear the story
oatmeal first story later it's the
greatest story Emery Elizabeth I will
take for me with eating a little open
you but if you don't want to hear it
ok bring your meal
coming right up it better be a good
story he don't you better be worth it
oh it's worth it all right just a snow
yeah
God finish your soup if i do manly tell
me the Snowden story and promise
now eat
I can take it
he lagging
you've been promising me all day frisky
right
I won't tell you this mountain story so
I have a right then it's no national
story
so taking that very going to tell me to
store your
yeah
there's a place far away
a place where there are no teachers no
parents no grown-ups at all
all the people there are children and
his fresh white snow on the ground all
year round
the children of the kingdom were happy
all the time because they felt safe and
sound thanks to the magical smile of the
ruler a kind and beautiful princess mean
Electra yeah that's a bit II just like
every little bit
so any help 1d Andrea Lizabeth and when
visiting princes Electress magical
kingdom memory and maybe Ben wagon
you and me yes you and me now be quiet
and let me tell you
yeah
landing in emory Elizabeth very exciting
because they had been invited by the
princess herself to visit the royal
palace
wow what I don't know but it must be
something very magical
Wow
I'll say it's cool
and that's the way uh huh I like it
cool that is
I talked to no man this magical place
welcome to the palace of Princess
electra I am Snowden Grand Vizier senior
advisor private counsel at hopscotch
partner to the throne huh
hi I'm Landon brother of the sister
pushed out of the chair maker of
snowballs and super skateboarder
pleased to meet you this is emery little
bit however pleased to meet you
now that we dispense with the
formalities would you like the 25-cent
to the place
you bet let's go that really won't be
necessary you know huh
she can do that herself well I can but
we can go faster than my brother pushes
not necessarily
huh what do you mean you just have to
train your mind hit get it
training you're my girl for goodness
sake
think about a train a train think hard
yes it is incredible
correction this is merely a train
you are the incredible one shall we
and we're off
yeah
and now the moment we've all been
waiting for the icing on the cake
the ps2 resistance that preeminent
pinnacle of Princess system
princess
yeah
she beautiful
I've never seen you smile and how wager
that you probably never will again
princess electra smile is a secret to a
power
no one is able to deny her anything
once they have seen it the power of a
smile is awesome memory Elizabeth
it shows that you're happy with the way
your life is going no matter what may be
happening in it
there isn't anything more powerful than
that
aren't we supposed to know something
no silly the only time when you around
here is when we're playing marvel
yeah
see kids in princess electors kingdom
there are no grown-ups except me that is
and all the children have to do all day
long is playing
go on what would you like to try
timeline
yeah
would you like to play on every
Elizabeth oh that's okay i just watch
watch going to show you right where do
you tell her
of course idea indeed idea posilutely
absolutely i did but obviously didn't
stick about the magic inside you about
your ability to make your wheelchair be
whatever you want it to be as long as it
has meal settings very it did turn into
a train a while back and I thought that
was magic
you're mine my magic you think i could
turn your wheelchair into a train that
that's absurd it's comical that's
ridiculous
no it wasn't snow naked
Emery elicited a review going to try
again
anything with wheels on it
yeah
not bad for a beginner
so your dinner was all right
the hot dogs grilled the way you like
them hey fact your milkshakes went too
thick
no no everything was delicious and what
a floor show
yes the dancing elephants are quite good
I day I think the Adagio from Swan Lake
is some of the best work are the beds
made of marshmallows
yes they are do you prefer you can puffs
we have another guest suite down the
hall no marshmallows are great
I just never seen will come to think of
it I've never seen anything like this
place ever
we do pride ourselves on being different
well you sure is there
anything else I can do for you anything
else
I don't think so nothing i can think up
yeah
I guess the lullaby birds will have the
last words tonight number of I Bert's
where they see for yourself
yeah
see
magic lives
like them
doing
just the way
you just
this
yeah
sweet
sure trouble
when I
yeah
and
land every Elizabeth week up hurry
something terrible has happened
why what happened oh it's it's just too
terrible to talk about
come on I'll show you
yeah
what happened why they play right
everybody laughing what happened to
printers electric
yeah
so now you know more open princess
select your smiling a smile has been
stolen stolen who story
I was hoping to spare you this on your
first visit to our kingdom but it seems
you were meant to find out
found out right
find out about that evil villain the
champion of darkness and all around
Lord of yuck the shameless charlatans
and
Charlotte
well well what what
well what is shopping guy and how do you
get a hold the printers and let your bro
tune in tomorrow you heard me
it's getting late and you need your rest
laggin that's not fair
maybe not but that's the way it is get a
good night's sleep and I'll tell you
more tomorrow night but nobody memory a
little bit
I don't know if you go right to sleep or
not because Snowden is watching you and
he tells me everything
brothers can be Mary annoying sometimes
goodnight Snowden
yeah
there and face with the beginner my
youtube your kind of deal can be the
story story what story you know what
story
wrecked off for strike he had stolen the
practices
oh that story I thought you'd forgotten
all about that forgot you
it's all I've been talking about ok come
on
you promised the girls are so impatient
don't you think snow
Snowden says he thinks girls are pretty
impatient too
he did not he said keep your party deal
and you
Emery a little bit the story ok ok now
about charlatans and how we still print
as electro smile
well it seems that during the night the
evil charlatan who ruled everywhere in
the land except for princess electric
magical kingdom decided that he wanted
to rule her land -
and so when everyone was asleep he crept
past the palace guards and stole into
Princess electric been
and with one quick awful movement
Charlotte she took the smile right off
the sleeping princess his face want to
tighten to a little black box
by who charlatans and why do you want to
stay with smile with privacy leg drop
well Justice Snowden had told them
charlatan was the word of young he moved
the entire land forcing children to
bring Brandi rainbows presence and
goodies with evil York factories they
brought this meat things from miles
around took them into his yuck factories
where the rainbows and stuff were turned
yeah
can you say she children
I want boy my master Yoel
oh it's worse than act on without
electric smile to protect them
the children are getting all frightened
and sad smile
both of you said smile
oh thank goodness i guess since you are
outside as you are not affected by
charlatans on chivalrous she camry you
can help me get princess electra smile
back
oh Henry Elizabeth
there is a time for questions and a time
for action which do you suppose this is
well I try to keep up
what do you mean try to keep up just
turn your wheel chair in your car or
something
hey why not
are you feeling scared em realism a
little like glass
just as I thought of fears interfering
with a magic
that's what fear does it always seems
bigger than anything even bigger than
one's own magical powers
i I'm sorry I tried I really tried
everything change so quickly i guess i
am pleased eard that's ok Emery don't
sweat the google push you
maybe I should just stay here I'm really
down
nonsense you better hurry and need all
the help I can get
come on memory Elizabeth this is the
time for action not questions are
pushing it
yeah
I hold I stared
well who isn't we can't delay we must
get the Charlatans lab before he
destroys the princess smile for ever
where is it land across limp and lake
okay well I guess we'd better start
walking around the lake walk around
we'll never make it in time look
it's way too cold to swim how we gonna
get across
perhaps Emery Elizabeth will come up
with an idea
no expecting a stupid wheelchair how can
I possibly help
I don't know anymore Elizabeth call it a
hunch
and usually pretty right about my
hunches
I just think that if you stop feeling
sorry for yourself for a minute
you figure out exactly what to do what
you're supposed to be smart way around
here aren't you
there's a time for questions and
Elizabeth and the time for i know we
know a time for action
let me shake
what is it do you have an idea I'm not
sure maybe I'm sure what is it
well I was just thinking about a nice
cold glass of pink lemonade an entire
kingdom is doomed in your Thursday think
she's onto something here
yeah something pretty silly and you know
how when you put the ice cubes in the
glass and port lemonade guess to float
to the top
oh great now she has to have ice in your
drink
how would a straw to Emory Shh
go on every Elizabeth well I was just
wondering if I said she was float
maybe just maybe you're drunk
that's it that's your idea
you were right bring silly
so much for my hunches come on let's
start walking
no wing stupid idea brilliant idea
brilliant I think not creative
ok inventive I grant you but brilliant
obviously she is not taking into account
that i cannot swim
nevermind swimming can you float I guess
it's really only one way to find out
give me a little push will you
yeah
that she blows all aboard mateys
no me for a lot i should statement in
just a minute
hey this is kind of fun hi Marie like
yes if you like living dangerously
first no man you make a pretty good book
smart but thank you think you see Emily
Elizabeth what you can do you make up
your mind me
I do a bit nothing except come up with
the best I get anyone could possibly
have
how come everything so much creepier on
this side of lipid league
we're getting closer shot yeah that's
all I remember
he rules everything except princess
electrics kingdom and everything he
touches turns to well
yuck let's go it's not that much father
yeah
you'll see my sweet rats in factories
cowardice her smile the children and my
kingdom
bored and depressed with each passing
moment today as long as I hold this
little present their subjects cannot
resist the doubt and despair that I have
spread throughout the rest of the land
sufficient in the despair and
hopelessness
I will force them to work in my yak
factories and noodle you spend over
everything everywhere shall be the ruler
of everything i see and Princess index
happen
shall we buy spray and will be no but my
own one
once and for all
my man
yeah
yes I'm afraid so princess Electress
magical kingdom is the only place left
where charlatans yuk yuk hasn't taken
over and if we don't hurry
that would be lost to come on let's go
we've gotta get principal like to smile
back
forget it landing
we're never going to get this chair of
the young you and snow d
go on without me what no way
okay well hello friends i did just fine
game
forget me forget my stupid chair just
leave me here free then don't care
anymore
Oh feed pretty like your smile from
charlatans and no help anyway
stop talking again right now we would
never living in a free today
what we know in its fine with me to
leave her here if that's what you want
what you're crazy we can't leave her
here
maybe you can't but I can but you
wouldn't
sure I would I have a smile to save
remember you she can't come and watch us
go save your precious smile huh
watching just take off and leave us here
to freeze in this mountainside
once you get here ok sushi sounds
it's late it's time for bed
no way you can leave it like that
Oh No if Snowden can leave you on the
mountain
I can leave it without an ending to the
story tonight come on Ragan just a
little more
okay if I give you a little more
we promise to go right to sleep and not
bug me until tomorrow I promise
okay then here's a little more sleep and
dream dreaming sleep rest your eyes your
berries will keep dreaming sleep
sleeping dream
you're more powerful things see Magic
lives inside of you there's nothing that
you have to do like the moon and twinkle
star
you're perfect just the way you are so
sleep and dream dream and sleep
not a word now not a peep dream and
sleep sleep and dream float away are
magical
be
yeah
ok where we're going
very funny you promise that you made I
hear universe story you should be
finished on Chrissy
it's Christmas oh that's right
it's Christmas Eve ok i'll be early
Christmas present for you
not naturally Christmas you tomorrow
really that must be why they call it
Christmas Eve come
maggen creek hauling tell me what
happened
you're stepping on my mind remember
still left in there alone
everything out we do get out don't be
let's see what does happen to them
so there they were stuck on the side of
the mountain snow net got ahead and it
was getting colder and colder so called
the emory Lisbeth thought that she was
going to turn into a Roman ice pop
you need not really nice pop hey who's
telling the story anyway
but what are we going to do Randy I
don't know but we'd better think of
something fast
Wow Emery Elizabeth remember what Prince
elector said about the magic being
inside of you that you could turn your
turn to anything with wheels
yes then you've got to do it and you've
got to let go of your fears and
concentrate on your magic
remember feeling seems bigger than your
magic but I can't yes yes you can
you got you come on at least try
okay I'll try
that a girl anything with the real me
anything
yeah
your idea my dear life
all you did was work your magic
yeah
wait what took you so long
come on we've got work to do hey you
would make me do all the work by myself
for what I that way
nice airplane make it yourself
yeah
Valley will be mine
look radiant electra subjects I within
my grass
yeah
i get HM soon
there's only one thing remaining to do
with a refreshing smile
yeah
what's that
who's there
yeah
that respect detik avenges my friends
were too late
they can will be - smile is gone which
by making it should be right
have out
yeah
yes you boy
Kim minutes
yeah
a little out of your conscience
snowman
the good thing about being a snow man
shot and he is that even though we might
lose our heads
we fix why he's me you go him or
Elizabeth
you want to give me a hand
I got my head screwed on backwards there
now you have to be able to see string
Thank You Man I always wanted to get
ahead in life
yeah
over here and make sure much
quickly you guys run
yes I am I can't hold off these flames
along
yeah
the German
it doesn't go kid
each be read
Merry Christmas Emery Elizabeth you made
it
magic lives inside of you there's
nothing that you cannot do like the moon
and twinkling star
you are perfect just the way you are
so sleep and dream dream sleep
not a word now not a peep dreams sleep
and dream flown way on a magical be
yeah
what's going on here wheres knowing
where every day
yeah
the magic is inside love snow
but how Puckett
how did this happen
trying requesting landing and there's a
time for action
Merry Christmas landing is a Merry
Christmas and realize mr. mr. marriage
Christmas ever
yeah
Oh
he's doing
still the same
sleep
yeah
this