since before recorded time it had swung
through the universe in an elliptical
orbit so large that it's very existence
remained a secret of time and space but
now in the last few years of the 20th
century the visitor was returning
the citizens of earth would get an extra
Christmas present this year as their
planet orbited through the tail of the
comet scientists predicted a light show
of stellar proportions something not
seen on earth for 65 million years
indeed not since the time that the
dinosaurs disappeared virtually
overnight there were few who saw this as
more than just a coincidence but most
didn't
Oh
everyone
fine
I'm sure you
the best way
this
wait this is 8
retailers
No
we're here or not hey Regina Regina give
that thing a rest with it in a minute
Mel look I don't pay you to do that kind
of stuff around here Regina I want you
to clean everything absolutely get out
of here won't you come everything's
cleaned up dan I want you to take this
flashlight and walk the house um no they
throw things at me who cares walk the
house you ever been hit with dot smell
Milk Duds those things hurt I oh how are
you sir the refreshments are right over
there thank you I don't want those
widows cutting up the siege understand
okay okay placing read in third place
yes place
wait a minute
somebody named DMK and six place when
did this happen look don't be an
overachiever you'll fit in better with
your age group okay this is really
annoying Regina Regina looked this way
Regina okay read my lips flashlight walk
house okay let me take this one okay
that's great they go to profit and
listen stay out of the projection booth
and stay away from debris no fire that
guy someday it's been doing to me what
he's been doing to her in the booth
you're right i want to check it out you
see i'm talking about a mint-condition
print of it came from outer space in 3d
man yeah right trace d menciones look
you know as well as I do you got film
freaks that go down on you for a bootleg
print of that up hundred bucks 100 bucks
right something wrong with the phone
here did I hear you say hundred dollars
look one hundred dollars isn't gonna get
it this time because I'm gonna have to
spend the night in your waiting for you
to bring the print back think I'm gonna
miss his common thing for a lousy
hundred dollars okay 110 is a little
better yet hey Reggie here's the deal
you leave I let you in the back door
okay i leave you let me back in melting
surveys done there do you know anybody
named DMK no oh well you gotta have a
rip back by six in the morning you know
if we spend the night in your witness
the comment it's not like you can't see
you on television all right get you guy
here to know yeah well maybe I want to
take for beetle
hey televisions real told us it's very
real so what do you say I'll give you
fifteen dollars are you kidding we spend
the night in here we end up making it
you give me fifteen bucks do you know
what that makes me look like Reggie I'm
not giving you fifteen bucks for making
it with okay well just so we have that
straight okay yeah for sure I mean you'd
be with lot more than fifteen bucks
everybody knows that the first
Earthlings to see the effects will be in
Newfoundland or Newfoundland this is
expected to begin it at 20 for that is
six at a time an interesting sidebar to
this story is is the fact that all
telecommunications seem to be out in
that part of the world it's good
hello Samantha the sound pissed I just
had it out with Doris once and for all
again she wants me to like haul chips
and dips around for a little comment
party yeah well speaking of doors look I
need your help tell her that you know
all about this field trip that I'm gonna
take ok with my science class we're
gonna go to the observatory to watch the
comment she won't go for it she'll go
just tell her okay mm-hmm Doris Reggie's
on the phone she's not having car
trouble she's gonna be out all night
with your science class at the
observatory I know all about it
yeah hi Doris what's this about a
science class Regina well you want me to
do better in science don't you I want
you home in five minutes after you
finish work you want to watch the
comment you can do it here look Doris
like I'm 18 okay and I can watch the
comet wherever I want to watch the comet
here's Samantha you and your sister
share a lot of Secrets I want you to
share this one with them if it were up
to me I couldn't care less what she did
but if your father makes it back home
without some sandanista blowing his
brains I got a little irresponsible for
any kind of trouble you two girls get
into what we have here is a chain of
command major jumps on me I jump on you
did you get that okay
now are you going to join the party join
the party for what Doris so I can watch
chuck from across the street stick his
hands down your pants I think that's
something daddy should know Chuck's a
nice guy he's certainly nice to be with
while daddy's down a banana land you
were born with an asshole Doris you
don't need Chuck
looks like a real nice crowd we have out
here tonight
hey where've you been you gonna miss
everything store Oh kids I'll never
marry another round
yeah two in 1910 Halley's Comet Reacher
hahaha everybody thought they were going
to die there
you're sad look
you want to know what bugs me about all
this what well I'm always afraid
someone's gonna see us you know see us
how there's no windows they can't see
through walls Superman can see through
walls that these walls are made out of
steel used to be a fire law Superman can
see through steel no it's one thing you
cannot see Jimmy that's led you nerd
good yeah I mean Superman can see
through steel like it wasn't there even
huh well I guess I'm the only one who's
not outside watching the meteor jar just
might win right it's not autopilot you
sneak out myself
you
god damn it what what I've been waiting
by that door for the last 30 minutes and
that pinhead hasn't brought the film
back yet Oh give the guy a break I mean
people are late sometimes no something's
wrong if you screwed that film up we
could all be in a lot of trouble I'm
gonna go over there in the bike oh geez
don't I get an egg mcmuffin or anything
you could do me a favor Stu favor last
night that guy calls you tell him I'm on
my way over and I'm very very very very
pissed and what about my 15 bucks come
you're pissed too
DMK trust you they get screwed over
every God oh is that you yeah it's about
friggin time
you
in the udm gay your history
god that's mock shit shit damn it just
right his clothes everywhere
I hate days that stuff like this
what is this trick or treat copier what
car yeah come here your ass
look I don't know what your scene is but
don't do anything stupid okay
then you don't seem to understand I've
been trained to take care of myself you
know what I'm saying I don't want to
hurt you
oh shit
I'm wrong
Oh
golden God
Meghan on spirit friends
you
Samantha Doris
what god what are you trying to do give
me a heart attack not you were Doris no
she decked me last night not one of my
teeth loose even wait till daddy hears
about that you know how he's always
telling me to be careful with my mouth
account of the dental plan doesn't cover
anything cosmetic Oh anyway get this I
think Chuck and Doris spent the night
together last night wait till daddy
hears about that I mean even if he
wasn't pissed off about my mouth which I
can't imagine what's happening oh yeah I
guess you are a little confused God you
look terrible I ran away last night
after she slipped me left a note and
everything I didn't have any place to go
so I spent the night in the lawn storage
ship pretty grossly the snare all and
everybody God ditch I know no anyway
some time is still here this morning I
thought okay I'll go to pep squad
practices fled after its acredito Pep
Squad practices on or not can't get
anybody on the phone Sammy you can't get
anybody on the phone because everybody's
gone what do the mountain I swear to god
they swallow my gum there's nobody I
mean there's no buddy all right nobody
I'm sure come here hey back off sweater
cost 80 bucks
Muffy stupid dog look look at this and
what Doris isn't it Chuck's I'll show
you Doris here's Doris enormous left of
her this is dust look here's Chuck where
are the kids
it's Saturday morning where the goddamn
kids
they're around they're not around look
if you're trying to scare me you're
doing it okay I'm not trying to scare
you and stop it i'm not doing it you try
kalixa not just your pep squad anyone
nobody's home unbelievable that song
number 16 on the survey this weekend
don't forget we preview the top 20 every
Friday night a great way to start a
super weekend here in Southland get dad
are you sure this is the radius
do you think whatever happened happened
everywhere like in burbank or places
like that lhasa DJ he does the news
doesn't he search me i always change the
channel when this comes on here's
something here
so where is he
I mean somebody has to run this stuff
don't think we got trouble not us that's
the name of the song and I'm Steve the
bow trapped inside your radio the guy
who really cares about you I mean who
else would sit in this little box every
day just play music quarter well it's
time to reach into the old mail bag here
got a letter from beam me up Scotty
what's the high school okay girls hold
it right there you the blog get into the
light wait why don't you just let my
sister go and maybe you and I can work
something out I'm not go anywhere you
got the wrong idea you into the line
i'll give it a buy one to know all right
let's right this way five four three
okay in a lot of dates this one open
your eyes okay hey I know what you're
thinking but that you're a cretin
sweetheart you haven't seen those freak
down zombies running around here yeah I
was jumped by one well you got off lucky
me and this girl pulled into town this
morning you don't work here no I Drive a
truck I was heading to San Diego with
this girl I picked up you were looking
for a gas station that's when we spotted
one of those
whatever they are look like it was
eating look like he's eating a cat a
dead cat she say my did who'd want to
eat a live cat beat the shit out of me
let's go freaked out took off running I
spotted her about 20 minutes later
looked like one of those things head
what
torner apart oh god Larry oh shit what's
with her I think she's gonna be stick or
something guys she knew same thing might
have happened good safe around here do
you think yeah I checked it out
Wow are you all right my name is Hector
what's yours just leave me alone okay
look I I know we got off on the wrong
foot but considering what the
alternative is I think we should try to
get along what do you say listen this is
no time for an attitude problem your
little sister seems to be taking this a
lot better than you that's cuz she
doesn't know what's going on and you do
I suppose whatever's going on isn't just
here it's everywhere she thinks we're
gonna be rescued that her dad's gonna
come back from Honduras with the goddamn
Green Berets she could be right it was a
break heck tour where'd you spend the
night last night
I spent the night in the back of my
truck with a girl I picked up what else
do you want to know skip it steals gotta
be the answer if Sam spent the night in
the long storage shed what again I'm an
employee I can't just our way of saying
merry Christmas to you from all over
testing one two three four this is
Samantha Velma one third owner of the
Greater Los Angeles basin speaking you
guys hey is anybody there did you get
this a dime store beats me I'm just
giving to me yeah well might be all
right for date night in the barrio but
if we're maintaining more of those guys
outside with me a little more stopping
power date night
and here's some other changes most you
guys had finals this week cook later
their history their canceled the legal
drinking age is now 10 but you will need
ID let's be real I'll be taking requests
from all you teenage comment zombies on
the hit line that's 5554 487 you get it
five five five hits
you know where the Armed Forces Reserve
Sandra is at Los Alamitos yeah my dad
used to take us there photographer jstor
automatic weapons there you know how to
use him come on Hector mac-10 submachine
gun was practically designed for
housewives I got a call hello it what
did did they say they were ok I don't
know he said they were in the desert it
didn't participate I don't know shit
think why don't you just pull your gun
on her maybe you can scare it out of us
they said they were like part of a think
tank research group or something where
was it in the state forget ok let's take
it real slow did they mention a town
someplace they were near like maybe Bly
bishop what about Edwards Air Force if I
knew I tell you I didn't expect the call
you know and then take notes or
something just try I think I'm not going
what they'll stay put we can get
anything from a psychological standpoint
the radio station represents a link to
normalcy I don't think they'll wandered
far as long as its operating dr. Carter
I just like to say up front I'm opposed
to this there's no reason for us to
bring those people or any other
survivors back here what about the
disintegration factor you just want to
let that happen and you don't know that
the condition is progressive I think
we've established that Audrey partial
protection seems to result in a slowing
of the overall effect a progression is
steady in any case drying up the body
fluids get to the point on transition if
you have some time to mately what about
the dust ultimately there is nothing
left but calcium dust right so there
isn't even enough hope to warrant
bringing anybody back here so what
you're saying is we shouldn't even try
you want to be caught a city after dark
relief tomorrow we've had an indication
of some survivors in San Bernardino as
well four maybe five yeah they said be
careful on the street because some
people were exposed to the comic a
little bit what happened to Doris is
happening to them only slower like
they're dangerous
like what happened to Larry
you're not gonna play me because the
phone was dead I'm not the phone company
nobody's the phone company anymore
why
cops
as earlier
shit a license
oh shit I know you guys are probably
gonna give me a ticket or something but
I am really glad to see
profits it everything must go big
savings on tuners turntables car stereos
also demos and freight damaged items
this weekend only Henry stereo warehouse
fourth and alamitos recall committee
those free balloons for the kids
what's wrong it's okay you got her yeah
I got her
it's a nice entry I know
I know why interesting technologies is
neat opportunity employer looks like the
weather is shaping up for a great
weekend you know it's hard to believe
that there's only 11 more shopping days
till Christmas good luck finding a
parking within hitchhiking distance to
the balls to you know jam to get
you
she okay yeah okay so come on in and
have a seat
listen I have to go to San Diego
tomorrow why my mom some friends my
sister but you know they're gone
I know but
I still have to find out I mean you guys
know for sure but I don't know you have
like a close family yeah
pretty close
you man
a real mom hung around to my dad came
back from Vietnam then she split so it's
been mostly me and Sam and dad in 3rd
Special Forces smoke bomb Hill boy frag
but then around the sixth or seventh
grade it became a breathable obvious
that we weren't boys I'm never going to
go and Ranger School so I guess they had
to figure there's nothing more documents
so not seen your mom I'm not looking for
a war
what about the guy Larry oh he and I
were quite steady
don't go to San Diego I have 20 but i'll
be back
please okay what does it give me if I
come back
texas
florida florida texas why I want to come
back
your choice
here great see this is the problem with
these things daddy would have gotten a
Susie's the car didn't know the
difference
so did you make it with him last night
who the Good Humor man who do you think
Jesus that was bugging you that's no
answer man no I didn't make it with him
last night why you so weirded out oh
right reg why should I be weirded out my
sister who swiped every guy I ever had
my eye on his now swiped the last guy in
the whole freaked out world
mom
mother bah
I don't know who you are out there but I
have a gun so if I were you I'd split
but I had a chance ok look Kate to stay
away we don't wanna
who you are my kids jeez neighborhood
Audrey what's the code
you
we found survivors how long were the
blood test take not long I've talked
with some of the others and we decided
that it would be more beneficial to
conduct the blood tests in the field so
I want you to go to LA with the rest of
the group whatever the charity won't you
don't seem to hold majority rule and
very high regard if something's wrong
it's wrong majority rule doesn't have
anything to do with it but it goes
straight to the core purpose of our
group which is to survive you'll grant
me that the core purpose never included
bringing outsiders to the facility
it's about the 12th can you down this
morning thirsty yeah well what are you
gonna do when your complexion freaks up
dermatologist is dead you know I know
and I'm getting a rash or something too
oh god you and your rashes hey I'm sorry
at the end of the world makes me a
little nervous
so do you like him come on Sam I'm just
interested yeah well I guess so I mean
he's nice who is this new guy at school
Paul Morgan and transferred from Taft
jr. oh I don't hang around with juniors
much I liked him I mean he was from TAF
but
he was nice
Kathy said he was probably gonna ask me
out hey Kathy she was flunking algebra
and she was trying to figure out some
way to keep her parents from finding out
it's really lucky break for her
no wonder I'm breaking out think we
could go home and change look why don't
we get a little creative what Jim Yura
give your MasterCard on you know good
cuz you don't need it the stars are up
and
Oh
rich which do you like better this
the second one
definitely how come sit stay in style
longer guess you're right up yeah we got
to think of these things you know all
right let's do it you know I've been
thinking don't set any dangerous
precedent look at jers got the same
problem with such as such as no guys
what really
I mean with Hector's gay
I'm sure think it over you said he
didn't come on to you last night so so
that means that the last guy on earth is
either a gentleman or fad I mean what
are the odds in LA things could be very
interesting around here Regina attention
shoppers I trust you've got credit cards
to pay for all that stuff
you
what's the matter lost something check
with lost and found on the second floor
I'm this one you dirty rat get her boys
well I think it's time to take the high
ground listen you guys we're expecting
some friends here any minute look you
just split now okay and what's housing
not to hurt you no imagination
hi
knock that shit off hello out there in
television land alright here's the deal
if bachelorette number one isn't out
here in half a tick I'm gonna ice
bachelorette number two got it
come on let her go I'm sorry miss I
can't have you holding one of my people
hostage even if you pulled the trigger I
can still take him out and you come on
Lily she means it miss you're not
getting the point I can't have you
holding one of my people hostage you're
crazy I'm not crazy I just don't give a
fuck what do you think 20 30 minutes no
more they could be anywhere by now let's
go back let's apply a little deductive
reasoning deductive reasoning where
would adolescence with nothing to do go
see we worked really hard to get ahead
in this business girls and we don't get
shit for it let me do it because we know
we can work our way up through the
system and the system works why just a
few days ago we were only stock boys now
we own the store the American Way and
then this happens what are you talking
about I'm talking about you coming in
here and ripping us off what do you want
you want us to pay for it what you
wouldn't believe what we want from you
in your worst nightmare you wouldn't
believe let's play again it's called
scary noises this is the closest
shopping arcade but the whole area is an
absolute monument to consumerism all we
can do is hope check all the floors
including the basement
isn't that a scary noise went to hear it
again gosh the suspense is killing me
let's do it an e-ticket attraction let's
do it again
now wait a minute I don't think there's
really a bullet in here no now see there
it's loaded I just needed to be a little
more patient I think this is it girls I
really do
oh we're not with these guys really like
we just met him an hour ago it's ironic
all the great minds of the world all the
great intellects who should survive
almost survive I don't have to see the
results of the blood test I can guess
what they say about that one
you're right
it would be senseless to take her back
look I'll stay and take care of it then
if this Hector person shows up i can run
tests on him too of course yeah it would
be out of the question to let you remain
by yourself I'll stay here with you
listen thanks for suggesting that I'm
late for Hector I mean I know Reggie la
biblia get him but I'd like to have a
shot at it Samantha I need you to lie
down Hector's not exactly a fox but
considering what's left he's not bad it
sounds cute is he coming back yeah but
we should wait from at the radio station
that's where I'll go what's that um I'm
gonna give you something for what well
your skin's been a little irritated yeah
a rash it could be a rash but it could
also be something else it's one of the
main symptoms of the comment no see I
always get rashes like when I have a
fight with Doris or I break up with the
boyfriend it's nerves and you know the
way things have been going around here
lately I'm surprised I don't look like
strawberry jell-o hmm but if I do have
that stuff this will get rid of it right
yeah god you had me worried don't worry
just a pinch now oh so you guys are like
geniuses right yeah I thought so
we have a couple of geniuses up by
school yeah yeah they're both wimps
is that it what did you want me to do
Oscar take her out back and shoot her in
the head I simply meant I was glad it
was painless I don't think we have to
stay around she didn't think that he was
coming back I feel we can wait but uh I
feel a radio station is the more logical
place listen Oscar you were right about
the condition being progressive but it
is also accelerating apparently we don't
have weeks we have maybe hours I don't
know we have a commitment but i do know
i don't have enough to debate the issue
i am not going to be a party to taking
anybody else back you have to live up to
it what do you expect me to do Oscar go
for my gun of course
I do whatever has to be
look at me let's break it over
450 FM in the PM I'm Steve phone you're
listening at 50,000 watts rock'n'roll at
tower power to the city of angels
Reggie Merry Christmas
Reggie
hi Jeff and I see two girls running
around here one's a cheerleader I'm not
thinking straight I wrote everything
down but i think i misspelled it that
hat on the table you need this no thanks
i have one seems to be the perfect
Christmas gift this year I'm gonna miss
Christmas permanently
I want you to know that I thought they
were talking hypothetically though they
found the purse survivors and they
really did it some of those survivors
were just kids hey wait a minute what's
all this about blood they think they can
generate and see a serum we were exposed
not a lot just enough
they left the ventilating ducts wide
open the fans going very scientific very
stupid in 36 hours
you will be able to vacuum up the last
of them from the carpet
hey you know what
she was right you are cute
have you ever had hepatitis Terrence
your pair scissors no have you ever had
hepatitis cute kids they party you guys
know their survivors just like you are
my girl huh he liked tight come on kids
come with me have you ever had hepatitis
no I'd mana once though cut it from this
guy named Randy shark anemia no are you
pregnant nope thought it was once though
it's not important that's what you think
was the longest three weeks of my life
you know I can't remember how much blood
were we expected to get from these
people ah 300 cc's yes that's it that
can't be right if we draw 300 cc's a day
they'll expire all together no I don't
think so now that we've terminated brain
functions I mean their brain dead all
they can do now is manufacture blood
well maybe but we are going to get
anything like 300 cc's out of those
children no but we will out of that
teenager I hope she's just healthy as
she looks boy did you see her hair what
I'd give to have hair like that what is
this place do you have diabetes my name
is this some sort of I know underground
hospital or what you're a very
strong-willed young lady cancer you have
cancer no I am a cancer I just want to
know where I am and what I'm doing here
oops oh gosh uh could you hear me that
our tier got it
well it's up to the respirators now why
don't we prep the children when are
finished with them we can start on that
girl they're so cute I love working with
kids yeah oh don't forget the lights are
you taking any medication have you had
any medication within the last 24 hours
where's my sister dr. Carter I see you a
moment all right I mean she should be
here by now shouldn't she even if Hector
didn't show up your sisters did what I
realize this comes as a shock but she
had been exposed and in 48 hours she
would have died anyway it was quite
painless I can assure you
you both have my strong hearts are we
gonna get shots no no shots I promise
Audrey not back yet listen we may have a
situation on our hands here I can't
locate Rogers any place in the combo
can't rule out the possibility that you
may already have gone into transition we
can't wait for Audrey you're gonna have
to start with the children and that went
in there we need blood to develop the
serum you don't have enough for everyone
we're not robots doctor we're not all
going to fall over at one time some of
us will last a little longer while
others of us have more immediate need
you're smart you can figure that out
psychology
I'm very sorry about your sister it's a
tragedy it truly is and I can understand
your hostility but no matter how upset
you are breaking an expensive piece of
equipment won't solve anything that
means striking out at inanimate objects
is really quite childish you should be
able to realize that
howdy partner how you do it who are you
names hick hick go man Hayden's real
finders you got there youmu tag
repairman hey did you find this place
well uh is lady back in LA sent me hey
you been to LA lately it's cleaned up in
I'm telling you hey hey come here I want
to show you something come on
hey you know how the Harbor Freeway is
always bumper to bumper when you can go
150 miles an hour if you want to me and
this baby we going through them freeways
like turkey crap through a 10 horn hey
you like girls look in here she's good
she did see this lady shot her up with
sodium pentathol make this feller think
she was dead so you wouldn't something
blood on your asshole bitch excuse me
everyone three in our adolescent guest
has escaped she's quite hostile we have
already gone outside please take a
moment crown
check those rooms and all genders
let's go everything's under control good
you said no shots this isn't a short
sweetheart it'll just you'll just giggle
and then you'll feel a little sleepy
that's right and when you wake up do you
know where you'll be we're with Santa
Claus at the North Pole in fact go live
with Santa Claus with the rest of your
life hey there's no such thing as Santa
Claus what don't believe in Santa
life support systems doesn't come with
me keep an eye on her right now Wilson
and the door turn off the alarm
hey
I don't know my parents told me never to
brief anything from strangers hey get
your hands up
what are you guys doing they said if we
breathe this we can go to the North Pole
and see Santa Claus that's sick whoa Sam
I give I give they said you were dead
they were exaggerating totally hey
that's a great outfit Thanks is that guy
in the hallway dead don't
well
you can give up if you want to Wilson
but we still have the two children
for the kids yeah my man ratchet that's
I'm Sam that's how protector can I funny
in a minute beat feet on collector
I picture of a flower
where've you been we change this ranging
a hotfoot few friends I really hate this
music give me a break what are you doing
I'm not kidding I get carsick without my
bunny come on Raj give the kids a bunny
we've stopped why have we stopped son of
it don't shoot them you idiot okay kids
cover your eyes for uncle Hector
hey think tank ah ah couldn't we just
like leave think over this we can get
them hey mija I get chasing some party
down huh the kids would like to say
goodbye it's been fun hope to see you
around real soon that gasoline smell
wait wait
Wow all right after
okay get smoked come on hmm don't god
you're don't you wait okay mr. bunny
needs to be in this picture too so okay
that's great can I take this jacket off
it is you can't I just want to take
another picture all right um please
oh-ho now you just hold on to that stay
there okay perfect your brother there's
still a few days around don't slouch and
Sarah hold that smile mmm-hmm / go off
kept telling these things hey if you're
gonna send those guns away can I have
one don't look at me I mean I don't know
where she gets that stuff smile head
handsome maybe I could be a nun or
something about 30 of them you know
we're gonna need some more feel I'm
street here time hey god they look like
the Brady Bunch what are you waiting for
can I see him we're waiting for the
light to change we do not cross against
the light are you nuts auntie Regina you
may as well face the facts Samantha the
whole burden of civilization has fallen
upon us what's that supposed to mean it
means we do not cross against the light
that's totally stupid there's nobody
here see we're talking ghost town
see what happens
god I'm sorry but you shouldn't cross
against the light like that hey you guys
are survivors too huh what nothing great
card thanks i have 23 of them you want
to go for a ride more than you know
we don't know anything about this guy
where's he from what's his name tonight
Danny Mason keener Danny Mason cater
okay yeah alright well just be back by
midnight okay midnight the our new
civilization is on us okay oh yeah
bitchin isn't it
this time to get back happy
we used to be
please don't either
Oh
we can
taja then it has to be weird
I trend
to give up so easily
Oh
yeah we got
big
you can
awesome
Oh
you are
I
Oh
faster
me
Oh
No