[Music]
where does a river begin with the
seasons changing the thaw of winter snow
or is it there all the time bubbling
from the earth Unleashed and running
wild there are torrential flows rivers
of cruel intent as well as pleasure and
life providing waterways and mountain
streams that no one sees along with
majestic miles of water that do little
more than irrigate but in a land rich
with rivers and soil at his damp with
their leavings there is one and only one
that flows through a thousand miles and
as many lives taking and leaving like a
woman but with a name like a man the
Colorado
[Music]
we've all had that dream a paradise away
from it all anywhere on your own small
down 50 years to pay and desert winds on
schedule so you saved and you make the
down and you've got it made almost sure
the desert winds blow on schedule but
they blow many ways and carry more than
the scent of water hyacinths and
flowering verbena and in a certain
longitude and latitude you can even
smell garbage oh it stinks you smell
yourself Helen good Holger hurt the
basin Mushu what's your pleasure cafe au
lait all ok where's the kid well she
left that girls instead of lungs no I
think it back without bill it's
definitely lungs you're getting loose
bad bed I don't like you talking like
that she might hear you he's only 16
since when is 16 sacred I was 16 great
my daughter that's what's saving you
anybody's well I ain't nobody's nothing
but I think I'm a lot better hoping that
kid is never mind that just call her in
nearly time Carlo meet baby your Papa
want you
bench postcard small upper I keep
telling her to keep her clothes on stay
right for the swim like that it doesn't
bother her why should it bother you I'm
her father right worried about wait I'm
sure you do tell me about it sometime
papa
you
[Music]
hi Carl how was Italy great just a swim
with me sometimes it's wonderful
exercise shitty what I need is good I
get enough exercise during the wild
Amazon bid for the circus father your
pins you don't feel well oh he's just
slow on the rebound still wet cold you
better dress cracker will be here soon
with the losers said get dress yes
Father must would do this many more
times I don't like what we're doing it's
better without the suckers but we gotta
eat all think you better get dressed too
you mean step don't you there girl is f
where they're already world was which
park I'll be the welcoming committee and
Carl can do down the dead girl does
enough dancing too much sometimes go and
get ready one more crack like that
Babette's you go back to the board
shaking your keister for busted out
Cowboys they at least knew the
differences in a wife and a daughter you
know a lot don't you you'd know our
mother she was a lady she was so much
alike like twins
wait I've seen the picture doing but you
must decide it's your wife that stood
and your daughter that's alive I know I
know I'm sorry forgive me 00 ride
machete I will prepare my body like you
say we must take maybe psych i will
place an expander for changer
[Music]
met through the gods into some of us
eclectic damn just poor laddie oh crap I
don't put out about taking make the
resort run early then I got lucky I
spotted a young pair to spawn the guy is
about average drain nothing average
about his own woman so I don't care if I
hypno action or not I just gotta get a
closer look right then I notice two
things quick they'd exactly the same
orbit and she's wearing half of
Tiffany's window on one hand and Charlie
they was really she was so I makes me
pitch you know the usual stand hopefuls
haven the host unique result in Arizona
beautifully remoteness const on old over
lake adjacent to a Colorado an open-air
cocktail out who by the gentle doesn't
win substantial drinks to satisfy an
Alec cuisine to tempt your taste buds a
beautiful young maid to administer to
your every whim and the base t
resistance a voluptuous amazon that
appears when you least expect it to
round out today and then her husband
cuts me off so I thought I was dead
another blank but Miss round bottom
collared me or I can make a step she
tells me she'll be there with or without
girls but gives me a fast song about
he's a croaker and nothing too good help
with a pump pump is running uphill and
with that
she swings off cui resolve is more like
I could almost hear the drum pleats my
next customer is a real kilkenny can I
don't sell him he sell me right off he
kids be like I'm the bark and he to the
calm a thousand questions where is a
spread and all that I expect them to
pull out a badge instead he pulls out a
bankroll ashokan up he slips be a double
sawbuck and takes off so here's around
autumn boats peaceful seat it's the only
way to travel absolutely ridiculous the
best weed in the spa here we are
embarking on this jaunt looking for a
sideshow that we don't even know exists
CeeLo will you listen to me will be
different I see the same people in this
Turkish bath and I seen your office
every day she live a doctor what do you
want me three healthy people don't
snivel there please you're wrong man are
you certain this is the bus no that's
that a little red Jeep this was supposed
to be an excursion I don't see that
dirty old man around howdy folks be
right we're here hiya doc this is Ross
this is mr. Rickard just a bar near it
where are the others there are no other
this is sort of an intimate type trip
those are the best don't you agree mr.
Rickard I presume you know how to drive
this bus yes sir you won't have a thing
to worry about the rest of the day now I
take the two folks understand its cash
in pants everything on the spread is
obtained the same way here's mine let's
get on with it
[Music]
well let's crank her up and get rolling
wait'll oldu get to look at these tender
feet
Betty yet wait until a cop a sneak of
hoople's Halen if after the Safari even
a sneaked it would look like Las Vegas
they're sure a cold cruel well that that
stands so far him out she's a mic warman
little piece players that redheaded
Aislinn digger good he sure got the
Ducks wife pinned the looks they're
passing it ain't a question a win but
how yep should be a right into today
[Music]
well this is where we disembark on our
second leg of our little adventure folks
short and squatty
I give you a hand with those bags mr.
Rickard this isn't an overnight trip of
the record oh don't you have a room in
town
it's more comfortable in the stern mrs.
Ross nothing like a river with hey Doc
son of a barrier busting my name is dr.
martin wroath sir and when did you last
bathe that bum thinks he's in surgery
[Music]
[Applause]
I mr. Rickett would you give me a hand
with the life we're almost there
[Music]
how long you been in his rabbit oh let's
see Joey took the place over in 53 and
he started a tourist been to 59 after
his wife died oh I'd say five years unit
three months more or less
you were just settling in these parts
how many city well I see one it's two
more in the stern man and a woman yeah
take a look
the only game reserve within 1,000 miles
price is right and could be ours and the
olefin for a pirate's time
you
hi Carl hi All Right girls let's get
with it now
it's a work I called you better go down
and greet our visitors tell cracker I
want to see him right away yes Father
[Music]
this place he's the welcoming committee
Dewey's pride and joy also his daughter
see boy local color maybe you'll get a
welcoming kiss a girl so we don't allow
her Goshen nobody if it isn't too much
trouble maybe you could give me a hand
oh yeah no sense all of us getting wet
[Music]
you always get a free ride welcome to
hookah savin you want you to be well
it's different honey I'll say that good
luck to you sir thank you now if you'll
just get us some shade in a pool
drinking I thought the pastor don't I
get one too hey pops bring the big 10
mr. cracker fight would like to see you
right away okay okay just as soon as I
get things stowed
welcome folks we've got a full day
planned for you a happy day when you
long remember that is the foul last
water I've ever tasted we're gonna drink
much water around here doctor hey why
don't you try one of these dude you have
a double don't you think that two
fingers with water would help him Oh two
fingers anywhere to help him Oh Josh
does everything you say mean something
else well it's not what people say it's
important it's what they do what do you
do sir mind my own business say yeah
where is all this entertainment we've
been promised you are a master with the
needle
you
[Music]
I get advantage for you never mind that
Please Please hell out of that outfit
take a look at his hand you are a doctor
aren't you
[Music]
I'll need your help nurse
you
open the band-aid open the band-aid must
you pant it's an animal traitor
sumbitchin laid here or don't you
remember
[Music]
it has been such a long time
what'd you do to your hair not for
nothing later crackers
stop bleeding yeah i can replace it with
booze it has less emotion than blood
kind of a freaky place to be bringing up
a good-looking daughter was enough when
her mother was alive she fell a lot of
gaps do you want something yeah I want
to buy your spread look let's don't fool
what's obvious you're broke you got a
teenage kid you don't even know what to
do is well fax your life I want to buy
this busted out dude ranches shot as it
is I still want to buy it what my action
that's not for sale I'm packing a bundle
enough to change your mind hey plenty of
time to reconsider
about an hour on cue there's a scratch
well you'll never let me get the cmas
bad back to her stuff on the wrist look
it over I know how much you charge guys
like this listen how about my back wages
Rankin didn't I tip you off about the
big guy did he make you an offer for the
joint listen Joey all I want is fine
just forget it I turned him down
[Music]
sure hope she's careful with that
carving knife be shameful to lose any of
her equipment you couldn't kill him
broad with an axe all the ridiculous
things now are you satisfied with this
farce of an adventure don't give up
there she may cut a juggler vain you can
save her life and both go off to a
coconut tree live happily ever after
looks like he's going to BBQ yourself
[Music]
[Applause]
you must use up a lot of Amazon's that
way after that I could stand a double
aye sir you another you sir nothing
thanks just tell your father that we're
ready to leave and so back to the
Turkish bath no no I dig doing a dance
like that really silly you never cease
to amaze me if you must show off your
body join a nudist camp we could start
one here mr. horrible we have a
wonderful idea a nudist camp camp and
I'll be president vice president that's
more fun and your lesson recording
secretary are you ready to record is
your turntable were cool shine heaven's
name just getting that boat and go and
don't come back for 48 hours now you
don't have anything to worry about when
you get back you'll have a new boss a
raise in pay and a tank full of bourbon
now you look in my suitcase you'll find
two bottles of bourbon empty amount in
the water and throw the empty bottles up
on the beach where they have you found
that way they'll think you just got
gassed and drifted away Alan you
boom in the water now you just get in
that boat and take off and don't start
the motor until your way offshore now
haul ass
[Music]
you baby are one hell of a bartender
these drink had me a midship and washed
or marooned and um what the hell hey
where is the midship is it far is it up
here it's about in the middle man of a
human or a ship not sure of anything are
you I don't think he's quite sure how to
handle a drunken woman fling he hates my
guts stranger they like me like you say
what is this a stag party where's the
girl your daughter-in-law marshmallow on
a stick she didn't join the water god
did she yeah where have you been I mean
feat since i'ma d'oeuvres
what is this I mean is it to eat it's
moving live food how perfectly wonderful
oh I do believe they're racing each
other across the plate you've missed
everything we're going to start a nudist
colony do you have any vaccinations
don't start that one hell of a lot of
maybe am i disqualified he'll know
you're president now strip down and
we'll look over your qualification let's
look over yours first because you've got
a lot more going far it's all right
should I show them how right dear don't
you think it's time we took our leave
it's time believe me it's time coral
tell cracker to crank up the boat whoa
baby I paid in advance for food drink
and entertainment she's not on the menu
you'll get your same as the others get
him a plate take mine it's still moving
[Music]
Carl get the glasses
you
looks like you got a problem I want to
swim is it to Yuma hurry up or get the
rifle
[Music]
like I said before ljubim how far is it
to human who fired a swimming too far to
walk even for you I just would like to
put you up for a while combinations will
be rough but comfortable get bad bad
dude that shitty and give you something
to slip into I knew it there's too much
of her to be dead right Frenchy you're
not even brown yet would you really
black and blue are you all right Mike
always baby glad to be here what's wrong
they want an uncle mr. cracker took the
boat he's probably juiced up he'll be
back when the bar closes you okay man
nice of you to ask shitty crackers gone
I'll have to put these people up for a
while you and coral can use her room and
rickard niall bunk on the veranda dr.
Ross and his wife can use mine could you
freshen up a little bit it should be
question of a lot all I I think you
wanna help well don't worry father it
would be all right excuse me mr. wicked
hey Hoople it looks like you got more
than you can handle no problems just
confusion my housekeeper will be out in
a moment with instant accommodations for
everybody hey how about another drink or
did we already use up our minimum you
know I can't change that who wants
change just give us all a blast we're
very easy to get along with I'm very
easy to get along with you ought to try
me sometime I had that in mind but it's
like starting a good book you just don't
want to put it down to your finish well
you can always cheat a little read the
ending first saves lots of time let's
take a little nap dear it's going to be
an arduous day who in the hell's tired
the fact mr. Hooper I think I'll look
your little sideshow over it's no place
to be exploring alone you're so right I
think I'll slip into my exploring suit
how about a drink I help yourself the
makings are right in the bar how about
you doc might relax you would you like
some coffee duck no just a tip leave me
alone
I really enjoyed your act you got a lot
of poise you move real well here that
malec that ought to be water raised was
worth that to me hundred bucks is this
guy for real shitty as real as that
c-note Frenchie yes this will buy some
nasty you better keep it you haven't
earned it yet anything you stomach
that's what you're gonna turn the
seconds me get by the spread so he's
trying to buy everything on it you
cracker right now probably
[Music]
[Applause]
ha
[Music]
Oh
you're supposed to drink out of those
things back write yourself a
prescription you're a doctor pills are a
lot easier I have a bad heart I suppose
it'll happen soon enough that's a bum
kicked out feeling sorry for yourself
I've been down that road do you have no
problem big for yourself doctor but your
woman she's all yours how do you claim
lost merchandise chicken lost and found
well I'm lost finally
[Music]
you
tonight's performance shula's lon you'd
paid much for that corny act no but it's
the only thing at the Quetico honey
you're not funny friendship not married
either but I still took my men one at a
time it's less carded that way you take
it any way you can get him like broken
down sailor Hallie or you'd be wearing
that bikini like a bow tie sailor for
the Kinlan baby now
[Music]
you
[Applause]
[Music]
what are you cooler so what you're doing
that means Colin I need a bad idea
Frenchy sorta reminds me when I was a
kid back in st. Louis you should do a
lot of skinny dipping down on the
Mississippi free and easy it's the only
way to swim trunks arter choke me off
but I guess you get in a lot of this
kind of action huh I mean maybe
you and Popeye over there spend a lot of
time here in the water on your days off
this waters real toasty I guess you had
something to do with that fangy you all
have visited looks Cloris I've seen a
little bit i'm still curious Susan doc
is missing something oh he ain't missing
a thing baby believe me she's just a big
blank hope she stays that way a 91
package would be a big surprise you got
you know Oh town a hundred dollars work
you ain't buying talent what are you
buying a minus spread look when i get
this place i want you to stick around
what for me you wouldn't have to run
yourself ragged jump into the just cook
nobody cooks seven it's a long supply
demand I spend I guess you know
Cleveland
[Applause]
can i buy just to
[Music]
[Applause]
father hi you doing swimming again i
thought i would do it now so i could
help you later never mind later there's
been enough swimming already the fund
our war nevermind i said enough's enough
okay hi hope you just take it off ya
can't make any false one such to be real
easy all they'll be to DQ jizz on this
plantation you've got the right idea mr.
hope oh yeah how's that this all brick
pity and raunchy and weather-beaten
while the room it's free hopefully in so
few problem ya heard that before really
all exactly that problem free cuz that's
your problem no external per aisle and i
think he's cute like an anteater pretty
kid see
are your batteries recharged I never
undone bad connection sometimes but
never a short circuit you see that you
must one you make one you're real good
at that ain't you're making things I
make everything but money but I'm moving
in that direction I'll be easy to find
just look for a suntan like oh
hello mr. Aiken you here under with
father we stuck to Russ he's asleep it's
time he woke up to a lot of things hey
hey
[Music]
I'm not gonna bite you father doesn't
like me wasting time oh no this is
business strictly business lemma to us
and your guide right so uh tell me all
about your paradise it's at home I know
that but I should forget bummed when I
see the big city thanks see you know
that big beautiful USA where everybody's
rich yelling pretty I'm very happy here
I find that pretty hard to believe but
I'm from Missouri so show me I don't
understand show me your paradise here
hmm show me what's so terrific listen
I'll make it worth your while business
strictly business
ok it's a deal that's good oh I better
tell dad I'm going with you Oh
surprising later I suppose there would
be okay oh yeah
[Music]
hey there and I'm helpless look doc I
come up with the cash my thought is get
the boat back back he'll be back when
he's tap city I've never been anywhere
where my money wouldn't help me you're
in the Colorado doc it's just like
monopoly when there's nothing to buy is
just colored paper and you turn it in at
the end of the game I want to thank you
for oh forget it forget it listen to
once you go back at the house and get my
trunks take yourself a swim you might
even catch a pearl I lost one sometime
ago
[Music]
just sometimes hidden I need not of
course we interrupt this musical program
for a special news flash Lawrence Talbot
the third of Newport Beach is still
unaccounted for our last contact was
based upon a rumor emanating from a
doorman on one of the Las Vegas Strip
hotels but the young heir to a 40
million dollar fortune was last seen in
but 40 million in Running of young lady
I wonder life station will keep its
listen closely advised that must be all
that long tall green he scares of your
musical interlude all right okay baby
let's see the other side hmmmm shaky up
baby 40 million lost in Marlboro country
feels so perfect for sale oh
[Music]
hey
ok
[Music]
let's call this gun something's wrong
I'll forget about it come on
here's your money back mr. Rickett torso
over that's what you think
you
[Music]
twenty-one-year-old Lawrence Talbot the
third of Newport Beach California and
sole heir to a 40 million dollar fortune
is classified by the police as a runaway
a spokesman for the family however
announced moments ago that Lawrence is
and we quote pleasure minded and the one
that's the kid Lawrence Talbot the third
oh my kid looks like we missed the boat
again honey
[Music]
[Applause]
hell did you come from you better climb
right back in that chris craft and fungi
they're shiny do I have to make you
you're not gonna make her whole it
Barney rickard dildo sergeant record
homicide 26 36 a loss I got a reason for
being here what's yours and your
thousand-dollar taste and the Lord dirty
road you been dragging me through you
are a thoroughbred you know you know
what just kind of fight y'all like I
never will Evelyn flutter around and she
makes it 200 feet for flaming see
Avoyelles now cooked and never move
again it's specially after you sir
[Music]
she do like to play with fire don't you
Oliza thought I can turn off shitty too
bad you can't turn anybody on I really
feel for that bod that's the problem
everybody feels hey Babette was the game
they'll be along well after the smell of
my cooking covers a long way yeah I keep
wondering why business steaks okay doc
I'll take a little chow not thank you
I'm still fighting that lunch
[Music]
we're gonna have one extra for lunch
let's feed him good I got a strange
feeling he might be a big tipper guess
we could use Carlin liquor what the
hell's she going with record you should
worry about yourself Papa Carl he's only
being a girl it's natural for her to be
with other men you have got a mind a
real gutter brain I only see what you
think suryun here are lousy it sounds we
have another guest father yeah we've
been expecting him how are you son had a
seat there he's hungry I never heard of
a singer this wasn't he must be a pretty
good one too we heard a description of
fell on the radio that you fit pretty
well Oh incidentally I'm doing opal and
Lawrence Calvin I couldn't be more
pleased it's some of it good kupil
chowder in you hold you together once
you get feza taste a fantastic oh I want
you to meet my housekeeper barbette to
say no to Larry Calvin hi have to know
your name oh you want to help Babette
there now tell me how did you happen to
stumble on hoople's haven this little
the most unique resorts in Arizona or in
fact the entire world cluster
I was I was trying to reach Lake my
teens by tonight when i happen upon your
daughter coral and she was on the beach
seeming to have some trouble with man on
the beach seven trying to force his
intentions on it trying to what so i
started my boat in it
[Music]
with my cooking it was never before I'm
just smelling it rich people it may be a
furniture food well late romance which
he just hadn't eaten period I think I'll
join that fun group on the beach looks
like they need every game for anything
would you like to be my heart not so
deep daddy sands are treacherous nothing
that I can't handle you know it's quite
a woman and all your yeah too much of a
woman all of the time you're surrounded
by beautiful women almost a herald your
own paradise your daughter I take a
chief your problem
what the hell are you trying to say
you're oversensitive about it
overprotective you remind me of me and
my wife better watch your own house doc
before it flows away to do unless you
try it back you could always write on
her shoulders
[Music]
I'd be very happy to be your horse
Amanda I ain't exactly built like a
jockey they loose don't get your people
stirrups baby the only thing I want to
catch my footings about a yachtie beauty
at handy with your support I won't even
have to push your sink
[Applause]
[Music]
you
[Applause]
save your breath honey and take his
pulse you know no Lily no I'm a nurse
did you think I can spot a dead man well
sure you can just the way you set him up
I suggest we buy in first your kicks on
your face of the dead and they kick back
I'll get doing it's a shallow grave mrs.
Roz she couldn't have your husband will
free internment your hometown I know
it's painful to discuss these things but
I have to contact the authorities in
human guise only down for an hour hardly
cold and he want to dig him up again I
didn't put him there he's no secret he
got a bad heart did you know he had a
heart condition mrs. rocks she knew his
bank balance why worry about his hawk I
wasn't on his shoulders and my phones in
his face either right that's enough it's
done where's the boy kalra duck said I
told them to take a walk ask me the next
time you're not an old lady
they'll be back soon doing you need that
boys boat what's the hush Kaka would be
back cracker may never be back police
have to be told the death arrangements
have been made to transport the body and
Undertaker all the little stinking
details that spell keeping everybody out
of trouble now I can take the boat as
far as picacho peak and go by overland
trail to Yuma hotter than hell but if I
travel by night I think i can make it
sounds to me like you make their an
awful lot of problems for yourself
Hoople how's that please they get kind
of funny about accidents good license to
serve liquor naked women running around
seem to know a lot about caps takes one
to know one he's buzzed local maybe now
listen don't be cute this is my Ranchero
here and get dumped it means a lot to me
nobody's taken away from me I police
doctors lawyers Indians her bagman there
just ain't enough money copper just what
the hell are you doing here buddy with a
hundred dollar bills and showing a lot
of muscle train up with a make on every
broad that walks by
maybe doing it all right that's a lot of
questions how about a few answers I'm
just waiting for a boat to you you got
it buddy today find the kids I'll go out
and check the boys boat for fuel
[Music]
and
okay come out of it now the curtains
down the audience is gone you are nasty
bastard just realistic I figure you the
same way go on you'll need it why are
you going to arrest me I could but I
figure you got an angle so vine what do
you mean well you got yours mate don't
even waste your breath day 9 and I was
there remember you Mouse you help me
you'd make a wonderful witness against
yourself sure we both go down the drain
but I wouldn't be throwing a million
bucks not quite no I got it good for you
what you gotta do in return is nothing
we're both out of here like big birds
what do you want me to do you got a hole
up for a while I got a bag full of
reasons and I don't want Hoople are that
kid going to you I don't want nobody
leaving your stiff either dead or alive
it causes attention so shoot amar you're
a cop no sir I want you working for me
like a woman on hopeful now maybe the
kid later I want you to be whatever they
want you to be sweetened hot cold
anything you have to do who do it to buy
me some time
viola yeah where do I start out dinner
with that kid on his boat I don't want
no motor racing you slow it down I
always find stop his
you
nobody illnesses that's wait a while you
don't know my father well I'm not sure I
do either I know mine too well that's
why I'm here I'm glad I ran out of gas
yes that's all it needs is gas how's
your motor working i'll have a lot
better than yours
put your money where your mouth is knock
it off will you any other time but now
it'd be great everybody's doing if you
don't somebody else will go find record
and do it
[Music]
Thank hell is your message anyway you
and me that's my message really came to
play I came to win I'll have to settle
for a time
you are expert I hope so practice makes
perfect / graphic yeah like an athlete
he practices so he'll be good for the
big game or in the case went after to
give his best performance in the plane I
don't play well wait you don't
understand
[Music]
you are with people one hundred percent
private eye huh you mean a big mistake
baby just like I thought break that
broads Joe with an axe
[Music]
coral baby walking around without any
clothes on how many times do I have to
tell you how many times wake up old fool
I'm not your dad I'm not even your
friend you call me sick you got a few
problems yourself face he's got more
than that hey you got the wrong broad
buddy your kids out there in the boonies
with the athlete yeah
she's out of you must be out of your
mind I'll leave a be coach let him have
some fun Wow Kyle injected large
[Music]
Carl
don't four next up more like a modern at
the Louisville don't you know the
difference
[Music]
Dewey going again oh that old donkeys
bag to each house an angle but I think I
got him shot that old man why who
promised there wouldn't be any case baby
we're all of a sudden your husband ain't
no accident you ain't gonna be one
leader
[Music]
or he's trying to blast cracker us
there's only a half a clip in that rifle
he's fired at all sure that vote one is
the beach I'll need some help I can use
to myself can't even scare with this
[Music]
here to tame out that way every now and
then fired them I bet some to pick up
baby it's a colt 45 a handgun nice to be
firing he can't hit a small range
she's covering for him one
[Music]
come on can we gotta help
Oh what the show you're all busted up
yes hello Boosh rubbing her tummy we can
replace that first we got to get you off
this now don't take me from this lady
duty she's all woman you never knew her
had a girlfriend the big guy a cop he's
got a million and hot rocks he stole him
from the state of Missouri the papers
are full of it everything from ice jobs
in the last 20 years people just didn't
claim you know Tim I don't care they're
crooked cop let me help you Reb I can I
think I can make it easy for you how I
Ernest is too easy I pay my tab
I made the trip let me be yeah you paid
in full now it's your turn record
stay with him sunday
[Music]
one second one second I'll blow her
brains out I won't feel a thing you kill
already what's gonna stop you're gonna
do it again that busted out drug find
some slot nobody's gonna make me for
that listen I won't do any more killing
I just want a chance to get out of here
that's not much of a guarantee well it's
all you got Hoople because you make one
move and I'll kill you kid you
understand gotta get some milk I'm gonna
kill her get easy that won't move it
blue light yellow bow don't waste any
time you too girly girl come on Dale Bay
get on there
[Music]
mission start hope you got me the start
by yourself
[Music]
don't you ever be stupid girly not if
you want to live
you're young you too you just get this
garbage scouting human power to give you
a great big present you're mine record
I'll trade you even up record me for her
but Rickon
we could please let her live let it come
to you with me huh because you don't
want me like tools come in threes it
brown Skippy's gonna call me decide
[Music]
Wow
what happened now they'd pretty but the
kids are okayed and boat clobber
brickers skull like a melon tractors
boat the sermon in city de safe it's a
nice day for it swimming to be alive and
swimming
two more funerals one with full military
honors what's with the kids fine he's
giving you mouth-to-mouth resuscitation
be nice to have another man around well
in a cellar at that
[Music]
40 million you know baby it looks
greener everything looks a lot greener
this is of course a fable but if ever a
crusty old man approaches you with an
offer of relief from the humdrum of
everyday life don't turn away from him
but instead lend him your ear you might
experience a most unusual day
[Music]