you
I'm tell me it's gonna be all right what
happened what was she doing in the
forest and you know I common their
clothes they think she's afraid of the
house that she jumped out of the window
to escape Nev do you hear your parents
are coming who's been caught looks like
a bite who did this to you was it the
dog me near I how does he go back
upstairs now she's covered in scratches
and bruises she must have father are the
dog
we did this to me did someone break your
ass why don't you jump you could have
killed yourself let's go okay let's go
upstairs mummys upset let's go
you
is that do you know
hi come in mogs need come downstairs
look who's here tonight it's like
something yes how are you not too shaken
up she looked so terrified that wound I
don't know what to think i'm gonna ask
advice from a fan and always a shrink
are you Nev are you feeling we came to
see how you are say hello Nev you've got
to exercise your tongue
are you all right two years is not long
enough I'm sorry we couldn't be there I
know Mary loved Henry he was her
favorite doctor
I just hope she soon cells into the
house a shelf fell down yesterday that
was my fault that didn't put it up
properly but she thinks things move and
the house creaks it's normal she's
forgotten what it's like living in the
country but if she doesn't settle then
we'll have to move even if it means
going back into time after only one
month in the high subpoena shyam but
still I'm we're gonna have to do her
bedroom up again let her choose
everything this time maybe she'll feel
better than and I've cooked the brunch
is done outside her window the casting
shadows over the wall we have to do that
to you for our kids they were scared
stiff by them and even went on for her
I'll we bought one of those this morning
she not miss living in tan if your
high-class patients I'm fed up with all
that besides a country is better for the
kids
ah that's enough me leave him alone how
many times don't you dammit I'm sorry
Navy is still very jealous of her
brother she doesn't mean to hurt him but
children don't always realize how
violent they can be he's still a little
tired sweetheart go upstairs and have a
rest and I'll come up and see you
that you okay yeah i just i have a swing
in my ears hmm it's okay it's gone
that's hurry up the kids are waiting on
us
shh don't be afraid everything's all
right trust us
can you give mommy a smile a goodnight
kiss
mommy daddy
Emily's who's this screaming hey what
are you doing bring your brother back to
your lock
Oh
fuck your brother
don't stare
ah
huh
to control two adults are still mr. Tate
you check around the back
there's something here Joseph need
his ribs are compressed to tighten for
too long you suffocated to death that
wasn't a smoke the cover protected she
was squeezing him so hard cuz she house
maybe but I think she would have the
strength she's saying as the house went
crazy poor girl I mean even if she
doesn't remember the attackers then
Frank you were here during the
investigation I'm not sure where exactly
I was going to take time to find her
foster him we can take her yes of course
horse I might take a while it would be
better for her to start back at school
at the start of time which doesn't fall
behind we can keep for as long as she
needs we have a spare room ok then just
the time being it'll help me out it's
very kind of you if there's anything you
noticed you let us know I better go I
didn't have her medical records I spray
the father looked after his remarks and
scarce she had a bad accident when she
lived here when she was little she was a
bit of a daredevil she mustn't have
changed last week she put her tongue
escaping her house last night was she
who she has abused anyway I'm not
allowed to tell you
she's had a shock so don't be surprised
if she's withdrawn difficult don't cry
in front of her
okay it's okay i'll be alright it's ok
Nev Nev
yeah be careful
I'm Tanya in the welfare officer from
school I'm here to help you
she's only here for the time it takes to
find the best possible solution for her
don't go overboard or get too attached
just singing for your sake
you okay
do you like your new room another girl I
know the girl used to live here but she
left well we can talk about that another
time did you try any of your new clothes
on do when I go and buy some more do you
won't have quick wash no okay well it
doesn't matter dinner will be ready in
about an hour if you want to go outside
for a breath of fresh air
what are you doing
nothing just something out the window do
you want a glass of water can't you
sleep I don't know
tell me if you're too hot or too cold or
you need to in our blankets if you're
frightened you can come in and sleep
with us or i can come in and sleep here
with you if you prefer okay good night
it was a long war they didn't fight like
we do nowadays look at those weapons
what do you call that long blade with
the handle see the soldier standing up
in the center of the picture don't worry
Neve you've only missed the first few
days you'll swim catch up
shush I haven't heard the bell yet it's
a sword a sword okay turn to the next
page
Oh
I thought it might be nice if we ate
lunch together from time to time just
the two of us what do you think I'm mad
about the other children are they nice I
don't know and is everything going okay
with NAT and Lucas and ranan Lucy do you
get on
are you still very sad that's normal do
you want to talk about your parents and
your brother not necessarily about what
happened we can talk about before narain
memories did I tell you about the day I
ate all the caviar my parents had put
aside for an important dinner do you
know what kuvira's
Oh leave you okay sweetheart is
something the matter tell me silly
aren't they when I'm finished with these
2 i'll give you a bath okay but not with
them so you're a big girl now this is
Lucas home yet that's enough you two
come on there you know Nev you really
must have a wash I've left towels and
soap in your room but you haven't
touched them it's been too long now
really can't go on like this I can't
I'll help you okay hey Beck's including
your eyes
Gnaeus what's going on this is I'm sorry
need this is ridiculous come on get up
stand up it's alright even you've done
oh you feel better afterwards you'll see
wanna turn around let me help you don't
be scared that's the way to do it
myself that damn sorry hey it's just a
draft just cows on the floor
everything's fine okay there's nothing
to be scared of trust me there's nothing
nothing whatsoever not even a lead I
know you spoke to Joseph today and
you've done at the police station he
came to school he wants to punish those
bad people who did all that nasty stuff
at your house so that's why he's
persevering you do understand and also
so doesn't happen again I've already
said it's the house
we can call your father sister later and
the one who lives in the state's you
like to see her speak to her it's my
belt one of the trouser loops is broken
and about Keith rising up ditches
someone had skill taught you or my
sister that you'd come back Ryan my dad
sister Mary you were friends when you
were little your daddy was her doctor
she had cancer thing 500 finish finish
finish finish you see please hey that's
enough if you're not back at the table
by the time I've counted to 10 you're
going straight to bed 12 not roller the
beer 34 I'll get some wine you loose you
come help me pick a bottle you're a
scared child you know I got you guys
know running we used to have another
little girl bow down she died
we didn't say anything because it
happened a long time ago that's all and
we didn't want to upset you
let's switch the light back on
did you knock it over it doesn't matter
don't cry
ah nothing
you okay you wrestle in here
leave me leave her alone okay I'll put
these two to bed and then I'll be right
back okay let's throw everything the way
that could harm anyone and we'll sort
out the rest tomorrow okay not this
impossible you seen what she's done it's
not the same for Ryan and Lucy they were
bumping into everything and scared they
art themselves but are why did she I
don't know Lucas can you think she got
scared by all the screaming and the
noises in the cellar maybe have reminded
her of that night I went into her room
just now and she was so scared as if I
whisking you've got to speak to tell you
straight away this is not normal kiss we
can't give up on her at the first
problem we encounter she is traumatized
we'll see tomorrow okay okay
diamond ring turns brass I'm just gonna
buy you a looking glass if that Looking
Glass gets broke
what the hell are you doing there
head out of here
are you coming inside with me help us
he's humble
what's going on
Oh
you
Nev Nev nice can you hear me
Jenny will pick the little ones up from
school don't worry about that Nev says
she hasn't seen Peter or Emily they've
disappeared I couldn't get anything out
of her it's just a coincidence i'm not
sure their fingerprints of several
children all over the house and Eve's
are amongst them it doesn't prove
anything she could have left them there
any time what what do you think nivas
done you think she murdered an entire
family nobody's saying that not but the
circumstances surrounding both murder
scenes are very similar and she ran away
from your house just when it was
happening so she can't even remember who
killed her parents I don't know that's
what she says but children are very
easily influenced and these people these
murderous maybe she knows them or maybe
she's listening to what they tell her I
just I don't know what the Ducas say
something maybe it's best just to keep
proud of the way for a while everyone
knows everyone's business around here
people are superstitious they're gonna
start imagining things no she must get
back to school as normal you must tell
people to stop talking rubbish and I'll
do the same she'll never get over this
if nobody helps her what about your
daughter she's the same age as Nev isn't
she and she has a birthday party next
week he should invite Nev it would suit
you to keep her cooped up here but Henry
helped your little girl when she was
tiny people protect themselves they
protect their kids that's all no one's
going to leave you in the lurch that
okay I'll come by tomorrow but I'm
asking you to do one thing keep an eye
on her she mustn't go out alone I sleep
by yourself can't find her wandering the
streets
you all right
yes
leave aren't you coming outside yes
it's
hey what's going on here come on French
it'll break it'll teach my you think so
open up yeah wait nice backpack you're
having your birthday party I want you to
invite her weekend okay Brian's gonna
check on me if she's in there on their
own okay she's got nobody and you've got
me and you've gotta do okay okay I go on
be good
knees shall we get back to the classroom
well then I'm having a birthday party on
Saturday you can come lie mobile explain
let's stay concentrated please
got to get out sit back down leave it'll
soon be break time and i'll come down to
you
knees come on come with me
what's the matter come on we'll have
someone to bring us to lunch trays
making it in the office is the two of us
okay are you okay
if it's me i'm i'm the one who does all
done i make objects move when I cry I
made I made them kill my parents Peter
and Emily's mother me what are you going
on about no one can do that it's not
your fault if bad things happen come on
let's go eat now is everything going in
that and lucas's are they nice to you to
keep talking to me hooking me smiling at
me and Dave you like smiles or a small
as kind isn't it oh you're right it
depends pretty can usually tell if
someone smile is kind or Gnostic on you
I heard you'd been invited to Ann's
birthday party on Saturday that's great
I bet you will have lots of fun I used
to have little parties when I was young
well I already told you about the one
with the big dog but there were others
man detective
hey you already know each other day I've
maybe you don't know that Matthew
Collins is my baby study
there are a lot of unanswered questions
here where she was assaulted that night
the first murders took place maybe by
that gang I'm wondering if it doesn't go
further back it's not her parents that I
used her that night and even before
she's could all the symptoms of an
abused child I capitan Emily's mother I
so strange coincidence try to think
about something else for a while for our
sakes and the babies I'll come and pick
you up after school okay I better get
going see you later
I was cool today I told us about Peter
and family I'm their mother they said we
must always stay together and tell
someone if we see a stranger we mustn't
throw in such a florist don't worry
sweetheart will be for too long yeah
yeah I'm not too many sweets today here
come on I'm gonna read you a story in
that it's bedtime story about murders
but think none sweetheart
did you like anything else I'm going to
my room to read yeah stop pushing me
away well now get on if you keep on
treating us like your enemy me of my
sweet little kitten you can read
downstairs with us I know it seems like
a nightmare but one day it could be
better you'll see trust us
for its knees please go to wiggle and
inducing it's just for tonight pretended
to sleep in your own wandering around
the constant site alone at night like
that is dangerous screaming meemies nice
stuff Eve I'm sorry I'm sorry sweetheart
I just wanted you to stop screaming and
come to bed I just want you to be a good
girl
panin are you doing not
she'll sleep in her room but I'll stay
with her it's just for one night can
block her window tomorrow
come on Eve
go to sleep please it's late
what the hell are you doing we give you
these I got them from the album
downstairs I like them what gives you
the right who do you think you are these
are ours they're not yours I'm from
Peggy the dog soon crazy she took those
she was playing with him did you go to
them I'll stay here Nev why would you
take these this is all ready to go and
marry one who got sick do you remember
why she showed into Lucas it hurts us we
loved her so much then why is she dead
wasn't our fault she was seriously ill
there was nothing we could do we loved
her and that had nothing to do with her
being you
try and get some sleep
area
Mary welcome me if the other children
are in the garden joined them yep she's
the prettiest doll in the shop do you
like her and love Stahli parties have
you heard of them before no I I want to
go home I don't want it um I can't go
home now sweetheart that wouldn't be
very nice for an anyway I'm sure you
play lots of other things and there'll
be cake and presents and I think claire
has even organized a treasure hunt I'll
be right here okay hello are you coming
to play okay have fun and be careful
stick give me a shout when you're hungry
disgusting music don't do it again sound
like they're having fun yeah that's a
good idea of yours so glad she came
mentally sick people
are you feeling okay do you want a glass
of coke can I see your doll she's lovely
I don't like the dress it's pink it
should be foolish on second thought
she's not very lovely is she bolted you
have to punish her planes crazy I have
to look at it and wake asleep and wake
asleep
it's not your ear again is a really must
seek wetland I'm sure it's night us I've
got a number I'll go get it free thank
you
come here haha
if don't
camera in the kitchen what are you doing
yes
yes I'm fine I'm out looking for her no
I want to be the one to find her but
they hurt
well they're talking a load of rubbish
well we left lit candles on the table
it's her own fault what do you think me
was actually capable of well what else
could it have been no I don't want to
call Lucas I want to find him myself
he's looking after the other two
who's there who is that me here fighting
me
oh don't be afraid all right what's
going on Nia please say something what
what did they do to you and your brother
befell me I've heard myself
look I've been here in much need of give
me my phone back
what's going on here knee what the hell
are you doing answer me answer me answer
me
gently don't be afraid let me
you're tired you're hungry but be good
children mommy and daddy are tired too
ah
you talk to the children now what they
said at school not just I have to be
punished they don't realize that it
seemed we do for them back then people
didn't used to get involved in education
nowadays everybody has their own opinion
you
are you giving me but my guess
ah
you