[Music]
hi guys glad we got your message you'll
be interested to hear whose broadcasts
live all over Earth primetime got good
reviews in the trades the time lag on
these messages is getting longer we
gather from the 10-year delay that you
are approximately 18 parsecs away drop
us a line more often okay
sorry to hear about the radiation leak
on the ship and real sorry to hear about
the death of commander Powell there was
a week of mourning here on earth the
flags were at half-mast we're all behind
you guys
about your request for radiation
shielding sorry to report this request
has been denied I hate to send bad news
when you guys are up there doing such a
swell job but I think you'll take it in
the proper spirit they've been some
cutbacks in Congress and right now
considering the distance we just can't
afford to send a cargo shuttle out there
to you but I know you guys will make
dude keep up the good work man
[Music]
what'd you say I said I'm trying to
reach shall be something wrong the damn
intercom I'd elastin a diameter of
approximation tubby tubby this is a
little sabi sabi you read me II shall be
oh oh yes to little what is it I need a
diameter approximation I need a ghf
reading on gravity correction chuck it I
have a bias a of +1 pinback got a little
your GI Jeff reading is minus 15 a
little girl I need a jittery on a fail
safe harbor in a second Pilar can you
set me up with some dr figures 97
million minus eight corrected your bass
critical that checks out here just drive
reading 7,000 i read that a quantum
increase on south pinback i have their
computer reading it's 95 77 timed stock
bombay systems operational
lock feel safe hail Satan lock uh
sergeant pinback calling bomb number 19
do you read me bomb bomb number 92
sergeant pinback I read you continue
well bomb we have about 60 seconds drop
just wondering if everything is all
right you check your platinum iridium
energy shielding energy shielding public
function well let's synchronize
detonation time uh you wouldn't have to
know when you're supposed to go off with
you County spindle six minutes 20
seconds all right then checks out here
armed self bomb well and everything
sounds fine dropped me off the bus for
35 seconds good luck in from everything
all right marquette ten nine eight seven
six five four three two one drop
hyperdrive sequence begun hit it pinback
racehorse
[Music]
lieutenant Doolittle it just exploded um
the planet just exploded sir lieutenant
attention attention ship's computer to
all personnel the hyperdrive sequence is
now terminated the target planet has
been destroyed well this sector is now
cleared for colonization you have
destroyed the last unstable planet in
this system congratulations on another
successful bomb run fellows what now
what do you have for us now boredom oh
not much nothing at all in this sector
don't find me something I don't care
where it is well I show ninety-five
percent probability of intelligent life
in the Horsehead Nebula sector don't
give me that kind of bull I know it's a
long shot but then wild-goose chase what
is number one commander Powell found
that 99 plus probability of intelligent
life in Atlanta clown how I there's
possibility than what we found a damn
mindless vegetable look like a limp
balloon 14 my ears for vegetable Owen
squawk little think when you touch you
remember that all right then don't give
me any and told you life stuff I me
something I can blow up
newstar hey guess what I got a star on
the readout which was another unknown a
red dwarf not on the charge any violence
yeah 8 it says here any of any good
Allstate Oh what are you gonna name it
what the new star what are you gonna
name it who cares don't bother me
commander Powell would have named it
commander Powell is dead a little I got
a goodie an unstable planet eighty-five
percent probability of an unstable
planet in the veil nebula they'll
probably go off its orbit hit a star one
blow it off real good boiler that's what
I'm looking for chart a course for the
veil nebula pinned back probably the
chatline let's have some music in here
boiler sure thing
[Music]
sunshine down dog has bigger ears move
faster than days how I miss those desert
skies
the same sardine described but they seen
so much time
you watch them you
in the sky but they seen so much
now the years pull us apart I'll young
and now you're old but you're still in
my heart
bring all towns and spaces or behind
where we spent our lessons on my mind
the same song in the sky but they seem
so much happier when we watch that you
ships log entry number 1943 Dark Star
cruising at light speeds through sector
theta 990 enroute to the veil nebula for
destruction of unstable flammable our
ETA is 17 hours ship's systems continue
to deteriorate oh yeah the short circuit
in the rear seat found which killed
commander Powell is still faulty the
storage because he's sitting next to
commander Powell cita continues to
bother pinback oh yeah storage area 9
self-destructed last week and destroyed
the ships entire supply of toilet paper
off
attention attention ship's computer
calling all personnel I must disengage
your recreational music repeat ship's
computer to all personnel this is an
emergency override all systems must
stand by an asteroid storm is
approaching the ship on collision course
this asteroid storm appears to be bound
together by an electromagnetic energy
vortex like the one we ran into two
years ago normally I wouldn't bother
your voice with this problem but as you
recall my defensive circuits for destroy
than that other storm therefore you have
35 seconds to manually activate all
defensive systems
cut the block
[Music]
computer to bomb number 20 returned to
the bomb bay immediately but I have
received the operation no signal it is a
malfunction this is not a barman we are
in a crisis situation return immediately
nevertheless i have received signal to
premiere for a crop emergency override
returned to the bay very well
[Music]
we're mad yeah attention attention
ship's computer to bridge there was a
malfunction aboard ship during the
asteroid storm I have not yet identified
the nature of the problem shall I
contact you when I find out what the
mental function is yeah let's get out of
here I remember the last time we're in
an asteroid storm I was down the food
locker getting a sandwich when I heard
the damn sleeping quarters blow up yeah
hey you know guys if we really wanted to
we could fix up the sleeping quarters
like they were before then we could
sleep on real pneumatic buffs again
check us why don't we fix up a sleeping
for this we can have a decent place to
sleep again all without dues patch up
the hole the ship pump some air back
shut up in back Oh having your own way
for your listening enjoyment we now
present the moonlight melodies of Martin
Segundo and the scintilla strings our
first selection is the perennial
favorite when Twilight falls on NGC 891
[Music]
how was the matter with him
shall be no missing breakfast
you know tally you really ought to eat
with the rest of us spend too much time
of you I like it up here must get lonely
being up here so much I don't like going
below since commander Palantine
filtering closed down there yeah you
should spend some more time below though
I mean you know you should see more of
the rest of the ship see I can watch
things up here to do a little I love to
watch things just stare at the planets
meteors gasps clusters an asteroid yeah
but you'll have plenty of time for that
later though I mean think of it this way
we've been in space for 20 years alright
we've only aged three years so there'll
be plenty of time later on for staring
around you know the little if we're
going into the veil nebula we may
actually find it strange and beautiful
thing the Phoenix asteroids they should
be passing through there about now
Phoenix asteroid never heard of them
there a body of asteroid that circle the
universe once every twelve point three
trillion years Phoenix asteroid from
what I've heard you little glow glow
with all the colors of the rainbow
nobody knows why they just glows they
drift around the universe Phoenix
asteroid you know what I think about
Toby
it's funnier I kind of sit around a lot
you know a lot of time to myself I can't
talk to the others but with time to
myself I can think about back home back
home in Malibu
I used to surf a lot i'll be used to be
a great surfer the waves at Malibu and
zoom are so fantastic in the spring
tabby I can remember running down on the
beach in those early spring mornings
with my surfboard in my wet suit the
waves are really be peaking you know
high and classy hit that water before
you know what you're coming down right
off one of those walls you just ride
pretty
you know i guess i missed the way is my
board more than anything
that's a little young
[Music]
goodness both have that out that's not
for target practice that's for
emergencies only
that's dangerous I'll tell Doolittle
sorry to interrupt your recreation
fellows but it is time for sergeant pin
back to feed the alien Oh laughs may I
remind you sergeant pinback that it was
your idea in the first place to bring
the alien on board if I may quote you
you said the ship needed the mascot oh
all right where are you come on quit
playing around yay
come come on but I brought you on the
ship I thought you were cute all right
soup's on we didn't have none of the
other stuff here eat it eat it take it
or leave it
[Applause]
[Music]
get back in there come on come on come
on dear boy watch your mouth nice mouth
predict how I watch your mouth here boy
[Music]
get out of there back there
[Applause]
[Music]
attention attention central trunk
elevator shaft is now activated all
personnel please clear the area
atencion atencion elevator descending
please clear the shaft
huh
[Music]
Oh
I'm getting something here in the
readout
ship's computer calling bomb number 20
you're out of the Bombay again I
received the signal to prepare for drop
again couldn't repeat this is not a bum
nevertheless i received the signal it is
an error oh I don't want to hear that I
strongly suggest you return to the
Bombay that was countered to my
programming allow me to explain one of
the communication lasers has sustained
damage this has temporarily inactivated
my damaged razors circuit you have
definitely received a phone signal
please return to the Bombay when I
identify the source of the problem oh
alright but this is the last night
doolittle I do have a malfunction on
this readout but I can't pinpoint it
exactly don't worry about it we'll find
out what it is when it goes bad I really
think we should try and locate it
immediately might be something important
you know i wish i had my board with me
right now even if I could just wax it
once in a while
[Music]
[Applause]
no I'm sorry this jela phone is out of
order please report the damage
for your listening enjoyment we now
present the barber of seville by Rossini
[Music]
[Applause]
yah we gotta pee gotta pee come up
you'll be good for you you've decided to
clean the elevator to clean and service
the electromagnetic coils in the bottom
it is necessary to jettison the access
plate on the floor to remove the floor
plate please press button number one
attention danger automatic charges will
now blow the explosive bolts in the
floor plate Union the plate will
disengage from the door in five seconds
please leave the elevator in meeting
till five four three two one
[Applause]
[Music]
now it's time to go sleepy-bye you
worthless piece of garbage
so that it is feared across the room
lined up alone I guess it was just
filled with gas hey guys how could it
live it was just filled with gas wonder
what we teach today I thought I was
gonna die I was hanging on the elevator
for 20 minutes rubber chicken I probably
save this yep that thing could have done
some damage huh really sing a chicken
well if you don't care I just won't talk
about it anymore that sounds like a fine
idea pinback chicken think we'll ever
find any real intelligent life out there
or where no bail nebula okay
[Music]
hey 73 you guys my villainous mission
there's a yeah the first ring see
conkers how long haven't an astronaut
begin with it Tyga he has for 700 on the
stres to the officer 458 they put me on
liquid fuel maintenance in the log pad
so ha naturally I was really difficult
oldest this uh you know four years ago
do yet anyway I was on duty that they
thought he was four years car I was out
scrubbing down the liquid fuel time I
said when this astronaut came running
out he was too stark naked and he starts
to these handsome oh I surmised that he
was insane and he 30 * sit on the ground
and jumped into one of my massive liquid
fuel which is very dangerous well I was
pretty shocked i can tell you i didn't
know what to make of it astronauts are
all supposed to be mentally stable and
here this guy comes along and jumps into
my fuel tank well actually I was going
to try to save it so what I did was put
on his sources for protection of finely
tuned to that you guys see so what
happened was that before I could leap
into the madness other guy King r-iowa
mrs. hey sergeant pinback you've got a
board immediately because we're in la
jolla Shanet for years and I tried to
tell him that I wasn't really starting
to come back but I couldn't figure out
how to make the helmet radio work yeah
sure years ago
[Music]
lieutenant Doolittle this is tabby
lieutenant oh yes Tommy what is it oh
I'm sorry to interrupt your lunch sir
but i'm in the computer room at located
the malfunction the scanner shows be a
break in the communications laser down
by the emergency airlock I can't
pinpoint it exactly but I'm going down
there with star suit see if I can find
it okay sounds good talk look something
for comes out let me know what's in
choppy entreat on you and restless just
light it up in the don't know what's
Tommy's birthday my first name
[Music]
you
the state news for posterity I just want
to say that I am NOT sergeant pinback my
real name is Bill Farook and I'm a fuel
maintenance technician I've been on this
mission now for one year and three
months ten backs uniforms do not fit me
the underwear is too loose I do not
belong on this mission I want to return
to Earth back commander Powell died
today we were going into hyperdrive and
well he sits right next to me well
someone wrong with you when we came out
of hyperdrive his seat mechanism blown
up he's dead well do little says that
he's assuming command of this ship and I
say that I say is exceeding his
authority because I'm the only one with
any objectivity on the chef and I should
be the one to assume command I'm filing
a report on its headquarters is like I
will have to do little to haul today I
said a little Easter
it didn't get this mission to follow the
parts as commander Powell died who
little treats me like an idiot Alby so
smart and boiler punches me in the arm
when no one is looking I'm tired of
being treated like an old war track
[Music]
I do not like the men on the spaceship
they are uncool and failed to appreciate
my better qualities I have something of
value to contribute to this mission if
they would only recognize it today over
lunch I tried to improve morale and
build a sense of camaraderie among the
men by holding a humorous round robin
discussion of the early days of the
mission my over tues were brutally
rejected these men do not want a happy
ship they are deeply sick and try to
compensate by making me feel miserable
last week was my birthday nobody even
said happy birthday to me some day this
tape will be played in the Nephi sorry
attention attention I have finally
identified the malfunction
communications laser number 17 has been
damaged this evidently happened during
the asteroid storm if you will recall
this laser monitors the jettisoned
primer on the bomb drop mechanism
communications laser number 17 is
located in the emergency airlock it is
crucial to attend to this malfunction
before engaging primary fauna and
sequence thank you for serving all
safety precautions
[Music]
here she is seven ninety-nine percent
plus probability that the planet will
deviate from her normal orbit and
another twelve thousand rotation it'll
spiral in towards the sign eventual
supernova sounds good let's vaporize
Bombay system operator
[Music]
fuck Kelsey they'll say can lock we have
eight ministers will rock 24 minutes
with that nation this is sergeant in
back hauling bomb number 20 you read me
bomb bomb number 22 sergeant pinback
Roger I read you continue you are now in
the emergency airlock please remember
that in an emergency situation the
service door can be opened instantly
without prior depressurization so be
sure to wear your star suit at all times
thank you for observing all safety
precautions
[Music]
oh can it do little dirt shall we don't
bother me but I think that's important
sir I think I found the Malcolm I'm in
the emergency airlock not now well I
miss Burton hair long and happy for
Minister da bomb have you checked your
platinum iridium energy field energy
shielding positive function remember
that next time definition in 20 minutes
all right that checks out here ok bomb
arm yourself the armed hello lieutenant
Doolittle hello hello can you read me
communications laser number 17
monitoring the bomb drop mechanism has
now been activated and we'll switch into
a test mode if you will look near the
surface door you will see that the
parallax receptor cell has been engaged
laser will now energize please stand
clear of the pad of the beans
communications laser number 17 is now on
test under no circumstances enter the
path of the beans thank you for
observing all safety precautions well
then everything sounds fine dropping you
off in 75 seconds good luck Thanks I got
a quantum reading of 35 or 35 er I read
the same here you little
cool little
I don't know if you can hear me but I'm
gonna try to adjust the queue switch in
the laser
well
here goes
[Music]
attention attention the laser has
malfunctioned under no circumstances
enter the path of the beams to do so
will Cozumel begin primary sequence mark
at ten nine eight seven six five four
three two one drop negative drum just
sitting there the Bombay try to get me
back mark at five four three two one
drop
[Music]
I then remarked marquette five four
three two one drop damping Justin this
is lieutenant doodle calling bomb number
20 I repeat my previous order you are to
disarm yourself and return to the bomb
bay immediately do you understand I am
programmed to detonate in 14 minutes 30
seconds that nation will occur at the
program target mom this is too little
you are not to detonate repeat you are
not to detonate the bomb bay disarm
yourself this is an order I read you
lieutenant Doolittle that I am
programmed to detonate in 14 minutes
destination will occur at the program
time 14 miss detonation attention
attention I have sustained serious
damage please pay close attention the
bomb has malfunctioned I have activated
automatic dampers which will confine the
explosion to an area one mile in
diameter this is all I can do at this
time it's up to you now
it's only one thing I can do after I
have to ask commander Powell have to ask
him what to do
[Music]
commander Paul commander Powell this is
Doolittle can you hear me commander Paul
this is doodle I'm something serious has
come up i have to ask you a question i'm
glad you've come to talk with me do it
it's been so long since anyone has come
to talk with me commander sir we have a
big problem the bail nebula bomb bomb
number 20 it's a it's stuck yet it won't
drop out of the Bombay it refuses to
listen and it plans on detonating in
less than 11 minutes you must tell me
one thing what that's her tell me too
little how are the Dodgers do what well
the Dodgers are they they broke up they
disbanded over 15 years ago Eddie pity
you don't understand sir we can't get
the farm to drop so many malfunctioned
why don't you have anything nice to tell
me when you activate oh did you try
asmith yes sir negative effect what was
that a negative effect it didn't work
that's correct sir sorry beautiful I
forgotten so much since I've been in
here so much what should we do sir time
is running out well but you learn
commander hello come in commander Powell
oh sorry sir you faded out there for a
little while son what was that you were
saying about the bomb uh it seems to me
sorry i've gone black hold it I'll
happen again in just a minute I forget
so many things in here so many things
hold on just a minute let me think you
can explode the bomb bank comes foolish
he'll kill us all there's no reason for
it I am programmed to detonate in nine
minutes destination will occur at the
program time when you consider another
course of action for example he's
waiting around a while so we could
disarm you know I can tell that damn
thing just doesn't understand look Bob
mandes are you still there oh yes we're
running at a time sir oh yes welcome if
you can't get it to drop you'll have to
talk to it sir Oh to the bar I have been
talking to it sir and pinbacks talking
to her right now no no little you talk
to it Egypt phenomenology too little sir
phenomenology do level six minutes of
that nation Doolittle
little good what the hell are you doing
right
breach hello Bob are you with me of
course are you willing to entertain a
few concepts I am always receptive to
suggestions mine think about this then
how do you know you exist hell is he
doing I think he's talking to it well of
course I exist but how do you know you
exist it is intuitively obvious
intuition is no proof what concrete
evidence do you have that you exist hmm
well I think therefore I am that's good
that's very good but how do you know
that anything else exists my sensory
apparatus reveals it to me ah hi this is
fun now listen listen here's the big
question how do you know that the
evidence your sensory apparatus reveals
to you is correct the guy God God the
support pins on the bomb shoot the pins
out don't worry Your Honor you stop the
bar Oh get out of my way we don't you
just put this out of the bottle holy
shit get out of the way or make a cake
don't do it whether you're a bad shot go
hit the box a little stock to the bomb
you're a bad job you'll save it you
can't do it what I'm getting at is this
the only experience that is directly
available to you is your sensory data
and this sensory data is merely a stream
of electrical impulses that stimulates
your computing center in other words all
that I really know about the outside
world is related to me through my
electrical connections exactly why that
would mean that i really don't know what
the outside universe is like at all for
certain that's it that's it intriguing i
wish i had more time to discuss this
matter what ojo more done because i must
detonate in 75 seconds now put it back
let's put the gun back in and what
you're doing
now give me the gun you can pull I'm
gonna shoot depends out of the farmer
too far away for shipping will be safe
why not give me the gun you don't know
what you're doing here you could have
killed me mm no bomb consider this next
question very carefully what is your one
purpose in life to explode of course you
can only do it once right that is
correct you wouldn't want to explode on
the basis of false data with you of
course not well then you've already
admitted that you have no real proof of
the existence of the outside universe
yes well where you have no absolute
proof that sergeant feedback what did
you get me I recall distinctly the
detonation order my memory is good on
matters like these of course you
remember it but but all you're
remembering is merely a series of
sensory impulses which you now realize
have no real definite connection with
without my reality true but since this
is so i have no proof that you are
really telling me all this that's all
beside the point I mean the concept is
valid amount of where it originates hmm
so if you detonate in 9 seconds you'll
cut me doing so on the base of the
fourth down I have no proof it was false
dad and I have no booty was direct data
I must think on this further
[Music]
and
attention attention the bomb has
returned to the Bombay the destruction
sequence is aborted
[Music]
too little what happened pinback toilet
did we blow it up hello hello hello
anybody can we blow up the planet hello
hello what's going on you know we've
really got it disarm the bomb hello
Doolittle are you there I'm coming in
now I'm down by the emergency airlock
too much trouble to come in the dorsal
lot would you blow the seal on the
emergency hatch so I can come in oh here
you are now leaving the emergency
airlock thank you for observing all
safety precautions Oh pinback what's up
Dolittle Toby was in the airlock he flew
him out of the ship he's drifting away
without his jetpack I'm going after him
turn on his helmet radio so I can
contact what what's wrong I hear tell me
he's drifting wedding the shift on his
jet pack kabhi kabhi can you read me you
beat that I always knew that guy was
weird Toby can you read me
alright bomb fair to receive new orders
you are false data mm-hmm therefore I
shall ignore you hello bomb false data
connect only as a distraction therefore
I shall refuse to proceed a bomb the
only thing which exists is myself Oh
calm down I'm coming snap out of it bomb
in the beginning there was darkness and
the darkness was without form and void
uh really hell is he talking Bob and in
addition to the darkness there was also
me and I moved upon the face of the
darkness and I saw that I was alone hey
mom let there be light
[Music]
bullion opposite direction away from
each other what happened to live upon
mr. going off inside the ship the ship
blow up what funny I thought I had the
same thing convinced that boiler and
pinback fit that shelving and we're dead
too maybe not maybe there's a way hey
hey my chest my jet packs busted oh hey
it looks like the skipper he made it
commander Paul he made it what happened
yeah the skipper always was lucky he'll
be looks like i'm headed for the planet
i'm going right toward it when you hit
the atmosphere you'll talk to her what a
beautiful way to die that's a falling
star yes you're right
too little i'm headed right towards
something it's behind me in the distance
something that close to little I think
it's a Phoenix asteroid Felix it is too
little it's the Phoenix Mercury I'm
going into them I'm going to hit them
too little yeah before we get too far
apart and our signals start fading I
just wanted to tell you you are my
favorite I really liked you too little I
really liked you too Toby hey some
debris from the ship it's coming right
by me I'm talking to them I began to
glow they're taking me with with the
Phoenix gonna circle the universe
forever
before it's too late
copy
hey Cal be I've got a piece of debris I
think I've figured out a way
[Music]
Bessie
the saints are in the sky but they seem
so much
[Music]