yeah
it's gonna be a
fire defenders of space ready for
revenge
I said on ruling the galaxy
traitor
no no no
let me come yet dime box
supers areas and super scorpio are
easily able to crush the small force on
the planet Aurora then your movie net
yeah
it's up there
Henry and marriage unlock this secret of
the Phoenix the only thing left that can
save them from destruction
the face
don't let me now i'm fine never loses
defenders of space
the saga of the fingers of space is
coming soon
and the right Henry
yeah
father there's no more
mmm
the City of Aurora will very soon be
part of my kingdom your majesty
I have always been your loyal servant I
proved myself before
give me the job Your Majesty I feel I'm
the best qualified for the job
you both have been loyal and faithful
servants general saga
you will take super service general mike
you can be the one to take super scorpio
of the two of you he who performs most
valiantly will marry my daughter Medusa
and inherit my wealth and Kingdom
embolus long live your majesty
see
our last three invasions of the Royal
were not successful but this time we
will not fail
no but that night look at the weight are
all around us
an invasion just delivering them are we
must quickly collar defense true
our soldiers we must keep attacking at
all costs
we can't give general make a chance to
win the hall
general saw is an incompetent fool we
cannot give him the chance to win
we must be the ones to conquer everyone
to their battle station
prepare to attack and fire the missiles
now
sir the enemy is attacking
what do you mean the enemy is attacking
are you certain courses on red alert
take cover immediately
yeah
stop it where did you learn that move
you should learn to catch with your mid
you just need a little confidence in
yourself
get ready now
yeah
I
ok quick all right sort of home plate
throwing slide
yeah
just because I'm a girl these guys made
me the stupid coach
hey you idiot what did you do like I can
you catch you guys follow instructions
I get you better not be my clothes away
from here real baseball girls know about
baseball stop making such a fuss so
we'll have you picking up balls in the
outfield
what what did you say you don't be a
bitch
thanks a lot some kind of friends you
are
I shouldn't have come with you guys in
the first place
Nicholas it looks like a bird
look how it shines in the
yeah
hold on you've done a good job on
Chuck's been hard to get time to play
I just got warmed up look at Dom looking
at bump on the head looks like an apple
you guys don't tease me
yeah
see you again next year
by travelpod member
computer operating room everything is
normal to my house until we arrive at
the civilized domain
hey Tom don't you do that what's the big
deal
why can't I see them because i'm giving
it to him me
that's why Henry what is so special
three
she won't let me see stones she says
it's for you
I got them for Henry I don't care
I want to see them i'll hit you you
should be stopped yelling and fasten
your seat belt
this is unusual it looks as if something
is approaching us at high speed
yeah
that was a cosmic magnetic storm in my
clinic must have explosion
Robbie and former are immediately we
must find out what happened
our base this is robbie about over we
are waiting on first
like the city destroyed destroy our are
destroyed
that's impossible it couldn't be their
God
everyone must have been destroyed this
can't be happening to us
will the only ones left I'm you had our
family but when we do now
yeah
nothing could have survived that
everything on the planet must have been
totally obliterated
yeah
is anybody
there can anybody hear me
yeah
oh my god
Henry was left of my home
I know Mary it's the same for all of us
I'm afraid we are on loan every mouth
you're dead behind your family too
yeah
huh what's that over there
what is that thing
uh-huh is that a man or machine
I can't tell for sure what should we do
should we leave it or take it back
we had better play it safe
let's go over and check it out yeah I'd
love to take backup prisoner
he should be in this area
dr hon can you hear me he should be here
somewhere
hold it don't move what are you doing
I'm looking for my father
I know he's here somewhere what your
father robots don't have fathers who do
you think your father is
answer me he doesn't know who his father
is no you wanna know who he is he is the
great scientist at that point then you
are human your little ass girls don't
move
damn still
you're as good as dead
me the gun lobby what do we do don't
worry Mary
I have an idea I think we can make good
use of this rocks
you guys have had it now I'll be back
yeah
all right it looks like a multiplied
with glass inside it
I can't see anything inside but i think
if i break the glass there might be
water inside it was to drink no water
nothing inside that all pain
for what
hey so you have made it back of your
mind somehow these a doctor honey - yes
yes he loved my son did you have fun
here
did you enjoy your trip to play baseball
on Mars a while you were gone
our planet has suffered a devastating
attack by NYX properties are humans on
the planet was destroyed by the enemy
they didn't even have a chance to hide
themselves his time
luckily i was here in my lab at a time
but there still may be hope
I believe there is an undying birthday
Phoenix King that lives on this planet
hear you say this Phoenix King is a kind
of bird right and i believe it is only
one that can save us all right then
doctor
I guess we better get out there and find
it sure we have to find it before Nick
finds our hideout
be careful they are searching for us
already
watching still some enemy gorillas why
is this so you told me before the
mission was successful and all humans
were destroyed
I'm sorry Your Majesty but some of them
escaped and they are still hiding
underground know where they have gone
why do you not think of a way to get rid
of them
general mike has filled you but I will
do the job done
good you can finish this task policy
general saga
you will be in charge of this mission
there must be no one left alive
yes your majesty your every wish is my
command
it's here somewhere
and then on the screen good idea
that's good now bomb it ok
that's not even up and running again
deeper this time we can't leave them
any chance of survival well as deep as
you can
must get rid of those best completely
destroyed
oh my goodness look there the next time
they are getting much too close for
comfort
we must do something this whole cave
could collapse any minute
then what will be killed her my goodness
dr. you said we must find his Phoenix
boat to help us right
so quickly you must tell us how to find
it nearly you're right but there's one
problem we must sound before the Phoenix
can help pass the problem you mean an
exercise that's all there is to it
newest autumn leave it to me I was the
very best in my math class
no matter how tough i can solve it
please doctor how do you can get the
problem to me
I know that I'll be able to figure it
out easily
all now they know but it is not the kind
of a problem you know I know what
no 1 x 1 equals 1 to x 2 equals four
three times three equals nine ER Mary
Mary but i tell you it is not the kind
of a problem
huh I'd ever seen anything like this
before
hmm
huh we'd better check this object
happens in mega system computer
yeah
goodness that's the language of the
Phoenix bourbon
this could be the key to our problems
the secret of the Phoenix King but where
is the Phoenix King with a terrorist
where we can find it hope
according to the legend it says here the
Phoenix sleeps on top as a great red
rock mountain where the morning sun rays
first type is a cool lemme go doctor
let me try to find the penis hanging
right I don't want to have the key I
shall have to go as well
ok hey what about me to go to
haha take that you scum that should
finish them off
yeah
Henry it is that fit that was really
close
thanks you'd better return underground
this is not a time for playing around
here
I'm sorry we have to get back to us
right away
come on Mary
hey I told you to go underground
stop that nonsense and come back here
right now
I don't get you little brat up good but
you're doing there
those kids on our side you know I'm
sorry doctor but those kids are really i
were doing at this time they are not
overdoing it
they are only hope they pick our city
arrived depends on them
what in city or aura I am the guerrilla
leader
I am the only one left who can
reorganize the resistance and get rid of
Nicholas me and my men of the only hope
remaining on this planet
you'll see a doctor you'll see
Wow dr. what a brave man he is
yes but he can't be too thick because
many men
come we must get back inside they will
be coming back soon come
all right let's go all right
what do you mean your men were attacked
by the gorillaz huh
why are you so silent general saga it's
true
I'm so ashamed I thought you said you
would destroy them general saga some
general you are you should be ashamed of
yourself
what do you have to say about that
general sagas Army has lost to two
midgets spaceship gorillas only 22 his
whole army
what you lost two spaceships
you have failed you yet
stop the deuce off we might still need
him because of his past loyalty or give
him one starter see what my can do
haha I don't like you you are a failure
Your Majesty please give me the chance
to prove myself
I can dispose of the rebels much better
than this worthless wimp
general mike is trust with it okay Mike
your commander of the operation
now I hope you can get back with general
song i have lost
thank you your majesty
this time I will not fail I must
complete my mission I can never let my
master manner and their interrupt what
the strange ship is leaving planted
Aurora sir
what did you say I thought all the space
ships were destroyed
it seems to be coming from somewhere
else General Mike
perhaps this could be my chance to see
where they are
keep watching them do not lose sight of
that ship
few days for engines ok all operations
of smooth
the check is done we can start right
away
yeah
they're going towards the planet Earth
make sure everything is ready is super
serious prepared for launch
super serious action
faster parm it now the spaceship is a
fast one sir
it will take some more time don't waste
any time or they could get away from us
we had better use the rocket fire are
serious rocket and that will be an easy
victory for us
the rocket is launched five minutes
until impact
yes very good owners areas to return
will have destroyed the gorilla soon
Henry tape
coming towards us rocket speed is twice
as fast as thousands gonna hit as any
minute
I can only try my best keep your fingers
crossed
yeah
it's only a hundred meters away it's
gonna hit me spoken
anyone going
what
you did it
yeah
writer it should soon be sunrise
wow you're so beautiful
yeah
hey no summed rising
it's here -
Wow
that's the great Eagle Mountain
wow it's really beautiful the whole
mountain is going red in the Rising Sun
Wow
any better k let's go in
yeah
everyone here so we careful
I guess this must be the way
come on hello
yeah
out of one eye open
are you okay that's just a piece of rock
it must have fallen from above
nothing to be scared of
yeah
I thought you're done
never see you again now you're not by my
side I have courage together I know we
can make it
I think the mark on the rug has
something to do with my letters
maybe it's a key it's see Phoenix never
dying bird
phoenix
yeah
quickly give it to me give it to me
- wait
yeah
maybe we got a volcano my mistake
it's Phoenix it stinks king
the Phoenix can have the laser cannon on
his shoulder
maybe we can get him to use it to save
the city or
candy
yeah
we are sure gonna teach nickel lesson
try again Phoenix purge
wow that's really great now we've got to
get back to raw
let's get into it and take off
yeah
take off Phoenix King
what is that look at the size of it
ok
we'll teach those jerks a lesson we got
two spaceships today
sides the robot let him try this one on
for size
yeah
is invincible that grenade didn't name
for the Maracana right but right now
yeah
I finally got them on the run
no more of your minutes bread you're in
my hands now
don't leave a single one of them kill
all of them
absolutely nothing behind
yeah
my finally meet the guerrilla leader
bread bread your face now you're gonna
learn your lesson
huh
yeah look at that it's falling apart
its mother
yeah
next god of the Phoenix key
not so fast when super scorpio gets up
you rolling have a chance
get up super scorpio attack the Phoenix
King now
ok
hey what happened to super Scorpio get
up you stupid thing
have you pile of junk to feed the
Phoenix game you must kill him
you must kill him for him up shoot him
doing anything
yeah
invincible there's nothing that can stop
him now
yeah
where we went to be the car run away
Bobby are you HOT it's all over now
monster
I was scared to death that's okay it's
no big deal no big deal
don't worry if you die I can fix us
Curtis no I have all the parts in my
life you know Nick thanks
yeah
Henry I hope you will forgive me for
trying to stop you
I was wrong i'm sorry forget it if we
work together with Phoenix King we can
rid ourselves of had evil make thanks
let's get rid of these invaders and then
we can rebuild our city or
yeah
and
heated by Phoenix King and then you
right away just to save yourself
you coward I won't forgive you General
Sir got killed him
yeah
Your Majesty I have killed the trader he
was not fit to be a general of the great
Nicholas Empire
I can defeat the Phoenix King Your
Majesty if I can't beat the Phoenix and
return
you may give me the same punishment i
will succeed I will trust you this time
general soccer but this will be your
only chance
long live your majesty nicholas
i will teach them are super service with
the iron ball super scorpio with the
Thunder axe
Janice scorpio attack together
Serpas arias chen super Scorpio
under the Phoenix King is approaching
poor fool he has come to die soon as
eric lewis carpio attack at the same
time from opposite sides
from Phoenix came just do your best
so now attack it on ships ships what
ships
where could they be coming from who is
approaching us defense group approaching
sir
this defense true heart leave them for
Nikki Medusa
let's take care of Phoenix King first
those areas coast copy Oh
s defense force approaching there will
be within firing range stones up
good now we just have tough they really
are saying only chips at once
commander the enemy fleet is approaching
they're going to attack us
fire on them first before they get any
closer prepare to fire
yeah
explosives are too much for us we can't
take much more
the troops are too big we're no match
for man
amanda is there anything else that we
can do I don't know
we've done everything we possibly do you
think you can beat me with that
destroyed them all and when General saga
takes Phoenix King he will attack the
earth
yeah
virus and Scorpio retreat get out of
there quickly and get back to the base
escape don't even get away we must
destroy them completely
keep firing we are succeeding
soon we will have destroyed its whole
army we are heading right into our trap
the further they come the more precious
fuel they use up
oh hi lo stato saga has returned a good
general saga is back i will tell you to
use super serious super scorpio and
destroy the air
sending my no oil service general saga
general congratulate what happened to
you soon as arias super scopia we can
feed him
Phoenix team is just too strong for us
wait I can explain everything
failure
we don't need your kind got all the
spaceships and attack Phoenix King
thirsty friends truth is being attacked
by NYX forces Phoenix King we must save
them
open fire
yeah
you know what those are spaceships
this is impossible we have no way to
fight back against the Phoenix King we
must retreat before we lose everything
now would be closed the door and turn on
the laser proof force field quickly
now
no explosives can penetrate our shield
so they cannot Thomas
stand by to launch our final attack
against the evil enemy
can be very well prepared we should talk
about the base centum
doing anything why should we do now hold
on
it's time for the Phoenix secret weapon
don't know what's happened here what
yeah
what's going on here but the force field
it is just blow up
humanism
everything is gone nothing is left to
all he's got
how can this be this base to be sensible
I am sorry we tried out based on
this is it the secret weapon will only
last one more shot
yeah
oh no next basis exploded and it's
setting fire to everything quickly
Phoenix King we must put out the fire
before it spreads
the Phoenix King now he turned into a
fire engine
look at him go let's go see a bigger
head is in my er um I'm not be left
behind now I could you please tell me
into a my engine
I want to help right there you're giving
me i hate he can't spend it
maybe I just pick your heart and make
other might be a part of you
this is the best way to free the robots
when they're not be at
well Henry with your help we were able
to correct our legal immigrant problem
Thank You commander I've heard that
Earth Defense Department is helping to
rebuild the city or are we can't thank
you enough
we'll try to make the city or or even
better than before and with your help
I'm sure we can do it
thank you thank you after we defeated
even exempt are we should all put down
our arms and live in peace huh
it wouldn't matter even if there were
another attack
that's Phoenix King would protect us
again
oh where is heat has he disappeared I
can't see him anywhere
don't worry dr hon he's still here with
us and your guard us forever
come out Phoenix King come on