[Music]
so
from people claim if seen ghosts of
soldiers in the battlefields around here
absolutely swear to how can you write a
book about ghosts of the American
Revolution when you are total
non-believer another token unbeliever
right I look forward being proven to lay
my plan to find verifiable estimation
for all things ghostly and ghoulish
here it is beautiful downtown ringwood
mall and i remember i'm dragging me away
after you marry thanks to be half you're
coming back so you think a new york city
girl like you can hack it look at
you're slow down I'll give another
excuse me are you the owner oh no my end
now she's the one selling can we make an
appointment to look at come on man I'll
show it to you hi im bored asheboro nice
to meet you listen Erin my daughter
Natalie hey you new to ringwood oh my
wife used to live here it's a nice town
what a beautiful cat
that's Margaret Lance baby
seriously
[Music]
under this road rage
hi mrs. asheboro what was that maniac
doing here oh I guess is good head right
for you don't take no for an answer
don't give in to him Brenda you'll build
those abominable cookie cutter houses in
your lovely field oh look I got your
present thank you I'm gonna do my
favorite guys you know what this is my
favorite boys if I had to sell this
place I'd never forgive myself whatever
the animals well then don't oh sure were
that simple things in the rest right now
Oh taxes have gone up supplies more
expensive dr. Melton used to volunteer
his services within you that charge is
almost full raked and at the top of that
right who's causing the pants again
Briker what he's bad-mouthing me all
over town so donations are down I
honestly think that's why the bank is
being so difficult what Brenda huh you
can tell me I'm a high-end mortgage
they're not happy that's just what Riker
needs to hear is it men vision new
furnace last year new roof three years
before that Lance lived her whole life
such a beautiful nature
oh I wouldn't better if I were you she
does like strangers bites and in 15
years of age it's a bad habit she isn't
about to lose Margaret say my aunt's
life once her really yep oh girl took a
nap left the stove on dish towel caught
fire Margaret woke her up whole place
would have gone up like a tinderbox
smart cat aren't you yeah that's why man
has to sell I was just getting on should
be safe for living with me or in a home
oh I should show you the cellar sure
there's no way you're going to be
bullied into selling I'm going to help
you've already helped no I mean it I I I
have a little bit put aside no I
absolutely Reza where would I be if you
hadn't found Margaret for me come here
Margaret
Oh
Margaret come home Margaret oh how are
you I'm Natalie uh my dad he's he's
looking at your house uh with your
nephew avoid he's not so I think they're
in the cellar mark great doesn't usually
respond to strangers have we met before
I don't think so well your face is very
familiar to me she's a lowly cat
Margaret is as loyal and loving an
animal issue could ever want she she
really seems to have taken to you that's
for sure you're one of the chosen few
Ruth I didn't hear you come in this is
West Marin I am just giving the tour
it's a beautiful house mrs. Burrell well
I hate to disappoint you but I am not
selling I'm sorry my dear i hope you
find a nice place and when you do
perhaps you'll come to visit us come
along Margaret let's go and have our
lunch
[Music]
she could be eccentric not to worry call
me if you decide you want the house look
Boyd I wouldn't seriously and if you
want a mortgage I can handle it my card
thanks but I wouldn't dream of flying
the house on familiar ground just a sell
call me anytime thank you can you
imagine how to sell the house you live
your whole life hey aren't you friendly
[Music]
don't you understand you have to sell
why because you're gonna move in with me
it's the right thing you wouldn't have
anything to worry about all right I'm
supposed to sell my house hand over the
money to you and go and sit in your
house and not worry about a thing sounds
peachy why are you so adamant about me
selling why is this come up all of a
sudden rubix thing I know you'll be
carting me off to some old folks home
look you can't live on your yes I can
and if I can I'll get someone to live
with me don't hire someone you don't
have the money to do that oh yes I do I
have something tucked away for a rainy
day but it isn't raining yet what money
you shouldn't have money lying around he
isn't lying around it's really none of
your business void I was just trying to
help Aunt Ruth I don't need your help
why don't you help someone who does like
Brenda excuse me oh she's got mortgage
troubles go back to that office of yours
and use your influence well maybe I can
do something about that after i take
care of this whole situation don't you
think that you've caused enough trouble
for one day and I don't appreciate
coming home and finding a for sale sign
on my house I won't have it fine fine
it's all about money always is with boy
[Music]
how can you get so upset about a house
when there's so many more important
things in life hey Jan Brenda pretty
cold out huh radio said we're due for
more snow yeah she feels like it listen
I hate to bug you but I've got a
complaint to hear from Walter wine dog I
was on the phone half the morning with
him one dog got out and I have no idea
how I had a complaint last week as well
I know it won't happen again you better
not Brenda you've been warned by
hi mrs. Ashford okay isn't this a happy
coincidence I was hoping I would run
into you to apologize listen dear i hope
i didn't appear to be rude i'm just not
ready to sell no no we totally
understand really where's your father
checking out the archives so why have
you chosen ringwood I'm you probably
told me but it flies out of my mind well
my mom lived here until she was 17 and
my dad's running a book on American
Revolution so I have the strong feeling
that I have met you before I can't get
over it and what was your mother's
maiden name uh walmart Miriam well well
there it is no wonder you look so darn
familiar I know Maryann walmer really
yes I was the librarian here for 25
years and your mother practically lived
here and this this was this was her
favorite table this very it's very one
it's so cool she loved books and you you
are the spitting image of her how is she
your mother my mom passed away a year
ago Oh
oh my dear I'm so sorry
No
words don't do much do they Marianne
did you know that your mother was quite
an actress no I'll never forget you must
have been about 10 or 11 I guess hey you
missed the meeting oh uh family business
they've got some auditors coming in why
there's weird stuff going on with some
of the accounts looks like someone has
like fingers inside job graton
industries you didn't get caught in that
Fiasco did you she's what I'm a mess
when when one of the auditors commune
and a month I heard this loud thump like
that she threw her book on the table and
big huff I turned out the school was
holding auditions for Midsummer Night's
Dream just having trouble memorizing the
lines nerves you know so I sat down and
helped her wouldn't you know it she got
the part I missed her so much when she
moved away with her family I never
forgot her and now I've met you I feel
like I've seen her again well I'm sure
that you're going to find a house that
suits you I just know it you belong here
thank you
and when you do you absolutely must come
and visit me oh yeah I will I promise
why oh wait um say a little Margaret for
me I will
[Music]
and how are you today this sash world
I'm just peachy Sandra I'm gonna check
out the family jewels well let me know
when you're through
[Music]
so I hated the one with the orange
carpets the glass bricks right I'll put
that second one but will the skinny Hall
we didn't smell weird or was that just
the age I like mrs. ash browse house I
mean no wonder she doesn't want to move
she's such a nice person
so weird that she knew mom I mean
listening to her talk about her when she
was little it was it was amazing
so you want to come back next weekend
look some more sure I guess
congratulations can you just made the
best investment of your life Walter you
and I have to talk to you why your
friend here is ahead of the game
seriously just check out the specs these
property doing double the value in
through your smash seriously guys
there's woodland development it's gonna
put this town on the map ringwood is
gonna become one of the most affluent
bittle commuter tax income you should
touch this you know hey Boyd asheboro
Ted Riker ya know who you are pretty
small town yeah yes it is listen I'm
just thought I'd ask good I have a
property up for sale near Brenda nc's
farm big one top of the hill gray with
red trim that's the one my aunt you
interested no sorry I have the package
together just one property outstanding I
expect to close that any day now sorry
no harm in asking right no problem nice
to meet you
that way I'll remember it would I you're
the only one I'll ever confess to them
and memories of what it used to be no no
now don't get any ideas you've had your
dinner put it where you can't get it I
feel like I accomplished something today
Margaret now Brenda won't have a thing
to worry about
[Music]
I knew I had this
I'm going to give it to that nice little
girl oh my good girl your life
companions are you and i we're not
getting any younger
[Music]
dad
another dream I was chasing Margaret
mrs. H bros can but I was in a very
strange place and there was a fire and I
lost her and Mama's are two waving and
then she was gone I miss her so much
we will find a house today down
you're gonna miss your school
with my friends what was it
or email right dad yeah
[Music]
so where's that tree bigger one oh it's
one more block says it's partially
renovated I can meet anything you wanna
go see it yeah I guess dad stop it's
more of it you almost hit Margaret
why are folks west right right that way
fuck i'm sorry to get your number i was
gonna call you cuz your head change your
mind about selling we buried that route
this past wednesday widen I'm so sorry
and Margaret I wish I just started on
him across the street good enough a cat
passed away the very night of the
funeral weirdest thing are you sure this
is a good time I don't want no no no no
better time than the present all this
friend of my aunts Brenna ganti she
lives on the farm across the field she's
the one that gave that Ruthie cat in the
first place she says Margaret died of a
broken heart the animal was 15 years old
for crying out loud not budging on the
price Margaret
you
[Music]
Marion dad dad we have to buy this house
it's a sign this was mom's
yeah what are you doing here mr. Riker
I'm not sure we're on a first-name basis
by now call me dead if you think you can
buy me off with flowers and wine we're
barking up the wrong tree I'm not here
to buy you off on you've apologized but
hey Brenda you have to understand you
wanted to buy your land your parcels the
only thing that's standing in the way of
the development that it's a fair price I
don't understand why you'd be so suburbs
I'm simple I don't want to sell I hear
you having some trouble with your
neighbors that's none of your business I
promise you it's only gonna get worse is
that a threat cautionary advice I sure
we can do some business I want you off
my property not final offer now fine cnc
of course
comfort comfort comfort that's a cool
name um so we're gonna be neighbors yeah
I guess I'm nya Lee ah Pearson it's a
great-looking dog see comfort you lose a
friend another one comes along you lost
a friend the cat that used to live here
Margaret oh they were bikes oh yeah she
was so beautiful so you should know I'm
basically nosy and all as soon as you
your dad no brothers or sisters no it's
uh it's just the two of us hey Harrison
that's Kurt my brother come on it's
lunchtime
well duh see ya come on boy stop what
boy Cooper scribble
uh two thousand dollars this can't be
early account she just had the one
personal savings account there asked me
mortal I know this more she cashed in a
retirement policy $50,000 that's a lot
of money what happened to it mr.
asheboro I do not put trace their dogs
on other people's money your aunt had a
safety deposit box you could look in
there if you have the correct papers to
give you access we're only living
relative
[Music]
duh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my god you scared me oh sorry front
door was open my dad uh he went to the
library but he'll be back soon if
there's something you need oh I think I
lost a cufflink the other day I was
gathering my hands personal things would
you mind if I just took a look around
see if I can find it hmm sure sure he
just walked right in totally freaked me
out said he was looking for a cuff link
he probably misses his at need an excuse
to come back I gave me the creeps told
me if I found anything that was
rightfully his it would be against the
law to keep it he's just a windbag
assistant clients funds but anyway
here's to those and the new beginnings
new school new book everything's kind of
going on hold this last year but we're
gonna get back to some state of oh there
is no normal at least we can try
hey I found some great stuff a library
today stories about a guy was hung for
treason to feel not far from me hey
charming really charlie apparently he's
deceived by about a dozen people and
amazingly they were all drunk at the
time
it's only comfort you probably just mrs.
Margaret sitting in the window huh well
this goes Jerry can you are a little
nervous n-no yes it is this i er no way
it's just a house 03 yeah I know how
much riding on the deal I won't let you
down yet now clearly we're running out
of time well yeah well can I do you can
I make a point here why don't you give
me the go ahead to make her a sweeter
offer I know that's what she's waiting
for that's what she's waiting on more
gamut oh okay finest yeah I understand
that i'll talk to you back so I see look
uh I apologize for the late hour when I
was driving back from the city like saw
the lights oh excuse me look I had a
word with the people at head office and
they allowed me to make you another
offer mr. Riker I think I've made myself
already clean this is really very
generous boy I have a look at it if I
were you hey you know I was a difficult
woman
good night night
[Music]
dad
huh
[Music]
hey Natalie what's up nothing much how'd
you like to take home from for a walk
maybe we could go across the field and
he was the animals what animals at
brenda's um she takes in strays and
helps them find homes yeah sure went on
okay look over here yep yep so where'd
you move from new york manhattan haha
western so cool it was okay you miss it
I don't really know yet what where's
your mom it would be afraid to ask
questions told you I was nosy she passed
away good one Pearson no no it's okay I
lost my mom too she swerved on the
highway to miss a deer I'm so sorry
one comfort what so uh you have the one
brother yeah Kurt and my stuff on and we
married a couple months in happened poor
guy I'm East cool it's Australia hey my
dad you got out of the bill won't get
some chaff of the old kiky what
any Kurt this is Natalie hey so you work
here part-time both down until the
breaks over oh yeah thank you to
experience the into scrabble pleasures
of ringworm hi so what grade ii would
Jen I'm a 9er the persecuted oh great
are you in love enough fifth try just
kidding okay it must be fun working on a
part it's an animal shelter not a fun
hey hey bring helpers just what I need
oh this is Natalie hi I'm Brenda nice to
meet you Natalie merit I know he moved
into my friends houses asheboro she was
just the greatest later you're gonna
love it there what hey comfort did you
come to visit and boy huh oh I missed
you too Brenda family is just after mom
died comfort inn somewhere you
been a good boy hmm anyone feel like
working follow me
[Music]
sunshine is what you mimic a doughnut
don't you and Anthony's me
[Music]
love
this is so cool I love animals will be
an apartment it's kind of difficult have
you ever been to New York she was school
trip so you probably went to the mat
kiya hai yeah skip down to mill
get it
[Music]
can you to go play somewhere else sorry
i was going for Pearson betting I guess
I never give you money with you why are
you so upset I've never seen you like
this before did she ever give you money
did she make donations I mean did she
ever give you money yes or no just give
me an answer yes she did so my rightful
inheritance was given to you and yours
ooh I mean she used to bring buy food
she's been doing that for years and
every once in a while she'd very
generously donate some money the cause
but I think that was her business it's
my business when the cash were supposed
to come to me I was under the impression
it was hers to give I want my $50,000
Brenda $50,000 are you out of your mind
i'm talking forty or fifty dollars every
once in a while $50,000 saw an old lady
with a ridiculous amount of compassion
for your babe is just a minute you
milked her you're suggesting that i took
advantage of someone that was my friend
you stir you you tricked her I've never
seen $50,000 in my life well that's why
money and I want it back so I'm gonna
get a court order and have your bank
account check go ahead I have nothing to
hide I think you better leave I'll be
back
[Music]
he's such a creep the other day I'm all
alone and he walks right in without even
knocking I was totally freaked doesn't
again call me I'll kick his boy he
practically called Brent a liar um I
mean you should see all these things she
does with these animals she nurses him
back to health she finds a new homes and
well she looked really upset
I heard something come on no I did that
dad look whether you like it or not
there is something in this house I told
you I can feel it
sometimes right after she died I thought
I thought your mom's presence in the
apartment little things like like
thinking the mugs y'all she's for
morning coffee had been moved on the
shelf or I hate her perfume all of a
sudden but I was just so used to those
everyday things by manageable but I
didn't imagine the photo flying off the
piano or the piano keys moving in up I
just don't think it's coincidence that
mrs. asheboro knew her I'm just saying
that your mind is very open to this kind
of thing right now could be fly
interview one thing in common they all
lost someone they want them back half
the stories and tracking for my book
you're not to have perfectly logical
explanations but what about that guy you
was time for treason you said 10 people
had seen it that's just an annual
Halloween prank that gives those people
who like to think that nicca blood crane
is still out there riding through the
night without his head well he is hey
let's both you and I stay up tonight
that way something happens we'll both be
there to see it okay deal deal hey
family hi hey this is my dad dad Brenda
Wes merit hey you must be the animal
lady I mean you look after strays dogs
that what else I yeah I never tells me
you're a writer I'm sure mr. bet some of
your books you read law the history oh
I'm a history buff but it's hard not to
be living around here in fact George
Washington used to visit ringwood all
the time one of his chief Matt knickers
lived an area general Erskine I think ya
askin I I bimini look him up yeah
trapper oh hang on I better catch up to
the dogs nice to meet you my pleasure
and Natalie you drop by anytime you like
okay yeah
she's a good worker yeah
[Music]
you
Oh
[Music]
hey what's wrong nothing give sensor
don't you I told you she's here what all
this water come from we'll stay up
together tonight what do you want
exactly no oh Ted is what you want you
want render Yancy's farm right I can
make that happen I am d assistant client
funds manager at ringwood sings along
downtown I I know things the most people
don't like like Bernie adds his client
she's in deep trouble way behind on
mortgage payments I could maneuver
foreclosure four feet
no boy I think we may be able to do some
business after all
well I guess is the case of the watched
pot never boils I don't grandma she's
always allows the full strange sounds
there the creaking moving all the time
it's not the house it's not your mama
why do you think your mom would come
back because she knows knows what so I
can say goodbye you said goodbye now I
didn't say everything i needed to there
wasn't enough time I know that so why
didn't you tell me sooner I know you
think what's wrong maybe it was but I
didn't tell you right away because your
mother asked me not to we were just
trying to protect you we did what we
thought was best if you think that
decision was wrong I'm sorry God knows
at the time was hard to think at all you
should have thought of me I'm sorry
let's get some sleep oh look up now in a
minute
[Music]
it was it you all sorry what do you want
no stay
hey why'd you get a cat you saw a cat
yeah we're in the front window you're
sure it's gone now it looks sort of like
Margaret I mean it must have jumped out
but you saw it yeah quit psyching me out
you mean you didn't get a cat I'll beast
i'm not completely crazy so ever since
we moved in let's just feel so weird
things going bump in the night pianos
playing that you're fine really freaked
me out I didn't really know what to that
don't look at me like that I'm not crazy
crazy people don't know when Kurt I saw
Marvin I saw her ghost it was a real
ghost sure you did not more Kurt I saw
Margaret ooh don't you believe in ghosts
no people die they're gone period end of
story thank you dad might get home oh
yeah yeah you should be back from the
library right now why oh good i find
this book i thought you might be
interested in oh I can just take it home
with me I mean you don't have to bother
it was okay it was on the way the bank
anyway it's no trouble yeah I've never
seen Brenda and clean changed she's
dressed to impress they're so cute at
that age Oh are we little possessive of
daddy and you should go home they might
need a chaperone sure
ah this is a great book it's just great
thank you god I hope it helps I'm sure
well so are you wondering would just for
the researcher are you planning to stay
at all well playing it by ear i guess i
thought a change be a good thing for
Natalie for both of us Natalie that's a
tough age to lose your mother yeah 15
not the best time for sure and she was
having a very hard time dealing with it
we both were so we decided to get out of
the city new beginnings and all that I
hope it was the right thing to do I have
to go away my late uh I'm gonna be in
downtown anyway enjoy it I will thank
you thanks for the teeth
my pleasure
what this might not be my place to ask
but do you have any plans for dinner
tonight yeah or any other night doesn't
happen you know uh tonight would be
great yes yeah okay good so I'll see you
run ate them sure thank you great but
I know you don't believe in ghosts but
at first yeah my mom started happening
noises and stuff I don't make fun of me
please I thought it was my mother oh I
really wanted it to be you just met me
you must think i'm lonely certifiable so
the coolest people in the world I were
told that it's my I guess I'll take that
as a compliment I just wish everything
could go back
well nothing seems the same
[Music]
we've been floating you for longer than
we do most clients I'm really sorry but
unless you can pay the arrears in full
the bank has no choice I just need a
little more time the spring is so much
better for me donations go way up I
don't get it you've always been very
understanding in the past Brenda it's
not up to me I got a memo you have a
week
[Music]
well done Boyd you're my man my money
your money Oh went Brandi an seas off
the property then you get your money
there's only one way to communicate
that's what the ghost seance sands you
two are nuts tonight Yeah right forget
it i'll bring my Ouija board maybe you
could bring your crystal ball two it's
not gonna happen oh come on it'll be so
cool right I'll see you tomorrow tonight
assailant there has to be a reason
markets come back ghosts always have a
reason yeah okay Pearson whatever they
do comfort hi hi have fun today yeah
president tells me she really
appreciates your help over there uh she
dropped out by today Jeff it's a great
book Brenda asked me to have dinner with
her tonight no problem you sure ya go I
might do something with Pearson great
well I won't be late I'll be fine
first the neighbors are other ones now
the bank know it honestly wouldn't
surprise me he was in cahoots with them
Riker don't get me started he just wants
me gone but then I think I massage broad
I know she would have wanted me to hang
in there so that's what I'm gonna do
good I can see this means a lot to you
the animal shelter is the only thing I
ever wanted to do since I was a little
girl let me tell you something I'm a lot
better with animals than I am with
people oh I I wouldn't say that Natalie
thinks the world of him Natalie's a very
special girl we've done a good job oh my
wife gets credit for that I'm just
trying on a lot you're doing something
right
Oh spirit come to us now make your
presence known to us come from the great
other world to join us you need to speak
to you now jeez can you not thought I'd
join the party Oh spirit sorry for the
interruption come to us now come on get
into it or won't work Oh spirits make
your presence known to us come from a
great other world to join us oh come on
the great other world you're not helping
this is so lame lindo home no I can do
this spirits of the night great feline
spirits come to us now let us know that
you were there come on guys ok ok um
please spirit
want to talk to you we want you to
contact us o Great Spirit you're not
concentrating are you involved this is
totally bogus it's not working pierce it
never works you have to believe to make
it work
[Music]
market oh my god
I don't believe this
cat food that's all she wanted cat food
[Music]
so here's the question why would
Margaret haanji for a bag of poo ghosts
can't be hungry there's no way was just
a bag of food she
[Music]
oh my god mari this is what she wanted
me to find Margaret you are the most
wonderful cats not only how are you guys
doing in here I can't stand by and watch
such a dear friend be pulled in all
directions I've always intended to leave
you and your wonderful cause a healthy
donation but what better time and now
when you truly need it love to you
Brenda mrs. Ashburn on Margaret how
could she be so amazing wait a second my
before i could pay the mortgage off how
did you find it Margo chilled us
Margaret don't ask I'll be home later
dad don't be late
are these yours how did they get out
Kurt put them in their pen inside the
barn last night right yes Jan there's no
way they could have gotten out well they
did take them inside and give them some
food I gotta warn you Brendan there's a
petition going around in town to close
you down I know who started that I can't
help you and last month I've had a half
a dozen complaints animals going louvre
scaring people getting into their
garbage you're at the critical stage
what does that mean it means if there
are any more serious complaints I'm
gonna have to shut you down I'm real
sorry
one bottle and you lose an hour I just
don't want you to get messed up again
you you could go to jail I'm not going
anywhere I swear I didn't let the dogs
you sure you didn't set that fire to
Natalie hurt I'm going to the bank if
you leave before I get back please
please make sure everything's inside and
closed up okay I'm serious Kurt or we're
history put a lock on the door thanks
Terry you just deposited 50,000 all I
know boy I know that's my money I knew
it I knew you had it your aunt left it
to me i will have the bank freeze the
front and bread i will show you to the
answer i have a letter i have written
proof so what she wasn't so mine she was
of sound her mind than you Boyd
I did my sternum ado I can't help it she
made it off I want my money you plan
didn't work you didn't deliver open
money now not until she's off the
property if I get you quite as Lana
it'll make your little development deal
what millions if if you get her off
that's a big if Boyd I'll get rid of her
I promise you I know the right buttons
to push and I can do a lot more damage
than letting her dogs on record believe
me much more okay you do it
[Music]
wait
are you taking me
[Music]
Natalie what are you doing here you
gotta get out you gotta get out of here
why not open the park or what is over
you will know
there you what's going on in here okay
so what were you really doing it like I
told Brenda I thought someone might try
and let the animals out again I decided
to check it out the barn was full teams
when I got here look I don't know what
you heard Pearson and I talking about
the other day I'll tell you what I heard
that Pearson thinks you're the one
letting the animals out in that you
might have to go to jail I didn't let
the end zone and I don't have to go to
jail then what about the fire he said
something about you setting a fire so I
went a little crazy after my mom died I
said fire to some guys dumping it got
out of control I got mandatory community
service that's why I'm working
apprentice well so you're forced to work
here no not forced just the way it
started I used that my hours long ago I
just stayed
so why didn't you just tell me like I'm
gonna tell you I'm a juvenile delinquent
the moment I meet you clearly that would
impress a girl right so you wanted to
impress me I didn't know what to do with
you
and it doesn't want me back she's
excited I didn't this way
I know there's no way that happened by
accident I somebody did it deliberately
and I have to find it home and I'll help
you
it's obvious someone is out to get me I
I can't believe it's Kurt but on the
other hand I can't afford to take any
chances it's got to be Riker he'd do
anything to get rid of me I just I can't
take this anymore oh you don't want to
give up now you don't understand the
animals could have been asphyxiated I'm
supposed to protect him not put them in
harm's way what kind of help I don't
need any help I'm fine on my own I I'm
just used to being on my own what were
you doing over here in the middle of the
night you realize how dangerous it was
Margaret came about me Margaret got you
yeah and it's a good thing she did if
Kurt and I hadn't have been there for on
Kurt you don't know him very well you
don't really know run to either what
school
oh yeah beautiful day I thought I'd drop
in and see if you have time to consider
my latest offer it's pretty darn
generous you know what you've been doing
and it's not gonna work what are you
talking about I'm not selling the firm
to you now or anytime soon if you ever
set foot on my property again you are
going to regret it no what matter
threatening see what yes it is mr. Riker
you idiot whatever you did it didn't
work not you want you 50,000 it's time
to get serious if I don't close this
deal my back is in New York and never
gonna give me another penny I'll be
trashed so we're in this together boy
you understand it was time to take care
of business once and for all
hey how's it going so big day tomorrow
hot the auditors are ring just down the
hall and I heard apparently they already
have a pretty good idea who's been doing
a little thing basilan on the side lots
of excitement would see ya
[Music]
just
No
now we wait
[Music]
all those months I didn't even know she
was sick I went to school I came from I
did my homework I went out with friends
and I wasted it all you know I could
have been with her I could have spent
time with her and it wasn't fair I don't
know I think they were really trying to
protect you yeah but state line to me
she don't like along okay for then they
pretended and all of a sudden it was too
late you can say a lot in a few weeks
last you got to say goodbye
[Music]
come on
ok I'm on here
we're so good
[Music]
don't just stand there come on boy
ok
last one let's go now
what happened towards the place we got
the animals out
what are you going
Oh
help get it out
slow down what are you doing just pull
over I give me my money I need I've got
auditors coming in tomorrow you still
don't get it do you boy I don't have to
sense to rub together I don't get me one
either so this deal was closed slow down
hi please hurry
what Allah
we have to get out of here Kurt Natalie
keep it
go
the scratches on his face this guy's
coming around drivers gonna be okay
so it boys up to his eyeballs in charge
district arson on the works Mike who's
finally out of my hair for good and the
insurance is going to rebuild the barn
cheers Cheers and here's to Margaret the
most amazing cat in the world may she
rest in peace tomorrow Margaret it's my
market even though i never saw i give up
how can you not believe something I saw
with my own eyes do you see her
[Music]
I do you see
thank you
[Music]