hi
your bum must hurt
my what your bum you know from when you
fell from heaven
did you actually just that's so sweet
really wow can I buy you a drink
no let me buy you a drink
ok I'll have a pint of landlords
colostomy bag
oh I love a man who smells of beer
that's amazing you're my dream girl
no don't kiss me like that like this
little I like you a lot but if you want
me to come home with you you're going to
need a pretty good reason
so yeah that's my video collection
wow I've never seen so many box sets can
I be honest with you it's not essential
I didn't bring you here to look at
videos i wanted to kiss you again
oh you sweet innocent boy
oh I want you to do what take me where I
want you to what
much about what are you supposed to pose
that was just a dream
No
oh and that's the door mom
hello child I was ringing the bell for
ages
what were you doing I was dreaming about
a girl oh I know you're going to meet a
real girl it's time for you to get ahead
and get on with life and tidy up your
room and again
that was a dream too
I don't even have a mother know
come in mr. headlock
please Giles just call me sir but what
do you do here i thought i'd give a lift
to my favorite junior designer Monica
for legal reasons I can't talk about her
Giles I saw what you did with the budget
range
nice what would you say if I made you
senior junior designer i'd say i'm
dreaming you're not dreaming next year's
range and the next yours so this is a
promotion more of the side motion will i
get paid more
you'll get a parking space
I don't have a car you can use the
executive toilets
mmm i use them anyway
Giles perceived to be encountering some
resistance here
the thing is mr. headlock just so this
is my dream so I can call you what I
want is that ok
dickface mmm now get out of my flat
dickface you stink moral corruption I
stink and I hope your wife finds out
about all those girls you're chasing
after my wife is dead
this isn't a dream is it i was going to
buy you lunch no no no
so I followed him outside smashed in the
window of his car and people over the
front seat
that's when you walk up no that's when I
was sure I wasn't dreaming
Charles one of these days you're going
to get yourself into real trouble real
trouble is there an echo in here just me
repeat myself maybe we've had enough to
drink drink or let's neck these and get
tequila
I just lost my job oh yeah what you
gonna do
I've always wanted to learn to play the
guitar what about finding work
I don't know I've become disillusioned
the whole thing Harry have you ever
heard of Plato's cave the night club
it's this idea that we're all sitting in
a cave staring at the shadows on a wall
and all we have to do is turn around
turn around glad exactly not Giles turn
its work and it's her I'm gonna chatter
open that's the girl of my dreams got
dipped but that I dreamt of her last
night
Giles last night I dreamt it was a giant
lizard walk into the streets of London
people running screaming from me
nobody would let me in all I wanted was
a hook
my point is just 23 Harry you're right i
wouldn't have even seen her if she had
brought me here to cheer me up
she's yours made nice one by M so what's
your sign
no entry what's your drink
no you look like you could do with the
long stiff one you call the bouncer to
kick you out lesbian so how does a good
are she's not really my type
can I talk to go on that she's beautiful
I don't think I can go there are no not
coming with you could talk to a friend
what friend and me you want me to jump
on the grenade
let's do it
ladies I wasn't talking to you I was
talking to you ignore him Gemma Gemma
you're beautiful
that's just the drink talking at least
you're talking
so
your but must hurt my what your bump you
know from when you fell from heaven
did you actually just say my that's
disgusting
wait up can I buy you a drink no let me
buy you a drink
really wow I love a pint of the
landlord's colostomy bag i was joking go
away sure showed that you're my dream
girl and no it's not a line I dreamt of
you last night me
yeah it was you you're beautiful you
still are
what's your name Stephanie and i'm giles
have you got a condom for me
looks like my was ready to go Harry
hello Harry not a good time
by job sorry about that
it's okay we're just about to leave
look miles child's your sweet boy and
I'm sure you have to go home to mommy
and daddy
no my parents were killed by pirates
what they were on a cruise near Somalia
and the dumb blonde don't don't don't
don't don't don't don't
why don't don't don't don't don't don't
don't don't
I'm sorry for your loss but I think I
should leave
what about us child you're a bit weird
weird in a good way there is no good way
but you're the girl of my dreams I'm
sorry you're not the man of mine i see
i'm glad you're being mature about this
goodbye yet by no not goodbye stephanie
wait I'm not gonna let you go boy
ah
and day out and don't forget about our
two-for-one special on mondays i walked
home alone that night you thinking of
all the things that should have said and
the things I shouldn't have let you have
a grant of matrons granted metrons one
regret led to another and i remember the
last time I've spoken to my parents
okay bye they give me that guitar almost
as if they'd known that would be killed
the Somalian pirates and the Indian
Ocean learning to play it wouldn't bring
them back but it would make me feel this
loan that night became the next day
and the next week became the week after
it was only when I walked past a certain
coffee shop on a certain day recognize
certain person that I realized there was
more to life than just sitting in my
bedroom playing with myself
maggot aah
Gemma I'm hello its me Giles okay Giles
don't you remember you had sex with my
friend Harry
Oh Giles hi I'm I'd like you to meet my
mother
hello oh hi I was just going darling i
hope you make the right decision about
that thing I will mum Gordon bye-bye
so what's happening you know your friend
never called me back
Harry yeah he's sorry about him what do
you want
I thought we could talk you know about
life politics sport Stephanie Oh
Stephanie what a surprise
boy wants to talk about Stephanie it's
not like that I don't just want to sleep
with her rarely okay yeah i mean i'd
love to sleep with of course there would
be a for awesome but I saw her in a
dream so so I want to love and protect
her and all that stuff but i can't even
speak to what if she's not who you think
she is
well she must be a good person if she
has a friend like you
hmm we'll need to get you a haircut and
do something about your clothes you'll
help me you're not the only romantic you
know
fashion fashion fashion fashion fashion
oh no story just not your passion
yeah that's not anyone
shy about this
fashion fashion I like to imagine when
we just need to get you a job but not
looking to start here at the salon and
here the hiring is stable I don't know
anything safe houses just be honest I
talk
what makes you want to be an estate
agent
I'm trying to impress a beautiful girl
so money sex help
congratulations you've got the job while
wasn't my honesty it was the tie
well here's where the magic happens
nice are you a magician figure of speech
i knew that i was making fun of you
oh uh huh Gemma yes I've kind of done
something silly like fallen in love
written you a song
Oh interested i'll get my guitar
you didn't tell me you a musician
I'm not really but I'd like to be
general Starr let's watch you
like
nice bright little eyes
shiny to tonight
my strong
I've always friends never kill me see
this home
sorry that was embarrassing i put this
thing away
no no one's ever written me a song
before I mean I'm gonna spend more time
obviously when I do one for Stephanie
Stephanie yeah great
whoo Gemma I want to thank you you've
given me the clothes the haircut
confidence and all you need now is your
dream girl yet while completing each
other's sentences
it's like me friends for years yeah
mm-hmm
Giles if you want to get Stephanie
you're going to have to join a gym
am I out of shape trust me as a friend
i'll get my sports stuff
Stephanie hey Stephanie hi
oh it's you
what a coincidence i hope you're not
stalking me
I'm working out mmm really I've just
been doing some bench squats unit you
know with the weights you
yeah I would cut all the time check this
out
impressed
yeah really oh I'm more of a cardio guy
i hit the treadmills on my lunch breaks
you know I work over at Wolf Pack you
work at Wolf Pack you've heard of them
I handle their conveyancing you're a
lawyer
junior assistant legal secretary
dreamgirls have to work to you know at
least until they find their dream guy
well you had me thrown out of the bar so
that rules me out but you didn't tell me
you were in this state agent
what difference does it make giles at
the end of the day
us girls one security and I thought you
was something flaky like a graphic
designer
wait you remember my name of course i do
wow your parents died oh yeah my parents
died too
what how in a car accident in my first
year of university are jeezum sorry I
blocked it out but there was something
about your story
Stephanie I want to show you up the
least I could do
let me take you for drinks on Friday 630
the same bar see you then bye
I wait you're actually going to go for a
drink with me
yes bye
by Stephanie by Giles Wow
mmm
mm you've changed Giles have I maybe
it's the time all that's it
it's the tie you shouldn't have I didn't
put my date you nervous no don't be
there's plenty of girls like her out
there
oh she's already my god you'll never
find another girl like that
Gemma's friend remember Gemma are ya
the one who keeps trying to call me
doesn't realize I'm a player always on
the go girls dripping off my arms the
ladies
you get what I'm saying here Giles yes
so what are you going to do tonight are
probably have a couple more beers and
head home with the takeaway why don't
you call Gemma tigon released Giles tag
and release but she's really nice
you call her then I'm just not ready to
settle down and start a family who said
anything about starting a family or you
know what classes are like not really
well just take care of yourself with
this one
goodbye hurry
hi hi Giles that wasn't that creep
Harry was it Harry no ah that's good he
really let my friend down
well maybe I should get us some drinks
and after that what you have planned
well well I thought we could have more
drinks yes then go on go back to my
place to do what
um look at my video collection child's i
am not going to sleep with you
oh no no I wasn't thinking about sex sex
sex
what's your five-year plan Charles
five-year plan
yeah I'm thinking and and I don't know
well not very impressed you know
hang on this feels a bit like a job
interview
what's your five-year plan though I like
that
assertiveness it's not too much as it i
just want to hear your opinions
okay what would you like them to be no
child's I need a man I am a man i'm just
a bit nervous you know you hear it feels
like I'm still dreaming like we're in
Plato's cave Charles I came here to have
an honest and frank discussion about the
possibility of our future together and
hears you talking about nightclubs
you're a sweet boy
goodbye stephanie wait I need your
professional opinion you need
professional help
the insurance monies come through for my
parents remember I told you about them
and I was money
yeah lots of it whoa so interesting
yeah yeah Oh Charles
can I get you a drink yeah okay and what
about later on can we check out your mmm
video collection
um yeah I've got some old sci-fi stuff
you might like oh let's get that drink
first beer please
oh I love a man who smells of beer mm-hm
mm-hm smooth like a smoothie
while that's such a good night
me too good to be honest I was really
trying to impress you
what did you think of the meal the kebab
yeah it's my favorite takeaway nothing
well it's too late for a video I'll get
a taxi then
ok goodbye oh ok I um hey
yes I get a room
ignore him he's not talking to us I'm
talking to you
I can't block it out I'm sorry Giles oh
look at him some kind of disgusting
drunk disgusting drink
hey Terry
revolting I'm glad you didn't call job
she's too
I'm sorry sorry
huh you should be ashamed of yourself
Harry are you okay Giles leave him
let's go I can't lose my best friend
just him or me him
Oh out he needs help Stephanie sorry I
hope you're not planning on sharing any
insurance money with him huh what
insurance money
yes from Giles parents i hope you don't
see a penny of that don't deserve able
they haven't found the bodies
nobody's no money yeah that's the policy
you lied to me I was going to tell you
after sex
oh you losers
what do you think she meant by losers or
glad I just found 50p in my vomit
sweet
hello hello
probably some religious Colton
hmm
coming coming coming
oh hey Gemma come in
hi Giles you heard yes you messed things
up properly with Stephanie I lied to i
know but if it's true love you must go
back
she called me a loser you're not a loser
Giles thanks Gemma you wonderful but you
need to get Stephanie back and I know
just how to do it
okay I'm all ears open mic night at the
bar
bring your guitar i'll bring Stefan all
she'll be swept off her feet amazed at
the songwriter
oh I don't know in front of all those
people
sounds a bit dangerous have you got a
better idea I'd rather go to Somalia and
confront the Pirates who killed my
parents
wait that's not a bad idea no no Charles
they'll give a proof I need no to get
the insurance money better start packing
okay thanks for coming around bye-bye
huh hmm
hey see you come back was told they
might be pirates your pirate excuse me
come back I'm not gonna hurt you I just
want information and I'm starting to
think this isn't a good idea i know
you're out there and I'm not scared of
you at all hear me
you don't scare me one bit what are you
doin up
hmm can I help you yes I'm looking for
my parents they were kidnapped and them
and killed so you want revenge at first
year but now I just want their remains
our claims dept San jun 17 that way
thanks maybe you and me answer different
yuck
wait don't leave me here please I don't
know my way around the desert
mhm
no hello claims department mr. and mrs.
peacock please no please check again
no we have no record of them one more
time mr. peacock I don't know what you
know about modern piracy but we are
meticulous in our record-keeping what
happened to my parents then if you ask
me I would say go back to the place they
were last seen malicious were they on
holiday there
yeah but now I wonder
mmm wait how do I know I can trust you
you're still alive aren't you
mmm yeah is that ok bye bye Joel ball to
ball to talk to children
no money for a plane ticket I'm a
derived thirsty tired sunburned and
really itchy i was a drilled the Indian
Ocean thing
k buddy buddy huh yeah you dry land
Wow is this mauritius yeah now move
you're blocking the view
oh sorry this here is a private holiday
camp
oh can I get a beer no alcohol allowed
well I thought you said it was a holiday
can it is but it sounds like some kind
of colors Church the Church of mental
called whatever hey I'm actually looking
for my role looking for something
oh I found it with the Church of mental
you betcha
must be nice hell yeah how do you join
easy you give Reverend mental all your
money
oh no it's called freedom away my old
life goodbye now I sing in the choir
no.9 ino even like no need i need oh god
e na ah car not calm
where'd you learn to drive dickface what
did you say
where did you learn to drive quick pace
thank you need to write yeah yeah nice
one
hmm
so when are you headed the police rarely
there's a religious cult of their
culture you say wow they're lunatics but
i think they might have killed my
parents
well that's a wild allegation it's just
a theory
mind if I put on some music this music
you're mentioning names chris mental
okay bye
where is that boy
yeah yeah how do you know my name
you look just like your dad so you knew
my parents
oh yeah but I didn't hurt them Giles
strange but I believe you can you take
me to the final resting place hell you
want to go to the cemetery
yeah if it's not too much bother I i
want to see this thing through you know
Giles you're a good son
no I'm a dick i'm a dick i tell my
congregation give me all your money but
what I need is love but it must be nice
leading the cult yeah better than
working in an office yeah i can imagine
want to join
nope I have to try it's my charge
come on let's go to the cemetery that
will be fun
well here we are
what's that noise just ghosts come on
your parents are over here
no markings no but you said these were
their graves they will be not now
hey whoa my parents they're probably
playing bingo with the pool right now
you mean they're alive what they're not
dear don't die down on you left the car
stereo on that's gold
hello
what do you want who are you it's me
Charles Johnson Charles peacock my son
missed you mom
oh I I thought you were dead
I'm sorry Giles sorry sorry but why did
you do it
come into the house styles no I demand
an explanation
come inside you stepping all over maybe
two years oh sorry month
Giles say something
you two are the worst parents ever Giles
please don't say anything
how could you let me think you were dead
I mean you sent me that letter and
everything saying you've been killed son
we signed that letter
surely that was a tipple come on oh i
don't know i was so stricken by dream
mmm
since joining the mentalists we are dead
to the world but in other ways were more
alive than ever
yes spiritually and financially we're
dead for taxation purposes so we keep
some of chris mentals assets
I'm not angry that you joined a cult I'm
just disappointed
Oh charge what made you come here anyway
after all this time I was looking for
your body's so sweet
yeah well I needed them for the
insurance money
yes i see well I met a girl and i
thought i should be financially
independent you know so you came over
here for selfish reasons
well when you put it like that yeah well
good-bye Giles wait
Giles please wait
if you go to the souvenir shop tell me
with the mentalists you'll get ten
percent off
oh thanks okay bye so what's for dinner
monkey monkey last night you cook then
no monkeys fine
do-do-do-do-do-do-do yeah no mmm mhm
mom dad I'm leaving
oh you're still here yeah and I want to
apologize child's we're the ones who are
sorry all my boy come with me where to
buy man room
I've got something there for you
wait there give this ring to that girl
of yours
Wow teller it belonged to your great
grandmother who did it
no I found it in the draw but listen
girls love that stuff
um ok thanks how about a non-alcoholic
whiskey
thanks but I need to go to the travel
agent arrangement flight tell them you
with the mentalists you'll get ten
percent off okay bye child's what this
is how you say goodbye
Oh take planned what a lovely boy
yes what's for dinner is off
this is rude
so did you get the insurance money no
child you've gotta pick yourself up and
get ready for the open mic night tonight
yeah why not I mean I've got nothing to
lose it
oh sorry so excited i'm excited to you
always inspire me
I do yeah hang on wait they'll talk
about something for you
what could it be
huh it's just some old ring I've never
been given a ring before
oh it's beautiful can I wear it now
yeah oh this is so exciting oh it's a
bit of a tight squeeze
it'll go on it will go on that what do
you think beautiful really
oh thank you so much
okay i think i'm gonna go nice thing
anybody's ever given me
I need to work on my song thanks goodbye
just by crew didn't
don't didn't didn't didn't get it and
don't don't didn't do don't down
hey I thought that was you Harry how are
you are good
nice surprise here to support me I'm
just here having a quiet drink you came
and just a few too many that's all
ok so what's the competition like then
take a look man really good i I'm
embarrassed
what's the worst that can happen lied
you could fall over
everyone laughs at you so what a nice
finished i'm on next door all go online
knock them dead or you don't stand a
chance
this song is called dream go bomb bomb
bomb bomb bomb
bomb
so I just the the day one did what the
world say I told you met you before you
said it's you I dog
I never stopped 21 there why you're my
dream girl three
three
dream
thank you
I
me again you can be dum diddy dum diddy
dum diddy kong dong oh here you are
I've been looking all over for you child
that was amazing
well thanks so did you bring Stephanie
oh yes are brilliant i'll get a drink
you want something I'm gonna go bye okay
bye i love a pint of the Stephanie hey
own hello child so what did you think oh
my song some I just sang a song over
there
oh I was in the toilet the whole time it
was a massive poo
oh I wanted to press you I'm not 15
Giles i know i'm sorry i just thought
that you and me you know where's Gemma
and she left
shoot she was acting really strangely
back how she was looking at me like this
Oh like this
yeah that's it she okay you really don't
understand women do you
she's sick she's in love with you you
moron
what have I done Stephanie I I better go
and see if she's okay wait
yeah I've been thinking and and i think
i like you know because your friend
likes me
yes jeez you're honest honesty integrity
money as a woman
these are the things I admire but I
don't have money you have ambition
you're chasing after me remember
no no this doesn't feel right you were
supposed to like my song and Charles
this is the real world
what about Gemma I I understand if you
choose her all I can't do that
no you can
you can run after say you love her as a
friend but that you're my dream girl
oh no matter what I think we both need
some time to think about this
yeah okay
that night we finally made love harder
you bastard
it was a bittersweet trying we've both
lost our parents mind to a cult knows to
an accident and now we're losing a
friend that we have made our choice
Charles each other stop talking to
yourself
was I sorry just shocked me
oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
ok I need to pee Oh
yep love was everywhere even at work
hi it's the estate agents are you still
interested in the house
yes it's beautiful well I'm required to
warn you that it's next door to a drug
rehabilitation center
oh that's handy I can get my methadone
there it's also next door to tire
factory for the smell of burning rubber
and and if you ask me it's on for 20,000
more than it's worth
Oh will pay forty thousand more 5016 no
that's not how it works 80,000 ok I'll
call the Select ninety a hundred baby
this is so romantic let's do it in the
car
I'm in the shower
ok man agree
hello child i want you i want you to
wait to stop seeing harry harry but he's
my best friend child he's holding you
back
I don't understand mm he's immature
irresponsible drinks too much and says
stupid jokes all the time
what about as bad qualities child's
sorry you can't just ask me to stop
seeing my friend
okay look at my phone I've seen it just
look at the last message m messages
let's have sex from Harry oh my god I
can't believe he left out the apostrophe
child's go and talk to him now and I
understood
ok I'll go put some clothes on he's my
friend
Giles lied Harry tell me it isn't true
what is just tell me it's not true it's
not true
Jesus embarrassing about you and
Stephanie all that
no no I don't watch it sounds like you
do let me jog your memory
you want BR 00 child's what was that
yeah yeah you like that there's more
where that came from I don't like that
why would i like that Giles texted my
girlfriend always that what you're on
about
so you did know what even know which
stephanie you were talking about really
girls I would never text your girlfriend
why would I even have a phone number
can't believe a doubted you
woman a war a giant yeah why don't you
get us a round of drinks for medicinal
purposes
yeah okay oh you'll have to pay for them
under the showing
ok no drops what are we having two beers
again or and get something for yourself
man woman woman man
Giles yeah could I ask you something you
want to focus
yeah two shots same old Harry hi I'm
just upset that someone texted your
girlfriend that they want to have sex
what what did you say oh no you didn't
tell me what was in the message
no i didn't did I
I'm sorry Giles I can explain everything
no I don't think so let's just have a
drink to like old times 1000
Oh
who
ok open your eyes
come in come in child how did you for
this my bonus from work i'm going to
give you a little bonus 0000
Stephanie you all while 0000 dad
hello son nice to meet you hope you
don't mind
they told me that you work it moved here
and well the door was open
no I'm glad to see me too
son I'm afraid I'm here for that ring
ring turns out it's diamond date the
most valuable substance on earth who if
I don't give it back
what will happen i'll be excommunicated
from the church of mental are known
yes it turns out that ring was more
valuable than I realized though that
google so just give it back I can't
why not always keeping it for me
yeah oh you were going to propose but
yeah yeah I've ruined the surprise
no you sure dad what are you gonna do
the about the church
Oh your mother and i'll have to go into
hiding oh that sounds terrible
no big deal you sure yes but they'll
probably try and kill us better get
going
oh ok well it was good seeing you dad
it was really good seeing you likewise
child's I can't wait each proposed i'm
so proud
hello hello Gemma hello can I help you
yeah is Gemma huh your child's yes we
met before
friends with Harry and your Gemma's
beautiful sister and how charming
I'm her mother oh yes well you could
have fooled me every you I'm afraid
she's not here
ok we're fishing Brazil result like such
a good excuse my cold i I'd like a
diamond type ring please
you mean diamond died yes i have this
how much every 50,000 a million trillion
billion that's a bit steep i have a dime
indict white ring okay how much is that
40 million billion trillion you have
anything cheaper
mm there's this dymond aight aight aight
how much 2000 you'll take it
yeah looks great yes good good i'll wrap
that for you
she won't be able to tell the difference
will she know Stephanie oh well must
have fallen asleep hope I'm not too
sunburned no you look beautiful
you don't have to do that anymore i'm
yours i know but i want to make it
official like this
Stephanie will you marry me yes yes
okay where's the ring the ring yet i got
a second society
mm-hmm
Oh Giles oh well what do you think I
love it
childs this isn't diamond night huh
it's time and I fight how could you
Oh where's my ring but I gave it to
chandler Gemma who moved to Brazil that
Jenna I thought it was just too cheap
the one who was in love with you my
exbest friend I wanted to impress you
with my personality
oh yeah I'm sorry
oh that makes everything better really
go out
oh my house is coming
great hey come in and I'm afraid I'm
only back for a holiday Giles but i just
thought I'd come and visit you or that's
great hollands are being too long i
heard you bought a new place yeah it's
complicated hey you don't bring it gave
you 20 no I lost in the Amazon oh well
you know what it doesn't matter
yeah i'm just like to see so what
supposed to get there
Stephanie hello Giles you're probably
wondering what she's doing here Gemma
called me she wants us to get back
together
you're my two best friends cool how do I
know you're not still in love with him
that doesn't matter i just want you to
be happy
I'll take him back but will you take me
back
of course mm-hmm
Wow looks like i'm in for a threesome
shut up Charles you're on probation
sorry so when can I see the new place
how about now Oh child put on some
clothes and hurry up thanks for the tour
places beautiful boo thank you for
coming
maybe I'll just not go back to Brazil
why did you go there in the first place
I wanted a fresh start
oh how exciting yeah tell you what why
don't we meet for coffee tomorrow okay
anyone about it i see you then
so mr. you're back yeah I really missed
you you know me too
mm I'm sorry I'm sorry too I'm sorry
that our lighting Charles I've learned
that there are things in life more
important than diamond night like what
o.o Giles peacock yeah that's me
what is it I've got bad news for you
buddy you're doing that exercise all
wrong you should straighten your back
like this
oh thanks don't mention it
oh one more thing yeah your fiance was
in a free acid attack Stephanie like
baby I came as quick as I could
ok trials you don't look okay I'm fine
really
Stephanie let me so why not leave me
please don't want you to see me like
this
do you really think i only like you for
your looks good now let me see what
oh god yeah what it's not so bad really
no actually it's pretty gross o.o child
what about going to do great
what are we going to do but I can't tell
anyone who did this to me why I just
caught stephanie was it someone you knew
yes whoo please tell me I can't she
knows where we live was a general don't
say that name to be her again
I can't believe that we need to tell the
police
no I don't want people to see me like
this
Stephanie
we'll find justice I promised he would
need where is she will live Giles
where's Gemma don't know you tell her
we're looking for
ok which would like a cookie oh yes be
8l good match them from the kitchen
sure it's not too much trouble you're a
family friend yet i'll just wait here
then
ok dingdong dingdong hello Giles you
wanted to see me
um yeah well looks like you've caught me
caught you
mmm i'm going back to Brazil yes I know
when exactly are you going
I was going to leave tomorrow oh really
well i know it become friends again but
my life really is over there
you're running away aren't you I prefer
to think of it as a fresh start
Stephanie they get back to bed I'll deal
with this
no I want to see what she's done is you
tell me what happened
don't get 10 come and look well show me
what you've got ok are she's dead
oh I'm ok now she's dead child's what am
I going to do is Stephanie what are we
going to do
for the crime of murder I hereby
sentence you to 15 years in prison
what do you have to say for yourself
Giles peacock come
is there Wi-Fi in prison of course but
we won't give you the password know so i
was stuck in jail rather meet Stephanie
because i'd watch TV
I knew how to survive
on endangers
for you
o mas'r What's Wrong mate good you to
ask if you wanted to be my friend here
now he's a big meanie isn't a come on
now i'll take you to the nurse
let's get out of here dick face
Shh
why do you hurt people child and I don't
know
does it give you pleasure what no oh no
oh no oh well have you ever heard of
Plato's cave
yes really they do it in margarita no I
mean the concert and that well sometimes
I feel that nothing's real and we're all
just shadows like these shadows behind
us and go on
well you're gonna think it's stupid
child
nothing is stupid silly when you're
within the walls of this office
the truth is I think that in reality
we're all just finger faces
like you make when you're a child
mmm
Oh by thinking of yourself as a finger
facing child's toy
you're diverting your responsibility
quite common rarely
I hope you don't tell anyone
Giles I'm a psychiatrist
boy finger face or ahaha face like I
think Stephanie Oh child you look
amazing
I had plastic surgery you can't tell Wow
yes it was free because I was attacked
well you don't have to worry anymore
Giles you're so brave i do anything for
you and in just 15 years you're out of
here
yep and we're back together you wait for
me from this course i'll wait for you I
know I say this all the time but I know
I'm your dream girl yet my dream girl
how was prison good yeah have you made
friends yeah loads but what's wrong
i miss you my child I'll always be with
you check the Sailor now see you next
week okay bye
so I just the the day one day what the
world would say I told you
hello finger face sasha m why do you
look so worried
I stabbed your eye out with a shopping T
per foot roll
I've got another I i'm here to see if
you want in
yeah yeah its turn good plan is to kill
all the gods and get out low sorry I'm
not provided criminal you think I'm good
place they've cancelled the prison disco
ok let's do this before but this way
finger face my dream girl is that way
for touching Stephanie Stephanie
Stephanie hey Stephanie stackerlee buddy
keep it down
who you who are you um this is my house
I bought it with Stephanie her how do
you know Steph she's my girlfriend was
sort of engaged sort of what does that
even mean
prague it's okay I'll handle it let me
give this joker a knuckle sandwich with
a side order of pay
maybe I've got it hello Giles who the
hell is that
Stephanie what's going on and all that
time since they locked you away things
have changed I've changed
I've only been in jail for three days so
Giles I'm sorry but I broke out of
prison for you
i I'd do anything for you you're my
dream girl yes but you're not my dream
guy and brokers when did you meet him
mmm last night Plato's cave i went to
jail for utility I know but no one girl
could ever live up to your expectations
so that's it
mmm yes mm oh but but birth charles rock
a sports car it's red like an apple and
i think what i'm trying to say is it's
time we all grew up
goodbye Charles back of the house whom I
supposed to turn to now I don't know
get out of my garden by oh I've only got
one friend in the world and I don't even
feel take me back
so this is Harry's place then I left it
like it was not sure if I like the day
call oh where is he anyway
did he leave a forwarding address you
haven't heard heard what the side coming
with all the drinky what he killed
himself huh Harry so this is not just
modern art are Harry why I wish I listen
more closely to you
I wish I'd been a better friend did he
leave anything like a note oh you mean
like a note
yes like a note well there was this note
mmm take care of her Giles what you
think he means by that kill her but who
is she
look there's something written on the
back and I know that phone number
Oh someone I need to speak to Stephanie
Stephanie Stephanie come down here at
once child saw the news
shouldn't you be back in jail Stephanie
I know the truth about what
don't play coy with me I know exactly
what happened
oh you worked out haven't you well I
wanted plastic surgery to look even more
beautiful but the health service
wouldn't give it to me for free
can you believe that you couldn't afford
it not after buying this house so i had
to turn to insurance i had to fake an
acid attack and who better to blame then
my old friend Jemma just didn't like the
way she looked at you
so there you have journals
hmm oh and we have to kill her because
she was a witness
yes so there you have it Oh Stephanie I
wasn't even talking about that was
talking about the phone number you gave
Terry yes I gave him my number and told
him to call me for sex
oh ouch i wanted you to catch him out
and see what a horrible drunk he was he
killed himself Stephanie I mean I feel
like it's partly my fault
don't try and play me I did it to help
you
I'm not but I wish I'd never met you
that heads up
sorry no it isn't Charles go back to
jail
god no longer you're a bad person
Stephanie you have a convicted murderer
now go before I call chad wait who's
Chad what up to the other guy chad has a
motorbike Charles that's something
you'll never understand good bow
no who oh no who
suppose a better get back to jail so I
was back in jail
knock no no or finger face Ashur hi what
are you doing yeah good bug brought a
friend
we got caught selling drugs when at a
nursery school but no luck old yeah
we're gonna have loads of fun great by
monday football yeah boy yeah good boy
good fun all too much too much fun for
all good time good time
hang on what are you doing this is what
they call me Russia wait wait wait I've
got an idea what do we start a band
move oh you can play the drums I'll play
the guitar could be quite fun better
than digging a tunnel with a teaspoon
and we're gonna get the guitar
remember when you brought in those
cigarettes up your bomb cranky
this is a guitar going to release
tomorrow do it will kill you when you
get but I ok who were going to call bone
and whatever you want basheh while man
in this is gonna be great guys a
jailbreakers you listen to each em
prison radio it's December so you know
what that means it's noon
don't step under the mistletoe do right
now it's time for our Christmas number
one ride ride ride right
kill kill kill kill kill kill
ride ride ride ride kill kill kill oh
you have the will
ride ride ride ride kill
right right right right kill kill kill
why
well hey they finally let us out owned
we only have to serve 10 years
yeah would have been less if you hadn't
killed all those gods oh hi bird
oh sure who from Group oohs oh stop
scamming so where you gonna go
I'm gonna start again in a place with
delusions and extreme violence I just
tolerated their way of life 03 gun a gun
howdy neighbor hey guitar run high
hey so you want to play guitar in my
club 'i yeah yeah I'd alright show us
what you got
ok stabbed a guy and I he didn't die he
just rolled away and cry why why did you
stab me and I
hey I'm gonna stop you there was that
okay
no that'll create my customers right out
oh that's okay thanks anyways bye have a
nice day man
now where's that stripper gotta get the
paint off these walls so I became a
busca de four quarters not watching
yes went by
sometimes I got so lonely I even thought
about calling Stephanie
but always resisted and kept playing my
guitar
ok
playing my guitar
that was awesome
oh thanks my name is finger face I know
I want you playing all the time
Wow thought I recognized you what's your
name melody say it's called why don't
you come back to my place
how do I know you're not an ax murderer
how do I know you're not well actually I
was jailed for murder
oh yes so funny um if you thinking of
letting me in
you should know that I really am a
convicted killer sorry I really
appreciate your honesty but this is
goodbye no come on in
but but I also stabbed this guy in the
eye and I think my best friend's dead
because of me
ok you got some issues but you got a
nice smile
you're right i should stop dwelling on
the past and start focusing on what's
happening now that's the spirit come out
did I mention that my parents around
away my parents died when I was a baby
or are sorry you must think I'm so
selfish focusing on the tiny problems
flickering in front of me when there's a
whole world out there
mmm I don't think you're selfish you
just need a friend melody thanks i don't
know what to say don't say anything just
come with me to my damn apartment
already who musicians so sensitive
wow nice place don't be too impressed my
grandmother pays the rent
where is she she's in England hey maybe
you've met her
it's not that small yeah i know i was
just kidding sorry i haven't had much
sleep it's pretty noisy where I live
I've seen you there under the bridge
well the rents cheap say why don't you
come stay here I've got a spare room
oh I i see i see what this is ok
here we go mi nah get away from me sorry
I thought you were a groupie get back i
feel really embarrassed
you're like twice my age and dirty oh I
see so this was all sympathy you men and
your pride
maybe I just wanted to hang out with you
oh I'm sorry or maybe I just don't know
a good thing when I've got it
hmm well the office still stands you'd
let me live here yeah why I guess you're
not the only one who needs a friend but
you're beautiful melody rarely inside
and out
oh you want a cup of coffee I'll make
them I'll get them
so how do you like your coffee served
naked
oh you're kidding no oh while the
kettle's boiling i'll show you around
okay great great
mm and so I spent my first day with
melody she didn't feel like a stranger
more like an old friend
yeah just friends but then that night
after we've got to sleep i heard a
scream from her room
melody are you okay I'm fine it was just
a bad dream
Oh what was it off oh you're gonna laugh
because I got scared
melody are never laugh at you well I
trip that we're all potato faces
Oh like how like you draw when you're a
kid
oh I used to do something similar that
the tree was so real
melody he yeah you are not a potato face
really know your finger face like me
oh thank you mmm your face
yes have you ever heard of Plato's cave
the nightclub no nevermind it's silly oh
no wait i dunno what you're talking
about you feel that nothing is real that
that we may as well be finger faces
you've got to fight it I don't know if I
can
my own but i'm with you I'll stay with
you tonight if you want
Oh will you yeah oh I love sleep on the
floor of course no stay in my bed and I
mean I trust you
mmm i think i should just sleep on the
floor
oh ok yeah and goodnight
finger face goodnight hmm
finger things
yes manatee can you switch off the light
oh yeah okay night
do-do-do-do-do do-do-do-do-do
do-do-do-do-do you do
oh hey sleep you had morning
um hey what's that look
oh this old ring my mom gave me it's
diamond date is it what's dominate the
most valuable substance on Earth my
grandmother told me that it was given to
my mom by an old friend friend yeah and
if it was special to my mom it's special
to me
what was your mother's name her name it
was gentler i had a friend call Gemma
what was your father's name Harry what
Harry what did your grandmother say
about your birth when my mother found
out she was pregnant she told my father
but he didn't want anything to do with
it
so mom ran away to Brazil where she had
me but then an old friend called it back
to England or where she died
yeah and my father killed himself soon
after that you sound as if you knew him
you
yeah well what was he like he was a good
person but I think you just couldn't
handle growing up
take care allowed take care of her so
melody are you dressed warmly enough
what why do you care
um I feel responsible for you finger
face and are you eating enough
vegetables the only person who should be
responsible for how I turned out
is the man who killed my mother of use
the tiles peacock
I've spent my life planning to kill him
but what if he didn't actually do it and
was innocent you know it's me don't you
yeah I know finger face we found out you
can to America after prison and you
followed me here I left England as soon
as I was old enough and I've been
watching you ever since
mm why didn't you just kill me I was
scared
oh and yesterday you finally got the
courage up yeah i was gonna stab you
with the kitchen knife nice but then he
thought i was maybe not so bad i'm not i
mean there's someone else
melody I'm gonna prove to you that I
didn't kill your mother okay well i'll
see you soon rig it by thinking face and
I hope you're not just trying to sneak
off because i find you
they be big
hello Stephanie it's me
oh hi Mark know it's me pull listen I
think marks coming home soon
no me Daniel Poland marker in tone I
don't think we can meet today your
ex-fiancée oh Michael hi I other one
Jack Deveny i went to prison for you
Reuben no Francois know Gary for murder
OIC well I'm sorry about everything but
you've just got to hang in there in the
stephanie at Charles Charles Murphy
peacock
oh I've been thinking about you listen
I've got something you might want yes
and diamond ring
there are you America Stephanie now
arrived white one from London child
hi it is you
yep it's me it's so good to see you
ready
I think about you all the time trial all
i think about you too
now where's that ring bar yeah bring
your friends house would
mhm anytime well your rings yeah way
hello oh she looks just like general
yeah fact my mom's name Jimbo you must
be her daughter this is such a nice
surprise
did you know her before she was killed
hello Stephanie tell me what we were
best friends yet
lovely nutella what happened Stephanie
the truth must come on i was there when
she died
yeah and Charles threw her down the
stairs and then punched her in the face
hey come on that's a lie he killed her
I didn't as a woman you have to believe
me so I should kill him
no she's messing with your head she did
it to me I'm gonna kill you anyway just
to be sure
oh look at that gorgeous sunset outside
i love sunset your comment
oh come back so I can kill you
where is it must be here somewhere
yeah night and I'll be two seconds how
happy you are here it is
ok coming quick break
Oh shiny shiny shiny could you move
please I'd like to stab it it's my shiny
shiny shiny King Stephanie i'll give you
the record so shiny
only if you tell the truth I killed her
you killed my mom I wanted free plastic
surgery to look even more beautiful as a
woman I'm sure you understand yeah
oh maybe you don't care how o.o i think
she's dead i'll kick out
still not too bad well she's dead now
and we're in a whole lot of trouble
let's get out of here come on child's
yeah you'll stay with me even though i
did that terrible thing of course but
you hardly know me
I knew your parents you know when I told
you that nothing feels real
well things do feel real when i'm with
you like this is the life is supposed to
look like you're family to me and for
once everything so normal yeah for me
too but I know the body starting to
stink and we'd better disposed that
murder weapon and so we went on the run
to the place where we could be safe and
it wasn't long before love is in the air
melody are you ready estrus do you take
this woman to be your lawfully wedded
wife I do you have and to hold to death
do you part
oh yeah I do and you melody take this
man a man who never thought he would
find his dream girl to be your husband
chris i do well you may now kiss the
bride
thank you felt like a proud parent
giving melody away and because we
brought the ring back my parents could
come back to they decided to renew their
vows in the Church of mental everyone
was happy
to me know right now but everyone's
watching
so yeah you're probably wondering about
me
well I didn't get married or anything
but I did join the mentalists which is
nice
yeah it's nice not to have to worry
about philosophy and questions of your
own existence and things like that
Krista's all the thinking for us he also
put me in charge is quiet which is great
I get to sing all day and well the job
as other books for example a petition I
finger phase
oh hi kandi coming to practice tonight
is that what you call it
oh they sellin hi hi think if a pilot
via hi big things
hi Ingrid so how are you ladies today
he's so dreamy
so yeah instead of finding one dream
girl I'm with a few and it feels like
that's what I wanted all along
who would've thought a I think phase of
I Roxy let's start practice early
yeah get him girls ladies I just want to
finish this film that I'm doing up
never mind why Luke base base base base
base base facebook facebook facebook
space will be finding a space its
fingers and squeezed and squeezed
space space finger finger finger party
people people hope