in the latter days of the 20th century
there arose a difference of opinion the
leading experts at the time believed a
nuclear war would only involve the
exchange of a few bombs and then the
suitably horrified combatants would sit
down at the peace table they were wrong
in just 10 days 10,000 years of human
progress was virtually blown to dust
ten years later they tried again
hey quit lift
you're not only ugly squid lips you are
stupid this is good for you not along
Greeners can't have guns
you
right you got that wrong friend anybody
who says any different is a lie lie lie
I think we'll start here how do i what
you can in here with this ambesed and
what the hell is med tech more hear him
good first he was accused of sexual
assault uh a daughter has taste the
story once she found out she was
pregnant she must have had a change of
heart it's impossible that's what we
thought too until we ran some tests this
man is carrying a loaded weapon and med
tech on a provisional government
authority now it claims it don't know
this man is a scavenger the teeth it
preys on young women oh we know his
record and yours that's why you're being
reassigned to the border there's a truck
waiting outside you're still here
some people think women have run into
many things you if you ever get out from
under the skirts of the medtechs I'll be
there
dr. amy
is this accurate mr. Hellman I can
understand why you're so popular with
the ladies you've left the string of
pregnancies everywhere you've been so
that you have the highest permits as
Owen count we've ever tested must have
been all that vibrate when I was a kid
I'm authorized to offer you a clean
slate all charges dropped nan med techs
main assignment is to locate and
impregnate fertile women in the
wastelands now we need potent young men
in the fields to assist in this great
work men who can take care of themselves
who know the territory who can perform
under difficult conditions do you feel
up to it are you serious well maybe
you'd rather be sent you back to Devlin
well on the other hand I've always been
Patriot sign this
the war reduced our male population by
68% it made most of the human race
sterile but we're still at war a
population war each side is desperate to
rebuild and rearm now that reply is
manpower manpower wise people and that's
where you come in yeah sterk it's an
electronic lock only we have the code
the ECR stays on at all times right come
on help me get this off ah it's in here
you signed it stays on well huh how am I
supposed to you know there's a flap it
monitors your physio sexual condition
it's for your own protection after all
it's government equipment this is a
pre-recorded breathing made prior to
your selection for this
and which for security reasons of the
highest supporters has been known only
to the Prime Council provisional
government 18 months ago a driver
bearden Greeners ambushed the 70 mobile
brigade of the Border Patrol 210 women
and men the googly massacre we have
reason to believe that several civilians
traveled with the three-day have been
taken hostage the rebel breeders
possessed firearms and distributed
contravention to the mutant isolation
and eq except for obedient that the
firearms were up taking somewhere near
Frogtown now and complain the weapons
all tape is still a total mystery
resupply flight out now approaching over
here
this is centinela watching for me
corporal pull the driver of me ap please
clear the runway immediately I'm not
going in that you don't read will drag
you on a chain get instead
your equipment take the care of him they
aren't many like him left I'll do my
duty
I know you will
Oh
it's matter soldier you don't look happy
suit yourself
whatever you are damn lucky to have you
medtech needs every hand it can get
still a war you know yeah which way to
the front
don't you take anything seriously used
to take everything seriously
then they blew it up
Oh
I can end it all here right now well
your bodies across the line to the green
who's got you or not a gun you down
let's see drops first near you hey oh oh
that's just all shut up one way or
another we're going through
I've been passed
hey ladies you just about got my ass
shot off back there now we're going into
hostile mutant territory at full crop
damn I hope you know what you're doing I
hate to think you just lost we're going
to frogtown their leader commander toady
is kidnapped some pilgrims who wandered
into their territory and what's that to
med tech they are fertile women why
would mutants wanna kidnap human females
ransom Tony knows how valuable turtles
aren't a med tech or maybe he wants some
for his harem oh that's disgusting yeah
and we're gonna do something about it
we're gonna get them out and then you're
gonna get them pregnant
are you sure you really want to get
yourself on the reservation don't rest
your diaper stead that's the whole point
of this Joyride
and now that you mention mind if I take
a little stroll why I gotta one of the
roses huh
no armed escort you're not going for no
just right there behind that Bush be
right back
see ya later sisters much later
if anyone hit me tries to unlucky a 1s
charge of plastic explosive beyond a
certain point the proximity sensor in my
earring activates the ECR electronic
stinger as you can see it can be quite
painful but not terribly damaging and if
you get lost my directional finder will
lead me right to you for the rest of
this mission you and I are like one unit
remember that soldier
ah
hey you know you look terrific in this
light see in the morning
I just thought a man of your reputation
might still be hungry I'm full are you
sure maybe not did someone teach you are
you just attained by nature I was just
following orders orders regulation 12
keep this up all excited state it from
us pose oh oh see I'm just doing my job
good well when we get back I'll how to
give you a raise
Oh
hey
we can't make any noise this is against
regulations oh not brutal they don't
want you wasting yourself well then why
I heard stories about you I wanted to
see if they were true Oh p people talk
too much oh yeah imum it male wrestling
in the last few years when we get only
how do I there's a flat Oh
over
Oh centinela I don't know if I can live
up to your expectations so you ready
born you're out of uniform corporal
you know you two ladies must have moons
for balls nobody goes on the reservation
not even the paw Patrol how the hell we
supposed to get him out with the plan
that's no plan that's a lot a murder me
I'm having no part you signed a contract
yeah the fuck for freedom but I ain't
meeting my Maker in frogtown that's not
in my contract page 12 subparagraph
eight if we can't get the girls out your
field potency will then be utilized okay
okay but what if I get them pregnant
we're still in frogtown what happens to
me fulfill all the terms of your
contract him you won't ever have to find
out why not yeah oh yeah yeah let's
renegotiate huh
oh not you motion tracker we got a live
one let's check it out get in get in
fear left
more laps go right
it's still moving more laughs more left
right
here it is
according to the tests I just ran on her
she's fertile gonna find out here
where are you from identify yourself
you're scared okay prince charming you
try okay
it's good for you that's a girl there
you go good for you she don't like you
cousin either easy Spangled what are you
doing she's no good to us traumatize go
get ready for work
you can start now what are you talking
about the girl I've injected her with
ova doll to facilitate procreation
that's why you're here remember just
like that yeah she's ovulating and
you've got a high chaos let's go oh come
on I can't work like this come on
hellman it's late and I'm tired she's
never ever brushed her teeth what is the
matter who she's not my type huh your
time yeah you have preferences well yeah
you know if I kind of Noir and a little
chemistry there you know a little
atmosphere would be nice Oh next you're
gonna be telling me you have to be in
love first maybe you ought to try making
love to a complete stranger in the
middle of all hostile mutant territory
see how you like it you need inspiration
what are you doing relax
I've been trained in seduction
techniques right hmm
you
I'm not a machine you can just turn on
and off whenever you want to you
oh come on
you
I guess I'm gonna have to live up to my
culture spangle put your blouse on come
on put your blouse
take your glasses
you clean her up not me
I'm grabbing some downtime okay
frogtown is back that way how far I ran
all day and all night where are the
other girls there in commander toadies
palace why didn't they escape with you
they're from an order of passive
resistance is not their way they believe
only the truly meek will inherit the
earth right all right go south for a few
days the Border Patrol will pick up your
signal and a vac you to a med tech
hospital no no no no no don't worry
mothers and national heroes you'll be
treated like a queen thank you
whole days
put those on me
now I'm your prisoner oh I think I'm
gonna like that Oh what's wrong baby
don't like being treated like a puppet
on a string now you know how I feel good
cover the best watch for my signal tied
us around my waist don't try to take my
earrings they lose contact with my body
your equipment blows if you get too far
away way your equipment blows and if you
don't do exactly what I say your
equipment blows understood did anybody
ever tell you have a wonderful
personality move out I didn't think so
Oh
when you stop with the chain
we have to trust each other now our
lives depend on it
but
you look good shall we might as well as
long as we're here
come on it was a neighbor
bring small
bartender give me a drink not me you're
my prisoner em
industrial waste you never could hold
you in liquor they told me that you were
pancakes and a mineshafter need to town
after the war oh you know I got 99 rock
howdy I'm Lana yo jewel discoverer of
the whopper yoga mother lode they call
me loony choice because I'm so crazy I'm
centering anybody you know ah well I see
your tasties and brood you know huh
what's the worthless puff like you doing
I'm frog down do a little trading what
about you oh I go with uranium is found
a big pocket here right under their
noses looney if there was any uranium
here they were minded up before the war
listen dim head I'm being foursquare
with you now if you don't believe meters
take a walk over to tunnel 43 and watch
that winners get it out now fine fine
what what the hell they're mutants gonna
do with all that uranium Saturday guess
water they can get I get twenty percent
ah mr. you want to barter yeah
why me you came to the right place but
you got a dog Leroy first he runs a
joint tell you what I'll do i fix it up
for you he right that old man must have
been 80 years old when I was born I was
down for the count he was the only man
that took the time to bother
look out Lachlan yeah watch where you
going sweet
I love you you want to talk about it
she's our contact handmade into the
harem that Tony's palace I love you as
the code phrase mean everything's going
to plan oh so far what do you mean so
far hey kid you don't know man my day
Roy waiting come on what is this blood
boil baby tortoise and brown lizard I
grind them up together to make a patient
first
a noble gesture mr. hell you see it so
rarely these days may I suggest a chaser
here real beer where'd you get some
miners found the case in an abandoned
mine it's only slightly radioactive now
that I congratulate you on your fine
piece we've not seen the like since bull
brought in those wenches wenches right
like her yes they were most jelly
commander cody was so impressed he
promoted bold to his first lieutenant oh
yeah that's commander cody blackley oh
he hates me and what aah all human
beings there is a lot of bad feeling of
course amenity it wasn't bad enough that
we unfortunate creatures were created as
a byproduct of human warfare but then
your time your kind herded us on to
these reservations as if we work cattle
had no pardon that I hate the government
all government so I am prepared to offer
30 lilies for this fine specimen no
offense I'm looking a lot of expensive
well I understand but you can see how
bad business is would 50 be more of your
lightning struck a spark now let's see
we can write
take another look at the lady hmm good
pose fer bigger excellent teeth she
could supply you with endless nights a
pleasure you misunderstand me sir I do
not see a sex slave I want something to
bolster sagging attendance something
with real showmanship can she dance
dance of course she can dance she's
especially good at a rotting dancing
hahaha excellent excellent I have an
idea hey wait wait a minute oh who
brought this here I do
what's it to you where are you from
stranger no are nice got a name he'll
Sam he'll never heard of you she oars
party to Leroy private party well yes
both shuts your private spot is allowed
in frogtown totis more Leroy knows that
looks like your deal just got canceled
how about it boys auction I fitting at
five lilies well the big Stanford five
high bid fire ain't good enough
I said it was high bid five flat lips
heroic your shut down till Toby says
otherwise everybody back to work I love
you uh-huh oh cool right where is it
back at the mind bull has closed the
saloon again
you're very fortunate how do you fear
that your life aren't you
what's going on I'm Arabella I'm sworn
to fight commander toady to the death
they've taken your partner to the palace
to the harem will demo right on schedule
you slipped me in I bust some out signal
Centinela and we're out of here right
theory oh you're making me nervous
by the way I don't know how to thank you
for helping us I do oh wait a second
lady I don't even know you but I know
you even hear your name is legend oh
yeah Sam hell helping wander the
wasteland The Fearless water you're all
so bad that's real tyrant John I
interesting you do give you rest right
here I'll be different around here men
throw themselves at me I can have my
pick well they're all idiots you I'm
real huh what are you doing yes policy
you won't be gentle look that I can
finish Oh Sam I know it would be great
hey wait a minute just wait me kill me a
favor oh you're just the same take heart
OT good did God
come with me I want you to identify
someone is this how you like it Sam it's
perfect just a little kink of mine what
is that it's DCR spangle gets out of
range explode I know a shortcut to
tunnel 43 go on without me work
how long
I gonna see you what's this oh just
someone we're having for dinner tonight
sorry I could join you
first shipment shall be another within
one week
teeth Han you away
ah easy baby girl I'm on your side what
can we do to help them no not a thing
you
I'm sang
I've come to rescue you oh
with a plan I see
what are you doing as I pop this command
awaken in your body
or spam
in the hell being prepared for a night
she'll never forget I'll see if I can do
the same for you
hey you don't need that I'm ready to
talk the commander is very curious about
med tech inventions so I'm going to do a
little exploratory surgery
feels a lie yes without great passion
you cannot face the dance of the three
snakes two of our companions went to
their fate cold with fear and did not
survive something seems to have stirred
your senses or someone
it's wired of law medtech wouldn't be
stupid underwire a potent bear alpha
what do you think to get more gas
this is nice we don't have time
I gotta tell you you are one weird dude
stay here old man wait this by trey r us
algo you to solve any action to hell
you're not even human why should you
risk your neck to overthrow toady
besides Sam's my friend too look you
three sam somebody else in command to
fire the signal flare now I've been
firing flares ever since before they
disbanded the Dodgers you're right give
me five minutes good luck I said cell
phone reptile
ah
Oh
wired to blow so fake she tricked me
remember this passion keep the fires
high and you may survive the dots of the
three snakes what are these three snakes
you come on let's all go just walk right
out of here we bend with a window break
sometimes you make your own will I can
get you out maybe you right then again
are you okay yeah oh there oh you want
oh god no
loaded bastard
you
Oh
damn for me the only dance i'm gonna do
is the dance on Your Grave dance or die
modern ballet the dance of the free
remember this passion and you may
survive the dogs of every species
ah
you
what are you doing here oh well let me
explain all right
you
you browse the freeze night come to me I
ain't your new or need those things wait
ah I just thought of some new steps
Wow
okay help me up let's party
they've arrived Oh someone's dealing
guns to the Greeners somebody named can
slot him it was your wife's wasn't it
it's my daughter's that's all I could
find the war was a long time ago not for
me
shall we might as well the three snakes
sure you need me they will it's a
miracle right let's go yeah your boys
are gonna eat dirt her lid why is the
choice since Noah this way are so low
not yet warty watch ever
come on people have double parked here
oh he's it's not easy you're always such
a calder and hurry
you're letting them get away I would do
something about it
I
Oh
you're really suck
I told you my plan would work
yeah you did
don't take it so hard son
I've lived my nine lives
Oh
I sure hope it heavens is good
cuz until it up fast behind us and it's
I can lose them in the rocks we're gonna
make it
join my way hey buddy
Wow
I told you was not finished and hellman
you see this used to be a man's world
Sam another too many women that I was by
the short hairs but i'm going to change
that ideal arms to the Greeners for
their uranium and then I give it to
renegade scientists for processing get
away get away from you soon I shall have
the only nuclear weapons since the war
and then I'll wipe the slate clean crush
like a resort once I the treble handed
to me I'm a passive and then read this
world of those meddling medtech bitches
we're all gonna die starting with her
long winded son of a bitch welcome to
the club
hey where you going to finish it stay
with the girls
Sam Sam will be waiting for you
you
Spangler
we gon
if you want to live Ron not you Tony
we're going down together
Oh
you
we thought you were dead where were you
when we saw that thing we took cover I
told you the plan would work plan I was
a plot to murder me I'll kick your butt
I'll just try it buster stop why you
would have saved yourself for furtles
not enough oh no you don't I ain't on
your leash no more then why didn't you
run off I knew you'd miss me
hey how's your shoulder I've had worse
yeah what's this for something to hang
onto when you're alone
mintek owes you a lot maybe after you
complete your duties I can get us a
couple of weeks leave that sounds great
what do you mean when I'm finished my
duties huh I guess what they say is true
what's that the soldiers work is never
done
Oh
you