are you all right oh say something yes
what is it my
who's gonna bring me ice cream
come on the ice cream man's here the ice
cream man here all right all right let
me get my change Roger I don't want you
going into my purse sorry mom well do
anymore you get back here right now
Roger can I have an orange push up
hey what's your problem mister
didn't say please yo man I could be a
grandpa by the time you get your clothes
shop I hope I push up please hey tuna
new truck creamsicle whomp up next to
creamsicles in a bomb pop I some of the
hardpack stash up yo man I said to
principal and a bomb pop he'll need nuts
they give me gas heck no ice cream bhuj
pretty freaky maybe just different good
ice cream is good ice cream come on
rocketeers to the park macy s girls
against boys less when they're growing
part
hey watch it help yours you had a head
start watch your mouth at least you're
not the wrong fart again hey guys have
been waiting hey Rockets here he's
mobile you guys got ice cream huh yeah
bomb pop you always get bomb pop they're
cool-looking damn
do not you're not good at Oh gross tuna
anybody wanna bite you no thanks most
viral contagions are passed through oral
submission he's mah paw it's a book Pied
Piper the kids through pies at him get
it Pied Piper party hard tuna he cleaned
the city of rats by enchanting them with
music obviously missed one of the big
ones he bed been to the river and they
drowned then he got the kids what kids
from the time the adults were trying to
stiff the piper for the job he did on
the rats so instead
let all the kids down to the river and
drown them just like the rats that's
what happens when you don't pay the
piper uh actually I think the kids got
away oh I thought they all drone next
the kids always good
you
ice cream man you feel okay yeah little
boy ice cream man feels uh huh very
happy very very happy well what have we
got here free weary pilgrims back from a
hard day's adventure hi mr. Leigh Leigh
you select Rinna yeah I just need a rest
after carrying these babies home oh yeah
right now the darling have you worked up
an appetite yes that well boys if mrs.
Langley and I had known you were coming
would have set a place oh that's all
right we gotta get going be safe boys
Godspeed
hello puppy
who's there happy day nurse Wharton
Gregory did you hear my dog no nurse
warden I did not hear your dog what's
that on your nose it's grenadine for my
ice cream treats well now that's nice
Gregory that's very nice I swear I heard
binky cry well you know nurse Wharton
you're hearing is not what it used to be
I've got to unpack the truck the ice
cream melts by always such a happy boy
my little Gregory
happy a little puppy
you sure this my son shoots me dead for
going 30 in a 25 zone hey when I become
a cop there's no more flesh and blood
it's just me and the law we are very
proud of you Jacob very where's racer
sorry I'm late I was ahead there's and
tourism um pick me up Oh what kind of
name is that tuna tuna tuna so stupid
now Jacob tuna is a very nice boy it's
just dumb I will admit the torque does
think like a rotten fished up hey hey
this is not very nice dinner
conversation racer come on I need are
you I got it that is the stupidest thing
I ever heard tuna honey what should we
name the kid hello hi well no I was just
really ah you're kidding me hey capital
meaty just Isis way up some respect at
the table nope what but somebody's tell
me where I lost control am i sees me
honey will you save me signals can tell
you your mates have taken over
Johnny did you see little Roger Smith
today here's at the park why because he
hasn't come home II and his mother's
worried sick
did she call the police not yet Johnny I
don't want you out after dark anymore
okay oh come on in fact Jacob why don't
you and Janet take him to the movies
tomorrow this is great I'm definitely
not going to a G film
white Gregory Gregory Gregory are you
all right Gregory rents due in a couple
days four gallons hi like one rocky road
I'll make it special nurse Wharton I'm
glad I can watch over you Gregory
besides the soul parlor was starting to
look like a lost soul to me I do so wish
you'd plant one in my yard I will bring
the ice cream tomorrow that'll be just
fine
so take the bus back and don't be late
well mom will kill me and then I'll have
to kill you okay yeah no prob oh yeah
lose some weight fish boy
dad hey my number one son and his tag
team yeah you saw movie yeah what target
to kill sleeping beauty Oh we'll just
have to see that this weekend don't tell
your mother mark Sarah hey gorgeous
keeping that oven heated up it's your
mom she's really pretty heart I really
want to see you tonight yeah I can't
wait I'll see you tonight then well
dad's gotta get back to work but at
later bye all right
oh by the way what's wrong cooking in
the oven come on Tina
we got a missing kid thought maybe you
might have seen something little guy
never made it home from the park last
night no have any leads it's classified
ice cream man it's classified listen all
I want you to do is keep your eyes open
for us sure Who am I looking for
anything strange so how about some of
that world famous heart back I've been
hearing about it's rocky road today
dummy two scoops on a sugar cone it'll
be two dollars
I got a bucket boom
Oh chuckles ooh
here you go detective just for you hey
that's an ice cream cone mmm what's in
it it's classified officer classified
mm-hmm you were quick my ice cream man
you're a quick one what do you think
officer don't worry about it Mitty will
find you boy can we buddy an ice cream
no thanks can we buy you an ice cream
what I was trying to cheer up
ladies first my I'd like to buy a gallon
of your heart back do you deliver no 149
that cute little house right over there
come any time charming 149 yeah she stay
oh you should talk next um three hard
packs and a bump up make mine a pledge
circle yeah and make mine a hardpack
risky of you um all right three hard
pacsun on a fudgesicle plain sugar or
new waffle calling I'm sugar sugar yeah
I have plain actually don't make mine
plan to any other alterations
three hardback and your fudgesicle man
there are no bad days Gregory only happy
happy happy days
now what kind of day are you having
Oh guys I'm gonna go unload okay come on
Leigh tomorrow yeah all right I'll see
you guys later okay all right
come quickly the Archangel Gabriel
speaking from your moving again ha you
know husband acting up weirder around
her mom lately for her father being a
minister all the more they just talk
about God oh but that's not it it's just
I don't know she's just acting weird
anybody for ice cream uh we just had ice
cream can you ever up too much ice cream
possible uh-huh guys get home my mom's
gonna kill me come to my house or smoke
on me I gotta get home tonight oh my mom
sorta gets mad about all the ice cream
ice blue shirts last one there's a
string of squid clap what now small
pause trying to pin the rotten egg on me
hahaha I'll see if I ever invite you to
my birthday party what I didn't do
anything
oh well well what do we have here want
some ice cream um maybe not it's too
close to dinner ah come on what's your
favorite flavor on a wait wait let me
guess let me yes I don't know anything I
it's I can taste it
butter brickle how'd you know that this
is my favorite flavor too
you like my ice cream truck
I never saw the inside
you know it's hard to meet friends when
you're always stuck on the inside you
know I had to stay inside a lot when I
was little
because i was really sick
that's why I'm so small you know I was
sick too when I was little but I'm
better now here you go wow I don't think
I have enough money for that my treat
hey boy what's a free ice cream ah this
little fella got hurt I'm gonna take him
to the hospital
hey hey hey you little turds gonna have
to learn you can't run for the ice cream
man I know where you live you tell
anybody I'm gonna get your mom and dad
what's the matter
how long have you been here all right
the extreme head he he killed the park I
he killed small Paul so what do we do
I'd I don't know what to do he's out
there I'll follow you to your house and
go through the backyards till I get to
mine come on I drove by the bank an hour
ago in the whole place was shut up
darkest attune so I drove by the bar
after I get off what of it oh so now the
story changes to you left work on time
but you hung out at a bar for four hours
mr. shoes on the porch you know the
rules
no I hope the bar mom I saw come on
Marion just admit it you think I'm
seeing someone else think I know you're
seeing somebody else Martin come on
Martin who is it tell them not do this
again dad I not now Chris go to your
room but Dad I said go to your room I
knew you'd have problems with my longer
hours come on why don't you just admit
it stop working at the saw how many
times we gotta go through this deal with
you oh sure that'll solve everything huh
to hell with me over here don't walk
away from me you know Marianne I got
news
what the hell is that ice cream dork
doing out this late
come on tuna let's go gotta make it to
the store and back before my pinochle
games huh well let's go then got to know
you can make a mess go find another pair
come on let's go
hey Sam morning ms gazzara nice to see
you there you go thanks honey
what
hmm
what do you think of this color I don't
know either I mean according to my color
charts it should work but last time I
follow does I ended up looking like a
clown spotted with cherry syrup cheers
sir it is good looks good on you get a
dozen
you
where's that
joke a little fella I'm with immigration
what on earth day suppose he was running
from I don't know well maybe you should
go on into it with it I'm sure once you
do that we can get to the bottom of this
by the way you're not gonna take us to
court are you Chris what happens oh and
here de Lorean appointed wendys Chris
unless you tell me what happened mommy
can you help you he said he truly loved
told what who said that the ice cream in
my polish me oh honey
I see you good officers you're Gregory
tutor yes yes I am can I keep this got
any large dogs ice cream man no
why the search officers want you to go
through everything find any hollow doors
or floors must am open got it yes sir
hell I remember getting ice cream here
when I was a kid who this guy owned it
reklam much metal oh yeah the ice cream
key it's nice to see somebody's uh
opening the place up again wow sounds
like we're missing out on all the fun
Jesus get to get my hand caught in that
I used chopped nuts fuck you find
anything it's nothing down answer do you
realize how long it takes to make butter
brickle
well ice cream man we're sorry we didn't
find in you sorry you didn't find
anything in wreck my place are you just
sorry you didn't find anything you boys
have the wrong house I'm already seeing
daughter where were you last night
around six he was here working to pay
his rent why are you bothering this core
boy I'm the one with the missing dog who
are you I'm nurse Wharton Gregory's
landlord neighbor and Guardian serve and
protect my ass you have to understand
the people get pretty uptight with her
as a missing child but on the ice cream
man I make children happy today you ruin
the happiness of those children any days
to come you understand the consequences
you know I never thought about it like
that yeah I bet you didn't you call this
number tomorrow tell him what happened
sure to see what about my dog you know
those daisies are magnificent how do you
do that actually I chop up policeman it
using this fertilizer they make great
fertilizer
you know there's something weird going
on here it's in background on that guy
you got a hunch what
let's put a tail on him anyway
you know I'm sure your dog is around
here somewhere that's very sweet of you
Gregory you have a happy day remember no
bad days Gregory only happy happy happy
days
you
oh don't don't worry I'm not gonna hurry
what do you think little boy
are you having a bad day
yeah you're right not every day is a
happy happy happy day
ice cream professor
butter brickle
quiet suffer little children Jesus so
wisely admonished his disciples on the
coasts of Judea suffer not to come unto
me from such as the kingdom of heaven
always remember that neither death nor
power the height nor any creature shall
be able to separate us from the love of
God which eternally rests in Christ
Jesus our Lord and Savior
let us pray
I told the police everything go get oh
yeah when I'm still grounded for a month
hey don't worry there might be an
opening in the rock tears you guys yeah
small Paul's dead no one asked you to
figure your visual your healthy thing
hambo well I know is I'm not letting him
to get us all the grown-ups worried
about their stupid problems what we need
to do just catch one foo
small poem
marble back back keeping a small for ice
cream I'm fixing up a little party for
you you're gonna like this looks like
you got a lot of friends
I didn't go how much ice cream right now
you can pass it out baby hey I'm little
really good
they love ice cream it's gonna be a good
summer
in too much business I'm talking to
somebody guys having a party
stir
you have an a happy happy day
sure is getting boys around
you
it's brittle ice cream
let's come
I lost track of tuna we better get back
you go what I'll be fine just give me
your bike so I can have a rocket I don't
think so don't worry I'm a rocketeer
just make sure tuna didn't fall or
something meet me back here all right
and hurry
tuna you okay hey where's Heather I left
her back the ice cream truck
you
shit kids got a gun this isn't a game
boys there's a child stalker out there
and you two are playing cops and robbers
one about Heather she's gonna die the
ice cream man's got her I've already
called it in there's someone already on
the way to her house you guys want end
up on the milk carton
I'm sorry to disturb you Reverend
Langley but we had a report that your
daughter Heather was missing well she's
tucked away in bed has been all night
what's the matter Charles I hate to do
this certain but could you please check
out her
she's sleeping like a baby come to
church on Sunday Charles I'm giving a
sermon on trust
the Langley girls fine sleeping like a
baby 10-4 look boys enough of these
stories first the ice cream man kills
the weatherly boy and now the Langley
girl I mean we've had up to here
when do you want him it says one hour
you could get our duplicates or you
could get our eight hours service for 10
depends on how many exposures come out I
need those immediately 4 x 6 oversized
his 12 back in an hour
the ice cream man is like the Pied Piper
really evil what well he drives around
in his truck tempting all the kids they
follow him and slowly gets rid of them
like rats huh another lovely we only
need ten dollars worth of quarters and
we can pick up the film I think we got
it Johnny what the hell are you doing
with my camera where's the film start
with you where's the film oh come on I
got it lets go
see
hey get that hunkajunk out of here hey
hey ice cream come on let's go I'm in a
hurry here no come on this isn't a
parking lot hey ice cream man well hello
oh if I'd no use with delivery day when
that standing that it would have never
made it to do I brought you something
special oh sounds yummy you know we
should swap recipes a creamsicle the
custard pie
well I checked out ice cream man
couldn't find squat put that weird lady
with the dog I remember she was just as
flipped as he was you're talking about
the nurse yeah nurse Wharton I called
and checked on her nursing license she
had a career from 1952 1993 spent the
last 20 at some private clinic called
wishing well for the mentally disturbed
I can't believe there's little perverts
but that are they doing developing like
pictures oh my god I'm gonna kill those
bastards
Oh
it's this kind of secret ingredient I
put it in here come on let's go put a
man yeah I just dumped a little bit of
this stuff in makes it sweet you gotta
just put a little bit in its the special
amount you put in now
the trick is is Sternin just doing do
not disturb yeah
when I would watch your hand then blame
it that little take your hand right off
cool
do you really think your brother's gonna
pick up those pictures without looking
at them I don't know he's stupid enough
well what happens if he's not oh geez
well you scoop it did you see the truck
no I gotta get home my mom finds out I
snuck out and ride with you I'll be fine
we're riding with you things aren't the
same as they used to me around here more
patients have died some pockets dried up
hmm of course when you die you will dry
up well the plastic flowers that's
because real ones dying we want happy
patients so you do a shock therapy
lobotomies it's like that cuckoo movie
we believe in keeping our patients happy
we believe in compassion shut up you
remember a nurse warden do I oh hell
everybody did what was it everybody
liked so much about nurse Wharton she
gave everybody ice cream when the pain
and the loneliness came she cared for
the patient Gregory was her favorite
Gregory hmm hurry tutor
Anthony's getting out of hand I must ask
you two to leave this is not a happy day
remember only happy day gentlemen a very
bad
come on
let's get out the cloverdale County
Sheriff's this is in our jurisdiction
all right off I'll beat you the car
Oh
no one leaves the wishing well doctor's
orders
you
everywhere
cloverdale this is detective mall
riverside pd emergency repeat emergency
yeah what did the wishing well hospital
get some people down here quick
Oh
vampiro big quite vast like Heather
fastest sure Paul fuchsia
Oh
trollin fortuna
your ice cream
okay pump it one more time
good all right shut it off how about
conga we punch you kick Cola please
comment you're the guys who cried wolf
look besides we don't have any evidence
and obviously either do the police or
they would have them by now so this is
my chance to mess him up cut the Lone
Ranger shit you're not a police officer
Janet I got the gun the badge will
follow no listen you guys you're gonna
get in the car right anything goes wrong
all you have to do is call in the radio
you calling for backup all right no
let's just go help the the fat kid while
there's still time get in the car please
I need to look after these two we're
still no sign it charlier Gus yeah where
I'll get some backup over to that ice
cream parlor keep trying to reach his
officers who is he it's the king
yes he's like the Pied Piper chases away
all the bad and leaves a world of good
yes now it's illegal to use this channel
unless you pd so nobody calls in unless
it's an emergency okay now this is
serious I want you all to stay in the
car no matter wat you hear shots or
screams or anything funny you press the
button your radio it in and then you hit
my alarm okay it sounds like a please
siren be careful
sounds like we got a customer I'll be
right back
you
to doing do nobody back at the hell out
of there soon
hi honey creamsicle
this is gonna be fine
we gonna find a way hey kids over here
I'm a cop what are you doing running
from the ice cream man don't you know
that he / day and night to make his
treats for you it's like big eyes always
said you can't always find a sweet kid
but you can't make a kid sweet
don't you know there's a curfew who's
always getting in trouble kind of makes
your head spin yeah looks like your
spine right off boy I didn't know you
got such a hearty sense a humor danzo's
hearty good you were
you
don't you know you can't run from the
law
Wow fun quick you can't just jump on
women you gotta take it slow
I guess two heads are better than one
hey guys
Gregory what's all this infernal racket
sorry nurse Wharton some of the
neighborhood kids want to play
hide-and-seek I told him it was too late
but they oh my little Greg are always so
kind to the little children will try to
be more quiet okay good luck he is just
like everybody else let's get help
we'll have to hide we have a report
agreement the kid now I don't give a
damn Warner not what's going in
you kids don't want to play with the ice
cream man you like his treat but you
don't stick by him when he needs you oh
who died made you Prince what are you
trying to run no you can't run from the
ice cream man you do that you won't get
any ice cream right please I made it
get visible of all time but I see the
kid check the back
yeah where was it
gregory ah my little twin bombs
now Gregory you're going to be with us a
very long time and I want you to get
something straight there are no bad days
here at wishing well only happy days a
kind of a day are you having Gregory
bakery
it's a happy day
Thanks ice cream man
happy happy day
is the pipe i will now ice cream dick
did you find my dog where's Gregory
I
hey hey OOP haha Hanks ready let's do it
so we're small Paul or else therapy
you