[Music]
I
you
[Music]
after the coke you falling Lady Bears
after supposed to coiling
[Music]
by controlling neighborhood by
controlling ladybird
[Music]
[Applause]
mango emergency at me calling the
ladybird bicycling ladybird that was the
fuck you calling lady please come in me
a love triangle emergency air base
calling the ladybird come in please
[Music]
bastard in the ocean
well I can think we run into anything
advantageous please nothing other taxing
topical lightning and Cisco
[Music]
may goes dead fuck you to the store oh
well
I wonder bang around in the storm like
this never know it
[Music]
Halep angle emergency air base calling
the ladybird come in please the radio
must be dead to contact every symbol of
eternity again but they're all calling
on broadcasting signal surf they had a
report they contact us I'm 80 discover
what is it wedding me your marine base
radioed again want to know if we've seen
anything of a ladybird settle mark even
a good look at but they want to know our
position give my position about 350
miles northeast appellate angle now
Isaac way that kept the local but they
tell from your radio signals foreclosure
autopilot bangle not a chance Biden and
having any directional radio finder on
just the same if they try to erase it
again don't answer i'm captain to this
ship and i'll give you always all right
your captain of this ship but whitey
forget about a Pangolin that missing
plane let me know if you get a good
method to buchi right i want to let our
chinese friend knows he'd have his guns
as soon as we can get to from upriver
okay fine ivan cruise around a long
enough waiting for those guns yes and
you'll keep losing around until I see a
chance to get them out without having
those Marines from qualifying going on
next well I'm tired of waiting and
effect I really use it in the board by
tomorrow and heavy shit back on Hong
Kong yeah this ship was shorter than me
for the purpose of the living dog on for
change
and he stays here until I say
differently my dear Radha you really
shouldn't argue with our friends kept in
a Hellion it is now you can believe them
from one end of the island to the other
but when you're aboard my ship remember
what I say goes sure it goes that's the
way I handled mutiny when I was kept him
die on the bounty Halep angle emergency
air base calling the ladybirds any time
now he's already demonstrated that your
new get because he'll consumption it has
we've enough gas supply to the South
Pole I'm not rest for the outpost whoo
stainless beside the publicity will make
you rich dream about all the money is
going to make us money would make me his
parody George makes
this is the ladybird Thanks Viking thank
them for Sophie oh I'll talk was not a
fan go Alf Alf angle oh ok now go ahead
yes my how am i cause Virginia I've been
worried to death he's okay George but
confidentially she needs a little
discipline your sister thinks flying the
Pacific is like leaping a profit
applause he will teach you hello Kostas
darling this is the first one we had
people Siberian tribesmen tried to shoot
us down for an overgrown even our all
y'all killed a little marine this is no
time to be flip report your position
half our sweet I'm not one of your g you
have to be overjoyed that we're coming
500 miles let the plasticity call dr.
Singh you you you'll leather like what
is your position take it man no no quede
start a video I've got it I think
lieutenant or transistor is the answer
to our prayer My dear rather than why
keep me in suspense effing I think
you're going to get your cargo if what
I'm planning works the lieutenant will
have enough worry to make him keep his
nose out of our business son you better
check on film and bond they don't they
give yourself look up
[Music]
parent faster with that calling system
hey right one thing I can't figure out
what's that lieutenant as well officer
all right so with all that though he
missed it has why don't you want a
thousand if a second place like this
money doesn't mean any of the olives
first one hitch height on the Mayflower
another one is better than new way to
scout the Indians and conquer the west
and from the newspaper reports the
latest one is busy enough to think the
flying around the world of the lab and
more money than brains i guess i wish i
had some of it which what money you
don't they right
I can't understand way well look relax
it doesn't get married hey Muslim you
figured I'll make a play for the field
sister remove your paw I'll bite it off
push nut I was just thinking a little
laughter office will stop taking over
get into more trouble the onion media
coverage
just those that putting up those shirts
fix those neckties chest out and swim
again now get these orders and get them
straight when the plane lands you'll
bring misfortune and mr. raft ashore
will you meet the lieutenant sister try
and be gentlemen gentlemen we're always
gentlemen you rather just because your
father senator of Virginia here shut up
then a son of the Sun don't make you a
gentleman its actions account and here's
another thing if I get you to forex
trying any of your on fully tricks well
that ladies at this post I'll make you
wish you never saw the Marine Corps
today pensions
any pension not good but probably the
best young birds can do get my hands on
this guy without a seven gonna tear him
apart inspiring snort of life or this
aunt EULA seal for this detail are you
blubbering moochers what would you be
without me ah fine if you got me busted
talking you're helping you prove the two
Marines is better than sink sailors so
bad you get your head buster before you
talk me into this transfer come to the
southeast I solo it follows a man to the
section beautiful native maine dancing
around Carl services you sleep on a bed
'banahna me this milk from coconuts
coconuts for you you will be and I and I
could have done to original evidence I
had a shortwave radio on for me document
open the volume Napoleon would have
amounted to study implies village and
motivated is destiny but forget all over
the life of yours in particular Center
who you are now dr. singh kannada speak
he imminent
that's the stuff doctor don't forget to
play a part when I bikini getting free
vector but I am definitely keen on the
street that's really need for your dog
in the cinema hero and eight king of the
change anyway doc don't make a mistake
and Regional Jail sickness well
[Music]
what can that be
not only bargains plane how do you
figure that guy Ezard i know i've been
here long it will pick up any of that
island after all i knows what the slave
driving projects is runs mix up plenty
of things you know soldier of fortune
prohibition run money next I'll get his
bankroll open up the 24 judge qualify
here lucky guy the Isle of book
I'll take that bar chocolate um
[Music]
here comes the ladybird
ladyboys rising
[Music]
I'm going out to welcome is all of them
come back the trick to making it appear
[Music]
I'm guys with it the other memory of
leading society don't worry i'm going to
do my duty soldier nothing more
[Music]
look at the mess tent in my back why
should give another kiss she keeps the
back welcome to polyp and Ole Miss Alden
now it's welcome to pella penguin is
that all here well we're delay the
common man's compliments and take you
ashore that's all perfectly illustrate
what I can salute you might wipe your
kisser well the CEO is pretty particular
about appearances why didn't you tell me
I can't have the tent and gentlemen see
me like this stay on it yes sir well and
he says one gentleman says please like
my kissing mr. buck the fireless private
Millard vines we call it Millie
big Masonic Temple is meant to back to
me how r check things over yes all
aboard MIT
[Music]
either way
hahaha would you get the double crosses
in one go look you for coming on my name
you watch the face that for us your
initiative preciosa and you're right
right not to give it a clean ocean say
some of that idea what one of the cuffs
are oversized the distance between the
tunnel and the docks begins to work with
and flesh we have a prison reform plenty
of the co not against off okay all right
hey well do all match and the one that
wins does the dirty work huh all right
I'll take it
[Music]
my life the olives are looking for a
place to light well we'll make haram are
made
almost an authority
time to get up
I must oppose really it red max didn't
see me like that although i think imma
cops pulled up and threatened to call of
the references that if you feel the
charges if you're insulting is my help
ladies right rom among state i can last
a few more days I hope I just made it we
had you wrong you can't be human me
because I was so flipping assessment
sorry if i seemed silly you're okay
thanks ocean
hi
I'm gonna help you with Jordan hello how
are you good to see if they look you had
us all worried haven't you any
confidence and a lack of the ology well
I suppose I do that knowing you all my
life Oh consistency Oh Virginia I want
you to meet mr. Barton and dr. screen
this is my sister Virginia gentleman how
do you do it awesome howdy there Gracie
relieves having with one of our iron
typhoons you have strictly conquered it
was fun while it lasted lieutenant I
don't think you have very suitable
quarters for a lady at your barrack I
would like to place my house at your
sister disposal well thankfully well
that would be lovely if it wouldn't be
impossible for now I'd be honored
get the boat ride up on some timing
double-crosser you on our wait a minute
Billy we had our own wrong she's a
12-person what did she do give me a kiss
in the cabin you a pushover you well sis
this is paulo panga you have a
picturesque looking place into this
what's the matter to the big song
senators boy get his teeth with haha
I'll get you
[Music]
jalan dr like a remarkable experiences
you certainly navicula quite true quite
true what I could remember 800
incarnations I Canada 802 the doctor is
always for Madison oh and you're even
corporal alright so what are you all
dressed up for your not figuring on
crashing Bacchus fire oh you know how it
is corporate guys got to keep up
appearances or ego nado but I the mighty
yeah weather report to me in yeah i just
finished making coffee water well i'll
be taken to the CEO okay bye save me a
trip oh that's nice friend my ladder
broke they don't you have a buy any
cigarettes so you know it is a little
short for payday okay help yourself hey
wait a minute one at at time but we good
you're a pal here at a corporal thanks
Emma to any influence over the dinner
but I'd never say it review nasally
whether it's right there
next is the document is been waiting for
Thanks no they displayed it all for the
weekly report George it seems to me that
started bond and sorghum Nordegren
lovely may I offer mr. Bob profession of
course all of them thank you to play 90
sixpence will be how do it Waka me yet
what everyone ya sure it's just a minute
well brother I'm about to do your favor
I'll take it over the CEO for you well
now that is big heart of you strike here
it is all made up with don't see how
about a cigarette see thanks Jonesy
you're a little short of cash until
payday aren't you so you took the words
right out of my mouth voice all right
take the whole thing you feeling all
right fine that's what I thought you're
a great guy you'll be a great guy why
you nice a great guy no thank you doctor
mr. ratifies me a question about the
island that I could manage it perhaps
you can I know it backward in coming
here for hundreds of years
well why do they call it the island of
lost soul well in the old days when we
pirates roamed the seas this was one of
the hideouts until man struggling his
mechanical wings no nation claimed it my
how we used to call a controversial the
present natives are nondescript origin
in other words of Genesis unknown are
lost get it then there should be buried
treasure here for the course each other
and beyond that this island has always
been a real a point for international
gunrunners but why live in the past when
the future so profitable look at this
report again well there's only one low
pressure area whatever it was there
should be a lot of interest in the
weather around here did you say the
weather will this isn't exactly my duty
I guess what did I help out come over
here barn
[Music]
you can boys know each other don't you
oh yes all right that'll be all you men
are excused oh no they're not Georgie
I'm very flattered they're so
interesting option none of your silly
old discipline I'm sure mr. Barnes would
endure another glass Avanti and mr.
thought you could definitely stand a
cooling off this from mr. Barton don't
be long indeed not what would it be
gentlemen ironjade
[Music]
yes
yeah take this and drink it all of it
sir all of it yes Oh a barn part of that
orange anus for you huh I mean sir you
heard me then detective lieutenant as
general of the American army I never get
that the general of the American army
still living at it oh no not George
Washington like why can't the boys Julie
don't be so snobbish about I'm sorry sis
but I must observe military etiquette
that's where the best soldiers I've got
separated that be tops in any way if
they won't separate if I fail to slow
them down one day they're gonna put this
outline that backs and swim away with it
then I'd encourage some junkie well
occasionally I have to take the iron pit
I don't think you do and new structures
can blow yourselves if you like but I
know where the fun is excuse me thank
your mug out of that suit becomes the
prison take a walk with Emily whatever
they want to go to I thought hello don't
you sit down I think I neglected to
thank you boys for bringing me in this
afternoon little long day nothing oh I
forgot my purse the other one a bitter
person would you get it Millie
confidentially in college I want to warn
you about something well it's about
Gandhi he's a very good friend of mine I
feel you should know this is he's the
type of Solomon you know what I mean
he's an opportunist tease he's always
after something why do you mean Oh took
misunderstanding the New York case you
probably want you to put in a good word
to the co-ownership promotion and I
should be oh my god oh definitely he's
really a good scrupulous but I
understand then I knew you would hey
where's mr. or the more I conference I
didn't ask for it because I didn't watch
it notice my shiny nose no I'll be the
bad people I don't want you to think
that you can try me yeah she said you
suppose you try to pull a fast one huh
no we just telling you what good friends
you to work oh yeah no we're gonna get
us a few years but what well see ya I
hate to leave him alone with a day I
mean lady is a hmm and unscrupulous 20
busy right here hurry up and get the
rest of the bunch and i'll give you the
signal win of course in your case your
brother be with the command ah you mean
he might ask me to get in the role with
the fish first don't get me wrong you
know work town here's your contract
Thanks thank you fight you know there's
one thing i like about you too yes
what's that your loyalty to each other
where's he's nice fellow is great great
guy
[Music]
oh my darling
sweet I'm
there
while still removing the wrong mama died
and little sassy our own atmosphere
masala you know I never expected the
reception
[Music]
I
that was very nice of these types think
nothing on it I knew you'd like it you
know it too bad you're not going to be
around them longer yeah maybe all right
that evening ok this one night you're
turning in early you little B when those
motors 58 them oh come on I might offer
a suggestion development I would follow
the coastline and heading along don't
try to cut across the island but we can
save an hour that way you better take
the coast it's dangerous over the demo
and it won't add many miles field trip
very well but I'm hi Cindy George they
all are females are forgetting sources
can I boss tonight I'll be waiting for
you at home waitin I'll take off for you
too boy they really believe you can be
helpful it that's a talent is the book
would you care to make a friendly wager
make it easy on yourself well suppose we
say five thousand dollars
five thousand and i'll pick up your
check it glow i'll be waiting a tattoo
from the ground okay the best influence
and i'll say goodnight expensable lovely
give out your Duffy in the morning
musume good night boys come on don't be
snow white time oh yes report the period
5 30 tomorrow morning from assaulting
suppressor yes good night so nice to
that I'd you know I'm wondering if
you'll be paying the lady with the wings
that wager you're playing isn't as fast
as hers well we'll try to make the race
interesting for itchy rich is wrong
first she collect ah
all set cigna salting out to the plane
yes sir safeguards million i will just
wanted why i'm in tolleson doesn't stay
invisible to lieutenant or I'll so much
perhaps Molina has more to do than visit
us get mr. Rapp down to the plane yes
side of our barton springs are they out
there in charge yes Sarge will you stop
yes dodging me yes sergeant oh so the
boys want to play do they all right I'll
make corporals out of you two birds just
those I can trick you not least sergeant
ears you'll have to hurry accounts to me
all yours believe we don't probably for
my head lift with us up yeah I've been
thinking about that face fights when you
reenlist let's get a pen for the pen on
my boy I know the place down there to
get the most beautiful voice for me with
that song and dance even if I do
reenlist we know more of your transfer
scheme for me right
[Music]
[Applause]
let me go I'll report like I can't be
think it's the wrong mr. Barton evening
[Music]
haha
thank you I just wanted to tell you that
stuff I thought about bonds last night
the book he's really a grand guy I know
it he's the first person to him he knows
all of this to know about rocks and
father he would ever leave the marine
cross he he go clicks and he's not
looking for promotion oh he's a tooth
missing straight you don't tell him I
said so i will and thanks for telling
you all this one other thing I wanted to
you it's about fun and careful that guy
he's are falling thanks so what would
you suggest well the race the Grom
you'll beat him but after that brush him
off as Mellie would say
[Music]
I almost forgot I hope there's not even
smoke by the time i get me just my
friend Miss Virginia yes just something
very important i'd like to tell you
before you leave it approximately
I think I see what's been having a
seminar for the metals if I gotta take a
little one strike to no I told you all a
lesson isn't his fault he had to go to
college in the grand guy just the same
sorry something is very very important I
want to tell you how exciting features
about that faker but without for him I
know all that all right by beating the
ground but after that Russian won't come
here have no trucks no problem very well
as something I that give you a little
remember
thank you does this mean garbage agency
[Music]
well before it could be an interview
day back and running women
baptists why do we dream oh well you
can't keep that face alone for the lady
please i bought this race you'll get too
excited max this is that important they
lucked into a cellophane a couple of
Marines oxygen I didn't know anything
come on
[Music]
what make you think there is not you've
been flying regular comment on
everything feeling well I am my own
cable yeah well it's likely to be nice
a part of the Falcons bogotá Frank
Virginia it's not going to get out of
sight except behind us that's the spirit
open like a soldier's we hung back
why don't you take your nose out of my
affairs put it in that password below
sorry Virginia here goes no it is
I my treat Mickey my losses my bag
speaking of that they are what garden
[Music]
bye to the bottom rope
maybe he thought it'd scare me are
following well he inquired hi you're
dating to the best I would risk related
to find out some they come see me that
Devon one-dollar bills and have
encountered swipe this has to be come
back to proceed hola
I
please
out of control
[Music]
can you see
better settle around
medical down a steep isn't this coming
down coming down hi video
[Music]
in the you wanna have Kareem plane from
important friends of mine getting things
yes but don't have so many questions
what difficult me when I doing here I
vote again the house my god better come
on
then get under cover for a while take
the native enter the rock come on
come the phone
sure
get back that guy here we are good where
you're better now yes I'm all right a
little out of breath and being it's over
the wheel birthday well the bottom line
is all right come on let's eat I have
many ideas you would follow dr. sprig
have been doing a little excavating at
the edge of the jungle swamp I would
anxious to pick up some specimens as I
want to send them from the brown to
catch the next student in New York I
figured he would only think of a short
time and that I could still beat you the
one but why this done button all that's
a failing of mine I I get a great kick
out of stunning and it amuses the doctor
it's very exhilarating it serves the
Eagles drugging me I'd like to get word
to my brother as quickly as possible oh
yes of course right I'm going
immediately and check your plane and see
what parts are needed then we can fight
back to the base and pick them up Becca
you wait here I won't be long I think
I'll check the plane with button I'll go
with you next I try Stan for sunday
Sotherton that's right for dinner we
won't be long I have to break off I
thank you Bob about
yes I like to find out a video all right
one remarkable is all the Latin
improvements in the heart of junk I
remind I say it reminds me of the days
when I was composing tennis now don't
tell me you close that I can understand
how are getting a stump for the both in
our radio like that well exited fucking
do big things you know you should get a
message to the elevator how about using
the radeon your place unfortunately is
when out yesterday I'm going to have a
fiction long
oh there's a radio the house we can use
that let's be not a useful months our
thoughts our radios broken nose doesn't
work and all of the houses out of use
the non coincidence isn't it especially
at a time like this yeah unfortunately
right now letting you see your radio
maybe I convicted why worry about it
rough knocking off line for the bases
afternoon any we're not apply all over
you I'll go ahead want you wait a minute
rap I thought I told you to stay in the
house why are you being wise woman here
what's the matter you're jealous
[Music]
will you go on your way tomorrow does
that make you happy
[Music]
what are you doing right these fell on
the wing I open the door I want to take
a look at your radio if I can fix it I
told you I was going to have a fixing
one there's no reason why I should lie
to you it's important I didn't say
anything before but I'm telling you now
there's something wrong I don't
understand it well I'm beginning to
understand you that cut off up there and
your fall with Bonnie a deliberate plan
to bring us down here just why I don't
know let it has something to do with
that gun running message I just great
your mind is working overtime well
imagine is it or not I'm responsible for
Miss Oliver I'm going to keep your radio
work
[Music]
fortunately there's comparatively little
damage to your flame good oh hey Doc
we're taking off to follow following a
little while where's max oh you'll be
here the moment perhaps we'd better go
down see what's keeping you yes I i
think is a good idea I like to be in
front of fungal Accord arc
just wife is all open cloud the flame
feel moved yeah rap thought it might be
better to have it out of the water let
be less difficulty making his hair so I
have some of the ladies put it on shore
where could Nexus gosh he was here
working on a plane when I got for the
house he must be around somewhere I
think we should look for him you better
stay right here miss Oliphant a few
yards off her path and you'd be lost in
the jungle we'll find him come on Doc my
dear Nautilus what happened to our
friend I really don't know dr.
unfortunate thing he got in the way with
poison dart team he is dr one moment
corpus delicti the next I wonder what
the penalty is for murder on the island
never forget it but this isn't going to
change our plans tonight we'll need a
plane shows up at one and there's no
word over the air every ship in this
side of the Pacific was not stretchy
just as you planned yeah but Sir I'm
sorry about Russell well he traps
straight off of the jungle probably not
yes I strings of happen before I caught
a delusion and all that no news yet why
don't you guys stop annoying me you
think masalan want to be bothered with
you during a race with Russia keep us
posted hey what's the idea free and
enter in here nuts allowed to see all my
period I out here holy amigo I get
thing I had right come on get out take
it easy with it does come back if you
get a report when you send us a note
Jones oh I know you're right
[Music]
run quick for dinner no having mr.
Barton returned yet you're calm
why are they beating of drums like that
may be tired look jungle field fence
fitness about and say will you be back
or have you sent world hang on tell me
will right mr. bulky why can't I had no
Remender you're right Neelu not lost
cool oh that's silly you love him don't
you give me my husband
you look a lot better you go through I'm
sway to mr. Rath yeah they're normal
come to thank you stay here swimming the
native that's why they're beating a drum
after your world up flow meter a good
race to jungle but mr. Barton said he'd
take it back to tell a penguin money who
are you calling our water warm fire my
room then subscribe come hopefully by
one
[Applause]
tomorrow Marlie Hall good night
I want to carry out their come on
tonight we'll have the less of the guns
down at the beach right fellas only
about a hundred cases law to go down the
river and in 10 days fuching will again
be an ignition business by this buying
the missing lady threat would have given
captain puffin an excuse to circle
around this vicinity apparently looking
for the plane however did you ever have
a vision no doc but I'll bet you had
plenty I just had one a couple of people
for my eyes are reincarnation I suppose
not reincarnation incarceration my dear
Oliver what are you talking about that I
had a vision at the lovely miss colleton
finding out that we were engaged in the
anti social enterprise of gun-running
you know but that would mean how would
she find out she thinks we're out
looking for us can t seem oh my dear all
of it the young lady is even now just
round the corner eavesdropping
I'm terribly disappointed in the peloton
listening in on a private conversation
the jungle must have corrupted a good
manners undoubtedly we should do
something about it yes for sure you wait
here doc I'll be back on top
[Music]
the safety of Virginia hortons round the
world Lady Bird and Oliver Barton
spelter the two points less travel tango
early yesterday in ruth dubois searching
parties are being organized Virginia
Lipton calling pilipenko please come in
packs I'm sorry miss all of them but I
never allowed us to use the radio
without my permission
where's max he said you were going to
look for him we look for why are you
who's next dance I'm really far in the
something here
some angles virgin nearly involve naval
station please
[Music]
well lieutenant commander person this is
lieutenant Allison speaking this is
preston lieutenant sorry we've had no
word yet metalloids from the plane has
been taken up here to begin some of
serious lieutenant I can't understand
one of the planes not coming through
will broadcast for an immediate search
and send out all available
[Music]
[Applause]
why would you turn in a second act all
right I keep looking you know what I
can't understand is both planes sailor
each one that don't sound off on the air
nice I wonder if she try to cut across
the island I was thinking that too a
milli remember the lieutenant and bottom
total is too dangerous that might be
enough to make our try it
hey would turn in the world what's up my
mom hey what do we turn this fall we run
out of fuel I'm going back to the base
the base you can't do that suppose the
place blows around somewhere Alex sighs
I'm doing the best I can we'll reload
you come out again lesson writer you're
headed straight course but what we have
to row take your hands off of me which
is a risk for insubordination yeah y mas
right guys knows what I'm doing any
bright oh you guys he goes on the water
what do you think this is a horrible
accident excellent because i have used
provide
[Music]
have a launch week you'll check the
searchlights and change the route
because it'll be shoving up again before
sundown they have to be mopping the
floor with the old and he tells another
long
Martin plate hey we're going to call a
CEO in the mining co will pick up a
party
[Applause]
mark explain is just landed orange is
trying to pick them up let's get out to
the pier parking what happened to you
you came down with a Brooklyn fuel pump
at the other end of the island what
about this album what do you mean Kiki
go right through the one no I've never
worked from us if you took off no word
on know that sorry phones rats on to ya
oh come on jump in
you're already on the base one every
available ship between your efficiency
over cause I register now when did you
last see the lady first after we came
down is best over as head of the one
never reach them miss or motor show
signs of trouble at all I remember you
mentioned Oliver that you would be
writing a check for the young lady in
black so very distressed review lacrosse
in the Senate and joining the search at
once music the Lady Bird try to cut
across the island we both get to the
coastline 50 miles out I develop engine
problems lucky you didn't try to go over
the arms as the land of the jungle right
that one would do not
[Music]
I'm better say about of West Virginia I
don't notice enough your man just wanted
a physical one is that was probably
poison you to grab it with a plant a
story at the number one idea strikes are
giving you know Blanton blind try to get
in the same song and dance and CEO right
now according to this little gadget it
was down on all right back in the jungle
somewhere yeah we've got to find out
where let's check this over the field
okay I knew Bartman spring to give the
feel the same line it gave us a stripe
maybe we got burned oil drums no we
haven't but doc didn't get stuck into
play 5,000 feet in the air or sea it
came from the jungle rotten lying for
some reason even though he is lying the
seal tents for any reason or motive for
or how his landing in the jungle could
possibly affect me for inflamed neither
can i but my heart says it doesn't
that's what's it up to us let's go out
to play before he takes a strike
remember the CEO said you take a chance
in your own responsibility I'll take it
I can get to the river called before the
bottom takes off our second flight from
a good
[Music]
Martin just a glossy is joining the
certain parties in this element Thank
You sudden I also wish to report that
private launch took one of the launches
without permission yes he was seen going
towards the river call oh yes that's all
done and another thing private Barton
has disappeared little bill what
lieutenant say that'll be all sergeant
yes sir oh just a minute keep an extra
man in the radio room and have them
bring me any messages as soon as they
receive yes sir right away sir
[Music]
the back Rick maybe I wasn't
you
[Music]
well my first I hope we made our rough
landing here it always feel it kingdoms
fell when i leave surroundings that have
to come in dear
[Music]
you
calling fellow plan which is here babe
[Music]
another thing I'm ecstatic
you
[Music]
Oh in this study drive
techniques and gentlemen should always
be quiet planning it or not a winner my
grad see lily and I suspected Thornton
had something to do with you disappeared
did I stowed away in the plane Wiz rat
and killed him less she's a tough break
now I'll keep your chin up we get out of
this somehow
[Music]
yeah people keep sold no I don't think
so it's like okay that's not a lesson to
the base come lieutenant how to get here
install until they do what's matter
virgin girls ruin what I buy those
movies that I'm familiar where you stay
here with a dark know it it's a mineral
out like you're gone
lady some things should never come a
marine
[Music]
you could sit over there while I like
you sentry duty
[Music]
our kids are right about looking
familiar brunch let's get go on that
camping couldn't get you to do well we
can lower it you can fly coffee
plantation how can we get them
marina supposed to be good for 20
natives if the guard not only worse the
network okay
[Music]
so
yes
before you text me goes on
well you're coming up here me you know
why I came why did you we just itching
for a good life that's all what do you
say
[Music]
that one do you any good something
that's what you think the bridge is
pretty what's around it and if you
expect any helpful the banks won't turn
too much on it we haven't forgotten as a
planar out here but you said if you
don't object too much not at all fun be
a pleasure to have a famous flyer the
controls get going the balance that it's
almost looking outside the whole lot one
peep out of them will be the last thing
you'll ever hear all right children I'll
talk to arrange it so the report happy
to personally cut again the news button
no gunfire do you get that here are all
of you okay
let's go
alright
start it up again
[Music]
no bottom
I understand you've been around these on
them for a long time now I think you're
about to leave them for good it won't
start what what's the matter by the way
[Music]
you go through there get white man on
skype
wait a minute no rush white girl
[Music]
and are you doing here
cool battle array you only want to show
you want to help you those opposed you
free to keep like you know more
[Music]
you know I wouldn't leave you
kissing you tell me love me more tell me
alone
man I'll be back in a little while have
you kill wife income white men are
coming here it's alway with me buddy
back
[Music]
hello right
right
[Music]
O'Malley
you
[Music]
started on we're leaving
but I lost sight of a mobile ban batanga
when he thought he tried to give in to
the claim sorry Thank You Minute Man
flying private phone and burn yes sir
right love it well so that believe is
that honey Oh
you would two minutes spoil all the fun
is getting hot hey Millie the plane dr.
Virginia wait a minute you guys you're
through plan heroes miss Olyphant is
back there a safe of the seal Robin
listen starjetter take these quizzes to
the launch but fags we got up get one
come on you guys you know I Shepherd
guard left right but with on your dreams
anyone doubt i hadn't destroyed idea
[Music]
spawn my just received orders that
Hillary Thornton Honolulu for the trial
of dr. spring Lawson to mrs. Byrne yes
the bullet puts in the day after
tomorrow you take it your lesson expires
in my database yes hope that you're
buying a real is it make a splendid
officer in this service on if you just
cut out those private ones of the others
and get down to soldiering thank you so
much I've decided to take up aviation
Missouri fine profession I wish you good
luck it I wonder sorry wrong I have to
go to Honolulu if I can't fly with Miss
Holly
well I'm sorry Tom but I think he's
gonna take the boat but it would be a
lot quicker you've got by of time if
it's because you think I can't handle a
control life and you like I said no you
have an actor that's right too and he's
really become a friendless life no you
mean I can't fly to honolulu with olas
that's exactly what I mean thank you but
I could make that's enough that's enough
for Virginia I all ready to take off
when I'm little in the morning
[Music]
I could act as copilot sir I said no how
do you do miss Allen how do you do
doctor doctor do you have a service
except all I wanted to know I wonder
what you meant by that lieutenant well I
think it has something to do with an
airplane flight dr. very long airplane
flight
[Applause]
[Music]
fula playing with you Julie a million
marine base calling the lady fern green
baize oscillating burn this place may be
good answering come in calif angle /
junior you forgot something forgot
something yeah your telephone i'ma
remember oh yeah I'm so sorry Billy so
you know how it is yeah that's right
that big lug listen wife Gauri when the
very telephone numbers around I'll take
them as usual not anymore there's a
little thought now ah ah did you get
that your big mug
[Music]
Oh
I