I first became aware of a movie called
the thing when I saw the original
through was nineteen fifty two and I
would have been about four or five years
old I think I saw it in re-release it
was one of those films where as you
watched it it was so frightening that my
popcorn came out of my my hands in other
words when they went up to the door away
and they had they had this a Geiger
counter he's any they opened the door
he's right there I'm with nuts I'm crazy
then I subsequently read the the short
story in high school and I realize it
was a lot different than the movie what
they'd done in the first film was kind
of make the the james arness monster
more like a Frankenstein creature and
yes he could he was a kind of a
vegetable that could reproduce various
life forms but he wasn't the the
imitator the creature that could imitate
any life form from the original story
the john w campbell story who goes there
was basically an Agatha Christie kind of
ten little indians you know this
creature is in your midst and he's
imitating either one or all of us whose
human and who is it and that that kind
of an idea really fascinated me so we
went in that sense back to that idea
with bill Lancaster and screenplay John
Carpenter was always our first choice
Stewart had some relationship with him
school Yoshiko
I knew John's work I did not know him
and so we had a meeting with him yes yes
yes and as soon as we had finished
escape from new york that was being
released i started to work on the thing
and we started writing from scratch
basically bill Lancaster wrote an
original screenplay and started all over
again there were several drafts of tobe
Hooper had done him I can't remember his
name now his partner had done a draft
and there had been some short story
treatments by various people but we
started over and studio like what we
were doing and proved it and off we went
it was I was reminiscing the other day
it was the longest prep that I've had on
the movie I haven't had one as long
since it was from the time I started
going in an office to the time the movie
was released was over a year the
business has changed so much now that
they'll only give you they try to
shorten your time on either end they try
to make you do it really quickly that
was one of the luxuries of the thing was
to have that much time to work on well
the short story itself was I wouldn't
say it was a really great when all
that's a very admired one in the
science-fiction realm back in the late
30s and I think it was the first story
to deal with this this shape-shifting
Body Snatcher type element and all that
stuff seriously that's not what a
hundred percent attracted me to the
piece it was more the ambience and as
all the characters involved and the mood
of it and the enclosure elements of the
paranoia and the short story was to a
stepping stone to take advantages of all
those kinds of elements from the story
and the film I loved the idea of being
trapped in Antarctica these people
working up there for whatever reasons
horrible winter freezing conditions cold
and is a monster 13
trying to talk about how to how to
approach making the movie is difficult
each one has its own personality what
basically you start with is an idea for
a director of photography you want to
begin meeting production designers you
want to begin the process of setting up
how to make the movie and one of the big
keys to me in making the thing was
discovering John Lloyd he said I had
come from low-budget filmmaking and I
had never really worked in a studio
situation and John I came along with
enormous enthusiasm and knowledge and a
great I but essentially I was working
for universal studio at the time and the
thing the script came across my desk and
I said you know reddit said my god this
is probably the best science fiction
films i've ever read in my life and then
I heard about john carpenter he was
coming on the lot and everybody's
reputation and i made a connection with
one of the production managers to talk
to him and then arrange an interview and
I took my drawings and things that can
talk to John and ended up
shawn i met john i'm not sure what year
it was but it was just before halloween
it was it was for Halloween Deborah Hill
introduced us and we John decided that
we would probably make a good team and
so he worked on Halloween and that I
guess was such a good experience for
both of us that we began a series you
know and I worked on the fog and escape
from new york and then subsequently the
thing and so I guess we went through
this over that formative period together
you know the the work I did with John
and pictures we did together I think
we're at that period some very
challenging ones from me and also a lot
of fun because they allowed us to sort
of experiment and work on visual style
basically it's a process of lining up
the people to do the movie and the one
of the crucial decisions we had to make
was on the special effects and whether
or not to hire what kind of an effects
person to go with him what kind of a
concept to go with and I chose Robbo
team I saw a Halloween and I instantly
became a John Carpenter fan he was you
know that film is just amazing it amazed
me and I had the fortune of working on a
picture which was a roger corman film
rock'n'roll high school I met Dean cundy
he did an amazing job I'm Halloween was
also big fan of him as a cinematographer
director of photography and I begged him
to introduce me to john carpenter you
know I said I gotta work with this guy
so i went in and i met john and he was
shooting the fog and I you know I said
you know what do you have any creepy
kind of characters that you know are in
this movie I said I'd love to play it
you know you got anything like the guy
with a mask and Halloween or whatever as
a matter of fact I do you know and
actually just sort of burst in on this
meeting you know and he's going through
this guy Dean right and I'm like going
I'm your big fan right and you know I
asked him this question then he said
stand up I thought he was gonna say and
get out all right you know when I was
hitting them up for this this part you
know and he looked at me a second guess
you got the job be there tomorrow you
know you got to do this with a makeup
that this so I got to work with him and
I was very happy and we had a good
working relationship and really had a
lot of similar interests and things and
he said guess what i'm going to do
you know and I said you're kidding
you're gonna remake the thing and he
said yeah so that's the idea around he
says I want you to make things right and
I went oh my god this is fantastic and
you know actually after I did the fog I
actually did a picture called the
howling and it was such a big success
for me and I was about 20 years old when
I did that and I think I finished up a
project when I was 21 and John saw the
movie you know and he called me up one
day and he said you got to get in here
we're doing the movie now you know we're
doing the thing yeah you got to get in
here he came in with a wild concept
which is that the thing can look like
anything it doesn't look like one
monster it looks like anything and out
of this changing shape this imitation
comes all the creatures throughout the
universe that the thing is ever imitated
and it uses these various forms and rob
was a very daring in his approach I must
say even sometimes I was doubtful as to
whether he pull it off because I got an
idea because we gotta because we got a
great storyboard artist on this movie
named mike ploog right and you know and
he says you should go down to the
universal art department meet this guy
and I said
you mean Mike blue you like that and he
goes blue blue yeah I mean he was really
trying funny guy and he's like whatever
because he's a real funny guy you know
and I said yeah I go he did a lot of
great comics you know this guy's like a
you know I'm a big fan you know cuz I'm
like you know rabid comic book collector
ever since I was a little boy and I said
god you know mike ploog cool you know so
he says yeah why don't you go down there
and tell him what you just told me and
here's what I want you to do is sit
there with mine and he goes and I want
you to go through all the scenes and I
want you two to show what it is you just
told me shot by shot and it's just
because he goes that's the only way we
can do this thing right so it took a you
know a couple of weeks to get all this
stuff down then after we had finished
the storyboard process I piled them all
up you know went walking back up to you
know carpenters office and he said let's
see what you got you'd like that and we
pinned them all up on the wall covering
all of his office walls then again he
looked at me and he said do you know how
to do all this stuff and I said no you
know so that that's what that that was
really the challenge of that picture and
what was great about it was that John
actually did give me a great opportunity
to say hey kid you know go nuts you know
and use your imagination and he was so
supportive during the whole process that
it was just you know a real amazing
thing to happen to a 22 year old well we
started to casting the thing and
realized very quickly that we had to be
realistic and although there are women
who work in the Antarctic and that that
would be a real thing to put them in
there it's more fun I think I thought at
the time to make this an all male movie
simply because you wouldn't have to deal
with that issue they had a girl in the
couple of women in Hawks's version and I
thought maybe it would be a more of a
streamlined approach in an all-male
movie I hadn't seen one in a long
and I started casting with Kurt Kurt
Russell wanted to play the lead and he
was the kind of rich pin and we looked
at every good actor we could find and
assembly great chaos John was trying to
cast the the role of McCready and we
spent some time together talking about
that thinking trying to think of other
actors I wasn't involved in the movie
and he was casting the movie and had
some of the other roles cast pretty much
when he was not finding what he wanted /
McCready and I gave him some suggestions
and we just his friends we were just
talking about it and then with a bad I
guess it was about three weeks ago or
months maybe less than that he came to
me said would you what would you think
about playing it and so then I really
read it and said yeah I thought it'd be
a lot of fun way at that time we were
going to try to do definitely as
strictly ensemble piece where McCready
was just one of the group and very
slowly came out of the group to have to
sort of deal with the vein at the very
end and that kind of changed slightly
once we discovered that we had that you
know these makeup and these wardrobe
problems where everybody looked the same
that was asked to come in for another
row like
who left me I can't remember what it was
and after I got there John and I were
talking and we had known each other
socially a little bit and I said listen
what do you think about Clark the dog
handler he said I haven't really focused
on that role yet and I said well that's
the one that interests me the most and
he said really and I said yeah he said
why and I said I because there's
something about him the fact that he's
more connected to the animals than he is
to the people I see him as a kind of
loaner sort of strange other entity in
the in the group and I think he liked
that in it and I like the fact also he
was sort of the red herring the one that
everybody thought was going to be the
carrier and we had the whole cast
together and we went over to Universal
and we SAT around the table of the first
couple of days and talked about the
script and talked about what characters
needed and wanted and so on and so forth
Lily worked on mostly the psychological
aspects of it that's what was most
interesting at least the way that the
script stripped of all the special
effects when you first read the script I
never read the monster turns here scene
so we had a chance to work on that first
and probably good because once we
started shooting the technical aspects
p.m.
take predominance it ended up being
great for me because I I was the one who
got to work the most with Jed the wolf
dog and when ral he who raised and
trained Jed and I got to be good friends
and and Jed and I got to be good friends
he was a very spooky dog when we started
because he was half wolf and half dog
and and the wolf half was a real
dominant and him he he did everything
like a wolf he would never bar he never
growled but the minute he would become
uncomfortable he would just so suddenly
go and you just went oh oh wait a minute
and he did that with me sometimes and
you know Clint had warned me if you see
you see this look on his face just relax
try and relax it you know he's something
spooked him in you never knew what was
going to spook him he was not very
experienced working around people so we
had to really lock the set down whenever
would Jed was on the stage and because
he had to do that one scene where he
went through the entire room and went
underneath the pool table and everything
he had to go past almost everybody in
the company so we were in rehearsals for
two weeks which was it's interesting
John originally I thought it was a great
instinct he'd never done it before but
to put this group of 12 people together
and then try and figure out what the
dynamics were going to be between them
you know who didn't like who who felt
you know who would react this way in
this circumstance and we came up a lot
of very interesting stuff in that
process but also we took some of the
control away from John and in the
process too because we really bonded and
we got very interestingly involved with
each other
cuz of that I remember at one point in
the pre-production John Lloyd came to me
and said okay here's here are our
options we're going to have to go
probably up to British Columbia and
shoot this on a glacier in looking for
somewhere to build the set before the
Antarctic ice camp they opted for
Stewart British Columbia because it was
purportedly one of the highest snow
falls areas accessible easily we scouted
it I believe was in the this summer when
it was still warm relatively warm and
the location we had chosen on this
hilltop overlooking at glacier was still
essentially dirt so that they could
build the camp so we were i would say
six months ahead of when we would
shooting when we would be shooting we
were choosing a spot it was a little
Knoll on top of a mountain that was
accessible by a one-lane Road that was
also used by the mining company the mind
would had only been open briefly and it
was shut down after that so it was kind
of a unique thing to find because you
just don't drive on top of glaciers and
you don't do it and here is this place
and it it worked it was just right there
and I the only one problem there were
trees to one side so I built the set
side of the set to hide that under
Monell shootings they want to see it but
I was really extremely happy with always
you know I thought it it looked right
my responsibilities were the opening
title sequence which involved
fabrication of the miniature spaceship
which was actually built by a person
named susan turner this is a spaceship
from the opening sequence of thing used
in two shots it's principally made of
ABS plastic I made out of that so we
could could help hold all the heat that
would be generated by these hundred and
forty-four lights we have circulating it
has a lot of brass etched pieces
including the grill around the outside
the vents the dome the exhaust I did
that because I wanted maximum detail
possible which is not possible in my
opinion was styrene I like the brass
it's painted with the many shades of
grades airbrush painted I by hand
masking techniques there's also a light
in the dome which has made of hammered
brass it was actually flat when it was
etched in it was hammered into shape in
would form I wanted you to be able to
see the lights at a continuous intensity
through the grating instead of hot
little hot spots or what usually would
get with a grain of wheat light when
there's a infinite values of intensity
and speed on this too so when we got in
and saw what speed we need to have it go
out to give the right effect we would
have them we would have the option of
making a go making the lights go faster
or slower or be brighter or a dollar
we shouted apogee four passes the
spaceship pass the past with the
swirling lights to give it the motion
which is presumably powering the ship
there's another pass with a little light
on the top in the dome where presumably
the the creature is steering the ship
and we also shot a mat pass the actual
title itself when I did the effect for
the title what I used when the title
comes you know the spaceship flies by
and and then the title comes and burns
on the way that that was done we had
like a fish tank that was about four
feet wide by two feet high and I put
smoke in the fish tank and then on the
back of the fish tank I put the title
the thing I drew it on an animation cel
behind that I had a piece of garbage bag
plastic which I stretched over a frame
and behind that I had a light which was
pointed up through the letters and when
I photographed it I hit the garbage bag
plastic with a little flame you know
like a match I would just light it
around the garbage bag plastic and then
the garbage bag plastic would open up
and let the light come through the
letters and that's how the letters look
like they form and you know and burn on
with the Rays and everything it was
actually a very simple process to to do
and look pretty good although we went
through a lot of takes 11 take actually
opened up forming the letters ng I
delivered the spaceship to Universal 2l
whitlock shop and that's what they used
to paint from i worked with it with
Albert Whitlock fur for the first and
only time I've worked with him I've been
a great fan of his work and he's a man
of unique talent he does an amazing
amazing things with
paint and brush and he did for us he
created this giant flying saucer in
middle of snow at a scale we couldn't do
and he solved some lighting problems for
us because painting a snowscape with the
correct light on it is not as easy as as
you might think we had to do a lot of
work on that but I'm extremely proud of
what he did and it worked out great well
the career in university started off
really with the boat Hitchcock called me
in and I introduced himself as somebody
little book with him in England and he
really didn't believe it actually
laughter I talked to him for a while he
got to realize that I knew things that
were absolutely authentic and then he
got interested well after that there was
torn curtain marni all the films that he
worked on her that he made after that I
did work on as he liked doing that shots
I mean he like doing anything like their
earthquake was a very difficult movie in
as much of universal indulge in the
luxury of fucking films into the movie
houses before they were even started so
there was a 12 week schedule and there
were 40 pieces of film to be done
hindenburg lasted almost a year but
there were 70 odd scenes on that but the
whole film was George Scott's at the end
when the film is finished said it's his
picture not mine
well a burr whitlock I had men on
Hindenburg cuz I had been kind of
liaison with Albert on Hindenburg and I
knew Albert very well got along with him
very well and really was I think one of
the shining periods of my career that I
got to watch Albert at work and watch
him do all his magic all the matte
paintings had a appropriate storyboard
so we knew generally what you were
supposed to see very often we had an
element that would be a live-action a
shunt for component than that and that
would just be cut in for the appropriate
length and then you would just wait
until I'm Albert delivered his work and
then you just cut in his little
masterpiece in a way you win and they
dribbled in all the way through the
making he would photograph say the
bottom half of the frame out on the ice
field or the top happened part of it
whatever was important for that and then
take the film back to Hollywood not
develop it he would store it in the
refrigerator cutting off just a very
small piece of it so that they could
develop just that or for testing and
core line up and then painting a
painting to match so it was actually an
interesting process for me to go through
i I've worked with him subsequently a
couple of times to to look at really
sort of one of the Hollywood masters and
how he did his particular about
technique but essentially what we did is
we just built a portion of a spaceship
and we planted then Albert what like
created this larger space ship out of it
but the big problem is getting the
spaceship there we had to hook up to a
helicopter and drop it
and then we went to shoot the the match
shots and Albert wanted to wait till
evening you know let's get the magic
colouring and we waited too long and the
helicopter came was waiting and we
waited we waited and finally Albert says
once more and the guy said now look this
is it we're leaving and so I never they
all had this heavy gear and we try to
get in a helicopter I couldn't get the
door shut so regardless of that we took
off I mean that was it was the end of
the day and then the guy gets partway
toward the can't he said my god I think
I'm going to run out of fuel nope and
then I say well if we run out of feel a
little happen well with this land he
said well spend the night and I could
imagine spending the night news
helicopter was six or eight people you
know it's but we did we finally made it
back and everybody was happy except the
pilot he said he really we didn't
realize you know really what kind of
trouble we were in but again ignorance
is bliss and in most cases that we had
to find a piece of high ground on the
backlog because I didn't like working
from a tower unnecessarily anyway
because the back lot at that time is
very plain and very hilly so we found a
high spot and laid the sheets out and
just place the people in the appropriate
position the vital issue in making a
match of work is having things standing
in space if it doesn't look as though
what your painting is actually in space
dimensionally in space receiving problem
which doesn't necessarily simply mean
the dissipation of color and tone that's
simple but still to get the feeling that
it's best standing in space you don't
achieve that you don't achieve anything
just looks like a painting remains two
dimensional that's the main thing you're
worried mming at clouds of course help
you get there
one of the things we were looking for
was how to really create the feeling of
cold how to get breath from the actors
mouths and we'd heard all the various
stories that you know people in the film
business had been trying up till then
The Lost Horizon stories and so forth
and we decided that refrigerating the
stages was really sort of the best thing
we found out that it doesn't have to be
really cold as long as the humidity is
up so it was a very careful balancing
act of humidifying the air spraying
water over head to bring the that and
then bring the temperature down which
happened at one of the hottest summers
in Los Angeles in a long time so it was
very strange for us to work in this very
kind of cold environment and then step
outside in our Park is in 102 degree
heat to watch the tourists going by on
the transit on the tour and have them
wonder why are these people wearing less
clothing and it was sweltering so more
people got flu and cold and that pic
they'd come out wearing that Parker
freezing they come out in the sweltering
they take off that Parker now they're
hot then they'd go back in they put it
back on it was so confusing the thing
that I remember the most was all of us
we got so tired of changing to go to
lunch that we would just go to lunch in
our complete little outfits in this
brutal heat and just you know and just
kind of blow it off and go well it's
going to be real hot getting over there
and then I'll get there will be
air-conditioned and it won't be that
terrible I remember that I also remember
for about three days or so I was showed
up in the commissary every day with a
big ugly bullet hole in my phone to eat
lunch the end you know and I wouldn't
come in and I go yeah you should
probably put me in a corner where
everybody doesn't have to look at me
because it was pretty disgusting but and
there were other people who showed up
you know with pieces of them hanging off
to go to lunch it was
we were we were quite a sighted on the
universal out there the thing for me was
on the thing was that the production
designing of the movie was so perfect
that my job was easier I could
concentrate instead on the acting
telling the story and the monster I mean
that was the big job was to convince the
audience that this thing is real and we
might have convinced him a little too
much
robbo Tina has a great sort of strange
imagination and of course is his
characters likewise the the creatures
and so forth I was really intrigued and
challenged by the fact that we would be
doing some things that hadn't been done
up to that point in creating these
illusions we tried all kinds of things
cranking the camera faster and slower
and and under cranking and shooting the
camera upside down to the backwards
action looked somehow strange a lot of
different sort of photographic
techniques one of the one of the tricks
with working with rubber whether it's
you know a mask or a makeup appliance or
whether it's completely fabricated
creature is is lighting it carefully so
that it it looks real so that there's a
you don't give away the tricks the
little seams in the paint and the wires
and and all of the things that are
necessary to make it work and rob was
rob was always very sensitive about his
creatures there was you know whether
there was too much light on them it we
always sort of joked that if it was up
to rob he would build the creatures you
know to be incredibly interesting an
imaginative and then not put any light
on him because he was afraid of showing
them so it was always a case of Rob
wanting less light less light you know
so we we developed techniques of little
tiny spots of light and shadows and also
that you you never really looked
blatantly at a rubber creature I went to
visit Rob on the set he wanted me to
help shoot some tests that he was doing
I was vibrating dog and I think when I
got there there were so many five-gallon
pails of KY jelly all over the place
that it's like my my impression of the
film was GI I never knew that you could
like buy KY jelly and in you know
five-gallon pails and have so many of
them you know
in any one place you know they used so
much of it I believe on all of all of
his creatures but that's kind of what I
think of when I when I you know think of
working on the health and you'd walk
into their model room we see what they
were going to eventually come up with
because they were modeling clay I guess
before they started the workmen making
you and it was incredible to see and i
must confess i think i spent about ten
days with them all told they molded my
face and a lot of different expressions
then with my hands my legs torso they
even took photographs of my chest
without a shirt on and they assigned one
person to make the hair pattern match
and it was so good but the day we shot
the sequence of my chest exploding i was
inside the examining table that my body
was supposed to be lying so that when
head was out it was really my head my
neck my shoulders and my arms and
everything else was the model and
richard dysart is an old alma and played
the doctor the medical doctor came in
that morning i was already in the
harness and he said but some clothes on
that guy for god sakes disgusting and it
came running over and it wasn't until he
was right on Tommy didn't realize that
was fake it was so incredible when I see
the picture I know what my chest hair
pattern looks like from looking at
myself married for 50 years I'm shot how
accurate is and actually uh it was very
funny because it was a one-take
situation we had to make him up and
blend this whole body off that had this
interior mechanism that would rip open
right and what happened was is of course
take one goes awry you know after you
know you know 10 hours of makeup right
and Charlie sitting inside this box and
was working on his stuff you know the
cameras are all set tweaking the
lighting you know getting it all set up
putting a little beads of sweat on him
and fixing his hair making sure the
rubber doesn't look these shiny and all
this stuff John says action right the
thing rips open and I wanted to have
like a lot of saliva flying
place and unfortunately what happened
was is it looked like a fountain in Las
Vegas it came out and it just looked
like there should be show girls dancing
out of his stomach and stuff and John
goes cut thank you very much mr. bottini
like that he guess what happened you
know he goes that was horrible do you
like that he gets to look like a
fountain in Las Vegas right and and you
know Charlie's going like wait a minute
you know do we got to do this all over
again yeah look no I go yeah Charlie
really sorry John goes wait a minute
what do you mean and I go well the
stomach ripped open you know we gotta
you know take this all apart and put a
whole new one and John goes we got to do
this tonight giving them going like oh
my god you know so on the thing take two
men hours right so we had to you know
clean Charlie up take them out put a
whole new skin on this thing and come
back and do it again and the second time
we got it you know when it ripped open
you know but that wasn't the end of it
and it was about 6 30 or seven by
filming at the second gen I spent the
entire day strapped in his harness took
my back a week or two to recover but
that everyone was pleasant fact the
worst part was every one every two
seconds I'm i say y'all right charlie
all right John I said just don't talk to
me when we actually get to the scene or
the actual shot within the sequence
where of who you don't Nora sir Charlie
you know has a stomach open and it's
actually going to bite down on the
doctors arms you know what we did is we
came in on it on a shot where you would
actually see the mechanism open and we
had you know the the doctor and actually
put his arms in and then start to close
the machine right and then we cut and
what we do is is we come to another
angle right where we've actually
replicated the
doctors arms perfectly making it out of
jell-o right we made the arms at a jello
we had wax bones built into the arms and
we had rubber veins and gelatin veins
and all this stuff so it was like you
know living tissue and at this point
what we did was we actually took a mold
of the actors face that was playing the
doctor and what we did was we actually
found the guy that had no arms his arms
were actually cut off here right in an
injury an industrial accident right and
a very very great job guy you know this
guy and we basically made a a prosthetic
that actually looked exactly like the
doctor included on this person's face
and we glued the gelatin arms on to his
arms right so we have him in there and
what happens is that the stomach is
actually hydraulic you know so it's made
out of something that would be like you
know same device that a tractor works
with and could pick up you know a lot of
you know wait and when this thing
slammed shut it actually rips right
through the jello punctures the plastic
things which sends blood flying all over
the place and then the you know the
actor but no arms it pulls his arms out
and now he's just got the prosthetic
damage you know on and blood shooting
all over the place you know and that's a
really good shot in a movie you know I
mean that that that one was really tough
to do and very inventive you know very
tough to do I would even be scared to do
that again that sequence is so etched in
the minds of people who see this movie
everywhere I have ever been in the world
someone has spoken to me and I could you
know everywhere I've ever been I do a
lot of traveling someone comes up to me
on the street and speaks to me about
that movie in about that sequence
specifically then we actually had to
start getting the the footage of his
head coming on and you know I
sleep for this shot couldn't use Charlie
hallahan right so he actually made like
a perfect replica of this guy's head and
and fully you know animated it you know
with the mechanical effects and whatnot
you know and in it had a hydraulic ram
that would actually stretch the neck out
and sever the rubber at exactly a
perfect point and again this was only
like you could only do it in one take
all right and when it when it stretches
open and the skin rips what I wanted to
see inside was something that was very
reminiscent of like what's in a comic
book where we see you stretching if it's
like really stringy stuff so we really
didn't know how to make that stuff you
know and there was nothing that would
sort of stretch that far so what we did
was we just started you know melting
plastic and and getting bubble gum you
know in making this crazy concoction
that I'm sure was like so toxic you know
is it couldn't be good for you right
what we did is we right before the shot
you know we had you know the whole
replica of hallahan body and we actually
had this this goo that we would pile in
there really quick and and the whole
time it's giving off fumes like paint
thinner and lacquer thinner at all this
kind of stuff and again we have effects
guys buried in the little table
underneath to operate the stuff and then
all these guys that have rehearsed the
motion of the neck coming off and
everything without doing a split camera
setup right everybody's going like
what's that smell you know and I'm going
oh it's the you know it's a stuff inside
the neck you know some nutty concoction
we made that will stretch you know
bubblegum and whatnot plastic melted
down there going like that it doesn't
smell too good you know so go well we
better hurry up and shoot it right so
camera said everything's ready and then
carpenter goes wait wait a minute wait a
minute shouldn't there be fire he like
underneath the the lands here you know
everybody goes why and he goes well
because they're burning they're burning
everything around them and this is the
shot where the you know like the you
know the head stretching off but
nobody's seeing it so just for
continuity want a little fire in the
foreground you know meantime nobody's
thinking about it and I didn't either
but the room is filling up with you know
explosive fumes
right so so finally you know the effects
guy gets a fire you know there's like a
thing called a fire bar which is
basically a pipe with a bunch of little
holes drilled in it much like you know
you would have in a fireplace it works
with gas puts it underneath the lens out
of sight and you know John says okay
everybody set ready to go you know I go
ready all the guys ready or bees ready
thumbs up hey you and there i'm knocking
in a little you know box you know you
guys you know you're ready in there were
do you like that okay great you know so
Johnson roll camera right so they roll
camera right he is alright light the
fire bar guy turns on the gas Shh you
know if the stuffs coming out guys up
there with that with a you know like a
lighter you don't ease and finally it
ignites right and the whole effect the
whole hallaghan you know replica body
explodes right the whole room goes into
this huge fireball with a whole crew
sitting in right because this is a small
set and when the fire clears everybody's
sitting there like in a cartoon you know
their face is black but you know nobody
had black faces but they were all going
you like this and I'm staring down at
the at the body and I'm in shock because
since the one take deal only I look down
at it and I go oh my god it's on fire
right it's on fire and then John says
don't just stand there put it out you
idiot like that at them and then I was
just so shocked at months of work
preparing for this moment was just blown
to bits and just a second so we you know
put it out with fire extinguishers and
stuff like that and then he just go oh
my god we had to set up take a whole
nother day to get back to this point and
finally just accomplished the one shot
where they had stretches and the next
hours all of us had had made a trip to
the shop I had to get this little thing
done for my head
everything we all made a trip over there
some of them like David and Charlie had
to have very complicated things done so
I haven't spent much time there but when
we were at the shop Robert already
started sculpting a lot of the things
like he's scope to diffuse bodies that
we find in the Norwegian camp and that
was lying on the floor when I walked by
the first time and I just remember
thinking this is this is incredible art
this is an amazing grotesque art that
he's created here the same thing with
the big fused dog think it was actually
before they put all the hair and in a
slime and everything and I'll that pink
slime that will let drippy stuff in it
and the pieces of king crab claws or
whatever the hell he used for that
before he put all that stuff on it it
was an amazing piece of sculpture just
beautiful I mean grotesque horrible but
also very beautiful so what I did was I
was so you know wanting this stuff to
come out so great I actually lived
universal for a year and five weeks
without taking a day off I work you know
seven days a week never took a day off
you know and it was their night and day
night and dad sleep on the sets you know
a carpenter would come in where's Rob
you know he's them the he's in a locker
room you know four or he's in the lab
you know and then he'd wake me up hey
you know we got to shoot this thing or
whatever and I ended up you know working
so hard that I ended up in the hospital
at the end of the show john looked at me
he said you don't look well think of
somebody take this guy to the hospital
right you know but since then you know
I've wised up and you know it's uh I
don't do that anymore when it comes to
the creature effects on on the thing
it's this is rob obtains movie I mean
and there was no kind of no loss for you
know incredible effects it was it was a
pretty hungry movie when it gets down to
that aspect of it we came in actually
with you know Rob's request because it
was an overload period where I think he
had sum some seven million creature
effects going on and talked to me about
possibly picking up one of the effects
as some of the overload which happened
to be the the dog thing at the beginning
of the movie it was we were just getting
heavily into this new element of
puppetry and animatronics coming
together at my studio and since I like
Rob a lot and I've also worked with John
Carpenter before and it was a fairly fun
and simple situation for us to have
jumped into it it's one of the first
effects that you see in the movie these
dogs have been taken over by by the
thing so I attacked it in a way of
figuring out a way of how to do it
simplistically how to do quickly and
economically and also create a you know
a pretty nifty effect and so we attacked
it as literally a puppet so when you do
see this effect in the movie I remember
looking at myself in the mirror I'm
going how how easily can I puppet
something if this is the head because
we're just starting to get into puppetry
at that point in our studio and had us
do a snapshot of me just holding my hand
like this as a human being so that it
was this is about the most intricate and
amazing a machine anybody could build
and then from that snapshot of me
standing it just like this with my hand
just like this we designed the dog thing
over that though it was formed following
function we did not create freely we
created based on the machine that was
going to to make this thing work and
when you actually see this dog thing in
the movie you will see that there's this
hump this interesting hump it is
meant that comes out this really cool
head that comes around and it's snarling
and going through all these gyrations
and it has all this wonderful organic
movement and it's basically because all
that organic movement is the person
inside it who was disguised by the
design so it came up with a concept
designed to that concept and literally
built a really cool hand puppet with an
animatronic face we literally came in to
help out to take a little bit of this
overload and to do a really fun
character and a neat creature and a neat
effect but it wasn't for the credit and
it wasn't for the film it wasn't my film
it was Rob's film and he should be very
proud of it I'm thrilled for him and I'm
I think what he did standing some of the
neatest effects we've seen and I'm glad
that we have a cool effect in the film
the big scene in the kennel thing first
makes its appearance set it on fire
flame through and then put out the fire
was one of the most exciting things I've
ever worked on that's a seven or eight
cameras nine actors with fire
extinguisher and we really had win and
put out the fire and the state was
elevated 15 feet or so above the floor
so there were real firemen underneath
there was a lot of safety apparatus for
us but I remember that you know usually
we roll them marker action all those
cameras clacking him flames building up
from the gas jets and us waiting and
then finally the call we always really
put out that fire it was really
wonderful the kennel sequence is
basically broken into two areas which is
one first a dog transforming in front of
the dogs and then the point which humans
see it and at the point at which the
human see it it was very important to
also understand that what again we were
looking at was in amorphous shape that
you know you could really call a thing
so when the big mass or the dog or what
it is transformed to pulls itself up in
the corner of the ceiling they're trying
to back up an escape you know from these
guys and the dogs and everything it just
wants to be left alone you know it's got
no
to go you know so basically you know
these guys are looking at it and they go
to torch it and what happens is that it
you know rips open and then this you
know this really strange kind of
formation comes out that looks much like
a flower and in essence if you go back
and you know freeze frame what it
actually is it's not a flower it's it's
about like I don't know how many dog
tongues it's a bunch of dog tongues and
there's dog teeth growing out of the out
of the thing and I wanted something
there that you know actually you know in
the mind would sort of be you know
something the dog used to be and has now
you know changed into something that is
like a twisted nightmare the burn I
remember the burn when when David
Clinton's eruption and then we burned
him at us that was probably the biggest
effector that we all worked and the guy
who did the burn Alyssa understand but
he's a specialist at dunnes full body
burns and that was very impressive and
spooky to be a part of because what
happens is he's got he can't breathe
once he's ready to go because of
congressional Sierra's lungs he has to
do the whole thing holding his breath
and it's all a matter of timing and then
the minute he came off he had to be put
out and immediately you know freed so he
could draw a breath and soon when I
started seeing some of the effects that
Rob head and created there was one in
particular one particular sequence where
Charlie how a hands head comes off the
table and that tongue shoots out and it
pulls across turns over and grows stocks
and lots of 12th floor when I saw that I
realized a great sense of relief because
what I didn't want to end up with in
this movie was a guy in a suit see I
grew up as a kid watching science
fiction in western movies and it was
always a guy in a suit or sometimes it
was a kind of bad puppet like
if conquered the world comes to mind
right now Roger Corman's movies and a
vegetable monster kind of going like
this wooden Lee and my fear was they'll
laugh at us you know delica there'll be
a joke I mean even as great as the movie
was an alien was a terrific movie it's
still in the very end up stood this big
guy in a suit no I don't want to do a
suit you know I want something that's
that's alive so I was when I saw that
stuff coming out I was like man now
there were some effects we had to fool
with they didn't work perfectly does
this stuff is not like his Rob said to
me it's not like ordering pizza on the
phone you have to build it and create it
and sometimes it doesn't work in our
case I think it did
you've got to be fucking kidding
bravoteens did the special makeup
effects and Roy are big ass did the the
set special effects the explosions and
so forth but they work together in one
area and that was in terms of certain
construction for the thing certain size
Rob couldn't handle in other words his
little team could go so far so they
enter intermeshed at one point and begin
a collaboration to pull off that last a
creature coming up coming up out of the
floor and opening up that was a huge
monstrosity the size of it was amazing
so we had a lot of work to do the first
part which was the the pass where he
actually has to run underneath the
floorboards that was done by Roy
Arbogast and what they did was they
built actually like a train track
underneath the floorboards they put like
a huge ball metal ball on it and they
actually dragged it with a huge table
mounted to a winch that actually was a
high speed winch they just flipped the
thing and then this ball would roll in
and you can just break all the
floorboards up and that look very
impressive then what we what we see is
the floor being ripped up and now we see
this you know image of Wilford Brimley
rising up by out of this hole you know
sort of stuck to a huge tentacle you
know with all these tentacles that were
riding off of it his chest actually rips
open this dog starts to struggle out and
because we wanted to open up the scope
of what we were seeing we decided to use
animation and there's this guy you know
a randy cook who's brilliant at
stop-motion animation i worked with
Randy before and known known for quite a
while and asked him if he would actually
do this you know the wide shot which
would basically be the worm you know the
Blair monster you know comes up through
the floor and now we were back really
far we see oh god it's huge you know and
tentacles come flopping out on the deck
you know and then you know we'll cut to
a medium shot of the dog actually
starting to rip through you know
Brimley's you know chest and then we'll
come back to the wide shot and actually
see the dog bleep out and land on the
floor right in front of Kurt and so
actually Randy and his crew set to
making a miniature version of the whole
set it was absolute beautiful didn't you
know really wonderful the miniatures for
the sequence there goes in was inside a
room that had a lot of oil cans and some
other miniature pieces I can't explain
exactly you know what it is guy named
Jim Bella hovik and again susan turner
who built the spaceship for the
beginning of the film Randy I screen
Randy cook the animator asked me to make
it on a two-and-a-half-inch to a quick
scale that seemed to be a good size for
him to work with so we made a rather
large one and of course it has to be
very solid to do dimensional animation
you have to have a very solid solid base
and we made it very solid made it so
apart broke away so when the floor
exploded Randy could get right in there
and work additionally when we built it
we built it with no supports in the
middle of the floor so that they could
have the creature come up at any point
we hadn't quite decided yet and of
course we have icicles hanging from the
top which were use silicon for because I
couldn't be moved either you know frame
by frame shooting you can't you can't
disturb anything everything has to stay
exactly the same I tried a copy of the
live set exactly I mean it was rather
difficult with the ice cave because it
was just jagged cave and so we had we
had to measure each bar part out and
make it exactly the right to mention so
it would match I like to make it look
absolutely I know a lot of people like
to take shortcuts but I do I think it
look exactly right because I think
there's no substitution for having it be
exactly right mathematically and
visually in the final picture what
happened was his carpenter had it the
sequence cut together and felt that at
the end of the day his I could attack
that there was you know stop motion
animation in the picture and at this
point in time again the
you know since it was done you know many
years ago you know we actually didn't
have the use of a computer which would
kind of you know smooth out the
animation a little bit and so you know
John decided that now we're not going to
use the animation in the picture you
know even though it was beautifully
executed we all met at vancouver airport
and then we were going to fly to Prince
Rupert where we're going to get a plane
to Stuart British Columbia so we we flew
into Prince Rupert and as we were coming
down we realized there was a snowstorm
going on so we thought it'd be a little
dicey if we're going to take a small
plane and flying to Stuart so we get
into Prince Rupert and around eleven
o'clock at night they heard the entire
cast and this huge like Greyhound bus or
something by now it's continuing to snow
and snow is getting deep we're driving
along I remember Peter Maloney was sick
from from eating something and everybody
was kind of falling asleep and you know
it's the low love that that buses it's
driving more and we're all just about
out of it and suddenly we hear the bus
driver yells out slide slide so we all
wake up and the bus literally slides and
it starts going almost like off the
mountain I thought it was gonna like
back bounce off the mountain and
ricochet and throw us off the other side
there was no guardrail or anything and
it just plummeted for a thousand feet
because we're in the middle of these
snow covered mountains and so now if
this was a movie you cut to the next
shot all the whole cast we are up in
front of the bus surrounding the bus
driver with our eyes completely open and
we're driving it by ten miles an hour
now and we're just kind of glued to thee
we're glued to the road but Maloney's
still in the back it means he's sleeping
so about three o'clock in the morning or
who knows when there was like a motel
halfway to Stewart and we were going to
pull in there to see if we could get
some coffee make some phone I don't know
what but this it's continuing to snow so
it's a
really deep so this Greyhound bus has to
make a right hand turn and then go up
this hill into the parking lot of this
motel or something and the bus slides
and it gets stuck like right in that
depression where you go up and he
couldn't get the bus going so like we're
sitting here and I'm not sure but I'll
take credit I said why don't we all get
out lighting the bus and we can actually
push it on the ice or something so you
have this cast of amazingly talented
people getting out of this bus in the
middle of the night in canada and lining
up on this side of the Greyhound bus and
they start to push the bus where the bus
driver put it in gear and we actually
got it moving so that he could get back
up in LA well we got into the lot and
the motel was closed so we had to turn
the bus around and we got back on the
road and we drove for another two or
three hours we got into steward British
Columbia and five the morning carpenter
comes out into the old the street he's
like welcoming us he's all bright-eyed
bushy-tailed he slept and had coffee and
we're all like you know like we you know
it was we were a mess from being up all
night and and he said welcome to the
story that was our arrival in sturbridge
the conditions are almost unbelievable
to imagine shooting the movie and I
cactus um somehow there's a part of me
that wonders how we ever survived it we
we had such problems all the way down to
the cameras we couldn't he had to leave
them in the cold because we couldn't
take them from the warm out into the
cold inside and outside because the lens
is brewed would be missed up I mean the
whole approach was one of just trying to
push this giant giant rock up a mountain
we had we had no comforts and it was a
dangerous spot make no mistake about it
we were in a very dangerous spot she can
miss me and I think that some of the
reality of that showed I know the cast
members bonded together and they really
became their characters they were really
standing out in the snow dealing with
from there was a real camaraderie
because these guys I mean they got the
actors got into the business of being
scientists working together thrown
together I would imagine in the real
world a group of people in an isolated
environment would have to pull together
and be friendly and we did some reach
lots of research people go up there for
long stays they bring cassettes and
Records and books and that they would
get flown in like videos of super bowl
games and baseball games the actors try
to mimic them they tried to copy that
there's been some great scenes where all
12 men are looking at each other and
trying to figure out who's who if if you
are my best friend or if you are about
to thing out on me and kill me but my
favorite thing in this whole picture is
to be able to be up here in a location
like this and just be able to shoot up
here it's unbelievably fantastic when
the set was built and then it got snowed
in as we had hoped we were then going up
a snowy icy dirt road one lane with the
mining trucks coming down in radio
contact back and forth so the trip up
each morning and back in the afternoon
in the evening was was sort of a long
tedious and sometimes kind of scary trip
it was one of those things that paid off
because you know we were able to put the
set in a location that we would not have
been able to otherwise we lived in the
town of Stewart it's the one of the last
ice free port sigh believe so they
floated Abe I I guess you'd call the
logging camp barge dormitory into the
port and that was the crew housing
it was a large flat barge that had very
small cubicles ended with it with a bed
and it was very much a kind of a you
know college dorm situation for the crew
and and it I think it was it made the
adventure more interesting you know
there's a certain bonding that that
occurred with the the crew but of course
it was not the most luxurious conditions
the drive up from Stewart to the site on
the glacier was about 45 minutes of
unbelievable stuff every day we passed a
tan bald eagle seedings you know having
just killed Sam and eating them on the
side it on the snow you know blood
covered snow it was just amazing
everybody went up every day so there are
many days she just SAT around and did
nothing except without the beautiful
eyes that was the extraordinary thing we
even though it's 20 below the gear we
wore after a few days of acclimation
kept you warm and you could walk out on
these fantastic glacial distance the
three chords the way up this huge
glacier and that pale blue color the ice
stretched for miles and miles and miles
and miles down as it sloped down into
the valleys and white snow all around
you and just hints of the darkness of
mountaintops it's a sequence of images
I've never forgotten really powerful
I've never been that high up for any
length of time in in the mountains in
there in that kind of cold weather it
was just gorgeous so I felt that sets up
your hands a tremendous feeling a place
which was important because the movies
about on a psychological level is about
isolation even though there were a
number of us there each one of those men
at his own trap prison that he lived in
cut off from everything else except the
guys around him and the introduction of
this alien which couldn't be seen but
could be sensed
intensified that experience for each and
every guy in it and that that was I
thought the most interesting part of the
movie for me in fact I felt my character
dr. Norris new unconsciously that he had
been affected by the thing and in fact
in the sequence when they're trying to
side what to do when everybody's
flipping out and run all around around
the hallways and somebody i think it was
Tommy weights his character had a gun
and to talk about me they want to take
the control away from moffitt they asked
me and my character said I had no fellas
I just I just don't think I'm up to it
in in my mind he was responding to a
signal from the inside you really
understand logically something's wrong
he was the wrong guy and so anyway that
that business of being up there and
seeing that it's sense that you were
really alone nothing the wind cold all
those elements fabrics we won't have
that white situation over there running
right so I think we'll be okay what we
made more might want to do it we could
just do a little fullback
they're wearing a good idea to come back
out into here and then and then come
into situation that sounds good Megan
put Palmer pulling with the hydraulic in
front of the plate
good JOHN CARTER created a tremendous
atmosphere on the set it was very
positive it was supportive and it was
also it encouraged you to work hard
Jonathan few directors who can walk on
to a set and be faced with the scene
that may involve five or six people and
some complicated blocking and with no
preparation work with the actors and
arrive at a blocking that they're
comfortable with and not one that he
dictates to them and then decide on the
spot what the most effective coverage
for that scene is going to be that's a
rare talent in scenes as particular
scene I think which if insistent that
ability is the one in which the blood
was in the refrigerator they find a
refrigerator and it's all the Bloods on
the clorox been broken open that's a
difficult scene because you have a group
of people in the semicircle up against a
flat object and if you think about that
that's an exceptional challenge to shoot
effectively I mean one can take an easy
pop out shoot it from within the closure
of the half circle if you will and take
individuals on each but I think if you
look at that scene it's much more
complicated in terms of how he chose to
cover it i was very impressed with with
that scene and the one that followed
where windows runs down the hallway
what's the gun which i think is one of
my favorite scenes in terms of cutting
those two scenes in particular and jon
always gets just the right angles very
rarely i can't ever really think of a
time which i would say gee I wish I had
this orgy I wish I had and that's a
testimony to his ability
the reviews were mixed I think with the
audience and that they there was an
alternate ending to the film that was
shot I'd spoken to John about this I had
said that I thought well gee this is a
terribly nihilistic ending very much of
a downbeat perhaps we should protect
ourselves while we have the principal
courage and just shoot an ending that
where we see that he survives and John
was open to this so essentially what he
did was he staged to scene in which Curt
has been rescued and seeing in a kind of
small office structure and he's just had
a blood test so that we know that he's
not infected and he has survived this
ordeal rather than the kind of mutual
death that that concludes the film now
he just shot this for protection we
never previewed this the issue did come
up at the conclusion of the two previews
as to whether we should perhaps try this
ending see how it it flew with the
audiences and or make other adjustments
on the film and I think John essentially
at that time was about that he had
achieved in the movie what he wanted to
do he had made the story of who goes
there the short story from which the
original thing was adapting was much
truer to that which i think was one of
his intentions he was a great fan of the
original thing he and I watched it at
least two or three times I'm John
striving scene at 50 and it is a
wonderful film but he wasn't trying to
do that film he was in a sense trying to
go back to the to the source of it I
think he filled he felt he had
accomplished that and so that's the way
the film went out a lot of the things
though that bothered the audience more
than the monster were the poking around
the monster you know and poking around
human beings that had been burnt and it
was like we all associated to it in
terms of looks like getting a deer
it doesn't it's part of life hunt and
you take me you got the deer and it's
it's I guess it's ugly the first two or
three times you do it but then after a
while it's that's what you do with the
you take them out you remove them and
clean it get the meat clean then you cut
the meat up all that kind of when you're
doing it you if somebody's not used to
doing they look at that my god this is
this is this is horrible but then I'm
any problem going to the store and
buying that rap piece of meat so they
just don't see the other part of it so
on this movie you see that part we
realized that those parts were probably
going to be to a large degree rejected
again I thought it was great that John
didn't stop doing the movie that he set
out to do and I'm very happy that the
movie did find its audience and that it
found its audience 20 years or 15 years
later was it to a great degree expected
people always come up to me and say you
know I you know my favorite movie you
were in was I mean a lot of times this
happens but they come up with the thing
is the thing as the thing that they like
the best but it's a you know as someone
else's probably said this film found its
audience not in the theaters at the time
it wasn't a huge hit it did okay but in
video and on cable and since then on
video it's that it has a very loyal very
intense following and that's always fun
i mean i've been involved in several of
those that haven't gone through the roof
in the box office but in certain ways
have an afterlife that's much stronger
than films that have gone through the
surface it was so much fun to be with
that cast and that director and that
crew I mean you had like 60 little boys
with helicopters and flamethrowers and
guns a monster and we're up in the
Arctic and I mean it was a gas man it
was like it was like going out and
playing cops and robbers when you were a
kid it was just it was a fantastic
experience in a in a wild and
unpredictable place with that Justin
once again I have to say it just a
tremendous casting crew it was just so
much fun it's a good film and it's
turtle survived for that reason you know
might not be an instant success but I
feel that it has legs in the sense that
people will enjoy and probably more so
as yours I think that at the time when
the thing was released it it was an
innovative very kind of unusual journey
for an audience and I think that it came
across an interesting phenomenon which
was at the time we also had a very
friendly alien that came to visit the
earth in the form of ET and it was was a
case of an audience
at the time feeling probably more
comfortable with the friendly alien and
back that you know the sort of dark edge
of the thing was something that wasn't
so appreciated at the time I think the
the audience's sensibilities have always
sort of change and they're now sort of
prepared to accept an alien that isn't
so friendly in the shape of the thing I
really believe that if they had
separated the releases amount you would
have been a big hit at the box office it
since turned into what they call a cult
don't seem like everybody had seen it
video or on television or something it's
it set a standard for special effects i
think that the people who like that kind
of movie went and saw it anyway the
interesting thing about the thing right
and and the fact that it was actually
done a long time ago you know people
actually think that that you know the
imaging and the special effects and the
creature work would ever hold up to this
day even in even in the light of the
fact that you know there are computer
graphics and things now and i think part
of the reason for that is is that it's
you know you just can't beat wild
imagination you know and no matter how
you do it as long as it's executed very
well you know it that you just can't
pierce through the magic you know
actually it's really funny because i
watched a movie now and I can completely
pick it apart you know I mean I can
actually look at it and go you know I do
that differently now you know I could do
that better you know but but the fun
thing is is that everybody that you know
like I run into on the street or in the
movie business or whatever they always
say do you realize that you know your
monster creation and the thing was a
life-changing monster and I go what does
that mean and you know like I even have
kids that actually grew up watching it
on video and they say yeah it was just
so crazy you know and it just sort of
made us realize that you know you could
anything in the movies you know so it
was it's fun to have you know that you
know part in history is you know having
made something that was so wildly
imaginative that it's actually you know
caused others to come up with greater
premiums there are some movies that you
do I've done more I guess than my fair
share of them and I do think that you
know maybe that I have to sort of look
at that and realize something that I
have a tendency to like movies that
aren't gonna perhaps be accepted at the
time and if they're done well though
they will be accepted later on and I
think that with the advent of video
that's that's a great I i I'm very happy
about that because ultimately you're
making movies for the enjoyment of as
many people as possible and I like that
there's video and then people can take
it and make their judgment later on and
perhaps without the politics of the time
or without whatever's in the air at the
time to set a tone to get in the way of
just the project and just the story
itself there's a very somber a somber
kind of inevitability to the film as it
begins you're seeing a helicopter
whirring and they're chasing a dog and
already it's i feels like the end of the
world and that's what this is this is an
apocalyptic movie this is the first of
three films that I've worked on that
have an apocalyptic theme I've dealt
with them in different ways this is the
end of the world it doesn't come from
bombs dropping
it comes from within and it was a movie
that that's tone started and and
finished and basically it was almost
there's nothing you can do because here
it comes and of course the thing is a
metaphor for whatever you want to say
it's disease could be aids could be
whatever it comes from within you it's
all so basically the lack of trust that
that's in the world now we see it all
over countries people we don't trust
each other anymore we don't know who to
trust we're with somebody that that we
think may be there are loved ones and
they may attack us and that's what the
thing is it has a lot of truth in and
kind of dressed up as a monster movie
you