at some level this is clearly a man of
immense personal charm you want to
engage him when you hear this voice
coming out of the speakers he has that
quality he has a wonderful line and I
think it's from a book of mercy where he
says the heart is a rage of afflictions
and that's to me very close to what
Leonard is engaged with not just in the
poetry but in the song Lenna Cohen's
early body of work is unique in popular
music I think the parallels you have to
look outside music he's actually a poet
putting poems to music rather than a
songwriter writing songs that was really
what made him stand out from the crowd
that made you want to sit up and take
notice
my mind was growing in leaps and bounds
by just being with somebody like Leonard
you're talking about a very special a
very special deep person
you
Leonard Cohen was born in Montreal
Canada in 1934 raised within the city's
large Jewish community he was brought up
in an affluent middle-class household as
the son of a prominent businessman he
took an early interest in literature and
also in his Jewish heritage and the
Holocaust in particular in 1951 Cohen
graduated from high school and rolling
at the prestigious McGill University his
interest in literature had evolved and
he was particularly drawn to poetry and
the work of lorca Yates and Elliott
notable college lecturers and alumni
also began exerting a strong influence
upon his writing particularly Canadian
poetry's enfant terrible Irving Layton
in 1955 after a series of his poems had
been published in various magazines
Cohen's first collection was released
under the title let us compare
mythologies during the first program
they met behind the ruins of their homes
sweet merchants trading her love for a
history full of poems and at the hot
ovens they cunningly managed a brief
kiss before the soldier came to knock
out her golden teeth not only did the
book's publication spur Cohen on as a
poet its success gave him confidence in
another area women he tells the story
himself he said one of the ways of
wooing the lady was to quote poetry on
if he could call his own all the better
but obviously I mean that there's a
wider wider scenario here he's a he had
great friends and Montreal knows that
there's a writing scene in Montreal I
don't think they called them pubs but
they met in of an evening had a drink
and read each other poetry and he
himself ascertained that they were the
strictest critics you could ever hope to
have you know your friends and that that
I think was was great motivator
forum you together right of it if he
convinced his friends then he could move
on in the autumn of 1956 Cohen abandoned
his plans to study law and instead moved
south of the border to New York City and
Columbia University here he immediately
gravitated towards the coffee houses of
Greenwich Village where the poetry scene
was embracing the dawn of the beats a
year later he returned to Montreal upon
which he received a
three-thousand-dollar scholarship from
the Canadian Council and succeeded in
selling his next collection of poetry
the spice box of Earth you tell me that
silence is nearer to peace than pawns
but if for my gift I brought you silence
or I know silence you would say this is
not silence this is another poem and you
would hand it back to me it has some
merit I mean if you looked at it in
relation to American poetry being
published at that time and you're just
at the cusp of The Beat Generation
Howell is 1956 for example preceding it
it's pretty tame stuff but for Canada
whoa great here is a young writer found
his voice wasn't embarrassed to write
naked ly about subjects that other poets
had been much more discreet about that
would be the tradition of say EJ Pratt
who writes this wonderful best-seller
called the last spike and it's this long
poem about completing the railway across
the country that's the kind of subject
you'd find in Canadian poetry you
wouldn't you know find too much poetry
about being totally zonked on drugs and
trying to write you know music or poetry
which is what some of those poems are
about a lot of the other poems are very
personal and I think that was the other
thing that made it unique a kite is a
victim you are sure of you love it
because it pulls gentle enough to call
you a master strong enough to call you
fool
because it lives like a desperate train
falken in the high sweet air you can
always haul it down to tame it in your
drawer if you want to talk in purely
formal terms about the poetry writing
it's not original it's not Gerard Manley
Hopkins suddenly bursting on the scene
nor does it have the content of Yeats
but it's important for the Canadian
poetry scene at that particular time and
in a way he was emulating Irving
Leighton who was quickly becoming the
outrageous Bacchus figure of Canadian
writing at that particular time it's
still a little early but he had this
acquaintance with Leighton which grew
into a powerful friendship but lasted
until Irving Layton's death I mean
Layton's the man and and Leonard
certainly was attracted very powerfully
to Irving but of course he found his own
path after a brief spell in London Cohen
moved to the greek island of Hedra where
he immediately identified with the
artistic bohemian Muslim in September
1960 he bought a house there and over
the following five years produced two
very different novels he had started the
first the favourite game in London and
it was released to some claimed in 1963
the follow-up Beautiful Losers was
eventually released in 1966 after his
publisher insisted on rewrites the far
more ambitious and complex work it met
with some controversy on its release
favorite game is rather conventional
coming-of-age novel about a young man
discovering his identity of sexuality
and early experiences Beautiful Losers
breaks the mould Beautiful Losers is
brilliant brilliant and I think still
underrated Canadian novel because it
experiments with form and experiments
with history it integrates a story from
what the eighteenth 17th century
at the same time it tells us about the
so-called quiet revolution in Quebec but
it does it explosively we are now in the
heart of the last feature in the system
theater with in severe limits like smoke
in a chimney the dusty projection beam
above our hair twisted and changed by
crystals rioting in a test tube
suspension the unstable ray changed and
changed in its black confinement it's
often difficult to be persuaded by the
story itself until you've read the
background of why he wrote it where he
was when he wrote it who he rooted for
it did take away a lot of his audience
because they felt after the after the
beautiful poems and spice box of earth
and flowers Fred ler how could a man
right this kind of prose but if you know
some of the background it's a very
persuasive argument perfect for hurt
many reacted very strongly to the novel
with a significant critical backlash
denouncing the work as obscene in Canada
Cohen was more than happy defending
beautiful losses both in the press and
on television quote this is among other
things the most revolting book ever
written in Canada end quote in one of
your poems you say now more than ever I
want enemies such a thing your poem
about how people conspire to make you
free do you feel this way about the
criticisms of your books oh yes well I
feel pretty lousy if I were praised by a
lot of the people that have come down
pretty heavy on me the book has been
scandalized because of the overt
sexuality of it people today are still
somewhat put off by it came out in 1966
that's quite a long time ago and yet
people are still somewhat anxious about
reading beautiful losers but I think
it's a very very important book and I
think one of the big questions with
Leonard is why he never wrote another
novel although it had benefited from its
notoriety the sales of the novel was
still relatively low
now 32 Cowen's income from grants prizes
and publishers advances were barely
enough to maintain his travels and his
life in Greece assessing his options he
looked to songwriting as an escape from
the financial restrictions of poetry
despite this late and apparently radical
change in artistic direction music had
in fact always been one of cones major
interests especially during his youth he
had been drawn to it ever since he was a
teenager I mean he loved folk music he
used to listen to lots of folk music
radio stations that he would be able to
listen to in Montreal he's get them from
New York I mean you know wherever the
ages of 14 15 16 he was going to summer
camp he was meeting people who played
the guitar and you know introduced him
to the sort of folky scene what was
interesting was that it was really folk
music then poetry then back to music
that I think is the pattern that one has
seen so it wasn't something that you
know happened unexpectedly in his 20s he
had this high school / university band a
country in western band called the
Buckskin boys they played at bar
mitzvahs and parties and dances and
get-togethers and he loved it he thought
it was great fun
planning to record a country record in
Nashville in October 1966 Cohen found
himself in new york city and the chelsea
motel
you
in a bid to capitalize on the booming
music industry he embraced the
flourishing counterculture and
befriended key figures within it
including Lou Reed in the velvet
underground and their benefactor Andy
Warhol
in hindsight it seems like a bad
decision that I was going to rectify my
economic situation by becoming a sinner
but III had been very interested in
country music for a long time and I'd
been writing songs for a long time I
thought I'd go down to Nashville and cut
a country-western record and that would
take care of everything Cohen starts out
as a poet novelist and he finds he's not
making a living and he gets out of the
game and moves the song which I would
argue is where the kind of poetry
enjoyed by people who sit on their
backpacks reading Yates and William
Carlos Williams has moved that's where
the interest in that kind of verbiage
has gone and he went with it Cohen's
gambit met with almost instant success
through key associates of Bob Dylan's
manager Albert Grossman his songs were
passed to folk singer Judy Collins
astounded by the unique and distinctive
poetry of the lyrics she recorded a
version of Cohen's most famous song
Suzanne for her 1966 album in my life
and would record three further Cohen
compositions on her follow-up wildflower
or Judy Collins was a great interpreter
of other people's songs and when Judy
Collins did a song that was obviously
completely different from the way of
something like he would do it as she she
proved with the other people that she
covered this
mercy they are not departed the call
they were waiting for me when I thought
that I just can't go
what it tends to do is it didn't say
Dylan's masters of war she decided that
in as a cut out the ugliness of masters
of war so that the bleakness that is
implicit in Leonard Cohen's material
wouldn't necessarily come through and
Judy Collins read it would be much
sweeter but it's a transformation job
from from top to bottom I mean you know
if you listen to Judy Collins doing
something like turn turn turn or
something sounds a completely different
song from the way you hear it in a you
know electric be grouping carnation
and a time to every purpose under
I think anybody listening to her songs
would have been alerted to Lenny cone as
an important songwriter and one to watch
but they certainly would have had a
ruler wiping when they heard Leonard
Cohen's own version which would have
been totally different of course now
close friends in april nineteen
sixty-seven collins invited cohen on
stage at an anti-vietnam war benefit
concert to perform Suzanne despite stage
nerves his performance convinced many
that he was not just a composer but a
very distinctive singer-songwriter he
was soon signed to Columbia by John
Hammond the man who had discovered Bob
Dylan and hurried into the studio to
record a debut Hammond intended to take
on the role of producer but unable to
find sufficient gaps in his schedule the
position was transferred to young talent
John Simon he had been signed by John
Hammond and Leonard's complain at the
time was that Leonard was holed up in
the Chelsea Hotel and he would have a
session with John Hammond and john
hammond would say some at some point
during a session or right before the
session I'm sorry I we have to stop or I
have to cancel this session and Leonard
was there for another month in the
Chelsea Hotel about another session so
he had asked Columbia I suppose for a
different producer and they had paired
us up well first I knew him as a poet
you know and then I began to realize the
kind of musician he was he wasn't the
guitar player like most of the artists
that i was working because most of the
artists came up through listening to pop
music so they knew how to play you know
rock and roller blues something like
that Leonard apparently learned how to
play classical guitar because he did
those things like real fast real fast it
was very easy to record and was a
pleasure it was a pleasure to record any
was smart you know it's a lot of these
acts that I recorded they weren't too
smart but Leonard was you know and smart
and fun to be with it and full of
insight about things so I was an honor
to work with Leonard you know what a
pleasure Cohen's debut songs
Leonard Cohen was a distinguished record
both in its classical sound and in the
remarkable poetry of the lyrics with its
unique opening track Suzanne it heralded
the arrival of an intimate and enigmatic
voice in modern music Suzanne takes you
down to her place near the
you can hear the boats go by you can
spend the name beside Suzanne as a song
I think it pitcher Mieses most of the
virtues that you hear in those early
Leonard Cohen songs in that it is
written from life not that you know that
necessarily when you first hear it and
not that you need to know it but it is
very specific Suzanne was indeed a woman
that he knew in Montreal and she did
have a place by the water and she did
feed UT and oranges because apparently
her speciality was this this tea that
she brewed with with bits of orange peel
in it so it's all drawn from experience
but then of course it's her a universal
in terms of its romantic message and
that was the key I think it was this
ability to take very precisely observed
details like the teal oranges and from
that create something that was totally
nonspecific and entirely universal I was
at the point where I was experimenting
I'll hold it was at the time 24 or 25
something like that and I had no idea
what I was doing so I was using my
producing to experiment on things and
one thing I tried with Leonard's album
that I really liked and I still like to
this day is the use of women's voices
instead of instruments
you want to travel with her and you want
to travel blind
no she will trust you for you touched
her her
with your mind I love the first album
and i loved what john simon did to it I
always you know people complained about
all the girls and all that stuff I
always thought this is cool Cohen has
actually for more vulgar than people
think he is and that's good I like that
about him I'm glad he's now Joni
Mitchell his first album is very spare
and to me completely unlistenable I
guess the the critical consensus on that
record at the time was a slight
disappointment but ready to give him the
benefit of the doubt but to me I thought
it magnified him I thought it made him
better and it was actually the second
record that I don't know like so much
that's when he spared down and I
preferred him a little SH locked up
myself there's an authority to that
first letter code record in a sense it's
not a debut it's almost more like the
next collection of stories or poems by
Leonard Cohen you know it didn't have
that tentative feel that even great 60s
debut albums have this was somebody who
clearly had an established voice as an
artist even though he was not
tremendously well known in the United
States you know you were not listening
to somebody trying things out there was
such a you know I the album is very
centered you know it just hits spot on
what it's going for there's something
really extraordinary about a debut album
an artist has been writing these songs
for quite a number of years generally
and so that the cream of the crop songs
the best songs and they don't want to
save the second the best songs for the
second album they don't wanna give you
their second best songs you want to give
you their best songs and along with that
is the fact that the second album is
often the most difficult to do because
debut album will come out it'll be since
big sensation and people say well what's
this clown got to follow up with and
then they're stuck and they have to
really scramble and write fast and
sometimes the second album is forced and
contrived but the first album is always
genuine and the the result of the
artist's soul from the time
they were born until the time that they
make that album the album said someone
at the top of most people's Leonard
Cohen albums I mean it's difficult to
find what comes second and third and
fourth but I think most people would put
out at the top and sweeping up the
Joker's that he left behind you'll find
he did not leave you very much not even
laughter like any dealer he was watching
for the car that is so high and wild
need to deal another the words were what
this was about and the music attempted
to evoke am you a mood but not in any
not in it certainly not in any
aggressive way was just things were kind
of sketched in whereas the words are not
sketched in the words are mysterious and
enigmatic but there are plenty of them
and you know he's he's almost reciting
you know his singing voice is almost a
kind of recitation and has a very
hypnotic quality so again you know in an
era of high psychedelia and you know the
wonder of the studio and all these great
sonic possibilities that everybody was
interested in you know this key was
coming from a whole other place this is
coming from inside they're not
complicated songs musically but they're
complicated in terms of the language and
in terms of the imagery and in terms of
the issues that he wants to confront but
now another stranger seems to want you
to ignore his dreams as though they
the burden of another you've seen that
man before his golden arm dispatching
cars now it's rusted from the elbow to
the finger I felt I was working with a
poet who said his words the song
Leonard's lyrics set him apart from most
rock and relax because they were more
finely crafted the imagery was there the
wonderfully crazy imagery that you'd
find in Dillon or anybody but the
balance in the lines and the inner
rhymes in the scansion that is the
number of beats per line everything was
regular and perfect and school and
studied this is a guy who read poetry
wrote poetry and I'd be hard-pressed to
think of somebody who had that kind of
chops you know coming into the Rock and
Roll field on his entrance into the late
1960s musical arena Cohen's profound
poetic lyrics as well as the spare
beauty of his songs led to inevitable
comparisons with the crown prince of
american singer songwriters bob dylan
despite the obvious differences between
the two artists many music critics
dismissed cohen has yet another in a
long line of Dylan wannabes a lot of the
misconceptions about cone came from the
obvious Dylan connections his
songwriting instantly connected into
Dylan the factory was discovered by John
Henry Hammond instantly connected them
to tell and the fact it was on CBS
records connected into Dylan there's
also the fact that they're both Jewish
they're both great wordsmiths and they
both you know you tend to use biblical
imagery apocalyptic imagery occasionally
they both right slightly twisted love
songs occasionally there's romance
tempered with a certain pessimism and
darkness and melancholy in both of them
as well so the connections need to be
implicit
Empire has returned into San vanished
from my hand let me blindly hit his Stan
what still not sleeping our witness
amazes me I am branded on my feet I have
no one to me and I ancient empty streets
to death ha dreamin it's not many it was
the desperate thing that people did
flailing about Cohen was plainly a very
different kind of versa fire Ben Dylan
at that point Dylan was free associating
plus calling on old sources but he was
doing more free associating it was in
the melodies that he did to use the old
sources more than the words whereas
Cohen was a somebody who had been
writing full-time on the page for I
guess six seven eight years by the time
he put out that first record and it's
much more controlled I think the only
point where the comparison with Dylan
was a fail or relevant one was that
actually for the first time you had here
a songwriter who not only wrote words as
great as Dylan but probably as a poet
exceeded Dylan so of course he was going
to be compared because you know there
weren't any other fish in the pond or if
the were they were minnows you know
there were these two giant beasts and in
in in literary terms I think the
difference between them is that Dylan
was a songwriter is a songwriter not a
poet that is to say the music and the
words work together and if you read that
big tome of Dylan's lyrics they don't
necessarily stand up that well a lot of
them are
the page they they need the music to
hold their hand as it where they work in
concert Cohen undoubtedly was a poet as
we know he was a published poet before
he was a recorded songwriter and in a
way he doesn't write songs in this
period he puts poetry to music and
that's the distinction I think between
Dillon and Cohen at this time because he
was a writer to begin with people always
think about his words you read these
books on him and it's verbal analysis I
think one reason he was as arresting as
he was is that however he came upon it
he had a musical neck and you don't have
to understand musical technique very
well to know that a good melody is where
you find it that they are that you can
have all the training in the world and
not be able to write good melodies you
could have no training and have an
absolute genius for it and I wouldn't
say genius is exactly where I'd put him
but he definitely had a talent for it
and and without much question in my mind
it was the melodies as well as all the
rest of the stuff that made it happen if
he hadn't had the melodies nobody would
have it wouldn't have happened I suppose
that he told you
but I keep locked away in my head your
master took you try
well at least that's what you say the
simplicity of the guitar accompaniment
on songs of Leonard Cohen itself made a
kind of point there was kind of elegance
very simple melodic elegance to it it
wasn't trying too hard to appeal to you
and it was very clearly an accompaniment
to his voice I think the other pneus of
the sound that did stand out from what
was happening in rock and roll at that
time with Dylan having gone electric and
so on and so forth he tapped into that
sort of European Jacques Brel type thing
and you can hear that in the voice as
well and that was somehow to me as a
teenage kid listening to learn a color
this was very grown up you know in 1956
I don't think he was really listening to
chuck berry and Little Richard he's not
a child of the rock and roll era I guess
is what I'm trying to say and I think
that inevitably had quite a profound
impact on the sound I mean with Dylan
you know even on the early so-called
folk records you can kind of hear the
rock and roll are trying to get out you
never get that feeling with Leonard
Cohen the album songs of Leonard Cohen
was released on Boxing Day 1967
receiving very limited public attention
in the US but faring far better in
Europe and Canada Cohen promoted the
album with live shows and television
appearances both in Britain and Canada
and with a tour of major American cities
which included an appearance at the
prestigious newport folk festival like
dylan before him cohen found that
despite his obvious talents his voice
was limiting his appeal both to the
public and to the music press what
Khan's voice at the start of his career
was always regarded as a problem by
people it was an impediment to their
enjoyment in many respects because it
was unusual for the time you must
remember it was only you know 10 12
years since the age of the crooners or
whatever and we've been through basic
beat pop music and the folk fraternity
you know had its own standards and style
and Colin was was somewhat alien to all
of that he was a distinctive voice but
not necessarily an attractive one or a
radio-friendly one and it's interesting
if you if you look at the trajectory of
you know vocalist since by 1970s a
people getting a bit more comfortable
with Cohen's voice by the mid seventies
it doesn't seem to be such a problem
anymore and by the end of the 70s its
mainstream almost because eccentric
vocalists as they would have been called
were more prevalent in in the rock and
roll era that first album it's kind of
it's not completely jarring after if
this isn't he's appearing in a context
in which people have dealt with Bob
Dylan's voice and he's he's similar in
that's a bit of a non voice but he has a
bit more of a kind of natural melodic
quality than Dylan ever did and it's not
quite as grating but over the years the
voice it just gets deeper and deeper and
deeper and deeper so he's kind of
gravely and experienced and careworn you
know really early on but but you know
anything from I'm your man onwards you
play it too loudly it kills goldfish it
was about conveying intimacy he really
something about is it the quality of his
voice is it the way he dramatizes
himself I think that these things are
very mysterious and I've I don't believe
that I've ever pinned it down it's like
trying to describe a wreath of
Franklin's voice how do you describe why
it is that Leonard Cohen makes you feel
intimate with him but he does so you
want to engage him when you hear this
voice coming out of the speakers he has
that quality after a chance meeting with
nashville-based producer Bob Johnston he
would notably worked the Bob Dylan on
the singer-songwriters previous two
releases Cohen decided that his
sophomore album required both a change
of scene and of personnel he moved to an
isolated farmhouse in Franklin Tennessee
and enlisted Johnston services for the
recording of the album songs from a room
it surprised many on its release its
contents far more somber and melancholic
than the songs of his debut the second
album I think was the way in which he
believed the music should go I think he
was striving to remove the music the
sound out of the studio into the self
and so he doesn't record it in New York
it's in Tennessee he was living on this
remarkable little farm in Franklin
Tennessee which is about which I have
been to which is about 30 miles perhaps
out of Nashville and it was very
influenced by the isolation of that and
that fit his romantic notion of the
artist the artist and this is really out
of Byron and it's out of Shelley and
it's even out of blake is a bard who
present past and future sees and he is
alone on the mountaintop Leonard was
alone occasional woman of course but
alone in the small little farm in
Franklin Tennessee where he actually
recorded some of the songs right there
very minimalist manner and then we go
into Nashville and you know do a studio
version of it but i think it was for him
what he believed to be the natural to
the natural evolution of his music when
i'm hard across the board
I was cautioned to surrender this I
could not do
I took my gun and then the nature of
those songs how they were recorded the
absence of ornamentation musical
ornamentation was what he wanted which I
think he also felt was part of a certain
purity to the music that he wanted to
intensify even as songs of Leonard Cohen
sounded like you know a completely fully
conceived work I think Leonard Cohen
felt that he had further to go you know
Justin and what he wanted to pursue and
so the even more extreme starkness of
the second album uh it gets at that you
know just say well how far can I really
take this it is more stripped-down it is
beautifully titled songs from a room you
know that sort of sums up both the sound
of the record and the sentiment of the
lyrics it's got this chamber quality for
those who have this image of Leonard
Cohen as the guitar strumming troubadour
this is the closest the truest it gets
to that sound although the majority of
the album maintained this minimal
aesthetic for many its strongest track
was the slightly more embellished opener
bird on a wire based on a lyric he had
developed while staying in the island of
Hedra it would become like Suzanne on
the previous album one of Cohen's most
recognized signature tunes and a firm
live favorite for the rest of his career
like a drunk in some old midnight
I
in my way
to be free
it comes from a very of course prosaic
account of what actually happened it's
it's about telegraph poles that were
introduced into the island for the first
time so there we have been a cone on
this island seemingly free from
civilization you know writing in
isolation and suddenly you know
technology enters his world and he sees
a promise window he sees a bird perched
upon a wire and that inspired him to
write this this song about freedom but i
think this the fact that the longing to
be free is a motif as well within the
song that connects with people
particularly in the late 60s and it's
it's just it's it's a strong lyric from
the time and it's a song that that
people just like to cover as well and I
think the effect that it you know it's
so amenable to being a cover version
makes makes it more Universal than it
might otherwise have been I think the
reason that so many people have come
back to it and the reason why had stood
up as part of his own work is that it's
it is a great tune you wouldn't
necessarily know it from listening to
his version it's a fabulous tune and
it's something you could say about any
of his lyrics but it's a great lyric the
couplet like a worm on a hook like a
knight from an old-fashioned book I
think as a description of of men in love
I think you have right there what we
think we are or what we'd like to be the
night in the old-fashioned book and yet
I think in those circumstances what we
usually actually are a lot of the time
which is the worm on the hook and I
think that's that's a that's a
definitive mine in current moment right
there if you had to pick one song to sum
up the appeal of letter code that might
well be it you know from that opening
line like a bird on a wire like a drunk
in a midnight choir I have tried in my
way to be free it seems to be a him for
all those beautiful losers that he'd
written about in the novel the drunk in
the midnight choir that we all associate
with you and we none of us want to be
the sort of prissy little choirboy who
hits every note spot on you'd much
rather be the drunk in the back row who
wants to be part of it and is actually
joining in from the very best of mode
kids and spirits and but he's actually
preventing the whole thing and you're
trying to express yourself and this is
my way of trying to be free yeah there's
something about that song that really
sums up the spirit of what early that
occurred was all about the album was
released in april nineteen sixty-nine
and was a tremendous success in Europe
it reached number two in the British
charts and made Cohen a star in France
where in one periodical he was declared
folk singer of the year yet in America
he was struggling to secure a sizable
mainstream audience despite three tracks
from his debut appearing prominently in
Robert Altman's revisionist Western
McCabe and mrs. Miller to this day a
large North American fan base is
something that Cohen has still not
attracted it always was a sense of his
being a little removed in the u.s.
partly because it's such a you know it's
a big country you know you it really is
hard work to become a star and people
think you know it happens overnight and
sometimes it does but you have to really
want it and be willing to do whatever it
takes and I don't think Leonard Cohen
ever particularly felt that way so along
with you know the fact that he's writing
complicated songs and the fact that is
his singing voice is not necessarily you
know you know a conventional hit
sounding voice you have a fact of a
person an artist who's probably a little
ambivalent about all that stuff Leonard
is not interested in entertaining he's
interested in engaging and that's what
he's able to do with that music both
recorded and in person he engages the
audience he does not entertain them it
appeals to certain people very strongly
but it's not mainstream what are his
album sales compared to dylan's we're
probably I don't even think they're a
third if you did the total figures right
of Dylan's Dylan has at some point in
his career probably very early on
encourage the mainstream effort in terms
of how his career is managed where he
has performed
the kinds of songs he writes and
certainly how his albums have been
marketed Leonard doesn't take that
proactive you at all and you know he
recognizes he's a minor voice and he's
been relatively satisfied with that you
never get the sense that Leonard is so
frustrated in not crossing the line to
be in what the top 10 Billboard albums
of the week in march 1970 work began on
songs for a further album rooted firmly
in Nashville Cohen once again teamed up
with Bob Johnston who suggested the use
of a group of musicians with whom he had
worked on Dylan's recent new morning
album guitarist Ron Cornelius became the
impromptu band leader and was involved
both in the instrumentation of the
as-yet-untitled new record and with the
preparations for a full band live tour
day one all I knew was that I was
getting involved with somebody that was
a intellectual classical guy that
doesn't sing very well you know they
just like that and it it took me a
little while to really understand you
know really what we're dealing with here
you know and so therefore it became more
of a mission you know and I think I when
I say that I'm saying I'm really talking
about the girls I'm talking about the
players in the band we were it was so
much like a family that it was like
we're on this this mission together you
know with many of the new songs written
and the musicians fully prepared Cohen
delayed the studio recording and went on
the road with this new band the army the
tour which encompassed many European
destinations as well as major American
and Canadian cities also included a
performance at the prestigious isle of
wight festival alongside the doors The
Who Miles Davis and Jimi Hendrix
translating what had often been acoustic
tracks into a live context required a
very disciplined approach from the band
we knew that Leonard's lenarz message
his lyrics everything we had to make
sure that the people that came to see
him got what they wanted to see it
became such a such a unique delivery
that
it was like it was like that feeling
that if one person wasn't there you
couldn't do it that night it was a big
responsibility on me because being the
band leader and that if anything wasn't
right they came to me they didn't go to
the person that wasn't well you know
there was that wasn't hitting it at
night you know they would come to me and
then I would have to go to that person
say we needed to get together with this
and fix this or fix that but
consequently it was it was a real effort
by everybody and it was it truly was
like a family running all over the world
and it was some some of the some of the
nicest music that I've ever been
involved Suzanne
to the river she's wearing rags and
feathers from salvation army countess
and the Sun Leonard as a performer is
happiest I think when he's got company
on stage he always has backup singers
and he usually has a substantial group
accompanying him it's not just Leonard
and a piano man or Leonard and you know
someone on a drum kit Leonard's concerts
I think achieve their effectiveness
partly because he's got a community with
him and when he does perform and he goes
on tour he establishes this community
that's crucial for him they provide a
support for you know for him as the
performer the fundamental thing is that
he is part of a group and that group is
becomes a tour family and they do things
together they travel together Leonard
doesn't hop on the jet and everybody
else comes by bus after the tool Cohen
and the band returned to the studio to
record the new songs under the watchful
eye of producer Bob Johnston Bob
Johnston he was born with something that
I don't know if I've ever seen it match
up to before or since his gift was he
could make somebody whether it be a use
ition or an artist a background singer
an engineer he could with he was born
with the ability to make you want to do
right here tonight the best you've ever
done now musically it is I'm getting
nothing he has no no one one one note
from another really however the gift
that I just described is priceless and
as far as the music goes you know I I'm
I know what I'm doing there and so with
with
me there Leonard out front and Bob being
able to fire everyone up to the to the
hilt I mean magic can happen when you
get that kind of stuff together the
album songs of love and hate was
released in March 1971 combining both
the familiar spare acoustic numbers with
live tracks that captured the new full
band sound despite its lack of
commercial success it was received by
many critics as confirmation of Cohen's
unique talent and remains a landmark
record in his cannon well love and hate
is possibly then it goes bleakest album
the cover alone would suggest out will
always smile on the cover it's
definitely it's black and white and
although it's it's called songs of love
and hate and I'm sure you know many
critics have looked at that album and
gone through and said yet that songs
about love that song about hate that
songs about love that songs about hey I
don't think it's like that at all I
don't think it's his structured as that
would suggest i think the love and hate
intermingles and that album very strange
in different ways at times there I think
there are at least elements of Cohen's
wry humor coming through Joan of Arc for
instance which is a song about Niko the
sometimes guest singer from The Velvet
Underground she was a known heroin
addict self-destructive in a sense and
thus the image of Joan of Arc but i
often find when i listened to that
record i thought it that this is roy
huber on Cohen's part I mean he talks
about a smoky night the night suddenly
becomes very smoky you said Joan of art
was burned at the stake for goodness
sake a so you know is he playing with
this and he put some particular stress
on the word heroin when he's talking
about Joan of Arc as a heroine and you
think yet Nico heroine ok we get it but
it is it is playful I think to the
cognoscenti and that's what coven is
doing a lot there
well I'm glad to hear you talk this way
you know I've watched you riding every
day and something in me is to win I've
got a long career behind me he looked
the color of this hair you know I got a
long career behind me and I've got I've
got a lot of accomplishments songs of
love and hates right out there in front
I mean it may be to me one of the best
things I've ever done you know it was
one of the most involved musical
endeavors that I've ever been involved
with in the studio it was just something
that you knew when you were working on
it that this is something that's very
special and it's got to be right and we
didn't settle for seconds it's four in
the morning the end of December I'm
writing it now just to see if you better
New York is cold but I like where I'm
living
music on Clinton Street all through the
evening now famous blue raincoat is boy
that's but that's another one that
although we don't relate very well to
the way Cohen relates to women in so far
as you want it summed up that sums it up
really good either it's explicitly
autobiographical or he wants people to
think it's explicitly autobiographical
there is no other reason why you would
finish a song with the line sincerely
old Cohen he really more than any other
song he's ever recorded it puts himself
right into the middle of this and it is
it is a letter and it's fairly clear as
the song goes on but it is a letter to a
former friend and now rival in love of
his who his wife seems to have left him
for but she's come back so he's won but
the general town of the record is that
it's a a fairly hollow victory there are
certain key things in the song which you
know leap out at you I think
particularly there's some wonderful
lines in it there's the line about Jane
after the affair has taken place taking
a Mentos a lock of hair that she takes
from the unnamed adulterer and it's on
the night that he tried to go clear and
then it can't pointedly asked him in the
song you know did you ever get did you
ever go clear did you ever get clear
clear of what you know clear of drugs
will know i think the clear is a pretty
explicit reference to scientology and we
do know that linda cohn was interested
in Scientology at the time and so to be
clear was the holy grail of scientology
if you went clear it and then you'd rid
yourself of all neurosis it imbues you
with almost superpowers took you to a
new level did you ever go clear I mean
that line what a great line I mean and
the interesting thing is that you don't
actually have to know that that's a
Scientology chol piece of jargon
you just know it's something like that
and it is a perfect choice yet the
despair and pessimism of such tracks as
avalanche and the reference to suicide
on dress rehearsal rag proved
off-putting to certain members of the
music press who found Cohen's work
depressing ever since his debut some
critics had reacted negatively to the
melancholy of the Leonard Cohen sound
and the painful introspection in songs
of love and hate led to further
accusations that the singer was
indulgent and self-pitying or an
impediment to the enjoyment of Leonard
Cohen for many listeners particularly
for many mainstream lessness is that
they see songs as bleak it's no
coincidence that the you know famously a
reviewer of someone's in love and hate
said you know they should they should
give razor blades away when they sell
this album in stores or whatever and you
know that is the popular image of the
early Leonard Cohen and it's an image
that it took a long time to rid himself
often some people would say yes it still
isn't you know that those old jokes
still are used to this day yeah I think
it's true I did start to break down
around that time there is a certain
bleep quality to that record yeah well
this you know it has other redeeming
features i don't i don't think those are
bad qualities for the sinners
I stepped into an Avalon
it covered up my soul when I
his hands back vid2c asleep beneath the
Golden Hill in my way of thinking
self-pity is not an attractive quality
in an artist i prefer the blue Xephos
right now why people talk about the
police they think it's about how said
colored people aren't Albert Marie will
tell you that no it's about having shit
headed to you and having a good time on
Saturday night and I think that's a
stronger more intellectually respectable
point of view most people think
pessimism is a sign of seriousness I
don't and Leonard Cohen is a pessimist
maricon has a very pessimistic cast of
mind but to my mind he triumphs over
this with his wit his charm his craft
the poetic nature tends to be
introspective and melancholic going back
to Keats and the romantics of the 19th
century that was also i think this
fascination with great poets burning out
and dying young Keats Shelley and in
fact there is a famous interview that
Cohen gave in the late 1960s where he
actually talks about great poets doing
all their great work before they're 35
and committing suicide so that he's
there I mean in in later years it gets
tempered with with a wonderful wit and
humor that that often gets overlooked in
1972 Cohen and the army began a new
larger scale world tour the following
year an album of selected performances
live songs was released stepping away
from the musical arena Cohen
unexpectedly became involved in the yom
kippur war between israel and egypt in
late nineteen seventy three traveling to
Tel Aviv
and performing on the front line despite
the many valid criticisms of the Israeli
position in 1974 he returned to music
into his old horn New York in a notable
departure from his recent musical
approach Cohen steered clear of
Nashville and began working on new
material with the young and relatively
unknown producer John Liesel he'd just
finished the tour I guess with the
Charlie Daniels Band as his thing and it
was very Nashville ish you know that
pose Dylan thing where you take a
singer-songwriter and you know put some
some country guys with him and that's
what that was and it was it was fine but
it wasn't Leonard wasn't doing anything
new in and of itself except for how
great he and his songs were the music
had that kind of it was that thing well
we started doing these songs we did I
think Chelsea Hotel which had a little
down bluesy quality to what I played
some very funky clarinet and it was
Spacey and moody without being standard
folk there was really no standard folk
music on this album with one or two
exceptions why he had faith in me right
off the bat I don't know it turned out
that we worked great together but he saw
something in a collaboration that I mean
I wasn't even thinking I was just saying
oh yeah let's try this let's try that
with an entirely new backing band they
saw a fashion an album that had more in
common with John Simon's production on
Cohen's debut than the stripped-down
Nashville sound of the previous two
records he mentioned that the first time
the John's I'm Simon album and I don't
know a lot of the details but I do know
that he looked at it the same way that
Leonard's music their pieces the little
work and the idea of framing them or
give them as you it's an embellishments
more in coloration than anything else
i'm setting the tone nothing that we did
on new skin was really thick or overdone
there's a lot of transparency to it but
there are colors going on like crazy you
know people talk about that field
commander cohen stuff and some of the
things that you are just floating around
the time must have been right i think
because he didn't did those paired
albums that Nashville / folk albums that
did to me just sit there a bit the songs
were so strong that it sustained it time
because he had that you was still so new
but the songs that we started working on
I thought could just have a little more
color to them so who by fire which has
all that little those little spaces and
those kind of emotional things and the
cars are happening in the girls and it
in a way and it came easily because for
some reason it his songs inspired me to
think that way in sunshine and the
nighttime by the time we get to new skin
for the old ceremony it's a different
lender conus emerged it's there's a
break there it's completely different
record from what we've what we've heard
before new producer is no longer in
Nashville he's in New York so everything
is different and for the first time I
think you know learning clone is using
the mechanics of pop music he's got a
full band there he's introducing a more
mainstream sound whether it's an attempt
to become more accessible or not it's
debatable but certainly that seems to be
the intent who by fire is an interesting
song it's like a more serious version of
Dorothy Parker's resume a in which she
talks about all the different ways in
which you can die in commit suicide and
here we have Lenny cope with this litany
of ways in which you might die and
civically he says you know there's a
line who buy a de launch and of course
Avalanche was was the opening song two
summers of love and hate so he there's a
link there as well it's an echo of a
Jewish prayer which was written in the
11th century I think by a German rabbi
called Amnon and it's a prayer that
spoken on Rosh Hashanah and Yom Kippur
and Cohen this is quite a common thing
for blending
the Bible is is a fairly common
reference point in all his works his
Jewish heritage comes up a lot both in
quite reverential tones and also in
extremely self-mocking ones more than I
think he's allowed to maybe contemporary
American or indeed Canadian folk sing as
you can see there's a sensibility
linking someone like linking Leonard
Cole with people like Bob Dylan people
at Randy Newman their songs are
extremely wordy they're very inquisitive
they're very questing they're also very
funny a lot of the time and who by fire
he's taking what is a prayer that his
people have been making for ten
centuries and there's a attaching a
punchline to the end of it the sort of
like the and who shall I say is calling
is quite a great gag to stick in the
middle of a recast prayer
shall I say is calling
I was trying to frame his stuff take his
thing as pieces and put them in
interesting frames make them visual make
them cinematic maybe so we did that he
would take songs like a lover lover
lover and instead of it being little
folk song we put kind of a Ethiopian
rhythm band behind him and it was great
it was exciting Leonard could write off
on and it was that it was like a
different approach
cohen need something to tense that
intimacy against i think that list our
was really perfect in terms of the way
he can see the music I mean I I mean he
you know he's Cohen's a smart guy he
works with good people and and he
doesn't mess up his productions anymore
but I wouldn't call the production in
the recent records inventive the way I
witless hours there are touches there
are arrangements there are curly cues
and furbelows in that music and the
voice snakes through it's an elder
Parcher and I think starts the second
phase of Leonard Cohen's career where he
is no longer the acoustic troubadour
that he's he's soon going to be out
there playing with you know it what's to
play with a full band doesn't want to be
the solar singer-songwriter in the
spotlight anymore I mean it's the end of
that whole era in a sense what we see
from now on is is cohen been much more
comfortable working with an ensemble
with the new skin for old ceremony he'd
been told or he had decided that he had
really done everything he could within
the limits of the sound of the three
albums that i regard as a trilogy and so
you do have this quite conscious effort
to expand the sound I don't think
entirely successfully but then I
wouldn't because these were my formative
years I bought those first three records
when they came out when I was 14 15 16
17 years old so you know that's that's
where I'm coming from I was never really
a fan of you skin crawl ceremony on its
release new skin for the old ceremony
was only a modest commercial success and
critical opinion was divided over the
more ornate arrangements he had one song
once again stood out to become one of
Cohen's most recognized Chelsea Hotel
number two its lyrics typically
autobiographical the song recounts the
tale of Cohen's brief love affair with a
woman in the famous
new york hotel where he had sporadically
lived at the start of his career cohen
later uncharacteristically revealed the
subject of the song to be Janis Joplin
now remember you will in the Chelsea oh
dear you were talking so brie and so
sweet
given me here on the only beer yeah one
of the great strengths of London Cohen
as a writer is I don't think it's really
necessary to know all that much about
him personally to appreciate the songs
and actually I tend to think a lot of
them probably better appreciated the
less you know about the author which is
one of the reasons I think Chelsea Hotel
number two really doesn't work at all I
mean for a start I don't I really don't
think it's anything like a great Leonard
Cohen song I don't think it's even an
especially good one I think that Thun is
one I've always forgotten even while i
was listening to it and the lyric is
even if you don't know it's about Janis
Joplin it just the line about you know
giving me head on an unmade bed bulb in
the scenes waited outside is it's it's
graceless it's showing off and it sounds
like David Lee Roth I mean really you
take it out of that context it's it's
not a very Leonard Cohen lyric and the
the line about you know the one about
her preferring handsome men but for me
you said you'd make an exception that
it's he's a lot funnier than that
usually and a lot better than that again
it underlines the fact as with Joan of
Arc that when the person is named
whether it be an eco or a janis joplin a
place for porridge sense of oh you know
that's a song about x and we can
visualize the person but in a way that's
kind of self limiting in a way no I
think it would be I think Cohen was
absolutely right when he said damn and I
regret ever saying it was about Janis
Joplin I think I think if it could have
been about every woman in the show's
hotel at the time it would have been
probably better I think you know
applying it solely to Janis Joplin which
we now can't help but doing and it seems
so explicitly so is regrettable Cohen
was happy with the album and immediately
returned to the studio with John lesueur
to work on the follow-up despite this
momentum with several songs completed in
the can the album was abandoned cowan
went on tours with many of the backing
band that had been involved in new skin
but in 1975 stepped off of the musical
stage and out of the public eye once
more he did not begin working on another
album until 1977
when he was introduced to legendary
music producer Phil Spector to the
surprise of many the pair planned a
collaboration an album on which Spector
would compose the music and Cohen the
lyrics Phil Spector was was largely
famous for two things he was famous for
being as mad as a frog in a sock he was
just nuts and you know subsequent or
recent events may still be sub judice II
but they would seem to sort of conform
with various patterns of his previous
behavior he was also famous as a
producer for something called the wall
of sound which was the sound that
informed those great girl group hits of
the 60s the ronettes most obviously you
know the leader of whom Ronnie Spector
he was rather fractious lee married to
for many years
he changed producing he changed the old
definition of producer was the guy who
came in and sort of made sure people
showed up to the session make sure the
contracts got signed and and put
together the artist and sent back and
said you know this is really good you
worked with an established artist and
the songs were done on the Angels for
done The Spectre came in and said I'm
doing this who wants to say it he's a
producer that you'll never find again
I'm sure he knows exactly what he wants
he knows what it's going to sound like
before he ever does it and yet usually
gets what he wants and I think that's
what an artist coming to fill would
expect the term wall of sound was
applied to the unique production Spector
had developed along with the engineers
at gold star studios in los angeles it
had been the defining characteristic of
many highly successful records and had
the potential to cross Cohen over into
the mainstream the wall of sound was
what it sounds it was it was absolutely
there's monumental creation of basically
compressing an entire symphony orchestra
into a three minute pop song it was not
dissimilar in a lot of respects to what
the Beatles did and of course he went on
to produce to let it be album everything
George Martin brought to those more
orchestral Beatles records he crept from
Phil Spector the Beach Boys Pet Sounds
was to a huge extent Brian Wilson's
homage or attempt to emulate Phil
Spector I mean he's one of the most
influential figures in modern popular
music has absolutely no doubt about that
at all there are many interpretations of
what the wall of sound was actually it's
a combination of many things the echo
chamber is a very important part of it
but the fact that Phil brought too many
musicians into a room added to the
effect and this is where the wall sound
came from because he had literally sound
from wall to wall but without the echo
chamber it wouldn't have existed and
probably vice versa either it was odd to
seem working with something I expect
but the same time I thought there was an
element of that relationship which could
and should have worked Spector had been
brought in at the tail end of the
Beatles career he you know worked
infamously on let it be and we know the
stories about his production there his
wall of sound his epic production was
something that had been strongly
associated with the 60s by the time
Spector was working in the early 70s he
got involved with John Lennon in the
early stages of his career and worked on
the classic johnanon plastic ono band
now that was a brilliant piece of work
and a brilliant collaboration and it
showed you what might have happened
between Spector and Cohen although a
fusing of the specter sound with Cohen's
lyrics would obviously lead to a radical
departure from previous releases the
producer decided like John Liz or and
John Simon before him to juxtapose
Cohen's voice with female singers he
decided to push this idea further on
three tracks by having Cohen duet with
the actress and country singer ronee
blakley who had recently been a part of
Bob Dylan's Rolling Thunder review tool
all voices blend with Leonard but I
think female voices are especially
touching Leonard has in his voice a
slight trembling from time to time which
is extremely vulnerable than real and
present and there it's at the front of
his head even though it almost has a
rumbling sound almost a biblical sound
at times it can also sound very
sensitive and charming and this sound
that he has in addition to the
Rabbinical quality of his Jewishness if
I may say so is almost what in Christian
music would be called bel canto or
Cantus firmus the kind that monks would
sing and that invites the addition of a
sixth or third above or below as a
harmony it just invites it and therefore
complements it
the scar
Oh
my buddy
you know Leonard's great when he has a
female singer singing behind him it just
it complements him so well and I just
remember one night there was a session
and I walked into there was a coffee
room outside the studio and somebody
walked in and he looked really familiar
to me by you know who it was with how
some rock or something and I was in the
studio half hour later and the person
had come in with a couple of other
people and I and I looked looked at him
and I did like a triple take 30 minutes
later and said that's Bob Dylan and that
must be ronee blakley and that's Allen
Ginsberg and I was I was like starstruck
I helped to tell you it was a wonderful
experience just imagine yourself to be
in the studio with Bob Dylan allen
ginsberg Leonard Cohen and Phil Spector
isn't that heaven yet the working
atmosphere was far from heaven Spector
after years of being teetotal was
drinking heavily again and acting
dictatorial e in the studio and Cohen
soon found that he had little control
over the producer or the record Phil is
really a take-charge type of man he
wants to be in control of the situation
it's like an artist palette he's holding
the brush and I would almost say like
Leonard Colton was the subject you know
so so you know Leonard wasn't a man of a
lot of words in the studio Phil you know
controlled the musicians and you know
produce you know Leonard in front of the
microphone sing and you'd essentially
ran the show well they were both very
comfortable there is a slight but to my
voice as you may have heard a slight
hesitation because when an artist is
branching out into new territory it is
unsafe and insecure and everybody's
finding their footing it's not familiar
it's not the old turf and so therefore
it's a little bit frightening I got
along fine with letters I got along fine
with everybody I even got along fine
with Phil but Phil couldn't get along
fine with the artist it was always a
trend Joe's transmission of
problems between the two of them because
phil was into this thing at the time
whatever it was and he that any
distraction would distract him a
telephone call bathroom call anything
would bother him and being on time
bothered him to that bothered leaded and
that's one of the things that really
created a problem he was just never on
time it seems to me that Columbia was
after a different tack on how they were
going to record Leonard I think it was
an unfortunate time to do it I don't
think Phil I know I wasn't at my best
Phil wasn't his best I don't know
whether Leonard was but Leonard deserved
better than he got I'm sure my main
memory of that whole episode was that
and Phil and Leonard were both very
unhappy with what was coming off and I
think rightly so I don't think one thing
fit the other the affair ended in a
farcical manner respecter confiscating
the final tapes and mastering them in
secret the finished work death of a
ladies man was released in November 1977
the specter approach failed to find
Cohen the new audience that many had
been expecting and the album was treated
harshly by critics it was subsequently
disowned by cohen who called the LP a
catastrophe the word I would use about
death of a ladies man is he son
dignified and I think that you know you
don't really need to say much more that
that word somehow sums it up because
then a cone had always been this hugely
dignified figure he was the poet he was
the artist he was the man who had this
wider experience than the rest of us
that was what made him special and then
this record just sucks I really thought
it was great I really really liked the
songs I thought they were really unique
I think today if you go back and you try
to find music that compares to that
album it stands on its own as one unique
statement of a two artists work the
songs are fantastic you can imagine
every single one of them being done in
concert and he has done memories in all
sorts of all sorts of ways with
different backup singers and it always
gets a great reaction it almost gets
it's a great crowd pleaser
your naked body it's not typical of
Leonard's performance style to sing the
song he's used to standing at a
microphone with a guitar in his hand
when he does memories you know there's
no guitar in 1979 Jennifer Warnes and
Sharon Robinson did a doo-wop routing
which brought the place to think it's
really hard for me to say that you know
like death of a ladies man is a bad
record you know I'm somebody who's
intrigued by whatever learn and Cohen
does I can find things in it you know
but you can you say that you know that
is a successful collaboration no of
course not it's ridiculous I mean
Leonard coming up as I was described it
as grotesque and I think it is grotesque
Oh on the other hand I mean what does
Leonard Cohen want from this what is he
going for you know there's a kind of
there's a garishness to it that is
revealing just anime just one thing to
say it's grotesque after it's done but
you made it you know that's your record
yeah what'd you think you were going to
Phil Spector for a subtlety I personally
felt that Leonard Cohen should never use
Phil Spector you should've gone with
David Foster because he needs someone
who really understands autistic people
who adeline those more about that kind
of performer than the field Spector so I
thought using phil was the wrong man for
the job even though phil was always in
control phil was the boss still he made
stars out of the people who work with
and he if he could have he would have
made Leonard a star also but I as I say
I just don't think he was creatively and
his best at that time people refer to it
as Phil Spector's album not Leonard
Cohen's album and I don't think you need
to say anything more about it that tells
you the whole story Leonard has been
subsumed by Spector and the
all of sound in this first period of his
career Cohen had resisted the temptation
to return full time to writing and had
passionately pursued a life in music
with his remarkable debut his to spare
Nashville masterpieces and his
experiment in a more expansive sound
with John lesueur and Phil Spector he
had demonstrated a refusal to stick to
one mode or sound in his later career he
would continue to evolve an experiment
but for many his greatest achievements
lay within those early albums which he
emerged as one of the most idiosyncratic
and insightful artists working in
popular music those early records are a
diamond their extraordinary body of work
and people are going to be singing those
songs for decades and decades and
decades and finding new things in those
songs of decades and decades and decades
there's so much in the words there's so
much you can do with the melodies the
body of work the first three albums in
particular I think stand supreme in
Leonard Cohen's canon subsequently he
does become a great songwriter but these
three records I think are not only
supreme in Leonard Cohen's canon but I
think in the canon of pop music as
records of poetry put music they've
never been paralleled
you