hello
all right thank you all right faggot how
you doing sorry I called him a faggot I
missed that word you knowing i grew up
saying that word and it I mean it would
never meant gay when I was a kid I
didn't I don't know what gay was no I
hadn't been told that people do that I
hadn't no fucking idea faggot than me
yay when I was a kid you call somebody
fat because they're being a faggot you
know being a bragging need shut up
faggot
and that's supposed to use those for
that shut up faggot didn't mean like I
would never call a gay guy a faggot was
he's being a faggot but not because he's
gay you understand like if I saw two
guys blown each other I don't know why
I'm watching him do it but if I just
have
I stumbled upon a couple of fellas
blowing one another on their respective
Tunisia support / penis that I invented
today indonesia i would be respectful to
them I would you know hello gentlemen
whatever you know but if one of them
took the dick out of his mouth and
started acting all faggy and saying
annoying faggy things you know people
from phoenix or Phoenicians or something
like that
I'll be like hey chef baguette
faggot quit being a faggot and suck that
day that's what I would say to him
I don't know I would never call somebody
a mean name because they're sucking it
because if you can suck a dick man
that's awesome I respect you because I
can't do it I can't do and I haven't
tried and failed I just have put myself
there in my mind I couldn't do it
because I'm afraid that's not the only
reason but that's why if you can suck it
I think that there's a strength in being
able to do that i believe that i don't
believe that blond somebody comes easily
to anybody even if it's something that
you generally do every new dick must
take something mattia there must be
something you gotta do get yourself
ready you know
nah Wow here yo
so faggot I don't know a lot of words
that her not bad words no words are bad
but some people start using them a lot
to hurt other people and then they
become bad they become hard to you
there's words that i love that i can use
cuz other people use them wrong to hurt
other people like the word cunt is a
beautiful word to me there's just beauty
in that word and I don't I mean
aesthetically it has it's like
chocolatey and round on the ends I just
like them I just like the way it sounds
and I don't use it as an inside min I'm
alone in the laundry oh my god huh I
would never call a woman a cunt except
for my mom because she likes us for some
weird reason what
it's a very misused word it's supposed
to mean vagina which I don't think works
at all because vaginas are so sweet
their little pretty things with lily
flower petal II lipson I hear a piccolo
in my head every time I see a vagina
even vagina's too harsh for they should
be called like a
there should be a butterfly fluttering
around every vagina all the time just
all the time little butterfly and you go
to the doctor said well the butterfly
looks good so we're good shape then call
it a butterfly how do you look at
something that pretty and say that's our
guns it doesn't fit at all maybe if it
was a giant vagina and it was attacking
a town and throwing buses around and
knocking over telephone balls then you
could say somebody shoot that come with
a bazooka
it's gonna step on the candy store so
faggot con everything everybody has
different words that offend them
different things that they hear that
they get offended by I to me the thing
that offends me the most is every time
that I hear the n-word not nigger by the
way I mean the Edwards literally
whenever a white lady on CNN with nice
hair says that Edward that's just white
people getting away with saying nigger
that's all that is they found a way
bigger and word it's bullshit cuz when
you say that n-word you put the word
nigger in the listeners head that's what
saying word is you say the n-word like
oh she means nigger you're making me say
it in my head what are you fucking say
it instead take responsibility
goodness shitty words you want to say
just say it don't hide behind the first
letter like a faggot just say nigger you
stupid punch i don't know i don't i
don't care
real kicks my ass I mean all this shit
goes on in my head I don't really you'd
like I thought the word nigger the other
day I'm gonna tell you this story and it
wasn't racist there wasn't a race even
context let me tell you what happened I
went to a coffee place and it was a cool
like a cool indie car I don't like
Starbucks anymore because you go there
and they don't care anymore they just
press a button and some old lady's
diarrhea comes out they just give us
real so I gonna like a young people cool
coffee plays like my bands playing
notices on the walls it's called like
the howling do whatever thing and the
dude behind the counters got a tight
t-shirt in a ponytail anees exudes of
man and I was like hey could I get a
cappuccino he's like yeah right on
generally like he's amazed that he could
help me like oh yeah I got all this
stuff right here that's awesome
and so he starts making my coffee just
so he worked so hard he ground the beans
just for the that one cup and put him in
the thing and tamp them with his old
thing and you click clack and click and
him that he took a milky profit like for
like an hour and they banged it on the
counter why it was awesome and he
scooped it in and put a little cocoa on
it hey there you go then and I was just
blown away and for some reason as i left
there the thought in my head was that
nigger made this shit out of my coffee
for what he wasn't black that's just
what was in my heart for some reason was
that nigger made the shit out of my coma
I don't care
I'm all sweaty okay Oh feel good I ate
too much and masturbated to recently you
know that kind of you know it's bad to
like jerk off and run out the door cuz
you run into somebody oh she knows like
you just gotta take some time alone I'm
gonna process the shame and I just I
can't stop it today I weighed myself
today I don't know what why I'm not
using the information it's not guiding
my behavior why am i bothering to find
out exactly how much of a piece of shit
I am I weighed myself and I usually a
hover round 2 30 to 40 today 240 I wait
240 Alex which is not oh no it's not
okay because there's no way like you
know when you go to a doctor to give you
like a formula for how much your way
like a rule of thumb it i'm pretty sure
it's not your age plus 200 pounds
that doesn't seem like like I was
watching a boxing match today and the
bolt guy they weighed 110 pounds each so
both of those guys still need a fat baby
in a dead dog to make man and its really
bad cuz I'm 40 and my doctors like you
gotta be less people you can't be so
much he just told me this is bad and he
starts asking me about my eating habits
you know like there's habits like
there's a pattern it's just chaos and
awfulness it's just desperate cuz he's
like how many meals and how many ball
movements a day I'm like I have no idea
I have no idea it's just a bore I'm just
shitting and eaten all day I will pack
my body to capacity and then blow it out
my asshole that's it every shit is an
emergency does that give you some idea
of my eating habits and he's trying to
get a handle on my knees like dual okay
look well how soon into a meal do you
typically feel full and stop eating I'm
like I don't stop eating when I'm full
the meal is not over when I'm full the
meal is over when I hate myself that's
nice that's when I stopped I guess
normal people eat till they're like oh
that's I just that's all the nutrition I
require right there I just reached it I
will cease the intake now and convert
this into useful energy throughout the
day now every time I eat it ends with me
why the bug to get it away i don't want
look at that shit that's all isn't right
here too it's like i got syrup in my
veins like for blood i got served
it's gonna be bad later oh I can't take
it hurt myself and I'm always just
uncomfortable just sweaty and just like
I this is such a bummer like it's my
nightmare it's my whole life that thing
that ever happened to me was boxer
briefs I'm so happy about boxer briefs
it doesn't seem like a big deal to most
people but before boxer briefs I was
trapped between the two awful worlds of
briefs and boxers briefs are for a
normal man with one leg here and one leg
here two totally separate legs with a
whole area between and the briefs go up
into this little Valley this little area
and I come down like this and they can
just make it just tuck up in there and
just hold them nicely because he's got
all that air and negative space but this
is just all just mashed together just
upsetting sting II read sweaty
just just like this looks like a pig's
ass when I'm David like even my dick is
curly like the tail this is a pig's ass
and I pull brief on they just are here
and they grabbed my dick and balls
here's your balls fat bastard you're
like that
and they just dig up in there with this
viciously sharp cotton and right after a
while I'd have just this wad of just
damp cloth just a lot of wet cotton just
like the size of a tennis ball like a
huge wad of wet cotton and boxers were
worse because they're just they just let
everything flap around and touch each
other and upset each other I need
everything to be segregated down here I
need everything would stick in and just
get and also when I had boxers on for
some reason I always had just water
like that like a quarter cup of water
just sloshing around my asshole all the
time
this water is hovering around my asshole
define gravity to like an upside-down
glass of water my ass I gotta manage
Mike cuz i cant savvy now you exercise a
lot i run five miles every other day to
manage it maintain this shit body that I
have because the food man I like high
octane crap like the wool the other day
I got a Cinnabon do you know what a
Cinnabon is let me explain Cinnabons to
those of you with self-respect who just
walked right by shit like that and have
no idea what dudes like me are you
because the line at Cinnabon is not a
varied group of people it's not all
kinds of folks trying out a Cinnabon
it's not like there's a skinny rich I
knees girl and then a little dude it's
just and no one's happy on the Cinnabon
line no one's like I love these they
can't wait no one's excited to get one
it's all dudes like me or fatter Santa
oh fuck i'm getting a Cinnabon
I gotta cancel that she was gonna do too
because this is gonna be here's what I
said about it let me explain to you it's
a six-foot-high cinnamon swirl cake made
for one sad fat man even if you if you
have a vagina you were a man if you're
eating a Cinnabon that moment it's a
sticky hot bun and it comes with a
little tub of Jersey hot syrup it's not
come there's no way that's not hot rod
how is that not come they should call it
a fat faggot tree just too
just to make us say that when we fuck is
Wilson we don't slow us down we don't
give a shit yeah give me a fat faggot
treat please
yeah with a hot cum dude I don't care
what do you think i have integrity i'm
buying a Cinnabon right now i'm buying a
cinnabon at the airport that i arrived
at
you understand why that's extra
disgusting right when you're leaving if
you're at your destiny you know when
you're let the airport you're leaving
for you can go like oh I gotta eat I
need to food cuz i might be trapped in
the sky forever and I should eat right
now but this is I've landed the trip is
over I'm 20 minutes from my house where
I got bananas and apples and shit and
I'm sitting on my luggage just fucking
eating a Cinnabon for the fork at night
just uh it was a shitty 12 it was old
the dude that's the thing he was about
to take it in and close now I gave me
gave me that give me that give me that
now and he didn't want to sell to me
like these videos please don't bite
don't buy it cool I was like dude I'm
eating man that's what's gonna happen
next
you decide if we're going to be in the
paper tomorrow but that shit's going in
my face
I already made the shitty decision don't
ruin it just give me the just give me
the jiz oh yes thank you Jim just
drinking the jizz with my eyes closed
Cinnabons is a big fat faggot that i am
i am i'm a fat faggot
is the or you are you know I mean I'm 40
now and that's you know I mean I'm 40
I'm half dead basically for you 40 some
weird days you get this point where like
you're not old enough for anybody to
give his shitty year old nobody's like I
helped a 40 year old guy today and it
felt really good to do something for him
nobody spends their holidays delivering
hot meals with four-year-olds and you're
not young enough for anybody ever be
proud of you or impressed they're just
like yeah do your job asshole nobody
cares that's what you're supposed to do
and the world looks eat it like when you
were 40 if you go to the doctor the doc
guess what they don't try to fix
anything anymore they stop trying to fix
shit when you get to be 40 they don't
they just go yeah it starts to happen
they don't care I went to the doctor cuz
my ankle hurt right now if you're 20 and
you have a bad shoulder the doctor will
reconstruct your shoulder through
miracles of modern science they'll take
your ear make up shoulder out of it it's
weird but when you're 40 they just give
you no options they took care I went cuz
my ankle like I was limping for like a
month out of nowhere and the doctor he
brings me any shows me an x-ray of my
ankle he's like yeah your ankles just
just worn out
like what do you mean I injured my ankle
he's like no it's just shitty now just
see that dark area yeah it's all
hardened yeah they get like that and
they're not good anymore I was like well
so just goodbye nothing is there nothing
you're just nothing there's no out it's
like an incurable shitty ankle is it it
goes well there's things you can do you
can stretch for a half hour a day you
should stretch your ankle like how long
will that take to fix he's like no you
just do that now that's just a new thing
you do until you and your shitty ankle
both die cuz I can do this hurts a lot I
think as well you can take a lead just
take a leave you can buy it just take it
and you can take whatever amount it
doesn't matter like don't pay attention
to the dosage look like really is it
yeah you could take ten a day you'd be
fine he said take ten aleve a day I said
I heard that stuff like hurt your
intestines he goes oh yeah it'll do some
intestinal damage after a while
but you just gotta weigh that against
how much you like your ankle not hurting
this is all totally true by the way this
is exactly what happened and at one
point I was like what if I was like an
athlete or somebody goes you're not an
athlete so no to whatever else you were
about to say bleak hard for old people
well I don't have my grandma's 95 she
can't see out of her left eye just shut
off the last time we went steer she
think I can't see out of my left eye and
where I go hey what was Christmas like
at the 40s maybe run out the clock on
the eye thing of her lucky you know so I
go to work doctor he's right at the end
of the hall he's they're always like 90
feet away from her so they go to the
doctor and I said you know she can't see
out of her left eye at all and I swear
to god he goes well she's probably got a
bunch of tumors in her head I swear to
God that's exactly what he said I
remember cuz I was blown away by how
none of his education he applied
to this particular diagnosis he said
this just probably got a bunch of tumors
in her head
he's a talker he called in her head
he almost said fucking head I swear to
God like this what he was thinking
talking about the tumors in her fucking
head Oh gives a shit that will be dead
in a week I ain't gonna get up with my
death as it were I what does she need
two eyes to see the shitty place you
click on Twitter cuz you don't love her
enough
I think my ain't there yet I'm halfway
there 40 year old guys are not good
specimens either we're not like I have a
friend who has a lot of young
girlfriends he always goes any and there
he goes a little too they're too young
and it's not okay you know he brings him
around you're like dude don't like
literally pointed her face ago don't
fuck her that's awful because and she's
like yeah then just bad you know but so
he was gonna have sex with her one night
and he said he wanted to go all night
like you wanted to really lasts a long
time so he said I'm gonna drink a lot of
milk so I can have a lot of sex like who
told you that that matter and he goes
well cuz you can come more if you drink
milk this guy actually thinks that like
you run out of cum but if you drink milk
your bot your body goes like oh dude
that's River you just send that way
through that's
nobody'll know the difference is go
ahead as an adverb
run out of common a pinch milk is fine
it doesn't you know this matter but
Senate right through sprayed all over
his cat's face whatever he was doing
what I'll come on my cat's face
if she's watching she's gonna get a face
full of cum she knows that right now she
knows her fall now
come on my cat's face once shame on me
I don't have a cat I never had one I
mean I would come on a cat's face i'm
not trying to say about trying to take
that back i just don't have a navicat i
have a dog and I had a dog when I was a
teenager and yeah I did once I i made my
dog like cottage cheese off my balls
which is something you now can't unknow
you just know it I did this and I only
hesitated to start the sentence only
because I wasn't sure whether to say
that I left my dog like how does shoes
off my balls or that I made him like
cottage cheese and really considering
how much dogs love geez I think I i have
this I made him an offer he couldn't
refuse I think that's highly the fairest
way to put it
I remember it so clearly and I remember
the look on the dog's face he was like
are you doing this to us just put it on
a plate why do I have to lick it off
your goddamn balls all right come on
fine let's do it I'm doing it I don't
care but you gotta live with it I'll be
dead in two years I'm a dog this is your
problem sorry I'm being so negative yes
I'm a bummer i don't know i shouldn't be
i'm a very you know lucky guy i got a
lot going for me i'm healthy relatively
young i'm white which thank God for that
shit boy that is a huge leg up are you
kidding me oh god I love being white I
really do seriously if you're not what
you're missing out because this shit is
thoroughly good it but let me be clear
by the way I'm not saying that white
people are better I'm saying that being
white is clearly better who could even
argue if it was an option I would
reappear all y'all take away to get
absolutely everything
stick with white thank you here's how
great it is to be white I could get in a
time machine and go to any time and it
would be fucking awesome when I get
there
that is exclusively a white privilege
why people can't fuck with time machines
a black guy the time she's like hey the
before tonight 80 No thank you I don't
wanna go but I can go to any time the
year too I don't even know wasn't
happening then but I know when I get
there welcome we have a table right here
for you sir thank you it's lovely here
in the year too I can go to any time in
the past I don't want to go to the
future and find out what happens to
white people because we're gonna pay
hard for this shit you got to know that
we're not gonna just fall from number
one to two they're gonna hold us down
and fuck us in the ass forever and we
totally deserve it but for now
now if you're if you're white and you
don't admit that it's great you're an
asshole it is grand I'm a man how many
advantages are could one person have I'm
a white man you you can't even hurt my
feelings what can you really call a
white man that really digs dije cracker
well ruin my day boy shouldn't a call me
a cracker bringing me back up owning
land and people what a drag I am married
oh that takes me down a few pegs
the other night my wife sent me to
walgreens to get toilet paper because we
were out of toilet paper because I had
thrown at all in the garbage so I could
get out of the house
so driving a walgreens was nighttime now
driving and then my I see a deer and
fucking hate dear I hate him because
they're everywhere up there I used to
live in the city and I love dear then
because I was a liberal in the city and
I'd see dear you know your drive on your
friends out to the country and you see a
deer nervous that creature scare you
it's just look at the beautiful team
look at me looks around it's just so
mysterious
I gave us a gift everybody just enjoy
enjoy
but I live in deer are in my fucking
yard every day and they suck they're
just rats with whose they don't matter
they have dicks that give you Lyme
disease and they shit everywhere and
they make a noise did you know that they
go they're assholes there's shit animals
I go out every wearing and throw rocks
in them and I try really hard to hit
them in on the head with rocks and they
don't care though yeah I don't care
I don't have a gun but if I did I would
shoot a baby deer in the mouth and feel
nothing I wouldn't feel anything I just
got all look he's dead that's
interesting I guess that's what happens
when you shoot him in the fucking mouth
I go out of my way to kill a deer I
would happily blow 20 guys in an alley
with bleedy dicks so I could get even
fucking deer and kill it with my eggs
second I mean it I mean it so I see this
deer and this is how dumb he's did I get
hit him with the headlights and he does
do that whole thing and then he won't
just go he's like gonna be okay if I go
thank you I'm like fucking go go nothing
new just gah
and then I got caught and I try to kind
of get away from it then I see him he
looks mean I mannix I spreading ran and
smashed his body into my fucking car
like just destroyed my mirror just
shattered my mirror broke his neck I
heard him break his own fucking neck and
then he just dragged his stupid deer
head into the woods and he died
and I'm glad dead
I was glad right away I got out of my
car I did not yelled in the woods I'm
glad you're dead you fucking idiot
hope your dear wife finds you dead dies
of a broken heart
hope your dear baby sorry to death broke
my Miriam faggot hunt nigger dear
so i go to walgreens going I got to buy
drugs all the time cuz I got kids kids
are like buckets of disease that live in
your house and you get sick from all the
time I got sick last week I had a flu
that I caught because my daughter
coughed into my mouth just hit me right
in the back of the throat Mike thanks
honey I'm sick right now I can feel it
already she did this by the way because
she's trying to tell me a secret and she
thinks you tell secrets into people's
mouths she takes her whole face
which is inconsiderate borderline
retarded behavior yes ma'am and by the
way she's 55 years old what secret does
she have that I really need to hear like
she's gonna tell me a secret I'm gonna
go holy shit are you serious oh my god
honey I won't tell anybody that is
fucked up though seriously she got an
abortion on Christmas Eve she's fine
five years old you know that means
nothing that she says matters she's
never said anything actually important
in her entire life I literally put a
miss every word this fucking kid has
ever said and nothing would be different
everything would have been exactly the
same I enjoy the things she says they're
beautiful and poetic I love hearing them
but I don't have to fucking hear any of
it and that's an important distinction
if you're a parent you just start making
it because you can't listen to him all
the time that they're talking because
they're talking all the time and they
just talk whenever they don't give a
shit what you're doing or if it's a good
time you i'm gonna shoot out with a
cop's and she's telling me all kinds of
shit she doesn't care because she's
fight they don't they're self-absorbed
people they have no ability no
five-year-old ever goes like no go ahead
and finish i'll tell you have first
claim they just can't and sometimes it's
impossible i like the other day i was in
new york city with my kids I got two of
these fucking things remember that
please too and i'm wearing the crowded
streets I got this one here the
two-year-old I'm care she can walk but
she won't stab ol shitter so I'm
carrying her and she weighs like 20
babies this kid I don't she's tiny but
she's got the density of a dying son I
don't understand
how she's this heavy it feels like a fat
raccoon holding a bowling ball that's
what it feels like and the pain in my
shoulder is intense and it's sending
signals to my brain like you don't love
her just drop her she doesn't matter to
better diet so I'm fighting that on this
side I got the fiber old like this I
hope it's her I haven't looked back in
about just dragging somebody tiny just
through many strangers by briefcase
corners were here in the temple I don't
give a shit I'm in a hurry cuz my
pockets vibrating at my wife's calling
to see where I am even though that she
sent me to do this shit and I'm yelling
in my pocket like she gonna hear me out
and this one is talking the whole time
the whole time with a tiny voice two
feet off the ground what am I gonna
listen to this shit really what am I
gonna take a knee every two seconds was
a sweetie go ahead what's that huh what
excuse me sir go ahead it's fine yeah
yeah sometimes dogs are brown that's
very true good thinking of missing that
shit coming out of your stupid face kind
of a father would I be if I pretended to
listen to that I'm air the first time I
daughters had a whole sentence that was
a big deal because she had never made a
whole lot by herself she just said the
little words and I was doing the dishes
and behind me I just hear she just goes
daddy I don't like chicken I dropped my
plate my wife and I cried and hugged a
big moment a week later I'm making
dinner she goes daddy I don't like
chicken will your for fucking have it
chicken what he was talking about
only chick I like you okay I don't like
you I like people that make me work it
don't appreciate what I make for them
you don't like chicken make whatever the
fuck you want then get out of your
shitty little plastic chair and make
your own good whatever it is you want so
much I don't like check it you like the
chicken when I shove it up your ass cuz
that's where it's going if you don't eat
it seriously I will grind it up in the
Cuisinart and then blow it up your ass
for the straws I gotta feed her she's
got a nice when your kid won't eat you
just go crazy because you have a
physical need to feed them it's an
instinct and when they're sinners just
looking at their food you're like just
fucking it up you'll die you idiot eat
the food
and I like it it doesn't matter put it
in your face they have your footprint at
the hospital they know that I have you
I'm not a lot let you die you piece of
shit eat it you have a social security
number your on the grid motherfucker eat
if you're skinny I go to jail to
understand and I love my kids and I die
for them but that my life is fucking
stinks it just does it what it is when
you're a parent you know you're told all
the pleasures are gone you don't nobody
fucks you ever again that's just over
you don't you you can't sleep you don't
sleep you don't eat you don't eat meals
you just eat at the sink fast standing
up some macaroni and cheese that she
didn't fuckin eat that's your dinner now
with people yelling you hurry i'm just
trying to get those you don't do
anything fun your single friends like
did you see that movie nine see the
fuckin movie okay and you can't even
enjoy being a parent because there's no
no pride in it cuz we suck at it
everybody suck we make huge mistakes and
then you just go whoops permanent damage
their move on I guess my five-year-old
has all these switches and weird fears
am I good luck with that shit honey
that's all my handy
sorry and it gets harder to do you think
it's gonna get easier like when they're
babies you think that's the hard part
because you got to do everything you
gotta feed them you gotta put their
clothes on you got to put them in the
car you got to do everything but you
think it's gonna get easier because
they're gonna grow up and do all this
shit for themselves but they're not
they're gonna grow up and be able to but
they fucking won't do it so it's
actually easier when they're babies cuz
when they when you want them to ease is
take food and just shove it in their
face you gotta put on a shoe you just
take a foot shoe on it pull her arms
through the sweater
throw in the car the door closed
and then you get the parents live for
the tiny vacations from their kids the
little tiny like when you when you put
your kids in the car and you close their
door and that little walk around to your
own door it's like a carnival cruise
it's just the greatest uh and you just
stand at your door like okay fellows bad
bullshit was what i say Fargo's fan I
was changed my daughter the other day
and she's too old for diapers now but
she's still in him it's bad because this
kid does not boot this kid cracks this
is not okay anymore I was change your
attack the other day it was like a 48
year old alcoholic man's shit in her
diaper like she was out all night
drinking jager she went to dennys and
got a grand slam
ate half of it got in a fight in the
parking lot and pass out a Pontiac and
shit herself her friends drove her home
with the windows open and dumped her on
my lawn and now I gotta clean it and
it's crazy and you can't even react you
can't go like what the fuck that's
disgusting hey you'll fuck him up about
their own shit you got to be nice you
opened our diaper is just chaos in there
it's just bananas it's just I've every
new every shit amazes me I'm never used
to it everyone I'm like okay wow that is
what is that you have been eating
diarrhea for a week I think cuz that's
awful and but you can't you gotta feel
like you know you just go oh wow you
really got something there honey cuz
that's really something that's really
okay
well all right let me scrape that off
your knees for you down off your back
get all this hazmat in one place white
deep down clean your tiny vagina at the
end who know that that was gonna be my
life I had no idea that my relationship
to the vagina was going to be clean and
shit out of a tiny one several times a
day they don't tell you that when you're
getting ready to be a dad nobody pulls
you the size that you know you have to
clean the vagina alot because every time
she takes a shit it goes straight up or
twat they don't tell you
nobody tells you and they should it's a
big part of being a debt it's bigger
than Christmas happens every day you got
to get it right print it back very
important I'm glad I got girls though
girls are great I I don't want to clean
shit off with some kids balls I'm glad
that's not my job I don't boys feel
weird about them I got nephews they come
over and they play in the sprinkler
naked with a little red Dixon I just
don't like their little penises bother
me I don't know I just get this weird
feeling like they're gonna come over and
fuck my nose or something with a little
bit I know it's an irrational fear but
it's very real to me
I'm gonna fall asleep in a launch here
we go
please put in my home
to the Queen fuck yeah
control your kids could you they're
fucking my nose while I'm sleeping boys
are hard to raise man i have so all my
sisters have boys and I just feel for
him because it's really hard and they
really do here's the thing though girls
are just as hard to raise but I'm not a
hole at the level they just they're
different here's the difference to me
between boys and girls boys fuck things
up girls are fucked up that's the
difference boys just do damage to your
house that you can measure in dollars
like a hurricane
girls like leave scars in your psyche
that you find later like a genocide or
an atrocity like my sister-in-law came
over once with her little boy he's like
four years old and she comes over and
she's just she's been with him all day
so she's bad shape she's got a drink
that she's like I can't do that I can't
do it again do it anymore and I put like
an army blanket around her trying to
calm her down and then her little boy
walks up her he's got a handful of sand
I don't know where you got it there's no
sign of my home he's got a handful of it
walks up to his mom and just throws it
right in her drink
it's all she had and he just ruined it
really confident to not like this year's
I guess where that shit goes right there
and I was blown away by this because I
have girls they would never dream of
doing that it wouldn't even enter their
heads that a person could do that but
they're fucked up like my five-year-old
the other day she whenever toys broke
and she demanded that I break her
sisters toy to make it fair and I did
that's how much shit she gave me I broke
with a little toy and I fell the awful I
was like crying and I look at her she's
got this creepy smile on her face that's
that's the difference between boys and
girls and it becomes the difference
between men and women really because a
man will like steal your car or burn
your house down or beat the shit out of
you but a woman will ruin your fucking
life do you see the difference like a
man will cut your arm off him throw it
in a river but he'll leave you as a
human being intact he won't fuck with
who you are women are non-violence but
they will shit inside of your heart
my wife and I we've been we've been
married for about nine years now so
we're almost done
after nine years of two kids you start
looking into the like no you do just
keep doing this it would do that we went
to therapy for a while and the therapist
was I eat one day he goes that you
should go on a date yeah I'm like fuck
you I'm not gonna go i did go on a date
with my wife and i don't think i'm gonna
call her again wasn't really fun some
things do get easier as you've been
married for a while you start to
understand each other better and you
start looking at yourself more you spend
a lot of your marriage litter the other
person in trying to change them or
figure them out let me start realizing
what you're bringing to the table you
blame them less free shit you know like
my wife will never fuck me again I know
that now but I just feel differently
about it I used to get Maddie's guys
she's in fucked me in months how could
she do that to me now I look at myself
and i'm like how did she fuck me for
years she fired me for years she
couldn't possibly have enjoyed most of
those fucks which means she took about
five hundred for the team you gotta
respect that shit
cuz I'm gonna because it's I think it's
hard for women to have sex if they don't
feel like it it's not ask Elly they have
generally men have it that's just
different with different sexual skills
men can fuck whatever we don't care will
fuck you when if we don't like you
everybody knows that but will fuck you
even if we don't be like fucking you
even if we're not hard oh fuck you give
me a second find a way you don't care
fuck things will fuck a rusty key hole
nailed to a donkey's ass we don't give a
shit we are jizz on demand we just have
no we don't care women have another
skill which is that they can decide
whether or not to have sex with their
minds which is amazing to me we're gonna
decide not to fuck in the middle of
fucking and it's so weird to me that
they can just stop cuz it's some other
shit that distracted them if I'm fucking
you you could show me a picture of you
cut my mom's head off and I'll be like
whoa
hmm
soon as I come we're gonna have a talk
about that that's really
because I need to come my knee 22 coming
is in need I came the first time when I
was 12 and I haven't skipped a day I
come every day and I fucked maybe 20
times in my life so it's just been me
doing most of the work and I really you
know I jerk off way too much and it's
upsets me I don't know why it is because
it's so selfish I don't know what it is
by no it's bad I don't want her to
somebody somewhere there's something
wrong with like I was thinking the other
day that you can figure out how bad a
person you are by how soon after
September 11th you masturbated like how
long you waited and for me it was
between the two buildings going down so
I
I had to do it i had to otherwise they
win that's the way i was looking at it
at the time these are the strange time
bro
I know you all waited a whole week
because you're awesome but I just
couldn't do it a boner boner it's got to
go something's gonna happen ballers just
they ruin everything and I really hate
boners I hate everyone I've ever had I
remember the first time I was nine
that's the worst thing about a little
boy's life is that you start getting
boners when you're nine and you don't
come for three fucking years it's three
years of just vicious little boners they
don't go away you just pass out moaning
in a ditch somewhere and you wake up
you're so hard it's awful if you ever
see a nine-year-old boy on the street
just give him 20 bucks cuz he's very
gonna happen or it's like a sting
however you feel like you're gonna help
him out I remember that man i remember
being nine just being hard and not
knowing why or what to do I just would
rub my dick against stuff that's all I
did everything I if I was sitting in
front of a car just press it against the
car oh it's warm from the Sun it's good
I used to run home from school after
school so I could fuck my whole house
basically I would just fuck the house I
fuck the walls and the floor if you have
a nine-year-old boy at home he's fucking
your house right now cuz that's what we
do I just fuck that we had a quarter or
a couch that house is my bitch I fucked
it all day just pumping with no results
just frustrated I do weird things with
my big to like I'd close it in the
refrigerator door I don't know why I
just like the pressure I like that one
side was metal and the other was at
accordion like rubber with a magnet in
it I just put the cold air on my balls
this kids good I don't know why it's
good
I don't know how I ever got laid really
cuz I was awful at it I still am I never
understood like there's guys they just
have this confidence and they can like
go out with a girl no one to lean in and
kiss her and shit I just I couldn't I
would just go could I fuck you like I
just blurted it out I remember when I
was with a girl I was like 20 years old
it's already doing stand-up and I did a
show in Washington DC and after the show
one of the waitresses came back to my
hotel she was really cute and we're
making out in my hotel and she's into it
she's like humping me so I started
putting my hand up her shirt and she
stops me oh my okay so then we're making
out more and I start putting my hand her
ass and she stops me so after a while
she went home nothing happened and then
the next night I started the club and
she goes uh hey what happened last night
I was like what and she goes how come we
didn't have sex I was like cuz you
didn't want to she's like yes I did I
was really into it I was like why did
you keep stopping me and she goes cuz I
wanted you to just go for it was like
what does that mean she says I'm kind of
weird i get to her gone when a guy just
gets frustrated and just hold me down
and fucks me like that's a big turn on
I was like what you should have told me
I wouldn't happen he done that for you
she says now it has to feel real and
dangerous like weather out of your
fucking mind you think I'm just gonna
rape you on the off-chance that whole
clear into that shit
an idiot I'm getting kind of a rapey
vibe from this girl I suspect you might
enjoy being raped maybe that's her thing
I don't want to ask first ruin it so
just take a shot and rayver what the
hell what's the worst that could happen
after all she is but anyway that's all
history sex for me it's gone it's just
me and my wife and it's sad because my
wife is beautiful i love to look at her
and I feel for she's gorgeous she really
is she's she just turned 40 and she
looks awesome and it's not because she
looks younger than 40 she looks 40 on
the nose but I like that I didn't know I
would but I find it really sexy I like I
like women women it's a huge turn-on
she's got she's she's got gray streaks
in her hair and I find that sexy I
really do she's got strong arms from
picking up the kids she's strong and
sexy on a whole other level you know
she's changing she smells different
she's def blue eyes they're black now
she's like intense kind of crazy looking
you know
all these lines in her face small as
shit I did to her you know she's a
character she looks like one of those
pictures from the depression of the Dust
Bowl farmers she's intense I like it it
turns me on that's what I like now I
like women women women you know girls
I'm done a long time ago 22 year old
girls god bless you go do a shot
whatever the fuck you do for your time
that's not me anymore I like women and I
know that that's offensive to 22 girl
girls like Hollywood I thought he was a
jazz and I'll and not to me sorry to me
you're not a woman till you had a couple
of kids and your life is in the toilet
that's really when you become a woman is
when people come out of your vagina and
step on your dreams you're still
standing after that shit you are a woman
if your cell go to clubs you have a
ponytail little dress you're standing
outside of a club waiting to get in is
two degrees you got no Jack it's a
little dress and it'd be great in there
you're a girl
I wanna give you a sweater to ride home
I don't want to fight I'll jerk off you
but I want to fuck you again Whitaker I
do wanna fuck you buddy won't fuck me so
fuck you anyway but I I would totally
fight you but this is the difference
between girls and women and it's not
about age like that's there's a reason
why they call it girls gone wild you
notice there's no women gone wild cuz no
one would fuckin by the wild women DVD
because when girls go wild they show
their tits to people when women go wild
they kill men and drown their kids in a
tub that's what wild women do they don't
show their tits to nobody they fuck with
their bras ons all other thing try
taking your four-year-old wife's picture
when she comes out of the shower fuck
you get the fuck out of here
it's not funny she said you thought it
would be cute like don't like fuck off
sorry cuz she doesn't have kids anymore
she has breasts that need to be checked
and maintains I get bills for my wife's
breast that's some grown-up woman shit
right there girls have the titties with
a little perky nipples and that's
awesome but you're not a woman so you
got long chewed up nipples
and you're not a man who you suck one of
those fucking big cheater by the way
thank you very much thank you
you