now
c'mon hereby commend our brother to you
lord and so it remains that Mathew
Cordell now live on in your eternal
prison my new they serve a cannot sit in
judgment of this man any more than we
might sit in judgment of those
responsible for his false imprisonment
and untimely demise you know damn well
in your mercy and love please forgive
whatever sins he may have committed
through human weakness
I said
you know
under
I
you
hey man aren't you supposed to be off of
some political bullshit that's right
just warming up huh so what's up the no
headgear I love the sound of them why
don't you out celebrating don't feel
like it go out for Christ's sake it's
your birthday you don't have some fun go
to a movie I mean anything standing
around here shooting at an animus bad
guys all night maybe they're not so
anonymous to me anybody I know yeah
maybe Hank honey from the mayor's office
what's the problem follow me it's a
deputation to answer excessive force
seems to be the popular complaint he
stays broke the bastards cheap phone
what was the charge attempted rape next
time wait a little longer now you can
kill the bastard
hello posture where accuracy is never a
problem well you know they are on the
maniac tape would you consider that a
compliment hey what happy birthday kid
crazy hey Mac I love it
Mac down here what's your step sorry had
a call you out of the function give me a
favor Lee I will see it some gruesome
shit least he died with a smile on his
face very funny
genet news out of here
should be good yeah what is it what do
you got homeless guy how about an angle
me kitty want an angle huh about 180
degrees I may give me a break huh so
routine OD you want to check it out go
ahead but if you were smart you go down
a 29th in park I got a jumper you ain't
what's up
good fucking McKinney not a son of a
bitch really gave us a shack that free I
knew there was no jump I knew it didn't
couldn't tell me trying to get rid of us
what else we got huh okay let's see what
we got I'm gonna bomb scare long island
city until the airport maybe string the
both of them together now the oh it's
not well drug-related homicide soho
National Guard wait a minute these are
the kid black male 18 to 25 couldn't be
a fucking Irishman or a fucking Greek so
they could high on drugs next next got a
four alarm fire in Brooklyn what about
it wait come on the network's won't even
consider it unless there's at least
three confirmed dead it's a warehouse
fucking mattress warehouse forget it
fuckin somebody
what are you doing praying to the news
guys the gram it's just one good
misfortune so Mike we're gonna chalk
this up as a routine out there let me
ask you something what do you think did
they stop the chicken Dinah's guys
throat before your dealer ft it's paulo
my own Bay you're not thinking about
food now are you spin-off of Santeria
they use the heads for their rituals how
you know about there's a potion ever
since Cordell it's been an interest in
mine they like this pull faster for his
head no they probably found them dead
they just got there before we do side as
a bird plainness it's a courtesy to the
stiff allows the soul to take flight
does it hurt is it hurt mrs. Sullivan
1084 arrived at seen cannot stir an
extent of activity inside an entrance
investigate over
bitch got us a shooter officer Kate
Sullivan it's beautiful
oh cool what does appeal come on
zooming out bit go ahead idea you want
to see your face when you come back here
give me a smooth what the hell is wrong
with you you stupid jerk hey carries the
spirit hot Harry's so ahead with no
heart spirit but no soul
you see what went down here I see what
you see
I saw a symbol dirt two triangles facing
each other across the line you see the
symbol of anti justice you can't touch
me stick with it stick with it
alright
Oh
this filthy creeps gonna make us rich
and we're on TV wait hi mom
drop the gun look like your kiddies
downs this would be on the world news
tomorrow oh yeah help you so let the kid
go no I don't want to I'll give you a
count of 10 oh is that what you're gonna
do one two three lady you can't hurt me
beside the mortal look at the sick
bastard for what she's done come down
backups on its way you're shocked you
bust him in
I'm buying a new foreign car
got a poem baby i'll finish no religion
catholic get a priest
I'm losing her pulse is 32
Oh Sean miss Ellen place what's
happening to my baby she was involved
with chewy the police brought me here
they said something about a chess move
but nobody tells me how bad it is they
don't know yet mrs. on you've always
been her protector please make sure she
got the best of care missile oven I have
seen wooden papers for you to sign if
the Lord calls her make sure they heard
of God
promise
lieutenant McKinney real would you like
to wait upstairs I think you'd be more
comfortable up there
you are first cop walked his speech in a
long time he's a dark days my friend I
need your very special kind of darkness
she went to kill me because I'm the one
responsible for your resurrection but
understand that could not have brought
you back unless you allowed it even I
cannot overcome the world a spirit
egress
and your spirit never Beatrice will it
harm
the gangs out there is the God who
raised the cops this psycho man their
plants one up check this out that Kate
Sullivan she kills us in the perpetrator
lives I mean what is this I Rap City
Cakes lucky meyerson's on duty tonight
Thanks what makes her lucky he's top of
the line in trauma well I hope so I
ought to know I've put him through med
school hope it wasn't a correspondence
course i'm standing outside larousse
pharmacy at 125th Street in Lexington
during an event which can only be
described as a black rainbow of terror
what began as a routine burglary call
ended in a gruesome tragedy earlier
tonight as a 19 year old pharmacist
assistant was brutally shot dead by
police news cameras were on the scene
with this shocking footage in what could
be the most chilling example of its kind
officer Kate Sullivan is seen here
shooting both hostage and suspect with
no apparent regard for innocent life
that's bullshit so if you call 911 and
Domino's we all know who's got to get
there first right you know something I
feel safer with a pizza you know I mean
while the suspect Frank Jessup is
recovering in the lock-up ward at queen
of Mercy Hospital at the center of the
controversy and fighting for her own
life is officer Kate Sullivan a six-year
veteran well known among her colleagues
as fearless opinionated and brash in
recent months she'd earned the nickname
maniac Kate a nod to another cop with a
knack for overkill a police spokesman
stated that an internal affairs
investigation has been initiated but for
this young pharmacist the last
prescription she filled was the bitter
pill of fate
look I find Katie seven floral are
thanks honey customs in Mexico City this
guy says to me you got anything to
declare I said yeah I can't focus my
eyes in a burns when I urinate oh they
help you yeah i'm looking for a doctor
nice who are you I'm friend of mckinney
well I'm Myerson can you tell me the
status of officer Sullivan she's alive
and he'd be a little more specific
reticular formations intact she got
primary whoa whoa whoa hey hey I'm a cop
not a doctor she can respirate and
eliminate you're telling me she's
Brendan yeah what's the prognosis stick
her in a rock garden I don't like your
sense of humor help these people
hey that cops up there right you know 12
shot the hostage okay
ask me she had it coming now time you
guys figured out this ain't the Wild
West pal don't you Cowboys yeah that's
just a bunch of funny cowboy hi-ho
silver
so how bad is the stench down at the
halls of Justice these days William oh
pretty bad um look uh don't tell anybody
where you got this from I never do city
it's gonna roll over on this case good
time let's come back he's already damn
self a lawyer now he's suing us so let
him soon he's a hopped-up junkie
nobody's gonna take him seriously
somebody or yes he's got himself a case
Mac your friend Kate she had herself an
automatic drop gun hollow points in the
service revolver come on price sake will
you been on the streets every hitter out
there's got that and more what are we
supposed to fight them back with pop
guns don't matter was her illegal
weapons cops can't use him you know that
I know that she knows that scumbag knows
that that's why I suing the city for ten
mil for each leg we pull out of it sorry
ass which at this point I think is up to
three what kind of deal are they're
gonna cut him
six months suspended sentence in
exchange for him dropping his suit
against the city what's that dedicating
just pretty friend doesn't make up
sit back Thank squirt some morphine in
my IV drip down my beautiful we wouldn't
want to turn you into an addict now
would we mr. Jessup oh my mind would be
a terrible thing to waste excuse me
that's the fella hi can I help you with
something yeah cuz like a minute I'm
sorry I don't have the time right now
with the patient oh I don't think that's
such a good idea I just need to ask him
a couple of questions no one minute one
minute please okay are you
told the story to your friends well you
know what I don't want the story come on
the truth did you wait for my memoirs
I'd rather not wait that long no I
didn't know my girl Terry but I do not
an officer and I know that when she puts
a slug between somebody's eyes Long's
they're not i want you to mull this over
I want you to think of that you don't
have to answer me now but are you
Schuller there is no balls so why does a
puppy all right there's something else
you forgot to tell you the 10 pitch wait
what's going on in here I don't see
nothing terrible when you have an itch
you can't scratch lieutenant the kitty
what went on in there we had a little
chat feeling if it had been a big chat
he'd be dead right now are you assigned
to this case it goes officially then I'm
gonna have to ask you to stay away from
my patient look not the father maybe I
slept out of line back there I don't
know anymore but katie is well she's
like a kid sister to me please try and
understand that
yes
good
nurse there's some kind of reaction from
Kate Sullivan dr. Fowler
I don't see any change her eyes were
open
you sure I know what I saw that monitor
was going crazy well there's nothing
there now she grabbed my hand like this
I'll go tell dr. Myerson you can't do
that if he knows it comes from me he
won't live defend her then he won't know
can you page dr. Myerson please dr.
Fowler so how come you so willing to
believe me cuz you don't strike me as
the kind of man with much imagination
lieutenant McKinney Thanks close him up
count the sponges hello gorgeous I just
came from kate's all of his room chest
wound uh-huh are you doing talking me
thought I might find you there I love it
when you pursue me you missed me don't
you not as much as you'd like to think
Oh anyway that's not what I came here to
talk about my loss there was Alf
activity on Kate's monitor mm-hmm and
she actually opened her eyes her monitor
was going crazy go crazy would that be
your exact professional diagnosis or
could you be any more specific no I
didn't stop to analyze the readings okay
how about crazy as a simple neural
seizure it's very common in cases like
this you take a 9-volt battery hook it
up to a dead froggy get about the same
result Peter I want you to authorize
another brain scan I can't do it why
because it is unwarranted it's it's a
waste of money it's a waste of time and
as far as I'm concerned it's a waste of
a bed she's Gumpy Peter listen please
Susan don't push me on this you know how
I react on it even you push me how about
dinner huh you're unbelievable if you
change your mind beat me I'm on vibrate
Oh
but
you
foula what are you doing down here did
you see a police officer nobody down
here but us what you better watch your
step it's dangerous down here with all
these pipes then I better get back
thanks
hey Mac don't smiley face this time
smiling on the inside
looks like a doctor here kiss something
with a hell of a jolt fried his brain is
right down to the nubs from the US this
one
they round up the staff anybody who
never used to smoke around Peter I
didn't want him to know just how much he
was warming his way under my skin
so tell me detective McKinney how do you
deal with pain chocolate chocolate that
I school
about a pint with a tunnel with green
works every time
sorry about your friend
Thanks you have any idea who might have
a motive to use that thing I lassie
practically everyone who works at this
hospital it's a hell of a lineup
maybe I ought to consider myself a
suspect well then you have to get up the
back of the wine
I've been meaning to ask you is there a
comp assigned to Kate's room know what
he was because i saw one leaving there
earlier I don't know I didn't get a good
look at him but he was huge and kind of
scary-looking I don't know why but I
followed him down to the tunnels under
the hospital what are the lead well they
used to connect with all the older
buildings in the area but now I think
they mostly don't know where
I've been expecting you in a Kenny I
have a way of attracting Satan restless
souls who find no comfort in
conventional wisdom I am a whore you
gone now got your razor up the dead does
that happen to include the secretion of
corpses stuffing them with dead chickens
you are not here to nail a humble
religious practitioner or mr. Minnick
corpse desecration
I want to know about resurrection I'm
not a priest some people you are some
people leave this world there unanswered
cry justice sometimes Dzeko don't die
away completely and when it does one
might be compelled to return but the
resurrection it's far or pain and
terrifying death cannot imagine to
torment since loss to walk alone on
living and not be alive
that must be the most cruel injustice
upon then you would know something about
caprara justice with new McKenney
where is he you're finding what makes
you so sure because you pull walk the
same man
we tied up after work tonight or what
god I love the smell of fresh plasma
before breakfast dr. Powell ah mr.
Cooney I'm hoping we might be able to
speak privately I've got my hands full
this morning my top trauma guy didn't
show up whoa sweetheart I off that
femoral there you could lose the leg
already has as far as I'm concerned
what's on your mind Kate some I'm
familiar with the case vegetative state
chronic right and there is some legal
precedent to remove her from life
support at this stage I'm not mistake
yes you're correct in certain situations
how we doing BP dropping going into
v-tach 50 cc's digit ox be prepared with
those paddles why do you ask well let's
just say we can save Kate a great deal
of pain and save this city great deal of
pain if we put an end to this episode we
need permission from next-to-skin
Christy over 25 hop another 50 what's
this that's the letter of consent signed
by the mother that's right we've been
talking to her she's a very agreeable
woman in fact he's a terrific lady BP
110 / 69 I think he's coming around
welcome back son nice to get down in the
trenches every once in a while keeps you
fit I would hope that we can accomplish
this in a timely fashion doctor I can
handle this this afternoon really that'd
be terrific sir I really thank you very
much and i know that cater to this you
could i'm sure she would well uh snowing
up there are we yes sir about time by
the way now that you're here ah i have
family coming in from out of town these
are real Knicks fans now I don't know
whether you can do anything about it but
the well I certainly can center court
for right next to Pat Riley how's that
sound perfect hey it's my pleasure who's
in there
don't appreciate my staff using this
hospital like a goddamn Greek restaurant
come on out was ever responsible for
this
Jake
where the heck are you driving live in
this neighborhood you're driving me
crazy I wouldn't feel safe we had a
police escort right now I swear to God I
mean either fucking National Guard to
coming through this place hurry up come
on let's get out of here where do you
suppose would happen we showed that cop
shooting in full my power I mean like no
don't cut out the stuff w to cut it out
come look at this rag top totality cells
just ask Rodney yeah I know but you
understand I'm fine yeah one little
twist that you can celebrate otherwise
we don't make a nickel I place shooting
five blocks from here Tara mice it's a
child but that's it
let's get this all right how much you to
go get the body chute the body alright
imma get some b-roll okay get you back
right hey did you see what got shot yeah
you did my fancy few questions great uh
was it a kid yeah yeah boy or girl girl
shot bad I'll been
shotgun did you know her
she's my sister
oh hey well life's a bitch I man
well is everybody
no trip
trip
should get a shot of this that's gonna
be it
would you get the tape else the bus you
bust him in why we got something here
what was an inside job Paul Katie this
will clear what helps
I think my client will be satisfied with
the basic terms but along with a
suspended sentence I think we need to
offer mr. Jessup the opportunity to
benefit from standard commercial
exploitation of his story literary
rights film rights TV appearance is that
sort of thing so what more do you need
from us when you reduce the sentence
just delete any reference to homicide or
manslaughter from the record those
distinctions would make it difficult for
him to benefit from collecting fees or
royalties and you can understand how
important that would be to mr. Jessup
well I'll see what I can do now have you
presented our offer to mr. Jessup oh no
as his attorney I feel I should be
satisfied with the general parameters
first no need and raising false
expectations oh of course not then i can
assume were in accordance mr. Jessup
will be very happy oh yeah hello Harry
listen I don't see any reason why I
can't have access to those records and
miss Lindsay yes man told you Gina of
course Hank once this is resolved maybe
you I can have a cocktail of her own and
do a little celebrating
I think we can agree on that okay great
i shut my lawyer fucking get another 150
what's this looks like a runaway step
I thought I told you not to mess with
other patients don't leave the cages
open I didn't
if you've got insurance oh yeah I should
send you a bill
dinner instead I don't know how long are
you planning to stick around this place
along if I can help
then I guess dinners out of the question
Mac I'm sorry bad timing k qs she's not
long could you stay off wife's hand
I'll take it from here coming with you
stay here
Mac I think you need me
come on
welcome back McKinney your path has
pitched his end what we do here is good
unite to torch souls in holy matrimony
that's bullshit there's nothing good or
holy about this you know that shit away
from her just too good
I can't imagine the kind of pain you
feel mad I'm not gonna pretend
but don't condemn her to the st. faiths
she deserves better you cleared it she's
at peace let her go man let it go finish
it
hey I'm below oh uh may I bar none I
cannot recover the soul she will not
allow it
oh my god it's you
let's go quita Marcy know
you
whoa
Oh
Wow
bitch
Oh
you
where are you
hey
take the wheel
wow this people
doing it step on the gas
Oh
you're getting that Python
nah
you
Oh