bye
mmm
down
all right mr. looks like you've got a
taillight problem no excuse running late
first vacation good getting tired well
that's too bad well can't you give us a
break officer well all right all right
sure to appreciate it we are running
kind of late well if you're running late
you should have started earlier anyhow
no tail light have it fixed Thank You
officer cut great job everybody great
job all right no no three separate cake
too and we can all impact I have to get
back on duty now I'm sure you can hang
out for a couple more minutes we're all
set up here sorry hell cron doesn't
sleep oh you'll get it just as soon as
we're done filming Debbie Wow leave it
up soon mr. Warren the faster makes me
up okay it's getting dark Donald you'll
be more comfortable once the sun is down
what I have to be a badly burned my
character would want her hair to be free
in this scene is it okay if I take my
scarf off well oh yeah that's fine
that's fine you know you guys we could
shoot the car seems anyway I mean we can
even shoot them right here I'm a
director and I same shoot the scenes
here all right larson scene 1 and art
rude we're almost there honey just a
little while longer then your vacation
starts fucking called mother I'm hungry
look we should be pretty close right now
the agent said it was 12 miles past
highway 10 that was highway gen back
there but you know we should have
stopped for better directions at the
last gas station listen I've never
gotten us lost before okay baby i'll put
the top rock never mind
she can come up and sit between us there
that's better baby they're going man
like there's nothing of that road now
look the sign pointed this way I don't
care let's just go ask those kids we saw
off the crossroads whoa okay okay but I
know we can't be wrong look the sign
pointed this way but it's were we didn't
make a wrong turn but you must have
where did the road go no need to get
upset we'll find it
this place cut cut cut cut Donald your
line there is wolf go don't care let's
just see if we can get some directions
look there's someone at the door
Who I am Toro I take care of the place
while the master is away but the child
I'm not sure the Master will approve or
the dog oh really a dog the master
doesn't like children we only want to
know where judge Caldwell's ranches
we're supposed to be filming there which
way to go there is no place like that
around here how I'm scared it's getting
dark well fargo which way is out of here
there is no way out of here it will be
dark soon there is no we help them here
no way you know you guys we could shoot
the night scenes here and then tomorrow
I'm gonna shoot here what but I don't
like a look for the place and the master
wouldn't approve well I don't know what
else we can do I mean hey welcome even
even be in the movie ah huh well I don't
know else we can do right now I don't
want to stay here let's leave I don't
know about it I just don't know
mr. warrior cold going uh well Dargo are
you in or out pace shit dear very well
ha the Master will be very disturbed it
I'll get the equipment Torgo will shoot
all right here and then tomorrow we can
go on us please you cannot stay the
master would not approve
how many times do we have to chase you
kids oh she's holy cow man you think
we're doing something wrong well
whatever it is you're not doing go don't
do it somewhere else oh I leave us alone
no no no wisecracks just get going okay
get going get going don't write already
see you're already Oh
so since him huh must be the master
himself Oh Hal I'm scared he has the
biggest look don't want to run of them
dead in the dark or the money for that
matter sinister sinister isn't
descriptive enough oh god oh haha yeah
that must be your master where'd you say
he was again he has left this world but
he is with us always no matter where we
go he's with us with some toys what is
that supposed to mean that dog it's the
most vicious looking animal I've ever
seen I'll be the winner goes there is
nothing to fear madam the master likes
you nothing will happen to you he likes
you likes me I thought you said he was
dead dead no madam not it the way you
know it he is with us always not dead
the way you know it he is with us oh how
I don't like this oh nothing to worry
about don't your imagination I think
it's best that I show you to the bedroom
now great I yeah we could do the bedroom
see how wasn't that supposed to be shot
with Bernie well yeah but his girlfriend
broke her leg so does have to shoot
around it mmm wait portal here in Philly
important uh-uh don't know the master
would oh no no don't worry about it if
he shows up and he's upset I love just
go on give him a share in the film and
he can't be upset about it uh yeah
oh ok ok I'll give them like I don't
know 10 shares you want to be a starter
don't you here ok you're just gripped
with violent napkins now let's get it
you
hey y'all
you take
Oh
you're so fast
see
hey
we
yes
all right that was great great great
great great all right larger fake ce9
and akron i'll be glad to leave I've had
as much of this place as I want madam it
would be very dangerous for you to leave
the lodge-keeper wants you what me what
kind of talk is that he wants you for
his wife he loves beautiful women yeah
yeah no movie no kissing claws well my
contract all right all right we're just
moving in like cursor on her up okay
just put your hand on her shoulder I'm
fine bowler elbow you're kidding you're
not even kidding me I how did that
experience during our town just for go
keep it up cut her hair stop diggin make
it look sexy like oh yeah
don't you ever try that again you Beast
the keeper wants you but you can't have
you I want you huh you stop that top
this instant you here he wants you but
he can't have you Oh Mike Mike oh where
could he be Mike you've let me out of
here this instant now for get me mad and
I meant no harm you just wait till I
tell my husband Oh no ha madam I'll
protect you I will protect you very well
I won't tell my husband now let me go
okay cut right perfect all right let's
move on is it oh no no that was fine
very real what was that that's great we
do to the dogs eat now donors Don did
you want be reported to the dog see now
mr. Warren oh it's very simple Donald
when I yell action you just run outside
party what was that probably some animal
in the desert nothing to be afraid of
all right on this is your time to shine
when I yell action you just run outside
barking and howling just like your plan
just remember to wait till I say action
are you ready Don all right do this
giorgia love sin seen by then I turn
what
probably some animal to the death I
think it'd be afraid of oh I'm scared
buck Michael I don't care what it was
chase it away okay okay I'll go see what
it is it'll make you wear that
hey get back in the house get back in
the house damaged Mike what's happened
huh that's puppy he's been killed get
back in the house what my god bye all
right honey here the dick fucking
outhouse top how really great work
Donald for a minute I thought you a real
dead dog uh-uh all right that is lunch
everybody oh I forgot to wear my scarf
for this team oh no it's fine i'm sure
we'll fix it in post just go on the
lunch we should do that money can you go
to lunch go on lunch will you go to
lunch
yeah how many times do you kids have to
be told and like wow have a heart will
you don't chase that another couple what
other color that's it going deeper into
the desert thought that you want them
while now we know the throat goes
nowhere so now get go on now no smart
stuff we've tried to jump on you just
get
the hell is that blasted caretaker door
go toward on you yeah portable where's
the telephone yeah Alexander Graham Bell
you know how phone there is done sir
what master doesn't approve of such
device that where the nearest phone the
nearest phone is at the crossroad that's
10 fire god mine is going to be 10,000
miles drop the master hold my you
staying tonight you know ergo I are
using a lot about what the master wants
which is core the water you know Torgo
the wise man once told me sterling
silver himself once told me you never
know who's a windbag who's got the goods
hell he said to me how vicious over 54
why spend your life making someone
else's dreams think about that door go
it was a wise man yes tortellini large
plastic bags any good chin chin oh it in
the kitchen you know say what you want
about how scrappy directive and right
hand writing and acting introducing but
the man sure can cook great flavor for
my brain look at the mango salsa exactly
perfectly with this portrait oh yeah
those were great just succulent mouth
feel bad Gothel didn't get anything from
you have a little bit of sauce on your
cheek don't I girls are didn't get back
to work mr. Warren where is my bicycle
oh not now Debbie you'll get it just as
soon as we're done with the film oh yeah
right okay let's go on so everyone we're
doing the telling the daughter about the
dead dog see okay all right great so
Debbie I need you at eleven for this
remember you're exhausted and frankly
without your puppy more than anything in
the world I need you to commit all right
all right casa de Manos how's the heads
of fake c6 and not rude Oh Mike what
could have done funny probably some
animal in the desert this place must be
full of it look happy he went away baby
he went away while you were asleep look
I want to leave this place the animals
in the desert cut it out Maggie will
leave in the morning and soon this place
will be forgotten forgotten I'll never
forget Pepe is gone I just hope the baby
will understand she'll understand she's
my baby she'll understand I sure hope so
darling I sure hope so she's my baby
shit under what energy go
my god it kind of the places i don't
know maybe she went into the other room
well she probably playing some game of
hide-and-seek or something um okay today
do you know come out come out wherever
you are teddy hey hey hey Oh torgul her
go have you seen gay no she's gone help
us find her she's gotta be inside how
the doors I lost her parents are going
to kill what God's sake don't panic
she's gotta be in here somewhere is
there another door to the outside in the
kitchen okay this doors boarded to
outside how she's got to be outside all
right all right look we're outside
you're confusing me tell me I'm losing
my voice
don't worry we'll find her oh so not
getting back oh you must never run away
Debbie don't you ever run away from us
you find the puppy maybe to find your
dog did in a big play in the big place
where there's a big giant things I never
thought dark but I wasn't afraid of the
dark and it was those many people know
we're gonna race every over here mr.
Warren
it's hope it is great nobody in the
camera I want her she's mighty fine you
here I want this one you all the wise
needy she's mush look it'll see how
could you are I won't need you anymore
I'm gonna be a star I won't have to come
in here to dream of having one of you
you your worst you his first wife he
doesn't want you anymore now even I
don't want you
that smile yeah you're a while hey girl
I say I don't have time to be waitin all
day just got a child wrong season up
singing this song
question time hey you wanna do anything
with me
come on a new thing
Diane I get by the damn script in the
dance huh the damn cameras gone to how
we need to leave this place now you
can't leave now damn it we're almost
done you have been saying that for two
and a half months oh this endemic we can
argue about this later right now I need
to find that dog damn script is great
why when I writing some changes take
advantage of that damn that he's and
back again creepy ultra stuff that's
damn place damn it every which way but
one day I'm gonna film making God's hand
you a gift like this you jump on it
lightning in a bottle baby damn liking
in a fun I haven't seen the dance of
course you've seen the damn script it's
a damn big pile of napkins now let me
look for it good give it four times
around the parking on his back again for
another damage no is leaving it tell me
faggot I script in the trash earlier
I'm sorry fucking shit all summer do you
really like nothing you look I need to
know what the fuck thats I'm I'm sorry
you would never work in this town again
if we get hurt or me down out here or
god forbid we happen to make a bad movie
it's your fucking Oh is your fucking oh
I can't work like this I'll be in my
trailer
Oh Manas valve primal darkness now who
dwelleth in the depth of the universe in
the black castle of night and the smoke
on the water the fire in the sky thou
art holy thou art holy odd thou thou
holy thou art art mattos thy will be
done thy kingdom come by priests it
remains constant my priesthood remain
steadfast my recent remains righteous
anyway the wind blows nothing really
matters carry on carry on nothing really
matters arise my wives and give ear to
the words of meadows arise and here the
will of meadows and that's where babies
come from Wow like ma'am you see this
road you kids are on goes nowhere you
should be smart think about the future
holy cow man haha now I'm trying to jump
on you I'm just saying maybe we should
wait for your don't school and we're
like 27 years old your what and we've
been dating for years and years well
then what are you doing doing whatever
it is you're not doing out here in the
middle of nowhere our car broke down all
right I can give you a ride back to town
well she's man you don't have to oh no
it's all right when you're in the squad
car hop in kids
so when you get finally gonna get
married they're all against you have the
whole world's against you but that's
right that's all right maybe you don't
have an Oscar maybe you've never made a
movie before maybe you are just a
fertilizer salesman from El Paso Texas
but that's alright that's alright
because it's not fancy awards the get
movies made no its balls brass balls you
or Harold p Warren and you've got the
ball to make this movie now get out
there and be the best producer director
writer at your camera out there
no doll why does the child meet part of
my and a female child at that have never
complained about working with a man
before but it sure we only want the
woman that the child must die they all
must die we've not even want the woman
the child is a female Mama's with letter
in the movie she should be killed oh I
don't do snuff film i goes to the wife
and it is my privilege to say this
enough enough of this stupid picnic
there'll be no movie if you persist in
this foolishness your usefulness will
come to an end say what you will i will
be that stop stop i see she must stop I
don't know what they're doing here in
the first place torkoal should have
never let them in we should never have
left mr. skin's mannequin mansion and
the master should shave off that
horrible mustache and he promised us
yeah you're pumped enough trouble I
think perhaps your service twist is at
its end now silence silence
and now my wives I shall deal with the
one responsible for the movie people
being here Torgo he's the one get torgul
you are the one responsible we shall
dispose of you later
it's a terrible mistake the man yes the
child no there's just like maybe we
share the child
is are not tapped perform with the dog
do not let the child performed to
satisfy him he had enough women yeah you
know time be all the wives just a new it
um jealousy is not part of us why are
you so jealous of me you are a
troublemaker you should dumb die I may
die but I'm not care I'm gonna live
forever baby remember my name would not
approve the law of matters is for us
only no matter sobs no
when the master tears of this he will be
furious yeah you're all mad mad whole
lot of you know the younger the child
Master what are you doing here you
failed us Togo I owe your visits to the
tomb my is it the women have told me
they may not be able to say anything or
move while you're there but they
remember everything that you say to them
and everything that you do to them and
everything that you sing to them but
master you have four lives I can't I
have one for myself you are not one of
us therefore you cannot have one of them
but why can't I please have pictures of
them maybe sometime I can fighting you
failed its logo and for this you must
die they don't do no huyn fail yourself
you never kill them I help them you have
failed and you must die
meadows thou primal darkness estella
secrete so by done the hands of feed of
doom this man thy will is done
fist erupting sister is married to Paul
of us yeah that's a me as they get him
to
you know where my post about you your
heart
police police police stop telling these
awful jokes
what foolishness is six medals must be
served this buisness must stop there's
been enough trouble our purpose must be
served there will be no further
incidents yeah we will not appear with
the charge and will not appear at all
you've got enough trouble we shall
dispose of you once we've disposed of
Togo your patterns not affect me anymore
I have no one for you see you sir and
prepare for sacrifice
well done my lives man oh shall be
served
it is the will of matters that he be
sacrificed Kim Kim Kim Manos has decreed
it kill kill kill
oh yeah ceremony is done
Oh
Kelly doesn't help anymore you're all
finished once you've disposed to the
film evil we shall take care of you hey
hurry joining them before the nights of
delay
ok
is a thing that I can't I know
I
and the like together again
all our time
I have
don't forget
Jung
the tender touch that says a fire ready
to
but I forget
hey here and it seems you are oh I love
this three-day
don't forget
we met
don't forget the tender touch inside
am I everybody
but I
hey you
years
I'm forget
we gotta leave now no I can't take it
any longer it's okay I'm here with you
always be here will hide in the desert
someone will help oh yeah I get that get
a longer to get me a drum know how we
can make it let's go let's go this way
are you all right no we can't keep going
like this I'm cool oh ok I would have
apologized to Debbie spawn at Diane's
bomb heaven my mom I'm so sorry i was
going to brought them out here I was one
every word long I wasn't gonna keep
going good it was my baggage with my
project a gun I just can I
we're gonna die I'm gonna get we gotta
get go that will destroy you your power
fails you cannot do manners has made me
permanent Oh destroy me hyah permit ah
destroy God's destroy me haha your power
fails you you're losing your control
even Torgo divided you destroyed even as
you shall be your power does not affect
me anymore even the otherwise do not
trust you haha see I do not fear you
know you beat me
I do not fear you think oh god they've
left the house we looked everywhere find
them they must not escape leave them
alone enough time findin matters will be
sure I can take it out take Jerry take
the bedroom know how we can make the
rest here for a minute we can make go
back to the house does everything a
living right there you know you're not
gonna point there no fish out please we
can't go on this way listen we can lock
ourselves in the kitchen I have my gun
let's go back to the house ok you might
be the safest place especially with Ted
are you looking for us
where's my bicycle please David
that's your sounded like shots we better
check this gentleman out there can't be
anybody out there this is the boondocks
sound does around a long way at night
maybe clear over in Mexico for that
matter with an investigational record
like that I should be Commissioner by
the year
Oh
whatever that whoa all right I've
decided to give you one more chance and
acting like professionals
I
to the edge of town
tracks where the tide
and cracks
the
fridge
I'm I gathering
from the time
the sleeve black clothes
right hand
be a lion is
very naughty girls
Bauer
shadow is cast where
snacks of green paper is red right hand
you
they are preparing vacations ooh fun but
this should be bright yeah I'll game
then we can
welcome my name is Hal I take care of
the place while the master is away
No
you