[Music]
another perfect day
oh okay how much would the woodchopper
al-sisi she sells seashells oh no that's
been done come on ghost get women with
WoW wee wee willie winkie ah how you
cooking good Wee Willie Winkie ran
through the town and downstairs in his
nightgown tapping at the window crying
at the lock all the pain in their face
for it's now ten o'clock
[Music]
yeah I'll tell me you created another
weirdo character mom yeah we're really
wiki what do you think I think we don't
need any more Winkies or dump these or
nimble course we do dear chosen love
them well I'm not a child I don't like
the rye me they're just so strange
besides they run the neighborhood
darling rhyme ease our two neighborhood
this is a rheinland yeah but why do we
have to live here why can't we live in a
real neighborhood like beaver cleaver
Ozzie and Harriet you know normal just
exactly what do you mean by norm well
take me for instance I'm normal and I
think it's the only way to be one year
away in Egypt academy and you become a
regular cocky call mom yes it's true
lately you act as if you're too good for
Ryan land by the way can you think of
something that rhymes with orange
that's another thing running the goose
down comforter shop I hate that place
I'm allergic to feathers you're allergic
to work no I'm allergic to rhyming
they're just so important don't say it
Gordon you'll be late for work
I don't know if I'm ready for this just
the start of another rheinland day
[Music]
Oh
versation if you change your mind
this you never the questioning loved it
what did you hope to find
don't why don't I really don't belong
here live in the truth what if Holly's
kids to behave I got so many I don't
know what to do how do you get so many
kids well what can I say stork has a
crush on me
[Music]
right
are you all right no but I'm very
emotionally upset I need to find another
booth quick it's a very watery emergency
hold on sister who are you I'm Little Bo
Peep and I've lost my sheep and I don't
know where to find him well relax your
sheep are always missing don't you ever
ever make fun of my sheep oh sorry I
forgot how sensitive sheep where to
criticism well I don't want to talk to
you when I talk to medical well she's
not here she's at home she is not is so
good not yes she is I just left her
there well I just left from there and
she's got ties to women she I don't know
I'm not my mother's keeper well I
pictures conquer was there but she
wasn't she never goes anywhere without
this we better check it out claim you
quick
you sure you know how to drive this
thing
[Music]
yours you always drive and reverse
should it's the best way to be with your
mom mom mom oh hey four chairs in the
wrong spot so no better what's it is me
well that sure hasn't moved from that
spot since I've been a little kid how do
you know cuz I'm her son that's how well
I get it you're good me well this could
be a very serious situation why because
you owe Gordy no i mean because of my
mother she wouldn't leave without honker
hmm nice no foul play nice
mother you bow lake just like it I get
it you know me well we honking it up the
other day I laid supply this yep it goes
into a box is getting us nowhere no
where's my sister back great I didn't
yes why does that not surprise me you
probably live there how do you know what
my mother is somewhere I think we should
find out where that is all right maybe
she took my sheep she's with my shoes
well you know you have the stupidest
little voice I didn't say anything then
who did I think it's coming from over
here yes Facebook driver if you can get
my last one but I can't see the game
does this spider bite is he poisonous
one machine thank you Oh is his renown
it away this is quitting 2 megabusa sons
Sean bonjour je it see you know
everything I've lost my sheep you know
where they are I forget about our sheep
you know where my mother is Mother Goose
what are you doing what happened to my
mother oh my goodness be the jewel we
know something came notice your mouth
great thank you have a wonderful feel I
can know if you're anything like that
get to the point going I just never to
be mistaken promises wind up
[Music]
great big huge what don't worry the
sun'll come out and dry off all the ring
he'll be back yo it see try your
climbing up there pal we need a little
more info about the great big huge he's
not climbing if he are you fine he's
probably gonna scare the bejeebers out a
little mix much what about this man I
want to clean all this up first we don't
have to turn those times and neatness
[Music]
apparently to come
oh look look look lucky to be alive I
feel like I've been on mr. Toad's Wild
Ride miss what which way we go and look
well maybe we should ask somebody for
direction what could we possibly ask out
here animal of nowhere there's someone
idea
wackos Bosma shadow where we def justice
reunion at my just let you the baker the
candlestick English
such dropout from barber college
with your happen another way
[Music]
that look people i'm not writing another
sport unless i'm driving forget it
nobody can drive my car
especially her
I get lonely you can drive
[Music]
no turn right wife go straight you know
you're going miss muffet know anyone
need him soon as you see and this little
pig went wee wee wee all the way home
and in other news mother goose is still
missing if you have any knowledge of her
whereabouts no I'm sorry the answer is
equaled out of love next question a pie
is made of four and twenty of them
what's the budget no car you idiot
that's one of the neon that game show I
could have been a consistent but no you
wouldn't let me oh sure blame me
everything's my fault much would you say
whether or not we'll be right
[Music]
what a dog oh I know I know and she was
the best student or less clothes
you remember her from ranked school mary
had a little lamb whose fleece was white
as snow Conrad Mary and everywhere that
Mary went the lamb was sure to go you
telling me one time I took it to the
driving the lamb SAT between us talk
about getting please oh oh art bar marry
someone at the door probably the way
inward looking for the win get 20 Mary
stop it you're not in the mood for
company I am asked it to do all marriage
after you what are you doing well when
you remember everywhere that Mary went
the lamb was sure to go I'm going Mary
that you'd who wants to know if these
runnable peeps from riding school and
you remember 42 come on in make yourself
comfortable
[Music]
Wow yeah so I hear your mother's missing
tough break pub you know when I was a
kid my father ran off with the goat shut
up sure so Mary I see you've still got
your cute little less lamb here he's
still here and you guys haven't changed
a bit you should have talked about a
nosedive into an empty pool I meant that
as a compliment listen Bailey we stopped
by hoping you'd help us find another
goose so he lost his mother you lost you
see big deal you think you got problems
I'd like to lose him my wife in a
shambles all because of oh sure he used
to be a cute little land and it was fun
having and follow me everywhere I went
until we turned into a gigantic of
Gnostic Medwin shoes give it a rest Mary
so can I get you folks some refreshments
coffee tea passed away I was too
wonderful husband all because the blues
resistance are following me everywhere
you know what I mean so unfriendly is
that a crime speaking of lemon however
two little sheep yours you know what
thank you hello when you get your mind
out of the meadow I'm talking to you
anyway so large it a whirl hey this
little lamb is ruining my life by you
think it's a picnic following you around
yeah you don't like it there's the door
don't worry about me i'll survive
because wherever you go i'll be sure to
follow I think we have to stop at any
time
that's why I don't have any pet well
amazing how spooky oh great just what I
need a parking ticket wait it's a note
sometimes a cute little cops like to
leave a cute little whining no it's a
ransom note you mean the cops kidnap
mother Goose well if you ever want to
see your mother again then bring about
400 no make that 650r I'm lamp dollars
and two chili dogs to the pickled pepper
patch put under fourth pepper on 7th
vine don't try anything funny because I
won't laugh please park perpendicular
that's not perpendicular all right
depends on which way you look at it
[Music]
what's this contraption pretty invention
yeah but where's Piper Peter Peter give
me the chili dawn wait here be careful
don't worry about me I can handle
anything are you Peter Piper precisely i
am peter piper proud proprietor of this
profitable pickle pepper patch you know
I'm Gordon goose I ran back reach a
garden and where's my mother and why did
you keep that person kidnap quit kidding
could you clarify the query well
somebody wrote this ransom note it says
to bring money and chili dog here if I
want to get my mother back cuz Shaw
that's probably a pathetic prank
perpetrated by some puny person out to
poopoo Peter Piper do you mean people
pick on me persistently it's a pity
perhaps but part of playing the piper
you need someone else cadets nugget we
can blamed it on you precisely my rhyme
Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled
peppers it's particularly puzzling
people can't pronounce it properly so
they presume that I'm peculiar and they
purposely persecute poor Peter Piper I
John practically prepared to puke you
didn't write this note who did let's
take a look
leaping lizard this letter is almost
illegible the only crook who could crash
such a crude communique is that old
crackpot the crooked man who watch
cleveland correct she's a crazy creepy /
completely crackers from Brenda continue
yes I'm completely confused by this
conversation we climb into the car and
cut out can do we've got to catch the
crooked man who conspired to comics with
his crappy calligraphy do you two always
talk in this asinine alliteration oh
come on you guys going to pick up some
pickled peppers or what oh we be pickled
peaches we didn't pay the piper to tell
us how to find a crooked man how else
yeah follow crooked mile drive helping
the Guru's monocles are still living
there are no reports that marry her lamo
participation sounds like the crooked
man added again yes very
[Music]
I you're looking for me yeah you might
say that yeah oh why didn't you knock I
mean I've been here all day yes running
around the house did you write this
ransom note well uh it looks like my
handwriting yeah well then you kidnap
mother Goose Oh give her back Yeah right
now I didn't kidnap anybody i admit i'm
a crooked man i'm not overcook good life
but i ain't no kidnapper yeah we'll look
you stay right here I read asleep if you
ever want to see your mother again hey I
never said I had a I just said if you
ever want to see your mother again
obviously know you're here so what hey
by the way you got the cash well yeah I
played a man no mother Goose no money
and no chili dog hey well I'm got your
mother but yeah how about a good deal
under London Bridge what about the dog
here don't get the dog doesn't ring
we're driving Rannoch circle we meet
what again we've already been here good
let's just ask somebody oh sure is if
those three dudes and it's how they're
going to come floating by
[Music]
Oh
what is this it's Little Miss Muffet
plane when anyone's fit in there that's
why they call a little milk hello
nothing we need to talk to you company
how nice three please come on in I I
think it might be a little crowded not
to mention anatomically dangerous
problem you just have to think to shrink
pink Harley things to shriek at least
you're not too big for your britches
anymore me three who on the couch and
sit down thank you much what exactly is
it off it it's what you're sitting on
are you hungry no time for food nonsense
there's always time for Karrde anyway
this fashion is especially yummy I just
heated up from instant in the microwave
when heat repeat
pass it over oh sure thang what the heck
is curds and whey / specialty hey thanks
for a roof of your mouth shit is not too
much way oh we know like way too much
play way too much work your way it's
just his way of saying you love the way
well can I stop you Tuffy no no my top
except fine it's just good and the Kurds
in wages the way I like them everything
just the way I like mm-hmm Little Miss
nothing we need to know have you seen
itsy bitsy spider
[Music]
hey let's play hard to get
when you being wow you disappear when we
were talking about hey look you gotta
tell us what happened to my mother hey
why women maybe what we think is a shame
is actually the wheel will ease and
maybe just maybe some inexplicable
phenomena from movies somehow interested
in designing and tentative a real world
laughs you know when you're making your
shopping you gotta go see such
how do we get back to normal well dad I
think you should get it oh wow go good
we want the game leg bring on again we
won okay we want the green where is the
fool rayon again
[Music]
plain bring all the King on the game we
want the game beyond again
[Music]
ladies and gentlemen I give you the
ground
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
hey
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
cleanliness
[Music]
Oh
Wow
[Music]
ah
you
[Music]
Your Majesty we're very sorry to
interrupt your merrymaking but we have
something very important to discuss with
you important you insult me by
requesting that are all kings oh the
merriest of soul this stuff something of
a pocket
managed oh my mother's missing serious
serious serious says the word serious is
the most childhood crime that can be
committed in my buzzes I will not
tolerate it to the dungeon with you but
we were thrilled to meet and the
merriment into you until you hahaha
[Music]
you know you're in there you might be
hiding you know we're happy we're
looking for you
[Music]
Oh
me
[Music]
Oh
now we show you why
[Music]
Oh
yeah you
[Music]
ah
yeah you know well scary times over no
believe me we're professionals don't try
visit I know he's a stylist and I'm
sorry to spoil the fun but what good is
it to keep a minute energy come on Pete
cheer up we're not trying to cook his
goose just trying to make him loose he's
just worried about Mother Goose and I am
too we think she's somewhere in outer
space but we don't know how to find her
p p look don't worry be merry it's not
allowed
she's someplace right here in one I knew
because mother Goose cream the phone and
if she does electron endless we were all
distributed but since nobody's
disability there is nothing to love it
Oh
[Music]
now there is something to worry about
you're right mother juices no more main
line is she's left for the outside world
you've got to find her before we all
disappeared and that King I will do
everything in my power to help then
you've got to release good done great
since I don't know how to get to the
outside world may I suggest that you
question my royal how old man Humpty
Dumpty he's an idiot he knows everything
about everything thank you had soft Oh
anytime baby hey you know think about
dungeon no it's cool stop and dank being
abducted what about the other notice
it's about gruel good g gu
I'm so we're good you it was living well
sure you want me to drive i led to much
to laugh hey watch where you're going
hey to hide NP mom coyote while I was in
exile you're done sir what's up No who's
the old character you got what your name
is Sophie not dumpster it is good Gordon
goose scoop scoop scoop any relation
Hamas you mean mother girl no my ma
daddy you dumped me hahahahaha I just
joking joking get it happy boy I really
crack me up it cracks another one to get
it did you ask me more these egg puns do
I have to listen to oh don't worry just
another dozen the one did it keep you up
on a wall whoo I offended you I'm sorry
maybe from now on I should walk around
on eggshells mrs. we need some
information about the disappearance of
mother to look I'm sorry so bad about
that my emotion are what the word
scrabble but seriously folks let's get
our coil about this door I'm Austin we
would call it you were ahead and maybe
you could tell us how to get outer space
shall I begin 1230 DC why is doing
exercise
[Music]
haha
oh hell we need all the king's horses
and all the king's men to come and put
Humpty together again whoa big fella
unless you again who are you who do you
think all the king's horses and all the
king's men but man implies plural you
know more than one hey budget cuts we're
scaling back so it's actually one King's
horse in 1 Kings man who come to put
Humpty Dumpty together again yeah it's
your service Oh so putting together
again no can go why not it's because we
forgot the goal
sorry honey looks like you've done off
the wall and into the frying game but we
just have to know how do you get how to
speak rubbish oh oh that's tough
Carnegie Hall Rose what nope nope
Citizen Kane just joking oh I'll be
inspired by that time you came out of
his shell just be your hope you get it
go ahead and you crack me up Oh report
confirmed the rhineland majors Peter
Piper and the crooked man have managed
to the Philly boy now we're really in
trouble heavy winds disappearing oh my
car is overheating we need some water
great there's jackandjill every day they
go up to your look that should be in the
water water gray first bit of good news
we've had since we started unfortunately
there are a couple of questions oh yeah
whenever they go up the hill to fetch
the water Jack fall down and break his
crown and Jill came tumbling after
I'll take it you mean oh oh yeah I need
to talk about our relation all not again
oh yes even though we are a couple we
both have individual needs and I feel
that my knees are really not being this
until I respect your need for needs but
I too have needs well what are your need
for one thing I need to stop falling
down this hill and breaking my crown I
mean this is like the 30th something
time I've done this oh yeah well I am
the one that is constantly forced to
tumble down the hill following after you
why can't I think Jill's turn to break
her crown and you come tumbling Astro
for change huh okay I guess I've been
insensitive yes but you must have been
we both do go off the hill together as a
couple to fetch a pail of water yes
that's true and thank you for sharing
but but it's still not enough check my
needs are not being met and what about
my knee what are you need I welcome you
both need to slam off and stop whining
hey we're a modern rhyming something
kind of couple okay we don't whine you
just talk about every little teeny tiny
problem to death all right I don't mean
to whine or anything but could we please
please please have a pail of water water
hey no problem we do water yeah Jill
would you like to go up the hill get
these nice people some water Jack where
are you patronizing me no I am NOT
patronizing you look what's compromise
Jack Jill why don't you both go up the
hill that's just a pail of water so i
can fill the radiator and then we can
get out of here behind i suppose i could
do that if it's all right with you come
on we can do that same here
Oh at least mine does he look like a
warning tonight okay I'll take it I'll
take it you're right they are clutches
are you guys go back oh yeah oh yeah
sure fine i just broke my crown again
you you your ground wire dramas you
would have had my knee what about my
knee this is what we're talking about
what about your knee well let me just
tell mostly let's look at your hair
again there ya go hair forgive me I'll
go fix the wedding myself I'll go with
all right watch your step anyone start a
relationship
I don't know either oh good at least we
understand one hear me
I'll go wait McCall
no now what are we doing I don't know
what I've had it with this out of space
business I mean I just don't believe my
mother was kidnapped by aliens with big
hands but if he saw it and if he never
lie I'm not saying he's lied but he did
see 50 everything looks huge to him and
I think it's about time we go to the
police
me
they started in confidence he needs help
divider time running out oh when chanela
never find a cop when you need one this
is serious Gordon more and more ladies
are disappearing all over the place hey
you yeah you give me come on walk over
right left right left right yeah that's
it come here yet to love bite yeah get
over here come on yeah that's it that's
it this isn't do me favor da why don't
you go down to the corner and give me
some jellybeans Stanley what are you
here what do you say I just don't little
girl you to stick looking for a little
fun little excitement um actually I'm
looking for my mother yeah are we all
well maybe she's inside my the goods
have been here yeah daddy to Duncan
Vinnie disculpa on it after that ok let
me say things when you say what a couple
of sets
bigger and me Veda
by here I got nine
I'd be but just be becoming I got really
lovely Oh
I got nothing I get we'll split a root
beer duty on the phone my friends
p
[Music]
this is the party
I
I just would like well
[Music]
just don't say stay stay
Oh
so my wife no more women hi
[Applause]
[Music]
there goes the kitten
ok
look I'm on a secret mission I'm looking
for my mother
and now a late-breaking bulletin mother
Goose is still nowhere to be found and
panic is racing through rhineland in the
wake of a rash of rhymey disappearances
and now an eyewitness report I retain my
wash and Boyd wanna block Hank snap it
shut on my TV anyway I see mother Goose
elected a mongoose and woloson kingdom
but right before my very eyes so figure
yeah why don't you tell me you were
looking for mother good try the private
detective agency upstairs I mentioned my
name they've been looking for me for
years
don't go anywhere right back Gordon
it was a hot and fifty afternoon you
know like doggin july or maybe you but
nothing to do but cut the cheese and
talk about past case history excuse me
when suddenly a ready today she was
blonde and brunette with the little
husky voice that could curl the whiskers
on muddy mouth into the office no she
just left yeah tell us another one bed
no the babe left I mr. Gordon goose dude
babe everyone's equal in our eyes yes
speaking of which what happened to the
color why are we suddenly in black and
white we cool it blood easier but I'm
not not you're off stage dude what's up
tiger well i was thinking of hiring you
to find a missing somebody okay we're
listening well it's my mom hold on
sweetheart is your mother the farmer's
wife carving knife have you ever seen
such a fight in your life that rewind by
[Music]
right
Oh
[Music]
you 10 sheep I don't get it Oh step back
it comes trouble hey looking all over
for you I got tired of waiting hey take
it easy stick you know what's good for
the goose is good for the gander you
know what I mean thanks doc well enjoy
your time in the land of I'm Hank what
were you doing with that creep drink
talking at least he's interested in what
I have to say yeah I guess you just
wanted to find out if you're a brilliant
conversationalist
cool
I think you're killing I'm not jealous
it's just them it's all right you
shouldn't talk to strangers no one's
going to the new except him maybe who's
that it's simple tournament let's give
them a ride look we don't have time to
stop and we don't have he's just a
little guy please can't we stop and pick
him up with such a simple guy
hey hey what do you want to ride or not
oh that's what I've been doing out here
oh thanks Oh
[Music]
on the road again okay remember why I'm
on the road yes hey I'm gonna be off the
road again if you don't get the guitar
out of my face I'm driving here all
right look if you not good at it too now
off to where are you doing simple oh
that's a tough one I know there's some
papers supposed to go the finish yeah
sure I could go to the fair no that's
your rhyme remember Simple Simon met a
pieman going to the fair time is called
time and that's what that guy in the van
was I musta really buggin he's dropped
me off in the middle of nowhere I'm
starting to get the same idea Gordon
don't make fun he's simple what play I
thought I heard somebody call my name I
didn't hear anything sinful there it is
a kid swear somebody call my name look
bright eyed and your travels you haven't
heard anything about where mother Goose
might be having mother Goose leather
booths I think I saw her face in a cloud
today and was a cloud inside of your
head or outside room sorry that's a
tough one I really want a little cloudy
on that issue
[Music]
well here we are where the fair so so
this is where you want to go oh well
sure what the heck as long as we're here
things were watching somebody asking
wasn't somebody asking where mother
Goose was every day I don't think so if
somebody asks where mother goose was
tell them that I tell them tell them
tell them I don't know hey great you've
been a big help thanks and thanks for
the thanks for the ride no no thanks I
can walk oh hey Reed it's this way oh
that's the way I don't think simple even
begins to describe old Simon hey wait a
minute you're going around with
it disappeared on it what do you doing
well we can't keep running around
willy-nilly we've got to make a plan
although I don't know why it's so far
the whole thing has been a total fiasco
we got one step closer to finding my
mother than we were when we first
started it's only fun no it's not
yesterday I'm a whiny I'm supposed to
know Rhineland how can I help you find
your mother I can't even find my own
sheet I'm a failure no you're not you're
very helpful it listen to you I wouldn't
even know my mother was missing
but anybody could attend
I'm you
well you had a car that was very useful
maybe
so what else
got me out of the dungeon I
what else
well
you're your car key yeah anything you
yeah yeah
I I can't put it into words you nice i
like okay I like your company no I seems
if you I do
voice you don't show it j so i'm showing
it now
I am
border well if your mother mom quarter
line in the real world and I can't last
much longer neither can the wrong
England you've got to pay me if he was
right she's up in her space what do we
do need I don't know I
I've got the stairs let's go to the fear
how could you think about having one at
a time like this
we got Rosie they say from little old
how long haul and fantastic is colossal
rattling the bullets in the gun is where
we want you're going to college you're
sort of the Moon see these things on
pitching hear me I so we got a coward it
goes over the whole table say that but
I've got a comfortable want to take it
was about 50 get away all right now
there's a total of progress big i'm a
coconut chicken cow this is all the way
over the ball this is important we need
to talk to this cow thing to you what I
said the cowl punk he jumped he's your
solo is part of it out of you to get out
some so what about you know something as
a bus it was super cool don't
reciprocate and that's where we have to
go we need the cow to take over the moon
tean gonna get over the moon kid away
you're bothering me your mother call you
that's just it we need to borrow the cow
to get my mother back the fuel to claim
your mother aight i love it get lost all
right no we're not out can we focus a
little more okay Logan can you really go
uncover new one half an hour one bad you
can see the cow jumped over the moon I'm
upsetting i'm a coconut chicken on top
accountable where Alec was so you gotta
help got to help us we need the cal it
jumps over the moon our only hope the
colors really jump over you it's show
biz it's an antenna and rebel Devils
smoke an l made a beautiful and you can
pair all right mr. Pratt we got out it
cums way way way over all you got the
cowboy Oh
[Music]
where we go from here oh yeah never
really been taxa 40
hey looking sharp
[Music]
Lisa Nandy fellas have around it's time
to boldly go where no cow has gone
before okay hang on
[Music]
and wow
oh wow where the places are we we're not
in my friend anymore mother found you
where have you thinking where have you
been where are we what's going on we're
in the real world and this a real little
boy Michael reality let's make confident
than I ever imagined it I hope it's not
feeding time this is so excellent I mean
I've got Little Bo Peep the cow junk
food who are you I'm going good mother's
son never heard of you but it's so cool
that you're all here now you can ask out
your story for me you get mother Goose
just tearing them to me look little kid
big kid I don't know why you've taken my
mother but you have to let her go she's
got to return to Ryan land why because
there won't be any more stories there
won't be any more rhyme there wouldn't
be any more mother Goose bells for
anyone see all the rhineland is
disappearing mother Goose created rhyme
land and all the rhyme ease and they
wouldn't exist if she wasn't there now
you've taken her you're destroying
everything that she's created you mean
I'm a bad guy I'm sorry I'm side when I
could love a good I ain't mean to do
anything wrong
I had me in a room rhyme Lance she's our
biggest fan and I wanted her all to
myself Michael fear what Martin says is
true my rhymes are for all children and
you're my biggest fan what deny our
future children of the world that they
enjoy my stories bring to you am I going
to get price of horse not here for a
couple of nuggies wouldn't hurt great
okay let me put you back before today
[Music]
bye-bye
with my mother it's good to have you
back mom it's good to be back and get my
little honker to me and now that you are
back Ryan landed all the rhyme you can
get back to normal normal there's
nothing normal about them son there's
nothing wrong with being different gosh
that's what makes life interesting if we
were all a life life would be very very
boring well maybe but I'm not one of
them personally I wish you well in a way
Gordon the time has come tell you
something important I knew it I'm a
doctor right no you are fictional
[Music]
what do you mean I mean I made you up I
created you I want to ride you mean I'm
am I me you are the first ride a play
misty videos
why didn't you ever tell me since you
were my first creation your wine wasn't
very good I was so embarrassed I didn't
want people to read it so I just told
everybody that you were my real son and
now is the time
and show you the rhyme
[Music]
here it is Gordon gooses pet got loose
early in the morning what's the use of
having a good brother you right this is
a terrible rhyme not your best with
Medicus can you think of anything that
rhymes with Gordon Schmoyer dean morton
no no mom couldn't just have named me
bill I don't think anyone should ever
read this sorry darling the drive didn't
work very well but you turned out just
right and I'm very proud of you and as
far as I'm concerned you'll always be my
dear
no wonder I had to try so hard to be
normal because I'm not what do I do now
I don't feel normal I don't feel like a
rhyming I'm confused where do I belong
you belong here in the Rhineland all
right well maybe you're right i'm
beginning to feel a little strange
already good maybe we could look for
those sheep yes I'm sure we could find
them of course it may take a long long
time
[Music]
Wow
I
[Music]
music
Oh
[Music]
haha
we gotta
we
[Music]
Oh
ah
[Music]
No
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh