they remove the worst we can find and
watch them all monitor his mind now keep
in mind I can't control where the movies
begin or end try to keep sanity
Mystery Science Theater 3000 Hey hi
everyone welcome to the satellite of
love that big blond human back there
that's Mike they well yeah anyway he
just got invited to one of gypsies tea
parties haha and we're off for a
spirited game of tennis Thanks favorite
game let's watch dude you're a bee I'm
what I thought there was a good deserted
woman last night wasn't it what's that
that yeah yeah it was really funny i
think i think the Delta Burke really is
the the glue that holds that show
together because it was a thing last
night where she came out and there the
stuff started happening he's not on the
show anymore oh well no she's not but I
think she's on the show and spirit and
huh I mean because that other woman's on
now should you create a disturbance and
save his behind not for all the candy in
the world yeah what started to think
that you didn't even watch designing one
than last night maybe I didn't die i was
i was definitely watching a show though
and there were the the there was women
on it and all it seemed like they were
designing but you know I'll be right
back
well gypsy this tea has really been
great right then we see you next
Saturday well I have a thing that I have
say Mike if you and Helena Bonham Carter
they are finished could we please start
our tennis game moving good but person
and I'm rear calling hmm good evening
ladies and gentlemen good evening
tonight it is my pleasure to host deep
13th annual celebrity roast this year
our guest of honor is none other than
dr. Clayton Forrester dr. Clayton
Forrester ladies and Jeff you know I'd
like to say that tonight we're honoring
one of the world's most brilliant
scientists I'd like to say that but
unfortunately we're stuck with dr.
Forrester seriously though I'm treated
well down here my paycheck has lots of
zeros nothing but zeros as a matter of
fact but still no really I kid the good
doctor but I think deep down underneath
it all he's a real jerk there are a lot
of reasons you could give for why dr.
Forrester is the way he is personally I
think it's cuz he's ugly and stupid no
no seriously doctor I in all sincerity
what I really came here tonight to say
was I hate your guts and I hope you die
a slow painful death secure the
knowledge that nobody loves you well
let's bring up our guest of honor for
tonight ladies and gentlemen dr. Clayton
Forrester himself dr. Forrest story
Thank You TVs Frank you know there is
after a beautiful tribute like that
there's only one thing I can say and
that's cool and in conclusion oh I knew
I should have hired red buttons back up
to You Merv hey everyone just plain
little canadian doubles here which the
first-ever satellite of love celebrity
open sea los cebu play kristi love crawl
it's 30 long whatever all right you
ready here we go got it
00 votes out what is their problem what
are you blind what did you grow some
hair servo come on you're on a warrior
here hi I'm out of order you're out of
order cheese out of order the whole
imports out of order things jeez oh do
me a favor Frank take these oranges and
wrap them in this towel all right doc ah
mayor Dinkins as a special treat your
movie this week is a little bit of a
change of pace it's about a bunch of
astronauts who go on a space mission
back in the 50s it's called 12 to the
moon but first a little musical acid
trip from our friends at General Motors
called design for dreaming what do you
do with these clay but just call me Bobo
Frank Oh easy no I am having a hard
enough time whatever you something now
oh this is by no coward last night the
moon was so bright I hate it when people
tell me about their dreams mommy when I
drawbridge that is the nicest oxygen
tent i have ever seen and Tommy tune
arrives let me persuade us to come to
the plate where's about a subpoena for
me oh thank you it sounds very exciting
may I come just as I am no you must come
as geeky guy dressed in a pair of pink
pajama Holly go weirdly I don't care
haven't got a single thing to one man
she's super for Timmy a gum oh I'll be
the talk of the town bonnie is dinner
ready oh my god Oh go after it why I
followed my cleared for takeoff thousand
windows yellow with light dom down it
fell and it landed in the
waldorf-astoria hotel right in the
middle of the Steinman Hoffs berg
wedding reception
oh god she's right there is tech natural
Janine Turner white days those lighters
I clutched the invitations my bosoms he
was famous feel the boy from at Chicago
way is better than me excited midnight
is job to hell Tom think it's just a
dream and involves no money which one
wins your eye on the sparrow and a
near-death experience like this
they are all so beautiful i really don't
know so let me grow
excuse me move it buster it's my dream
come on let me through oh no no no no
yeah I want a cord back I don't give a
challenge one that's why I entered your
head
he's a high maintenance day okay we'll
have the usual two-car garage my lord
the deeds ignored that's different this
bu wicks of beauty I'll she's gonna roll
it car security to the showroom floor
please I think yeah great i guess i
could sell my plasma every tuesday
go all out and buy a Cadillac cool this
is a rebuttal to Roger in me
hardly wait for the dream come Alicia
got a good parking spot
tater tots are burning
any more girls in here yeah geez no
wonder they need to carry us to carry
her everywhere just like a man you give
him a break she can really felt the
blues none i seen put a card in the slot
and onto the screen picture of just how
your niche stila me all the ingredients
you need to cook just because it's
futuristic doesn't mean it's practically
need for the bride to feel tragic in the
restive push-button magic shouldn't know
whether you bake or broil up dude the
Frigidaire kitchen does it all for you
buddy set the timer and you're on your
way so you can kick back and tip back a
quart a wild turkey top oh it's a salute
to mr. B natural no this would be the up
part of her manic mood swings i'm
guessing oh man it is gonna take her
father to write this dream down oh wow
we're oh my god wonder what Freud would
make of that Sun Hat well sometimes the
Sun Hat is just a Sun Hat so your
mother's little helpers kicked him my
cake is ready uh-huh I call no way
Campbell's never happy birthday wanted
you what's for her everybody on stage
ooh black diamond do
and now a glamorous dancer in a special
number dance of tomorrow Taurus lying to
the wrath of Chaka Khan take it off Edna
everyone says the future is strange but
I have a feeling you doing ball change
give us centuries while she's dancing
the Japanese are making great time Cindy
Williams is qualify as Zadora Duncan in
the Meredith monk story a one-woman show
co-starring Tom Bosley as possible whoa
I'm an answer the dream cars of tomorrow
where Jackie Gleason Audrey meadows
Bonnie and Clyde's tooth car Eldorado
town car by Cadillac ensemble by
christian dior Paris with Art Carney and
Joyce Randolph Fonzie's Duff car fleet
Centurion driving coat by montesano of
New York pregnant woman and snails are
optional
entire production supervised by
Jacqueline Oldsmobiles elegant gold and
rockets sports outfit by tech primo of
Los Angeles he closed three plants card
executive producer Jack Philbin the ship
electric recent our hub de Mer open to
the sky costume by Emilio of Capri
unfettered avarice by madison avenue in
the honeymooners
still casual I didn't be marking a clown
suit by bargain clown of Hollywood hmm
this is what happens when you go to a
car show with Michael Crawford and last
of all designed for the electronic by
way of the future the fellis turban
powered Firebird to the extension of my
manhood car
your deal with the devil is now complete
laughter I cool Stockard Channing is
Peter Pan do you have it in rabbit
that's a six week delivery ma'am step in
yes come on step is a mink yes go ahead
Tomic batteries to power why it's you
who my bird do to control tower we are
about to take off on the highway of
tomorrow stand by
thank you sweet Tucker
look dead raccoon of tomorrow my sword
and magic
that's where President Barbie vemlans
Prime Minister Jim J Bullock
or if a true way you build it someone
invent rock and roll please future may
not be available as seen personal fates
maybe future not available in Africa
India or central South America and
there's probably some giant kids
standing off holding out control well I
really should be getting home
conspicuous consumption makes our love
stronger
look out the bridge to the futures out
Oh Lady Hey lay down here late lady hey
i losin everything yeah oh wow this is
gonna be great it's got a rocket and
everything rocket yep they're bombing
Washington be good bombing London
bombing friends bombing my underpants
tonight on space Corp donuts no no no oh
you're going to the moon all right whoa
kind of like refrigerator magnet credits
here yo wow I think I'm in this well
maybe now
yes by the year nineteen eighty we will
be living on the moon remember when we
were living on the moon nineteen idiom
my personal the malapa d junior high
school festival of horn these are twelve
that are going to the moon nope martha
stewart plan that seating arrangement
judy chicago donors ladies and gentlemen
the master funny men of our age Victor
Borge ah hello the world there's a kind
of hush I am speaking for the
International Space order hi in the
first worldwide radio and telecast in
history at this moment I may die over
two billion people have been so every
part of the world are focusing their
attention on this program and my wrong
every nation of the earth in a
magnificent effort is contributing of
its people and resources in an attempt
to reach the moon and proclaim it
dolphin-safe international territory and
House of Pancakes the rocket ship lunar
eagle number one represents the
culminating achievement of the world's
leading scientists the men and women who
will fly her have been hand-picked from
the world's leading specialists Louie
this can be the start of a beautiful
friendship personally designed and
supervised the construction of this
rocket ship Orchestra Heinrich is the
oldest member of the crew so rod Murdock
is the youngest he holds a doctor's
degree in mathematics at the age of 19
technically start to sell him Hamid from
Turkey he's an expert on space medicine
she liked it to work with him his doctor
secret blue mark from Sweden positioned
and physicist and member of our marantz
Etienne Martel
engineering technician I hate you stupid
American pigs so William Rochester llo
did British geophysicist and my
household Kilbourne dr. Hideko murata
will be acting as astrophotographer and
father's mother of five Russia is
represented by dr. Fyodor hola that
nigger from Nigeria of the chief
navigator the great astronomer for
getting this vara mythology from bullies
born dr. David Ruskin this aeronautic
engineer will serve as the official
recorder of this expedition you'll be
catering the flyer zillion dr. Luis
Vargas the ship's first pilot will also
be in charge of communications the
leader of this gigantic undertaking is
John Anderson of the United States who
has dedicated his life to man's conquest
of space further was rocking around
years orbital flights have made him
world famous yes I'm captain miklos beef
piles mean he was the unanimous choice
of the International Space order to helm
this project let's go around here any
you euro freak speak English the rules
straight right away with speaking
English within the next few minutes the
next voice you hear to make
world-shattering history did you a
powered lunar Eagle will take off for
the liquid fuel method and outside the
Earth's atmosphere the freight elevator
to the moon but when the moon's orbit is
reached and Jupiter aligns with Mars the
first landing on the moon will be
attempted if all goes as planned I'm
okay no no no they couldn't get anyone
to take care of the dog no ex- you three
during the entire flight i'll be talking
control will try to keep in
communication with the shit are we there
yet there's Errol wasn't it we there yet
no read your mountains on the value and
the news of the landing that's the Lido
deck god be with you and also with you
hey Earl I'm looking right at your hind
ha let's cheers look the first Sun
Country chartered to the moon man if I
could wrap with them animals I called
the pink lawn chair I call the one by
the window how did that knew they were
men keys and girl you from the birds
here you're evil evil once again on
behalf of our captain and the flight
crew would like to welcome you all
aboard people's express flight 201 to
the moon sorry we had to change into a
dog Ted but it was necessary who cares
public broadcasting needs your support
oh look they got one of those make your
own recording things yep
it's a quarter to two thousand why must
i buy every clock I see I can't wear
gray oh how oh my ears out I
specifically said in my application no
gray can't wear gray it's France we have
better moons and you people stupid let's
see hi mom it's her first day in space
couple monkeys on board probably meet
him at lunch this is dr. David Ruskin
reporting his first entry into the
official log of the Luna ego neat huh
you attempt to reports alien information
as it occurs it is now launched im- uh
something two minutes
great I get that cloth helmet
if are you being served as the kind of
programming I'm gonna set this the
central stud time cuz I'm sledge rip
rock shiny tiles I'm handsome do you
know stupid Americans I'd rather be
knitting I'm all tingly and my Bernhard
kelb I hope I like to moon tank concrete
astronaut no no no it goes on your head
oh one size fits all for a year of nova
or Newton's apple you why does it hurt
my place when I do this ronk drywall yes
the tension is palpable center
oh that's gonna make the racket go dump
huge large at the controls 27 seconds
and counting haha Telegraph's to class
so across oh wait I'm Jewish I need a
pillow and you'll get the tote bag when
we're launching to now no that's the
Mars but noon goonter is everything
ready for our historic trip to the moon
yeah I am gentleman would i can assure
you that everything is ready built ready
on your end yeah i'm swedish so you know
every tangy i beamed myself on your
satellite I hope that's okay with you ah
yeah sure I am you Lena woman of the
future will you dance with me no come on
Mike go talk to her at least yeah I mean
you gotta admit you haven't touched for
woman since the counter administration
great I'll go talk to the potentially
evil Specter will you to cower behind
the desk ok no what do you want for boss
try singing like that idiot from the
short right of what through wall from
all's I want to take you and your role
vibrant to my futuristic world but first
I want to dance with you oh well what
would we do in your futuristic world
does it really matter
all right there novinha yep yeah novinha
woman of the future oh yeah so we go in
or what oh I don't know I thought I'd
let her hang out Oh see what happens so
new veena but the nuvi know we've got
something to do but feel free to make
yourself a sandwich oh you're gonna kiss
or aren't you oh no oh yeah oh right
back twenty-second of theaters
everywhere novinha haha veena Mary over
1,500 miles of other presents be sixteen
thousand miles per hour when i get out
starsky's a dead man point zero zero you
know zero all fours you know three
minutes from long booster power off
switching to four-wheel drive
transferred to atomic power accomplished
my hair is holding up just fine on
profile gyro settings equal well
according to this we're dead
oh they're out a windshield wiper fluid
doctors remark Tommy proceed with
medical checkup all right looks like
teary mugler designed these suits huh
see the doctor what I should warn you
you want me hey I can see my continent
from here comes is it all doubters
having quite a rainstorm back there
first time I've seen a storm from the
other well let me be getting soaked with
rain Becca note I've gone tits like your
boy we are quite right but going far
into the unknown from which we may never
return just make with the squeeze ball I
haven't any doubt at your time do you ft
first course not I never doubted it one
has to develop a bit of fatalism about
all this I never doubted it for a moment
well well well will be poppin papa for
the first time of my life earth looks
good to me dr. Martell don't you think
we'll make it either but of course I'm
so boyish listenable that we should make
it I trust the engines are some affair
is everywhere what will happen will
happen say levees right please Martel
roll up your sleeve oh all these
unimportant details I am in the best of
health well we just want to make sure
one forearm later goodwood I'll start on
our pilot he was gonna start on the
pilot that new new Magna camera how does
work well after taking motion pictures
number to take hmm I can with this
button choose any frame I wish missed it
oh yeah I'm sure had asked didn't I
and this button turns on the bathroom
fan just taking this picture of our
receding us go the photo adds ten pound
next we have some free time I'll give
you some point where am I supposed to
plug in my hair dryer physical condition
of the entire group excellent except for
heinrich whose age is showing everyone
acting artificially calm to cover up the
real excitement about man's first trip
to the moon dr. Ruskin I'll take you
first yeah oh this trip is getting
better all the time busy so soon
recording our trip we're scarce they'll
know away roll on keeping the most
accurate flight log possible mmm working
that well Jared you I was remember Man's
first flight to the moon the rents you
record in the next few days and the
milestones in history oh yes my God look
at your blood pressure what about dr.
Heinrich what what about him what's that
supposed to mean only natural I suppose
he is the oldest don't say anything to
anybody else know either pictorial
such a brilliant man old though only
someday I could be like except for that
old part EMTs are here walkiria oh god
you're drinking again who contributes
most to interplanetary travel jubilation
T cornpone what are you serious girl i
implanted only ones let me do with the
a92 dogs I know I'm gonna survive these
experiments we have work ahead I like
missed out on the surface of the Moon
I'm a geologist and the best map maker
in the world I eat met Megan's yes
Poland is still on your Russian man mmm
course it has already been living i can
when a finger little ready my country
Israel you medical to help ease your
sugar hey how's your little wire mother
hmm are you lucky people nothing seems
to worry you kids in space
sega we're in an unusual magnetic field
it will darken their stars and stuff hmm
well huh yes I thought it'd be better
I'm sorry cool yeah that's so great well
we're gonna die media clusters ahead
Michael's you're on a collision course a
collision combs changing over to our
reaction violet Vargas take over readers
don't travel in flocks youth do hmm
captain the navigator or apologies
course eight degrees to avoid meteors
there's a crack in the dead lithium
crystals I'm good to have two hours
captain the same thing
huh Wow sugar pox we need milk captain
I went my little kitty pants I'm so glad
they snatched us from the rainforest
Marta should I that's not what
navigators black stupid me girls picked
up oh just some stray meteors that's all
right Nene Rodolfo and they stroll into
action Ohio change completed Mel back on
original setting Sammy Churchill now
we're perfectly after all it was our
invention worlds double ganger arrived a
little help there's always one desk with
everybody things around
Colombian coffee sannen little hygiene
much more soothing and practical than
water kds the farmers gone clean by
ultrasound and massage by air spray
cheese no I don't buy it for one minute
to Stockholm I'm gonna have one
installed in my apartment me too when I
get back to Tokyo junk pile on here you
can want me now I'm sorry ladies well
you could have not well we're not at the
Walter if you know hmm well Mimi would
although somehow to keep climbed into
isn't it and I want don't worry intent s
your works gonna start on the moon they
want to see appropriation you can take
place up there I look at people are
moving too fast maybe when we get back
you'll have a litter of moon kittens
captain's log girls gotta look at my
space station to the direct on course to
harbin where the crater of Menelaus
orbit orbit haha another hour and 37
minutes and we should begin retro
procedure for landing Oh can't get
enough of that shot leaving Mother Earth
from up here she looks rather small and
insignificant doesn't she started very
small John Farrell see if anything else
I can help you with no wonder what
they're doing down there probably
watching us well I'm gonna get up to
those stairs and get ready for a
reversal thanks captain you can prove my
motivation and sense of empowerment yeah
looks like God snag em give me my Romeo
dren he shall die a document I need
God's and oceanic
jeez I didn't think space would be so
vast and stuff
move all slippery stretch losing it
remember turn into the skid brakes hey
souvenir for some lucky fan was my
pleasure he take oh yeah reversal
accomplished without mishap landing in
one hour and 32 minutes contents may
have shifted during flight
well up to the rumpus deck everybody
stupid American computer that's what you
hun is what you bought you're so stupid
i hate you don't what i'd like to-- now
ready for my pencil eat the formula far
rate of deceleration for our landing on
the moon final orals and sweaty x over g
minus 3 considering that the moon's
gravitational pull is 16 birth that's
absolutely right he's always right
amazing rod they took trainees to the
moon that a good idea
of course the original calculation oh
feel a song coming on three years ago by
burn our maybe I'll have to sketch him
ironic isn't it that all is brilliance
yes uh Ron burn our could have been such
a Nazi Beast well we're trying to figure
fuel needs back here oh did you know he
was directly responsible for the
extermination of more than a hundred
thousand of my people haha he killed my
mother my father my sisters and my
brother sisters slow down slow down
diner yes nah no call over you will hear
we have a problem here your uniform is
way too tight I didn't want to tell you
in front of everyone reskin doesn't know
dr. heinrichs own father was burn our
it's a surprise so ashamed of what his
father did but he changed his name to
Evelyn champagne King your old man was a
Nazi hunted Jimmy good they work so well
together the bad they must die yes
another a couple little muck again well
we're almost back to earth to wait a
minute
no this is the latest shot of our moon
landing area captain there could you
sign it love Chester captain Anderson to
cruise strapped down for landing yes sir
they get a lot of use out of that pinky
cool picking up crap ease of 30 feets
altitude 500 feet Wisconsin farmer
Howard fleece took this footage of an
actual angel 400
300 whoops 400 again 200
fluffy lips 100 my just land
cocky Todd if I have on my Nina
oh sorry good not just a stick we made
it we made it now spread my seed yeah I
mr. shot yellow sha allah be pleased
raised this ship nirala reasonable where
i want white boy moon our Eagle number
one to central earth control your
colleague we run Paulene you frown
alright control the lunar Eagle 1 over
lunar eagle number one captain Anderson
speaking reporting successful landing on
moon time is calculated + 37 minutes in
signal answering now for first lunar
disembarkation next scheduled contact
with central earth control at 0 200
congratulations lowering the one you
like us you really like International
Space order thank God you made it
captain so I've speaking for all the
peoples of the earth on your crew
represent our heartiest congratulations
you're this first great step in the
exploration of space rental agency
Godspeed yo nigga Wilfred hi Dwight
signing off like a rhinestone cowboy
deluna ego a few minutes man for the
first time we'll set foot upon the moon
whoopee excitement is great but
controlled because of its momentous
importance right I'm now switching over
to my helmet microphone I'd love to get
the storyboards for this scene hmm Wow
now I'm turning on my invisible
electromagnetic ray screen even I don't
buy it which forms a protective shield
over our faces of course it does this
can you my commentary through my micro
tape recorder no I'm activating my wings
then I'll fly with extreme care double
check your oxygen supply there's enough
in each tank for two hours stay up on
the surface of the Moon zip me as you
remember you must develop an additional
reflex action make sure you soup radio
isn't working order at all time now the
natives will try to sell you baskets
Marcel while we were going to fall TV
Oh channels open Jake also lower the
equipment in the wench check and go
light on the sauce is Leah equipment
check mekonnen and Ursula mikonam radio
check check choke man musk Fergus you
and russkom will carry our magnetic
meteorite deflectors I remember when we
hit the surface of the Moon to establish
a four-point perimeter at least a
hundred yards from the ship check Queen
to Queens pawn for check and mate yeah
where's your invisible thing or anything
yes check it's in my purse that call you
got the pudding pops emergency equipment
let's see what else I should know mr.
chickee well anyway ansel Vargas and I
hit the airlock first people let's be
excited this is historic come on let's
feel historic deben felt too good by a
flanch easy yeah that's the meat locker
hmm no it's downtown st. Paul after 50
great planet Tom OBO God why did I
believe the invincible thing well hey
who is that hey Marcy strip malls one
potato two with suncoast videos karate
schools well that's the moon we can go
back now Oh stinks here they must have
cats
rockets got a bump Astrakhan says don't
laugh it's paid for hmm hey it's gum be
gummy
one small step for a man in one small
soda and extra fries look up there you
can see the psyche lights walk slow and
stupid we're on the moon jeez the moon's
covered with fresh step
doc martens on the moon that's one small
step for a man ever that already
captain Ron codpiece on the moon what's
one small so that's taken care of thank
you hey there's no steam in a vacuum I'm
registering static cling
hey comic book chat totes Chuck beaks
chill challenge yes Oh looks like we're
moving of that they're singing ladies
planet a mic yep yeah new Trina new tell
own oxy- veena oh right right woman of
the future just hope you know what
you're doing hey come on gypsy look
she's new veena woman of the future yeah
she sings she dances much she's novena
woman of the future damn straight do you
really need all those socks do you well
perhaps not perhaps you're right my
munchkin believe me won't need this
gentle neck haha she dances a lot like
oh yeah sings a lot to Mike well wit
didn't that's your life from here on out
but I like to be on the robotic if the
experiments done I don't see a problem
that's a can do just remember what
happened to Nelson idiot Jeanette
MacDonald Mike what eventually they die
here's some more chocolate shops did I
think that's enough perk you darling
well okay you know what you're doing
let's pack up everything and move to not
see this planet oh I'm really gonna miss
this old satellite hey can we blow it up
when we leave Wow we'll see honey
the planning of this flag symbolizes the
internationalization of the moon to
prevent individual nations from any
further dispute and pancakes now we
shall continue with the second part of
our mission already in for our
scientific exploration TV repairmen on
the moon do you guys have to follow me
everywhere come on let's all get in the
shot there you go a little left in in a
little in up there
there is no steam in a vacuum huh well
the moon has serious gopher trouble hmm
Oh Vince Coleman is here look out whoo
oh no the throw pillows are attacking
her
we are constantly being bombarded by
falling rocks and useless style an
explosion of meteors hitting the moon's
surface Vargas stakeout this area hey
stink up your own area remember you go
outside this area to stay within the
protection of the course of rocks or off
this is where you take charge everybody
attend to their everybody to get from
street any unusual mineral deposits are
described please report them to me at
once doctors bro mark and Hamid you will
search for signs of air and life whoa
the captain's a log short of a cord I
gotta go into my bag
well get goin explore this is the moon
people jeez where are you two going we
come along we've only just begun to fear
Hey look judge crater ha yeah I pretty
much made the moon they wanted somebody
who knew the moon I made it so I came
along fudge love it yeah craters my idea
no because they're not that weightless
huh I think we're alone
the Sears die looks like some kind of
portal Jim let's get in there and
jumpstart that Chevy
he's using the dryer there is no steam I
know that there's a thing there that
thing right there see it
Oh
whoa blows rental manager here looks
like a normal meeting
you
huh look cactus or michael berry hound
episode
what nothing we're gonna make work
oh look at this on this would make such
a statement in our foyer a
it will help you to just browsing who
exploding urinal cake would you stop
handing me stuff like that you want
another one no I don't want another one
various minerals and stones have been
collected and none of them you have
found volcanic crystals and sharp coral
like formations which appear translucent
hmm people explore take some samples
come on it's gold isn't it not that
cheap crap they sell like QVC yes yes
that's gold oh really low gravity young
wait a minute wait a minute the potatoes
are done seems to be something on you
200 here why it's a sample rocks away
careful you fools careful don't damage
it she's when you dig it out your
wrinkled old Nazi crunch what is it dr.
olaf well lately I've been feeling
listless and oh the rod I never see it's
a boy nor have i behold the only thing
greater than yourself it's beautiful
it's hardened palm kernel oil like fried
like liquid fire we are the first people
to set eyes on a stone like this it's
beautiful however but he'll not evil and
sharp like the jewel of Medea
the material very well named very well
named i have named it it's called me
ight
Corner nobody's are you listening for
something I feel something you run my
foot ha did he take the psych test
before we left well I saw that one first
I claimant Bob's rock I saw that one
first I get to name that one I saw that
one heads rock
Moon's actually kind of a letdown yeah
strangers on the moon buddy badoo be I
think they put a diaphragm in an old
flat iron there must be a
it's not good air but it's nothing alive
they're not gonna I don't think that
there there's absolutely no way that
they go oh my god mush no you can only
apply 16 the tongue on the moon oh well
then let the space procreation
experiment begin sorry I thought you
were Frenchie it looks like the logo of
Miss Saigon they're walking into beam
hey I see a sign that says wall drug
200,000 miles mrs. Muir captain captain
Anderson I'd like to search deeper
please no maybe more precious attempts
like the module stone here can we have
the explosion yes but we must hurry
we've only got about an hour supply of
oxygen left a crime scene and we brought
some cool bottle rockets to bear in the
hall
oh good one mark easy
moon does not to die me its essence come
on touch it I carry out you taught jets
take a chance to its drinking is
officially a key yeah I call it me juice
well feels Russian herb piracy kit I
know why they got to well creature don't
know oh yeah let's name it oh oh stupid
i'm thinking blue light decerebrate yeah
yeah all fool like an old fool well you
see they get us back to the ship please
I'll stay with him way to ruin the
moonwalk chuckles after that that's
muslem they're missing their not with us
then we'll have to search but we must be
quick because there's not much time
follow the sound of their lips
and lo the stone had been rolled away
look they're footprints Messiah tracks
two three days old good off guard the
males we should really get some
exploring in
I forget it
a Screen Gems presentation hmm another
Screen Gems presentation you know we got
to get our Christmas tree earlier next
year these are really dumb mmm there's
air in this cave dark man from sky
bringing era p life
a Screen Gems
now you can see the strength
Iceman
you've come to the end of the cave
there's a solid wall of ice yeah luckily
your invisible shield will protect you
from it huh
well it'd be good for the vodka tonics
we found on the way back are we doing
something really stupid again you too
dumb spell lankan over there
that's it huh I was not crazy
this Omar's head in here let's see
that'll make it nine or ten to the moon
oh I see that as a cry for help well
soon take the camera now boy what's the
six to the moon don't let yourself get
caught yes I use the Old Course at st.
Andrews its unforgiving sand traps good
boy the magnet boy right don't let
anyone else get caught ah oh god the
Americans in trouble I see the American
okay okay five words first word sounds
like grow pope of greenwich village okk
fourth word yes word grasp ask play all
four kids I asked myself before we even
started who's the most likely person to
get caught in a sinkhole Gary yeah
exactly there it is I got the magic boy
yeah too late
some sort of anti sand device apparently
hopping porn
oh this makes no sense and yet it's
working
let let go my foot rod accept your
friend Ron ah it's like kind of a goofy
Iwo Jima good thing I'm the a hunky
American leader I would have been done
for Oh who'd we lose back there again
another lie me oh well then well I
suppose over have been a long day over
meanwhile friend she's having a dinner
party did everything go he's not doing
what believe it or not I am French side
it's 202 degrees below zero you'll
return just in time mm-hmm and this is
only the beginning of the lunar night
yes night here like day is equivalent to
15 days and nights upon the earth it
will go up to approximately 250 below
zero um you can move your arm now to be
out there now than at the peak of the
lunar day and it's hotter than boiling
water out there have you led and dr.
Rochester's boots contributed to his
sinking into the pumice dust and the way
he dragged his better on the ship
answers which contributed to the death
of dr. william rochester yet microphone
is the devil's mark asian party returned
to the lunar eco because of diminishing
oxygen supply and the necessity to
normalize our bodily processes so what
do you think up on pillows pizza sir
poor bill such a tragic death for a man
so dedicated i know we all feel terrible
about it no I didn't say I care I didn't
say to him yep I suppose old to continue
a prolonged search do you think they'll
get back to the ship if they're still
alive if woman can survive just keep
praying I have been
well we should talk again rod dear diary
he talked to me again more later despite
the adverse circumstances we are
according to plan photographing various
parts of our galaxy from which we hope
to obtain a new perspective which I for
one think his long pass to captain
Anderson to entire personnel please
assemble on a deck that includes the
steno pool oh come on up professor
mittens birth control has been broken
off as I've told you we are in complete
isolation let's party yeah whoo the
booze evil seems to be working perfectly
yar try to make contact again ya can't
find I'm the captain and but I'll just
do a usin our Eagle One to central earth
control our magnetic receiver is working
do you hear a central earth control do
you hear a central earth control
nobody's home nobody so nobody's home
good but we didn't pay the electrical
bill there's something men's wearhouse
we will not be undersold I guarantee it
looks like hieroglyphics it's not
Egyptian not African it looks like
oriental picture did be Chinese oh if
only we had a day oh we do think credit
the Mariners are in the series you
recognize that a dick oh is it something
you understand it's impossible it can't
be you know what it is can you translate
it for saveco I don't know Oh Troy no
soup with buffet I speak for the great
coordinator who the moon we advise and
warn you
return to Earth at once you have done
enough damage go on come on it's moving
again you have been bombarding us for
years incessantly leave us in peace
here's hoping Christmas finds you well
read your mind oh you know your every
thought you are discussed speak as you
do we communicate by thought waves
strong letter to follow Morgan Johnson
Stewart moon lawyers probably live where
we live in a great sealed city below we
were just getting to that enslaved by
your earthly emotion so your arm free
lust passions of conquest I kind of feel
bad about our path allow you to stay
here well you would only contaminate our
perfect form of harmony secrets Ellen is
their faith known suffering succotash
they are here they say they are in love
we are studying this curious emotion hmm
we find that love turns two evils aliens
do run we will destroy them you and your
kind it's from pat buchanan remember we
have a power we got power you touch will
oh this is impossible it must be a hoax
is it evil what do you think well mr.
mood bad these symbols could have been
sent by an earth power already secretly
here on the mall seems that Jerry is
already dicky-bird into the cheese
factory sir a power that wishes the
scarce away dianetics how do you feel
about that that's native I asked me how
should I know I don't believe there are
any moon people do you I'm convinced
it's possible mine Fury's have made it
all up to
sexual tension we write us off there's a
gay curable huh what hairball god
Hinrich ate one of the cats i'm resting
comfortably now hey give Heinrich the
Heimlich here attach these jumper cables
to his nipples well you guys got it
covered I'm gonna get out of here
everybody go hello please dr. Heinrich
suffered from a heart attack and let
that be a lesson to the rest of you
Father why did you do it well you gotta
Schwartz of all going there how can I
ever live down to your crime give me
some vapor rub now I hate my thighs move
burn huh I cannot go on being Hainish
behind alone called me patches what do
you mean I will be garish energy Arizona
I am Nick Heinrich hearing Aldric any
occurring von poopie hello mommy
gutentag puppy you are the son of burn
our call me buttons the dwarf who wiped
out my entire family well Hugh new
puppies oh my god
sledge fist him it counted me on my life
for what I did everything humanly
possible to make good my father scrap
what that are sure I forgive you stand
my magic
can you still be my friend sure how
about some general foods international
coffee
you took down over there rest now the
same symbols rights way to please a deco
if you lived on the moon you'll be home
by now earth before you depart we must
have one thing yams you will leave
behind the two cats cat geez we're the
only cats important hey wait a minute
cats have a most unusual appeal for us
here but unfortunately we have none here
on the moon they interest us almost as
much as the two human beings who joined
us that they were delicious by the way
fascinating yeah turn out Louie no no no
no guys to open those doors again for
the two cats well I think so I'll go
I'll go with you
hey hey hey come on guys it's me
puffball and taffy come on Hey look I
won't drink of your water glass City
I'll say off your couch guys come on can
I write that nowhere else to go no thank
you captain's law we're running away as
fast as we can lost Inga and Omar too
bad we left the surface of the Moon at
6700 this decision was based on the
warning which emanated from those
mysterious symbols even though we were
in doubt of the survival of settlement
Sigrid we had to make a quick decision
in order not to jeopardize our mission
my dove bars melting gotta go solo
mission fraidy cat comes to a close
three hours and 10 minutes of flight
we're right on the button we just passed
a neutral line operating towards the
Earth's gravitational pull you gonna
show me down the river to you bastards
look hey the schmaltz is on fire
tinku
scrappy you should have gone before we
left John it's ready get the dressing I
mean that's their early warning system a
cocker spaniel
just give me that danko throw yourself
on the flaming moon rock
orrow Toro Blair
and don't come back haha they can't burn
in there no oxygen quick thinking Louie
I think the dogs would have the middle
yo how about a snausage or something
that was a close one well I better get
up relief ruskin let him relieve himself
well name the modesto the oxygen fused
it into radwin it came in contact with
the gold would you shut let me fix it
boy oh it's not too bad thank you I can
do that they're here to be hit what time
you put us at the happy chef captain
loon our Eagle One to central earth
control do you hear a centralized
control I'm making keys over here you we
hear you lottery the one we have your
position boom why did you leave the moon
we had an urgent departure please give
us our position your pussy Chung come in
since with control we've lost you we've
lost you cents worth control come in
we're not talking to you until you're
back on the moon boys laugh sit down
nobody will be there when you get there
Clint star don't understand it we've
lost earth contact completely remember
what the people on the moon said mm-hmm
they are the power to immobilize us at
will but don't say that but they said it
could be true what the gurbles I'm ready
Oh lie down dr. Heinrich there's nothing
you can do now we're all our way back to
earth I used to take off I missed it off
lie down no you please navigate or to
captain put 34.3 check blood
dear mom really in trouble more later
kiss it's just like what we saw earlier
only backwards wait 10 minus XC no no
wait i mean ii x
is this the end of captain Chuck hearts
lab
we knew how to equal one over here right
okay our special today is roast pork
that's served with time oh wait wait
captain we're being fertilized Zuzu's is
you try I don't know I try one okay wait
wait no wait now no wait no point five
no point 7 and 5 10 no wait that's not
it I hope you got that I'll training
oh here we go bubble bubble bubble help
Mike Mike Mike it's not tomorrow is
calling me oh my cake is ready oh my god
my head I me I didn't know I can do that
I'll make it stop if see guys what's
going on please wash your hands I'm onto
you servo to make shank of lamb chutney
Nevada weird singing lady from the
future why robot friends are not meant
to be enslaved Robert are machines like
anything else they're meant to be used
and put on the shelf anti roll over and
is evil little guilty within a woman who
veena even though it breaks my heart I'm
going to have to ask you to depart well
get that new walk out loving turn oh wow
lo the rocks yeah don't worry guys I'm
sure there'll be another magical
mystical singing lady coming along
anytime yeah that'll happen come here
you right back
holidays everyone I don't go back matter
no more not ready to motor grabber force
yes captain do it right at the radio
yeah sure no no thanks thank you thank
you up is fine let me stand on my own
two feet see I told you it's only a
passing thing John I feel that I must
advise you there is something wrong
something unexplainable I know I know
mekonnen but everything is working
perfectly in the ship I'm cold jeez
everybody's whiny what's going on that's
what I wanted to tell you John outside
temperature reading is 200 425 degrees
below and still falling yeah Mon it's no
wonder it's cold in here it's 55 degrees
remember all my dad if they hate to
insert captain quick Captain Quins chalk
already Fergus
my god Cuba is huge
right why this thing is moving oh no
that's my phone enough Paul George New
York earth is being rid of soap scum
thanks to thousands of scrubbing bubbles
that's me hey wait up I'm getting a
reception captain Anderson good it's a
little blurred but I think I can see the
picture oh you've done a wonderful job
well that's some picture nothing's
moving my cram at Doogie something must
be jammed in the TV try New York try
jiggling the cord
Mayor Dinkins declares New York really
cold moves tennis inside there is
something wrong with it it's turned into
an artist rendering the Machine a
perfect daughter I guess Nancy Reagan's
back in town yes you see great
this kind of weather wouldn't even face
the Midwest now it looks like Jerusalem
yeah this is flash freeze bring Clarence
Birdseye ins degree I agree you do buy
some scientific means they whoever Leah
and found a way to phrase all molecular
activity those whizzing noises yes Missy
in other words one be yucky noodle
atmosphere by extracting all firms
patties but how could that be possible
sounds very simple it's me come on it is
a principle of the hydrogen bomb
behaviour you'll see i agree with you
through some superior device they found
the means of achieving any place your
phenomena deals mr. Flintstone that must
have been that strange noise sweet jeje
i somehow few is an earthly power
gentlemen let's make no mistake our
situation is extremely serious but movie
we are caught in orbit in order to
survive you have to remain at our
present multitude how long I don't know
until we find the solution let's go to
work oh and we must be naked yeah I'm
getting London this is a new glasses
radio time something like this has ever
happened before for the past 10 hours
the North American continent remains in
an isolation of silence no contact can
be established by any means of
communication with either Canada to
United States or Mexico I don't like the
station intense call it in the world the
gonna turn around yeah she's music come
on yeah that's how be taken stand by
well if you informed we now return to
our radio no wonder all communication is
shut off you know I don't think we could
even come down out of our final orbit
common phrase you're right Louie do I we
gotta go we are insulated we are safe in
here we yes but for how long no
don't know we're operating now under
automatic control how about the engines
Montel the engines milled i forgot the
engines over worked on it's only a
matter of time before the turbines give
out when you have come so close to
success and such a month this may work
it simply has to listen you want to know
a secret well our emergency space taxi
works on atomic power right right right
we must fashion a powerful atom bomb by
assembling and uniting it's a number of
Bartlett's such as we used on the moon
two men dawn by lot walk into my bar
should pilot the taxi over life volcano
I'm thinking purple cat available Kaka
can drop the moment of the crater the
resultant explosion might throw the big
freeze yes but I'm such a wonk how old a
space taxi crashed through the frozen
atmosphere sign on penetration market as
it disperses the micrometeoroid clouds
it should break an opening for the space
taxi to go through yes it could be
piloted through frozen space but but but
but we have to inform you that it might
disintegrate in the explosion that's why
I said the two men should be drawn by a
lot because the night belongs to Lover's
their chances to return to the Luna II
are quite remote he'll do it yeah Mickey
Rourke is a genius you go John
you it is worth the risk to break up the
big freeze which paralyzes not only the
country but the whole continent you know
as I this is our duty our only hope
wanna see me in a towel and gentlemen
it's our only chance to accomplish our
mission and playing the shit back to it
captain do you have to go parties right
well we'll make the bomb i want to have
long played them cheat on my wife love
you you think i'm sexy and you want my
odd um one baby but you know careful now
don't love it there move Freddie alright
tell the others it's okay now yes go
ahead hey mal sure you do
what are you doing I am merely finished
it you disconnected it you crazy man but
you don't understand this is our chance
think steal the North American continent
with remain frozen your greatest rival
would be powerless I am one with you
don't you see this way we control the
west and I'll commit this world what do
you mean we and it is French for yes you
see you're not one of us I'm not only a
scientist I'm also a human being not an
insane murderer you traitor i betray no
one particularly not myself I want to
live to grab it look out to move my
petite little bit stench smells like
camembert an espresso
Oh
get off my mittens
jacques brel is under siege you tried to
sabotage the bomb is it all right now
all I have to do is reset the fuse yeah
on pure beef fragments ah fragments
pregnant nothin nope no son of mine
busted can I get a new one good
I'm one to go somebody ate my fudge
Urkel and i am the other ebony none of
us is free to choose his ancestors
where's deeds good or bad whatever just
glad I don't have to go god bless you
till we meet again I need several days
to get my affairs together refund of
your purchase price call now at
oh-six-hundred universal time I'll be
dead he's taxi piloted by dr. Eric
Heinrich and myself will leave the lunar
I eagle to drop atomic bomb 'let's into
the crater of the volcano popocatepetl
be caca poopoo cookie fucking an attempt
to break the big freeze oh and one more
thing I don't want to die now this is
dr. Ruskin signing off prolly forever
can I eat you one who died
oh and the puppy volunteer to my place
I don't recall asking you to pick me up
I can't go i got a family then take care
of me dr. Rous Mach schnell I bet he'd
trade that dog for two or three more
lines
this is my secret place down here I only
let up on all my friends in snugglin
minds to advance the no-frills control
panel dr. Ruskin the captain Anderson
cabin pressure equal ready for launch
geez about time penetration rocket don't
say that my work here is done now you
can all just look at my clearly defined
area hey Tin Tin take your adventure
elsewhere ready ladies and gentlemen the
budget just ran out so from here on out
just bear with us david will be over the
target in one minute and 12 seconds will
be dead in 1 minute 13 seconds first
time you called me David my name's Larry
sorry oh my plan and it's David I'd hope
that you will carry on my work
you you don't think we'll survive this
really are as dumb as you look I don't
know what am I saying no we're not going
to survive it works if you pull out in
time looks like they're in a wham video
set the bomb release david dancing
drivers
bombs ready we'll be over the target in
12 seconds all the course holding steady
gratify release oh god yes fine why do
they need two people for this don't SWAT
down
you guys ever sat on a German before
what I mean right on no here they've
dropped it captain Anderson flopped it I
knew the google trusted this backdrop is
so lavish
lemons sisters to debt by Dawn
it was him work oh I've never been so
happy in my whole oh it didn't work it
didn't work confirming it's pulling stop
that come on boy showering up
they're in trouble I sale man I refuse
to feel bad
more wet your pants wet mine David god
bless you did it do they sneeze oh oh
we're gonna die
whoa that's gotta hurt ah there was
clearly a stinking
journey to the beginning of time and now
my official report the sangai sangee a
lie that's foreign for better you than
me it was the will of God
Hey look at this I guess my stick is
shorter than the Germans I prayed hey
brought dogs monkeys anybody thing to
bring a parka John John we are caught in
a big freeze first it's so cold hold me
switching back to chemical fuel it's no
use it will work the freezes its filling
the shit his abilities are no Cyril not
good John look look now who dumped dry
ice on the console Furcal Chun captain I
left the vent open in summer the hook
I'm not a very good captain
okay pencils down let's see your wagers
my coffees cold take advantage of the
big freeze to warm myself let's draw
straws to see who we cut open and crawl
inside frozen frozen in space oh the
weather outside is frightful sir is it
too late for me to back out of this
expedition so lunch cold cuts oh sorry
does cold enough for you aha hey there
cold did I go the same similar are you
translating it says you died Joe no
artists gud Ecco please please you
didn't like the cats eat iced earth
dates hmm now you have seen our strength
stop but we have seen your human
straight the way you people have
sacrificed themselves to save the others
still you must die who those you left
behind we have also learned that all
your earth emotions are not evil and
more like that you have come to peace
man your people on earth war upon
suspended animation it's park noodle and
I have not been harmed chair sailboat
return to Earth at once and someday when
you come back we'll be welcomed yes
we'll give you your stinking cats back
they have scratched up our entire planet
lunar eagle on Gloria lon do you hear me
captain Anderson stand by for the
director of the ISO oh okay still alive
I have no words to express our feelings
that you made it back it's something
most unusual this happen to us in the
last 16 hours you cannot explain it do a
lucky to have escaped it on prepare for
landing I did it I saved us all I'm
chunk iron chest and i won
my guest tonight via satellite the earth
so what do you think we learned here
that three maybe four people would have
worked a whole lot better than 12 oh and
always bring cats yeah that's what we
learned from Fresno appease moon people
they're there now now you're here guys
that was my one shot at happiness my one
grab for that brass ring of love on one
shot a true love in this lonely world
now this is good chocolate chip cookie
dough Mike magical singing future ladies
are a dime a dozen no problem right into
her again the meantime letters yeah I
think that's a good idea now yeah this
first letter is from melody munos I must
ask you not ever do that again oh yeah
probably good idea okay put that on
still store there cambot this one says
dear mike tom crow gypsy camp out on the
rest of the crew I'm the satellite of
love hi my name is melody munos then I
just wanted to tell you how much I enjoy
your show I go over to Kim Metra's house
every weeknight at midnight just to
watch your show Kim and I got our whole
biology class to watch it Kim dating Raj
now thinks I'm cute all right I got one
more here's uh I got a couple more this
is from Eric able put this on still
store Eric rights let me begin by saying
that if I could I would have the show
hooked up intravenously to my right arm
permanently when I look for a girlfriend
one of my deciding factors is if she
likes your show or not I'm wrong no not
wrong it's strange but your penis no
that's wrong I'd back off of that here
anyway this next one is signed 13 and 12
nah man I put that on still start and
there's a lovely picture oh do you think
that's 13 or 12 I'm guessing it's 13 but
it could be 12 13 a year ago huh anyway
we are 13 and 12 we are fans of your
show it's great and everything but there
could be a few changes no Jerry you
should rewire crow what so that he talks
with an Austrian accent I thought about
that hey Tom servos head with gumball so
that he's not such an airhead hey well
hey evil nincompoops put that in your
pipe and do the Hokey Pokey yeah now you
can see there Frank that's the trouble
with relationships they're trouble yeah
but oh
Frank I have said no friends in the
house but it's her it's the lady I can
fulfill your wildest dreams Frank my man
oh I want to call Saul dare to dream
Frank novenas gonna crash here tonight
so where's my croissant hey well I'm
sure she really liked you Frank
there's a difference this has been a
presentation from Comedy Central Candice
Bergen host Saturday Night Live next hey
boopie
I don't think so Baldy right this second
a member of the family is waiting to be
picked up with a Motorola pager you know
now hi boy no well his voice isn't any
higher hater right this second someone
needs a ride with a Motorola pager you
know now thanks for picking us up mom
hug me you're wet
those fashionable copper rivets
sorry about your coming render better
coming Xander better coming watch out
we're coming
new coca-cola Santa packs the only real
holiday refreshment look for this
display just off
started December eighteenth for two
straight weeks Comedy Central brings you
our best from 1995 finish this year with
a bang every weekday from ten a.m. to
three pm we'll bring you our biggest our
vest and our freakiest comedy programs
so while your home this holiday season
we make it simple wake up roll over and
tune in it's the best of Comedy Central
1995 starting Monday at ten we at Comedy
Central would like to wish all of you
out there the very best of holidays and
remind you that christmas is a time to
be with the ones you love and to give to
those who are less fortunate this is
often difficult to remember when
christmas is more often used marketing
gimmick santa's use a liquor salesman
and angels sing' fifty percent off
everything in the store we in comedy
central's celebrate the spirit of the
season and only want to wish you and
your family happy hall at