mystery science theater 3000 show 508
real one in the not too distant future
next Sunday ad there was a guy named Joe
nothing different than you owe me is
Moloch institute just another face in
red jumpsuit we did a good job cleaning
up the place
as watch them all the monitor is my mind
control head because he used those
special robust healthy eats and breathes
and other science facts it's just the
show mystery
oh no what is this aho this is my second
grade piano recital and gypsy wake up
check this out oh you actually get a
feeling for what it was like to really
be in there oh yeah this is really Oh JA
fees are fascinating now who took these
uncle Roy oh yeah the guy with the mole
right exactly gypsy continues are so
huge hi everybody welcome to the
satellite of love well you can probably
tell by now that Joel just transferred
all his old home movies the videotape
you know what I think this is that
picnic we took up to koshkonong mouth
osculum mouths I'm kind of worried about
time served and salsa Oh watch what I do
now gypsy check this out you pull the
shorts down now that's funny yeah they
are this minis kids no that's Brett and
Brenda there Bryan and bridges kids
minis kids are all rain Tony right and
Therese oh yeah yeah this is fascinating
tell me don't go in too far Hey look
what I found swingley quite right
explain to me again how this bulky racer
fell out of the closet and onto these
home movie transfers when the closet
isn't anywhere around here yeah weird
isn't it yeah yeah no matter I've got
duplicates in my footlocker ha yeah I uh
I know I found those Oh Marilyn McCoo
and Billy Davis jr. calling crawl
baaahhh Jo I wonder if you wouldn't
indulge me today Frank's been down a bit
lately and well when the poor fellow's
not shuffling head down through the lab
he's locked himself in his room watching
old misfits of science episodes so to
pick him up I thought I'd let him do
this week's invention exchange really
put the spark back in
for this week's invention we're ready
for you Frankie right my invention
exchange this week these fully lined
leather sprinkler pants that i like to
call lederhosen hose it now i can in my
lederhosen lalalalalalala I just wanted
to wear lederhosen okay it's a stupid if
that should I admit I just want to be
for variant for what brief shining
moment is that so wrong Frank yes it is
wrong deeply wrong but you've been under
a lot of stress lately tell you what
we'll get you an elf into horn would
that make you feel better yes mhm why
don't you go on with your invention
exchange Jim it's joel and if you'll
indulge me or hind earnest I'd like to
turn over this week's invention exchange
to our own crow T robot thanks y'all the
vulture long associated with pestilence
and death is in reality a clean and
helpful bird who is quite easy to get
along with so to improve his image I
invented Sarah the bombing buzzards row
yeah based on the water drinking bird
this friendly carrion eater cleans up
roadkill or table scraps that's great
crow yeah it kind of looks like you
crawl I think you'll agree there are a
few sights in nature as beautiful as a
plump member of the Cathar today family
pulling a sinuous string of fetid meat
off a week dead Thompson's gazelle
there's a theme song want to hear it oh
oh sure crow 5 and Buzzard caw caw caw
Bob and Buzzard ha ha ha Bob ozzard
immediately deep or what hits DVD
of your movie this week Joel stars the
Ricola oh thank you Frank would you just
get back there your experiment this week
Joel stars Sean Connery's brother Neil
and more than happy to tell you that
it's called operation double double 07
and now i have to strangle Frank
Robin Buzzard caw caw caw by crow
illegally deep deep deep pit they run
hey assault on a queen the Danny
Bonaduce story mutiny on the birds good
thing they have an espresso machine get
over here and turn the music down
I like this
all hands on me
don't how to make
it's tuna salad sandwiches
honey
is there anything this guy doesn't do
kid power I sailed to Tahiti with an
all-girl crew well like that was this
wet t-shirt uh oh you know when there's
four people on a screenplay there's
gonna be trouble
you know I'm suddenly hungry for cracker
jacks and I don't know why
he sat on his glasses walls she would
like to get permission to come aboard he
likes to admit to means he's got a
deviated septum
he gets his hair cut on Tuesdays he
prefers stopping to potatoes yesterday
for shaggy clothes me this guy can't
possibly live up to the song they wrote
about him holy just in the common name
Wallace so you're saying you like this
guy
no please don't hold back how do you
really feel women who sing too much
missing about port of call Cindy
now this is one naughty Navy we do more
hair and makeup before breakfast and
most people do all day it's the old
spice guy it is must be one of those
airplanes I've heard them talk about so
much me yee-ha Paul Williams lunchbox
stay there my friend no one else has a
lunch anywhere as good as mine we now
return to ship of fools skiddley
huh you know William Conrad were there
they could watch a letterbox version he
wants to change the channel does he get
another woman
Oh yuck she's fo being his bad huh oops
wrong room should I come back y'all
Oh oh thank god i thought we're gonna
see his naked butt thank you sir I'll
bill your room hello I'm Merv Griffin
I was just gonna press pause but yeah
what's it like being the TV Cindy well
it's better than fo being is bad now
showing on my back Morgan Stewart's
coming home at two four six and eight
yes may we help you when did I hire you
this is one great motel six another life
thank you for touching me sir that will
keep me going for the entire day L&R is
this your robe around the pms pinafore
someone's on a pogo stick it's been
nearly two minutes since anyone's
fondled you sir I suppose it's for you
tell him I'm not here
a block really really really
hmm
don't wait a minute how is it that he
gets color on his girl but only black
and white on his TV what's Moneypenny
doing there isn't that a conflict of
interest hmm oh that's nice they have a
bar sign up there for the Pirates they
have a very loose dress code at this
business or
Tora just the one
um this is cysts on the back of your
head it
pop your zits it's been
come in Thunderbirds Johnny Astro real
radar Claude Rains pops the clutch and
tells the world to eat his does he hmm
James Brolin in the car Michael I want
all episodes of Captain nice burn oh my
god herpes gone bananas
well this is Bob going my imminent death
hole
a Screen Gems presentation
the way Waldo pepper thanks for the all
clear Moneypenny suddenly she's a coffee
table
you know i love my torsos and you
I think I know why Thunder ball was a
hit you never saw him kiss anyone in it
this is Rita braver reporting to you
live from Krakatoa east of Java
here come the clown there might be bees
burning in there I've gotta save them
hmm smells good Hey look what I found I
think it's a guy oh he's patron now
better call paul / dom
I'm gonna run on the sprinkler will be
picky no you know there's probably
nothing but bass jigs in there
colette foamy is so thick put out this
fire Oh guys I'm gonna go start lunch
I'll meet you back at the ranch
sandwiches again okay ya later
too late stead all right only getting
out of here let's start them up
quick some lip blusher
oh this game again thanks Roy I
appreciate your help
now why is she dressed like Barney
Rubble Mustang Sally you better slow
that Mustang down hello Maya speaking
Ward died in the explosion it's that ok
the box with me ok fine now let's get to
work on his girlfriend the Japanese oh
and puppies secretaries week I bought
you a god how will you make it on your
own it's up to you now mmm this time I
want the girl alive I've got a few
questions to ask her oh and lose the
ring go hat
so you're not wearing any pants
the banks of circle pines add new city
ordinance all buildings to be painted
beige
get Christie wha Oh see this is what
happens when you Bob for french fries
mmm gentlemen here we have a practical
example of the theories I have
Illustrated I suggest we ox acute the
two weeks ago the patient you see here
miss Yasuko sustained first and second
degree burns at my hands on her face as
shown on the slides I'm looking for Fang
me here from Edinburgh last week when i
saw this girl's condition he decided to
operate immediately before scar tissue
began to form I'm glad to be back here
in time to show you the results of this
operation personally it's great to be
here thanks for supporting live surgery
fantastic she now Michael Jackson's
journey is complete a miracle in plastic
surgery don't you think a miracle yes
plastic surgery hmm oh she's turning
Japanese I really think so the results
are due not only to modern surgical
technique but also to an ancient Tibetan
process defined as the hypnotic process
of total recall it differs from the
usual hypnosis in that it allows us to
operate with the complete surrender of
the subconscious you nurse obtain the
patient's collaboration Japan Oh dr.
matthew g maputo jata hoon kal kal me
your vote in yards last Nanak
experiments yeah aura ho sakta Doctor
Who Fung was asking me if it would be
possible to make a demonstration of
hypnosis of Total Recall know this
experiment requires the outlay of a
great deal of energy why don't you try
it why aren't you bye no no not the
young lady her hats too big excuse me
doctor I really thought that I was just
whispering actually it's my fault I
didn't hear you but I am capable of lip
reading I would say the young lady is
not an ideal subject for this sort of
thing she's hot he appears to have
unusual willpower I'm afraid he would
take too long I found that out the hard
way however we have miss Yasuko with
whom I have already conducted
experiments of the same type and it
would simplify things if Miss Yasuko
would agree Thank You mr. Connery's
brother
all right what an evening gentlemen
please watch Neil rock maybe a second
pair of it we'd all right here's the
church here's the steeple open the door
and go to sleep on the sixth sense with
Gary Collins
the powers of matthew star you know is
rick wakeman on the premises you did
about the cast of Jacques Brel arrives
on the scene now Monsieur schuco has
lost direct contact with time he thinks
she's in dress later in the war room
right up to the present day is at our
disposal it can be totally brought back
if we so desire because every experience
she has lived through has been
registered on her subconscious or from
the year boy to precision than the most
highly developed electronic brain let's
pants our subconscious for now what are
you doing leave her alone I ever tell
Tuesday
well the Rodney King verdict Chris came
in
Nancy Sinatra's kicking ass
role in Massacre fights back
not exactly Jackie Chan isn't everybody
stop flipping I'm not a hugger please
you heard me you know I can read lips
could I tell you I can read lips I'm
read lips right now
naughty little girl
sam donaldson
sales from the dark side they need
coffee in there quick it's michael kay
look out well that was easy geez I'm
already running ahead of schedule
I wonder who that yes hurry
we just came to beat everybody up we're
leaving now thanks I hate to be
interrupted when I give a lecture you
hurt or John fries dead
this man is dead no duh yes
unfortunately I found myself distracted
so i used the sublime attend me it's me
don't tell me doctor that there's
anything that would be able to distract
you oh yes for instance when a charming
girl keeps gazing out of the window
while a brawl is going on okay get it
it's your fault if my jaw is broken oh
I'm sorry look what can I do to make it
up to you meet my house what do you mind
your gadgets ago I've got an idea like
you should live in missionary or cease
maybe jewels really gone off the deep
end this time all I know is in this
outfit I feel like a total femme you
know what I don't have a problem with it
you know well I do
me
all right time for my daily backrub
who's going to do the honors Joel none
of us have working arms I know
hey Joel what is that thing it's all
part of my diabolical plan but it's just
a useless prop that you built it's not
even connected to anything I know
you
Joe is there any point to this I've got
a lot of work to do would you mind
telling us what this is all about that's
stole your ruining it for me
you
it appears to me really fun schedule I
know wait until the judge gives his
verdict what else can you do don't
forget we have a corpse to deal with
here Corp mr. Shue goes disappeared too
sorry dr. Todd Lewis George remain in
our disposal until the investigation is
over how long will that take we're
moving as fast as we can but please
don't set foot outside the limits of
montecarlo until you get the okay from
us but I have to go back to columbia
university I have some operations that
are waiting I can't remain here
indefinitely the former Miss Moneypenny
sir your highness there's your van come
on I hope you'll be very happy together
oh he's hardly Sean I realized but he
comes cheap the Osterman weekend miss
Shizuka was right that's an ugly beard
you can see the resemblance to john
saxon thinks that i'm not so sure that
really i don't think he's quite so
good-looking yeah oh yeah why don't we
shave the beard off just to make sure
just peel it or it is mine I'm attached
to it I wanted to remain right there and
furthermore I'd like to know what's
going on here I'm cunning and allied
can't recipe a knowledge for Western
Europe remember the elf empiricism is
max will my assistant you're the brother
of our topic michael ovitz so i think we
can trust you Tommy me candy candy cane
mmm the flirting non you'll got it
mm-hmm swiss steak for lunch lucky guy
I'd like to make a confession i think
you're hot huh you know dave barry's not
funny I should have used mission turn
your head you're fine
drop that knife in your mind will find
walking what does he have a fur ball or
something drop i said i am the walrus
coo coo cachoo yeah i think i had her in
eighth grade now time for his catheter
ooh she's a flibbertigibbet love the
wisp clown I want this problem called
Maria taken care of permanently sister
Mary mayhem Father forgive me for I have
murdered yea though I walk through the
shadow of the valley of death
make me happy how'd I do she is good
there is a role for women in the church
sisters are doing it for themselves sin
and the art of archery this handy
hostage packs into a compact 9 x 14 case
hard case also available she's making a
human burrito make it snappy sister we
got other pickups come on our channel
our journal well boy I'd kill for a jump
cut right about now oh lord please took
my work reflecting in darn I a few the
proud the Opus Dei benedictus qui veiny
it in a little bitty boo do pal is this
a documentary on how to do this whatever
this is or she's a stunt done you know I
saw her get interviewed on the sci-fi
channel
she lose ender don't outward bound and
this is the result now this is when you
sit back and watch it all come together
let hurts put you in the ambulance check
Turk 182 will ever back tomorrow human
cleaners will clean your humans
overnight husbands were ruled same right
now let's review the steps on how to run
a hostage down a rope um could we stop
it at baskin-robbins
older repo clergy dr. country would you
look at that photo it was in mrs.
choucas bag she said you know him it's
Ward Jones he was planning to marry her
then I showed up I met him when he took
my course in hypnosis the one I gave in
Japan a very capable chat thinks he's a
chicken saw Jones killed this morning
what's been killed by the same people
who try to kidnap his shuka this rivalry
she's back in our hands Ward had
important information he wanted to sell
us unfortunately was killed before he
got it to us naturally Ward asked us to
protect Jessie ago because he'd given
her some secret information and he was
afraid she might be in danger now she
denies this abscess is supporting to be
Jones wrap up and I'm inclined to think
she's telling the truth but we can't
find any explanation of his business
then I'll explain it to you what
happened was just this is a special yogi
technique quite complicated but very
effective briefly it's very possible to
communicate 90 days of the state of
hypnosis of total recall the subject
himself doesn't know he knows but he
would be able to repeat verbatim if he
was again hypnotized to the same extent
but do you mean let's have war Jones
precisely you're well it's clear Ward
used Yasuko as a human electronic brain
a sort of impregnable safe to keep his
secrets in go go go hey that you know
how to open of course I'm sorry but I
can't help you I'll be too busy for the
next few days why doctor all you have to
do is to walk around Monte Carlo for the
next few days and so the police decide
to let you go and returned out and if I
help you out you'll get me out is that
what you mean freedom always has a price
tag attached to it Oh
oh I guess we're early his I hate that
suit well he's had it poor guy I've
never seen a knife like that before one
side the scalar and Hillary for any
clues he died listening to rush only 112
put it in a projector right away he then
had time to get a photo the pocket-sized
machine that goes ping this is the GAF
murder viewmaster sister chuck yeager
that flower actually tastes pretty good
pictures lucky craft off and it's
trametes Thanatos one of the most
powerful gangs in the world they beat me
up when I was a kid so they're mixed up
in this then what kind of a hospital a
running here this has been a little
pretty silly really better being Sean in
a spy movie is starting to sag and Ed
Asner is there looks like the bigfoot
video same stride the Alps are beautiful
but dumb
from the street this place looks really
small but from the back it's huge oh
good god I'm ugly scared my own children
out of the nursery today
I've decided we're entering from
schlotzsky's standing in front of a
trumpet below we're ordering lunch what
do you want excuse me I'm three minutes
late that's okay we're a pretty loose
group nice head
he's three minutes late
gentlemen start your engines operation
black man will Bailey is drawing to a
close it's been a lot of fun for all of
us to carry you through successful it
suddenly they control the world's gold
reserves requires on poultry discipline
ups plunge for me sir here represent the
gold reserves of the six wealthiest
nations of the world and your respective
duties are waiting for it to lure these
six powers into our trap you realize
gentlemen I'm binding that this is the
greatest financial undertaking in
history you trace the japanese girl
she's in malaga nice beanie if you mean
you want me to go with you to Spain I
can't accept the invitation but it's a
quick trip and pleasant sorry but I
won't play any spy games if you let them
snatch your sugar from under your nose
that's your fault take off the
tam-o-shanter eight a minute you come
back out now I have a cable from the
Minister of Health mr. under my orders
for a month see I like you do you like
me look Minister of Health operation
double oh girl scout I can't read that's
an older doctor it's well kiss my white
Scott is ours have time to change 7 i'll
be waiting the valve you Solari you have
a plane to catch waiting in the bomb in
the bra
I'm gonna get you I will just hanging
out in the yard have you lost anything
yes it's at third of my dress the button
came off very thoughtful bow she has
handles thank you it's very kind of you
nor any reward oh yeah can I get your
brother's autograph come on dr. you a
plane to catch one second there's a
reward I must collect hey just remember
your name is Neil Connery now getting
the plane to leave the account open
Nexus wedding people the airport that's
all below double entendre I hope I see
you again I think she's neat will say
gonna plugged in now and it sounds like
the British invasions waiting for flight
out and when you deplane in Malaga
you'll be greeted by manfred mann
we should believe you i have enough time
to beat up the band
they call it the mercy beat in five
minutes you'll be screaming for mercy
thank you to play in a penguin song
it's money buddy for over twenty penny
that's okay will you marry me the
telegram just came and I left my day
little bride Consuelo and all of the
other guess in front of the church
max I'm getting married today ha
Moneypenny oh where is your shoe co
watch me dance oh not another Bowl is in
hockey at first sight I took youporn is
it what have you lost me and my necklace
it's so sweet to see you again doctor
hey it's Bernie from room 222 to Connor
you're so very kind as usual my pleasure
I'm very kind by nature I'll remember
that hair by Jim Henson why don't you
remember it night hey who's your
favorite clown oh hey that's me doctor
sorry my husband Fang haha this Friday
on streets well this must be the
traditional call to gambling in my car
one gets mayor fatso
well it's a little drafty in the winter
but you can really stretch out
you shook up hey this isn't how we left
her with you he who withdraws the blade
is rightwise born King of England who's
been here some guy with a knife huh poor
girl she didn't have anything to do with
this but this is not yeshu co where was
no your shoe co she's a double I tell
you a good double but that's all solid
double down the line are you sure
positive I know her pretty well I've
operated on her face that means that
they used her as bait to keep us off the
track are you gonna marry me or why I
want to find the real Yasuko and still
alive I've a feeling you'd better begin
moving fast
right what have you lost this time I've
lost my lighter and my dignity do you
ever walk upright like other people
pantsuits from The Mary Tyler Moore
collection I were a lighter where would
I go oh there it is yeah huh excuse me
huh yeah oh yeah do you have a nip
cigarettes not in front of Sir Walter
Raleigh plant plant
my reward that's it
you've got gorgeous eyes you know ah do
you really like very much and i have one
o'neill this isn't right I don't think
that she's got a key on her face secret
agent John Ivan Palmer and now you will
do whatever I want and you will tell me
everything I want to know let's talk hug
you and you must obey me who sent you
here Thanatos yes lip-synch who was
there chief Edna tell nobody knows the
trouble of alien planning I don't know
do you know where they've hidden you
shook oh yes in lattes villa near malaga
just past the crossroad of marbella by a
Tom Thumb and is it heavily guarded it's
surrounded by a high-tension fence and
there's a machine gun to whether that's
heavily guarded I suppose it depends on
your definition of heavily guarded can I
get your brother's autograph you know
you've got beautiful eyes to know you've
got beautiful eyes know you've got
beautiful eyes and then of course I oh
my god well it looks like nobody in your
family is a rank amateur let me get
rearranged yeah the big this was
supposed to be my wedding tonight I'm
sorry to break up your little
tete-a-tete but we received information
that your shoe co is being held prisoner
outside grenada that's funny the
opposite direction what told you that
she told me she told me hmm no let her
go oh we might ruin everything wow what
a cigarettes
maximum tanning
the president's analyst
you know some people just can't wake up
no matter how many alarms they said
doc now looks like you got an extra game
there sacre bleu sacre bleu huh oh yeah
sacre bleu now let's go lift looking
good it's all right you can rest calm
down Martha Graham with her hair down
they've made you suffer haven't they how
can they make such a pretty girl suffer
like that I'm asking myself the same
thing you mustn't be afraid of me yeah I
have seen no Miller clear we women
understand each other don't worry here
water it's what's for dinner drink it'll
do you good your bread will be out
shortly i'll let you look at the menu
what you want from me I told you I don't
know anything I really don't know
anything why are you so obstinate I get
it from My Father we know that Warren
confided something to you it's not to
know it's that term is that true how
many times do I have to tell you I don't
know anything for how can I convince you
if you talk I shall reward you in a way
you can't even imagine I'll leave you
live with me do you smoke a princess but
I don't know anything I sweat it welcome
to Nucky hell I lovington a lot down
here is good sir I'm here they all over
to raise i feel like Gauguin and friggin
Tahiti here yeah I'm really hot are you
hot Jesus go
Charlie you're my knight in shining
armor
hey Greg heard it through the grapevine
is that darn thing going to work
operation double double oh he hall my
calculations are correct the
short-circuit should cause a return of
current capable of blowing up the turret
with the ammunition hmm anyway I got
Lulu backing me up who do you who do you
keep this is her local utility company
reminding you to call before you are
fran lebowitz need it Hansie everybody
welcome to a segment we like to call the
Shona Neal show parallel lives in which
we look at and contrast the careers of
Sean Connery and his brother Neal
Connery well star of today's moving yeah
yeah this line represents Sean's live
this one represents Neal's life give you
example Sean's acting talent is
discovered at an early age and leads to
a long and lucrative film career while
Neil's tell him for selling light bulbs
over the phone is discovered leading to
a long life of menial jobs and aimless
drifting well up here is when Sean gets
his first million-dollar royalty check
for the James Bond series while Neil
gets his first $65 unemployment check
after being laid off from the cheese
factory yeah here Sean is declared
sexiest man alive by People magazine
while Neil is declared the stinky cap
man in room 4 be by the other tenants in
its SRO hotel here sean calls the most
powerful and influential people in
Hollywood and has put through
immediately while Neil calls pizza hut
and is told that they won't deliver to
him because of bounced checks here Sean
is quoted as saying during the making of
the man who would be king I had creative
differences with director john huston
while Neil is quoted as saying my
manager at the happy chef won't let me
off for weekends what a dink man here
Sean goes to Spago's and is seated
immediately while Neil's hot plate
malfunction and burns down his shabby
furnished room so Joel what about that
point on the graph where Sean's line
actually goes lower than Neil's oh well
that was the point where Sean agreed to
do Highlander to the quickening and
ironically that's when Neil had to
comfort Sean mmm boy you know we should
remind the nice folks out there that
this is merely artistic speculation on
our part of Neil Connery's life for all
we know he's leading a prosperous happy
existence on a farm in Scotland with his
beautiful wife and adoring children
that's right tom and no matter what's
gone wrong with his life Neil can always
look in the mirror and say to himself
well at least they didn't do zardoz
right and so Neil wherever you are we
would all just like to say
went well don't you think I was wrong in
what that one ok move let the girl go if
you love your hostage let her go drop
that knife
drop it do your samples and Linda hunt
in a deadly game of cat and mouse
she's so calm her roommate just got shot
and she's so cool asad squaw Julie pig
album
and the calla lilies are raining hot
lead gamelan Hammond crew cab lon
Jeffrey heparin is the shakiest gun in
the woods
cover me Norman
the rocketeer
oh it's the only way he can talk to
women I am ward you are June ward I told
you something about Thanatos remember
what I told you about Thanatos yes
Thanatos Sally Ann Inaba clueless good
what else did I tell you go 22 bar six
two words that one two words bite me
Judy Kern wait a minute she looks like
shields and Yarnell she's a Tony girl go
on what happens in Tetuan watch bomb
take shorter ninth work in that 10 photo
blank died take up in touch the second
half the blind try again I wanna come on
Lady you are due back in the space 1999
second Joan Jett just walks in and she
takes over me
sorry it's nothing I'd hope to get here
before she talked couldn't get a cab
perhaps I could have saved you Oh was I
supposed to do that Mama pickin and I'm
a killer nice going you just killed
Sacagawea where'd you get out of your
shoe co nothing much mostly in a sort of
quote it was peda psyched as if i'm not
busy enough she spoke also of teach one
something strange the blind to die in
take one what else did she say she
wanted my brother's autograph it seems
that Thanatos isn't joking they're
planning to steal an atomic nucleus
atomic nucleus oh that's what I use on
the Iron not possible North Dakota
before the apocalypse Wow
da-da-da-da-da-da consider Northern
Illinois University
atomic nucleus and only a jeep for an
escort hey we're from a bride's does a
road show why Matthew were to her to
miss kitty no they can hit 60 in breech
births tailhook takes it on the road a
few good men meet a few Nocti women it's
a man's life in the new modern army our
partridge family van broke down she
looks like an oil fire yeah then you can
tan it's the busa dark van no they're
just gonna tag them and check them for
parasites
camera camera I'll see gays in the
military right there hi gals wind is a
sec start then Felina good hi don't
sleep good morning now just what are
these women trying to liberate All Right
girls get out of those clothes hmm where
angels go trouble follows oh she could
be a candidate for big bird definitely
very my dress at Wounded Knee now let's
get to work on the truck we gotta hit
llop use place so the composer's
whistling animal am i tripping Joel
and Las Vegas was born they keep busy
doleful you want to help out here Susan
tonight the dirty doesn't meets plan
skis beauties she's like the seductress
polecat had other things on her mind
they're setting up a goonie call
terrorists were more fun back then this
is even better than mission impossible
when they take a street in LA and make
it look like Belgium its Big Al Hirt
Pete found Martinez all out of this see
who the hell was that gentlemen I prefer
blondes with his usual brilliance and
imagination carrot top they tie a secure
the atomic nucleus we need yes I did the
dumbest in a position to continue with
our plans they told Alex play deal the
experiments our technicians are being
carrying out dressed as showgirl over
the past few weeks thanks for the
marvelous introduction Irv I'll take it
from here gentlemen I shall start by
saying these are all just small-scale
experiments these are all just
small-scale experiments of causes but
now with this powerful material is our
disposal we are at last able to generate
ultra-high frequencies heap and to
direct the magnetic wave to at least a
third of the globe all metals will be
instantly affected animals will be bred
in small degree will fuse solidly
chilitos will be half all dynamos than
most ships planes guns tanks on alerts
everything mechanical must be so a
useless lump of metal or important
from high atop the topkapi palace in
downtown Istanbul it's Fred Waring in
his orchestra battle may drop later
remaining monkey brains have been
reduced to a dollar 19 are nice digs
Austin's then where's the guy with the
pickled eggs
take it to the Red Room one more time
you look like Electra woman and Dyna
girl I guess I'm coming here up
arthur rubinstein and sammy cahn walking
arm-in-arm doctor how nice to see you
again thank you one second you're
dressed as a space angel why how lucky
Maya ask you to come I was going to get
in touch for you to arrange a meeting
could you feel this bump on my head as
they return game I had no idea you were
so interested in archery no I'm not it's
your services as a plastic surgeon I'm
interested in hmm why would you like to
have your features change me oh no I'm
quite satisfied with my face and with my
nose also although i do weathervane in
high winds it's for a friend he wants to
become the exact double of another man
Bob Eubanks but for the time being
there's no need for you to understand
and of course you don't you can state
your own price welch's for me it's not a
matter of money it's primarily a matter
of principle although I'm a little odd
name will come to an agreement you'll
see we'll have time to talk about it I
lost my pockets Bobbie Gentry is so good
to see you again
I don't know who invited him will you
excuse me for a minute I won't be long
I've been advised and look with decline
show so many beautiful girls round you
won't get bored no no you're right it's
women are just all over me I mean I got
no problem
rocky mountain oysters thank you no
thank you do you have any snackage type
foods here summer sausage two aspects
maybe a little raw tease it well what
have you done not very much it's
difficult there are afraid of alpha
idiots maybe they're right after all
alpha is powerful you've got a good
bench come in
there's a message from the yacht it's
very urgent right well she hurts just
take off that ridiculous getup and it's
sign yacht it yeah huh it's from alpha
he's having a good time he's set today
he wants me to join him immediately
we're to be married timing it'll be the
last time he gives me in order hmm i'll
destroy him and i'll be the head of
fanaticism is key it's not for me what
about the girls there may be dangerous
witnesses as soon as the operation is
over the yacht will blow up remember
folks he can read lips he is reading
lips right now the girls aboard yes yes
I ought to it's inevitable a German the
yellow frog what bozo the piano chive I
used to be good at this there must be no
witnesses only you will share my secret
you know that you can trust me huh now
let's go inside and see if we can
convince and remember to have fun
Marla maples
dr. Martha Smith thank you from your
meditation coincidence I was just
thinking of you I'm flattered that looks
like your tomato aspic got away from her
Maya there's a bigger guys in danger in
serious danger are you threatening me no
certainly not but i have just overheard
a conversation between your mr. Thayer
yes I've seen few villas as beautiful as
this one it's quite splendid natural
lips my people
Oh Donald Senor Mendoza Jesse Norman
wants her kaftan back you're not going
are you I was hoping to play a hand of
sham and affair with you hmm I don't
gamble mr. Thayer I only bail on winning
horses that's why you should stay
northern Laird's getting cheesed I have
an important announcement to make I'll
brumac Lana me out there I thought you
had the voting majority as far as I'm
concerned this meeting never happened
miss Drummond leave things as they are I
shouldn't advise that I'm sorry Colin I
want to know whether you are with me or
what alpha or with child I won't you be
careful how you answer the Beatles oh
you can put yourselves in a dangerous
spot under my captain's a lot more
dangerous to listen to you who in a few
days alpha will be dead Criswell
predicts don't go down but no one will
know except us within hours I'll have an
exact double for alpha neat huh
everything will go on as if nothing
happened nothing has happen mmm but with
this difference your hair can have more
body and shine the new welfare will be
my man well my man I love him so try to
blow up soon maybe even tomorrow with
you one board uh you're kind of hard to
dance with you read too many novels by
Fleming Jerry Fleming Ian's brother I
assure you it's true your life is in
grave danger I'm that bad at answering
haha serious I'll keep everything under
control somehow with my control top
pantyhose but seriously if my
information is right you'll be indebted
to me it sounds like Hercules
anyway why does mr. Thayer hire only
blind people in his rug factory wait I
know this one I hi Largo I don't know
I've never been in there only blind
people are allowed to go inside and I'm
blonde but seriously I can excuse me I
have to go talk to an interesting person
she seems nice enough
shrewd of how to bring me back some
three-bean salad basket bloat hmm I
should get me one of those it's red
october i shine I mean I could have
gotten a ride on that I didn't want to
you've installed a screen door sir how'd
you get this thing out of reverse this
man could win five thousand dollars that
he could shut up
depends Roger might go down to you
haha yah whoa brother to see your land I
hope you can read Braille lips you're
new here
pookie and they say a Lou Reed shall
guide them casting call for name of the
rose it's the boys in the woods spicy
you know I bet dolphin temp has a hard
time filling these positions Bruno Bruno
all right you win they're all blind Dick
Enberg here
hold on to each other by the shoulder
and come with me well it felt like
shoulder so any of you sure play a mean
pinball wait a minute it's the blind
leading the blind leading the blind
weaving blind oh yeah I'm blind yeah
blind listen a lot and you shall hear
hear you will weave rugs don't worry
it's a simple easy job you'll get your
food and your family will get your pair
there's a Coke machine in the baltic
room of you will be placed at ilume and
will begin with an easy task the little
good will you will learn quickly now get
to work we will start with a hot pad
holder first wait a minute he's
infiltrated a quilting bee Goodwill
Industries now it can be told somebody
heard him looking
SI you know ironically Connery wears a
rug who's the sign for that must be
where they make the nuclear power drugs
ah
hmm shut the door I do believe I'm
developing pictures of rugs in you ha
tell Baltimore ha tell Baltimore ha tell
Baltimore would you please stop tapping
like that you know a buffet would never
work in this place are you Hank not
smell like Hank this is like soap woody
only in a rug factory silkworm yeah you
got some marmalade on your hand you're
working with radioactive material if
okay but is it that you mean by that
sometimes I take you want me to fail you
are working with radioactive materials
do you understand yeah well I get paid
two dollars more an hour they're trying
two murders that is why we have a source
we must go Neil's a skilled rabble
rouser
that's not the door that's the war
I'm staying I need the money pressures
down there
it's gonna take you the police fight
partner in the National Guard to get me
out of here
hey this is kind of fun
you know this must be five o'clock on a
Friday you wanted to win we're telling
me can't you tell I am fragile
everybody be sure to sign Vicky's
birthday card before you leave show
won't be here on Monday no looks like
casual day backfired maui this pony all
right let him go Oh heels just a little
to Damascus and wham-o look at me
wearing a Braille jack cummings pretty
good huh can I look in a visit bad touch
your Arabic is quite good are the dates
from the time of the Crusades dr.
Congress oh I could never fool you give
me a hug
is it nice to know there goes
ladies and gentlemen Maynard Ferguson in
the centennial senior high school gym
Bobbi Jo get back here you're an
extraordinary man doctor I know let me
show you my time life lively imaginative
and resourceful my sons of humor too
it's too bad you prefer to play on the
opposing team too bad from your point of
view who yes but it is my point of view
that counts know you are but what am i
if you've done me the small favor I ask
dear marketing by now there would have
been more chip dip no such complications
as these now you'll have to operate
anywhere under less favorable
circumstances you understand well what
else can I do again oh it's a new car
well neat where's the bar here is your
patient doctor doctor patient patient
doctor everything's ready for you I want
to be generous so here's a quarter in
return for your services get you rub my
tummy your life you come a long way baby
to get where you got to you today can I
borrow your mini skirt for the party
leader because I've got to warn them
I've just learned that we're going to
have to fight for our lives there's
decided to blow up the yacht with all of
us aboard come on that's a bad thing
right if it stops so will your look I
just came in for a haircut really just a
little off the sides oh hey how are we
today good good uh-huh looking good
how's that little prostate problem you
all right you can go and we have the
night canopy please you know I think
that operating room clashes with the
college just relax they were tired you
want to risk hmm that's right relax you
have nothing to fear we're going to
enter your nostril good Steve Austin
relax
that's a classless a couple of talks he
could be Roy Thinnes where was your
chest on the night of the 23rd oh he
typed that speaker from a drive-in ago
as soon as Connery is completed the
operation you'll get new sweater in
eliminating hi it's Toni Basil who the
lust boat boy women have really broken
through the glass ceiling in this movie
yeah but there's a guy looking up
through it women can love widow Callan
without moi it's closing time at hooters
oh he deserved that still it was worth a
rule olay now you will follow my
instructions sit stay you won't have a
moment of peace till it's all finished
can you even die my eyes to match my
doll any old time let's see here that
you haven't been flossing know how do
you like your martini shaken or stirred
I'm taking the president's nose now go I
love you dammit
police squad in color think this John
Entwistle oh good too
boo-boo Danny let's settle this in court
we watch out for the model ship an
actual Donnybrook in Easy Spirit pumps
it's the wackiest ship in the Navy went
up with people goes bad that was a real
capezio kick
someone's a fight
enter the chiropractic
chocolate
stop this thing right now I violate some
rules
I woke up you weren't there I hate that
watch out for the model
fell right into a bob fosse routine mrs.
partridge look out
no this is a one-seater Homer until a
blue were where the action is or
hootenanny happening 60 yeah if Sam
Peckinpah directed the boat Nix
what he's wearing a line as sure it's no
reason to hit him if there's no one to
these little blue guys Andy's well
that's a cute top Cindy where'd you get
it
with that is one figure-hugging
turtleneck
oh poopie
licorice oh oh great now the boats
sinking finally got used to this wait a
minute he's becoming part of his own
entertainment center excuse me pardon me
coming through excuse me off broken out
oh hi oh oh excuse me pardon me oh I'm
sorry oh hi Betty oh excuse me pardon me
and as delco shows his true colors of
yellow and flees the calypso and as we
left the clam flowers that day stop
tight yeah let's see a hypnotized him
from here mr. cool he's heading there we
can't worry about that right now we got
to find Thanatos headquarters now the
radioactive rugs were made at the
factory where were they said I really
never knew that but once I heard
something about a place near Munich
no no no Mon just let me try to
hypnotize you crow like Fort Knox look
you can't make me you can't make me you
can't make me what up ha Joel so sorry
to interrupt your little skit but Frank
would like to do a number i was a little
hard on him during the invention
exchange so here's our own TVs Frank
accompanying himself on the accordion
with the haunting beer barrel polka two
and one two three four that's rather
nice not really a poker 40 march three
familiar your guard the mister tibbs
that you ordered sir oh thank you just
put them on that you what did then you
either pair I specifically ordered a
diet squirt I'm so sorry gentle men um
make it right no no no Frank have the
mr. Pibb you can have the mr. Pibb this
time no my doctor says I can't have mr.
Pibb Frank I'm your doctor and I say
have them mr. Pibb hey master wanted you
to have these coupons for for our veggie
feast he wanted you to have them but I'm
giving them to you there thank you thank
you very much i have to thank you thank
you yes have a nice day I was thank you
goodbye oh um may I use your bathroom
they're on the left all right let's land
the directional r elevator indicates
that's the spot
Oh high on a hill let the lonely
goatherd so you might want to take an
alternate route this afternoon this
place is crawling with Chad can hmm
hey maybe you should land before you get
out oh honey you got your keys your keys
she's new oh
oh this feels great pleather is really
something I'm beginning the countdown
countdown knock it off Trevor good in 20
seconds the warning signal country
whoopee it's concrete he's found the
secret entrance such a curious man I'll
satisfy his curiosity heading in
double-double and silver design turn it
off sir someone's doing a drunk test
outside I'm gonna shut you down till
about 20 okay Trevor Trevor Connery's
now in the tunnel oh that's the outer
limits I'm not going in the tunnel oh I
am in the tunnel how do they reach down
here I put that thing away right there
well she's not the only smooth one
that's for stealin my naugahyde couch
Maya you better call London eating over
the vibrators vibrators incident yeah
you can't say that anyone so how come
everybody's got Count Basie following
Heidi's grown up
what
oh the back stab of stabbers thank you
Ron Popeil
what would my brother do
well that must be the fine arts building
so I guess nobody's going to notice the
guy in the tan suede ranch jacket are
they
sun ra's BAM I leave me alone
airwolf meets dr. Zhivago
but should we be moving or something Oh
giggle okay everybody when that lady
gets off the helicopter check out her
pants it doesn't move Jesus Murphy
wait can I get help for crying out
where's the valet forget it hello mrs.
pants that mean shoot me an espresso
please it's terribly urgent London in
England how do you expect to do that
telephone please help me it's a matter
of life or death you can try I don't
know if you'll get through well there's
Waldo whoa 31 30 seconds magnetic
intensity at concentration level Thank
You Charles Aznavour me when he pawed
netic wave ready to function just an
elaborate close sorry hello London
extension 142 I want to speak with
commander Cunningham immediately it's
terribly urgent never mind Who I am
hurry five bottles beer and four bottles
of beer in the wall free to the castle
hill lonely goatherd but our Father
Munich one singular sensation the
headquarters are 20 miles per wha ha ha
hello hello I don't know why you say
goodbye say hello we've been cut up well
I'm not calling her back I'm wondering
what are the simple folk do
you
whatever will they stood to my underwire
bra that does it now where did I park we
smooth go get it boy you know those
slacks hurt me then you say but people
the cloud so mr. bonds brother I'm happy
to have you as my guest again oh I'll
show you how the operation works on our
anti-magnetic you could fit more you
give me a neat don't you think and
that's the last favor I can do you I
only allowed you to live because I
wanted you to witness my success I've
got what I wanted without your help yeah
take him away i think i'm supposed to
have some snappy comeback
no further keep going don't look at me
like that suddenly it's the brothers
freaking terawatts off the magnetic wave
is blocked it on to you a champion aceh
to know sorry about that I'm a pretty
good fighter though and I guess that can
be useful to an it
their cars broke their horses will poop
on the parking lot
but they outlawed night oh you guys look
really stupid plastic pants plastic
pants
Jim Cooper's gun
oh boy another staredown with neil oh go
mental Rick what's wrong with you
there's my philips screwdriver
duty to do
a wheel young or we go
which they'd stop pretending this is
exciting
looks just like a YouTube video under a
blood meal connery you should be able to
get him all my pants my hands oh what a
time for a fire drill
ah co that alligator skin hat helps you
now huh
come on girls they hurt buddy
mummy Jolson
wait does not know I'm now taking me oh
I got it now where you going to try to
blow up the tower poet take this my
grandma gave it to me it's an anti
magnetic thing can i set the dial show
you good we'll cover you okay i won't
meet you there
good sailor fuck brigade Oh throw right
on it ooh again
Burke Burke Burke Burke Michael later
room trade ya oh
the archer must be on this case the
arches these everybody gets a turn here
huh encore mommy mr. Belvedere better
Park the hard drive here let's take this
is your last chance for a witty remark
at your own game doctor that's a perfect
setup for witty remark come on I mean
come on doctor it's no good if you don't
retort can be anything to be about my
nose or my stupid alligator suit
anything hey that's not fair these are
soggy in this search oh okay use the
stunt bad
you know guys I think this is about more
than just magnetizing and this goes much
deeper stop margot what guys yep
hey somebody punched the Foley guy okay
okay take back everything you ever said
about me oh man my Moyes totie Fields
was never this moist haha prepare to
meet collies brother near he'll go fight
at the ok corral I'm gonna do it
you know he's gonna need a vinyl patch
kit yep
how are these guys still at it great
they're beating up LeBeau you know for
some reason I like to fight on the boat
better you feel
haver
hey everybody there's a party going down
before the tower blows up well oh oh and
I forgot to tell you earlier that
there's a tower that's going to blow up
in this
oh I just got it that's the tower that's
gonna blow up didn't tell us about quick
we gonna die we're really not that far
away
he Brigadoon compound exploded today
Jana and Meg escaped unharmed
unfortunately bonnie jean has died
kinda like watching bonanza in Reverse
that must be the Thunder ball I heard
them talk about hey relax we won your
hot head okay Connery okay you were
fantastic you even meet my best agents
look like beginners oh I shouldn't think
so commander I was lucky that no you're
too modest you should have seen your
brother's face doctor when he had it
settled back with a smooth ride info you
happen to have a few days free I'm just
thinking I'd be happy to have you back
in the reserves with the rank of meat if
I wasn't so Placid right now he would
as church Stevens a good sleeper wait
you watch Major Nelson what was I say
that you have to return to London
immediately isn't that right commander
boom it works on my brain tumor this is
summer yes of course i miss return
immediately add i will say this loud
singer i am mrs. Norman Maine yeah this
is the part my brother told me about
nope I guess I should take my own life
if
Yeah right the Angel of Death
high-powered rifle emulated crossfire
we're having fun at his expense it's fun
mm-hmm ready girls let's go you probably
hypnotized through no liking it yeah I
should think that life would lose a lot
of its if it fell yet ultimately one to
do Sean Connery's brother won't be back
again in anything
I guess so what's that how do you
suppose this happen we're stuck to the
war crime in a leak at oh are you guys
stuck to the wall yeah we're immobilized
we're stock oh I bet I know whose idea
this was sirs was this your idea huh hmm
why do all I you got me nolo contendere
I saw the movie remembered I had my old
magnetizer these things are great gotta
admit it's pretty funny i'm stuck in a
wall it's no use Jolin ain't gonna work
I'm stock oh oh no wait give it rocking
number nine very funny sirs but I'll you
know that you're probably interrupting
at your goblin that don't tell
communication yeah who wouldn't want to
do that don't worry will demagnetize you
guys later hahahahaha black eyed mine
hair whoa Lindsey I'll each it how about
a recall an hour
until next time Joel off Peter Zane
thank you