the world few things in her purse and in
Moroccan chickens in mall across
I can't do yourself it's just a show
just relax for Mystery Science Theater
hey everyone welcome to the satellite of
love you know since we are stuck in
orbit over ancient Rome I thought it
might be a good time to teach the bots a
little something about history Mike this
encyclopedia is worthless for my
biography of rolling gift yeah Mike it's
really old it lists Hitler is a fairly
stable veteran of the Great War come on
they're not that old they're fine oh
yeah it mentions the light bulb is a
charming theory and Congress is spelt
with an F what is it Congress localized
when I was a kid well they seemed fine
then the periodic table has three
elements in it Mike there's a volume for
the letter epsilon as a mailing address
for Machu Picchu it's got a picture of
Stonehenge so under construction yeah
well so what you high-minded
encyclopedia snobs are trying to tell me
is you want a new set I'll get you to
set anything that's not a handwritten on
papyrus will do that's very funny we'll
be right back you know they got me
through college you never finished
college Mike oh yes
I mean look someday we hope to harness
fire to serve man not simply terrorize
him with horrifying random yeah and
here's a whole section on out deadly
foes the dinosaurs okay your belly acres
got you a brand spanking new set of
encyclopedias each page with an internet
up lick so you can constantly update
them man this is incredibly up to date
Wow 27 pages on Gwen Stefani alone well
I think I have more than answered your
encyclopedia grievances no it was much
more fun to complain about the old ones
and they have new ones yeah I miss
complaining already quickly so I gotta
check in on that planet down there that
down there you know Thank You Maximus oh
hi Mike well this whole Roman thing has
taken a turn for the crappy Flay via
here discovered we weren't God's and all
and had us thrown into this slimy
dungeon and they're being pretty rough
on pale face here they took away his
brain which sucks for him I like fruit
fruit is good talk here sit 10 do you
plot against all beloved Emperor I
please I can't stand it anymore Bob oh
man they are totally torturing him right
now I mean it's bad Mike you guys should
probably write to Amnesty International
House of Pancakes or whatever wow I
broke a nail Oh talk smelly figure God
don't say anything you watch just give
me some of that yummy mutton look Oh
does it say I don't care if it's safe it
smells delicious montes reworks fool Oh
camper is about to give his violin
recital upstairs ma'am right listen I
must go but I'll be back and yeah you
three will be like so tortured it's like
me not even funny yeah
so Mike here's the deal if you help us
out of this one I promise I'll let you
and your little windup toys go and
you'll never have to watch another lousy
movie again yo more coming movie let's
do it do it do do do they say hey I
don't know pearl I mean you've lied to
us before I know but but it wasn't my
fault in a way that I haven't quite
figured out yet but this time for real I
mean how are you gonna get out of this
stupid he's stinky Roman time without us
anyway she's right Mike I don't want to
have to see you in a toga no no okay
what do you want me to do oh yeah I need
you to come down here and get grain guys
brain Boris they put it too far out of
range so he's at quarter power which
means he's even more of an idiot than
usual pearl told me about the rabbits
again please and pathetic as it is he's
our only hope so I'm gonna have him
bring you down here to fetch it okay
brain guy send Mike down send Mike down
okay go do you I'm allergic mmm not
goose down you don't bring my down her
Mike everyone says you're ugly and dumb
and no one likes you what they do really
real man that really oh man it really
brought me down yeah Mike listen you
empty-headed albino I said bring Mike
down here okay nice lady oh hi nobody
doing here I wish I said a 401 K
planning meeting oh by the way my name's
Mike down I'm a CPA
oh this might take a minute Mike in the
meantime why don't you enjoy your final
bad movie ever I promise it's a real
piece of cheese called space mutiny hey
brain low think you can manage sending a
movie okay should I stop my overhead
projector now you pipe down movie you're
like fearsome 80 gypsy like amazingly
idiotic productions a Jonathan winters
Billie Holiday production
oh good hands 20 exclusive hits by the
original artists it sounds like someone
owns himself a dx7 keyboard huh whoa
whoa watch out watch out I have my
doubts that this movie is starring
anyone it's just the usual stable of
David winters actors yay oh no wait oh
because she's Cameron Mitchell's label
his nickname is tiny featuring music
normally heard at the Days Inn lounge in
Columbia Heights passed from editor to
editor in a desperate attempt to save it
there's going to be seven levels of hell
in this movie too dad big favor can you
associate produce beans hope John and
holiday de Kock and completely botched
by David winters outlets in space 13
generations ago our overpopulated world
built the Southern Sun did a
self-sufficient spaceship that would be
home to thousands of migrants would
attend like your journey to a new and
uncolonized world cool huh our current
descendants have come to accept the
Southern Sun as their home and work for
a better future for their children
they're known as dupes while most of the
inhabitants of this generation are
content there are some with grown
restless and impatient too i Pat Reilly
here for instance
where the hell did I put that old ping
pong table and this feeling and being
followed by a lobster boy
still he's not nearly as creepy as most
meter readers it's like an armando Santa
want a big show you how to use a label
maker properly
he made a bomb out of soap and paco
rabanne attention prepare for shuttle
Lancer landing Lissa Manchester Lancer
to Southern Sun located rescue beacon
and survivors they are all female and
identified themselves as polarians we
have initiated landing procedures than
are returning to base I could watch the
stuff all day Mike you will you will
enter the Summer Sun in fig it's fun
millennium and your knowing me is 190
Roger tion lands are locked to guidance
control or dad a data lame pom-pom Fame
shuttlecraft determined to be cute sir
shuttle landing successful mullerian
survivors disembarking attention all
hands to the landing complete prepare
for incoming stingray Viper squadron to
Southern Sun in sight excuse me excuse
me attention it's all those wishing to
meet the incoming Viper squadrons
proceed to the docking bay you're going
down to the docking bay to meet your
friend from coriolis you better hurry
boy the Vipers and final protein well I
came down to check that he's on the
flight lieutenant Lemont contact the
pilot of this thing ray Viper and ask
your professor spooner is aboard I'm
insane thank you son control I have a
request do you have a professor Spooner
on board Oh stingray to sun control
affirmative for look sting Debbie
Reynolds and God my guys got another
tongue we are starting our landing
sequence
and the future geese will be
rocket-powered comments on the port
landing Bay Affairs coming up fast on
our tail sigrid sigrid 3 we are under
fire prepared for defense formation
Roger stingray new graphics by kenner
stinger i want assuming defense
formation will cover for you and the
professor what the hell's going on out
there rent-free in town I never liked
red three anyway damn it better crap
special effects by industrial light &
morons are we the good guys with a bad
game attention all hands man your battle
stations were under attack uh-oh an air
show look out below
hey I told you we should have landed at
laguardia tell me about it these briefs
i'm wearing huh so their spaceship is a
huge basement mm-hmm commander calgon
can I help you Oh God excuse me sir did
you have a reservation commander sir
what are you doing a hostess will see
you in a moment sir soul huh without a
perfectly fine bars they'd like the
lowdown no-good Sudanese nothing to
clean up a ball any faster sir I'll get
the manager calgon blow me away
since that guy inflate his pants to
attract mates good work you blew up the
septic tank
oh no I just tried to open my garage
door
morning dump our mom to rights energize
our emergency landings from there
officer it's dead I said I'm bailing
relax you're in your own room
it's a good idea for a pilot to eject in
space oh come on a minute violent
emergency beam down ejection system
activated attention all so really how
does this help the Basque separatists my
stair stepper a pilot beam down
successful medical team stand by fire
control to docking bay if the first ten
minutes are any indication this movie
it's gonna blow my buns of steel videos
are in there come on mother
oh yeah that'll take care of it remember
Carl's blonde joke what happened
lieutenant the Viper was locked with the
sun's guidance control commander we lost
power commander the Energizer mines have
been sabotage sabotage what of the
little children and their toys John
Waters headquarter Blake here give me
calgon right here go ahead sure I just
saw something I thought you should know
about some strange women came on board
with the Lancer history I'm sorry the
information is so scanty but i'll send
you up for as I get it Blake out hey
leave this the office newsletter says I
look like Susan Powter Santa's playing
freecell over here oh man what I do what
do you think David I spent 20 bucks for
Griffey I think whoever did this knows
his way around spaceships I agree I
don't know if this helps but ho ho ho
one thing's for sure we've got to reduce
speed drastically till we repair the
damage you know i'm thinking more about
the possible motive why come in oh oh
you get a computer readout on the damage
in the docking bay also the pirate
fleets position and load the file into
the computer I'd like to do some
research on our new female guests the
Valerians nude research they're ready as
soon as possible hi sup
so we got some Benedictine monks in the
floorboards unfortunately we have set
some traps with fresh bread and brandy
though lady this is your new home I know
it doesn't look like much but if you'll
bear with us I'm sure we can make you
quite comfortable leave we Valerians
wish to be alone this place will serve
our purpose leave Oh drink too much
surge rice you okay it's a pleasure
having you on board I guess gentlemen oh
and by the way ladies there's a ferret
cage by the wall if you need it
well I polished the back corridor anyone
else need their room done
hey you guys he got my dad's enforcer
for the weekend well we have fun huh I
can you help me out of this thing our
timing was perfect two for the price of
one we had a coupon who'd have thought
the one small spacecraft Robbie
Robertson could have done that much
damage that Vipers missile pod took out
the entire wenching system for the
docking bay doors man you should've been
there according to the damage report see
from the chief maintenance engineer
it'll take at least two weeks before the
doc you made to be used again I know
yeah that means the Southern Sun is
completely personated nobody can enter
her and more important nobody can leave
her excellent they no longer have a
choice oh god you look good hmm it was
cruel fate to be born in space but I
have vowed we will not die here it is my
destiny to set my feet upon a real world
to accumulate wealth and power beyond
our wildest dreams I have offered the
people in the Sun Sun rich new life
that's good and now they have no
alternative but to accept my generosity
and alter course for Corona borealis
don't you love it you know we're always
laughing you in me it's okay dad boy
what's the report from damage control
it's not complete yet captain but the
first reports indicate but two of our LM
5,000 excellent drive motors have been
sabotage boy this also affects the
performance of one of our Vic's impulse
Drive generators oi give me a computer
readout on our hosts respect sir
neuspeed by two-thirds shut down two of
our booster engines yes sir oh one other
thing boy you said we should with your
contact with a docking bay uh one of the
missiles from the Viper took out the
video control tower down there but we
are trying to re-establish contact with
a Sarah video robot did you sign Shari's
birthday card we've been in space too
long let us land the ship where we can
do it we have the power it's true we
have the power to do this shit but this
would directly oppose the law of the
universe the lure of the galaxy yet
forget the law no no the law must be
upheld we cannot break it Oh gentlemen
it seems that we are not all in
agreement I disagree engineer parson
seems content to spend his remaining
years upon the Southern Sun and let him
do so alone yeah this is mutiny this is
treason which I warn you I must report I
just have to wet myself first will you
allow him to spoil your ambitions for a
greater future Wow easily led thighs
counsel what I meant was I totally
endorse what you're doing rip his band
uniform then you'll have to pay for it
next they're gonna give him book so they
can dump them okay
death by snicker-snack can inflate him
to 35 pounds
okay then moving on to number three on
our agenda Shari's birthday pop are
there any other of you that wish to
confuse freedom with treason I'd like to
confuse bok choy with cabbage sir report
to the enforcers bridge your forehead oh
yeah well it is the rare meeting where
something actually got done hmm district
sir you have done well alone at last
oh hell chef normal red norvo this is
Goldilocks nighter up coming in second
prepare to die oh yeah we'll cold gets
all whoa servo what the hell Michigan is
going on I can't talk now Mike I'm
locked in a death struggle with servo
yeah me too Mike holy with crow cambot
give me rocket number nine will ya each
step servo the funky crunchy chocolaty
cocoa death Oh enjoy a nice serving of
brown Betty with death but mostly eat
death row servo you guys be careful out
there oh we won't Oh Oh terrible you
just ripped a hole in my toys oh we oh
ah too late for me hehe i took a laser
blaster the dome whoa fellas well shall
we order these babies in after you
thermo
Oh serve all you you guys okay fellows
okay now this isn't funny anymore okay
I'll lighten up Nelson were robots
member man that was great yeah so
where'd you get the spaceship oh you
mean the hyperwarp escape shuttles which
we just trashed yeah I've been down the
hold waiting for us to use them to
escape and stuff like that oh I see such
don't you think we maybe should have
used the forest gate purposes what's he
on about oh you mean escape from here oh
jeez how stupid of us man why is my face
red I'm sorry bud we had escape pods we
didn't you wait wait wait listen they're
just one more oh yeah gypsies got it out
she'll be along any second now 10 all
right go for a chance thank you oh sorry
my Scott Bieber's babe right shall we do
it this is sudden Oh Jenna sir please
file this certain sir thank you you know
where I can get some Zubaz man commander
Jansen well welcome aboard mr. Ryder
you've met our captain Peary's sit down
son thank you sir why do but I had your
space and Status car please thank you
sorry it's so moist you've got mail
well there we have it any questions mr.
Ryder sir I'd like to see a video of the
crash if I'm a good idea come this way
I'll show you where my elves are working
day and night at your chair and Ram it
lieutenant yes sir did you punch up a
video of the crash please yes sir on our
computer disaster analysis guidance
system engaged you are now on the
Southern Sun gun control system over
pilot control release warning critical
power loss now switch live to spencer's
gifts hey macarena hey it's a Wicca
Tupperware party
Steve called my poultice we've got this
itch right I meant like there look
familiar MA what am I saying no way
damn Swedish ergonomic chairs how do you
sit comfortably on these time I get a
bunch of women together it's either
witchery or a wedding shower that's what
I say Mother Angelica aerobics I heard
that
no I better get the phone you guys you
receive your message I'm glad you've
come you've been waiting for you hey you
the Valerians are off-limits you've
never heard of the getting some flaws
well there we are gentlemen tell me Dave
slab bulkhead your Viper was equipped
with a new high density the atomizer
escape system right yes commander right
now it only works over very short
distances but who knows what the future
potential of it could be what about the
professor what's his mad commander I'm
sorry about the professor there's
nothing I could have done the system's
only hooked up to the Viper pilots don't
blame yourself son it's not your fault
you're a chunk head you're lucky you're
alive like you saved yourself I can't
breathe ah Leah you had us all worried
please next time there's a fire leave it
to damage control you ok ok next time
young lady you stay out of the way dad I
was there the pilot chickened out
otherwise Spooner would be alive right
now David rider won't you beat my
daughter Leah we're about the same age
professor never had a chance there's
nothing I could have done to prevent it
oh so you left the dial Leah stop it he
ejected and he's alive listen lady
doctor doctor doctor lady I don't have
to justify my actions to you but since
you're asking that explosion cut the
power and there wasn't time to grow legs
or a backup system I had to eject I had
no other choice that's dr. I had no
other choice commander captain excuse me
I have to file my report coach will
totally ream me if I don't file my
report
Lea you're getting a lump of coal I like
playing with the knobs all you can eat
me tonight excuse me sir I think you'll
find this interesting yes what is it
it's an inventory of all the explosives
under our control hmm hey one of the new
monkeys Oh gopher are you lost he's
calling to check on his gender uh give
me an audio video linkup bridge to
console seven please hurry there's
something come through on the voice
monitor from the engine room area put it
through on five the electrolysis is
working those Formica monitors don't
have a lot of resolution my name is
Flight Lieutenant Lemont well according
to my printout from the supply stores
inventory we're definitely short
unconventional ballistic explosive check
somebody would direct online access to
central has been transferring a large
amount of explosive event simply
covering the requisition I wouldn't have
found out about it unless central asked
me to confirm acceptance of a hundred
units of chemo plastic and atomic
continent I mean that's crazy can you
imagine that amount of extreme flying
around the ship's engine come on skull
fuck out of my skin I think I'm tres Tew
it is when the hell is he talking to me
put it through the bridge I want to
speak to somebody from a man that excuse
me al Lewis for the sake of security I
think it would be better if you came up
here and asked for me lieutenant Lemont
send a couple of men over there to stop
that engineer before he gets to the
bridge unless I get to him first I time
me yeah
look well I think I just have to report
this I mean I really thought about it i
think i really have to report this
everything you need to report it Herbie
the misfit elf it's like Billie Jean
King no snowmobilers I've seen this
before compulsory splat ball you know if
we pretend we know what's going on this
is actually kind of exciting eyes above
the stage now he's gonna fall right in
at the end of the Opera in this basement
make the spaceship kind of bottom heavy
see I can throw my laugh
why give me your bio notes r I'll get
addy come on man third engineer Steve
Goodell known as stinky to his friends
you have two choices soup or mouth join
me or the deep freeze I prefer to jump
calgon by the way calgon we need more of
you a guest know the death of Rick
Springfield I just wish I have jesse's
girl oh we had a mouthful of starburst
well known ET keyed him a nice they have
the best mini golf in the galaxy one of
those she raising recycling bins all
right can I get a spot got a nice place
here yeah bite my nice place listen up I
understand how you feel it's dr. listen
I understand how you feel yeah how could
you know how I feel listen lady I did
what I had to do what you think I
realized the good man died a man I
respected in love hey I don't need this
wait they missed a couple of lines here
it wasn't a way that you knew him what
difference does it make he's dead and
there's nothing we can do about it now
married to an entertainment lawyer in
Sherman Oaks forget it I don't need it
whose is like when I plateaued on my
dealt me she's a sexy senior citizen
shake it Ralph Macchio my ebay you were
really into the Thompson Twins right now
you were weighing chun-ying all over the
place huh huh uh you know I hate it when
the chaperones start dancing with the
kids so in the future there's absolutely
no shame oh my pantyhose are itchy
pantyhose are itchy itchy itchy Shari
Lewis has got it going on oh mama oh no
without metric Elvis would not be
possible yeah rather they get a table
dance from trent lott what is she
thinking I'm a weightlifter come on this
is less subtle than an Annie sprinkle
performance piece oh she's presenting
like a man drill no two-for-one techno
drinks cool did you see my butt I don't
need this it's a woman allowed to buy a
man drink in your Galaxy good guess it's
okay I had to find a man now doesn't
what Oh what or not you want to accept
wow it's like Nick and Nora Charles
you're still angry checking good yeah
but I'll get over you know the professor
taught me everything I know it took him
20 seconds let me start again
yeah why not I made a mess with the
first time they write it we r jansson
blank media person can I came here
that's not bad bennigan's 1985 I should
show my butt to that guy what's that I
know that woman over there she works on
the bridge she's got an awesome package
I never noticed that before she finished
out was there any reason for I don't
know looks like she's been arrested
she's walking with two Mexican wrestlers
let's go check it out it's gotta be
better than this the dancing has gotten
even whiter she's got Normandy low down
her trousers Flight Lieutenant Lemont
yes did you assign Sherry's card thank
you gentlemen you were speaking with
third engineer Steve Goodell that is my
business but now I'm making it mine no
I've always liked the vanilla sport
shakes better and it's just beneath
tell my wife I love her well yeah
sometimes I pass out when I do a
military after a bench there they go
hervé Villechaize his death car mistake
this fridge large meets on to speed
chunk much dead lift
you can walk on your hands and catch up
to the guy put your helmet on we'll be
reaching speeds of three get the siren
oh let's see what this lark can do
we need both horse powers on this thing
now this is a fool
can't go any faster I'd have to drop the
waxing compound put the top up put the
top up
doo doo doo dah dah dah dah it's all I
want to say to you hey hey she's dead
she died Wow sure I think it's very nice
of you to give that dead woman another
chance your report sir so your doers d
and comportment you really believe sir
that this act of sabotage is good
something to do with our navigation of
course yeah I'm convinced give this
proves out I think they want to drive us
into the neighboring constellation Oh
Becca I love that phone the consolation
of the corona borealis pirate territory
precisely so we have to find out who's
behind this peenya dis comin yes you
know captain I have a whole colony of
people living in my beard it's always
very dangerous to speculate isn't so it
would have to be somebody on this ship
brilliance gain by this stand to gain
that leaves us with what exactly squad
sir that flak master the enforcer
waitress wait she never sees me I just
very perilous for everyone on board no
we do not make wild accusations so we
keep this top classified secret top
super duper maxi extreme ultra secret
check okay look alive everybody hold
sorry Susan it's me your dad I just did
get off the Stairmaster bold big flank
splint chest hair it's Kevorkian
yes can I help you yes you can we're
looking for the enforcers headquarters
here we are really is awfully lonely
here can I show you one but I was just
about to do the Monster Mash let's see
what I forget to hide before they came
in here yeah mon let's get the hell out
of here wait this looks interesting here
at the underpants testing ground so well
these guys died lost all their muscle
mass man what would you care for a spot
of tea because doing so would be very
ironic well not for a bit of a hurry so
we'll take it to go what are all these
bodies for a personal collection
collection yes when anyone is under
suspicion we were immediately arrested
tortured and give them a truth hug me
when Calvin is convinced from no longer
use he simply has them ejected into
space boom boom boom however if they
seem redeemable Caliban pleases oh do
they keep well that means all the
enforcers are corrupt and Calvin's
running his own personal army here
that's great Murray enforcers calgon
kill to daves 38 socal God's control the
enforces its complete an Indian enforces
that resisted him or dead all present
how many enforcers are there must have a
200 oh here comes Laura to the dance
deep freeze oh we're going to the deep
freeze I must say but thank you for
calling do call again I'm late for roddy
mcdowall fragments the population who
the Southern Sun being so large surely
we can do to be a bloodbath well if
they've broken intergalactic law that's
mutiny we can call for help cannot we do
I guess that Calvin has already
installed scrambler in a communications
computer oh hey Mike I'm a bellerian
sure looks that way doesn't it yep I
just found out and you know it's weird
it explains so much about me about Who I
am where I came from what motivates me
and such well sure I mean you're a
bellerian yep why don't I look like one
nerd no you sure you do yeah yeah me I
mean I've got to be a bellerian
otherwise I wouldn't be dressed like
this gosh am I balerion yeah yeah I have
to be yep yep I am a bellerian now hell
am I I no no no I am a bellerian I am
mm-hmm guard guard sick man we need more
moisturizer hey not give her I may have
a way for us to get out of here what how
well it just so happens that a clever
young kid named Bobo just might be able
to regurgitate up a key that'll undo
these Lots oh well that's remarkable you
lift a key off a guard and you've
smuggled it in your stomach oh well no
actually the fact of the matter is that
I've swallowed took darn many things
over the years there must be a key down
there somewhere that'll work I don't
know do I want to get free that badly ah
Carl right that come from oh that's
right I swallowed a bunch of that blue
stuff with the barbers I got a couple of
those a weird you just are you doing it
I'm doing Oh a Zippo
no wait a hair tail piece is one of the
woman he swallowed a woman I did not
dream guy I swallowed a wig oh just
freaking undo me this is not here yes
yes I'm free oh great BOGO great great
okay bubble listen very carefully go get
observers green and bring it back here
we'll be out of here in no time leave it
to mr. stone oh I like lettuce shut up
ok follow where's answer is wrong with
you to just give me a little bit of
credit to me for crying out loud I
screwed up so many things in the past I
just like an opportunity to redeem
myself and if oh oh I was supposed to
get observers brain wasn't I and now
you're probably mad at me aren't you and
I suppose you want me to hit myself now
don't you Oh handzup in how good angle
in it Oh could I regurgitated anything
to make it up for you or I'll take some
lettuce if you have any lettuce coming
up ok ok kick ask me if I'm a bellerian
point blank uh are you a bellerian no
dude damn I'm not shit what am I then I
am I just some kind of a gauzy fruitcake
am I just some kind of a gullible freak
ooh who allows the core of his own being
to be blown to the four winds I mean
well I guess so then well that's what I
am that a gullible freak good good huh
wait wait what am i again
we got movie look good as a bellerian oh
you do you know might take away all the
muscle mass on this writer guy it's
pretty much you know you know they
shouldn't have set their phasers to miss
no railing kill don't really take away
his personality and the fact that women
are attracted to him and it's you then
thank you that's that's fine you killed
mitch gaylord Flint iron stag both van
der huge we this is exciting as exciting
can be MSA got penny creep oh no the
methane how are they gonna fill their
cows thick Mick run fast oh forget it
the headed for the bridge my skulls
almost out now yeah let's go
hey you stay with me Trent open file on
lit ssin valerian behavior not planning
based practitioners of magic see these
balls magic huh mosquito got it the
stevie nicks workout
command heavy sigh and Sherry's card is
now time for us to talk you yes I am
genera the 14th high priestess of the
tripped on lineage the pigment the
Southern Sun are no longer able to
distinguish light and dark your people
are falling prey to the powers of
darkness yes sir I speak the truth
actually she thinks the truth very
loudly oh-ho-ho finally christmas comes
to Santa um mrs. Kringle and I have an
understanding it's basically over
between us wanna see me shake like a
bowl full of jelly oh oh someone did
leave a cookie out for me oh I am a
right jolly old elf
what happened I have shared with you the
way to truth now you must use what you
have learned face calgon and his evil i
will let me just check you twice here my
father and his father before him also
tape Walter their face reasonable men I
myself have tried to follow in their
footsteps mm-hmm I'm a man who believes
in peace not war captain Deavers and I
have decided David you're fired if you
will accept we would like to name you as
our new flight commander I mean
attendant and we trust and pray you will
maintain this as a ship of peace rockin
and we will in due course that all the
people no one warned them of calgon on
ease men yeah I was gonna say that so
well David good luck we put our faith in
blast hard cheese I'm gonna go let the
bull Arians play under my robe Hey
Shari's birthday party finally she's
nude she's fully nude ah lieutenant
waitress yep yep she's a graduate of MIT
but she still has to serve drinks two
men okay that's two bull shots and a
pink squirrel here well David cheese
puffs drink lots it's real fruit flavor
it's a great honor serving you and your
ship to Southern Sun here's to you David
and happening that's what it's all about
whoo-hoo we got iso 9001 certified
commander where's Leah take that back
yeah olya my grandma daughter David I
think you'll find her usual place hiding
from you greenhouse
excuse me yeah he's gonna have so much
sex with your daughter well captain can
you remember when you were that young I
am that yeah we damned if I can Oh slab
Oh Oh hunk o flink why do you need that
guy over there to spot you mmm thanks
this is really good for my abs she
dusted herself with super weight gain
powder to attract them
mm no pic no wrong no nothing nothing
step what now what is that cut it out
Claude no not there don't look just get
on with me hey you want to wrap it up
chunky there's a tour coming through
super intelligent dandelion seeds don't
worship anything okay practice your dog
paddle ladies I can't get this water out
of my ear I hate food my people look can
I borrow a cup of sex and she makes
Shelley Duvall look like Shirley
Hemphill
come on it'll be all right you stupid
food lovers pantene pro-v
glenda jackson is Kate Moss as Isadora
Duncan Red Rover Red Rover let Jimmy
come over da da da all right why did you
call me the second major senator post
the minute they didn't respond i gave
you I didn't know what else to do what
happened they rock just like a hurricane
sir huh what hap hap some happen oh we
just talked and looked at glowing balls
calgon warned us about these women knock
it off Holton grab these idiots take him
down a refrigeration to put him on ice
but we're all idiots sir heads are gonna
roll the calgon finds out about this but
we were just working on some Night Moves
sir not a playin anymore yeah come on
meta mutual work your magic is this the
man well I know sir you demand soften
him up some Lance Kerwin is there thug
what are you doing by soften him and
moisturize him he's an artist with a
fist
quiet Mitch Miller is on oh no more Wow
okay little more than I don't like
people who make mistakes we're gonna put
you on ice for a while I'm Vanilla Ice
wait I want to know what's going on
what's happening with my men what's
a-matter Ranger afraid you're losing
control yes I'm losing control over my
man and over what I'm responsible for
don't be so naive you want off the ship
as much as anybody that may be true but
I'm not willing to sacrifice the lives
of him look it's over Ted calguns got
his plan we're getting up the ship with
the help of the Pirates and there's
nothing you nor I nor anybody else can
do about it ditch this is the Olmeca
pirate fleet to those on board the
Southern Sun listen carefully mornin to
have entered the Alpha Delta restricted
zone we have claimed on the section of
space for people oh yeah astro dust
shadow the previous explosion Alert red
alert we are under fire we are under
fire okay gotta go Gary target baseships
in range repair Cabaye removal are your
nipples that's what he said
death death death i er cow oh oh you
know iren have terminated return your
boat god I love pac-man wall on board
congratulations we have definitely
defendant under Klingon against the
latest pirate attack they're having the
same party but now focus on internal
problem wait Commodores young watch
please blonde three groups the first
group is going to be responsible for
making weapon making wap it's the second
group is quite active soldiers not sir
we were on break the third group is
responsible for getting food and
supplies I suggest we close off all
entries and exits to the engine room
we're going to hold out here and never
let him take over the southern side
let's get out there kicks the back trunk
slam just pissed Rock bones dumped beef
knob smash lamp jaw so you usually see
Denise to do your hair huh I'd like some
mixed flowers for my eunuch lovely spot
isn't it what are you doing here you're
much more attractive with your mouth
shut bring her to my headquarters at
once and get her some pants hey oh she's
really struggling i must say she's going
mental on us but then again she isn't
don't touch my chin tuck it's new let's
go hahahaha oh well I thought it was
funny anyway Jason go get Leah I want
her on the bridge immediately Lieutenant
Commander Jason Jason come on the
message coming through on channel 16
what do you got for me Rick a sleek
Johnson has something to show you I've
got your mother you have 12 hours to
surrender the bridge otherwise your
daughter will be jettisoned into space
no downside well captain calgon lives
like that sir he lives by the sword I
thought he lived by the galley ruthless
there are many people on board this ship
sir boy we have to fight back strength
go on so we both know if there's only
one man on the ship who's capable of
come back to right who's had the
training physically mentally all right
that's me my warrior moo moo we will
prepare for battle the crowd stands with
applaud so she's helped off movie you
animals how can I do ab crunches in this
let me introduce you to the
high-intensity probing laser I do have
one weakness name and French silk pie
other people's now I'm going to use this
laser on one of your teeth it works not
unlike ancient dental equipment how did
you know anything about that so you're
too stupid to learn about dental history
CH dare you insult my knowledge of
ancient dentistry know about your
father's contingency plans can't believe
it there's a sale on power bars things
never go on sale man huh sounds like
you're knocking Tom you might need some
premium gas I think you really need the
masks punch Rock groin really kill all
right must be a very elderly woman with
a flu under that costume fuck plank
chest stump junkman Dirk hard peck rips
take face slate slab rock crud bone meal
what a shame to burn out these lovely
teeth I want those countermeasures brick
hard meat so he fits into a suit that
was restrictive on a really small man
with Lauren what was that sounds that
you sir well i mighta quiet that's the
laser that words like a drill just keep
smiling don't let know convey
I don't feel a thing I'm an emotionally
stunted night I had a prophylaxis
scheduled can you sign a check so I can
go to office max does his entrance Ward
that dun duh-da dun-dun nope I see you
got the girl I'd let them know we meant
business Carol I'd better get back to
the engine room this will they miss me
oh okay still why did he wander around
the engine room in the first place stay
damn eol wall-mounted keyboards it must
be the future I'm Marie is Joseph here
yo pal listen my monitor has gone off
again a heavy of the next week ok you
pictured any sooner backed up already ok
whenever you can anything for you ok
tigi their computer problems of Marie
and Joe make for gripping cinema I saw
goes
rip slag cheek punch side iron gristle
Mick thorn body hey you do you mean me
or my familiar yes a man born without a
brain stem
oh you know the last eight times has
happened the woman just wanted to get
away you had a little pop court on your
lip it was bothering me oh yeah yeah
who's just like the time I got lost at
Bally's but wanted out of the tennis
courts couldn't get out standing right
under a toilet outlet there slake fist
crunch buff hardback bob johnson oh wait
now you're lucky the smart guard is on
vacation this week Morgan Fairchild and
Phil Collins no I see a sunken chest
please my breasts are very sensitive the
rest of the equipment as good as their
what's a look what's he doing Mike don't
oh there's a season and you can't see it
very big this is supposed to be an epic
at right now that's the cast of the
Poseidon Adventure coming the other way
she needs the guys just coming down to
scoop out the cat box look I'm sorry
whoever you are is just getting really
frustrated no no doc hey hey don't okay
it's all I got my shoe sure
holy cow that was totally out of left
field blast thick neck crunch butts date
slam squat thrusts oh you lovable
trollop what took you so long I've been
busy too oh so is gonna be a 3-way ok
that's fine good rawhide rawhide come on
found this place that makes these really
healthy shakes I'm moving bossy boots
man milk milk milk movie see how it
feels move mom beef broth
move-move-move malfouf know you move
though you'll move ooh now you move okay
now move move move one leg then move the
other now breathe breathe I'll meet your
heartbeat come on you can see right up
their jumpsuits he decides Sherry's
belated birthday card no don't oh y'all
doin huh how my mask put this on okay
but I just boost my hair these will make
it so we can't see anything all right
let's move the boiler room has a
receptionist yeah let's go and have
concluded that the boilers have not
moved for some time hey you guys let's
see some ID oh not technically a railing
but the same spirit yeah sure oh why do
you hate my groins on mine I don't Mike
that's who I mean we'll move move stupid
freshmen you located the girl I'll poke
my skull out of younger me
I'm did by incompetents I've been
undermined by my own disciples let's
dance space pitch slip through our
fingers she was our food what do you
call that or that get you to let her
escape we've got him a nicer chillin at
one yes sir and then tell McPherson our
plan is operational put the entire squad
on red alert they woke up the Oakridge
boys oh yeah that's a nice one oh yeah
careful there might want to just things
servo do you know anything about this oh
yeah i just installed a bunch of new
safety railings on the ship oh really
why look at why what happens when I
ocean stops by and sees everything
completely unreeling huh big fat finds
that's what but more importantly Mike
we've got to want to do it for ourselves
we just can't put railings up randomly I
mean there was a railing in front of the
door to my room that there was a
ankle-high railing around the rugs in
her and there was a railing around the
leftover hash browns and out only I
better put a railing around that railing
there Oh ah crow just found the whisper
quiet high-speed spinning spike railings
yeah cool Wow all right server you've
got one hour to get rid of every railing
on the ship okay one out where I mean
all right crying Oh
yeah Mike I forgot to tell you that I
had some oats put in because it's pretty
hard to justify having this many
railings without at least having some
big heights to have railings in front of
know what I mean
Oh we'll be right back sir well there's
a railing around my seat welcome oh
thank god I'm okay too yeah I've had
some sugar for sting and Dolph here
commander we have a problem I'm not a
mega fuel yes David Macpherson's a
traitor yes I saw him with calgon at the
enforcers headquarters can't believe it
I mean it could be dad I saw him there
today they that being the case this is
serious he knows I'm cozy has our
weapons weapons and he knows all our
countermeasures I'm this unbelievable
wake up you know I best men he's my
chief engineer rounder if I may say so
you need to cut some weight let me do my
job now I'm coming with you I'm coming
too I'm not captain I'd rather do it
alone as you please Dave thank you
you're welcome may you stay here
commander there goes our big brave brick
a meet new squid in the globe
it's really hard music to dance to Cindy
Laraine Newman and the new monette's one
can delay it indefinitely and have a
beer go again I clogged up the toilet
but we're going in oh no they stole the
enterprise's red alert sound thing well
lady 6 the pan sear tuna you guys chef
says we're all out now I'm gonna miss
this old wherever we are don't get smart
with me ceiling touch rust rot reef
blast body
coach has us doing wind sprints
oh sounds like a tyro fell asleep on
this keyboard Big Mac large huge damn
you so where the hell are these two in
relationship to each other stop right
there would you like to sample some
canoe hold on let me come down and tell
you geez cut out you guys here's a
little free advice for the mutineers
just stop and aim you idiot why is he so
impossible to head why did he keep on
missing the slow giant white thing
mo out loading up some railing fodder
here right my flamethrower is kind of
weak here you know in this movie people
don't seem to trust other people's
ability to move for a horse my kingdom
for a horse
someone get me a zantac oh send my mask
to mother huh stay together cheeks stay
together cheeks well they rented a
pneumatic catapult and damn it they're
gonna use it somebody good lives wasted
not these guys lives but poor always
brings out the worst in man I don't know
I feel that I failed you did daddy blame
yourself had to happen was no compromise
no that scene really makes me stop and
think about how much better a root canal
would be than this movie I think they
just borrowed the South High marching
band uniforms
so this takes place at the
anheuser-busch brewery or I'm having a
craft fair
giant toilet seat hanging there yeah
handicapped accessible I don't things
please don't use those stairs please
don't shoot us okay that you don't get a
box lunch then it has to be noted the
captain Santa Claus really is failing
absolutely who's yeah I'm handi-capable
huh the railing contributed to his death
area that's a really nice to get smoked
man muscle
let's see if I had lifted so much those
razor to hurt me whew he needs a giant
tux stupid Buddhist monk Vietnam wars
been over for hundreds of years if
there's one thing this movie does well
it's tosin Canadians around me eating
come on Mike this movie's right with a
stench of back bacon please wow I am on
the edge of my seat I should probably
scoot back a little be more yeah you got
a lot more room than rush you just go
back I still support the railing system
hey Don can I work in here
I'll loosen up the paint we can scrape
later
he suddenly have golf ball sized throat
nodes don't watch the growing out lunch
the groom seems to me they're randomly
blowing up things is not a good strategy
in a spaceship always the time you'll
never get to do that I must say we're
being totally defeated I'm us a heat
punch beef won't give me some coffee
Leah give me some coffee here come back
forget it daddy for my name's knife w
you can't stop love he must have blown
out his knee in an earlier mutiny oh
this is new
Pearson you time has come you wanna ask
one of its too late unmute aney now that
is exciting Mike that guy just fell over
a railing as he died now tell me that
isn't a good movie after seeing
something like hack blow fist Oh watch
it man is he all right it oh yeah
Macbeth that that's a really good strut
suspension fighter skank spider skank
who took my purse
oh man I shouldn't have ridden my
recumbent bike to work uh into a nice
sitz bath he's got into the gas
explosion sup right he doesn't have to
be this way I love you think about it we
should work this thing out we'll get
couples counseling sorry Luce valve here
what were you saying what are you doing
that but that's now what are you doing
yeah Chung ket just beefed got the gas
bill go and you guys want burgers and
our brave hero roast the disabled man
well I have learned one thing from this
movie Mike not to sit in our gas
expulsion sump we got out stop having
lunch day and even point you should stay
up on the bridge safe with your father
hey guys horses are not going to attack
again see how the hell you know that
well if you chuck I am nice and Prince
calguns dad yeah we only later they have
no choice but to surrender to my father
hey guys just drop the reports off
besides I thought you would be happy to
see me of course I am that's not the
issue your father should have stopped
you my father stopped interfering with
my life when I was 15 years old hey
again guys got something for your father
he's a good man I just wish you could
control you as well as he does his ship
mean have a mutiny on me or control me
if I hadn't saved you in that engine
room oh come on I would have got out of
that situation no problem well that's
gratitude gratitude stop throwing your
ten dollar words wrong why did you do it
because oh never mind oh you really are
stubborn does that mean I'm cut
music that means means means nothing at
all off
now it is time recommended by top
readers it's gearing up for a really
intense video game oh man why is this
seat so far forward who was driving this
thing lasts
well someone dropped a jar hellmann's in
Aisle seven I got to go clean it up you
believe illegal cut back up perfectly
legal
LeSean mighty Cushman
how these things were a riot Oh didn't
see you my fault totally my fault
damn I'm losing speed cuz I'm also
trying to buff the floors yup sorry you
cut me off by the boiler it just took me
off know when there's silliest moments
the Three Stooges never reach this level
of indignity you know a lot of people
have compared the scene to the climactic
chariot seen and been her yeah you know
they usually say then her was really
good this movie totally sucked
who wish you'd never come here writer
Leia help cow God's JCB active seniors
lifestyle says thumbs up it will make
your heart race though maybe that's not
such a good thing any second Leigh is
gonna jump on her big wheel and get
chase
battling bunzy snidely whiplash you can
actually get another three miles an hour
in these babies you could take it off
the shag setting a curse it mountebank
seems a wire bottle brush inside of
smoke before illness see turo turo these
things are made by tero still it's
better than Days of Thunder yeah oh this
is a riot hey that's for not knowing
anything about ancient dentistry sauna
bath oh I forgot well honey we got that
out of my system old fizzle beef
boy Wow big explosion for a tiny
electric car they should have been
carrying that case of cleaning fluid and
nitroglycerin angelic night in there
Flossie microwaved an egg at the same
time finally got some time to lift yeah
yeah okay come on move mobile fo you
okay well I'm what happened okay 25
Calvin's gone forever I'm guessing it's
finished
Oh
yeah thank my personal trainer let's get
out here come on bow bow bow bow not
since the fuzzy Zeller Lee Trevino
collision of 1974 has there been such a
horrible golf cart accident
yeah we've had some marshmallows you
know we could stuff him in our eyes and
ears and never have to see or hear this
stupid movie
Leia this could be the start of a
beautiful alternate day bulk up routine
attention commander Ryder ding ray
patrol ready for takeoff won't you miss
your flight does that mean you won't
marry me huh I think you skipped a line
yeah there we go got a little bit of a
workout in it last it was a little draft
over there let's make out over here way
meriden had a healthy eight and a half
pound pork roast oh right yeah I think
chunk heads more of a shuttlecraft if
you know what I'm saying yes sir haha
good good back to the rusting septic
system of this futuristic spaceship I
hope they spend the last few minutes on
the apology I heard there's a tacked-on
bit of film featuring the Attorney
General explaining how you can join in a
class action suit against this movie
well right okay pans over because
there's calcium okay we're all really
surprised or shocked y'all gon die
within its energetic in flames coming to
help you is he waiting for his pants to
come out of the dryer I don't know
hahaha to sort
cajun pan blackened calgon and his eyes
open and his eyes all eyes open I know
his eyes open i'm sitting in something
wet
me take me away
we don't need more kill boo boo boy you
know I retarded jellyfish could make a
better movie than this who a severely
impaired box turtle with a very busy
schedule just give him a camera for a
day he'd come up with something better
than this music rejected by the band's
survivor hey I'm here so he knows enough
dream me too I feel like that sometimes
too yeah I the lobster man was played by
guy Pringle Wow wouldn't want to slam a
stack of that guy hey she's a maniac
maniac on the floor don't pay the
ferryman don't even fixed a crazed
maniac maniac uncle everybody some day
love will find you may the bull Arians
all right hi my name is Jeanette multi
I'm a bellerian this is my friend Laura
fremont blaring there's no feeling
you know it is statistically proven that
seventy percent of white guys can seem
like this really no one else wants to
though I highly doubt it I'm staying in
my parents basement july by the job a
continuity Beth wilbraham can she be
legally arrested now you know they
really did have excellent clapping and
loading I saw the best boy that they
could come up with was fuzzy Skinner no
I got one I wear my sunglasses at night
this band will be appearing at the
bombay bicycle club later this weekend
ok ok Mike be honest with us this music
can really gets your blood going on yeah
Mike this is your music done by your
people so I blame you for this entire
movie yeah it's just like you to make a
movie let's just cheese what did it do
what are you picking on me for you were
a young guy during the eighties when
this is your world admit it
okay now that's it this year's the kind
of music it get all weepy at at the end
of a drunken Friday night sitting there
with your hair all feathered scarfing
down cold potato skins yeah your attempt
to get little Susie what's-her-name
drunk on lime vodka ended in humiliating
rejection right so you sit there all
mushy and sentimental reciting to
yourself the words to some song by night
ranger yeah maybe one homely girl feel
sorry for you for a second but then she
sees how stinkin drunk you are and gets
disgusted yeah and maybe the first chair
trombone player from the high school
band from Spy you know he takes pity on
you tried to drive you home and I'll but
no Mike you want to swerve home and your
cherry doubt dodge charger yeah you wind
up wrestling for your kids with the guy
then finally he drops you with one punch
and he leaves and you lie there knowing
you got your butt kicked by the leader
of the high school bed your puss you and
you're a tease your precious it you know
when it continued to be the 70s if not
for you yeah all right that's it that
cheery note I made man come on I'll take
you ladies jerk come on cool Breezer
hope wait you guys wait this isn't us
man yes it is you here feathering
freedom circle he's writing right this
movie has is turning on each other it
won't end these credits just won't and
it's just like the stupid ADC never read
it either actually they did time that's
okay see you see there's a copyright
that means it's over sorry buddy
so what do you think am I buff or what
am i blue twisted cold rolled steel or
what are you sure you've lifted already
you're not planning to lift at some
future date or anything about nope I see
it I see it your arm goes along and then
there's a little bump there there is
this little ripped bicep is what you
mean Poindexter crow your gun no more
than pathetic we need to be pushed
around at will yeah great hey cambot
watches Oommen with a macro lens maybe
we can get a shiny dome macro lens
Nelson I am superbly buff and that's
that yes sir hey Micah could I get a
spot over here man certainly your yeah I
know I've got eight arms and a colossal
tuckus and all this from one leg press
huh I am quite susceptible to bulking up
well maybe you've done enough for one
day then probably but I'm addicted now
if I don't lift I die so if I get a spot
over here yeah sure no problem man Chris
I gotta talk to pearl though alright
alright CC I was going for tone hi well
Mike Here I am chained to a wall with an
exceptionally stupid monkey thank you
and a brainless drooling nitwit string
tastes funny pearl Forrester great life
pearl good job Oh pearl eagerly I
thought I'd come down and remind you
that you died dawn tomorrow you died
down tomorrow your breath stinks really
well uh I'll be back later to remind you
bye bye well there it is Mike I see no
way out observer is useless without his
brain doing what up what about my brain
so we die tomorrow oh I guess you guys
are free to go all right rich what huh
Wow boy we're happy and all that we can
go but we'd really rather didn't end
this way and when you die in and all
right guys oh all right yeah yeah this
is awkward anyone
yeah yes yeah yes well thank you but who
maybe it's all for the best this gives
me a chance to make my peace with God
whatever so I look back on my life I see
that I've been tormenting you for no
good reason and perhaps even at this
late date whatever powers over us all
might see fit to forgive me for all the
years found it over my brain Josh
nevermind Nelson hey brain guy you need
we need some sort of distraction for
when Flay via returns I know could you
try like a fake seduction honor no no no
I could never seduce a woman verla oh
because here well I I thought you knew I
am completely and utterly but without a
body I have no body well thank you for
coming out with that information oh I
know let's get Mike down here here we go
I like a fake seduction on flavor yeah
oh well okay seducing a beautiful woman
not my forte can maybe give you a 15 to
20 seconds fuck you look old or lonely
or infirm but I want you please here she
comes I'm on it don't worry about then
you are you doing here well hey if it
isn't flavia's daughter was it even me
well I hey yes it just means it what
yeah what is it video well what enough
guards feed them what
I just grabbed this we love
you