future somewhere in time and space and
his robot pals chase wants to rule the
world through these things in her purse
and in the rocketship you
the worse I can
do yourself it's just a show just relax
for Mystery Science
hi everyone welcome to the satellite of
love just to bring you up to date we
recently escaped along with pearl
Forrester and her companions from
ancient Rome which by the way Bobo
burned down and then we went back
through the wormhole and now here we are
who knows we're just knocking about in
time and space God say Mike just for the
sake of discussion um what would be
another way you could put that last part
there we're wandering in space aww we
don't know where we are in space or what
in space I don't know adrift cast off
unmoored location list lots of ways you
could put it ah lost maybe sure lost in
space hold on bro uh-huh you galloping
garbage bag of collagenous plop you
pusillanimous pigskin of puffer a
warning you're happy birthday bro Thank
You Will Robinson a terrasphere
tumescent tenofovir you in a desert
hypertonic in erotic in anger you've
ever you quickly wearing green you are
you dare interested no you just said
that all right you dichotomous time a
bad drama major and that timber do you
work you you suck hey I'm sorry Mike I
gotta go straight now we'll be right
back your guys was hate you whoa tell me
i suck Goa hell you don't sucking it's
just kind of early sorry I so can I am
really you can understand my reaction
sure sure
okay that's really in danger you know
what Pearl has just to pull this over so
we can find out where we are and i'm
going to do a really tricky docking
maneuver so why don't you go watch a
video with gypsy huh oh yeah yeah Lily
mando Connie mando Connie cool yeah okay
all right here we go now this is the
heart just ease it into place gently
it's perfect i'll go check it out
Nelson Mike zat you come on over your
neighbor are you sure it's not too late
uh I'll be up another couple of hours or
so come on over i just put a fresh pot
of coffee on hold on over here bro oh
sheesh hang up I just put Bobo down and
sometimes he's a little fussy oh boy
she's a cold one yeah supposed to get
down to absolute zero that's why I
always wear a sweater so pearl how come
you're so evil hmm I'm filled with hate
I don't know if that helps you know Mike
people can be awfully judgmental about
evil Mike Mike you know we were watching
TV and we had it on something we all
liked and then servo change the channel
okay well I'll tell you what if you're
real quiet you can stay here with pearl
and me hey hey hard hi well I suppose I
better be sending you guys your movie
huh oh I'll see that's another thing you
said you weren't gonna send us any more
movies you know sometimes I think I lie
because I'm evil so you're gonna send us
a movie though yeah and it's pretty bad
I hope that's okay it was made in
Vermont and it's about this guy who
travels through time and then he has to
go back in time to change what he did in
the future it's it's called time chasers
oh it's got that guy in it on that other
guy too mmm yeah yeah
oh yeah well yeah we're gonna get
factored once you take off thanks for
stopping by yeah aren't you take care
kid boy oh hey Mike yeah I despise you
and all you stand for and you'll never
accept it you know the rest early
goodnight girl he's a good kid haha no
way come on sir 10 turn back to dr. Jane
Seymour medicine quill no way forget you
what hey where were you guys hated crow
get to go over to pearls that's not fair
girl gave me lots of candy and popcorn
and said that I can stay there any time
that she was gonna take me to France and
she like the best man
hello I'm vital Hitchcock director of
this film he's got a bucket of crotch
flavored popcorn oh so early two Reds
wood r entertainment remitted results
okay stop get it out there supposed to
be happy about this a David giancola
film is something you'd want to see no
all of us Koch of the time chasers like
NFL graphics here but it up put it up
it's just that subliminal advertising
you hear about I don't know but suddenly
I'm hungry for a guy with class was
anyone else guy with glasses villain you
are genius the crop dusting genius got
it part well cut the lawn way too short
he's down to the bedrock it's gonna
annum awesome gatorade
that's the leftover Miami Vice music
here
plane looks like it can't think of
anything to say uh-oh hey wait a minute
this isn't our star is it I will not
accept this as our star sorry yo you was
spectacular ain't no tongue I think it's
a few and think I put in work good oh it
was it was fine great was outstanding
hey party but do me a favor no tell me
to stop acting like Richard Dreyfuss
could you uh can you fuel that up and
put it back in the hangar for me Oh 40
yeah I've got something for you
collection your other gallstone thanks
20-footer lon
co-starring Bruce Springsteen's little
brother Wayne I come on this can't be
the hero of the film is a geeky 10-speed
you should at least have a cool burnt
orange stingray on down for parallel
parking days
no no this can't be the star tenant
movie movie hey movie can I see your
supervisor movie this will not stand oh
maybe he's going into the house to meet
the real hero with me k next we're gonna
see the real hero of the film coming up
the down geez just a floppy disk for
breakfast honey you've got male pattern
baldness flying toasters are pretty
The X Files goes to Dublin Bay koz
reclining loser damn I thought Night
Court was on at genCorp we believe that
listening to people is winning approach
listening breeds new ideas and new ideas
breed innovation innovation is this
country's greatest natural resource its
most powerful defense weapon stops
playing where we champion innovators
because of them double hull tankers are
here in oil spills are a memory a good
memory in car now sets worldwide
standards in aviation one fear all
because of innovators genCorp innovators
we really can't afford to live without
them a division of plasma I'm part of
calm medtech Tom new technology to know
no barb hey it's me and I'm nude yes
hello I've just completed work on an
amazingly efficient fuel intake for
small engine flames oh it's a radical
design and uses thirty percent less fuel
I notice you have a plan here in town
and I was wondering if you might come
over and take a look at this is pizza
hut sir rockin sure sure I'm an
unappealing actor in a bad movie sure
yes hello I think I've got a neat local
story for you you see my grandmother is
turning 75 tomorrow and she's come to
try skydiving for the very first time
it's not gonna go too well if you know
what I mean
sorry I killed you Gary nothing personal
the modern bachelor lifestyle flying to
work or play any failings of reporters
come swooping down well someone from the
home shopper pulls up in a k-car
well two different plaids and imma make
it robot and even I know that's a
fashion nono oh no it's plain protection
services they know I kissed my plane so
I'm great it's good to see it's been wet
since reunion yeah still the city
actually I live here now ok what do
whatever I became toni tennille oh
nothing really I you still pick you yeah
yeah up the college physics we are out
for the summer though yeah yeah so what
hey what brings you here I'm here about
a skydiving grandmother you work for the
banner yeah that's my job here pretty
lame huh thank you sure your grandmother
well sort of yeah what do you mean uh
there's grandma now I'll introduce you
excuse me tell you minute be right back
hi hi I'm Nick Miller hmm nice plane but
needs more plaid that's right thanks for
coming out that's quite all right no no
we'll keep this together mm-hmm he has a
computer wow that's pretty radical well
where the WG yeah i just realized your
grandmother died when we were kids uh
Lisa I'd like you to meet Matthew Paul
he's with gen Corp aviation nice to meet
you this is Lisa Henson she's with our
local newspaper mm-hmm I'd like to get a
look at this intake if I could well what
I'd like to do is give you both a quick
demonstration first so if you'll jump
right in we'll be on our way all right
Nick there's no grandmother no I lied
about that ah but don't worry there is a
story here so Mike no skydiving grandma
huh man they lead you up to something
great let me to shoot it down stupid
grandma lever routers
that's easy there could be dozens of
grandmas jumping out of planes right now
very entertaining very informative
ripoff okay now the real reason I
brought you both up here today to crash
see I talked to others and no one
believed me so I decided to lie a little
bit to at least get someone to come see
this what are you talking about oh no
don't you see this plane yeah this stuff
enables who's ever inside it to get a
film career that quickly dies travel
through time hi you mean this isn't
about a fuel-efficient intake things
never change do they met oh no this time
they do you brought us up here this
morning to look at your minder time
machine that time transport yeah look do
you think you could land this plane I
really don't have time for this nonsense
time get it scheduled today what you're
kidding right Hey look I know you both
think I'm full of it but you won't in a
minute now go ahead and pick a date in
time past or future whatever now you're
serious oh absolutely what the hell
nitpick is 50 years into the future okay
anyway yeah I'm puter signals the
molecule and celebrated right in turn
charge the skin of the plan what abling
was every okay the skin to the plane day
we're with travel through the past do
something now a waters join farther into
the future you go and of course I can
reverse the polarity and go back in time
as well that's my but you've got to be
kidding ok now let's see 50 years uh
September 24th 2041 at twelve-thirty and
if man is still alive reality I'm listen
to me Alicia what hold up look guys the
transport countdown on the computer oh I
forgot to ask neither of you have heart
valves do you oh and did either of you
eat breakfast this morning did huh
what did you do how's this for a reality
check
we're in Dar es Salaam the future means
cheesy graphics
yeah okay all right the future Oh call
you back so in the future kids become
gay agents so 50 years from now it'll be
three years from now Lisa Kudrow card
rotate your car now made completely of
animal feces
come on yeah but
see in future men were long leather
coats and there are junior colleges
right here look a lesbian of the future
food courts of the future don't believe
it like a dream this is 2041 this is
2041 you did it you are a genius all
your life yeah Satterlee gonna fit you
could use this thing to change history
oh yeah we could prevent Newt Gingrich
Jim Carrey and the smashing pumpkins
that's not why I brought you here I want
you to buy me an Orange Julius honestly
I'm out of money and I need more so i
can continue my work now that i've made
this breakthrough so what can genCorp
good for you I need nor indeed great I
want to be able to continue my work this
is big big and pink this is very big
what's these of a time machine for
genCorp I give an example you could send
an egg into the future study the
long-term effects that we're having on
our environment we could you send Bob
Saget to meet Charlemagne if we could
figure out a way to stop shooting at
each other you know if you went back 100
years in the past but a hundred dollars
in the bed and then came back a hundred
years to the present God the interest
alone would make you a millionaire yeah
well I'm going over to spiral same way
these ideas are Justin just the tip of
the iceberg listen Nick I'm going to go
over the heads of my bosses here and
take this directly to jay kay robertson
the CEO of gin court the other guy that
does the TV coverage that's the one look
I will drive him up here from the city
personally if I have to that would be
great all right it's a Radisson I think
it we're ready to go I don't think I'll
ever be ready I'll bring it back on it
or something
no man here we go I got to get a call in
to Robertson I'll walk back to the past
and fly through another spirograph
drying I left my keys at the manchu wok
of the future you they come who's got
the rice hi I'm Bob evil everyone this
is an auspicious day in the history of
the world nope today we have entered the
fourth dimension food about to be the
only ones with the key yup yup yup yup
Nick hugged me I'll have a car pick you
up in the morning to take you to my
headquarters in the city that's real
pretty miss Henson you're part of this
project and I want you working for gen
core I need someone to document and work
on promotion to the transport mr.
Robertson I currently have a job at the
banner it's time for you to make a
career decision I'm offering you a large
salary and an opportunity to report on
something very important I think you
understand how the transport will change
life as we know it no thanks well free
coffee you turning me down I'm not
interested in working for genCorp I
understand you think you got yourself a
scoop here probably thinking go national
makes itself quite a name yes ma'am
that's possible no it isn't no ma'am i
don't think i have to tell you how
important this is this has to be kept
under total secrecy until we understand
what we're dealing with if this fell
into the wrong hands it might who said
you were the right hand you know what
I'm talking about even more than you do
look Lisa make these guys are gonna bury
you with a corporate crap take the job
they have to keep this under wraps I
understand that I'm greedy and stupid no
thanks why are you throwing this away I
are you we don't Brooke back-sass from
our phillies and they have to expect
this sort of thing Nick people want as
big a piece as they can get nope now we
have a couple of men here to watch the
hangar until we can set up a full
facility here you think that's necessary
absolutely but it's just a precaution
trust me and Nick I must also ask you
not to discuss this with anyone from now
on besides the fact that my company all
to see
corporate spy's the transport is a
national security risk well all new
technologies at first what am I making
myself clear on this do you understand
yeah yeah you're evil and that's okay no
one won't believe me anyway you know
you're right all right we'll see you
tomorrow let's go boys let's go
directors college buds who brought their
own suits to the shoot Leonard Jacobson
I want you two to stay here until the
deployment arrives and Matt you are now
VP I want to see you in an office on my
floor first of the week yes sir in a
more dignified soup
more of a prom limo isn't it search
celebrities nude Cameron Diaz I wonder
if I should have held out for more than
sixty five dollars he's looking for the
names of other girls who talked to him
in high school and nothing's coming up I
know it's a good time it's somebody tape
at dinner also his chin this point I'm
getting pretty tired of watching the
security video of his Bachelor life
loser status confirmed come to Martin's
wat up
some fruit I suppose I better buy toilet
paper girls coming over later Who am I
trying to kid I never went to castleton
mrs. hi how are you how's your ketchup
Empire that's because I haven't had any
of your good home cooking in a while it
always come to my house but you never do
cuz I'm frightened of you anymore either
and it's your fault you work too hard
when you're such a nice young handsome
man you need a young lady Dale all right
all right I'm going but you be good see
you and community theater practice ah
the haunting bakery theme yeah sample
ladies got pizza in Aisle five I'd like
to double back you shit oh great I was I
was gonna call you hi how about last
week that's okay the reporter in me
wasn't trying to blow you or design sign
the next day hide the mic in the
broccoli
so you're cooking dinner are you
offering dinner no I'm saying make me
dinner yeah not thank you huh I've got a
better idea let's eat a bicycle that's a
better idea we're listening to the light
jazz stiffness and then the truth that
17 perfect chance to help Mike you see
you go back into his past convince him
to take a new direction in his life yeah
and then time changes so that Mike never
becomes trapped on the satellite at all
yeah yeah but what if things go wrong
yeah there's a small chance will warp
ourselves and the rest of the universe
out of existence cool accessing 1985 now
okay let's see central Wisconsin homing
in on my wow man what a loser Hey look
at him we're gonna the cheese factory
he's going absolutely nowhere Oh Great
Scott oh he's a journey fan we have to
help him I'm coming Mike okay crow
remember try not to be conspicuous blend
in like no piece of the lunchroom
there's a robot from the future waiting
for you so much for blending in oh hello
dude hey man food we make this quick
it's coming on my break time yeah yes
greetings young Mike my name is crow and
I've come from the future to help you
change your miserable dead-end life geez
nobody said anything about that how does
that work you got to Mike you are about
to embark on an endless worthless string
of temp jobs and man happens great you
know it's flexible hours you can sleep
in you can ditch whenever you want
laughs that sounds pretty good you get
Betty's with that we cross that sounds
cool neither what am I saying Mike I
have seen your grim future if you don't
change your life and
you'll be shut up into space and forced
to watch terrible movies shot up into
space did you hear that man MV
outrageous would be like space 1999
listen to me you simp yeah what about
your dreams your hopes a hollow
desperate eternity in space that's no
future for you yeah I'm gonna beats
getting burned by the cryovac machine do
Oh exactly when in the future will you
become not stupid mica crow this is tom
maybe you should just kill him or
something I don't know hey who's that
that's uh God whoa dude go wrap it up
it's almost commercial sign I'd coming
okay Micah I'll be back in just a second
eat your lunch or something and don't
take any temp jobs while I'm gone okay
right robot from the future dude
well I'm lost in love and I don't know
much when you get caught between the
moon and New York scenes ever in
I'm lying in bed holding you close to my
room whoa
hey we rented three vintage cars and
damn it we're gonna use them ah the 50s
when everyone walked around saying a all
the time say can I get skymiles if I put
this on my visa goal the 50 huh yeah
there's mrs. Khrushchev sweeping the
sidewalk we're gonna get poodle skirts
right away
now for some good old-fashioned 50s
heavy petting shouldn't he be like
piloting the plane Nick what is that
that means I like you did it I I don't
know where are we it says September 25th
2041 well we were here it doesn't look
like that my god there's something very
wrong here there's no food courts looks
like there was a war you'll have to take
my word for it we can't afford to show
it I run diagnostic on a computer
everything isn't fond de lithium
crystals are fine and is everything out
of 41 something's happened futures been
changed we got to find out what happened
for you ray gun well no tsunami in that
enclose so for some reason Vermont
became the epicenter of the dystopia Ben
& Jerry's was the key to the Armageddon
future still has Mason Reese yeah see
they opened a Walmart across the street
just a week before and this is the
result hey servo the future looks like
your room mmm if we find an old couch I
could really use it after the apocalypse
things were really fairly untidy
so apparently they didn't reduce the
capital gains tax after all shame really
yeah still guys tape up posters for
their bands totally destroyed yeah looks
like it's been this way for one there's
got to be something around still
somewhere Chimney Sweeps took over the
future ah I'm Nick and this is honey
permission it's easy look we're not from
this time boy from the pass rebels that
we chillin yeah yeah you know about time
travel wish transport council Catherine
here please tell me why you drew the
death of anthony michael hall wow people
are opening a lot of beers in there
so it's an armed levi's add the future
people will rub themselves with olive
oil filters ha so drew carey's nemesis
me me survive the apocalypse you're
gonna give me all your Soylent Green Man
you see a higher the guy who works in
your dad's print shop as an actor and
this is what you get we're taking you to
see the Grand High dirtbag now well
welcome to t very walk it's part of our
riverfront revitalization project yeah
yeah tell anyone else about the
transport right I don't think their
dates going that well oh you know on the
other hand this is always going to be
their own little apocalypse right Mickey
gonna shoot no wisdom at the dangerous
game oh that guy got shot how could they
do that he was great ok I'm not all the
best characters dying the danger going
with men you meet at the grocery store
clearly Illustrated right here the
llbean gay
our sixteen men on a Dead Dodge Dart
they found safe haven and Jennifer Beals
flashdance apartment what a feeling huh
sherry action realtor
boy I hope they end up together the
bottom of a well torn apart by animals
your butt looks good in the future hey
lion big boys don't cry
hey does this ironweed all of a sudden
found them in the sector their travelers
travelers and you still have your
transport huh no stolen by elves yeah
how did you know the wheelage ain't from
around here nobody from around here
looks like you were long where's your
fills so uh huh damn did you find water
no made some though I found this now you
know that guy could use chinder where
thanks for leaving me with the bums this
is all my fault exactly you couldn't
have known what would happen I never
should let anyone know about the
transport till I had a chance to test it
more you didn't invent the transport to
destroy we were here before and
everything was fine future wasn't
affected but what about my hockey air
Robertson it was Robertson the last time
I was here was when i gave the demo on
the transport to Robertson but
everything is fine fine yeah but I must
have been after that and he decided to
use the transport to be a weapon so I'm
blameless we do what got into Robertson
we've gotta make him change his mind
that doesn't work I'll pull the project
are you doing out you'll be seen just
wait where you going I'm gonna try and
change things Yeah right can you change
the fact that I have crunchy pants
everybody wants to change his me I just
want to find a little Beefaroni at the
bottom of a can I'd start by finding the
guy who invented the time transported
cut is michael moore in 30 years
yes an exciting career in aviation
awaits you wet time chasers Community
College
hey Tom Bosley sirve la cancel all
testing today tell every person has
military back you know the big generals
he's not gonna blow the biggest deal of
his career very easily then we'll take
them in the future if we have to laugh
to agree with us after he sees that Nick
my boy hello I have a serious problem
with the project what do you mean we
need to meet right away okay take a
helicopter and I'll see in an hour I'll
be the guy sitting at the desk in the
mall skyway am I exploiting my core
competencies oh and a drunk i love you
go girl from Vermont City on the go we
were so excited to be in the limo they
call the driver like 26 times
you and your date will be whisked off to
marry and Jordan junior high so the guys
office is in a branch library children's
book circle will be Madeline's rescue at
3pm Nick Lisa how are you both not so
great we've got a problem so you said
have a seat do you need your books
renewed now what's the problem we've got
to stop the project stop the project
don't be ridiculous why don't be coy we
know you're developing the transport to
be a weapon you got me I am NOT how can
you say you don't know we've been to the
future it's a it's a wasteland in the
future the world in anarchy because of
its use as a weapon is not the transport
when you affect history you affect the
future it causes a tangent right it
gives the future I know that but listen
to yourself you're saying I've affected
the future no you will what I haven't
yet we're not in Anarchy yet in 30 years
we will be yes but until that time we'll
figure out a way to change it right well
yes but but the only way to be sure is
to stop now listen do you want your
library card rip oh he's reasonable
we're talking millions here what we need
to do is find out what our problems are
and fix them now I want you to get on
this thing and I want you to find out
just what we know no no there's nothing
to work on except your goofy office if
you don't stop the project I will pull
my license agreement with your company
are you threatening me no I'm telling
you if we don't stop now they'll be no
future for any of us including you you
castleton snob look just come to the
future with us so you can at least see
what you've done what I have done what
did you think did you think we were
going to use the transport to take kids
on history trips you knew full well the
power of the transport just come with us
to the future you have to see what will
happen forget it I don't have a swimsuit
I've been there and we will take care of
it
you've been using the transport already
I've already built another one you've
known about this for some time that's
right and we will be careful in
presenting this project but that's it
how can you do this after you've seen
what will happen it's easy not really
this project is over come on Nick this
is now a government project you no
longer have any control what's wait a
minute you read my contract I can change
anything anytime I want so you've read
it no you eat it section 57 paragraph 4
if a manufacturer of any product from
the outcome of this contract is deemed a
value or a threat to national security
the government will appoint a project
supervisor that supervisor a total
control over riding any previous of
rules that washed in this that's a
government law not a gender court and
who's the appointed supervisor Harvey
Korman while I have of course Singler
beyond a contract I think you're right
jacobsen we have here a couple of
corporate spot what they've just
informed me they're going to try to
destroy the ttp project I informed them
that was now a military operation and
they can be tried as traitors they then
threatened me hand them over to the
military attache I'll call down a report
later don't you do this sorry you need a
screw gun up here you know how serious
this is yes I know I think they give
traders like in prison not you probably
on a check with a lawyer get them out of
my office let's go you mean out of your
mezzanine sir so why the big circus
mirror
what Wall Street Street Jeff Nick yeah
five a lawyer right mm don't mind me
saying so that's a real cute top man hmm
yeah he's through michael medved at him
I never should have joined the physics
companies mmm seal off the elevator now
waiting for us downstairs me alone the
crossing guards
they got off on the second floor their
masters of escape I know where the snack
machines are come on but took on Barbara
dumb
we have time for a passport photo
probably not good to talk bro you know I
wonder if she ever got her groceries in
the fridge yeah The Adventures of the
average people oh come on we got a cock
those windows to let go of my bra strap
real acid wash action right now the
garbage trucks backing up didn't tip you
did you do today took the two buh buh
buh buh even though I see them running
the other way super duper duper as Gena
Rowlands arrives for her temp shift what
how you understand they're both very
dangerous people you worried absolutely
shoot to kill I've got a whole building
full of people here i want to take i go
home you'll you people you don't you
were JK what's going on at time for you
to decide if you're gonna be one of my
team place your Chin's gonna have to go
on the trunk sir no please go anywhere
north I'd like to point out that North
is not a destination her boy the
direction yes and it's Russian we need
to go please I think we lost them yeah
for now now what do we do I don't know
Nick we've got to destroy the transport
wouldn't do any good they've copied all
my software they just make another one
excuse me use me I come from New York
New York you walking internet yeah
that's good if you could act your way
north that would be great good ol dude I
suggest a suicide pact personally we've
got to go back in time
we've got to stop my pastels I'm killing
them or I may go into Robin can't see
him anything because if he doesn't give
a demo none of this happens listen Mike
of the past you are a promising young
man right handsome well loved culturally
aware oh yeah hey look man loni anderson
we can put those down you idiot you
stupid repulsive ax I hope of our
nation's future did you rise the gifts
you're squandering if you stay trapped
here like like your band your wonderful
music well that's true robot from the
future I won't be able to make my gigs
if I'm stuck up in space yes your cage
dim young version of Mike your music
which if you nurture through these
coming years could bring meaning and
solace to millions what's your band's
name again sex factory yeah and you're
right we totally rock and I don't want
to be stuck up in space watch and stinky
movies when I could rock the world right
I'm out of here man I'm I'm quitting
rock on thick as a slab of Canadian
bacon well bit of effort but still in
the end a plus crow dude uh dude yes
excuse me I'm gonna go check on the
Gouda Wiz yep good work prob why thank
you bro all right all right watch where
you going you're skinny freak she was
sorry Mike I didn't mean I close Mike
Eddy Eddy hi Eddie sorry Eddie area many
that where you been midget yeah sorry
any won't happen again anything was
ashen okay so uh oh boy you're not Mike
or Mike who else but I don't know no
Mike's just grow Eddie don't know Mike
hey hey shut up shut up Eddie right away
except for my loser kid brother Mike oh
that idiot quit our temp jobs to go work
with his band and yeah I missed out on
some really great job some of them even
minimum way
wait this would have been a great job
except for those two guys shot me up
into space that's sleepy a guy left so
uh Edward Eddie names it Eddie so Edward
your brother's band didn't do too well
kidding they were doing great they were
already opening from Motorhead when Mike
bought it what what very couldn't he
totally character right on state hey
what are you stupid ass assume I am hey
you know the Cleveland Civic Center
leave no chicks were really digging them
they're throwing their hotel keys up on
the stage a couple of them big ones
caught him in the beanie went down never
got up again guide like a mangy dog
right on stage yeah I was really proud
of excellent death excellent this
reality is even worse for Mike I gotta
get back in warnings hey this little
pencil-necked just a reality suck yeah
he sure did Eddie I her too many happen
ah now I got movie sign get excited to
see the rock can you bring me a beer
anyway Eddie oh that's mine oh thanks
Eddie
never gonna get to that plane yes we are
Odin look I ever did get cancelled gonna
go home and turned into a nuclear device
and I'm out of gum no nothing short of
planes crashing on the runway we're
gonna get these guys out of the hangar
because in time chasers they don't take
American Express
sir would you mind crashing on the
runway so my friend can get away thank
you you know they use these planes for
running black market maple syrup into
Vermont this guy's swallowing condoms
full of maple syrup the state and
Northwest could fit two hundred people
onto this plane usually when I'm in one
of these big chin guys trying to kiss me
oh she's disguised at least our time
life operator let's see did something
with a switch when he was pawn me
directors cousin can I help you Ron
unicon go ahead ah my pilot just had a
heart attack and I think it's dead you
got hell because I can't fly what is
your end number thanks Eddie it's
located straight in front of you on the
instrument panel ah x 5 2010 I'm not
really sure I think I'm close to the
airport though and oh yeah I'll work you
register for a while because don't worry
lady will fuck you down did you guys out
there he's gonna drop short of the
runway hey she's gonna drop shorts on
them hey everybody she's gonna drop
shorts on the runway that's what I yeah
that's their special truck devoted to
when women drop shorts on the runway
yeah really funny when shorts are
dropped we'll be there
oh so they're the really nice evil guys
what are they hoping to catch the plane
I can't help with the plane crash I
screw everything up pull it takes a chin
you out of paper towels in the bathroom
you didn't count on the assistant
janitor you know I find myself wanted to
suggest other places he could hit him
it's probably not what they wanted is it
yeah how much fuel do you have on board
oh I don't know I think it's on empty
I'll which way out of the hangar thing
um I don't know uh supposed to be it's
the square box to your right with a
light on yeah I think it is um you hold
on a minute I think I'm gonna be sick so
she wasn't crashing after all that bites
just like the grandma thing all over
again how am I supposed to trust this
movie huh
he farted a shot up that was you
he's fighting Michael frags that's my
favorite to buy for give it back I see
this is north west's customer service
this guy's real strength is that he's
totally used to getting wailed on I just
got a really strong girlfriend that
helps trust me I got me all over me
climb aboard time for another make out
session
whoa
just the Spruce nat
leave for 20 minutes and evil Co is in
shambles I'm a team player crash and get
eaten by a soccer team or a baseball
team or a bridge club I don't care I'm
gonna squint the hell out of them the
other one ready yes sir get it started
gotta get going before they time to you
want me to ready a crew that won't be
necessary gotta quit smoking the villain
takes off and hot well warmed the tappet
pursuit your head off my leg sir
so they travel back 30 seconds and crash
into themselves when are we going to
well I think it will go back to the
morning before I give the demo I
Robertson that ought to give us enough
time what'd you do with my groceries
Vince yourself not to get the demo would
you listen yourself oh you're right I'm
stupid yeah well I don't know just
seeing myself in the past ought to cause
enough of a tangent to change all of it
and he's making up physics as he goes
along I guess I'll have to bike home
from the grocery store we only met
because of the transfer
Lisa I want to see women from other
centuries Lisa I slipped some artichokes
into your cart
Oh as chin but is engulfing her where is
your tongue right now because I seem to
have to Eddie I bet you've done this a
lot after you bet every day um should
the sky have trees and houses and be
rushing right towards us sure if you let
me out of the half-nelson let's go let's
buy more plaid
I'm willing to settle
cool Zubaz faces okay we're here I like
pie track meet is starting and starting
and starting and starting few hundred
time jankis that was a big bug Wow yeah
they thought I was a good chicken head
oh god no stop got to take my coke out
of the freezer
running out of alt and their myth knots
are going down can't get my umbrella
open
sir I'm a little worried about lunch
it's almost 1230 should open the window
before I snagged
it's a ir the tiger to do too
he went so far back in the past he
wasn't flight certified yet
rich guy look nice let's go
he's going to land on escal as his head
arcineh burst broke by Lisa hope
everything works out
ah great scenery a crappy movie man I
got shrinkage it oh wait that's normal
sorry Edward shit get the gaff Wally
yesterday they're none too soon anybody
else Abby what oh dude
ah
taking all your wax worms buddy this is
as good as any fine film gold bond
medicated powder that is good the movie
really heightens the lack of interest in
the film I took huh hey John Oates know
Michael met dead
that's an illumise I can't do it
can't do it Jake it was moving in fast I
couldn't get a big wad you were part of
the team that doesn't mean I'm a good
shot and you guys such a jerk he brought
a bag and zebra mussels toss him
overboard hey that Moss is taking a
liking to that tree hey what'd I say
about ponds to jam them up by that's
right okay hey I don't tell him anymore
he must've made the tree it's very lucky
man so where were you now that's on the
head of a fortune 500 company what's in
the future and in the past Yeah right I
have control of the situation he doesn't
have to get rid of this one hey Miami
Beach yeah man I wet every bit of me
look oh if only he were between a mother
grizzly and her cub right now let's see
I could kill me hollow me out and live
in me what about his grandpa oh no Mama
logs with poopy pants please yeah so
he's my past self doesn't give the demo
for the transport told Robertson this
kids don't work you hear that squirrels
and bunnies bunnies the hell's here for
tonight on a very special episode of
family Kristy McNichol goes for a bike
ride
it's weird with the training wheels off
you ought to get a real big sissy bar
what's the hockey hair please Oh Phyllis
Diller is cooking again whoo hey
children of the corn hi Artie drinking
fuel straight from the tap party but I
wasn't playing Sun City what's that I
don't know some government genCorp
they're looking for something what thing
I don't know but the really serious
check
let's go build the homecoming float
and finish my column Mabel torgeson was
the guest of the Elven Johnson's on
Thursday nights juice and lemon bars
were served Lauren tweeze in absence of
malice I know I'm on my way to find
grandmother no we're dumping it what
plane crash over they've gone as a class
in yourself just came over the box maybe
with the grandmother just get over there
hey wait a minute hot Conde Jeff and
Terry our unemployment visit grandma
gets injured loz dead grandma pictures
they bring in the readers
my own 27 minutes it's pretty good
master disguise
does its Prefontaine or post Fontaine
fellows like to buy some maple syrup if
he's gonna run he better put vaseline
all over his nipples great i'm gonna buy
some little snaps on a hosta I've always
wanted a ten you go wait the klutz kind
of sticks and one door doesn't close and
you gotta jiggle it to get it into
reverse oh whoa yeah I did that on my
first driver's test they're still kind
of drunk from the night before we also
raise llamas if you'd like to bet a
llama it drive like a Kennedy you idiot
I don't drive you got a dead alien in
the Attic okay
haha so it's bicycles then a we accept
your choice of vehicle I'm god this is a
very healthy chase well just give you a
warning this time Oh a k-car come right
through ma'am she's doing caricatures of
the victims you kidding we'll be lucky
if we get dental records how many were
on board yeah looks like just one any
idea how old can you tell how stale
bread is if it's been posted you make on
a plane yeah wait a minute who are you
I'm with the banner my name is Lisa
Hampton and I'm a hard-boiled reporter
well from the numbers we got it looks
like it belongs to Nick Miller came up
in that airport across the way yeah
she's a really good actress yeah you're
right it he's shut up she is now here
look at that kid sorry I think the
cameramen shy come on honey you can get
closer come on along dad Billy there
Nick really this is the most incredible
thing great so what's the next step well
like I said I'm going to go over the
heads of my bosses and take this
directly to jay kay robertson when well
i'll be back with mr. Robertson that uh
dork 34 p.m. is that ok fine I'll be
ready great great or and it's in the
meantime don't tell anyone about this
and I mean anyone trust me on this okay
all right great we are going to be very
rich
dig dig diggity pedo pedo pedo
when really short guys try to walk oh
yeah the throaty roar of a cake are they
somehow gave her plaid theme music mr.
black will put her on his please kill
list
alright we finally gonna see some
horizontal rumba or what hey Lisa Nick I
shaved this morning and got a nick all
right get up here golly Edward okay he's
fine for the banner in town now I was
called to your graphic arms off at her
playing crossed over by the lake what
what are you talking about yeah it
exploded on impact I'm sorry I thought
you would have heard by now Lisa my
current parents died when you and I were
kids that's right but you called the
paper I was just trying to get someone
to come out take a look at this claim is
registered to you it was one of your
plane but lisa i only own one jar of
mustard one plane registration numbers n
505 b c okay
after the
we listen now to the Jefferson middle
school string quartet yep grandma came
back from the dead built a duplicate
plane and crashed it what's going on
it's time chatha we need to take a
little trip we need to go out for some
Amish fudge be nice walking on broken
glass
what did you get the pound cisco kid who
was a friend of mine it's really good at
he you would like that with war remember
when everyone got the Nick Miller
haircut and started wearing castleton
t-shirts miss the barn dance well seems
you forgot you were in the past y'all
varmints say you like Northwest go ahead
your drug dealer you're busy this isn't
it mm-hmm yes but the more you could
afford all this stuff on a picture Sally
electronics waiter look Marty I don't
know how to tell you this you know but
we got a serious problem right here I'm
here well gentlemen take a bite of this
century look leave Marty here he doesn't
know what's going sorry knows enough to
disrupt your past self
it kills I'm gonna make you a part of
history that a sexual overture of some
kind look at too many 7s in that date
I'm going on for us okay do that Eddie
hitting play you do that oh mah friends
Robin lowriders hey Morty let's do lunch
Morty Wow the present is amazing that
was absolutely incredible party it's me
your cousin saw where's the phone Marty
let's get some blintzes Marty Marty ill
bacon grease good call ok there Eddie
slow as they are they should have a
dental record matched for an ID by now I
have got a demo who jen call in two
hours and he's probably out getting
drunk somewhere yeah this is leave the
Hanson of the banner we're doing a story
on the plane crash I was wondering if
heading out beyond the pilot yet yes
with the band it was the chopper news
yeah that's me no this isn't a joke
myrtle johnson didn't serve lemon bars
you sure I should have checked my
sources ah
thank you
they watch the boys gonna hit her in the
can when he comes in that'll be great
well the person they identified as being
killed in the plane crash was Darrell
dragon was Lisa henchman of the band oh
well that's a big loss good well then
fall down
hey the New England Patriots someday a
lot of puffy old losers with no lives
will reenact this battle then Eddie
you're going into battle in that outfit
Ted Nugent's family reunion just try to
go Harry we're not watching dr. Demento
Patriot oh good thing the Minutemen
built a runway
General Washington's plane has landed
are going to the company picnic damn it
listen I understand limit Mac but this
has to be done to wipe the slate clean
they'll just be unaccounted war dead
here no I know but I can't be a part of
it I'll wait back at the transport if
you want me to sorry genkai that's all
right I can handle this myself I'll see
you back at the transport in a minute
okay okay there goes a damn good weenie
Oh Matt and I changed my mind you're
fired it's still a better boss on the
Sunbeam guy now what were we talking
about ah yes history put that weapon
down Oh huzzah I think I'm not sure whoa
minutemen correction they are pissed
Minutemen be sons I'm not believing this
I told him the truth Robertson the truth
they know you're a spy working for the
British and they aren't letting you out
of his fourth don't play games with your
life Nick this is an Uzi you're
outgunned sidebar so history is just
circling the drain at this point I guess
and so children the British defeated us
because they were all helping this lunk
head whizzed history down his leg I
don't think they ever seen a nosy no
place to run Johnny CEO CFO sold
separately my god iso 9001 certification
as a license to kill we were getting
poison sumac we the seven ammo clips of
highly effective people all right let's
go Hey look at this mess from last night
I thought I told you to clean this up
well gee Eddie I did Eddie but but but
these are just from a couple of minutes
ago don't you remember hey shut up okay
I'm shutting up right away yet around
away that your head huh servo Edward I'm
going to rinse out a few things I'll be
back in a minute just don't get that guy
and the other way around you like him
greetings young Mike my name is crow and
I've come from the future to help you
change your miserable dead-end life hey
robot from the future there's another
one of you guys to see you hey me oh hey
me can you hang on a second so anyway
Mike that's why I think no we screwed
something up royal didn't we well you
screwed something up royal oh really how
do you know it's not you who screwed it
up look I'm for about a half hour into
your future I think I know a little bit
more about what the heck is going on
than you do listen mr. future pants off
I steer Mike away from a career of bad
jobs he'll never end up stranded in time
and space well listen mr. half hour ago
do if you do Mike will end up bludgeon
in a pool of his own blood oh yeah and
what are you guys hey Mike this doesn't
concern you okay look don't change my
future or he dies okay
I see yeah it's about time ooh I gotta
get back man was like a jerk a half hour
ago oh um Mike hi forget what i was
saying forget your band it's going
nowhere stick to a life of menial
low-paying jobs okay that's cool good
thanks so much for the frame river for
me does everyone have corn Dodgers and
pemmican so they were playing splat ball
one day and they just decided to make a
movie a pillsbury corporate retreat goes
bad you're running out of Carnegie
actual he's got the whole North American
wilderness no covered by the way I thank
you yet I think he was the Tony Danza of
its time
you can see a character's eye boogers
you're too close have you been
I don't know how to downsize these
people and all that guy's just a pirate
or my grandma's hat what do you think
hey karate instructors
we all borrow their wives blouses for
this movie whose woods these are have no
clue damn child safety lock t you guys
alright man who's this ugly jerk thanks
I'm welcome listen she's got the demo
destroy the transport I know you know
sure I got a transport to are you seeing
the same in the split-screen all right
Lisa oh god it's good to see look I
don't like you and I don't like you
either or um well you grope everyone I
guess we better get to cover we got to
stop Robertson before he gets to that
transport wait a minute what about Lisa
she's ditching us what about her won't
you and heard me and her we oh yeah she
discovered your plane crash I know that
she was on the plane with you yeah I
know but you too we uh what are you
trying to say no he's trying to ask
himself out it's not important well come
on man God my butt looks weird in those
pants let's get to Barney's for a new
shirt
you guys see the game last night I mean
Liberty never chase a wounded executive
into the woods and our forefathers were
dumpy
what's gonna become of gender I'm gonna
facilitate connectivity our young
nation's first spaz attack party right
come on come on relax will you okay come
into the light it's crazy guns be chancy
you go clean the guns and uses and the
bullets fly at your head what you want
and I'll be right over here relaxing
done come back everybody fuck yeah yeah
screw the revolution run a lot of
general milling around in the
revolutionary war / castleton
look that was Robertson LaVon 10 quits
my sights young executive off he makes
it to a transport this is all for
nothing use me general I'm a left-tenant
well Oh what are you general dung beetle
I i think they oversold the weather at
Valley Forge it's a little chilly is all
Treva through wet leaves on the fire
like a big plastic things holding their
feet together I'm not back drop party
off in the present here's some
predigested food for you what is kiss
yeah this slips on microfiche in her
mouth oh please hijacking yeah they
study this battle of military colleges
well unaccredited military colleges and
malls next to hair salons right whatever
well I suppose all their bags say let
bagon them dude the good news I got to
get to that star cept meeting he's
enjoying the new active lifestyle with
his new hair
see if I can get Tetris on this oh oh oh
he's wearing cuff yeah so right now they
are breathing the air around Tom Paine
technically yeah still in da Oh will be
due to the unusually high volume of time
transfers your routing huh and it's all
over good
when I chased you in a horse and
supposed to win Oh God
there's a man on the wing in the plane
wanna fly let's fly I got a million of
them guitar
this is just like the end of mahogany
hey oh I'm supposed to be sad
screenplay by Nigel Calder and jim
Varney
aha unlucky for you I secrete pine tar
from my hands
oh I haven't the strength or the screen
presence to pull this off look he
doesn't want you in there except it oh
why am i doing that that's my hand check
your flaps before taking off time
87 pays at a clock
thanks stephen hawking's zero two four
three two one two three two one two one
what up well better start drinking my
urine someone garnished him with parsley
it's nice oh if I could only fart I'd
feel better 47 Keebler elves were killed
today when a light plane plunged into
their tree PL fudge remains in critical
condition must sail but of my pants is
um is he ki rock now is that how that
works yeah oh no no no we don't show his
body come on by damn tree hugger maybe
he'll be torn apart by Ewoks oh he's
trying to get honey like poo no he's
like poo all right so what did the tree
contribute money to the film why are
they showing this he's climbing an aunt
Hong oh I see it's man against machine
come on machine kazoo machine Joe Joe go
go a machine Oh Benjamin Franklin's kite
is up there George Washington is trying
to chop the tree down to make wooden
teeth Thomas Jefferson is down there
making time with a slave oh thank you
movie but we'd like to move on please
Oh Spielberg stole that bit for Jurassic
Park he should use his chin as a Pete on
good Kerri Strug oh good he's all
stained again why did the movie just
cover him in cat vomit jockeys scooting
hey Nick there was a stairs on the other
side of the tree I have a severe injury
to my sleeve oh man it's my boss oh man
it's a guy from R&D ah Nick I have an
aileron up might well anyway you should
have just left this one alone son sorry
dad lay still be alive you did mean a
man out the both of you lived to a ripe
old age escape to some simpler time in
the past it never would have affected
you know I wish uncooked liver than the
star of this movie you still don't get
it do you Kevin Spacey was Keyser Soze
it would have it would have affected the
rest of the world who the fuck we're all
connected you fool you me nipsey Russell
Ruth Bader Ginsburg chesty Morgan
everything connect me to this
oh well thank you movie yeah appreciate
it he died as he lived mud-stained and
splaying he's dead but don't worry they
have a spare now they make love
a giant fingerprint run there's the
movies funders come to pull the plug
later in the prom I took Sally to the
airport and showed her the tarmac oh wow
jump back kiss myself is here I think
it's snap and a half of it went over a
hill lucky you I'll be right back
Michael Keaton damn good prom honey Nick
haha Nick Nick Nick Nick Nick appendix
make my deck I'd like to introduce you
to jay kay robertson mr. Robertson this
is Nick Miller the next Edison what I'll
wait a minute that's a bit line we think
so JK will you get a load of this Nick
why don't you take it from here okay mr.
Robertson are you trying to seduce me
can i call you JK fine can i call you
dickweed JK we've been watching your
television commercials for years and
well frankly it's time for a change what
Nick stay with me on this one map though
we'd like to present you with a brand
new marketing idea Marty she ready she's
ready let's bring her out thank you
chuckle hut middle act who thought this
was his big break JK i'd like to present
you with some soiled pants Gilda Heinz
starvin OU gen core television
commercials 80 years old in a
world-class skydiver baby we see her
everywhere across the entire logo all of
your t-shirts all of your merchants I
don't go out here what's the matter you
love this idea five hours ago Robbie up
here for this no sir no sir this point
this plane can travel through time you
just wait until you see how this
electronic equipment your junk won't on
your fire behind your old right back to
them okay what the hell you don't you I
should've gone with a skydiving dog
right one time good but you don't
understand this thing I hate what I'm
reading you I'm Batman
Oh Oh terrible gas today oh you had the
misfortune of running into me I'm a life
wrecking idiot he's been shooting this
time well that's true roof roof crawl
into a saltine box to do the ADR andrew
wyeth's pink boy on tarmac my name is
Nick no no no my name is Stephanie and I
am a 17 year old girl and listen so
eight five and a quarter inch floppies
hold the keys to time travel sure you
want to do this yes delete copies of
film yes delete memory of film for
mankind's consciousness yes well he
retains the knowledge he should kill
himself mm-hmm what did I ever see in
these things she's I don't even declared
war on a surge protector
it's been a long week time for a big
bowl of Dijonnaise please eat me maple
syrup three for a dollar oh he'll just
take it it's free we got so much of it
now I'll put these in a ziploc let them
get brown in my fridge hmm these aren't
plaid
yes yes i do need care
this kotaro playing in the dairy case
sale on romaine lettuce
ah well this is a nice shot I like this
better than the other ones is good yeah
we serve a delicious brunch every Sunday
who's playing the chamber pot as you
Paul Oh pink boy yeah right George water
does Jacob watching over this was
written I don't think so walking down
walking on walking on broken glass oh oh
I'll kiss go back and I'm broken glass
you see dude should really stop doing
that done yeah it hurts whoo-wee demo
button on little keyboard hit by tonight
Mel Tillis plays at the SAS SAS ihara
lounge
executive parents I mean producers
Wow look at that what a great name
Heather killing back I'd rather have it
be Heather killing paula cole boomer i
have a feeling craig boomer buzz al is
the only one who calls himself boomer
now by the way speaking of the
revolutionary war and all that but
whatever happened to that whole deal
with the Spanish aren't they supposed to
take over oh yeah you know what I think
they ended up getting molten gold poured
down and throws it just didn't work out
shame really Spaniard to them whiz it
down their legs huh Jim yes oh good
evening I'm observed tomorrow night at
seven she's a Wiccan she's a nun ken two
sisters share an apartment together
tomorrow night find out on which is
which but coming up next several
neighborhood kittens are alarmed by very
loud noises that's coming up next on
observer eyewitness news Frank I get
your pale butt over here yes pearl be
with you in a moment double that funny
mica sometimes i use my nearly humna
patent powers just to have a little
giggle I think you have to laugh every
once in a while even if it's just
occurred I'll be right safe or something
oh man anyway I hope that I've made you
laugh mica sure that I did hmm shall I
think I didn't know what dope she could
see your faces in their room
could have come across just as an idiot
I suppose I'd be mortified anyway I'm
sorry Mike this was ridiculous i get up
goodbye stupid stupid oh it's pretty
insecure and weird man oh i thought
which is which sounds good i might have
to check that out sounds like i don't
know must-see TV damn it i must see it
i'm off says so getting back to the
movie who do they think this would
appeal to anyway elderly squirrels or
who without heads toadstools clumps of
dirt maybe a barber poles the coffee
tables for heads of material to break
off plastic trays and use napkins
italians maybe row what little off the
point there oh I'm sorry I see what
you're saying Germans knows what they
are special thinking that hell out of
these people huh all these people bear
some responsibility which means I really
really hate the citizens and officials
of rutland vermont I'm not kidding Mike
I never liked the citizens and officials
of stupid rutland vermont this is just a
nail in the coffin as far as I'm
concerned go to hell citizens and
officials of rutland vermont filmed in
vermont the other smaller Wisconsin
nasty cool
oh boy what a day huh uh yeah whatever
say Mike if there was a guy named
Gilligan and he wanted to name an island
after himself and he did and then we
were here on it what would we be here ah
no no no what do you mean no I just know
I'm sorry why a little buddy wait benny
didn't say it yet oh sorry now well Mike
come on if we were here on that island
what would we be here on come on just
know I'm sorry but no well don't now
what doesn't he have to say it I mean of
course he has to say it it's not real
unless he says it I mean I know you're
right he anyone would happen if he
didn't say it and we just went ahead
anyway I mean oh no no no I'm not
suggesting that there's nothing we can
do about it don't those are the rules
well sorry but no Shh so how was the
movie Oh would hurt hurdle oh good good
well in general the movies do hurt quite
a bit actually you know Mike that is so
great to hear because to tell you the
truth I don't get a lot of direct
feedback so so thank you that means a
lot welcome you know I'm just telling
the truth hey crow went back in time
really yeah yeah he went back to
Wisconsin 1985 to try to talk me out of
the temp job that put me in your evil
clutches oh yeah he succeeded actually
and then another CRO had to go back and
try to talk that curl out of talking me
out of taking the jobs a big mess when
we go hmm so what happened to the other
crow what's here
well think about it somewhere there's a
spare crow running around in Wisconsin
in 1985 right no well no well yeah huh
well cheese ain't gonna cut itself on
dude
Oh
bad time for you to decide if you're
gonna be one of my team plank