you creepy and never let you take me
complete something
[Applause]
No
you know it's a crazy
please
[Music]
you at the hotel for the ferry drop off
yep down to an eccentric popular tourist
spot
better for I you know half of people get
into the shot
there's a bar around here the food's
done right we didn't see the sheriff is
possible check in and get all this
[Music]
morning neighbor Jesus Christ Lucas is
gonna shut down this week he'd stop
sneaking up on people you're starting to
creep them out Lizzie he's a cutie it
fuck you want you called me shit all
right is that our message today dad is
nothing with good news here said fuck
Lucas you need to control yourself yeah
and just what are you or anybody else
going to do about that stuff last time I
checked you can't control your wife and
that city you're still is it straight
about what we do here come on your own
goddamn backyard your weak spot don't
just
we can ditch everyone go to be bring a
blanket it wasn't even explaining how i
got sand all over me okay we my dad
bought that I'm starting to think they
know what we do actually I don't my dad
would be way too pissed not to say
anything I'm more worried about your mom
and dad what's to worry about my mom
he's cool is it for sure and my dad
don't know lately seem distracted just
walking away from me yeah he's got a lot
on his mind is that film crew coming and
I haven't really uptight about that for
some rerun yeah here's something special
princess the beach something really take
me by surprise oh maybe I hope you think
it's a good rest to you but you always
come up different and good fam
[Music]
I had no fucking idea there were no
pictures well this is the only vote on
the island oh I can help you hi we have
a reservation for two rooms right the
phone crew the Ryerson's and miss Cain
was it oh I'm headed over to the card if
you see last week's find an open
customer
I'm sorry okay with the cash or credit
card usually we stay where we leave we
require you pay out franceour okay okay
alright we have three for the Ryerson
and room 24 April Cain you guys need to
give me a call thanks my son Sam I hope
he is your bag BAM hi hi step 4 yeah oh
thank you song a fug April we're going
to meet at the bar for drinks at seven
Stace you gotta go meet the church all
right room whatever sheer of course hand
I know this is not the marriott or
anything but uh if you need to melt look
for me my dad's almost never here cool
Sam thanks dude thanks much folks have a
good visit this place is an absolute
shit off I don't know if I can sleep in
this bad hum that is even worse what the
hell hey what this is staying near the
very peculiar Oh put the shower oh let
us take a shower a few showers box
oh well I'm going to make the best of it
I'm trying to get clean Hey brillion
here is nasty yes you Polly hello Jacob
how can I help you prepare a message
today what message oh right there's
always a payday alright when do we start
as soon as possible I let Hydra know he
was overjoyed of course when he
absolutely had to know don't you think
we're just better off without him it's
for timely John Lucas has a temperament
for it hey you know where we are on this
right this new girls our best chance
otherwise there's only one person left
you know I'll do whatever I have to to a
point see I keep my word but not my
Brooks Jacob well ty first I know John
we're all men do our best Amy
ah
welcome down their Island I'm sheriff 3
you're the Ryerson film crew we share
thanks to meet you share it my pleasure
it's not a good time to talk about
shooting schedule nylons well yeah you
pretty much can shoot anywhere you want
but beware the filing can throw people
they get lost and we've had a few
instances where it'll get back I can
come by tomorrow noon you conduct that
interview I gotta be honest I don't have
a lot to tell you yeah but as we
discussed you can go a squeaking Stein
he's the owner of the island well he's
actually the owner of the hotel you're
staying at so I'll see you tomorrow noon
very great all right there's more sure
appreciate my pleasure Thank You sheriff
Oh have a good day you folks be careful
out in the woods
honey you need a lot more than that
something yes 15 on the silent they can
imagine there was no forensic technology
is an old Native would if I was doing my
research I invariably had to go to the
local haider to get anything even a
single on the mainland attack list about
this place some of my heaven seems to
suggest that the reason everyone this
show closed off to outsiders is that the
ironies actually have had a hand some
successfully taking place of use by
someone stopping by Broadway
[Music]
the winning side families mentioned here
whores on the hotel and uncomfortable
isn't it this Reverend really lived here
coming to me indeed he did leave him God
will decide if he lives or dies it's
over Reverend you and yours want to
answer for the murder of Han Schultz
come out peacefully and surrender he's
pushed them too far my love no my dear
wife I haven't pushed them enough and
now they need to arrest me without
justification for their sins see it
through their eyes it will be days
before the mainlanders can get here the
boys and I will gather the flock and set
things right but not a faded into shoes
[Music]
show them that you are better that yours
is the way of truth and the rest of the
congregation will follow no one will
oppose you then my wife you were still
wise
[Music]
you leavin you will pay for this I will
tear out your heart like you tore mine
your family will never happen
that would explain why I didn't have any
followers reaching from fears never lost
its appeal oh look at the time I look I
yeah I have to go meet with some locals
I will be back let's get together for a
drink share some stories I'll be back
later for that drink sounds good you
later night professor hi professor
you Billy had seemed legit some of it
makes the families on this island a
little inbred Diggins for April hungry
yeah yeah me too
we're in April after 70 he had a lot of
sign the restaurant this is a restaurant
it is to restaurant / bar so those
office what hold answer your question no
I'm just taking a nap cover a few more
minutes then we'll give her a call
she'll never forgive us if she misses
dinner okay you guys I'm totally
freaking out right now open I swear I
just saw something in my bathroom come
on April don't lose on us now no i'm not
i was just in there I mean are you both
sufficiently disgusted by our lodging
circumstances that was the grossest
shower I have ever taken till dirtier
now than I did before April don't be
scared me my god what of it what is it
not funny he's being a jackass there's
something on you okay time to plate that
yeah Ned come on there's bad enough yeah
met and we're hungry let's order huh the
restaurants too and a post office
how I folks couldn't take your order we
haven't seen the menu yet future selves
there's no this one things we got
chicken tenders little piece of beer and
hard liquor
the rest of that menu stop being remade
okay can you give us a second thank you
chicken fingers for me I guess boom take
the little pizza and a shot and a beer
that's a beer for me too
oh okay to the drinks you folks decide
what you want yeah tours of chicken
fingers one pizza three beers and shut
up jack it'll be about an hour now
microwave food
I
Ariel
okay open a tab for us hey how are you
Mike hippie friends what makes you think
I'm a hippie captain my own ship looks
fucking fewer than that I'm just making
conversation you look like one no not a
hippie it's nothing wrong with that is
there yes there is a bunch of free
loving assholes doing drugs and
generally being weak human beings like
Manson he was a hippie to ice no not
like Manson you make very fucking
mansion launceston but at least he had a
plan you just fucked it up that the
hippie in a box it up
all right yeah cool man well you have a
good night too where there is love
Jesus just please cleared out faster
it's for other people shit Paisley here
you go to bed April you guys are it now
can't believe I got this drunk oh come
on one more no no fuck no I'm going to
bed cascade let's go come on damn i do i
stayed out here too long
ah
[Music]
the focus okay
[Applause]
[Music]
oh baby no birth control fuck would you
say
[Music]
no this will not
you cannot rush
those are my own
[Music]
ah
[Applause]
[Music]
so young so sweet you beg me you give me
so much more than I gave you it is not
fair to make me wait 20 years now my
father's no one left on is the island
week motherfuckers don't make it tough
on its Lucas tell me it whispers back
you waited fine I do all the hard work
on this island phonology do is get some
good night well I'm ready for this time
so this has been your job for the past
20 years just about and how many unusual
deaths have occurred here since then boy
maybe seven to ten and what about the
tales of the Reverend keen on this
island do you think that the deaths
could have anything to do with that
every time I hear that story I just have
to chuckle I mean island king king of
home well his followers who supposedly
gunned him down and stories gotta be at
least 150 years old I was talking with a
professor more
and not only did he claim that the
legends were true but he also inferred
that some of the natives on this island
have seen the Reverend presents more
than once over the past century do you
have any comment on that Sheriff look
there is no connection between the dust
and the Reverend as an old Native tail
and it's ridiculous you know this has
been a good time but I got to get back
to work okay well thank you sheriff you
did a great job you know there's a lot
of crazy stories about the silent some
true most not you know somebody
embellishes an old tale and credited to
the natives you got just off the truth
it's true people can I believe what they
want to believe so it's also true if you
look too deep into this you're gonna
find more you bargained for you folks
have a safe stay you can let yourselves
out
[Music]
there
it is believed that some of the families
on the island have been paired up the
horrendous crimes that have been
committed heidegger ree and the wicked
selling can't be real he really needed
that air view was that the sheriff guy
one minute he was fine and then the next
minute is freaking out did you start
talking about the Reverend wasn't it
forever ago I don't know maybe one of
his ancestors was involved I don't know
why are you so adamant that it had
nothing to do with the islands history
you've already been asking him that did
you misunderstand the question or were
we insinuating it may be well let's not
worry about it when we get back we'll
just look at the footage holy shit
okay okay I got it don't let it touch
anything
thank you folks get the hell out of here
sheriff sheriff okay we saw the body the
woods we think it's a friend professor
more take it easy take a deep breath now
tell me what you saw we're pretty sure
it was bad but who did that who
definitely is that that does not sound
good why don't you show me follow me
then they shot the rebbe family now I
mean we got here how could he not know
about this hey listen don't get me wrong
the fam I believe you
right there's more my dad said he'd tell
me later God we have to go up this
island
I know how crazy all this sounds another
plan to get us out actually I've had two
players I shouldn't always use it oh you
have been winning New York hang on alien
her menagerie I know so I picked it we
can leave sunday night on a theory how
many just going to disappear I'm working
on
so this is just how you found my median
touch them or take anything off the body
no that's uh that's how we left him
what's bad
I'll have to get you folks back into
town so suddenly got a lot of work to do
Jesus Christ you guys I signed up to be
in the documentary not deal with this
crazy shit I've never seen anything like
that before we haven't either I really
want to get out of here I know you do
April with two way to the boat back
tonight when I have to try tomorrow I
just never seen a dead body before I
don't know if I can take this i'm going
to go go back to my room and lay down if
you guys go anywhere you promise and
you'll come get me right I'm sure
I want to finish is just as bad as you
do but something does not feel right
Plus April didn't sign on for this this
was an accident his leg got caught in a
trap in an animal got him if we're
careful if you say so again that doesn't
feel right we need to get out of here oh
come on they warned us about those woods
over and over again he should have been
out there by himself I don't think he
would want us to give up this easily
this is his work lately I think he was
murdered I saw the body up close no
animal does that his head would cut
clean off is Oliver cut clean off there
wasn't a bite mark on him plus his
fucking heart was ripped out I would
have told you sooner but I've been
trying to process it myself it doesn't
feel right we need to get the hell out
of here
[Music]
looks like pumping out to the body
someone he was half apart Heidegger did
you contact the mainland authorities not
a chance good still believe in control
of them
going out
raw the hell are all the men I've been
asking myself that question for a year
oh man so what you haven't really um I
don't know got any tequila thanks did
not know so we have one with me okay all
right nice you like worms sure you ready
for this oh yeah well gonna say that oh
yeah Chris the burn
ok I can't go back to the hotel it was
so creepy I can see
Wow I don't know why i like how buzzer
the bed wait look hey too much
stay here like a leave no no no no no
your God time to go I got close up now
I'm on girlie hey you're talking
abi-maria you tomorrow see
[Music]
hello Maria fucking in here which your
husband should have long ago now let's
see if we can find some niceness on the
inside
you
[Music]
hey
Johnny wait you weren't planning on
we're gonna get real
[Music]
Sam you want some breakfast damn where
you going you right back mom I don't
know you know your mom April April you
in there the hell is she
so fucked up we gotta find her swim the
chef
hey nice backpack is that new yeah my
folks she's got it for me oh how you
doing this morning bud it far so good
you look a little worried man and I'll
tell you what there's much to be nervous
in this world about and friends of
family aren't two of them and we are
friends and family Hey look don't get
too agitated you stick with us and we'll
stick with you right sure dad yeah bad
boy you're gonna get along just great so
you're looking for Brooke yeah I was
actually just head over there hop in
he sounds hi dad I was gonna get some
ice cream honest if you come off he's
not cool with you dad sure sweetheart
peplum look after my girl fan you're not
gonna believe
you
oh my god I got on the woods it was that
professors on staying at the hotel what
does mean think I get a lot worse well
if it isn't the island club oh my you
have grown into a beautiful woman you're
lucky boy fan I wanted you to tell your
father that I took care of April you
know such a pleasure to you i would like
to deliver more messages to you in the
future
treasure like you have nice TV Sam
I contacted the mainland sheriff's
office and I reported you fighting the
professor's body we're starting to
should be sure if it doesn't have to do
with that we can't find April please
have a seat a cute little girl you came
in with when's the last time you saw her
last night we waited for to come down
for breakfast but she never showed up in
return she wasn't there is it possible
that you still sleep no go check where
is empty time to get this hello sure re
here where the fuck is Maria John how
the hell am I supposed to know she's
your wife fuck you John I know what's up
I'm seen her all day I come home last
night already fine i'll be over soon
look I know you're just concerning what
you saw here with all due respect we've
already had one person died and they you
honestly think there were two killings
in two nights Wow look why don't you two
go look for your friend it's a small
town and she go missing for hours and if
you don't find your by six you come back
here and see me Oh keep an eye out leave
a message your hotel if I hear anything
okay Thank You sheriff of course you
folks be careful now hi darlin what's on
your mind girl mr. Heidegger just spoke
to me good yeah just now he said that
you would know what he meant if I told
you that April had been taken care of
who
Jesus Christ he's gonna screw this whole
thing up after noon sharp Jacob okay
good for you cut the shit you got the
girl in there what but I have time for
games Lucas she's not of your concern
I've moved your lovely daughter it was
taken care of let's not forget your
Brooke may be our last hope don't
mention my daughter don't you look at my
daughter my daughter doesn't exist doc
let him go
nor he is until chair army
Lucas are you done what had to be done I
shouldn't have to explain myself to you
she could have been the one you fool you
put us all at right now I dealt with it
she was way too much of a whore for him
he'd had never taken her besides now she
can't go back and start asking question
everyone is off limits to you nobody
would start asking anything at all if
you just let it be where's the body
fucking lost I mean I'll chop some body
into little pieces and buries its next
to train us a psychopath that's so we
all know Lucas is Delta some kind of
doubt that's unnecessary and enjoys we
need to have a serious talk with them
good
where's Mario no room in this place for
an adultress I can't believe them my
folks have anything to do with it I'm
shaking up I could if you complete
website he did I have is awful three you
about each Issa would say something I'm
gonna do tonight I have to run a couple
okay spend the rest of the day getting
some stuff only the most important stuff
wait your dad's agostic is together
pretty Stefan want to put back for a
trip tonight off into the dock
hey Joe which is actually better today
[Music]
you can do this watch and listen I'll do
the same maybe we can get some Emperor
my help I mean a couple but don't tell
me you gonna try you later Beecher no
sign of April anywhere now no sure I
can't fucking believe this island has no
cell service how many
you find April yes I found her body how
about sitting for the day that's what
I'm telling you what the hell is going
on here that has to be wrong you need to
explain this to a sheriff yeah we're
responsible for her Sheriff hey I warned
you about the woods these things happen
you might want to watch it here mr.
Ryerson don't you make my job any harder
you to get back to your room and wait
for my call this whole mess could be
over for you come on look Nikki goes
don't leave anything behind like her
what did you mail out of here you're the
shit out of me so we're willing to see
you then
oh hell man i'm here help this is you
see okay okay okay he's also going to
get off it we don't know if you know we
are how was that that's great but you
have to take me my girlfriend with you
we don't know anyone in the manor and we
helping forget you I'm calling back you
get off this island spam you have no
worries don't worry granted you going
we're taught everything up we'll meet
you up for 10 minutes 10 minutes okay i
get my girlfriend do you think I'll be
right back okay okay
folks plan on checking out
[Music]
I used to go now grab some stuff quick
we're gonna leave the Ryerson yeah
there's your thing a dodo did another
woman with him she's gone gone there I
don't think I want to know excuse
doesn't get out here really sorry about
this folks thank you you think we're
worried about prosecution I can't speak
for the sheriff here but I'd gladly go
to jail so what I've learned this town
has something on you sheriff for
Christ's sakes what the hell is going on
you know it was a reason I've been here
for 20 years one day many years ago I
came home and found my wife in bed and
no she wasn't alone he was my best
fucking friend I took matters into my
own hands they're both gone now I moved
here it became part of the family could
say the reef and was part of the
original deal I changed my name I became
an Islander and my daughter and his son
quite close
relax the Reverend was not overly cool
the Reverend what the fuck are you guys
talking about some Reverend going around
killing people you mean d Reverend from
the legend you know it doesn't matter
how you see him he's always been here
Reverend kill them all in one way or the
other and we have to help them you see
the original families on this island
we're all cursed we're century and a
half ago our families worked on an
agreement with the Reverend maybe even
my family's in pain forever since
agreement to put you where you are now
this Reverend came to my ancestor Peter
William Stein's house very night is
resurrected from the grave I told him
that we were to find him a new wife to
rebuild his family when the time came I
know it seems hard to understand believe
me it it's total insanity if you aren't
living it our families had no choice
Reverend become something inhuman and an
unreal
so freaked and the rest of you are
responsible for April and the
professor's death that's so directly
this time but you can say we all took
part in some way I just can't tell
anymore well oh no no no like this like
this cutter like that okay I hate and go
let's go let's go let's go ahead look at
all by doing your hangover 3 Roz we're
going you know must be here all right
stay here move the car if anyone comes
quickly come back be fast
oh they're going we're taking mean we
have to go to the wood yes she can i
remove / you okay okay you're driving
now yeah yeah tomorrow right are you
kidding me back up with ours right
that's the thing i said i was asking you
to make sure oh my god
[Music]
think about what you're feeling Figgis
it was a long time ago what does it even
matter they buried the river on graves
island for the Indians bury their dead
for centuries nobody knows why you came
back to life oh my god what happened
where'd they go get up you wuss yes I'm
a bitch
[Applause]
[Music]
I never let anything like you happen to
Mike Brooke your death means nothing to
me
[Music]
Daniel save your own soul eater holy
shit okay okay keeps having the marina
oh my god or maybe we'll keep on shuttle
place we can take my family closer all
we have to do is give it a dock before
they do the boats more doing the teacher
name don't forget all the docs we're
good we get stuck you
we'll just don't forget you promised
that once we get to the mainland it
would help us and not just this when we
get there you would never dream of using
price you could stay with us as long as
you want Sam you goes out of your
mission I'll build you get stuff like
go
her
back get back her fucking barbecue fuck
you you're kill my god you're fucking it
we're both dead now yeah probably are
you haven't got a charge
[Music]
[Laughter]
and last the simple is blinkin I've
waited for so long the reckoning has
finally come for you all I'm not peer
you know what to do with you I'd like
you to thank your son for me but
unfortunately that's not gonna be
possible
[Music]
you
and
[Music]
ah
[Applause]
you