[Music]
ok
you can't find that you create just go
to himself up for it
BRB rejected applications again somebody
every face for the prodigal son returned
everyone this is everett Bernard his
work with instrumental in helping us
discover our freeze drying techniques to
extract ensign from mice so work hard
because of ever hear can be success so
can all of you
well thanks i think I'm hey you think
it's quick
he got tired of waiting for you so we
went to medical school once you anguish
have been colored anger necessarily i'm
ok thank you get back to work people
you must really hate that bag
good grief
thanks it's the same is better than
worse still working on
yes I was my finger again
yeah let's change won't have to decide
that you wanted to focus on your studies
yeah well you know it's not an issue
anymore introducing as resident this
weekend you back here for him to me
they're feeling better
that went according to plan
right thanks
welcome back dr. Barnard behind yours
was not to procure he hasn't been here
check the unit
[Music]
not for two years i'll look at that
Valve much better
she's good to go to the main floor
though absolutely a little bit of
walking
no more than 15 minutes
hey hey my boy
dr. corrections that boys sorry I tried
calling but oh yeah no belltower sounds
came to protect residents right
hey that's quick again so sorry i'm late
i missed your flap flap
I'm Maria I'm just having a look at my
last surgery
huh hey man whats good many strokes of
summer but don't worry i'm still looking
for resident yeah why the suicide
precautions over those she used to
foster dad's heroin with a dirty new lot
of information around the heart which is
endocarditis
there you go down the wall you got some
order to sign on the floor and then
you're done i will do that
how does it feel to be chief resident
main hospital there's never a dull
moment
oh I'm sure the whole would you mind
taking care of this for me thank you
making friends with quick huh smart to
remove ya know you guys are coming up
quick
actually my foster moms
eugene is don't let anyone tell you
different
the disease has no cure them
guess what hello I'm Brittany here to
watch over mr. Hanna much over with that
shooter suicide prevention you bring it
over from unit
what's in the bag oh thanks to cheer
Sarah
see don't try to cheer her up all you do
is watch her
well I can most certainly do that that
remains to be seen alice can you
separate the please
I most certainly can do that hold on
Barbie I'll be right there
should I tell her that my name is
Brittany why not start yourself
brittany of all know anything
relax relax happens every day
oh yeah yeah no false start back in the
90s hotel ready to charge 360 potential
charges
everyone clear where
building hit him again no she is not
before him again
[Music]
okay we gotta sign up for the max let's
stabilize them
[Music]
you're making progress only two shots
sorry that was your first step
besides dr. James a bit of a prick
that's not be so hard on yourself come
off you know for you could ya please
place i don't know maybe I need to tell
him and I like the jellyfish white the
jellyfish that we want to why I want to
know what appeals to you about it a
jellyfish is the only creature on earth
that lives forever 21 doubt all yes they
stopped the size of Apollo Group
full-size in back down the sides will
follow and keep recycling that way and
they are immortal legacy turtle um they
wash ashore
well how about the eternal mentioned
I've been washed up ever it there are
many smart and talented people that
never get a whiff of greatness this
greatness requires two things
fire in the belly and willingness to see
it's real you about the fire in the
belly
let's see if you have the will
you want the same password
luckily you are a woman of many talents
when do I get paid for my talents you
got quite a mouth on your kids you know
what else my house cat was talking you
know i'm very glad that I made you
choose president you from well i'm going
to see how hard your job will be in ch
why would that be Raymond George's
country HIPAA violations enough to land
your pretty little ass you so i would
try to keep that kind of mouth shut
just some computer work nothing more
oh you're trying to draw attention to
yourself
joining attention
oh you mean like with a books they will
yes your most recent harvest victim his
windows lawyer wants to know why an
otherwise healthy 48-year old days after
a routine procedure and then as an
unauthorized autopsies
well i authorized it funny it is maybe
you can tell their attorneys back to
yourself when they get here tomorrow but
they're coming here we had an agreement
Alex only those patients who are dying
at that moment
well the official cause of death is a
fatal arrhythmia EKG back that up
we're in the clear so if that's all you
forgot to buy golf Darren
oh I've been nursing us along with baby
steps you wanted to kill a books
extracting up in time for their in the
mass produce for you meant you're gonna
screw me out of the largest farmer
dealing as long as you like 50 50 your
time here but 6040 I'm 7030 did you
I covered your ass for seven years even
let you building these please don't do
this
I'm the one that made this happen I made
you laugh
[Music]
ok we're going to close the lab early
today really a couple home and have some
fun this is that we have fun
you can add that back i'll be done a
moment when you don't I'll be done in a
moment and then put more already done in
a moment nurse blackwell
I was a I grab my question your office
and they got the new remote access codes
have a look at this right now
when was just today he has files on all
of our subjects eaten surveillance video
slideshow
he wants my hands on what do you mean it
works well is coming with the watermark
meet with right he's gonna show this act
like he's just discovered troy 25 sports
what are we gonna do
good stuff
she bought this up with work okay
somebody else is going to find that ring
a creek all this construction we've been
offline today these files that can
upload so we go back online tomorrow
morning at 6am so we have some new
password to give us a limited-access
okay to get a large doors power
we're not gonna give it to the network
to change medical files we have to
destroy the network
we can get inventive works
apparently he had two prior am I you
didn't know the world of trouble heart
attack in a file and it was an invisible
we are so close we just eat one more
subject to extracted from well that'd
kill two birds we wanted
you know how the Jewish stone Virgil
just pain and perhaps
[Music]
pray for me i'm sorry i can't do this
but what's what's wrong is it all wrong
[Music]
Sarah
i'm dr. Bonner and yeah yeah yeah so
what did you do to bringing she asked me
if I would accept Jesus into my heart
what stellar phenomena and people you
religious answer
[Applause]
how am i trapped here chef's of our sins
are cautions much equipment we need the
car that decided not so I have to ask do
you still want to do you think about
this
do you want the apartment where our
world from that planet
ok how do you feel please rephrase the
question of concrete and can you still
want to yourself
absolutely i'm putting the dust progress
self unique rd fer
thank you
ok
the patient needs isolation
[Music]
but you know guiding light them to take
out the trash every Tuesday was the
resident on tonight
dr. Jenner she was sleeping with a girl
I don't know you want after know ya get
hurt it handle this junkie
you get that correct by blow up in your
face
gotta have to make an appointment to see
the cardiologist
ok you have insurance yes michigan
across Russia oh ok that should be a 200
on the copay ok ok we will get back with
you in a couple days and give you an
appointment
sounds good thank you okay have a great
day my heart get me weep
you know I was a dancer one great dancer
ballet and michigan in New York for you
what happened tell them of my director
that's not good
he likes to push people as hard as you
can and I a used it anything you wanted
to question you push include no yeah
are you aware of what cryptid he
replaced the infected aortic valve the
same valve that stop you from Dancing
with the direct effect right so in creek
replace the valve he treated both your
problems really so it's all good now one
of the girls probably shouldn't it
should
wait so you're saying that if this heels
i can get for anything really hungry
what are you doing
let's meet God
taking money logs you know you see
developments happening alone i could
show you sometimes you free
self Union cardiac
no sir don't accept that insurance no
sir I can't describe morphine
no sir I will not go to help
hey you already got your residency and
stop studying now after this morning our
chance
yes you can see one do one teach one
that's how you learn you one do one
teach one
yeah like you and Marie see one do one
broker mario has dumped one
okay sorry sorry I don't dump her
ok children that I wanted to focus more
medicine you okay why not just cheat on
her and post the video on facebook that
would have been more humane hey suddenly
dr. freeze over there is talk about
being humane you dumped her to study
more
I mean at least the guy who's cheating
is sexually active
i I'm Way sexually active ok you're the
only woman I know who is defending
cheating i'm not i'm just saying that
that's like the worst possible reason I
don't somebody but it's true
you know it's true you totally dumped
her because you wanted to get closer to
creek and that's so beyond arranged and
now you're defending her which is
another first know this isn't about him
or her it's about you and your ambitions
if you want cardiology so badly when I
just apply to in program we can main
hospital look Ric's just a surgeon and
the hospital is so small i had an
academic hearing two years ago they
wanted to Starling kick my ass help you
didn't tell me that didn't tell anyone
and during the hearing I was too scared
to speak to sketch defend myself but
creek decided he was that they see
something in the in my work that no one
else does so you know you don't know
creek anything with what is that oh we
in this morning yeah all areas
yeah hop up what will allow you to do
that for all know he's not really in a
position to allow me anything right plus
because that your favorite position is
on top
excuse me
really no come on say no okay if I don't
want to know I did mommy go or no cheese
journey
come on look I don't see him anymore
okay
[Music]
can I help you change change Ross my how
you've grown
I hate to do this
looking good
really but not sorry just checking in
thanks for all that click cancel
restraints recital starts quick search
on trucks there are extreme she doesn't
need retreat doesn't matter it's
recreation she what she's quite patient
for all the mission i am not big here he
saying she wanted to count she was that
she's fine fine
does not capture you ever like anything
important to you this really that's what
I lost you through your Bush romance
lines you've dumped me remember
coming on-site training and you never
was like for anything
I'd like to accept this award number
list lol prize for a man of exceptional
brush and x one small step for man
except this public i said it all in all
humanity
I hope this is tony enviable bullshit i
would like to accept this Nobel Prize
for me and all my friends my mommy and
my daddy i would like to i would like to
accept this award I don't want your
reward
[Music]
just hold cheap bastard forgot to pay
the bills
this computer source so you ladies might
like a warm beverage and pink you just
used to be your favorite
so where you want to go check on sarah
would like more ice chips morality to do
for his meds and high then we're gonna
mess with you soon every sorry about
earlier though it's okay actually taught
me a very important lesson what they use
don't care
like a lot
[Music]
he's ready out out out here right
right now my good buddy raised here Alex
hello you're in my private underground
now that you never wanted to know if you
built by my years of grants now it's
time to you to pay for training is going
to help you but it sure isn't going to
help you haha just remind me on this
table right now don't worry about your
return
captain motive that let me out of here
we have got to get there
Ray's going to mrs. to time
[Music]
it's a little surgery I'll never leave
you
depression anxiety
I love you very much it's all right it's
all right
[Music]
alessandra like it this button and get
missile posit or using its sensory he
doesn't know still alive mr. Morales at
Coopers in your sleep here if I shot you
again it will be between your legs
[Music]
oh never killed everyone in the archive
as i go discuss actually killed
everybody in the ER an hour like this
you know something's cold and an idea
about me or anything it needs because
right now because I tried to get a life
is always no bars set where your phone
off right
Oh Watson ok he had a scar on his face
this vertical mad at me look at me look
man okay we're gonna be okay we have to
get out of here we have to find a way
out of this is where you going because
the meeting about leaving you can stay
here on my yeah yeah you need we cannot
read you figger going to the ER than the
uses and ship ever
[Music]
Alice Alice in your path codes
ok
ok you think your mom's proud of you
give your mommy in my field my money
alone
Tommy Burke
ok
hurt can be a puss
that's great for you and it will open
your mommy look
other popular oh gee can use that girl
is a cold-hearted son of a good that you
know what
we gotta deal with that I will do
[Music]
over your journey cover up their journey
with your breathing ok leave it here
what do we do now right here
I'm not going anywhere you have flinched
plus my choking I crushes to grow if you
feel anything
got your back
are you bleeding
feeling like we just splitting open
every temperature breathe even up there
was amazing
I help she would think about it long
most serial killers have dominant or
over protective mothers who work
compensate for distant RSS farmers that
right childhood trauma usually involved
the scarring hold on it used in front of
him and made him attack you
she distracted him to me you're making a
point that suicidal behavior no matter
how genius it is don't need to suicide
your voice leads to suicide
[Music]
attacks separated her incision causing
internal bleeding around her long some
probably around our heart
yeah she'll continue to bleed and her
lungs full class go into shock and died
here on jun stop we doing beautiful
supplies very quick way you doing I'm
not gonna stick around crazy he would be
right outside the door believe you're
not hiding in a corner like you you calm
down please
I'm come I'm not just going to sit here
and watch her die position here and I
say we stay put
oh alright ready don't have a choice
always a toy
we will die we say goodbye okay dr. you
the bitch kind interesting practical so
you tell the girl go right and how
Amazon job
we're done arguing we all leave so we
all this now we need medical supplies
for Sarah and a way out of here
you worked here for years so you find
the escape route August applied you stay
life and heart
Jenny see the computer analysis and i
get a message out of here every I think
that you will manage the patient are you
wait in the hallway your choice
are you serious you need stitches
you're bleeding there's time in the roof
[Music]
acts from chopping up tissue in a
blender calling it research people hold
is to provide perhaps like data dollars
my colleagues to some of the shooting
but the red probably the IRB so I really
couldn't say we're going to think from
what we don't have any Bible suggestions
for changes in peril a killing
listen what the hell are we going to do
[Music]
with her
ok
[Music]
I only have enough liner for long cut
here
better yeah
I ok
get ready for the lidocaine train and
that's I just do it attitude like that
you are not gonna get all
I
okay fine
ABAC science isn't supposed to do
ok
[Music]
sorry no eres in that when you broke up
sweet i was going to dump you know
however that made me do actually
reeling and my sister Jennifer weird the
pocket coach bishop multi-state not
telling efficient tool and when you
first met him
is that common touch Bishop Heelan
whatever tell me i'm a subjective there
anything i would have to be and
something that connection string wedding
well Jen finally got her divorce papers
together but coach center first he
divorced after all the arrest the rehab
and you're driving make it through the
internet dresser yeah yeah well
that he served at work she's school
teaching second grade if you ever did
that to me I'd kill you give you don't
patients me serious i would never die
ever
how's the past year going huh
he's so host pick one I got something to
show you
James froth that's his name can
appropriately surveillance video now
there's only a few cameras it's weird
it's like like the power was cut from
inside the buildings have someone
helping from the outside ready to fire
alarm went off right when I had dreams
of the control vector coordinates to
where the fire checks one deal i'm still
going on okay good point i also uploaded
a bunch of files today for the grow and
they all have tricks name on them and
then try to look those wire with the
board about because it grows killed on a
day when he uploaded files for creek cop
shows called motives every way
take this in case you get a signal and
don't break it
family can be more now be careful we
will thanks
baby
sound
three what are you going here I'm
talking to you
ice such as that that thing attacked me
up to the lab and I came down here and
hit how you survived that had survived
yes
what is that leads to nowhere that's a
dead end
you don't wanna go that way huh listen
you and I should stick together you know
like this is safety in numbers for mayor
for you always with that drive with
sorry I think ever in our dying patients
are eager to leave everything ever he's
here yeah why
nothing I'm just glad you're safe ok
wait memory
let me ask you something we see him
excuse me
you're smart you're beautiful you're
hard-working he dumped you
no I just do that conversation is over
don't walk away from me
[Music]
should
wow you actually can produce tears I'll
Maurice I've got a little shit didn't
even check my pulse
I thought you were expecting
mouth-to-mouth that we grow faking your
death is the shooting thing to do all
that you know telling everyone to let a
young girl died in front of you know
there was a race least you're honest
I don't begin to the comp you hacked
into the Grove account
no comment
oh my god James Ross medical records
he had surgery to get rid of a mole and
it got infected three surgeries
what is tramadol your alpha it's an
inflamed cranial nerve in your face it's
so painful they call the suicide disease
no wonder you two hit it off i must be
lying
click there after not let's use mother
[Music]
oh my god
I
let's just change it so we can watch the
security camps for ever and race 3
happens to be up
how do you have any on your head
what I got it
Jenny tonight
[Music]
I know about your mother Katherine rush
staffers on the ball
starting to run the ball
why are you doing this is all because of
your mom get us out of here
he can't which were locked in by someone
else come here look at this
well no hold on there's more
you know
I see
ok
alright
that is James there is no question that
the quick
what are you doing okay whatever doing
here I don't know we got together
oh come on we gotta get finished that
here we can't show and I'm not no I'm
listen to me I'm not fucking hey listen
to me
we're not going to risk everything to
save difference well Alice look Alex the
matter with you
nothing's wrong i don't know what about
their balance everything just a matter
of sure your palate
we can't risk everything to save we
don't need him stop talking about
everything everything I wanted out of
their office we don't need it would you
help me get over the Englishman be look
look
that's what
you're doing the right thing
going
has to be done
we fell off
[Music]
all
come on
we have to go we have to go right
let's go
what was the last place with less
go back in the corner you go for your
first
Sarah to take this awesome it earlier
outside the hospital like to ask you a
couple questions if that's okay
see the thing is we did a complete
search of Chef unique cardiac hospital
we find any survivors yet did you
actually see every Bernard and Marie
black will escape but dr. Jenner did you
see anything else you think I want
okay thanks to better their full but i
wanna break it down to give me one great
cell phone
yes
internet that he does you had that
number check the bad detective
am I gonna do in your work
how's the lake
look pretty bad for about fifteen
stitches how remember we talked about
aging disease
this secure wanted to do it reverses
aging by extracting enzymes from freeze
drives themselves from living heart
issues Princeton like to work
oh yes i perfected but this is our win
our success best think about it never
losing of line never watching him suffer
and living to his full potential for
price
everything surprised but I do no harm
dark nothing segment sacrifice is the
production of sacred things nothing is
more sacred than immortality
now this this is not sacred this is
sacrilege sacrilegious harvesting
embryos from a woman's womb and using in
stem cell research that's sacrilege
how are you different
if live full lives without action is
your permission
who says you get to play God quick maybe
haven't noticed with judgment no show
and in his absence
somebody's gotta step up
well good morning
ok
it's gonna get
reality check is a little while after
freshman patches
route now marino ever I want you to join
me
I don't have a choice when you have a
choice right now let her call forth now
their sacrifice will change the world
no there have to be about an animal
subjects or or going to tissue or what
about a new subject and rejoice has a
price
[Music]
fine you're right what and why does your
various medical discovery of our
lifetime and it's ours
think of all the people to count she
sold man the money mean this is what
millions billions show you
that's bullshit
further
I was sure he appreciated
I should've known better this whole
generation whining and complaining
mention that 80-hour workweeks oh my god
i don't have enough friends on face and
protest anymore they occupy I should get
people like that secret return life
why
it didn't have the others way you like a
son to me it's not comfortable your
parenting style tricks and so he was
lost me
since you killed his mother
captain Ross nothing to really what
happened to right we should treasure
complications you have a tragic
complication he let me work we did that
and you want to sound like a Polaroid
blush I did what was necessary and I had
the world she had through
[Music]
right
and
[Music]
business pointless
believe me she starts from returning my
watching my new church starving
the only reason I'm regio resident
she was do whatever
[Music]
will end
ok
[Music]
alright for sure
hi dr. Barnard I'm gonna go back
sorry I i would call it I felt home
yeah great thanks you look at same great
thank you have the both of you were
there is some questions thanks started
back up against healthcare you know that
I can trust
how's yours
other than never being able to practice
medicine again went really well
sorry I'm not
only still a free man when are you going
to go back to work
I haven't time to process
not your fault you know
silence
did it
detection
you've got nothing to worry about
hey everything for failure
and what's changed
No
correct
[Music]
no no
why not
you need me cell phone
[Music]