I love Valentine's Day and the fourth of
July I'm a little bit sad when halloween
has gone by
thankful thanksgiving comes around in
the fall but I've always loved Christmas
effective them all
every day special I'm not complaining
but I'm always counting the day still
remaining till Christmas oh wow hey
what's the matter Rhoda oh hi olive my
husband and I took the kids out to buy a
Christmas tree but they're all much too
big too big huh wait right here oh here
you go all that wonderful piney smell
and no needles to vacuum up it's on me
Merry Christmas Oh all of it thank you
and Merry Christmas to you much obliged
Nate out
Christmas my favorite day the weights
almost over it's just hours away
oh thank you genuine rolex rolex genuine
Rolex 10 bucks I didn't know Rolex had 3
x's typographical error factory seconds
genuine Rolex 10 bucks i also got plans
and stationery real cheap why does it
all say city zoo i used to work there
the office supplies with my severance
package when i left to pursue other
opportunities you mean you were fired
fired don't make me less they begged me
not to go now come on by a watch I don't
know huh okay okay i'm a victim of
oppressive corporate bureaucracy yeah
yeah they fired me i was a hard-working
entrepreneur smuggling in junk food
dirty magazines files hidden inside
cakes until a stool pigeon an actual
stool pigeon ratted me out so stand up
for free enterprise fight the man buy a
luxury timepiece pooch I'm olive what's
your name martini for you all of nine
bucks um are you selling counterfeit
watches again I warned you out first of
all they're real Rolex second i was
giving them as a christmas gift to my
dear old friend olive right olive oh
that's right thanks martini hmm I'm
watching you penguin don't forget it
thanks for helping me out there I love
here Merry Christmas hey thank you nine
bucks hmm
where were you all if it's late it's not
late it's oh how your dog chores coming
did you bear any bones today no Tim
chase any cars or cats fraid not did you
even make a token attempt to tear up any
flower beds uh-huh and I haven't heard
any senseless barking at all woof I
don't know how you can call yourself a
dog olive come on Tim you know I'm not
for that silly stuff I've tried to be
man's best friend by being your best
friend haven't I yeah yeah well get with
the program olive and start acting like
a dog I'm sorry Tim let's not fight at
Christmas there's no Christmas this year
uh-huh he's known for years that you're
not like other dogs he even teases you
for having a pet flea why is he so upset
all of a sudden ever since he was Tiny
Tim's loved Christmas but he thinks
there's no Christmas this year I don't
know why are you still gonna give him
the slippers yeah I probably should have
chewed them first hair oh I wouldn't
give for a poseable thumbs hey how about
some music that might cheer you up
prescription eyewear fat dogs do you
smell your best when you're wet check
out the marzipan shacks pre ramadan
clearance sale or what is it
high-pitched sound on the I can hear
forget it tonight on Fox the world's
wildest mistletoe accidents recapping
our top story Santa is expected to
cancel his traditional Christmas Eve
flight Blitzen the Ranger was injured
earlier today during a practice flight
and won't recover in time oh no Santa
had this to say ho ho ho I'm not sure if
I'll have to cancel but it doesn't look
good maybe somehow we'll make do with
all of the other reindeer but if not
Merry Christmas anyway did Santa just
say olive the other reindeer he said
maybe we'll make do with all of the
other reindeer you silly flea no he said
olive the other reindeer I heard him
santa needs you to be the replacement
reindeer that's crazy that's why you're
not interested in chasing cars and
barking like an idiot you were reindeer
not a dog that would explain a lot but I
just don't think so Fido I'll bet Tim
would rather have you pull Santa's
sleigh than chase flower beds and tear
up cars or whatever I'm sure he would
but I'm serious olive you've got to get
to the North Pole
even if I olive oh here comes Tim I
really don't want to get yelled at again
hide olive I came to apologize What did
he say i think he said I'm ashamed of
all your lies wow you didn't do anything
wrong Santa's not flying and I took it
out on you you always do everything
wrong Santa's not flying and I shook it
a trout fondue we can still have
Christmas come on in the house I'm
lighting the yule log and there's a
space for you you can't kill my
Christmas get out of this house I'm
getting a new dog and I'm replacing you
olive are you there
oh he's gone Tim's getting a new dog
he's replacing me I wouldn't believe it
if I hadn't heard it myself you were
right I've got to get to the North Pole
and pull that sleigh Tim seems to blame
me for Santa not flying but maybe I can
still be his dog if I can be Santa's
other reindeer now you're talking all of
the other reindeer hooray gotta go i'll
call you by fight oh I love you could
you finish wrapping those presents
oh no sorry oh that's okay olive new hum
dum aren't you going to kick me or spray
me or something no not today wow I guess
he really got the Christmas spirit
that's right the no more Christmas
spirit did you hear Santa's not flying
he's through yes but at last we're
breaking the cycle of despair by next
year people will have forgotten about
Christmas what's the matter with
Christmas the matter the matter in the
summertime the delivering so easy my bag
is light in the world is fresh but by
autumn I'm getting queasy the shoulder
strap tears at my flesh amazon be by
thanksgiving with four weeks torture
still to come this is no way to make a
living Christmas bah bah get home
one flimsy little Christmas card surely
that can't be too hard but multiply at
the billion-fold can see why christmas
leave me cold Christmas bah bah gang
home
they cut down bigger fatter log so i can
bring more catalogs first pastured
passbook gradebook is it any wonder why
I sold Christmas Bob began home send a
friend to tan gift I don't mind I love
to lift especially when the weather's
freezin oh yes I love the Christmas
season Christmas Bob Morgan home by now
my ligaments actos but here it comes
more Parcel Post who unexplored send it
priority what's one more pain in my
posterior T posterity so here's one hope
our cancellation of all that Christmas
celebration it's aunt is grounded that's
a start for taking strain apply for
heart so turn around go back home rather
as of now Christmas is over hate to
disappoint you but I'm going to the
North Pole to save Santa's flight you're
not a reindeer you can't fly you can't
do anything you wait and see I'll be
zooming right over your head pulling
that sleigh and it will be a Merry
Christmas even for you if you let it now
if you'll excuse me I have a bus to
catch nobody's going to help that lousy
old Santa stay away from the north pole
or al hand cancel you
riding or chasing riding I need a ticket
to the North Pole bus in 34 connects at
Arctic junction boarding right now i'll
take one ticket please make that two
tickets hi ol buddy can you pay for my
ticket no martini why don't you go
pursue other opportunities come on I'll
pay you back later it's Christmas
there's no room at the end please this
is absolutely the last time I help you
out okay this dog committed mail fraud
I'm taking her into custody mail for
Olive cool well see you around what's
all this about she's wanted for several
counts of mail fraud including her
licking the self-adhesive stabs and not
merely early for the holidays yeah
martini help me last call the bus and 34
serves to the fall martini I'm innocent
I'll root for you on Court TV help me
martini I helped you
yo me for those pens come on grab my
tail quick wagon it
thanks martini that postman is bad news
ah don't mention it so how come you go
into the North Pole blitzen's hurt so
they need another reindeer oh they can't
fly I heard Santa on the radio saying
that he needed olive the other reindeer
excuse me Olive but Santa said all of
the other reindeer I'm afraid you just
misunderstood it happens all the time I
used to think the Pledge of Allegiance
was about me Richard stands it's not so
you think Santa asked you to pull his
sleigh that's sweet I almost hate to
point out that you're a dog I really
think I am a reindeer I've always been
different than other dogs and somebody
has got to do something or it won't be a
very Merry Christmas well more power to
you then and why are you going to the
North Pole martini well I figure if
Christmas is canceled maybe I can pick
up all of Santa's toys cheap and make a
bundle on him also I need to cool off
Who am in for there hey are you going to
the north pole or the North Pole
metropolitan area we were vacationing
down here the 40 degree temperatures
were fun for a while but it'll be nice
to get home do you know Santa's reindeer
oh sure they're really big tour three
times bigger than you and their hooves
instead of paws and their first much
thicker than yours and the Magnificent
antlers and they really can't fly well
that'll may be true but I'm a reindeer
just the same listen Alan I'm from the
zoo I know reindeer I work with reindeer
reindeer were friends of mine you olive
I'm no reindeer I'm strong for my size
and however it is that they can fly
magic beans or whatever here's a
practice plus jetpacks I know you're all
trying to be helpful but sometimes in
life you just suddenly know exactly what
to do ya like the time I suddenly had no
brakes going down the mountain road what
did you do hmm i don't remember but i
guess it must have turned out alright
maybe we should have taken a train
move it slowpoke
you know you can run but you can't hide
he's desperate to wreck Christmas but
I'm not going to let him
deliver this hunk
yeah yeah I hope that's the last of him
yeah Richard how long till we reach
Arctic junction a couple of hours
olive where oh where can she be oh I was
too hard on her now I really ruined
Christmas I wonder how she's doing so I
pointed out to the judge that
technically it wasn't a pyramid scheme
because i had Arctic junction Arctic
junction connect here for the North Pole
how long till that bus leaves almost an
hour we've got time to grab some food if
you want hmm yum yum
yeah that's better what do you have the
bone dressing on the side please I'll
try the deep fried candy canes add a
small dead fish sampler maybe I should
have tried the reindeer ciao here's the
latest from the North Pole Santa Claus
has scheduled a press conference for
eleven o'clock tonight he is expected to
cancel his flight for the first time
ever hey everybody don't despair I'm
olive and I'm going to the North Pole to
help Santa I'm the other reindeer what's
the matter haven't you people ever seen
a small dog like reindeer before i live
i live i live i live olive okay you're
all of the other reindeer Santa's
looking for you he's out in the parking
lot he wants to give you a flying test
oh boy my big moment wish me luck guys
coming Santa I take the waitress like me
Santa Santa could make it I'll let him
know you failed the test
neither rain nor snow etc will keep me
from keeping you from the North Pole and
saving Christmas
it's beginning to look nothing like
Christmas poison me
dear Santa I hate you and I hope you
never come again stay home love Bobby
hmm
change
hey don't tamper with the mail it's a
federal offense but it's addressed to me
oh okay then great for zoo monkeys hmm
postal regulations require you to stay
put and keep quiet
hmm
aleph it was the postman wasn't it we
found the waitress clothes how'd you get
away it's kind of hard to explain have
you ever heard of deus ex machina nice
who look it up but listen we missed the
bus you should have gone on without me
ah spare me to modern him I just called
the Postal Service to complain about
that postman guess what I got that
voicemail how can we get to the North
Pole now that was the last bus I take
you up myself olive but if I don't get
back to the depot on time I lose my job
I'm sorry you could always sell watches
you might find someone in the bar who
take you up we'll try it thanks Richard
for everything I'm rooting for you olive
you other reindeer Merry Christmas and
Happy Hanukkah goodbye
I'm Santa's replacement reindeer I need
a ride to the North Pole so I can help
pull the sleigh and save Christmas
anyone you don't look like no reindeer
to me mutt well I am and my name's olive
can you fly um oh sure she can fly she
could fly like a bird like the kind of
birds that fly I mean oh really let's
see amazing just watch santa needs it's
a miracle we found another flying
reindeer and christmas is back on again
oh sorry Arturo please just let me hey
let's take up to the roof and see how
she flies
that's enough fellas uh well just leave
now we don't want any trouble oh it's
mr. briefcase let's see what you got in
there Raja pal that's valuable
merchandise it's mine up barking
reindeer isn't that just stow it tundra
breath maybe I'm just a little runt with
no antlers but it looks like I'm the
only one who's trying to save Christmas
you could at least wish me luck there
are actually people out there who want
to cancel Christmas are you on their
side uh throwing someone off a roof is
that how you want to remember Christmas
you must have asked Santa for something
do you think you deserve what you've
asked for hmm it's a two-way street
Santa doesn't just give you stuff
because you ask you have to deserve it
I'm trying to deserve the good things I
have and the good things i hope i will
have in the future if you want me to
fail that i guess it's too late to save
Christmas it's already gone come on
martini adria what I asked Santa for a
reversible three-speed cordless electric
drill I'm too naughty to deserve such a
nice drill all right pull yourself
together let's think about this olive
huh that's right I'm sorry olive we're
really not such a bad bunch when you're
this far north with no sunlight
sometimes tempers spray
but it's hard enough now Santa's flight
it's been an awful day why my
nice latitudes depends on all
so forgive us if we all have attitudes
we're up a frozen cracker
we're not so bad we're really sweet and
funny we're not so bad except for that
funny we're not so bad enough so bad
we're not so bad
may I be frank of course we were
suspicious it seemed you were playing a
nasty prank that's why we got malicious
but we're
so bad we're not so fearful once you get
to know us we're
I'm right rip off
not so bad we're not so bad now that we
promise not to throw you we're not so
bad I'm so bad go on you guys he can
take you up in this half truck olive
round yon virgin Oh like in the silent
night song I don't know what you're
talking about anyway round John can take
you as far as the North Pole gates after
that you're on your own we'll figure out
something I'm blitzen's cousin schnitzel
flightless unfortunately it happens
we're ready to go Thank schnitzel the
puffins going to that's penguin to you
pal good luck and Merry Christmas do I
look like a puffin
you
Tim wait Tim hey hey come on all up I've
to wake up
North Pole time to do your thing good
luck Colin and I'm sorry I was such a
jerk earlier it's okay round John you're
not the only one who slept their
emotions get the better of them today
hey thanks for the ride here high
quality office supplies for you gee City
Zoo envelopes Thanks Merry Christmas
what if is a casino anonymous
high-ranking elves are confirming that
Santa will shortly make a statement
officially canceling his traditional
Christmas Eve flight your reaction
little doggie um I think that maybe my
client has no comment at this time you
better get in there I don't know why
what you even got me believing this is
gonna work I'm olive the new reindeer
I'm here to help pull Santa's sleigh
olive olive no olive on my list but
Santa said on the radio that he was
counting on olive the other reindeer
that's me I'm filling in for Blitzen I
can't let you in but I have to know
isn't there someone who I could talk oh
don't you even care let me think no no
no move along or I'll have you arrested
and I'm warning you the fence is
protected by alarms so just go back
where you came from but I time to think
a plan B hmm
while you're thinking maybe I'll just go
use that pay phone payphone yes uh-huh
oh huh repair centers Oh we'll send a
man over right away sir it'll be a
penguin actually oh he'll have it work
it in no time i'll be here till six all
right then goodbye you know this could
be an exfoliating carburetor or a
decaffeinated dodecahedron what let me
get out my tool hmm oh yes I see I'll
just have to recalibrate the time I'll
need you to kill the alarms along the
fence for a minute though what well
otherwise the electromagnetic wave will
interfere with the signals from the
satellite all right it just needs a
complementary engraving e.l.f right I'll
tell you what I'll have it back be on
monday and I'm sorry for the
inconvenience Merry Christmas
special delivery more children's letters
to Santa let's do the press conference
boss and hope for better luck next year
there must be some way you could go
can't we fly with seven reindeer Adele
we could handle a chief maybe we
shouldn't even try so many of the kids
letters this year haven't been very nice
dear Santa I hate you don't come to my
house Johnny dear Santa lose some weight
and get a real job yeah maybe it's time
to retire anyway no those letters are
fake Santa I know who's been writing
those letters they're all from a very
mean postman who wants to wreck
Christmas mmm look at the envelopes no
postmarks hmm that's true but just who
might you be little doggy I'm actually
not a dog I'm olive the replacement
reindeer you asked for I'm not quite
following you olive you say you're a
reindeer and I asked you to come right I
heard you on the radio we always get the
crazies on Christmas Eve never fails
well can you fly olive can you afford
not to find out well now if you're sure
all those mean letters aren't from real
kids everyone loves you Santa and all
over the world everyone is hoping you'll
fly tonight make their dreams come true
I know I don't look like much but give
me a try for all those good folks who
deserve what they've asked for I guess
they'll understand if you can't make it
but round John virgins sure would like
that electric drill and my master Tim
well maybe he does want a better dog but
mostly I think he just wants Christmas
I don't think he'll find a better dog
olive even if you are a reindeer thanks
for coming 000 people we're Flay tell
the media okay load up the slave come
and help Alan here get hitched up I just
learned that you'd better not pout you'd
better not cry you'd better not shout
I'm telling you why a mysterious other
reindeer has arrived to take blitzen's
place as of now the flight is on again
I'll be darned she really did it who's
she what's going on well see um earlier
today
oh she had a clear sense of mission
cares deeply about Christmas close close
friend of mine for years not not not
housebroken not to my knowledge she is
housebroken haha there you go by the way
where's Rudolph there's no Rudolph it's
just one of those urban legends slaves
loaded everyone ready ready all of the
other reindeer huh well why not it's a
season of miracles good luck kid oh
thanks comet Santa one niner niner niner
cleared for takeoff on 22 left punch it
boys
hey Christmas
come on
Oh
unorthodox style but hey whatever works
for you you had me worried for a minute
there though are we good to go vomit
oh-ho-ho I think so just don't pick up
any hitchhikers you okay Oliver I'm
solid
all if the other reindeer you'll go down
in history fine fly as much as you want
you're still out of business cuz this
year even though I've been naughty I got
all the toys the Lords of breaking an
entry as they pertain to Santa are
unclear hmm excuse me look I got another
presence hey I must have been extra bad
this year let seem dull jack-in-the-box
cordless drill aha here we go the train
set that should have been mine when I
was a kid that was the acela started
putting me on his naughty list he didn't
cut me any slack so I'm not cutting him
any slack Oh fat boys finished
ruly at the first house and I'm beat you
want some like in flavored gum it'll
perk you up what's this edit card offers
catalogue sweepstakes mailings bad news
gang somehow we got the wrong sack this
is all junk mail good Santa let me smell
that mail ever the postman I knew it
let's go nowhere just head north sooner
or later I'll pick up the scent
it's getting awfully late
this way
ah
fish breath you got martini 20 now
you're in for it
Oh
get off me you jolly old busy buddy
hmm haha give back the present never you
shut up stayed home
then again
hey was that you were your stunt double
oh go on are you okay martini shaken but
not stirred anyway all the toys are here
also a cordless drill huh thanks for
your help martini I'd offer you a lift
in the slave comin says no hitchhikers
just our luck that you're flightless hey
don't worry about me i'll drive home I
mean how hard can it be Plus someone's
got to take care of mr. zip oh hmm
cardboard wings time today ho ho coming
thanks for everything martini what will
you do now yeah you know I'll do a
little loan sharking sell a little lamb
wait don't worry about me Merry
Christmas olive Merry Christmas martini
Holly great job getting the toys back
but we're way behind schedule any chance
we could go faster than warp speed
captain oh
I don't have antlers I don't have hooves
high-flying works I have no clue but now
got the reindeer moon
you can't give up on Christmas
now the troubles are me
is all done
Christmas after all to everybody
small I pulled the sleigh christmas
if you've got the Christmas spirit let
nothing you dismay
don't need springs or wings or strings
to fly on Christmas Day soul is Terry
on this Christmas
it's all right there
you
so there's this
to everybody
marry me
of nature's rain
Boise
somehow
that is
it is after all
I guess I could deliver his stuff not as
glamorous as helping Santa but there'll
be trouble if the folks can't enter this
sweepstakes besides Christmas gratuities
that's it Oh done excellent work boys in
three cheers for Olive the other
reindeer after we get home and relax for
a while we usually go out for some
reindeer games will you join us hmm
maybe hey it's my house Fido and Tim
well think about it oh no that Arctic
fog olive I'm sorry but we're lost in
the fog could you smell us home mrs.
Claus is baking cookies cookies
gingerbread 10 degrees starboard
all if I'd be honored if you'd call me
coming the other dog sure but first
cookies yeah well I gotta hand it to you
olive you saved Christmas no I only
convinced everyone else to do their best
oh don't you be so modest Khalid you
were great and now oh-ho-ho presents for
the staff and crew Oh
ah both from an insurance point of view
the jump ropes probably not a wise idea
olive here's something for you thank you
I know I'm not really a reindeer but I'm
proud i could help anyway you've all
been so wonderful i'd love to stay but I
really must go home I thought so let me
finish my cappuccino and I'll give you a
lift yeah by Allah will miss you I'll
keep in touch Merry Christmas
look it's martini martini you helped
save Christmas we saw you on TV oh well
I hope it was a color set black and
white doesn't do me justice I'm pleased
to offer you your old position back
martini the zoo can always find room for
an extraordinary flightless aquatic bird
who attracts media attention and we've
been a little short-handed since the
monkeys escaped oh it's tempting but I
think I can get you an even better
penguin all of the other Rangers is
Christmas huh Merry Christmas Tim I hope
you're not too mad at me olive I was so
worried you'd never come back I'm sorry
I was so mean can you ever forgive me I
was so upset about Santa that I forgot I
have the best dog in the whole world Wow
and the best reindeer too merry
christmas holly good girl good girl oh
you the best
valentine's Day and the fourth of July
I'm a little bit sad when halloween has
gone by
giving comes around in the fall but I've
always loved Christmas the best of them
all
every day special I'm not complaining
but I'm always counting the distal
remaining till Christmas
you