you
there was once in Venice amor or fellow
who for his merits in the affairs of war
was held in great esteem it happened
that he fell in love for the young and
noble lady called Desdemona who drawn by
his virtue became equally enamoured of
him so it was that since her father was
much opposed to the union of Desdemona
with a more she fled her house at night
in secret haste they were married now
there was enough fellows company an
ensign named Iago for very amiable
outward appearance but whose character
was extremely treacherous in peace I
have told the orphan and I retail the
gay I hate the more I poison his delight
how a girl claimed him in the streets
means since her kinsman and though he in
fertile climate dwell bacon with fly no
they come Oh what will I do fix though I
go to bed and sleep I will incontinently
drown myself a villainous what should I
do who put money in that first here i
would say i would drove myself for the
love of a guinea hen i would change my
humanity with a bat poop cumbia mare huh
brown ice and drown cats and blind
puppies it cannot be the Desdemona
should long-continued i loved them world
or he to hurt this was a violent
commencement thou shalt see an
answerable sequestration he'll die purse
with money when she has sated with his
body she will for in the era of her
choice she must have changed
senior is all your family within this he
did your pleasure that you ought to be
transported with no voice no better
guard but for the name of common hire a
gondolier to the growth class similar
hideous more dish oh shit on me satisfy
yourself if she be in her chamber all
your house can I depend on you not sure
of me go make money if they're not
charmed by quits the property of youth
and made hood may be of use all of all
my people raised my kindred
keep up your bright sword for the humor
all of cold feet where's who stowed my
daughter hands both your mind tiny of
the rest within your will ensure that i
go to answer this your charge type of
Lord cost of the recession or we'll be
to answer now at the same hour there
came messengers in haste to the Senate
so there was news that the Turkish fleet
is moving against the Venetian garrison
in Cyprus the Senators already raised in
met had elected the more to the
commander their troops and offices were
searching the town to a prize of hello
of his'n wanna when hello Desdemona's
old father himself brings the war at
swords point to the council chamber upon
a charge of working upon Desdemona with
unlawful in Chen disabuse stolen from me
i corrupted by magic spells very sorry
fer she changed of magic were not bound
were made to tenure fair and happy would
ever have to incur a general Mach one
from her father to the surety bosom of
such a thing as that damned as the octo
hast enchanted her a fellow what in your
own part can you say to this I think but
this is so did you by indirect and for
said courses subdue and poison this
young maids affection most potent grave
and reverence seen yours I very noble
approved good masters but I have tain
away this old man's daughter it is most
true true I've married her very head and
front of my offending at this extent no
more brew demand my speech little
blessed with a soft phrase of peace for
since these arms of mine at seven years
pistol now some nine moons wasted
they've used their dearest action in the
tented field little of this great world
can I speak more than pertains to pizza
broil and battle and therefore little
can I grace my cause and speak
for myself yet I heard racist patients I
will around on vanish tail deliver of my
whole course of love what drugs what
charms what conjuration and what mighty
magic for such proceeding I am charged
with all I won his daughter provancha
loved me oft invited me still questioned
me the story of my life I ran it through
even for my boyish days when I speak of
most disastrous chances of moving
accidents by flood and field of
hairbreadth escapes to the imminent
deadly breach are being taken by the
insolent fo and soul to slavery of my
Redemption Vince importance in my
travels history we're in a van trees
vast and deserts idle rough quarries
rocks and Hills whose heads touch heaven
it was my hint to speak this to hear or
Desdemona seriously inclined but still
the house affairs will draw offense
whichever as she could with haste
dispatch she'd come again and with a
greedy year to power up my discourse I
found good means to draw from a a prayer
of earnest heart that I would all my
pilgrimage dilate and often did beguiled
her of her tears when I did speak of
some distress heat stroke that my youth
suffered she gave me for my pains a
world of sighs she swore a faith to
estranged was passing strange it was
pitiful it was wondrous pitiful she
wished she had not heard it yet she
wished that heaven had made her such a
man she thanked me and she badd me if I
had a friend that loved her I should but
teach him how to tell my story and that
would woo her upon this hint I spake she
loved me for the dangers I had passed I
loved her that she did pity them this
only is the witchcraft I think this tale
would win my daughter to come here or
Desdemona
perceive in all this noble company well
most you owe obedience my noble father I
do receive here divided duty to you I am
bound for life and education my life and
education both to learn me how to
respect you you are the daughter of duty
I am either to your daughter but here's
my husband and so much duty as my mother
showed to you preferring you before her
father so much I challenge that i'm a
professor Steele to the more my lord god
be with you i have done when remedies a
past the griefs are ending is it your
grace on to the state affairs but tech
were the most mighty preparation makes
for Cyprus hello the 42 love the place
is best known to you you missed away
this morning with all my heart when we
consider the importancy of Cyprus to the
Turk we must not think the Turk is so
unskillful to leave that latest which
concerns him first neglecting attentive
ease in game
look to him war far as eyes to see she
has deceived her father and me thee my
life of faith
marked me with what viola and she first
love them all but for bragging and
killing a fantastical lies and will she
love him still operating ah let not thy
discreet her think it lifted and cat yet
Iago I know my price I'm what apology
sir had the election then what is
Shiva's Michael Cassio this Florentine
who never said a squadron in the field
nor the division of a battle knows
mother a spinster yet Castillo muscle if
tenant be and I god bless the mark off
fellows ensign well then you I ha Logan
to serve my turn yah go Iago honest Iago
I wait upon your lordship my Desdemona
must I leave with thee pray bring her
after in good time to Cyprus well Meghan
lord I do it the moors of a free and
open nature the pinks men honest of it
seemed to be soon will as 10 deliver
late by the nose in this is a scissor
we can't all be masters not all masters
gonna be truly followed you shown marked
many adieu to sneak looking knave who
doting on his own obsequious bondage
wears on his tie much like his masters
asked for not the problem of him when he
sold at sheared whip mr. Jonas names
others there are throwing the chose of
service on their Lords to will fly it by
them and when they've lined their coats
to themselves hommage these fellows have
some so and such a one do I profess
myself for sir it is sure as you are
Roderigo were I the more I would not be
in following him I fell over myself or
when my outward action dr. mønsteret
the native act in figure of my heart in
compliments externe tis not long after
but I will wear my heart upon my sleeve
for doors to take it I am NOT
comme des Demona I am but an hour of
love to spend with e we must obey the
time
good Iago hot toddies can you tell me of
my lord you've not yet arrived that the
Turkish speaking up clothes shelter they
are draw he's impossible
you use the desperate chambers to solve
and the Turks the third assignment holds
a world of gun
he takes a manip am wealthy an excellent
quarter-zip with as little of web as
this will I ensnare as great a fly ass
it gives me wonder great as my content
to see you here before me oh my soul joy
if after every tempest come such comms
may the winds blow to lay up waken death
Oh My Fair warrior to prattle out of
fashion died out in mine own comforts
worthy Montano your pardon sir good
Michael look you to the guard tonight
come my dear love once more wellnitz at
Cyprus
it is a fellow's pleasure they upon
certain tidings newly arrived importing
the destruction of the Turkish feet
every man put himself into trial each
man to what sports and rebels his
addiction lead him or besides this
beneficial knew the celebration of our
generals heaven I must tell you this
Desdemona is directly in love with well
hurts not I must be dead and what you
like sure she had to become a fellow
that in nature will come to look upon
second choice browser Oh stand so
eminent of a degree of this fortune as
casio why not neva mind a lot of
occasions and evolutionary he is
handsome Jesse oh yeah Oh what was it in
him but Holly and green mind look at a
pistol and complete name and the woman
has owned him already now I cannot
believe he'll in Desdemona
no not see her pedal with a palm of his
hand he's not master yes that I did but
but that was but courtesy courtesy
lecturing an index dubsteo prologue to
the history of lustin whole thoughts
when it met Sonia with her lips of their
breaths embrace together villainous
fourth Rodrigo sir bunny left me left
and a Casio tonight watches on the court
of God casio knows you not I'll not be
far from you do you find some occasion
to anger him by what course you please
well their ration with a sudden in
kollam have him strike at you provoke
him that he may for even out of this but
like all these of cyclist mutiny indeed
dis planting of casio lehtonen Cosmo
dagger I'll see you well the other in
the sincerity of love and friendship
farewell i'm leftenant a stupid white
here an abrasive galaxy game have a
measure to the health of blackrock
fellow up tonight cariago i have very
poor and unhappy brains for drinking one
I must to the watch not these all
attendance is not jet into the clock our
general casters as earlier for love of
his lezdom owner is not yet made want on
the night with her and she's offend you
he's a most exquisite lady and I bought
a couple of gaming what an ia she has an
inviting I and yet I think right modest
well happiness to their sheep another
cup I'll drink for you I've dropped two
cups tonight and dare not ask my
weakness with anymore my man is a mighty
rubble I do it but it dislikes me
if I were now to die to an out to be
most happy wife here my soul hath her
content so absolute but not another
comfort like to this this exceeds it on
Oh God an excellent song I learned it in
England will indeed their most potent in
potty your Dane your German your swag
billet hollander drink oh nothing during
this Oh is your Englishman so expand in
his drinking he thinks you enlisted it
he had gained Cape drunk he switched not
to overthrow your l main he gives you
Hollander of vomit and an ex patre you
fill through the health of our general
I'm for it left in and I'll do you
justice
you
make a little one but faster fighters
I'm a soldier
well God's above all and there be stones
must be saved and verba souls must not
be safe food good lieutenant for my own
part no offense to the general or any
men of quality I hope to be saying so do
I to leptin and I but by all leave not
before me Oh gentlemen I am truck this
is my inside my right hand this is my
lip I am a drunk now I can stand one up
equal excellent well really you must not
think that I
oh don't you row you rascal hey boys is
this teach me my name
could be shaped forever and you forgot
oh and take the places you should eat
already
silence metric fulfill who began this
Iago I do not know friends all but now
even knowing quarter and in terms like
private and groom de vetting him for bed
and then but now Thor's out and tilting
one another's breasts worthy Montana
what's the matter that you unlace your
reputation the SAT spend your rich
opinion for the name of a night roller
your officer Iago can inform you
watching a town of war to manage private
into misty quarrel in night come
a-courtin god of safety Iago hope
against those days more or less than
truth thou art no soldier I heard rather
had this tongue cut from an orphanage to
do a fence rule Michael Cassio sermon
and rage strike those that wish them
best yet surely cast you I believe
received from him that's played some
strange in dignity which patients could
not pass I know Iago I honesty and love
with minced this matter may he'd like to
casio casio i love thee but never more
the officer of mine look if my gentle
love be not raised up i'll make thee an
example
what you're hurt lieutenant I passed all
surgery Mary heaven forbid reputation
reputation reputation I have lost my
reputation I have lost the immortal
pastor of myself and what remains is
bestial I reputation II I'll go my
reputation reputations knocked up
without merit and Las without deserving
i irritate you what you shall do our
generals wife is now the general
confessors are freely to her Desdemona
is of so free so kind so blessed a
disposition she hold the device in our
goodness not to do more than she is
requested farewell
my money is almost spent I've been
tonight exceedingly well cudgelled I
think the issue will be I shall have so
much experience for my pains and so with
no money at all and little more whip
return again to Venice how far they have
foundations does not go well casio have
beaten the other by that small herd has
cashiered co content herself a while or
why is this fool plies Desdemona to
repair his fortune sushi for him plead
strongly to the more know by how much
his tries to do him good sheesh lon do
her credit with them war so will I turn
her virtue in to pitch and out of her
own goodness make the net that shall a
mesh them all
do not doubt casio but i will have my
lord in you again as friendly as you
were volunteers madam whatever shall
become of Michael Cassio he's never
anything but your true servant I like
not that what does that say nothing my
lord on it I know not but I know my
daughter I've been talking with a suitor
here man that languishes in your
displeasure who is jireen by your
lieutenant Cassio 20 hands now I sue so
humble that he's left part of his grief
with me to suffer with him cut love
calling back some other time Chad be
shortly as soon as sweet for you jumpy
tonight at supper no not tonight
tomorrow do nothing I do not dine at
home I meet the captain's in the Citadel
I then tomorrow night I pray thee namee
the time no more let it covered he will
I were than I be nothing
wherein I do entreat you brought me this
to leave me but a little to myself Jen I
deny you know well well muddle my noble
Lord what is the sale go did Michael
Cassio when you wooed my lady know of
your love good from first to last what
is the ass but for the satisfaction of
my thought no further harm cry of a
thoughts Iago I didn't think he'd been
acquainted with her where's went between
is very off into eating teeth I indeed
discerns thou art in that is he not
honest honor Malone honest I honest my
lord what I know what I don't think
think middle think well just mean
something I heard he say even now thou
likes not that when Cassie who left my
wife if they'll does love me show me thy
thoughts My Lord you know I love you I
think so dust or Michael Cassio I Davis
when I think he's honest how do you
think so too
men should be what they seem certain men
should be what they seem why then I
think casio is an honest man hey yet
there's more in this me privy speak to
mr. though thinking's good name in men
and woman dear my lord is the immediate
jewel of their souls who steers my purse
tears trash just something nothing it
was mine tis he is and has been slaves
the thousand but he that filches from
him my good name Rob's me of that which
not enriches him and makes me poor in
deeper now know the thoughts all beware
my lord of jealousy it is the green-eyed
monster which doth Mock the meat it
feeds off that cuckold lives in blissful
certain of his fate loves not his runner
but oh god damn Ned minutes tells your
who don't split down suspects yet
strongly loves haha why is this thanks
though I'll make a life of jealousy to
follow still the changes of the moon
with fresh suspicions Booya go I'll see
before I doubt when I doubt prove I
speak not yet a proof look to your wife
observe her well with Cassio
I know our country disposition well in
Venice they do let heaven see the pranks
there dare not show their husbands best
conscience is not to leave done done but
keep ton known gusta su so she did
deceive her father marrying you and when
she seemed to shake and fear your look
she loved the most so she did why go to
then p that's so young we'll give out
such a seeming to see her father's eyes
up close as oak he thought was
witchcraft but I have much to blame I
humbly to beseech your your pardon for
too much loving you having gone to thee
for him I see this heather little dashed
your spirits photo/jorge not a jot if
ever fear it has I hope you will
consider what his folk comes from my
love Cassio's my worthy friend my lord I
see your moved no not much smooth I do
not think but Desdemona's honest long
live she so and long live you to think
so and yet our nature birding from
itself i dares the point has to be bold
with you not to affect many proposed at
matches of her own clime complexion and
degree
what may smell in such a will mold rank
holders proportion aw it's unnatural i
would i might entreat your honor to scan
this thing no further leave it at time
yeah well believe me hago
oh no my dear Jenna my lord I take my
leave are you not well I have a pain
upon my father dear that's with watching
to the way again let me but bind it hard
within this hour
I have a thing for you thing for me is a
common thing to have a foolish wave is
that all what will you give me now for
that same handkerchief what handkerchief
that would so often you did bid me steal
give it me if it'd been up some purpose
of import give me again poor ladies you
done matter ever use for it leave me
hello general I swear tis better to be
much abuse than but to know a little I
know he's my don't agree you idiots but
now I'll go and certainly in strange I'm
quietly I won't go seek him there's
metrons indeed if he'd be angry
villain be sure that proves my love a
whore be sure of it give me the ocular
proof what by the words of man's
immortal soul has been better have been
born of dogs on answer my weight drops
grace make me to see it's or at the
least so proven to the probation bear no
hands nor move date him oh woe upon my
life never prayed laws abandon for
nothing can stop the donation and take
them take note o world to be directing
honesty don't see by the world I think
my wife be honest I think she is I think
that thou are just and think the locknut
i'll have some proof her name that was
his precious Giants visages now begrimed
and black that's mine own face what I
was satisfied satisfied my lord would
you the supervisor grossly gay born
behold her top where satisfaction is
impossible you should see this where
there's claim as goats as hot as monkeys
give me a living reason she's destroying
I lay with Cassio lay p.m. being
troubled with a raging tooth like could
not sleep there are a kind of men so
elusive sold in their sleep will mutt
other affairs one of this kind is
Cassiel in sleep I heard him say sweet
Desdemona let us beware let us hide our
love's and then so would he gripe and
wring my hand kreyol sweet creature and
then kiss me hard as if he plucked up
kisses for the roots that grew up on my
lips then laid his leg over my thigh
inside and kissed a man cried curse it
fate that gave thee to the more I'll
tear
all to pieces you never this have you
not sometimes seen a handkerchief
spotted with strawberries in your wife's
hand gave her such a warnach a
handkerchief I'm sure it was your wife's
did I today's he casts your wipe his
facebook give me that or any that was
hers it speaks against her were the
other proofs well do I see tis true
oh the slave at 14,000 drives one is too
poor too weak for my revenge he condemns
patients I say your mind Pabst med chain
in every ah go right to the pontic see
whose icy current and compulsive course
near feels retiring head but keeps you
on to the pro pontic at the Hellespont
even so my bloody thoughts with violent
a chanela back there in too humble love
till it's a capable and wide revenge
swallow witnesses here Iago don't give
up the execution of his wit hands heart
to wronged Othello's service within
these three days let me hear he say the
casio snot alive my friend is dead he's
done at your request but let her live
there for you drinks Oh
oh I left-tenant I am your own forever
ico ico
give me your hand this hand is moist my
lady if you had a felt no age no no no
sorrow this argues fruitfulness and
liberal heart heart heart of moist tis a
good hand a Franklin man deed say so
foot was that hand that gave away my
heart a liberal hand come now your
promise what promise chat guess you'll
be received again Wren me thy
handkerchief I have it not about me not
no indeed my lord it's a false that
handkerchief did an Egyptian to my
mother give the worms were hollowed the
debris design good to god I'd never seen
it he's lost he's gone speak it out of
the way it is not lost but what an if it
were oh I say it is not lost fetch it
let me see it why so I can sir but I
will not now this is a trick to put me
from my suit pray oled casio be received
again retreat i got you i pray told me
of casio maker chiefin anatoly's time at
the fonda tease good fortunes on your
love shared dangers with you I could
just come come you'll never meet a more
sufficient man away away
lieutenant this handkerchief whose is it
I found it here I like to work well have
it copied take it leave me for the time
yes you can I see you so much I see you
so Bianca I tell you yet again in
fortune Desdemona how to have to put you
in your place sure there's someone then
this handkerchief no biggy rat who
shares as a man they're all but stomach
will be over food I sure the heaters
hungrily and when they are full they
Belcher's ha good kiss you what's the
news with you
what rubbish at see something from image
I noble Lord iced were here all film it
with your grief casio came hither eyes
shifted him away at him a non-return and
here's speak with you know Martha flares
the jibes and notable scorns that well
in every region of his face for I will
make him tell the tailor knew where how
how oft how long ago and when he has it
is again to cope your wife I say but
mark his gesture Mary patients or I
shall say you're all in all in spleen
and nothing of a man it's no here Iago I
will be found more stunning in my
patience but is not here most bloody how
do you know that's in it yago not this
suit lead
how quickly should just be alas poor
creature haha i never knew a woman love
man though she gives it out I the laws
and weeps upon me so Haley's and pulls
me I must leave her something what you
mean by that same image if you gave me
there this is a minx token I'll take out
no welcome I know my sweet be a girl now
after after did you see how he laughed
at his voice go did you see the
handkerchief was that yours Desdemona
gave it him and he had given at his
whore
I had been happy if the general camp
pioneers at all had tasted her sweet
body so I had nothing know what sense
that I have a stolen hours of lust I saw
it not hey Tom not me I slept the next
night well was free and Mary hi I'll not
Kassius kisses on her lips
a fine woman a fair woman a sweet woman
he must forget that I let her rotten
parish should be damned oh how I'd is
turned to store I strike it and it hurts
my hand oh the world is not a sweeter
creature she might lie by an emperor
aside and command him tasks may that's
not your way hanger I do what say what
she is so delicate with a needle and a
drobo musician oh she will sing the
savageness out of a bear so high and
plenteous witten invention she the worth
would all let for a thousand thousand
times then so gentle condition I too
gentle may that's it forget the pity
video we are go the pity of it our
chopper into messes call me Oh
would you think so big so yeah well to
kiss him played an unauthorized tour to
be naked a friend in made an old old
morn of meaning a harm naked in bed I
give my wife a hank locklin why they
diss her smile orden being her she may I
think bestow done in a handkerchief by
heaven I would most gladly offer
gossiped he had my a guitar part of that
that's not so good now what have I said
I'd seen him do you wrong or heard him
say have he said anything he hath mellow
but no more than he's happy that he did
I know that party right why lie lie with
her with her on her what you will
hello
there's no mock me i mock you no by
heaven
well now forever farewell the tranquil
mind farewell content farewell a plumie
troupe and the big wars that make
ambition virtue Oh farewell farewell a
neighing steed and the shrill Trump the
spirits during drum the ear piercing
Fife the royal banner and all quality
pride pomp and circumstance of glorious
war and OE mortal engines who's rude
throats the immortal Jove's dread
clamors counter feet farewell
both fellows occupations gone
god save the worthy general see you did
you can senators a Venice greet you I
kiss the instrument of their pleasures
is their division tricks my Lord and
Cassio I'm most unhappy one I won't do
much to a turn them for the love I bear
to kiss you my lord maybe they moved him
on as I think it'll come on in home to
Putin castle here as government by my
troth I'm glad ups did why sweet Othello
get me out of my sight stay to offend
you truly an obedient lady I do beseech
Your Lordship call her back mistress I
know what would you with us sir ooh aye
my lord oh you did wish that I would
make a turn so she could turn and turn
and yet go on and turn again and she
could weep so wheatland she's obedient
you say obedient very obedient I'll seat
you and your tears concerning this earth
oh well dated passion I'm commanded home
get you away I'll send yer on sir I'll
be the mandate and will return to Venice
passio shut up at my place
you are welcome sir to Cyprus
outs
ok
I sweet safe is he not like a brain is
that he is
you
let me see your eyes what would my face
what Rocco your wife my lord your true
and loyal wife had him pleased heaven to
try me with affliction had they rained
all kinds of sores of shades on my bare
head steeply and poverty to the very
lips given in captivity me and my utmost
hopes i should have found in some place
of my soul a drop of patience but alas
to make me a fixed figure of a time of
scorn to point his slow are moving
finger act yet could I bear that too
very well but there well I've garnet of
my heart weren't even I must live up
there no life but fountain from the
witch my current runs or else
dries up to be discarded Vince or keep
it as a system for foul toads to not and
gender in I hope my normal or just seems
to be honest hiya summer flies are in
the shambles but quicken even with
blowing oh wait what are so lovely fair
smells so sweet the percents pick Sedin
what arts never born unless what able to
see if I committed committed committed
oh the public commoner I should make
very fortress of my cheeks that were to
cinders burn up modesty did I would
suite Syed's what committed heaven stops
the nose at it at the moon wings the
body wind that kisses all it meets is
harsh within the hollow nine of Earth
and whereas here it what committed
impudence rumpet I have you to me wrong
are not you are stupid i'ma Chris just
possible heaven fuck him I cry you mercy
then I took you for that cunning hora
Venice that Mary
how do you madam how do you my good lady
yeah father sleep good madam what's the
matter with my lord why with my lord
matter who used I know here it is your
sweet lady I have none to not talk to me
Amelia I cannot weep or answer by none
but what should go by water pretty
tonight I did my wedding sheets
and
get me some poison my uncle
this night they're not expostulate with
a best her body and beauty and provide
my mind again do it not with poisons
strangle her and her bed even the bed
she had contaminated good good a justice
of it pleases and for casio let me be
his Undertaker excellent you shall hear
more by midnight
heaven pardon him hooked up bother him
on a hell knows of spice before you home
huh who keeps your company time or place
what form up likelihood the laws of used
by some roasted on a slave some face
notorious knave some scurvy fellow
within doors some surf squad it was who
turned your with the seamy side but I'll
then made you to suspect me with the
move Desdemona
get you to bed dismiss your attendant
there look it be done
I do not mind about deals just a with me
what in the contrary every day thou
gavest me with some device Iago I've
wasted myself out of I means the jewels
you've had for me to deliver to
Desdemona with half corrupted of
motorists of Tony she's received them
and return the expectations and comforts
of sudden respect and acquaintances but
I find none well go to very well be well
go to I cannot go to man not is not very
well I will make myself known to
Desdemona if she returning my jewels
he's not I will seek satisfaction of you
I know I see this miquel in me and even
from this instant who build on the a
better opinion than ever before give me
thy hand Roderick I protest I have just
most directly in my affair
not appeared I grant indeed it if not
appeared and your suspicion is not
without wit and judgment if thou has
that Indian deed which I have greater
reason to believe now than ever I mean
purpose courage nella is not prove it
you vowed the next night following and
joy not Desdemona take me from this
world with treachery there is a special
commission come from Venice deputing
casio in a fellow's place why then o
sailin Desdemona well turn again to
Venice unless he's aboard be lingered
here by some accident wherein none can
be so determinant is the removing of
Cassio how do you mean removing of him
by making him incapable of a fellow's
place knocking out his brains and that
you would it
I will be near the second your attempt
he will fall between us I had no great
devotion to this deed it makes us on it
Mars in combat
Oh
Yago
hi guys do it does that vote beeping
Disney the yellow there I've had it set
sir this man race man does their own
conscience team tell me Amelia let there
be women to abuse their husbands in such
gross kind there'll be some such no
question what's that oh such deed for
all the world why won't you know but his
heaven at night your I'll either by this
heavenly light I might good as well of
the dark it's how do such a deed for all
the world the world the huge place it's
a great price to pay for a small vice in
short I think that would snuff winters I
think I stood Mary I would not do Stu
thing for a joint ring loafer measures
of law oh for God's Pittacus no caps nor
any petty exhibition but for the whole
well I do not think there is any such
woman yeah well gosselin but I do think
it is their husbands faulted wives Duval
oh say that they let their duties poorer
treasures and depositing laps or else
break out in peevish Genesis throwing
restraint upon us or say this try cos
we're full we have gold and though we
have some grace yet have we some revenge
net husband's know their wives have
sense like then they see and smell and
have their palates but for sweet and
sour as husbands have what is it that
they do when they change us for others
is it sport I think it is and other
fictional breeders I think it done it's
fair to the bus fares it is sent to and
have not we affects your desires for
sport and frailty as men have then let
them use as well else let them know the
gills we do burials instructors so nice
you
it is the cause it is the cause so my
soul let me not name it to you you
chaste stars it is the cause yet I'm not
shared her blood nor scar that whiter
skin of hers than snow and smooth as
monumental alabaster yet she must die
hilfe should betray more men
put out the light and then put out the
light if i quench lead our flaming
minister i can again my former light
restore should i repent me but once but
out thy light the cunning stratton of
excelling nature I know not where is
that Promethean heat that can die former
light will you hello hi this Damona will
you come to bed my lord
have you prayed tonight s tomorrow if
you bethink yourself of any crime
unreconciled is yet to heaven and grace
solicit for it straight unless my note
what do you mean well do it and be brief
I would not kill I unprepared spirit no
heaven forfend I would I kill my soul
talk you of killing right I do I've met
miss you I'm him with all my heart if
you say so I hope you will not kill me
hey peace and be still I will sue and
yet I fear you why should fear I no not
since guiltiness I know not and yet I
feel you live here
that handkerchief let handkerchief which
I so loved it gave me now gaze to Cassio
no but my life and so then for the man
at us kids so take heed take he's a
perjury a lot on my deathbed I say ah
man you have mercy to I never did love
kiss you in my life I saw the how could
she found it then I never gave it
himself i'm here the legend could face a
charge she has confessed what my lord
but he accused thee no he will not say
so no his mouth is stopped honest Iago
attain order for it what did you did had
all his hairs been lives migrate revenge
at stomach for them all strumming we'd
suffer up to my face banish me my lord
would kill me no strumpet give me
tomorrow let me live tonight it is too
late
cold I go even like the chest oh good
see cuts it slave with me that was in
the possession of this Emily site hey
Nia Martin wins roast me and sulfur war
Sri and steep down Oh normal it is the
very error of the moon she comes more
nearer earth she was what that makes men
mad oh that was my ladies boys oh wait
this Mona who done this d
I myself
you heard her say yourself it was not I
almost needs for poker she's like a liar
gone to burning hell what either killed
her sister Holly since she was a hard no
tougher but she results to wedlock I
what can't you hey achieving true if
Evan would make me such another would
one entire and perfect crystal but not
so different I'll up and hey the key
word oh all right we'll see the told me
first an honest man he isn't hates the
slime that sticks on filthy deeds to
fund a puzzle to pay bargain yes I was
even finest know over the headland our
buddy hugs your best
who the villain is not be some man you
just thought Joseph it is Mike response
I know that it's not speak for my
heartbeat oh I told him what I for them
for no more than what he found until the
captain Lou Tennant she was off I did
know your family huh oh my oh my oh
wicked not she felt with Kat you did you
say when Castillo with Castillo mistress
go to charm your tongue I've a lot charm
like I'm bound to speak my mistress your
life mattered in her bid hey they're not
masters it is true indeed I think I
snapped oh they're lucky I thought so
then I'll kill myself agreed mad good
gentlemen Roger get your home let me
have leave to speak tis proper I obey
Him but not now pochamma Seattle I shall
never over nay lady down and wrong but
thou has children sweetest inner through
the tear didn't lift her eyes oh sure
foul diago knows that she was casio at
the act of shape a thousand times can be
held here kassius confessed it and she
did gratify his amorous works with that
same a kitchen laughs hello hello hold
your peace right no I will think it's
different the doctor way heaven mendham
pebbles nickel oh oh oh Christ shame
against me get our people um stone that
handkerchief I'll speak survive on by
touching and to get my husband
she loved me
this matches Park confessed his ability
what the hell did you and he consent in
Cassie's death I dear general I never
gave you cause a fellow your power and
your command is taken off and Cassio
rules in Cyprus
they are afraid though you to see me
weaponed here is my journey's end here
is my butt and very CE mark of my utmost
sale
will you i pray demand that damn a devil
why nothing snared my soul and body
nothing are there no stones in heaven
what surf at the Thunder
I pray you when you Shirley's unlucky
deeds relate speak of me as I am nothing
extenuate nor set down aught in malice
then must you speak of one that loved
not wisely but wiggle of one not easily
jealous but being wrought perplexed in
the extreme of one whose hand like the
bass Indian through a pearl away richer
than all his tribe set you down this
you