I'm ready this is the US Attorney's
Office Southern District of New York in
reference to the World Trade Center
bombing case would you state your name
please Special Agent John antis ephedra
Bureau of Investigation New York office
we're all on the same side mr. Han Tzu
we're here to prepare you for what you
might face on the witness stand right
and you were part of a joint task force
on counterterrorism for the New York
Region yep did you have any idea before
the fact that this bombing had been
planned no nothing like this had ever
happened in America so as a member of
the Joint Task Force you had no leads at
all to these guys well not enough to
take to the bank counselor it's hard
standing that the FBI prior to the
bombing had confiscated terrorist
training films from the very same people
accused oh there's then and now then
they were amateur video tapes propaganda
no I agree they look pretty scary
I
so these videotapes for how-to guide on
the construction of a bomb what was your
thinking about these people as far as we
knew they were devout followers of a
blind sheikh whose mosque was a shabby
storefront were you aware of the
influence to shake out on these people
we knew they revered him yeah enough to
kill people for him there was no
evidence they were doing anything
illegal there were Muslims didn't mean
they were terrorists
land of Satan we must conquer it to
purify it all or has imposed the holy
war on us it must be one of the
pinnacles of our lives we all God
obedient an obedience is owed to him who
disobeys God the laws of God had been
usin my Crusaders loss the hand of a
thief is not cut off the drinker of
liquor is not whipped the adulterer is
not stormed Islamic holy law should be
followed the letter the society where
the design is mix money night so soon it
must be bad are you sure it is the right
thing don't ask me we spread Islam by
calling the infidels to Allah and the
text and in our way o Lord great said
against and make ready your strength
including steeds of war to strike terror
into the hearts of your enemies
must be one of the pinnacles of her life
Vivian's an obedience is odd him who
disobey police
license and registration
ego
where are you gentlemen going surfin do
you mind if I look in the trunk you wish
you
stop see a friend about what the
dealer's license
your car dealer to
stay by the car
what is he doing this is Eva then he was
a policeman it would shoot us this is
Afghanistan and he was a Russian out of
shot a minor but this is America it will
do nothing and we will do as we please
is one of you gentlemen else said nose
hair to say yet no safe that is me can I
see some identification
these are yours yes from some used cars
i'm selling
you keep those safeties on now always
assault rifles high-powered handguns
what were the police thinking the gun
dealers license was current they weren't
breaking any laws they have rights the
police didn't even inform us of this
until long after the fact I don't have
any jurisdiction over the state cops to
you we didn't even know who they were
until after the ramp I was shot about
kahani yeah you could say that woke us
up
Travis
o.o duty I don't sit here whoo whoa
haha
yeah where to
rabbi meir Connie leader of a fanatical
Jewish sect based in Crown Heights and a
central figure of radical
conduct was shot and fatally wounded
tonight in midtown Manhattan gani had
just delivered a speech as a sealant
divert the trouser and fire
jews to emigrate to israel when the
arriving rabbi was shot at close range
in front of his followers at this hotel
in midtown Manhattan last night he died
shortly after being taken to know what
we have and all we know is we have a
lone gunman who committed a homicide in
the city in Europe el se na saya there
was no indication at all of any
conspiracy by kahani was pronounced dead
at approximately 945pm el Sayyid Nosair
who was wounded by uniformed postal
policemen while attempting to flee the
scene was arraigned at his hospital
bedside and charged with murder a police
spokesman said no Sarah walked up to the
podium where kahani was speaking and
fired quit swearing no sales car and a
no standing zone where a mile from the
hotel repop Connie the lone gunman parks
a mile away how was he planning to get
back to his car she wasn't planning on
taking that cab you think maybe wasn't
so alone oh it's too soon to tell looks
like the NYPD wants to keep the public
calm and ignorantly I'm a member of the
NYPD enters if I don't care where you're
ignorant or not well you're part of an
FBI task force Napoli an NYPD FBI task
force yeah yeah yeah so is this the hall
yeah they found 47 boxes of crap no
there's a part of tapes videos
newspapers pamphlets books looks like a
diary how's your Arabic are you fed the
rich don't you have translators yeah I
could spend about a half hour on this
before they went back to reading Saddam
Hussein's male Washington's a little
more concerned about Iraq being in
Kuwait than the sponsor mmm they get
anything we will demoralize the enemies
of Allah by destroying and blowing up
the pillars of this civilization
translator says this is Islamic poetry
doesn't rhyme
maybe this does sermons by Sheikh Omar
Abdel Rahman Muslims must perform jihad
huh this one says Jesus come the USA is
the land of Satan where do we start got
to find Satan get him a bodyguard this
guy Center to life in Attica shut the
ratline front of andhra witnesses take a
fucking magician to get him off
courtroom spectators were stunned by the
verdict of not guilty on the charge of
murdering rabbi cahana defense attorney
william kunstler apparently succeeded
with his hints that kahani was actually
killed by enemies in his own
organization no Sarah supporters were
jubilant even though he was convicted on
weapons in assault charges where did
that leave you didn't wrestle questions
yes we suspected there were others
involved was there any evidence of a
conspiracy laughter no Sarah was
acquitted the case wasn't a priority
with the bureau thank you Napoli and I
were still hunting for leads but we
didn't have much to go on nobody in our
office spoke Arabic your informant did
do you have an appointment no I have
information the FBI will want to have it
and what's the nature of this
information I must speak to someone in
authority is the director of the Office
you I'll see who's available will you
have a seat mr. Salim I met solemn dena
me here over there please
I told me in a way to yeah they will see
don't see the messenger can't wait much
longer he has to get back to the ship
but shit you know he has the plans to
kidnap the president and replace him
with a clone from the Crab Nebula
miss I don't know the take hmm i'll call
you mr. celeb all the other girl I must
speak to someone in authority hmm I'm
special agent Nancy Floyd of the
Intelligence Division excellent
this is Special Agent John ants above
the counter terrorism task force how do
you do so you want me to talk again if
you don't mind it's these guys I know
what guys friends of know Sarah the one
who shot the rabbi the old fellow Sheikh
Omar Abdel Rahman they are planning they
are talking all the time about ways to
hurt America more they want to hurt
America huh it supports Israel supports
Mubarak in Egypt shake hits mubarak he
had to sneak out the view ship they had
him under arrest and these people trust
you do you think I am one of them I was
in the Egyptian army for the Jews since
I me so why do you want to work with the
FBI they dishonor of my religion Islam
is for peace the world Islam it means
peace and the precious Sheikh Omar he
encouraged the ones who killed my
president so that I was in his bodyguard
when he was murdered I took three
bullets one in the head and two in the
belly and these people don't know your
background that was underground
undercover with army intelligence i
traveled everywhere I met the King
Hussein I'm it Saddam Hussein no one
ever knew me so you were a bodyguard who
or you were a spy that's both and an
intelligence analyst like you like you
huh yeah you know Colonel Qaddafi uh the
FBI doesn't get to Libya match well I
can explain to you him he has scars on
his temples you you can see in the
pictures well when a child is bad and
mean and crazy they say it's because he
has black blood so they cut the temples
to let the black blood flow that's
fascinating mr. slim but I think we're
more interested in those friends of mr.
nose hairs you're talking about so here
to him I am gonna man did they help
recruit the rabbi and I don't
they haven't told me are they talking
about shooting anybody else hey I'm
talking about all kinds of things they
talk about the shooting bombing bombing
yeah all I am looking for is a small
weekly retainer I recommend we use them
meet you Sheikh Omar is going to an
Islamic action conference in Detroit
celebs officer driving there I see from
your report is also offered to explain
how black blood makes people crazy and
me the guy's a little screwy mr.
cultural addict the guy is full of shit
you and I both know no sure didn't act
alone crazy arabs killing crazy Jews I
believe that is still against the law
sir he asked you for money didn't he
they all do we checked him out he never
got anywhere near Sadat and the only
Israelis he's ever fought with a falafel
sellers on macdougal street was he in
intelligence yes and we think he still
is Egyptian intelligence would like
nothing more than to get this Sheikh
Omar in hot water he's a major-league
rabble rouser over there and the
Egyptians wouldn't mind manipulating the
FBI to do it so which is it sir which is
what what it means to work with us
because he's hustling us for a buck or
because he's manipulating us for
Egyptian intelligence and their kind of
mutually exclusive on a limited basis
only using just make sure he doesn't use
you
seven to twenty two years in jail it's
an average the jury said no sir is not
beautiful but the judge gives him 22
years for their little charges I'm not
surprised this is America Israel and
Egypt not the tail of the snake America
is its head it will always persecute us
you were in the Army in Egypt serving
the half your government infidel move
back and said that before him I'm sorry
say you should make it up with God I
will how can I turn your rifles barrel
to the chest of President Mubarak I'm
telling him he asks everyone he needs to
kill mubarak what are the rules of the
unbeliever take over God's justice good
thing I went I think there were a lot of
terrorists there and they get a very
good price of a rental of the van what's
this Oh the Sheikh wat batteries for his
Walkman the shade but we're not paying
the shakes Hills I map we're paying
yours Nancy look at these huh everybody
at the conference in Detroit but who are
they k grave risk security was very
suspicious so you don't have their names
I'm still working and I am still waiting
to hear about my salary's well i think i
can get you about 500 a week you think
he asked me to murder the President
Mubarak how do I know that Nazi I need
more gas money huh
I want you to kill the judge Gilly or
can that be my drinking for me I'd want
to get out of here maybe we should wait
till your appeal has been decided cousin
this might prejudice the other judges he
was not merciful with me well you'll see
what can be done good he does not have
to give you all the time you could kill
in this weekend I did my part drama huh
you are sitting outside do nothing do
something build some bombs put the judge
and the Jewish Assemblyman dollar stores
the serta parts in China top on Canal
Street Oh America everything is legal ah
so I will do it good also ask my lawyer
about the post office policeman who shot
me you want us to kill him to know him
I'm sorry you cook fish four minutes per
centimeter measure the thickness the
women always cook too long my Egyptian
life she knew how to cook my American
wife she did not do you spice how many
wives do you have I met at the moment
none but there is always the possibility
no I have something we can use for those
bums no sato told us to build nail gun
cartridges I can get thousands through
my work they are contractors supplies
yeah for shooting nails there is
powdered in there use your imagination
nail gun cartridges yeah he says he can
get 10,000 well he'll need him he can't
do much with the hose good no sad is
telling us to kill the judge anybody
going to try well they're counting on me
remember we don't want you killing
anybody I don't want anybody killing
anybody okay so you have my man
five hundred dollars they like to buy
you a drink I'm on duty American women
hmm well the country hey Jen
one informant what are we getting here
conspiracy to commit murder our guys the
murderer and he's not gonna do it still
a crime to try samachar out at least we
got a good recipe for fish judge is
still alive we are making progress about
this in chinatown phosphoric fuse what
you going to blow up your soda or do
something for sure hard i still need
detonators i still need a safe place to
work and I need people to help me one
hand cannot club my friend I told him
when the right time comes he will meet
the underground people but first we must
have a fat we're from shape tomorrow
does the sheriff know what you up doing
this she knows what he needs to know
what we need to know is that we are in
accordance with the law of Allah we knew
no service dangerous but he was locked
up our informant was bringing us nothing
and the others didn't seem to have the
material of the knowledge to use them
what they did have was religious fervor
and that is a very very powerful thing
they are waiting for a religious opinion
from the shake then they want me to make
12 pipe bombs for the judge the Jewish
Assemblyman people all over New York
City because America is the puppet
master of all the enemies of God they
see this is your proof no Sharon told
him where to get it the yellow pages
could have told him where to get it okay
telling you everything they say and what
are you telling your friends and
Egyptian intelligence everything we say
they called me I told Nancy I told him
what Nancy said it was okay to tell
right mr. Sammon for this operation to
continue for the FBI to believe anything
you tell us you're going to have to wear
a wire I know how that works if I make
tapes I have to testify where I made
them how I made them is this please
people are dangerous to me to my family
no tapes no more money that's the policy
here one condition
you listen to the tape so that you can
believe what I'm telling you then you
give it back to me so i can destroy it
give you back the tape why don't i give
you all our files while I man how about
my tie you like my tie sir I really
don't think if mr. Salim won't wear a
wire and let us keep our own fucking
tapes then he can be polygraphed lie
detective or he can kiss this five
hundred dollars a week goodbye and
peddle their stories elsewhere mr. we
are not going to run the FBI or mr.
celebs uncorroborated word Napoli and I
are gonna try to corroborate we got some
lists of people who are in touch with no
Ser fine then what do we need this guy
for do you mind that is exactly the
wrong way to handle him this is a
terrorist task force and he's the only
source of information we've got that's
what intelligence agents always say you
get conned by your own diamond think
we're being calm put that son of a bit
on a lie detector or fire
so you have the result well you passed
up here up here uh wounds wanted to be
extra sure so we sent the grass back
down to Washington and they changed the
evaluation team conclusive so I'm not
lying yeah but as far as the FBI is
concerned you're not telling the truth
either so I must wear the wire and they
must then testify there's nothing i can
do you know how it is i mine yeah i have
children you're a family still in Egypt
is too dangerous we can protect you
forever i magnin see you must watch
those people who follow them tape them
that's what we need you for think about
it well if you're gonna bow out now
you're gonna need to come up with a
pretty good story good son I'm good at
that huh ask mr. Williams I wish you
peace
this was your only source i wanted to
use him but why'd you let him walk
wasn't my call it wasn't any one
person's call he didn't pass his
polygraph you can go all the way back to
Washington on this no sir cold he asked
about your progress there is a plumber
who can get us the fives for the pipe
bombs not me brother I must stay away
from this and you will stay away from me
why FBI an agent talk to me today they
were watching me I saw their car they
follow you on a lot I took three samples
that you will have to carry on without
me I knew it I knew they were watching
I wish I could be with you my brother I
will tell no sir
Oh struggle is not surf do not worry my
friend the shoulder there are others
coming salaam really excellent
we'll see how the brave this country is
but I live here before I used to deliver
pizzas you walk separately now the girls
met me at the door is in their underwear
practically you will not believe it
brother do not call me brother you do
not know me get in that line who your
part
thank you down there next passport you
don't believe me look it up in the
computer you are Swedish mr. car my
mother was Swedish mr. Kong I think you
better talk to an inspector you're from
Iraq mr. usage yes I am where's your
visa don't have a visa I request
political asylum
you always travel with four passports
mr. Khan or should I say mr. Mohammed
that seems to be your name in England in
Iraq mr. Josh in Pakistan to judge I
live in Houston I am only trying to go
home do you solemnly swear to tell the
truth the whole truth and nothing but
the truth so help you God yes I did what
is your true full name and Z with
yourself are you traveling alone yes
what is the purpose of your entry into
the United States to escape political
and religious persecution which one of
these is your real name my name is ramzi
yousef I needed these to escape the
authorities mr. Josh or whoever you are
you are caring fraudulent passports it
was attempted illegal entry into the
United States I'm placing you under
arrest you are entitled to an attorney
if you cannot afford an attorney one
will be provided to represent you have
you ever been involved in subversive
activity against any government what is
your occupation electrical engineer you
have attempted illegal entry into the
United States you may leave the United
States voluntarily or if you wish to
stay up here before an immigration judge
which do you choose to do appear before
a judge waiting
sir what are you go asylum application
from an Iraqi I think we should detain
him until his court date he's carrying
multiple ID cards in several ranges who
is it cousins just arrested some yo
you're with four passports and number
one sir I really think we should hold on
to this guy cells are full you want to
take him home with you no thanks do you
understand your rights as I've explained
them yes wonderful you'll be transported
to your cell in a few minutes sit down
this your airplane reading Jesus looks
like a diagram for a bomb mr. Youssef
your asylum hearing will be conducted on
december eight three months time yes do
you promise to appear yes of course well
in that case you're released until then
on your own recognizance I'm free to go
you're free to go
your Foreman didn't know about yourself
at that point we had no informed if you
want to hear about youssef you better
get the AI NS the CIA and the State
Department down here no one told us when
Yousef came into the country we had one
thing to go on the kahani killing and
they'll see his phone records that's two
things I don't know no no Sam he says
you don't no no no ser makes me wonder
why no sir called him three times a week
before he shot kahani looks like a few
wondering this might a bit easier if
your boss hadn't canned our only inside
source left us nothing but antique phone
records maybe but you didn't know slim
how many more names on that list 37 I'm
based on what we've seen so far that's
37 phone calls to total strangers
welcome brother we have been waiting for
you your presence is an honor it's very
private your presence is a blessing as
private as you can get in jersey city
and it is close to the most five hundred
and fifty dollars a month you had to pay
one month in advance and one more
security it's a reasonable investment
one hour of button is worth 80 years of
prayer are you ready to go into battle
brother it is the path to paradise
excellent
take a little longer than an hour to
strike out blue
your unit will be in Billy number two
that's right over there now he helped
moving or packing we have supplies you'd
say all right do we take care of it
ourselves okay you're the boss mr.
Campbell come on can I pay you know uh
actually you sort of have
Weber this is dress no Sarah called him
twice a day shark oh honey no ever huh
I'm just like we're gonna play Avon lady
no one's bringing down and confessing to
being in some conspiracy with no Sarah
shall there isn't one and it's just
possible John Williams was right solenn
with blowin smoke up our asses now there
was something there I'm telling you
that's this guy well I we're looking for
mr. Weber whoever yeah he's supposed to
be in 68 oh yes she is revered the wife
she's German the guy is an era of 0
halima well drives a limo you guys are
cops Leah can you tell by my haircut
good luck I obtained he some kind of
terrorist he got a lot of guys coming
and going at all hours and some of the
mail he gets here gan catalogs you name
it I hope you know the bastard bingo
wanna talk to now I'm tired of talking
just get a warrant
okay mr. Kamal I think we can take care
of you nitric acid 105 gallons sulfuric
acid 60 gallons ninety-three percent
pure please that won't be a problem urea
a thousand pounds what is the nitrogen
content forty-six forty-seven percent
the fan of me now that we're gonna need
a different kind of paperwork on what
paperwork is the banana mean you know
someone unscrupulous could turn that
into RDX and make a hell of an explosion
so we got some extra regulation on that
you just give me some background
information on your company are so you
want this delivered to the storage
facility such beauty or chrissy i know
it's terrible i got some forms if you
could just never mind no I'll get them
the time I mean later
mahmood Abu Halima yes Taxi and
Limousine Commission we're investigating
some reported irregularities in town car
services so so we need to see your logs
how but I have a break I was going home
now it won't take long
white dinner
hey what are you doing there they're not
home carnet gasoline oh my I don't smell
anything should I leave the building
we'll let you know got it
clear yo gun magazines guy wasn't lying
no gun the recorded sermons by Sheikh
Omar Abdel Rahman boring not illegal
anything in there yeah a lot of really
ugly clothes mr. time you know we never
did match some of those fingerprints we
found a no sales car then I just shot
the rabbi why don't we subpoena these
jocas for prints see if we get any hits
Floyd's people got two surveillance
photos of celeb and espouse at the
shooting range so put on a show
Jones uh-huh Brad here huh
here we go you
so you searched Abu Halima's apartment
and found nothing we could use it was
helping you set back the bomb could you
follow this guy wouldn't have let you to
you Seth we didn't know Yousef was Jesus
hindsight's a pretty amazing thing isn't
a counselor you wanted me to take these
inside that's why we got them isn't it
yes please smokeless powder as you
wished thanks
very good Bellamy take this inside too
how's it going Shh is an idiot otherwise
well chemicals are being delivered to
the storage we're setting up
manufacturing here it's just a few more
things I need yeah there's anything else
I can get you ready to serve you are a
true warrior red hair something with
Europeans left behind in our country so
they say but now I'm a warrior for Allah
tell me what you need I will get it we
have another brother very American it'll
be easier for him she's beautiful yes I
think so but you're gonna marry her
without even meeting her I met her I
spent two weeks with her family in
Jordan last year but aside from that our
families arranged it she is a very nice
person well I guess you can't do any
worse than I did my parents are making
the wedding here do you know a good
place to get the gown Chemical
Engineering mr. I adds office I'll see
City chemical I'll take it in my office
hello yes I need lead nitrate and some
of the enamine two pounds no no don't
ship it here it's for another small
business i'm working with Kemal and
company I'd like delivery to be made to
our storage facility excuse me one
moment riedel concepts in Somerset
she'll love it
yeah fuck those pictures they know about
us if they know anything you'll be
sitting here and I end of it is just
intimidation mr. algo brownie please
step inside
the share is a great man a religious man
you've never heard him advocate violence
he is a man of God he talks only of the
ways of God what do you talk about when
you go visit your cousin America their
family he always likes to hear about the
children why do you bring me here you
suspect me of anything why you doing it
I don't see these people anymore you
know that John was that well I met Emily
country were out there being
fingerprinted photographed invited have
a friendly chat they wouldn't look funny
if we didn't invite you to the party yes
you're right all right whatever you do
to them he was also do to me you shake
is a great man a religious man who
writes the material for you guys there
needs a little snapping up allies are
guiding this and everything he wouldn't
be guiding you into the area of guns and
fight bombs would he know he would not
so
where'd I go to give my fingerprints hmm
well I see you broke him down real good
you got any better ideas we subpoenaed
all the names we got from no stairs
phone records they could just be his
bowling buddies yeah goin great huh guys
look more bad news Washington just
turned down our proposal for a wiretap
on the shacks phone the hell do they
need to get us in there evidence of an
ongoing crime wait a minute I mean
pardon my ignorance but isn't that what
a wiretap is supposed to get exactly if
we had a wire to have them to have the
evidence we need it a wiretap or so it
wouldn't eat a wiretap plus the check is
a religious leader well there's all
kinds of agency guidelines about I'm
bridging his First Amendment rights even
though he's on a terrace watch this one
supposed to be let in the country in the
first place uh-huh it's great freedom of
religion protects a bunch of murdering
fanatics and if these guys feel like
blowing us off with a line a sermon
there's not a goddamn thing we can do
about it back home the police would be
shoving barbed wire up their asses hmm
no wonder they all come here America a
great place to live you're a terrorist
even I hate
brother is josh take that into the
kitchen I'm working with an imbecile hmm
put it in the sink it's not another mix
I goes it in prison beds they are
excellent they are better than home and
they have color televisions the others
watch music videos all day with nude
girls I turn away so I don't offend God
that is excellent of it and they had my
court date that you have yours yet oh my
i think it fast and i forgot to go i got
only a six month sentence that i have
nearly served already plus a fifty
dollar fine fifty dollars we can manage
that I list me about the explosives
manuals I was carrying hmm i told them i
was using them to compile an
encyclopedia the judge believed me she
told the prosecutor that they would have
to return the managed to me and if
anything is missing or damaged he will
have to pay it's too wonderful i will
give them to my attorney you should have
everything you need now i'll call him
and guess what they're giving me a
course in computers it is so wonderful I
got to go
Oh too much shriya then go go to the
storage we need more nitric acid to for
you real we can substitute Yuri but not
even an ass like you can piss nitric
acid sorry how cold is it tonight do you
think 25 degrees Fahrenheit I think 15 i
miss the weather of calm it's not one
time only in my mind when i raise a boy
whether it's little benefit ah shielded
nitroglycerin if its source can be
ignited by the motion of its own
molecules I hear what we need then we go
to make history Mohammed think about
that I think so let's write the books
ourselves system so the world knows
in 1118 with the Spanish attacked
algeciras it's not my fault then I see
green light on over here and I'll get
caught dog not my phone when I kick just
lie back mr. you're gonna take good care
okay the car what about the car my
things are in the don't worry about that
the police will take care of these
things okay so you gotta relax where
will they take the car don't worry about
it just breathe relax relax we'll take
care of you the police who take care of
your things oh my god i can tell you
where you always got what what you do my
cousin this is unbelievable yes you mean
to say that the jersey police had the
master bomber his accomplice and the
chemicals under their noses before the
bombing be funny if it wasn't true you
got everything we told the police garage
man we were taking some personal papers
out of the car no one noticed and we
have been working nearly a night ladies
ready excellent i'll be working too
right here very convenient I've ordered
some powdered metals fateh I thought we
were finished they are few without them
the urea nitrate with them
and now flying here I have a better idea
what we have made will push the building
so far at the peak of this explosion at
our one's breaking point if we could
make a secondary explosion the whole
thing could collapse into the next town
both towers down I need compressed
hydrogen some the restricted list dal
brother I had let him work with the food
I ordered the hydrogen that you said
wanted the banks will be delivered to
the storage facility tomorrow and we are
ready to do it tomorrow night
they are so proud of those this is it we
go in here happy new year from a tap on
the shakes phone I thought it was a lost
cause how'd you get the warrant think
someone adjusted the bribe to judge the
pig Mubarak is killing more believers in
Egypt the Sheikh talks a lot about Egypt
get the boys work that can begin sitter
jihad all of these particular boys from
Pakistan there's nothing about new york
new jersey united states there is
nothing about anything anywhere west of
libya maximum flu and seven feet hmm
Oh blaze
but we are big men
so do you think we can do this we cannot
fail we must find the outer wall of this
tower and place the bar next to it when
it explodes one tower will knock the
other down over there
this is the law of tower one where we
must be haha you can't park there and
you've done I'm making a delivery and I
work here gasps home what just go we've
seen what we need
should I not tell him we're making
delivery to
piss off this time it is not my fault
what do you think you got wasted three
months knocking on doors talking a
wiseass Egyptians sallam said they were
going to kill people yeah damn it John
there is something going on out there
and I know it well if there is will be
the last to find out
door back door yeah some what could you
want if this one's not big enough I got
a cute band you can rent right there
that's when is how high about eight and
a half I think this one talk to the odd
two times he said it's coming today she
found another supplier yes hey you guys
want to wait inside sure this coffee if
you want it but I wouldn't drink any if
you plan on sleeping in the next 48
hours so I see you guys here quite a lot
what do you do for a living I'm gonna
fuck turning oh really what do you make
I don't know how you say it in English
oh that's for us thank you
hey where's the stuff compressed
hydrogen and it's uh co d kappa money
order no you can't bring them in here i
just did where do you want me to put him
yeah but no there's no flammable gas is
allowed yes no you've got to take them
back out of here keep the caps on
keeping away from open flame nothing's
gonna have no flammable gases allowed is
what I oh wait he isn't read your
contract hey look my and loan irawan I
got a schedule to make that it's okay we
are not taking them inside we have a van
coming when 20 minutes 20 minutes
thank you thank you what's going on I
caught them bringing in gas cylinders
they got a van coming to take them out
again those guys are in and out with all
kinds of shit I wonder what they snuck
in here we didn't catch it I'm gonna
have a look how we don't have a master
key do we headquarters does if I explain
this shit to him they'll mail it to me I
gotta find out what the hell's going on
in there first thing next week
no we are ready
push the bottle
Oh
no I'll Drive
hello far around 60 25 a secretary for
smoking pot they want me to change all
the locks this minute I tell them I'm
afraid I have a lunch meeting how about
that the one you call that lunch
eggplant parmesan home court and this is
an excellent opacity are you two gonna
fight this battle again I'm gonna go out
and get some air we're gonna bear down
here don't we yeah yeah Bon Appetit Wow
just because a horse runs better in the
mud then she does when it's dry doesn't
mean she runs faster in the mud then a
horse that runs better when it's dry you
have the horses all figured out how come
you're still down here with us cuz I
like you guys Steve you told me it
didn't like him
something I don't understand these
people will go out to the Hamptons they
sit on the l.i.e for four hours a wild
good fishing off Montauk I can buy a
fish in eight that a king and his court
the King has eggplant parmesan and I
brought you an extra portion what are
you gonna call the baby OddParents
deviation to run to it in a broad 3 jun
abroad pepto-bismol
anything like this
ambulances fire engines and police cars
are crowding the Narrows
district attorney the US Attorney Secret
Service da bomb squad Port Authority
that's everyone with the Coast Guard
confirmation that at least two people
have died as a result of the explosion
at the World Trade Center and hundreds
more have been injured by what was
reportedly a massive blast that shook
both towers the official cause of the
blast is not known but a Serbian group
has claimed credit for Obama to protest
the police it was not the Serbs it was
the fifth liberation battalion of the
Islamic Jihad it was me
there are unconfirmed reports that a
bomb not a transformer malfunction as
it's an earlier reported cause these
floating rental so we know a little bit
more than that guy but not much there
are traces of nitrate in the air which
means that we know that it definitely
was a bomb what kind of bomb a big bomb
it had to come into that garage in some
kind of a truck now ATF has people
sifting through the rubble they're
looking for bomb fragments car fragments
any needle in that haystack any claim of
credit well the most believable so far
has come from the Serbian Liberation
Front there fella called in early and
the Serbians aren't exactly thrilled by
our policy in Bosnia but we have also
had claims from the Black Liberation
Front the Chinese Liberation Front
islamic jihad and just about every wacko
east of Kansas we're gonna have to work
together and put everyone we can onto
this cuz whoever did it isn't stupid
money attended from you is stolen really
oh is that yesterday I want a refund on
my security deposit it was stolen
yesterday why don't you call me
yesterday I didn't know what to do I
told police fine you bring me the fish
before and I'll get started on the
paperwork for your refund I cannot have
a refund now no without a report huh I
get it
who are you looking for anonymous tip
Serbian bomb mastermind flying home male
average height green sport jacket looks
like green is the in color
yeah blue nah it's another Lester time I
don't know what I'm looking for we found
a piece of the van de sure carried the
bomb it had a VIN number computer spit
out a vehicle ID stolen right now all we
have to do to find the bomber has solved
some week-old car theft now was rented I
rented it claims it was stolen but I
don't believe in you're not gonna
believe it either his name is Mohamed
Salah me Shh now faces spell when I albo
Helena's buddies a big fan of Sheikh
Omar celeb must have been this close to
her she hears the kappa salami is
pestering the rental place trying to get
a refund of his deposit John we had
those guys will get him
right
yes in a report on stolen van I get it
from police the other man told me to
bring it from my refund four hundred
dollars is he here uh no I'm sorry it's
his day off but he told me you'd be
coming we've been having a lot of
problems with stolen cars and I really
want to help you settle your claim but I
thought maybe first you could help us
with little information hey bandhu was
stolen from shopping center birth mother
plaza it says here I see um you were
shopping I a rented van to help friends
move really from where to where I cannot
remember address here which address
either one both I see uh Jill anybody
else drive the van just me listen I feel
the gas tank with gas I think I should
get back fifteen dollars for that too
because the van was stolen with your gas
and exactly how much should it cost you
a full of tank what does that concern do
it in there throwing him out this is how
unbelievable no this is unbelievable
excuse me miss who are you police you're
gonna have to move out of here right now
nee-san reported one of the Bombers was
expected here today newsday report have
to leave this police action please hurry
thank you you put down four hundred
dollars and then you had three days use
of the van before it was stolen so that
comes to 271 dollars and sixty-eight
cents and I guess that means technically
speaking we only owe you 132 dollars and
thirty eight cents it isn't fair okay I
think we'd be willing to go as high as
200 to settle your claim and keep you
happy this dish is not to justice okay
what about 250 250 keep you happy get
you out of here I have idea we split it
equally half of 400 you'll take 200
that's good yes plus 15 foot of us okay
all right good wonderful that's terrific
we'll do that um yeah just sign right
there maybe sign okay
there you go thank you yes sir any much
thank you video goodbye do you have a
good day yes take care hi thank you down
on your knees hands Baghdad ticket to
Amsterdam come on address book Mohammed
Salim a you're under arrest what can I
help you FBI don't move
why I tastier why am I solitary I did
not to know if the devil leaders of this
taking place in here will end the war
can we stay but our bowling what is so
important not here let's walk what is
happen they have arrested salami
they've taken the out
how can I have your ticket I am flying
to Saudi Arabia then I will go to my
family in Egypt but not sure it won't be
safe go to my country that's done i will
give you letters to some people they
will take gather for them
no thank you we appreciate the district
attorney's cooperation but this is going
to be a federal case yeah you've done
such a wonderful job of it so far we've
made some arrests you should have made
the same goddamn arrests after that
rabbi was shot have you seen this lately
the stuff taken from no Sarah's
apartment this is when he was the lone
gunman that's what your people said
right because you didn't give him a clue
your translator said this was Islamic
poetry we had 47 boxes of material we
didn't have the people to excavate it
all Islamic poetry we will demoralize
the enemies of Allah by destroying and
blowing up the pillars of their
civilization and the tall buildings of
which they are so proud even if we saw
that it's not against the law to ride it
and what were we supposed to do stake
out every tall building in the country
no but you might have done something to
protect the tallest what is your own
explosives man think about this formula
for your Rio nitrate bomb found in nose
hairs possession oh there was we're
going to have to get that to you
wonderful communication maybe we should
be looking ahead here people and not to
the past I'm afraid we're looking ahead
to more explosions six innocent people
have died and you've arrested a couple
of foot soldiers in this thing not the
brains what are you doing about the
shake so far there isn't enough evidence
to charge him with anything but
immigration fraud apparently entered the
country while he was on a terrorist
watch list and how did that happen
officially it was an error by a clerk in
our embassy in Khartoum what do you
think CIA let him it as a favor they
were on the same side in Afghanistan
officially or unofficially do you have
any idea what he's up to now we're
working on it well if you do happen to
hear anything to please let us know
before the next building blows up excuse
me
well I understood we used to have an
informant in with us p so yes but we
were never sure where his loyalty leg
will figure it the fuck out and get him
the fuck back in here
John the lie detector is now I suppose
you only believe me this never would
have happened I know but don't repeat
that I told you so I told you the World
Trade Center is one of their targets go
back to your nose I said the World Trade
Center Empire State Building grand
central station I did go back to my not
so mad I didn't see that you know it
takes a bomb for you to listen you're
not listening yet we are listening now
and it touches you John huh I was the
one who didn't want to wear a wire I
didn't want to testify 50,000 people
could have got them killed because I'm a
coward like shit six people did die a
thousand were injured if the shakes
involved we want him people arrested
won't testify against neither do they
love him we need to hear on conspiring
this time I will we're aware good cuz
you know this not going to stop it's not
the last bomb at the rest of my life and
my children's life will be in jeopardy
if you have to testify will put you in
witness protection yep Manny John have
another job in the year mastercard is
calling have to tell them I'm it's a
lame is not at home my divorce lawyer he
wants a thousand five hundred when he's
up to the US Attorney but a big case
like this you're talking six figures
easy maybe two hundred thousand million
dollars John right
I'm not selling potatoes so the man who
wasn't worth 500 bucks was now worth a
million we were after the shake and it
was worth whatever it took the only way
to get the shake was to put sell em back
in with him they still trusted him the
shake and his followers were preparing
for a holy war they think with the devil
they want to destroy our society period
there what do you think of that beauty I
have a friend in the Sudanese embassy he
can get a slice in place to get it oh
very good very good we should use code
words for United Nations how about
because the big house Allahu Akbar Andy
bomb let's call it groceries and we will
do more in federal plaza with the FBI
office is it does to New Jersey why not
have you spoken to share home are about
the big house that is not how he
operates you don't tell him what you are
doing you ask him what is allowed by
Islamic law and what is forbidden that
is his rule is the big house allowed
it's not allowed is a must is a duty
can it be
you don't believe me and we just feel
better if I heard him say him self
I had to stick chewing gum over the red
light in this briefcase you call this a
hidden tape recorder no I'm sure he'll
be bail on us for the gum tapes
Salaam alaikum Salaam alaikum peace be
upon you your shake I wish to talk with
you I never forget how you told me how I
wasted my years in Egypt I wish to
please like and I wish to give to you my
allegiance and to death how can I do
this may God correct your ways I mean
Allah bless you Sheikh god help you
redeem lilla see see dick and I are
trying to do a job if not this willing
to be a great deal but I must know if it
is allowed in regards to the United
Nations do we consider it the house of
the devil because my blow against it
will be devastating that's his screw-up
like the Trade Center job we are
planning something that will bring it
upside down but I must know if this is
allowed or forbid it is not forbidden
however it will be bad for Muslims so we
do it or no forget it find a plan find
the plan to inflict damage on the
American army itself but United Nations
would harm Muslims tremendously because
the United Nations will be considered
the Center for peace and the Muslims
would be considered against peace well
see being suggested that the second
target would be the FBI office in the
federal plaza what do you think of this
one wait for a while we will talk about
this later but we are prepared for this
digna a shake nevermind slow down
the man who killed Kennedy was trained
for three years ramzi yousef walked into
the country last sep tember asking for
political asylum walked out again a few
hours after the explosion his
fingerprints are all over the bomb
factory another beautiful job by the AI
NS caught his buddy a jars on the way in
he was in jail when the bomb went off
that he conspired with yousef on the
phone so they managed to catch somebody
who was in their own Jail what about you
self the State Department has posted a
two-million-dollar reward publicized
that the matchbooks on Middle East
matchbooks they smoke alone over there
any relationship between the shake and
yourself nothing firm no we don't know
where Yousef came from we don't know who
said him all we know is that he blew up
the world trade center now how is your
man salaam doing you have the
transcripts what is he up to with them
now working out a plan to bomb the
Holland Tunnel well we put the groceries
any center
two cars go in they stop you drive up
the car decals your groceries gets out
and leaves with the other car
how long will the timer be three minutes
enough time for our people to get out
not enough time for a tow truck to come
in a movie god
there you see it the blue line that is
his center
haha water will be going everywhere no
jobs will be able to get to the city it
will destroy the economy of New York
well Jane center was nothing back
compassing a scratch the Empire State
Building Lincoln Tunnel Grand Central
Station the federal building good God
but now we had the tapes we'd been
grasping at straws but now we had the
evidence we needed brother Salim rented
this place for us he used in a yahoo
arrived a Jew that's good I don't think
the jews did you hear the Mafia action
and deception they are the key have you
spoke to the shaky at about your plans
wait is it a lot of prohibited look I'm
trying to get the paradise here brothers
the shakes it must go slowly but he told
us to go what are your targets
you can speak brother I checked the
place for bugs myself it is better to be
cautious surveillance is always possible
it's good very good we will shake the
thrones of the tyrants here so many
targets all on the same day five minutes
apart it will drive d well crazy boom
after five minutes boom the people would
think there is nothing more
and your head
this is an outrage you are agents of
Satan God will win this is a little much
from a camera in the ceiling you've got
the whole party great finally I can't
believe this we're not done yet solo
male home arose no polo
Sheikh Omar Abdel Rahman shake-up del
Rahman you are under arrest fight for
you shit no this is not the day you have
the right to remain silent do not remain
silent anything you say may be used
against you
oh maybe we'll put these terrorists in
jail but others will come here and take
the place I mean that's what this
country's all about isn't it land of
opportunity now I can't build a bubble
around it John let's get back to what we
were talking about we can throw more
agents at it put more funding on it but
when push comes to shove it's just so
easy this isn't
next time we'll bring them both down
you