yeah
i'm terrance dire honorable discharge
from the United States Army
july 17 2006 whoever i should send this
to you should know first and foremost
that I love my country and I've always
served the best in whatever ways I've
known how to at the time I've loved my
country above God when I was foolish
above man when I was killed in dreams
I've loved my country as if it were the
dream itself and waking were a tyranny
everything I've ever done in my life
I've done for those who have betrayed me
yeah
okay Terrance was a Terrence yeah
what do you know what do you mean what I
know what do you know that i don't know
i mean why is this your talk show
ok I mean if you're the smartest man on
the face of the planet
why aren't you sitting where I'm sitting
look carrots I'm just saying you know I
get 20 you guys a month calling me soon
he made up just got the word you
wouldn't believe the things I'm thinking
man
hey guess what buddy I do believe it
you're not alone
so stop feeling like you're in an enigma
because you're not you're about a
surface is concrete
I mean I could do a 40-yard dash on your
psyche in like 4.5 flat Terrence what I
want to know what the people want to
know right here right now
is this how many people did you kill
what did it feel like
and how can I get some of that it
halftime my man
come on this is about advertising and
ratings parents not your PTSD
I don't have PTSD you sure sound like it
to me Terrance
I mean you sound like a goblin or
something go get some sleep or go down
to Mexico like the boys did after they
got back from Nam
I mean you people you come back from the
war and you're like wearing white sheets
with black charcoal around your eyes
haunting my hallways for Christ's sake
it's like this whole subculture called a
chabad crane now you know what soldier
go do something for the economy write a
book or go sell some gourmet mustard
with little jalapenos in it or something
will ya
carrots Shh
what a surprise next caller
what were you once before anything
happened
what did you inherit from the world
your heart the dream you have other
people who could make you happy
if I believe in that then I believe in
the dream
a single thing to reach out to
all of mankind is sad
we were babies and then we learned for
life was
you're not a human being until you
suffer
it's touching the interesting part is
here
are modern-day government continues to
be funded by the slavery states instead
of Baghdad we should have invaded
ourselves
starting with the sound and working
upward the way you cut it open it dear
what exactly did you mean by the Hat
invading ourselves
ok
yeah
great place to live right in the shadow
of our well marketed quality of life
facade
we got more jack shops and strip clubs
here
per capita than even los angeles on our
streets out there girls as young as 11
years old are routinely solicited or
trunk into the trade you know what that
is trunked what it sounds like it is the
pimp rolls up and sticks you in his
trunk is what it is
you're his now your 11 years old and
you're his
I know I should let up a little I should
take it easy after all suvs right
fast food good food fast right when you
want it
there's a guy up the street from here
he'll take off your shirt and rub your
back to 15 minutes twenty bucks all the
stress just disappears
money buys everything and we got money
so you know what
fuck that
all right man
yeah
hey you want to get something to eat
ok
hey come on
already ate
secondly you don't even give up a name
it's nola
yeah
well NOLA
I gotta drop this bag off across town
you want to walk
yeah
walk
don't shoot
yeah
brought your books
I see that but you seem to be forgetting
i only have one leg and i am lazy as
shit
who's this this
I just learned is NOLA
did you tell noah that you're crazy
yeah
ok
you want to know what I think about this
country
I think it's a luxury automobile
I think it's beautiful and we gave it to
a child to drive
we crippled ourselves by putting our
faith in a drug addict
bourgeois born again President you hear
that in there
write that down bourgeois born again
President you scum
my brother might be in there watching TV
but he gave his life for this country
it doesn't look like it but he gave his
life
I went
I came back with both my legs but only
half my brains
traumatic brain injuries the signature
wounds of this war
just sticking you to fall for somebody
despise it absolutely sickens me
you're right it makes you want to do
stuff they got guys in there fighting
this war their skin so soft you could
cut it with your fingernail
they got babies right out of high school
remember high school
you remember how you felt
remember how your body felt
what's your skin felt like
you think I'm a spectacle no I heard you
speak a couple months ago
remember you and I've been following
your website
and
I'm a writer writer yeah I'm not washing
dishes down at Benny's so what does that
make me Joe Schmoe a journalist I'm
doing stories on people back from the
war I'm like in the zoo now you're
doodling little pictures of me is that
it like a hundred thousand hits a month
on my blog
I'm a serious writer want to do a story
a hundred thousand hits a month
are you like five well I'm one of them
yeah
there was a joke in my company that goes
you caught me at the right time
I wasn't doing shit that's the whole
joke you apply this to everything
you could be doing nothing for 72 hours
straight
stare at the Sun until your half blind
squint at the Sun think of nothing
dead silence and sand and Sun and
nothingness
it's unbearable
nothing to do and an enemy you just
forget about sometimes
wait until night when you're out there
on clearance and the FP start pounding
you out blowing holes the size of
basketballs through solid steel guys
burn up
you caught us at the right time we
weren't too and shit
yeah
you pick in my pocket what is that what
you're doing here
you know what i'm doing here you show up
out of thin air 20 hours later i'm
waking up with you in my apartment are
you with them
with who come here
I know who you say you are
who are you
I take a piss longer than 10 seconds I
swear to you somebody's writing that
down
you understand me
do you are you wearing a wire
now
yeah
I know I'm supposed to come back somehow
come back to living
I come back how cell car stereos for
some big box retailer that was bought by
some bank that was bought by the
government put on my blue shirt spent
all my money on for our coffees at fuck
you bucks until I'm comatose
you come back to nothing
happy birthday
thank you
yeah
it's empty you know why it's empty
because you're gonna fill it
you're gonna go out you're gonna buy
yourself something with the money you
make something for you
you're gonna put in that box and you're
gonna give it to yourself is symbolic
you got to get used to giving yourself
things that money is yours it's not your
pimps
he's not my pen Terrence you're 17 years
old
you've been a kid your whole life he's
pimping you're so young you don't even
know that's what it's called
look at me
you're a boy you're 17 years old mark
its Maggie Maggie mark Luca
I don't care what your name is these
people take advantage of you
it's disgusting it's disgusting mark and
you're so young you don't even know you
don't even know
you can let go of me
I'll let go of you if you talk to me I
just want to talk to you
yeah
there's a dream i have a long fields of
snow stretched out endless fields of
snow and mountains in the distance
maybe one person in the world you can
talk to and it's enough
one person would be enough
yeah
tell me about your brother
which one the one that wears his balls
my brother is a soldier yes that one
he lost his leg in the war
did he not yes he did
the blood is still flowing from it how
biblical i have a term paper of his from
the semester a community college in
which he describes the process of
creating the primary detonator mercury
fulminate from the fillings in his own
teeth
his knowledge of explosives like your
own
is in Cimmeria
everybody that's ever mattered in my
life has lied to me you want to be able
to trust their intentions
what's on the surface is always a mirage
we didn't know this has kids
one brother gives his body
the other his soul
this isn't home anymore
the pages of a magazine
one dimensional
nothing penetrates you forget what the
fuck is out there but you better
remember that burned up guys you
yeah
no man is an island my father used to
say
my father
is it possible he ever said that thing I
can remember
here's another joke I know
fucking loser walks into a bar
that's it end of joke
yeah
i'm terrance dire
honorable discharge for the United
States Army july's seven
july 17 2006
how long have you suffered from
post-traumatic stress disorder
yeah
don't have disorders
well what do you call it then my man
call what
ok ok you wake up at night
I've always walking up the night but you
wake up more now and when you do you're
like a greased him am I correct
what do you mean greased ham you're
sweating
you're sweating now aren't you look last
time you called
you told me you don't remember shit you
still got bad memory loss
it's like reverse déjà vu is not who
you think this happened before right
with this
you think it's not even happening now
look at your hands and you think whose
hand is this
it's only a second but it's enough
every move I've made in my life I've
made for those who have betrayed me
the end
even my memory will turn its back on
what's about to happen
what do you mean what's about to happen
what's about to happen my man you don't
know a lot Terrence do you and I mean I
feel for you my man
you really don't know shit I know about
explosives
what is that like wile e coyote shit you
know you got a box from acme T&T sitting
on your front porch sitting on yours
maybe
hey don't fuck with me here Terrence you
called me remember
tnt that's a secondary explosive RDX hmx
dynamite same category like they they
said it used the nfo ammonium nitrate
and fuel oil
it's like a wet bag explosive I know
about a banal chlorates perchlorates oxy
liquids nitrocellulose I know how to run
tests four-cylinder expansion for
fragmentation for detonation pressure
and pulse vs scale distance relative
bubble energy does any of that mean
anything to you ever heard of those
things
No
you know the children in the backseat of
a car rigged with c4 lower suspicion saw
that once
yeah
items found on route one large metal
drum 130-foot tarp 10 gallons of hme
with washing machine time initiator one
dead dog
three sandbags one bag of carrots
one pair of flip-flops - 1:55 round
strap - 20 gallons of liquid hme cell
phone detonator spool of command wire
three dead dogs one chocolate bar
wrapper 11 spent nine millimeter rounds
13 month old edition of stars and
stripes
the corpse of one smaller rocky man with
a body mass index of about thirteen
wrapped in detonator cord
only the 9-millimeter rounds don't make
sense
somebody out there alone
shootin at nothin
some things don't change about the world
no matter where you are
overseas its massive overruns of disease
and dr. Lewis state's criminal
enterprises chopping your arms off
because your grandfather grew up in a
different tribe then there's the
commoditization of children from infancy
for the worst kinds of slavery
and over here
there are people dying in our faces
everyday people who need our help and we
betray them
one thing you learn walking out of a war
zone every coffins about the same
fucking size
we did that to your eye
just to John what john-john Kennedy john
lennon and johns hopkins you know pick a
John
it's not funny
you look like shit
you got a chance
not bear not me
you do
don't talk like that
it's true
yeah
my brother fought for you
and you chopped off his fucking leg for
it
and what do you give him a few hundred
dollars a month
you want to talk to me about incendiary
we got you mr. Dyer
which building are you talking about
yeah
you come back to nothing
not to the loved ones who wrote you that
the job's not to the ideas you had to
begin with and 20 or 30 or 40
you come back to waiting and mostly you
wait for another war
you don't know that's what it's about it
first the silence in you
you think it's sadness but it's not and
then after a while you can feel it
it's crystal clear
every next conflict is right around the
corner
yeah
war is just a numbers game when you get
down to it
when we dropped the atom bomb on
Hiroshima 50,000 Japanese died instantly
a hundred thousand died from radiation
poisoning within the next few days
a hundred and fifty thousand Japanese
burned up in a flash
a few bricks here a few breaks there
one block at a time you carve out the
center to save the periphery
yeah
they would have you believe the only way
to stop a terrorist is to exercise the
rights afforded to us by roe v wade
aboard the greasy bastards
those are not my words the way you stop
a terrorist is to keep your dick in your
pants in the first place
don't fuck what you can't face what is
it
I felt mark
what
appearance
other people who could make you happy
if I believe in that then I believe in
the dream
you picked mark you turn them into a
homosexual
they seem market for fucking years
yeah
you touched me too
you think I don't remember you did it to
mark this thing you did it to me two men
it's in my head out man
you fucked me man
the gun away son that's unto you
I'm son to my country
yeah
I don't know if one person makes a
difference effort not out there is it
different here
can one person change the course of
events many
yeah
give it to me
give me what you got I will take that
hit for somebody
there's a dream i have a long fields of
snow stretched out endless fields of
snow and mountains in the distance
maybe one person in the world you can
talk to and it's enough
one person would be enough
there's a dream I have
to live
like other people live
- joke
like other people joke
- sit
in your dreams for one moment
with someone you could touch
who could touch you back
there's a dream I have
I pledge allegiance
to the flag
the united states of america
and to the Republic for which it stands
One Nation
under God
indivisible
think of it this way mr. Dyer we get rid
of one small building in the vast
landscape of them and we save the rest
guys like me are over there doing your
laundry Iraq some place wherever we see
what you don't
every coffins about the same fucking
size
well we could do what you too mr. Dyer
sell off the social security numbers of
our peers for profit that anyone with a
bag of rice into the country
I don't do it for the profit
other people every day who need our help
and we betray them
these people need passports to escape
the certain tyranny of their geography
that's not good for you
that doesn't fit with your particular
philosophy of the world
helping people out of the most dire of
circumstances you can imagine
not when those people are potential
terrorists no I don't sell information
of terrorists
yeah
I'm glad you came
I'm glad you got my note now
yeah
first noticed I was being watched
several months ago when you sleep you
feel something on your neck
that's what it's like it's like a bug
that's what it feels like being watched
and then finally when they contacted me
about the bombing wait what
bombing
the one that's going to happen
it was relief what was
contact - no I wasn't wrong
they have photographs of me they have
files
I didn't hurt some of the recordings
they made some of the wiretaps I mean
I want you to know something i do not go
around killing my own people
I go to the gym I eat my fucking food
don't expect you to understand
I'm not mad at you
that's the thing with people like you
I'm not one of them improve it
how promise me salt
promise you what anything just make me a
promise and keep it
what's this
these are your discharge papers
you want to talk about it
but i can promise you Terrence is a
voice this is my voice
you went to them you told them what you
were going through
they wouldn't treat you you deserted to
find a hospital
once you've found one they called you
when arrested you and then you were
dishonorably discharged
you didn't leave the army
Terrence the army left you
they cut you off didn't they
yeah
a good war is won from the center it
carves you want to get inside
you got to get inside there's only so
much you can do on your own
yeah
no wars are won in a room
the one in the room behind the room
a few bricks here a few bricks there
one block at a time you carve out the
center to save the periphery
yeah
whole life I've been preparing for
something that never came
preparing
what for me
cleanliness I think
a lifetime of shit
just one clean moment
yeah
there's a reason it's always ex-military
this is what the military does best and
blow shit up
we need a person of interest
somebody that people can fear
in line - hello this is terrance tire
hello Terrence there's something else I
know what's that mid i know that at
three o'clock sharp
that's a minute and a half from now
Darren's
Terrence
yeah
that you off didn't they
they're going to blow up a building in
this city they're going to blow up a
building in our own downtown and they're
gonna pin it on me
are you getting it down there
yeah
that's good
that's good because you want to know why
because there's never been a conspiracy
proven because the feds have always
gotten there first
Oklahoma the two towers
nobody's ever had the access i'm giving
you now before the conspiracy starts
i'm terrance dire honorable discharge
from the United States Army
july seventy two thousand six whoever i
should send this to you should know
first and foremost that I love my
country
I've always served at best in whatever
ways I've known how to at the time I've
loved my country above God when I was
foolish above man when I was ill in
dreams
I've loved my country as if it were the
dream itself and waking were a tyranny
everything I've ever done in my life
I've done for those who have betrayed me
yeah
if I say no
have you ever heard of anybody saying no
in a situation like this
there are situations like this
they don't exist that's right mr. Dyer
they don't
every move I've made in my life I've
made for those who have betrayed me
the end
even my memory will turn its back on
what's about to happen
yeah
mmm
how long have you suffered from
post-traumatic stress disorder
don't have disorders you still get that
memory loss
I told you that's from my sickness came
back with both my legs but only half my
brains to do talk know that you're
cruising
nobody's ever had the access i'm giving
you now before the conspiracy starts
getting it down there a patriot nola
know about explosives traumatic brain
injuries the signature wounds of this
war
men are not judged by their intent but
their deeds
route clearance 72 hours
route clearance 48 hours 10-day mission
set for de mission set route clearance
48 hours
route clearance 10-day mission sent
route clearance one month route
clearance for months
route clearance 10 the emission set
route clearance six months route
clearance nine months
this is bullshit what is
you want a story i'll get you a story
yeah
war is just a numbers game when you get
down to it
when you're in country the numbers don't
mean shit
the numbers finally disappear
some guys lose it
this is my stop
they pull the wire just to get out
yeah