No
it was the week before Christmas that
I'm talking I spent the day shopping
with my grandma walking all through the
pilot balls a pumping deck the halls
countries with lighting all and I'm just
cocky cuz all the toy stores are looking
mighty packed electronic toys video
games balls and backs I saw a scooter
with a motor that was flat I hope they
were pulling Santa's sleigh just that
I've been told this coming year is
forgiven get to please other Santa this
is how I'm living but if you can t find
the time delivery give 78 not on my list
I'm not selfish I'm just ribbing I been
a good way to leave here you better know
it you're ready Santa Claus to start
back in the halls with gifts from my
Christmas list those cold outside is
warming my soul gotta get a get to give
the beautiful kool
1 2 3 is all I see
one two three and no more mama i miss
you big momma
you gave me the spare cuz of love so
I'll give this bear cuz of love Nicole
another day another d at rat city street
elementary I have to dress extra cute
the mommy schedules me for my own hair
lady messy Dana cold duck I mean
dinosaur haha i would just giving it to
make sure fluff I guess the pressure to
buggy is just too much for me to resist
whoa the pressures really get the smithy
done God come on Ricky's gonna decorate
the tree let's just see what Ricky rhyme
master can do hey watch me help them
heads up Ricky whoa look at all the
ornaments hey Ricky hang ten I'm a
decorating master the one is faster
don't you know I'm a Christmas tree
blaster Wow Ricky that's not bad for you
but don't get a swelled head you're
still not one of us shrimp
dude that was so cool that's a tough
break Ricky no man that's a lot of dog
breaks all over the place
just one tensile too many hey Ricky good
job looks like you made a smash hit
already it's still a nice treat no
matter what Todd says he can't bother me
and I want to have friends like you
thanks Ricky we need a kid bad with you
wrapping a song about me smithy the cool
dude Smith he's small and round his
closest to the ground he's nobody's fool
the coolest kid in school ha hey it's
putting a cold the honey I know she's
into money from me she cannot hide cuz I
know she's good inside yeah you're
pretty cool Ricky except for liking
Nicole now that's gross class sit down
you too young miss Nicole yeah Nicole
sit pretty not funny now sit down please
yeah Ricky don't you know how to sit who
can you only fall down that's cool spin
round and round and find the ground Wow
hey Ricky let me know anytime you want
to fall down again I'll be glad to shove
you in the right direction let's get
ready for recess good I'm ready to skate
bigger and faster than my mom can make
the biggest sandwich in the world Oh
recess when we return we will exchange
gifts can't we please give out our
presents now please pretty please I said
after recess because I need a recess ok
let's go out and do some skating you
won't catch me hesitating that will be
enough Ricky ok ok I'll save my rap in
for the present make sure all of you are
bundle up good I don't think your
parents would appreciate runny noses
over vacation am i right sniffing yet
miss Farmington remember come in
promptly at the bell teacher don't you
worry be right back in her oh I think I
less Santa for a vacation to a beautiful
Wyatt
Cheers
I'm gonna get you schmoopy I'm gonna
take your sandwich you won't get away
from me I'll get him fully itad he's no
match for me Yeah right bully-boy no one
catch this myth man i'm gaining on you
smithy
Oh
Gaia you're mine now snippy look a tug
of war I'm betting on snippy hey god I
can feel a big done get it big yeah
you're asking for it Oh get you good
smithy watch me everyone but what I can
do Oh watching Nicole slut you Rick and
I didn't think it could get any colder
out here come on the night let's pretend
we're famous Gators had enough yet
aren't you tired and tugging along don't
let go jog you better give up if you
know what's good for you yeah yeah yeah
whoa this reeks I want waves not ice
sorry steaks on
this time everyone's feeling fine get me
back like salmon oh you'll be sorry
nobody messes with my food it gets away
with it come on your mommy what did you
get from the grab bag Nicole anything
good oh hey that is so cool i wish i had
one here cheap is not cool an a now my
gifts the best it came from the mall I
brought that for the grab bag Nicole
it's a great reindeer I picked her out
myself miss Barrington get him away from
me get him away from me that means he
likes you he just doesn't know he does
yeah yeah yeah Farmington class I need
your attention and I need the calm ferry
to dust this room this is such a great
time of year miss Farmington how are you
and our little angels doing our little
angels are doing just fine thank you
very much hello sir I hope you have a
really really happy holiday why thank
you the neh I just wanted to pop in and
wish you all a Merry Christmas and you
to have a happy holiday miss Farmington
you as well I know that my family is
just going to spoil me rotten to the
core I as it's been another wonderful
year in the Farmington house oh yes Mary
is principal dude okay children I wish
you all a wonderful holiday now please
clean up your area before you leave
remember things in order teaches you
good skills yeah yeah yeah I guess those
skills come later hey Ricky where'd you
get the ratty old bear get it walk you
home from school he probably has music
playing in his head the way he's rocking
back and forth cool Hey Jude can I
listen well I was waiting for nicole
well what you want Ricky what could we
possibly have to talk about we can all
discover something important about
giving just like Santa Santa Claus duh
you know the very important man that
won't visit you if you're not good to
Santa shop at the mall no so that makes
me perfect since all of my presence come
from the mall you're perfectly weird get
cold I know that's mine it better be
good this is from the heart
Merry Christmas Nicole have you lost
your mind are you purposely trying to
embarrass me I can't even exchange this
nasty old thing you might be smart with
books but you sure are stupid I give you
a real gift and you don't get it
hey Pratt who do you think you are
treating people the way you do it's
really gross that Ricky likes you but
he's my friend and you're not whatever
whoa this is so great I know you like
this stuff Nicole of course it's sold in
the malls so I know they spent lots of
money uh-huh and we go to this really
big store mm-hmm and it starts with W
whatever Ricky who gave you that candle
oh it's a really mean thing to say why
do you see anything else oh co for the
lytic allah it is nowadays dear Santa
please send me a video box and please
send toys to all the kids in my class
even the coal I gave her my special bear
the mama gave me before the Angels took
her thank you your friend Ricky Rogers
there all done oh my baby must be
sending littles I'll be back in a hurry
great-grandma from ways in a hurry
hope you get lots of stuff I know I will
what do you think Santa will bring you
this year you still believe in Santa
Claus that's so last year I suppose the
Tooth Fairy still comes for your baby
teeth
Santa Claus has my princess been a good
girl today not only live and good today
but I've been a good girl all year long
you know I'm the best kid in the world
mommy I know you are and I'm the
luckiest mom in the world at me look and
you'll see the best kid in the world
look at me look and you'll see just how
good I can be cuz on Christmas Eve whole
Santa will see how best kiddin
look at me my room spotless everything
in a world
look at me brush my teeth twice behind
my ears are so cool
on Christmas me the best kidding me
don't you see straight-a student come
works always on time look at me tell me
what else what else you might believe
hey old Santa Claus you know better so
you know I will try to be like that kid
who I said I was I know I could be
Christmassy
you
you're the best guy the best guy that I
know and thank Santa Claus you made me
feel like the best kid in the world
well there must be a Santa Claus hmm
Nicole seems sure that there isn't I
don't know what am I gonna believe honey
is something bothering you no nothing
but when's daddy coming home soon right
after he picks up the christmas tree why
don't you play with your little sister
until then well I love Jenna mom but I
just want to wait for daddy okay that's
fine nana is on her way as well so we
can all decorate the tree as a family
come on it's Christmas cheer up
hmm I wonder what that letter is doing
out there there's even Nicole gave her a
special bear that Mommy Oh No Ricky what
have I done it ok careful it is what if
you just country for edit it isn't that
what Santa does it was from my heart Oh
see I for the AP political upheavals
even a flapper boy feel she doesn't get
it oh yeah at the whole Christmas oh ho
ho how when I feel so bad
hey Nicole we're looking for Ricky's bag
I've got to find it oh boy here comes
trouble if I didn't see it I wouldn't
believe it let me guess you are thrown
out of the mall so you're shopping at
the dumpster do they take credit cards
yeah the poor little princess is turned
into a garbage man yeah cool the ice
queen hey when you melt your hair is
gonna be a mess very funny don't just
stand there help me find that bear yeah
you should help us too what is it about
girls being so bossy anyway hey Wiz come
on guys let's get out of here hey have
fun digging in the trash hope you find
the garbage you're looking for don't
forget to take a bath before Christmas
you girls stink enough as it is and now
sniff he smells worse than before yeah
smelly smithy and princess of the trash
Nicole come on get out of here before
someone sees us with them or smells us
with them those guys are so lame never
mind them Ricky's mom gave him that bear
I can't let him give me something so
special I've got to find it for him cool
you killed the bear now he's got a trash
heaven it for Ricky's gonna cry because
of you
oh come on smithy please it's for Ricky
help us find it where could it big wait
I've seen the cleaning man take trash
down in the basement before maybe it's
there gee do I have to come up with all
the answers of what smoothly I love
creeping out creepy girl this is gross
look a spider oh not funny sniffy this
is classic twice in one shot I can so
blackmail you guys you will be black and
blue if anyone hears about this now keep
looking now what do we do how about the
junkyard oh no not that oh do you want
to find the bear or not okay but I'm
definitely going to throw this outfit
away not to mention have my nails done
your nails gee I will never understand
girls being a boy is definitely better
yes I saved you again my friend you just
wait your time will come and I'll be
right there to get you yes Miffy all the
sandwiches in the world won't make you
skate faster next time cool stinky
smithy Jason is skating Sam bitch ah the
big fat pony thinks it's martinique will
just be back we can't let them see us or
my plan won't work this is so great
they're good at digging through trash
maybe they'll find us some cool stuff
yeah they can find it and we can take it
maybe we can build a cool fort out of
this junk why whoa who's gonna hear us
what now what are you gonna do the
doggies are gonna get chewed look at the
babies afraid of some little doggies
what are we gonna do I have a great idea
what have a picnic just watch how smart
I am how are we getting over that oh
that's easy just climb into that tree
and jump over hmm ah what a lady does
not climb trees she does if she doesn't
want to be late besides now is not the
time to be a girl
look we finally made it
Wow what are you doing here and what
happened never mind here I'm so sorry
Nicole this was a gift for you but
doesn't it mean a lot to you yes and so
does friendship
this is my very favorite time of the
year I can remember you Robert as a
little boy oh you had such a hard time
falling asleep on Christmas Eve hahaha I
remember one early morning my sister
brother and I running down the stairs so
excited only to find nothing under the
tree we thought that Santa had
completely forgotten about us well I ran
to the front window to see if Santa was
flying by and to my surprise they are
right on our porch set brand new
bicycles I want a pony for Christmas
Santa can just put it in the backyard
and tie it to the apple tree okay
hi sweetheart I understand you can use a
little extra Christmas cheer Santa's on
his way you don't believe me come and
take a look do you see him do you see
Santa ah I do daddy
there he is
he's there because I believe in him
right daddy exactly it's what's in your
heart that matters most do you hear that
Daddy I sure do sweetheart and I love
you daddy will you try and help me
understand daddy are you sure that he's
special daddy tell me you believe is
tempered
and if we all believed in Santa they
will always be alive inside of me
because even Santa Santa Santa live
inside of me boo goodnight daddy oh I
love you it's Christmas
I
oh honey by the time I got out of the
mall the cleaners had already closed so
I bought you a new suit no surprises
there that's how I get most of my suits
Merry Christmas Merry Christmas Merry
Christmas Nicole let's open your
presents precious Oh princess as my good
looks and your spending habits oh dear a
present from Grandma came last week in
the mail I may have put it at the back
of the tree oh cool grandma always sends
me the best stuff nothing's too good for
my princess and I've got the credit card
bills to prove it this is what Ricky
asked Santa for put a big smile on
pumpkin it's Christmas and you know what
that means even more presents than on
every other day mommy daddy may I go
visit a friend of course princess have a
good time it's a wonderful Christmas I
got the most beautiful wife and daughter
and of course they have the most
handsome husband and father
I am the perfect little girl
nicole Santa made a terrible mistake he
sent this present to the wrong house so
I ran over here as fast as I could are
you sure Nicole look it has your name on
it well don't just stand there open it
you
I thought you didn't believe in Santa of
course I do how else could your present
get to my house pissant to make a
mistake well you know he has a lot on
his mind Christmas Eve come over later
and we'll go to lynnae's house Merry
Christmas Jana I think I see something
in the backyard
oh how cool is that it's too cool oh
I'll get it hey I'm so happy to see you
guys come on in pink lenee and what I
said about Santa well I it's okay McCall
I understand me too we can always work
things through my friends believe me
when I say is true belief and Santa is
where we start but what matters is
what's in her heart if you want to know
what you can trust is that Santa
believes in us do you know what Nicole I
never stopped believing in Santa and you
don't have to stop either I won't that
makes two of us great grandma you always
know just what to say don't give me a
Christmas uh yeah yeah yeah hey
Wow believe is Santa yeah that's right
that's right I believe in Santa I am so
proud of you princess and a merry
Christmas to all shut that door
Oh
and the season is upon we call him Santa
Cruz but all the toy rings are sometimes
don't get lost could there be a place in
time with Jesus attorne the laughter the
feeling of a christmas day but never
after one game he removes playin nice
joyousness AMS ways off speaks hi
where we sing along
and we love along wise we see the world
through a child
I
oh my love and in every single country
they know Santa's name
the magic of a season made for every
girl and boy hearing more than stockings
fellow
hi
we'll see you know
and we love me
you
Oh
we're on the same
nothing that divides us should remain
let's raise
ha
what song
who
my name is Jenna I'll be battling Easter
bandage finish done gone awesome REO
slam my heart oh those medallion go now
look hot move is over
the end