yeah
best best girl moment
fine
it is talk of course he's dead that
dosage was too large you know i did not
i gave him life
yeah
zapper again charging handles all the
compression
straight line
alright
she just needs a little more time to the
drugs is feeling pain we have done
everything that can be done for this
woman she has not responded she's gone
ok your optimism is touching a waste of
time a good doctor knows when to stop
and take her to the morgue way
ok
miss k14 a lot back hills in your room
thanks don't know why they keep my
daughter out here nobody wants in and
ain't nobody getting now
yeah
ok
well I'm sorry then I didn't mean to
scare you it wasn't too bad and halsey I
just didn't know anybody was here
you mean anybody else damn this is
Herbert West will be joining you in your
third year he was doing independent
research and switzerland with dr. Gruber
shortly before he died
the West this is Daniel Caine one of
Miskatonic medicals best young hopes for
the future of Medicine are you
researching death we don't see you
around here much anymore
well I was just showing our newest
student her Midwestern not so grand tour
this should interest you Carl he worked
with scuba i missed west this is our
eminent brain researcher and grant
machine dr. Carl he'll I know your work
dr. hill quite well your theory on the
location of the wheel in the brain is
interesting though derivative of dr.
Gruber's research in the early seventies
so derivative in fact that in Europe is
considered plagiarized and your support
of the 12-minute limit on the life of
the brainstem after death 6 to 12
minutes mr. room West Herbert West
frankly dr. hill your work on brain
death is outdated a car while I remember
I we were having a grant committee
meeting thirsty
Megan and I would love it if you came to
dinner well I'd love to i'm looking
forward to it and looking forward to
seeing you in class mr. West
yeah
a lot buddy
I have to go
stay knows I'm here
I don't care what he calls it the reason
of all if I didn't come home one night
just one spell me out of touch with the
times just the way is the world's last
living Puritan
the day that you graduate the minute you
get your dl marry you and I'll help you
I'll be with you as much as I can
promise back to square one
well at least it gives me a chance to
housebreak you housebroken is to teach
jury in the world would convict me
hi can I help you
you're on here about department huh yes
did we meet this morning your quest for
requests with should just thank you
I startled you
yes you did hmm
may I introduce my fiancee Megan hold it
yes Halsey mr. less i'm afraid the place
is still kind of a mess mr. Wessel
Herbert
so you've just come from Europe
Switzerland what was dr. Gruber light is
pretty famous he has some pretty famous
does this building have a basement
oh yes yes I think this will be fine i
have my things upside shall I move in
now
uh look I have to go I think you mr.
West have a lot to discuss before you
decide anything
oh I've decided well know you'll never
even know that I'm here dad of course on
the first of the month Mr West miss
holding you didn't say why you left
Switzerland there was no more like alone
do we have a deal done . you make the
incision at the base of the skull
cutting away enough of the cashier to
get your fingers in and then grasping
firmly with both hands pull the skin
forward over it very much like dealing a
large orange once the skull is plainly
visible you take the bone saw
and you cut around the perimeter
and there you have it ladies and
gentlemen the human brain
once the brainstem of an individual i'm
talking about the reticular activating
system are regulation respiratory Center
once these activities cease the brain
can only survive an additional six to 12
minutes 6 to 12 minutes until brain
death brings about an irreversible
conclusion
we all want to retain our personalities
and some idyllic afterlife we all pray
for some miracle some drug potion pill
perhaps though it takes something else
perhaps it takes desire an obsessive
desire perhaps city
we will discuss the location of the will
in the brain structure at another time
mr. worst i suggest you get yourself a
class dismissed how can you teach such
drivel these people are here to learn
your closing their minds before they
even have a chance one of you for mr.
well you know you should have stolen
more groupies ideas that he should have
ideas for wet
there's gonna be a pleasure to fail you
I would like to propose a toast national
science foundation for recognizing the
genus Carl hill and rewarding Miskatonic
medical school its largest grant ever
had your new laser drill is going to
revolutionize neurosurgery to the
foundation to miss katonic
so much we don't drink up some great
I know daddy but i have to go soon
preparing such a feast
you must be tired study date today
yeah UK Westers moved in with him for
the time being and that must be him
excuse me
so daughter is seeing you think that's
wise
yeah dr. help would you join us for
glass one actually we have some work to
do
why don't you study here on our
homestead Valley one last toast debate
my esteemed colleagues capable beautiful
loving daughter the obsession of all
fall under her spell and
no please
ok what is I don't know look it's not
you really it's just a lot of little
things like what
well West is always in his room with the
door closed no I mean do you ever see
him eat
I told you he's he's a little crack
bothers you too
don't be ridiculous
Rufus terrified of him when it comes to
any runs and high roof is runs and hides
all the time standard character yes but
not when we're together then he's all
over is trying to get your attention he
hadn't seen him since we got here ok
around I haven't even heard him usually
at least knock something over when I'm
here
Rufus
your kitty try to hide from your right
pelvis are you boy
boy
yes
yeah
what are you doing in my room
how do I thought I was like five wrote
and say what the hell are you doing
I you please leave now easy in the head
I was going to show you out
what happened it was dead when I found
you killed him he hated you think it's
suffocated not the garbage over and he
got his head stuck in a job you weren't
home so I put it in there I certainly
didn't think you'd want to find it like
that i did not want to stink the place
up
I was going to show you could call are
ready no I was busy pushing bodies
around you will know what I know it's a
dam cap dead details later
I knew your father you killed him I know
you didn't kill I do not like people in
my ruler again
I think you better leave now what the
hell is this
that is none of your business yeah i
think it is just this is none of my
business that you're sleeping with Dean
holds his daughter you know I would not
want to see a fellow student especially
when it's promising as yourself be
thrown out of school out of the
profession on moral grounds i think dr.
all just not understand do you
you may well be right are you sure you
want to find out
you're that sound West West West
ok
it's really quite simple
all life isn't physical and chemical
process correct it stands to reason them
that if one could find extremely fresh
specimens and recharge that chemical
process bank we have to the animation
theory is not new West but my reagent is
read with various animating solutions
I've killed and brought to animated life
a number of rabbits guinea pigs cats and
dogs I've broken the six to twelve
minute barrier cart brain death with the
higher animals and the consequent
increase strength solution reaction has
become more violent my research become
more difficult which is why I need you
to help me help you are the perfect
person to assist your hard-working
bright people respect you and you have
access to certain authorities we can
defeat death we can achieve every
doctor's dream you'll be famous and live
life times you have done this on people
I've done all I can hear i need new lab
space you will help me know why because
it's mad
no because I don't believe you how can
you say that you're seeing the results
no Rufus wasn't dead to begin with
you drugged him and reduce his vital
signs you Lord his body temperature
could have been dead
do you agree these dead now do you agree
that he's dead now
West low
West stop i'll show you then you'll help
me know she will
that is why I brought the infernal beast
back to life in the first place
great of course I don't expect it to
tango
it has a broken back
birth is always painful
dick
over west is affected reanimation and
dead animal tissue mr. i'm surprised i
have seen it he brought back i dead
animal a cat back to life
I hadn't expected such nonsense from You
mr. came but I should have guessed when
you took up with mr. West
I know he's unstable but I've seen the
results and so is your daughter even
doing with my daughter she walked into
an experiment
you've involved Megan in your sanity
never intended to involve tomorrow
morning you will submit to me a written
apology for this entire affair these
experiments were clearly beyond the
scope of your legitimate studies they've
obviously interfere with your ability to
do your classwork if any equipment from
the hospital or from the laboratories
Miskatonic University were involved in
any of this unauthorized activity
criminal charges may be pressed you will
in any case at your student loan recent
I will be able to continue school from
us the West he needs submit no apology
you may tell him that he may continue
with his research without the impediment
of an education so now he's no longer a
student at this university so can we
please just discussed this i think
you're being blinded by your emotions
that will be all mr. Kane don't take
this out on Meg she tried to tell me I
said that will be all
yeah
keep coming up
you ain't got by lunch under heavy get
one meatball run over by a semi I lost
my appetite you gonna be around for a
while I might go catch me some coffee
take your time
yeah
sure
come what will they do all this
ok
burn victim
here's your meatball shotgun wound to
the head
Oh got right
practice
come find me
right
yes I think you he write early see John
Doe just dropped it
no record of any damage almost perfect
most damage just find another way to
work at time tonight is a specific
conscious reaction he's been dead for
hours any evidence reanimated
consciousness of justified proceeding
started on record at the entry to her
subject early twenties
physical condition appears to have been
in excellent physical condition
parent
cause of death
what are 3 3pm 33
yeah
15 cc's
15 cc's of reagent being administered
he's where I've seen the sample medical
students before good here it is mr. Kane
loose in this hospital morgue I
specifically told dr. Wright suspend him
and take him off the floor he reported
to work dr. Reilly has been an emergency
surgery for four hours I time elapsed
15 seconds
picture of happened by now
yeah
ok
obviously the human dosage factor alone
increasing the dosage 20 cc's of region
Roscoe
yeah
mr. can report to level security desk
and make sure that she stays right here
you can't stop me I followed you here
and follow you until you listen to my
daughter and you'll do as you're told
sit down miss Halsey mr. Kane will be up
soon
you can discuss it then don't blame him
daddy
come on what's called be coming any
minute she failed that I let's go let's
go right
yeah
it's west
come on the recorder
no just listen to me it made a conscious
act we heard you as an animal would know
you can't be serious
you may be right it probably been dead
too long it wasn't fresh enough we
probably only revive the senses and the
instincts of god help me get you listen
to you of course will you give me a hand
here now he interrupted an important
experiment in progress
granted it was an accident but this is
the freshest body that we could come
across state of killing on ourselves and
every moment that we spend talking about
it cause results that will give me a
hand
we can bring him back to life
yeah
now get the recorder find my syrup dream
here there's other ppl breakable plastic
one of man's few durable conventions
certainly more durable than this we need
to the crash room
coming
yeah
12 cc is being administered the dosage
lesson in accordance to the freshness of
the subject
five seconds
come on I'll show you
15 seconds I'll show you
17 seconds reanimation at seventeen
seconds he is open
doctor doctor Halsey you want to get me
a favor by letting me into your medical
school
yeah 10-inch Meg
what is it you're right
trying to speak the recorder
what happened here then you're right
that is the Halsey sir
you see I came down here to visit with
mr. king who was here working and halsey
entered and started ranting Addison
rather irrational Oh was just angry
yeah that was not always just corpse you
see holes you came in
grab that think i'm crazy-eyed healthy
then all I'm calling the police
shop
don't worry
yeah
you can't hear you or see you that's a
one-way mirror what is wrong with him
dr. only ever be too we know exactly
what happened to him
there's no way to determine his course
of recovery
that's why I need you to sign a release
so that like to perform exploratory
surgery is that absolutely necessary dr.
hill
I know how difficult this must be for
you but I'm convinced that your father's
problem is neurological of course will
take every precaution must trust me
I want to take a look at the right
frontal lobe I'll open the skull don't
want to know just helping
please stop
please let me talk to him
I must insist you leave his treatment up
to me I want you to think of me as
someone you can come to with your
problems
or if you're ever lonely
I know you all by yourself
Wow
yeah
I'm going to take care of dr. and I'm
going to find out what happened
yeah
doing here waiting for you
I have to
what did you in West do to him to make
them like that this horrible i didn't
what did you do
it's not
he's dead
no you're not
actually egg everything
good evening to us what do you want I
want to know why holds his heart was
killed by his pulse is erratic
I told everything I know to the police
why he cries out in pain
you can leave now doctor when we both
know he is went dead
interesting little laboratory you have
you are mr. West I recognise this yeah
what do you want
yes we are both scientists let us get to
the point I want your discovery whatever
it is that gives the dead the appearance
of lying all it is not the appearance of
like it is life that's not magic as you
say i am a scientist I love you locked
up for a mag man for murder
you will do
what I tell you to do
yeah
genius mr. West
your extension of that old fool Gruber's
work is really quite booty
yeah
dr. hill examine yes I wanted to do
exploratory surgery on him find out
eventually find out let us see my new
system at work and dead cat
creation
yeah
%
be a mess
yeah
yes parts I've never done Oh
yes dr. Herbert West what are you
thinking how do you feel
yeah
oh my god to him
looks like a laser drill father's been
the bottom
yeah
but took my serum except for what i have
upstairs
whoa what happened here hill by Sarah my
notes everything perfect are insane now
what happened I had to kill him but he's
dead
not anymore no it's got like a blackmail
me
doesn't anybody to disappear
oh oh that's why I did it
what you've seen healthy lobotomized him
so he can control in case you ever tried
to talk or tell somebody what happened
so he could protect his discovery yes
they're clever i gotta tell meg what
does negative to do with this helicopter
squared file honorees full napkins and
hair and photographs I think he's
projected some sort of psychotic need on
door
yeah
that you dr. hill
it matter
I don't know I was just worried about
you
i I just feel horrible about everything
i guess i'm just getting paranoid
it's just
so hard to lose you
you should go away
transferred to another school don't
worry about me
you're the one ish way
life
somebody
I hate you
I wanted so much
yeah
dan dan dan come on you know well you'll
be alright Meg
oh my God we're hurry the hospital i
imagine stand up
yeah
your beauty
I Drive all ways
where I must say dr. Phil I'm very
disappointed in you you steal the secret
of life and death and Tristan with the
bubble-headed colored you're not even a
second-rate scientists to where I'm
actually glad to see it saves me the
trouble of having to send all you never
get credit for my discovery who's going
to believe a talking head get a job in a
sideshow five telligent young man like
yourself should make such a fatal
mistake of coming here to challenge me
oh I have a plan
yeah
I my discovery surgical 3x possible
technique bottome which results in total
of human subjects
yeah
and
ok
yeah
thank you
I have a theory
yeah
ok
no make
yeah
my god
she's gotten up
activate
Iran
yeah
ok
his face
camarillo we're clear
yeah
nothing
scratch and I awaiting response
ok
yeah