[Music]
watching human heads out will take the
stage those
[Music]
my ways
a little boy
hate to part company with me
[Music]
howdy stranger
so I'm gonna have to buy a house for
spell right now but I borrow your gun
too
why did it had most of my angle but to
drip somebody put the book to us force
me getting different setup
let's roll up your shirt
raise your hand over yet
about it much
let's go out
[Music]
why don't you say what you're thinking
i'm not thinking anything
[Music]
do- this will have to keep your mind off
the paint
the Sentinels what that nothing nothing
at all
[Music]
this is the state depot they'll take
area
I still need Josh you're welcome to
anything else I have to get it
watch what are here I look like when I'm
nothing I never see this caliber or what
you want
what's your name straighter Edward
Creighton watch it on their surveyor
share
yes I work for western union watch
western union telegraph company we're
going to your next you on our way to the
coast
I guess he's all right anything well you
have a bank all over North Platte today
we killed one of the rest of the
scattered it's like the roster now for
good
[Music]
hear me o god are you ready thanks /
actually now if i can just manage the
navigator on the same but i reckon
you'll be back this way with a heavy
great line for long if everything goes
right well I do look trap and now and
then so I was wondering how much it
would cost to send my pelts into Omaha
by telegraph your champion belt but
telegraph UK mouth or you can send is
writing in The Telegraph being gonna do
me any good birth
no I I can't repay you for your kindness
place but it may help a little
h-hold it much you manage all things
yourself
yes let me take that too
what it what it I want to have this
along with my gosh screaming thanks
if I wanted to say lecture
[Music]
yes very but you don't believe what he
said about that Telegraph going through
your duty of course not three no such
thing as a telegraph known but she's
right nice feller guess the same year
shaurya going to get man you want to
change need now wanted to fellow that
goes a bit of sundown in beats up at
sunup want with a watch
well as a mite equality thing to wear
sounds nice too
[Music]
across the plains to pay for drivers
diggers home and summertime is just two
dollars a day always been and concrete
three dollars every man supplied his own
gun
ok what do you mean ok Telegraph's all
means all right now the doc here fast
you why you buckle you've got yourself a
job you know that kind of the final or
your work for your group and it's like
they're gonna flavor it therefore
therefore in generic don't bother me
none
there are some members of the medical
profession like the custom things up but
I don't say was that comfortable you
know this country we're going to 100
miles from here i love this hair back in
56 better sort of relaxed whole sale and
use his pc a hundred minus mu all that
was five years ago
nowadays we don't see no engines it's
like a cotton with springs then you will
be start going down x without a history
teacher takes me ourselves strangers
when i get back to Angel i figure i'm
keeping my hair instead of telling the
folks I lost it and then don't always
counseled color not a fellow Scouts from
first thing for me I've got to have
peace and quiet when I'm preparing my
little but are your cock at 20 years
with the same hair and I intend to be
for 20 months Jim I bid you good the
former doctor doctor doctor
yeah it's great because you don't need
these no more for them down right out of
the car until that good-for-nothing
poison that he's class
I just can you call and nine different
ways to cost money and I know them all
oil still fricassee
never mind that you're cooking with a
hair on it i should say not when you're
high
no no your job is to the stage are we
might become time to show you an old
Indian way to cook prairie dog i should
stay safe
that's great Albert was great just what
you do with algebra we're buying some
you are today
that was my sister
as the bell i have to do is confident
John realize dr. hello
so we don't tell me you're giving up
selective are all right
I'll edit them so glad you're back
[Music]
what the dr motion contain he says I'm
fit as a fiddle
I can walk from here to salt lake on my
hands man to close that they're all
there is another great in the big boss
the only man around you have to be
polite
glad to know you shot that take a lot of
horses and cattle a long way you think
you can manage say so but sometimes
you're supposed to be too late for you
know band addition to my mouth
but Sir the right shot
we're not leaving here for a couple of
days
I'm leaving tonight why you know life I
like being alone that's place to be
alone sometimes in a crowd that's the
way i think it to run into you
it's a good chance for you in western
union is there i think so
talk to you you don't owe me nothing
how could I never saw you before
I have to meet my screaming yes
good chula is keep your mind off things
[Music]
I told him I want a real man
thank you i like saying it's a great
waves next office girl you up your
spell's use the Ute hall he's singled
out like that you put a dash at it like
that but I get nothing the sword
sometimes I don't even know what you're
talking about but I know what you're
talking about
next time I talk about the script
yes I'm great I'm Richard Blake
reporting for work
what are you doing splake i was
expecting by sage well it stayed with
crowds and Bobby that i bought a spring
wagon for the last like myself but
there's much more comfortable that way
right almost breaking I want you to know
a former cattle my assistant is Pat
growing up on how do you do gentlemen
all right right i don't know you're
right the last leg of your trip mr.
Mallinson well I didn't mind that much
as i did the best i could do with a bad
o.o better yet don't you approve them
aware of the weather brought your narrow
River I'm gonna give him i want to a
type of work would you prefer to be
assigned to the break I anything at all
i had some engineering at Harvard and I
know the Morse code inside out now I
think we can figure out something for
the present why don't you run on over to
the hotel and take your bathroom will
have a little talk later well thank you
very much a gentleman and YouTube well
done
great i'm sorry sorry because I
understand the Morse code
no I mean I you'll have to excuse me I
have work to do anyway I'm having to
magistrate and you are the big boss mr.
accurate it's because you're not I know
you both have that intense lift the
Great Western outdoors do that to you
know people we need to meet with some
people you meet are going to insist on
meeting you again so i want to say
goodbye or overruled
thank you very much oh by the way we do
directly to the hotel along Main Street
you're first starting to write down your
street thank you very much stronger is
remind you know who I am I haven't
painted I'm a provisional governor of
the territory of Nebraska you are well
when you come up the reelection al4
don't go to a provisional governor is
appointed by the president all the next
time I'm walking up with a good point is
what's wrong
would you mind telling me what that was
just passed through so that is the son
of couple airplane made his fortune
hauling Freight to the cumberland gap in
the 30-hour Blake that and his father
think the job of western union will make
a man out of him that was back he's
there and gave me fifty thousand dollars
for life
I see you got the Sun with the money
do you see what I hear I am all ready
for work
OIC let's get that outfit and down on
our new york and i want to be sure the
fifth that like this is shark out
naughty do well nice looking bunch of
ours you have here
glad you like the ride oh yeah feat any
leverage table and some emerging pretty
wild
well that is the way I like them we
would you mind picking one up for me I'd
be right is that my crown over there
this way please what about it cold out
murder
[Music]
you don't really care
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah nice animal gentlemen you have
anything else you like you to try before
your heart watercoloring better at it
like brothers United have your chance
universe right
so I guess I got to be running along to
talk i thought i wish you a happy fourth
of July test tomorrow so I thought I'd
be the first but I'd see I one with that
what you came for tuning shop
well I like I'd better be going on too
goodnight
thanks goodnight
[Music]
I that we can show you before but you
did all right today on that bucket heart
that wasn't so bad
gave it away from the life you always do
that with every gender for touching
hands on the Tenderfoot I'm sorry I
disappointed all of you but I was riding
horses before I could walk
that's a good night tonight you were
going my way to change continental
Telegraph learn has long in the bream of
Americans know there's two big harm our
ER doctors are great reality that will
eventually triumph over hardship and
privation it now gives me great pleasure
to present the chief engineer of western
union mr. Edward quickie
I've just received a message here which
I think better than any words of mine
will explain the urgency of our task
allow me to wish you Godspeed on a
journey that will do much to help this
union in its hour of greatest need it is
imperative that our government have
quick communication with the West the
messages signed Abraham Lincoln
[Applause]
[Music]
you
you happy on every man is when his dream
begins so much realized I know things
like this that make some women which
they've been born men don't forget
you've got a job to do to you by side
with god bless you
Caminero long haul
development great but I'm afraid it's
divided imagine make you think that my
brother function i'll do my best to you
want to hear me do i do that to the
radio station supply
[Music]
hey watch where you're going mobile
heart not my friend
[Music]
man where we're doing fine 11 miles in
two days but we've got to do better
this is Prairie country and we've got to
make every minute count because pretty
soon we're gonna hit the hills and we're
liable to run into trouble that's all
it's turning now get a good night's
sleep tomorrow i will get out of the
game right Nelly
ok
even with treatment
well I can expect the u21 no nothing
wrong just a few miles out so last night
I started good like the I have some
unfinished business here and I are
meeting with just I asked the month many
students who believes due to life
company on your ride back to the
professor
[Music]
it's not right click here and our that
first what happened and this comes just
got the best the kitchen
sure you did it right killed
is where you at least not getting that
extra dollar
[Music]
all right through your heart and not
being our trouble at all given my chain
boys will have more like to work by 100
feet
it won't take it
[Music]
too bad it was a real nice fellow yet
again yes well I got a week's wages says
he will be four morning I'll take that
back
[Music]
and they get all the cattle that's what
the chasers and I can't figure this up
this is tony country and partners don't
go at the Capitol and there's plenty of
Buffalo around you think it was rustlers
don't know i'll go have a look how many
men do you want none
you don't expect to bring back to
catalonia I don't expect to get an
indian war started either first thing we
got to find out is what's all the game
was sitting in all all right
double guard tonight pet yes sir come on
Homer I want you to call for you
song
wait you're going after them yet if you
don't mind I'd like to go with you
sorry but this one job we don't trust to
attend foot
no matter how good he is yes
how is he
but unlike next time docks
[Music]
reach around slow
bad jack
hello where we know you'd come back
sooner or later
well we got a mission that look they're
not flat where you been Missouri know
Omaha Omaha was that was risky that very
much
my face is well known as yours haha what
are you doing out here working for
western union
okay we got those cavity Russell buddy
I'm being wrestled where soldiers now
fighting for the Confederacy and clothes
you got on don't look like no uniforms
to me last night where gorillas under
orders from general Mosby the audio
dressed up like engines and steal cattle
as far as you're concerned yes he's here
my raiders just like most he's got i do
whatever I think will help the cause a
lot you might help the cause a lot more
about going down south and joining the
army
you talk like you forgot where you was
born you come from Missouri same as me
you're going against your own people
when they turn against their own country
than they have my people anymore well
they're mine and they don't want this
Yankee wire strung and as long as I'm
alive it ain't gonna be you wouldn't be
making a little money out of your
fighting with you sure there's money in
it we started combine business with
pleasure so to speak
I want those cattle Jack you know what
you're gonna have to do to get them
don't you
you went well now wait a minute how do I
know you won't tell creating about us
you don't suppose and I don't let you go
why don't you stop
go ahead videos check
what do you think you'll do what can he
do away things straight
yes those heathen savages sure cleaned
us out what am I going to tell them when
they start yelling forget where im gonna
tell them we'll get some more be just as
soon as possible that somebody in
definite answer to give to a hungry man
oh I've tighten up their belts for a day
or two did you ever try telling that to
a seller every set down to the table and
tidies napkin around his neck
I did just once
I'm finally begin jobs running down i'm
going to do that myself
you find any traces of the rubber over
20 miles Indians yes we'll get two men
together and we gotta be a bunch of
color to a couple hundred and forty i
talked to dr. another inviting trouble
by stealing our cattle they know there's
no calorie around here tried to reason
with him but they wouldn't listen
my advice is to charge the default
Indian goodwill and let it go at that
much as I was also developing it's my
fault it was stolen
best thing I can do is quickly route
that's nonsense show you can't be held
responsible for something like this side
I need you you're the boss so LOL shark
diving straight me what in heaven's name
are you doing out here and the new
operator said first good
are you responsible for this well I i
telegraphed all that i didn't know we
were going to send i'll bet you didn't
think that much that nobody wanted the
driver was that eastbound stage pass you
in an hour to your going right back to
Omaha young lady and you're going to
stay there all I really same for you
I can help you send me think a bit weird
to take just to see you know that i'd
like to show you are thriving metropolis
you really need a guide to get about you
know very nice of you Blake but I want
you to go ahead with the wagons but sure
you'll be responsible for his crate
while she's here and seeing that you get
safely on the eastbound stage it'll be a
pleasure say well I must be off it seems
goodbye mr. Creighton goodbye mr. Blake
I'm sorry you can stay in my butt then
that's the Telegraph business for you so
if we responsible for this
i'm now not altogether i just want to
see you under 30 we're going to be in
salt lake before you know it
I've got to go now man waiting at the
head of our soon thousand things to ask
i got a thousand things to do good by
the Bible and remember the next time I
pay you a visit and I'm your only system
and I love you think it's a great name
em all families are great
coming
[Music]
what is managed my brother into the
lines that haven't you gone yet
what did you say no
thank you
it's beautiful my brother's even looks
like recording prejudice no man not this
time
ok
with western union God will be 50 years
it was thinking well as much excitement
again like me after the stage weeks
oh i hope i have another thing i had not
of course i know i have an attack
against somebody like flake wouldn't
even let me decide that
I should have met you a couple years ago
since then I've made some mistakes can
be corrected
[Music]
page connect with a railroad to go to
st. Joe be sure to party
mr. you got a passenger we all about you
wanna take a little walk to work up an
appetite but I don't feel like walking
and I don't feel like eating just for
saying that's what you're going to do
[Music]
I'm not saying it doesn't men will meet
assault me maybe and I'll be thinking of
you
this might help
[Music]
bye
job looks like we got company on the
other side ma mommy back to make
champion
[Music]
regardless all back
look my best Vicki understood coming but
you driving in the wrong direction i got
a 10 minute the main camp I just about
make this connection maybe quick of your
worn by telegram that is unless you're
short anxious to get out of here
you have to connect our ass don't you
worry i go that we do too
[Music]
they're right in the head
take it
[Music]
the writer way the way you won't need it
i'm not sure i am and i told mr. quick
and get your I'm boss
[Music]
Wow
no whiskey by Indian brother he'll get
pretty no God we really look at them all
on one of the others had my way I'd like
38 on every tomorrow
[Music]
I put that out there you are get it
perfect Christmas except that specific
equipment can have I make it good
medicine now keeps
[Music]
stop by gonna happen
look there is i want to take you apart I
suppose that's the thanks I get for
trying to help you whatever I need to
have my last point you ever get my help
again you have to get out of your knees
and beg for any of the ready to make
[Music]
thanks Carly will open duck
I think you're gonna lose this patient
at a time as good a doctor as you are
aware that had I wouldn't mind so much
was only engine buddy age why no one
ever looked like that
[Music]
about to get some of the alignment to
create underwater asking your questions
for dr. I gotta have medical attention
and I gotta have a quick shot Harmon
knowing what's the matter here
this is private
it's going to be
well I why didn't make it mr. Creighton
did he say anything before he died
call me if you bad names follows on him
up having buried immediately i don't
remember the number for the time being
he's been slapped with a spade right now
what do you think of this show I don't
know you got any ideas
no you said those Indians that you met
today with drunken you
yeah a white man disguised as an Indian
participated in the raid on the camp
that means white man musta got the real
Indians drunk and talked him into
attacking us and all Yankees out you
know
apparently not you sure those Indians
that got away without be for thinking
well where Indians it looks like Indians
to me
alright that's all voice and what about
your jobs as if nothing happened
Charlie you're taking over Grogan's job
as Foreman I don't have to tell you I
want a responsibility it is thanks mr.
Clayton but i can't take that job i I'm
had the experience you have more
experience than any man in the outfit i
want to only you're not going to let me
down at a time like this how you shot
somebody has got to take charge of
things and pick out some new horses and
all i can do that they ought to be 67
ahead and sage and you take the job if
that's the way you want it mr. Creighton
that's the way I want it into town
tomorrow we'll buy up whatever we can I
tonight's the night
I talked to the manager of course I
don't like about ensure but I think
we're making a great mistake
yes i know you have great faith and show
you just made informant and no doubt he
deserves the post come to the point late
well it seems to me if we ever want to
get this wire strung will have to act
differently than we have up to now what
do you mean you know i'm not looking for
a fight or trouble but look what
happened to our cattle look what
happened today I suppose Sean knows his
business but the way he let those
Indians manhandle s you think he was
deliberately going out of his way to
encourage them to strike at us again
however I guess there's a lot about the
West I never will understand goodnight
I don't think we'll have to go any
father
advanced
audiojack your red creating the western
union agent that's right my name is Jack
Slade nice but hard to make a nice you
want to be in the market with you know
why don't you want both that doesn't
help yourself
our camp was raided yesterday by Indians
I got most of our stock and these are to
be just the thing for it
there are 24 hours i said their hours it
was stolen problems i'll get grating you
would accuse me of being a heartbeat
with you know our way to leverage your
explanation why i got these largest
mortgage Indian they didn't say where
they got them you didn't ask i didn't
and in this country when you call a man
a heart be better have some proof i
bought these cars in good state and i am
the cell in the same way
well then i guess i've ever seen a law
about this i have to go back to Omaha
you do don't run beyond their i'll make
some mild that would look so good with
its western union swinging up white men
want a bunch of Indians did you got all
the answers and you show there might be
able to give you a few more you know
this country inside out what he said
makes sense mr. trading at least it does
out
all right i'm gonna give you that five
thousand dollars because I've got a lot
of work to do and no time for fighting
i'm paying your own assumption $5,000 or
buy off but if you ever bother western
union again the next game will be inlet
clear let's make a developed a lot of
each of the following 15 minutes due to
know one another pretty well now we know
old friend's far less we were both
raised in the same car Missouri
[Music]
going to add still fail
and all right here that straps on the
bank of omaha often $5,000 case this by
telegraph if you want i trust you
I suppose you do and travel to well I'd
like this you're in the market just a
question
I'm integrating you're right good
management but only watch
[Music]
alright was not at all right by the
thousands yeah and I instead decided to
stay and create yes no no first of all I
want to take a great big drink to the
confederate states of america was not
considered it wouldn't be no war that
something think those yeah but I
something else a good thing we made the
last a long time if you don't spot sides
[Music]
are you mr. creating yeah I'm take I'm
shot hollow for love I'm afraid I've got
some bad news for you keep squad advance
and biancalana still sending word that
you can't build any more lines Louise
nation know why not one of your men
wounded his son yesterday they were
drunk captain the radar camp immediately
after women to kill several of my men
spotted horse there's none of these
Indians kill any white men to run
against gonna kill these young bucks
drunk and talked him into a horse
stealing ready to get some more whiskey
the Renegades did the killing
so the chief field that only white men
are to blame for the renegade heart says
he doesn't know Indians are not I'm
going ahead with the line captain
government's counting on it I realized
that mr. eight Washington has already
notified me to help you all I can but
unfortunately most of my troops have
been ordered to the Army of the Potomac
decide and indian war means the massacre
you wouldn't want them close that we
have spotted horses brother at Fort
Kearney as a hostage for the behavior of
the ergonomic i might try putting a
little pressure on him David in Georgia
we like and wake the winter is almost
here and from now on every day count if
I could talk with the chief that's like
getting to change his mind i'm going to
greater risk after what happened you
don't want his territory alone or with
normal in a couple of men and on even
then there's no telling what he might do
we've got to take their chance and with
your permission we will thank you
something
[Music]
looking devil dr. just don't get your
wires crossed
whatever we do we gotta do quick Indians
can stay interested in one thing going
off a temp track your wife
cool oh ok nardin on my god you guys you
know what's wrong but Nick I'm going on
where they are getting frantic he said
you come in peace today but they won't
be in it if you try to take the singing
wire through the organ donation and tell
him that the great white father who
speaks of lightning over the same wire
is sorry for the wounding of his Indian
Sun but the lightning talk is strong
medicine and muscle true i know i said
money was for eng our high and do you
know what the key
what do you wear your top will not last
you're not quite tasty he said the
autopilot doesn't believe the singing
wire strong better ask him if you let 10
of the strongest Braves hold a ton of
the singing wire that is after we proved
the time was what any and daddy
IDK not get wedding is located buddy
Western had enjoy your not about it this
way you're not going to get locked up
let's hang on the sludge of it where
you're not you can get around it but I
have a lot of our target your dog
because yeah the end of the game and
then combine your love ourselves from
this guy did a workout in with your
mouth of the
so I just you're not he said yes
[Music]
my guys are you get your chance you want
to know why we for water on the ground
following will tell him tell him we must
make sacrifice to the rain god whose
brother to the lighting and what is they
has me all this time we're going over to
you by the offseason connection between
the gods
although I show and explain to him that
it's good medicine for us but it's bad
for our enemies are quite see Annie and
they are beyond what you get done
oh well that's good
[Music]
[Applause]
Wow
[Music]
they're gonna do is we're gonna turn the
other way when they actually have talked
but not when I was no question he said
the great white father is lightning is
the strongest medicine they've ever seen
that the singing I can go through his
nation in peace i'll tell him I promise
that the singing why I will make good
medicine for the overall against their
enemies if they not watch Tony and where
they are we are 18 overlaps arguably
yours and what do you watch on you and
what you worship he says peace Pete
let's get out of here before they have a
chance to think it over
[Music]
I was sure everything's going to be all
right from the first thank you card now
I gave it a thought
[Music]
why is that
I've called you together tonight to give
you some good news for a change with
practically licked their job
we're on the last leg and the finish is
almost in sight
your Palace of all done a great job and
so when we reach salt lake city
everybody gets an extra 20 months player
bonus
and tonight double portion of the ground
for everybody
[Applause]
I'm girl
just want to see let it fall to matter
of life and death in an argument fell
over now Philip logged in the stomach
where is only a couple miles from here
alright i'll meet you on the other side
of the camp
sorry that's this is artist I want your
boys
web
almost all blanks are I got jumped in to
save my roasted I'm gonna burn out
western union tonight that much to be a
part of it
that's mighty white of you well used to
be one of us as far as I'm concerned
you're still I kept your mouth shut and
played square that wanna see you get
hurt
get hold of yourself Jack you can't find
a thing as big as important as western
union by plumb loco de to me this thing
don't work tonight something else will
I'm gonna stop him about to cut down
every Yankee pole between Omaha are you
gonna be with us or not
listen Jack I want to give you some of
the best advice your other head
yeah like western union alone I'm not
gonna let them along delayed 10 times
over really put a wireless string it
why doesn't better-known ago my stay
like a toasty largest bring them out and
when they need more wagons more harder
and more cattle will be on hand to sell
until you're fully Jack you can't go up
against the things because this without
getting home
maybe I will maybe I walk you got any
sense you'll spring along with it
ok what I'll do you come along with us
now cut into half of my share
it's a bargain on one condition yeah
that you agree to give up this bonfire
doesn't come back to Missouri living
with John Apple general most in be real
develop time abroad and type
so you won't change your mind and come
with us not this trip
alright I'm white
I looked everywhere mr. Creighton like a
flight
all right i'll see you in the morning
nice good i don't you're looking for
shop
yes I saw him right out of camp over an
hour ago
as a result riled up like they were sure
your circle whole camp
[Applause]
fire fire everybody out like everybody
talking about across my back later
[Music]
[Applause]
what
like
doctor
God
[Music]
[Applause]
why
[Music]
I'm just tired but to my department will
accidents all 15 thought that he was
effective mentoring other pictures haha
don't know I'm not behave yourself here
it could still like a good ball here
those nice little piece
come on not good
I didn't think you've got back in time
to get burn your next 10 show come to my
temp I want to talk to you thanks
never seen this before No
char for a long time I've been expecting
you to tell me something you didn't have
given you every chance
the only conclusion I can draw always I
was wrong about you know I didn't say
anything on the cattle stolen and I
didn't say anything about that horse be
on stage with your absence last night is
something I won't put up with once and
for all I want the truth
I pack up your things and get out
at all
Wow
you're clearing out the afternoon after
I go there's a favor i want you to do
for me a favor for you mr. Creighton
Jack slaves my brother your brother I
wanted to tell you myself but want to
follow your own brother very much you
can say i'm going in the alkaline little
business almost great not to worry Jack
Slater harder western union
[Music]
che a pleasure friends
Jack it out for you
oh yeah we'll stay here
alright you'll excuse me I send out the
one-hander but that clot around me I get
the work done but my wife she's a
stickler for punctuality and I live way
over to the side town shadows I had this
weekend but you don't make me if you
know what's good for you
sorry yes
if you didn't see it is seen its alright
then of the heads are we going to do
that depends
we'll see
ok
he comes
out of it
how did
did you call the journalist no I'm gonna
give you an even break check it can't go
on this way any longer
it's got to be the ume so get up and
take that in front off
[Music]
ok
like well like a nice sound of coming
across the continent music show could
hear a long way from solid city boo TLC
but I think