did you see captain claw yeah it was me
real good yeah
you're really scored very very well on a
school board exam so well in fact that
she outdid most of the first graders
throughout the entire district my Ruby
yes
ha
dancin
you
I got the blue I'm just to do as I hey
room is me I got the blue
looks like you've groans a bit huh
sweetie pie since last week and couldn't
say over the counter thanks for your
little faster I'm sure Ruby will do us
proud I have no doubt and thank you mrs.
beddows see you again soon oh this
here's my husband haven dr AC bro out of
the n-double-a-cp glad to meet you mr
Bridges and this here's my Ruby is this
the little girl I hear is so smart
congratulations honey well you've got a
special one here sir special indeed
she's been picked with five other girls
and they're about to do something that
no other Negro children have done in New
Orleans you got a lot to be proud of
good bye now hey governor change Houston
Davis call for a special legislative
sessions to determine how to stop the
racial mixing in New Orleans public
schools which is set to begin on Monday
the attorney general Ward the governor
not to interfere with the federal court
order to desegregate the schools but
Davis bout vehemently to preserve
segregation despite the warning helo me
see are you sure about this we gotta
talk some more I heard what he said Aven
and I'm not letting it scared me the
governor Davis can fuss all he want to
but the federal government is above the
state so we just ain't got no choice but
while we gotta put Ruby where she ain't
even wanted I mean if she did so good on
that test that must mean she doing just
fine where she at but you know colored
schools ain't as good as the white ones
now dr. boyard said that ruby has what
it takes to go far honey no one ever
took that
her interest in you and me his kids now
did they she won this right with her own
line so don't you think she deserves to
take it if she does this this could make
things better for other children too for
all colored children
the church say amen let the church say
man
lord for his annoying you know there's a
message in there we walk with the Lord
if we stay we are never alone even when
it may seem so today we are a people
under fire there's no denying that
there's no denying the fact that America
does not and have not embraced us
because I don't have to tell your
brothers and sisters get every day
there's a new plan to keep us down to
keep us up
pahala you I got some news for you here
today can order Buster Buster eyes out
yes we gonna have to stay before we go
on good in spite of the Opposition
persevere
gonna be walking with us tomorrow I'm
going to new school we're gonna get
trying to call mom says Oh daddy I gotta
go to a Catholic schools done soon and
we'd even Catholic why did I do that Wow
still see at school still with your
buddy game no you as out
you nervous baby girl I wish I can go
with you but you can tell daddy all
about later okay hmm and daddy's brave
little girl
morning
are you raising a logan street yes sir
do you have ID no I it's fine for now
but you're gonna need on your way back
in case you run into the next shift so
uh just people pad to all the gods know
everyone
isn't she pretty she's oh thank the Lord
for you Miss Taylor I don't think I
could have done this without you honey
you know I love dem kids now Ruby you
remember to answer the teacher yes ma'am
when she speaks to you okay baby yes
mama
good morning miss bridges I'm deputy US
Marshal al bummer but I thought the man
from the n-double-a-cp was good being
escorted by u.s. marshals today man
y'all my Miss Taylor you here
come on
I bro guy
speaking in just a min gonna drive
school baby that's all
Allison
get down
wait till I opened the door before you
get out we'll get behind you the two men
in the front car will walk in front of
them we'll all go in the building
together stay between the four of us and
do not look back no matter what happens
don't look back at the crowd say nothing
going through it I'm late for a medical
conference but hey what's going on here
oi
Oh
ah
governor of the great state of Louisiana
says you cannot enter thank you sir
President of the United States says that
I can
scoping
you
give only fessenden that little me buddy
yeah good beer come on boy come on mrs.
Reed what you doin go go back to your
columnist rated vice principal at bring
your friends superintendent Redmond I
said ain't going to school with no
jiggaboo mama well yeah the girls who's
supposed to come with me didn't know for
sure was going to be here what about the
other children they told me there was
two more supposed to become the school
with Reuben ale well I suppose their
parents have a good sense not to put
their children through this hello tell
him to call this wood man miss wood man
this year woman says she's the new
teacher supposed to be here you don't
look like no teacher though
yes can I help you yes good morning I am
Barbara Henry superintendent Redmond
told me to report to the principal for
work today oh not today not today well
she's in a board meeting downtown and
it's just not sorted out just yet come
back tomorrow okay
she don't
she is dismissed come on Barry let's go
the school's easy mom
with children in crisis if away hey
stress seems to present itself alrighty
away I never got there streets are
blocked you're never gonna believe why
it was crazy I'm sitting in the car
right let's police everywhere I can't
move there's a crowd of women standing
in front of a school then this little
tiny adorable Negro girl gets out of a
car surrounded by huge marshals and in
these women I'm pretty sure their
mothers state they start chanting these
these hateful things at this little
bitty girl I've never seen anything like
it people can be so mean Bob I grew up
watching had the treated Fe my nanny
that act like her color made her guilty
of something maybe I could work with her
you know offer my help to her and her
family I've studied the situation and
try to help her cope I think it would
certainly be as important as the work I
did with the kids in the polio award I
think it's a great idea yeah
go away okay okay miss Bridget
Oh
don't mind and will be keep walking
get back you
this is your teacher mrs. Henry well
hello Ruby now it's so nice to meet you
very nice to meet you too mrs. bridges
likewise so Ruby I hear you're quite a
good student is that true yes ma'am well
that's perfect cuz I'm pretty good
myself this here is the captain dr. Rob
occults pleased to meet you captain
pleasure sorry but I have to check
everyone who comes in here I understand
you turn range ever
there was a phonics book in here just a
minute ago love to forgive me I I
haven't quite gotten my bearings yet how
long have you been here 30 humidity
here's something where you from Boston
originally but I've been teaching
children overseas on a military base I
just recently was married and my
husband's work is here in New Orleans so
I've come to join him well welcome to
the staff
well I'm here today because I'd like to
talk with the Negro child who's
attending here and what would you want
to talk to that little nigger for I'd
like to see how she's doing the focus of
my work is to study how children handle
stress how they cope with crisis country
and tell you right now there's nothing
intriguing about that color job
certainly respect your opinion man um
but if you would allow me to speak with
her mother I'd appreciate I can't get
more involved and I'm required to maybe
you could give me the child's name we
have strict orders I'd be breaking the
law
well if you're so interested in the
colored you ought to go talk to their
organization I'm sorry what organization
that colored people's organization okay
okay I'm gonna write a word on your
paper christmas very good now listen
using the letters in Christmas I want
you to write down as many words as you
can using only the letters in the word
okay see h.o.t hi her dexterity is
advanced for this age she writes fast
and well she picks up everything just
like a sponge see oh ah oh ah shit is ah
Chee 6h ah M
ah you tell me where the lounges please
this one you know I don't envy you mrs.
Holman you must have really needed a job
there's no need for consolation miss
Spencer I've taught children from many
different backgrounds and I enjoy them
all this is a disgrace this place is
ruined in your part of it well it's
unfortunate that she feels that way
frankly I think it's pretty silly for
almost full to empty out because of one
little girl I'm superintendent Redman
offer me this position I had no idea to
have one city I told miss Woodmere I
couldn't teach that little migra we have
friends that gave their resignation
Heather than teacher for what we are
about to receive may we truly be
thankful amen round here we don't teach
them our kids don't learn with them
this is dangerous Lucille it's only day
two it ain't too late to back out of
this why are you always scared
everything huh never want to make no way
while the way we don't have something as
if we my fault in the Warren I won the
middle you think I got that metal being
scared oh you best mine who you talking
to me I'm sorry baby I've been to the
school and I've seen it it's better it's
cleaner it's nicely it's noah and i
teach our teachers from up north and
she's smart and she's kinda supposed to
go alone tomorrow now she's just a
little girl how can we put her through
that I'm sick of people telling us what
we can't go what we can't do what we
ain't supposed to have my children are
gonna have more they deserve more and
the only way things are gonna get better
for them as if we make them better honey
we can't be afraid your mom associated
looking my kids and here it baby you
know mama's got to go back to work
tomorrow and daddy's working so you
think you could be a brave girl and go
to school by yourself with the big man
hmm okay
you know Jesus faced a mob too baby just
like you you know what he did he prayed
for them because the Bible says bless
them that persecute you bless and curse
not
Ruby remember what I told you keep
looking straight ahead
Oh
daddy's great little girl
your daddy's brave little girl
remember god loves you opening
god loves you baby
your daddy's grave
Ruby now that you look so very special
today dress is lovely and your bone mass
is so perfect so you Catholic yet uh-huh
no one's on me baby hit me with knuckles
and stuff yeah my church is not dare say
so knuckles in the past you have to pay
for private school and private school
means you better you got to get in your
class got it right there my school is
private I'm the old one down my daddy
said it show fault we got him houses up
the street and they nobody like him
neither
daddy daddy Dwight hungry something
wrong with my cooking tonight why I got
so many dogs today daddy hi folks down
the bakery heard what a brave thing is
gone and then they wanted to give you
and your sister and brothers an extra
special treat and Tim Macedon
boss told me today I can't I can't have
no nigger up working for me what's got a
child in a white school been working
here 18 years now never had one unhappy
customer not one if nobody better at
fixing cause to me I know baby I know
but it all work itself out you get
another job my buddy owns a big shop was
watching out the window I guess me on my
boss Co told me to go game y'all don't
as yet I told him how appreciative I
wanna take all he got he said hey man
don't even worry about it I can
I can always make more
what can I make more of seal even dumber
I wasn't all me I know about integration
I've know all about it it don't work it
don't work you know they they treat me
like a soldier I was a colored soldier a
nobody it was it was just fine with
white folk when I was willing to die for
this country for you try to give my kid
ma my beautiful little daughter when
their kids gotten there all up on my
back reminded me how is that country a
become one and no everything seems wrong
and you're probably blaming me for but
honey we don't get through this I'm
leaving you so much I know gospel
microwave us I just know
Oh
my daddy's coming with me today I'm
sorry sir it'll be too dangerous why I'm
a father what answer and you're a man
but as a man and her father I'm not sure
that you'd be able to restrain yourself
listen up she'll be fine them crackers
will make you want to beat him down
let's go movie
this one here this one near as you know
she has no phys ed and she should have
some type of music listen I just wanted
to know what you thought I'll be to your
student I really don't have time to
think as you know we're forced to vacate
school property expeditiously is not due
to my students one year we must be
escorted from the premises because of
people's attitudes toward my student
that is exactly the point they've given
us no time to prepare and I'm caught in
the middle now what do you expect me to
do good very good I ok ok
now the other kids come back so it can
be like normal school they'll come back
eventually their parents are just angry
right now but soon they'll get over it
and bring them back for now you should
just think of this as your very own
school what do you think of that yeah we
can have fun just the two of us can't we
ok I will be back in 30 minutes and I
want you to eat your lunch now too
here we go good afternoon good to see
you again seal good afternoon mrs.
bridges I'd like you to meet dr. and
mrs. Cole Jane pleased to meet you nice
to meet you both pleasures ours ma'am
he's a psychiatrist a what suckage sorry
for dropping by unannounced but the
coals have wanted to meet you for some
time and they came all the way from
Biloxi he and I have spoken at length
and I'm confident Ruby would benefit
from talking with him I'm aware of
what's going on out at the friends
school if I've seen and I'd love to be
of help if I may oh well we came for no
psychiatrist no oh no no no I won't be
charging you anything well thank you
very much but uh we just regular folk
ain't no by the crazy here I understand
you should know though that I have
extensive experience working with
children especially children facing
great adversity and in most cases it can
be quite helpful if they have an
opportunity to speak with someone
outside of the family
y'all have a nice day
good afternoon um I'll tell you what if
you happen to change your mind for any
reason please don't hesitate to call
thank you very much thank you thank you
dr. Boyer you know my husband's been
laid out for quite some time and we were
wondering if someone in the organization
might be able to find him some work I
mean he's really good at a lot of great
you don't think that now is a good time
for him to be looking better to lay low
for a while let things simmer down so
I'm supposed to just sit around here
doing nothing except worry about how
i'ma pay the rent and take care of my
family these donations ain't gonna last
well I understand how you feel I'm a man
with a family myself but it's just
temporary in the meantime we'll make
sure your family's needs are met and try
to remember what a privilege it is for
Ruby to be doing this really any them
low color girls at that otherwise school
happen to be children of n-double-a-cp
fo huh I mean how many of y'all put your
sick shows up to this here privilege any
of you had the privilege of losing your
job
I want to talk by now going back inside
baby as you see hey my mom with me today
come on
Oh
mama rubed car car nigga and she said
she was kidding why don't we start with
you drawing a picture of your school can
you tell me something about your school
it's fun my teacher likes me oh no what
got t say now okay um no why don't we
just keep drawing for now okay okay
money time I teach you now why don't you
want to finish this one it is strange
are these the people out in front of the
school so how they look to you I don't
know how but good cuz I don't look at
him why don't you look at me cuz my mom
and the man told me not to so I don't me
and McHenry come home too jumpy Jack all
the way two hundred hmm they were just
lovely next time you should really sit
down and chat with him you know Jane I'm
not there to socialize okay
so how did it go in there Oh according
to Ruby everything's just fine at school
she's having a good time well maybe I
mean how can that be it doesn't make any
sense she doesn't show any signs of
being scared or traumatized honey you'll
figure it out it's the first meeting
what's my berry I'm scared did you have
a battery no but I was thinking laughing
hmm you say your prayers how I expect I
I want you going there get back on the
knees and you ask him to take care of
you
hi I'm so sorry able but will you please
not come here anymore what please please
just go
okay fine then coming here no more if
that's how you want you remember who was
first to come in here and you first
moved here and then crackers wouldn't
buy from no Jews ain't never been
nothing but nice to you man but if
that's how you want it that's how it's
gonna be come on y'all let's go let's go
get ready for bed come on we know you
better eat that food ciao you better
finish that plate and stop your
foolishness I'm just drunk angry you're
at your daddy baby please please eat
something maybe I have some tips out of
the bag leaning back though and a cola
here's swallow this
my cooking that bad all you want to eat
is packaged foods you didn't eat nothing
yesterday you ain't eat nothing this
morning all you want to eat his chips
this mrs. Stanton doubts at my school
he'd say those swing eggs no baby she's
Jewish they not much nicer to her either
but instead we can't come on this door
no more she did wow that's not very nice
but it because me right how come you
likes me mama no baby no no see you and
the other colored girls are doing
something that white folks don't like
it's not you they don't want color
children going to their schools but you
know what you're special and you're
smart and you deserve an education just
as good as theirs they say those mean
things because he want you to think that
you don't deserve it but no matter what
they say you know God loves you and they
don't know what they talking about
here inside
I'm just trying to take my daughter to
school
Oh
crazy honey some people were raised with
funny ideas about people that are
different than them you see the they
think skin color is everything and if
you don't have the same skin as theirs
they don't like you oh not all people
are like that we're not like that we
know that all people are special and
that we should respect everyone is it
all my skin
Ruby do you know it what slavery is no
well there was a time in the South when
white people used to own me grows like
you would on a header or a toy and they
used to make the Negroes work very hard
without any pay but in the north where
I'm from we knew that was wrong and the
north and south had a big fight in the
North won and they told the South that
they had to free all the slaves praise
the Lord you see some people still
haven't gotten over the difference
between Negro and white and they don't
want them to be together and those
people outside are angry because the
laws are forcing the whites to be with
the Negroes and they don't like that why
do they say those men thanks to me I
didn't do anything no you didn't do
anything honey you see they just they
just feel threatened and they're so
angry that they don't like anybody not
even themselves you know some people
sometimes when they feel kicked down
they don't know how to do anything else
to kick other people down you and I both
know that that's not right right
why don't we take a look at our drawings
now shall we let's see what you've done
hmm see that is this you here Reuben
uh-huh it's my friend Alison her daddy
she SAT because he don't like her play
with no one who died doesn't make as
much money as her daddy makes oh so
Alison's a white girl no no she said me
oh why couldn't tell because you draw
her and her father with pink rounds
instead of brown in fact you you draw
yourself with pink crayons a lot to see
you've got blue hair instead of black
and you John yourself and Alison and her
father with missing parts you you you
don't have a mouth there and Allison
doesn't have ears and father has no eyes
but your teacher and I you've drawn us
with all of our parts carefully intact
why do you think that is
you called this good this kitty godless
Udrih better than that what's wrong with
my drawing yeah that is pretty bad huh
Oh Bob gotta try this this Hill took me
how to make red beans and rice uh-huh no
thank you he never gets anything that's
good at home everyone in bed yeah you
have to seat up oh no no thank you it's
kind of you but we really need to hit
the road well these let me give you some
time in Biloxi is a long way no I'm not
hungry really oh I should tell you
though before we go that i'm a bit
concerned about ruby and what's going on
out at the school have either of you
noticed any peculiar behavior with Ruby
aside from the doll and how she spoke to
her siblings no she seems alright to me
she won't eat like she used to doctor
let me tell you something she don't want
nothing said packaged food like cookies
and chips and she won't drink nothing
but coke Cola
um I think I know what's happening
I've observed the hecklers out in front
of the school and there's one particular
woman who well she threatens to poison
Ruby I'm sorry very much to have to tell
you both but she threatens to kill her
what
Skip's sorry mr. British I am so full
i'm gonna shoot yourselves up I got
course yeah can I
you
how can they be so cool to my baby I
thought I was doing the right thing I
really did come on come on anything all
your fault I should've put my foot down
I shouldn't let you talk me into it I
never been for this in the first place
so you think we should stop will be
ain't standing there school see I just
need to pray about this I know my god
wait give me more than will hit him yeah
what do you think he doing I'm doing
what's best for our daughter I watched
it in that and I listening see she she
got it in her head that white folks is
better than cover she draws colored folk
deformed and white folk perfect but
what's that got to do with Jesus
nobody really know what he looks like
but she sees this every day tell so that
God looks more like my folks outside of
school then huh
can you make something on that please oh
it's you're hungry huh yes oh wow I'm
not I had a home-cooked meal can I have
to show you something ah port god
where's my take a reading a spell may
music hey oh hey oh hey daddy I'd see
that's great where this yes sir
and hiking in school don't you yeah I'm
glad you did
well go get changing go play Marian call
waiting for you up the street
no Ruby you was with me at the
supermarket when I bought that rice and
those beans you saw there was wrapped
tight no one's put nothing in there move
it baby you got to eat you hear me good
girl mama you set those pretty box at my
school will stop they will honey hey
well when you know Ruby when you feel
like this you gotta remember just turn
into the Lord remember what I told you
Jesus did they can't hurt you honey
those men are there to protect you I
remember god loves you hmm hey hi hello
got some goodies for you what can I get
you two oh nothing thank you just some
coffee down it but let me help no it's
mom no not everything comes in this
house is for you and you gonna have to
share oh my word y'all like to adopt a
couple of kids excellent we'd love to
have Ruby spend a day with our girl
sometime if that's all right well I'm
sure she would love that honey we've got
a piano and my wife would like to teach
you to play would you like that mm-hmm
oh my you have your very own piano you
know she's been learning a bit with miss
him
well we just want to spend some time
with her let her know we're here for I
gotta give me some hair I'm sorry he's
having a hard time don't understand what
he's going through has got to be hard on
any man aven hey then honey I know you
don't believe me but I really think they
do mean well she's most people ain't
interested in Ruby and I think it'll be
a good idea for her to see how they live
show her what our folks can have when
they have a good education they were
just being polite but not polite enough
to invite us huh no tell me did Elmo bro
yard invite you to tea oh no no why okay
then no visits every once in a while huh
having Ruby to their house and and
showing her how they live didn't gonna
help this family how where are the
Broads when my daughter ain't eatin him
when she's having nightmares they don't
want to know about all that they don't
want to support us like real friends and
you you just just smiling just sucking
it up that's enough David there's
nothing wrong with me one Ruby to see
another side of life I want her to learn
to play the piano if she wants to I want
her to experience being in a nice house
without having to clean it I don't see
my daughter being used no more but
nobody
hey hey man that's gone still I know
this folks told you not to go out
looking for work but i have a few
painting leagues then i can show you
your help i can't pay a mechanic salary
there is something
appreciate see you in the morning I've
got a gig how's ping
hey sweetie how was your lunch bye is
everything okay movie Oh kids came back
whence is Henry it's not my schooling mo
how'd he know that more kids came back
Ruby I so how come that all in class
together nom not
why did he make some more Valentine's
sweetheart and and I'll be back in just
a few moments okay okay there is no good
reason why she should be by herself all
day especially since the other children
are first graders and right next door
miss Spencer does not want to teach that
child and nobody's gonna force her fine
then let her children come into Ruby's
class for part of the day and I'll teach
them as an outsider what makes you so
concerned miss Woodmere it is cruel to
isolate a child those children are not
going to accept her so you just let it
be this school was ordered to integrate
if you continue to separate Ruby you are
breaking the federal law shall we call
superintendent Redmond and discuss it
with him
children we're gonna go into this is
Ruby everyone go ahead go this Ruby
rubies in the game to know Skippy
my mother told me have to tell you the
creature Anita Scott you're in don't you
want to play Scott come on it's fun to
be it
you can do it
stand up let's go no Kevin get hurt my
feelings cuz it's my mama oh my daddy
told me not plead someone I wouldn't
need them Allison daddy told her not
clear to me too will your mom let you
ask the mighty special bread and poured
it from up north hmm yeah I think that
would be a good thing Oh be just a
moment while it Bruce Ruby what would
you be disappointed if my mom is said I
couldn't have tea with you
hope be sad it's me one visit me anymore
is it is it lonely for you at school I'm
by myself how lunchtime this is Henry's
nice but the other kids don't play with
me you know it it's good to know how you
feel and to tell someone movie it make
you feel better I'm certainly glad you
told me is there anything else that you
could do to make yourself feel better
like cry or laugh for draw with the
crayons are kiss ready Oh
Oh for me
mm-hmm but we have to pray before we eat
it hmm god is great God is good now we
thinking for this food in jesus name
amen amen
your daddy gonna much be in the ballgame
next time right don't thank some says
colorful can got time to be playing
games since you got to work hard if you
want to have some in this world oh I'm
coming daddy what did I tell you you
just mark us up on back over to that
house Lewis ain't no need to holla I
reckon we're here you all right you know
bridges oh your kid went to that school
this neighborhood was doing fine but now
we got barricades a welcoming stands
white bumps up the street looking at a
sideways now colored folks is talkin
about boycotting mardi gras which means
my tavern ain't gonna do no business so
if i wanna holla are you sure gonna hear
me all right
Ruby don't hold it guys Oh Ruby come
back sweet
but honey I saw you talking to them did
you finally get angry with them did you
tell him to just leave you alone no I
didn't tell them anything and he talked
to them but roomy I was there I saw her
lips moving I wasn't talking to them I
was praying for them praying for them
yes I prefer thing every day in the car
and I forgot that dead Oh what pair did
you say please God forgive these people
because even if they say those mean
things they don't know what they're
doing so you can't forgive them
just like you did those folks alone
tango
terrible things about you we SAT one
painting of jesus on the wall
somebody stolen so what going through my
paintings up on the wall now hey Lou boy
Carlton chapel Mustaine like that get
off there he's okay he's okay so doc
how's my little girl doing you know you
come in here paying attention to it like
that listening to it that makes it feel
real special dr. Cole's would you like
something to drink ah that sounds great
thanks here we go come on baby come on
curl and it's Bob please but I
appreciate your kind words very much
left my thick what makes me feel so
specialist you and your family and
something greater than in all of us all
this time I wondered what makes you so
strong don't be too hard on yourself
down I think that things were not
supposed to figure out till the time is
right hold on me uh-huh
I mean look at these pictures remember
all the one she did with the pink crayon
uh paint and the phone yeah she's
certainly wearing out the brown ones now
huh that's progress here yeah Wow what's
that yes gumbo looks great mmm try and
so I learned that a family and a child
under great stress and fear could show
exquisite dignity and courage because of
their moral and religious values and
because they had a definite purpose in
what they were trying to accomplish this
purpose made them resilient I couldn't
figure out the source of this resilience
because I only worked with well-to-do
children who really had nothing to work
hard for no reason driving them to
accomplish anything so now I see that
the issue is not stressed but stress for
what purpose having something to believe
in protected Ruby from psychiatric
symptoms and gave her a dignity and
strength that is utterly remarkable so
all we could do was to sip since she is
a good teacher who can't read that well
yet miss Woodmere from the Chandler
thank you
there have been mice and cockroaches in
here and the janitor needs to see why
what's all this discuss
I'm not angry with you honey I'm just
very concerned that you're not eating
your lunches I mean you're so tiny as it
is I've been eaten more than I used to
listen anyway really but I don't like
what my mom makes now the time
hey Ruby here's a test to see how well
you'd learn this year now how do you
take your time and lead to your best
it's in the box it's a surprise that's
what's in the box what's in the box hey
I'll look at those later okay I'm sorry
about that Bob oh that's okay hey what
you pay they play a game okay this is
your classroom and let's say that these
are you and the other students and I was
wondering if maybe you could tell me
something about them you know who they
are and what they're like this one's
married she's nice her dad is a minister
mm-hmm this one Scott he's ok but it
doesn't relax this is Jimmy used to be
bad no it plays okay sometimes but then
who limbs uncolored look it's bad again
how exactly does he act when he gets bad
he pushes me she calls me lame things
what do you do Ruby when he calls you
mean things to get angry and didn't do
mean things back no I used to be badly
someone give me thanks to me at church I
hope if someone is bad God makes a bath
they come back on that person so I don't
do it anymore I want to cook all up okay
you want
you got seals teaching my wife to make
gumbo oh man it's gonna be a while huh
feel like taking a walk when you get
done sure great okay
things finally calming down around here
yeah thank you I said tell me darling
why you got to be so late
please may not ever see
don't
we got the metal home
I would tell you I've got me a Purple
Heart I know that Janey told me how'd
you get it got wounded in Korea saving
the white soldier so you shed blood for
a country that doesn't really allow you
to enjoy the freedom you thought to
maintain I can't feel good nope that's
why never put much faith in the
integration you know I mean even in the
war fighting side by side we were still
colored they were still what miss my
life for me we still didn't mix actually
never hung out together little nothing
before I met Ruby I never thought about
segregation you didn't have to
gotta make you angry huh
no not no more don't do me no good you
no doubt believe it or not I learned a
lot from watch my car I definitely
believe it huh she's a great teacher I'm
so happy to see us coming to a close you
have no idea miss Woodmere may have
Ruby's test scores please oh this is
wonderful I knew she would do well her
test scores are incredible hmm that's
what I thought that's why I'm lowering
them to more accurately reflect a true
assessment of her ability what
well she's been privately tutored the
whole year through which makes your
schoolers inaccurate she's had special
attention the other children just did
not have that's what this is you're
upset because she did better than the
other children crystal is her too ha and
I'll change them as I see fit and I
would like to discuss it with the
principal I already have she did the
work by herself so the scores are
accurate the only reason she was
privately taught is because you would
not put her with other children to mix
those children and you failed didn't you
they didn't accept that's not true Oh
their children they don't care what
color she is it is only their parents
and ignorant people who teach them to
hate if you are unhappy here please
don't come back miss Woodmere shuttle
what about the children miss Woodmere do
they mean anything to you you may
dismiss the hard work of one little girl
but there will be other little girls and
boys the country is changing miss
Woodmere whether you like it or not
that woman worked her behind off this
year miss Woodmere she spent nearly
every minute of every day being
dedicated to her job your job is with
you is to support all your teachers not
to sabotage them I come on its grip on
the bed
hey how about that car little sluggish
and Ruth isn't playing real good too
then go to not on now see she don't need
my help just got natural talent she gets
some up food there it is y'all real
proud of you
popsicle oh boy oh god you guys will
have a birthday party soon no and you
and mrs. cole's can come to it you know
what we'll be there yeah yeah tell me
about your picture this is your missus
clothes that's hidden that's the boy dog
why'd you put us in there cuz I like you
there who's this here that's Jimmy he
says it's got to be my friend now in
those mom told not today he doesn't call
me that name anymore that's good I think
people are happier when they make
Bradley's what do you think huh I think
you've done a great teacher that's what
I think can I have a hug teacher Roby
you
mine Barbara I'm sorry we didn't get to
know each other better this year
I think what you did was the right thing
and I think you did it really well
believe it or not that means a lot to me
maybe next year if you get Ruby or
someone like her in your class he'll be
able to do the same
in 1995 Ruby Bridges establish the Ruby
Bridges Educational Foundation which
seeks to build an understanding of
cultural diversity within public schools
across the nation under her leadership
the growth and success of this
foundation continues to prove that the
sacrifices her family made were not in
vain