now don't get nasty my little friend
your pump is not gonna hurt you one bit
just relax needs you been in the morning
you'll find yourselves in your nail hole
in my kids
you
good morning doc what you got there Oh
upon some new friends
what better be careful they can sing a
man to death don't worry we understand
each other they know who their friends
is they can tell ya but they know when
you ain't to your new boss wants what I
know have no fear of them are horse
hey give us a hand here blow that mr.
Barker yeah surprised to see you out
here in the field sir now our Things
runnin at the front office smooth as
honey Renfro huh I see here you turned
in over a thousand pounds of orange
blossom honey and 400 ease back last
month Renfro congratulations you've made
the top of the list again thank you sir
okay honey needs our kind of matter and
throw you sit with it I can see a bright
future for you with the company well I
did try to do my best mr. Parker I try
to take my inspiration from the bees
always busy busy busy yes what about the
sulla doctors in from sensor but doesn't
nut him and his bees you know it and
surprise me someday to see him flapping
his arms taking off after some queen bee
with the rest of the drone hmm he's paid
to do research on royal jelly haven't
had a progress reports on him in a month
he has a little workshop up there back
of the orange grove he's few colonies
suppose I'd better go up there and take
a look
hey you where's it fellas in from guys
up for the extract is up there hey this
is Anna honey bee what what who's
responsible today most likely dr.
syndromes I told you is a crackpot this
then
Ventura
then from
telecare since worthless all this
nonsense about what I'm so glad you
dropped in mr. rocket mr. Barker I'm on
the verge of a great discovery discovery
what do you mean well sir I almost
perfected a new method of extracting
royal jelly from between wash according
to my figures you're better at
extracting funds from the company now
look here's in trip over a thousand
dollars last month for miscellaneous yes
yes I know mr. Bartlett let me just show
you something just let me show you
something already I've learned to slow
the process of aging soon I shall be
able to reverse it entire what are you
getting at Winthrop
look what do you see see if they done a
little dog let's say an old dog and his
young dog all right so what whether
exactly the same age you see the little
one greater has been given regular
injections of my compound from the Queen
wash just like I told you mr. Barker now
look here is in trouble I understand
about science and progress and all that
but you were saying to extract queen bee
royal jelly oh it's a health food as a
cosmetic it's not a miracle drug or an
elixir of youth that sort of thing is
impossible but mr. Farkas min truck I'm
sorry he's interrupted I'm going to have
to let you go you just don't seem to be
one of the team you understand good luck
I'm sure you'll fit in somewhere
fitted somewhere
oh don't worry my friends we shall find
a home somehow somewhere over to sound
impatient I know your pizza you're
hungry and that they must be sued now
how would you like a nice juicy little
catheter like that Lipton strong because
o lot of work to do together yes
as you can see gentlemen sales to the
last fiscal quarter have dropped 14 and
one-half percent there's not been a
corresponding drop in our competitor
sales I trust one of you gentlemen has a
satisfactory explanation mr. decline of
one little suggestion general we'll
start with you Thompson it's public
relations manager no doubt you have some
faint glimmering of what's happening to
stolen products counter well you see I
no idea you were such an excellent
public speaker Thompson oh I'm sorry
miss darling i guess i am not feeling
very well this morning i think i can
tell you why styling products and
falling off so badly miss Carla where
would you put the responsibility for
this decline on you on this darlin I
imagine you have arguments to support
that contention we've all been looking
at it for the past 20 minutes the most
convincing argument is right on that
graph naturally thank you
oh right here in April is when Stalin
sales started falling off very clever of
you Lane would you mind waiting until I
finish my spot that's enough lane relax
Willis my apologies for the interruption
thank you now they said sales began to
fall in April but the reason for the
fall was back here in February the
Stalin products have always been thought
of as something of a modern miracle in
the cosmetics trade the farm bill to a
multi-million dollar a year business on
the strength and appeal of one person
Janice darlin from the beginning right
through until februari of this year only
one woman's face was used to advertise
those products your face mist on the
public have come to accept you as a as a
symbol well now after 16 years they see
a different face they don't trust it
they feel cheated the simple fact is
that Stalin cosmetics should have Jenna
Stalin's picture advertising them well
that's about all I got to say that darn
good job of saying after I agree makes a
lot of sense on that score miss starlett
I think I've had enough flattery oh and
one
very convincing argument once your
effective overlooked not even Janice
darlin we mainly glamour girl forever
miss darlin yes Mary Richards with the
reception he says he has a point thank
you huh it's been a very informative get
together and we all for now
I'd like to see you in my office take it
easy hotshot something on your mind miss
Dolan you've done some work on where
Joey have to talk hello very real things
you examine I'd say so because lot hands
on each individual's reaction to the
south what do you mean just that no two
people reacted precisely the same way
one man's meat another important oh that
you think royal jelly candy then
officially funky queen bee said a lot of
still alive I'll accept that as an
affirmative answer supposing a more
powerful form of royal jelly could be
obtained from the Queen waltz for
example I what do you suppose that might
have some rejuvenating effect on the
human beings stay away from wasps if I
were you mr. socially the Queen lost is
on level with a black widow spider
they're both carnivorous they paralyze
the victims and then take that time
devouring them alive they kill their
meats in the same way to strictly on one
side and romance
not exactly interested in a love life at
the Queen womp I want your opinion
possibilities of using enzyme expects
from royal wasp jelly commission if you
want an honest opinion miss tall and of
course I want another stupid and my
advice is forget about it thank you
anytime is gone
hazardous in truck coming you can go in
out there Janice darling enterprise yes
how do you do I'm afraid I won't be able
to give you much time what it is I who
give you the time we started oh yes
plenty time I give you 10 maybe 15 years
I give you I want you to understand one
thing very clearly mr. history expect
absolute proof of what you're clinging
you're less tangible proof not words
such proof you shall get mint app and
more but I think I'd better show in the
laboratory yes
look they look terrible why don't you
put them out of their misery but damn
you watch for proof please be kind
enough to look at proof you watch for
membership thank you
and if your minutes me down you'll see a
miracle you shall not believe oh no
tricks you may look at your life I have
not rich well don't look at me I'm not
changing
my
I see you do not believe one animal so I
bring to I assure you there yes I don't
be sure
while this government my secret have
interest for you here what are you
turned mr. syndrome first I must have a
laboratory look at everything any for my
research if we're successful well I
asked for little percentage but I must
get full credit for my discovery that is
most important to me I have Gordon draw
out the complex oh that's Gondar fire at
me did you be your world good enough for
me you're amazing frankly when I
received your letter I thought you were
just another eccentric there was always
a chance you might not be then you walk
in here and show me nothing short of a
miracle to miracles you say that you'll
accept my word that I won't cheat you
your look I know you're a good woman
even if you do not let other people to
know it however my formula may not be
good for human beings have not tested
yet you will on me oh no no no there
might be danger those are my terms this
decision Jana Stalin will be an
experience though it may take a little
time to prepare a sufficient extract
that we may be more I'll make whatever
Arrangements you may need the equipment
thank you madam now I share your built
all this very close to losing at misters
interest may be working together we can
save Janice darlin enterprise maybe even
make it bigger than ever before oh yes
I'm sure the next three months will see
a rise in darlin cells that will surpass
anything we've dared imagine mr. Zinn
trip
is working on the final stages of the
development that will revolutionize the
cosmetic industry if you have a free
hands in his experiments and will be
answerable to no one but myself at the
moment I cannot divulge the nature of
mr. centers experiments but I can assure
you it will bring worldwide recognition
to Janice darling enterprises
Oh Upsy the granddaddy of all confidence
undertaking a guy like darlin why
doesn't somebody wise her up like you
for instance still what makes you think
Center it really isn't on the level
after all we don't even know what he's
working on it could be very majestic or
as bad as she is Oh women man everytime
exception handsome nor we come up with
you're not getting out of this one so
easily I'd like to know why you think
the truth really hasn't got some fish
well you can call it male intuition if
you like just there's something about
this whole business it doesn't smell
right the private laboratory secret
experiments syndra themself the only
thing missing is a genie with a lamp
that amazing intuition to me I'll let
you buy a dinner buy you dinner without
me your sporting blood but we were going
to toss for the chink oh no you won the
last race on high I'll make a deal with
you dinner is on me if you promise to
keep an eye on what goes on in there
what do you want me to do reedom
inhaling thank you message if you keep
your toes you could do worse oh no mr.
Cooper not you too I've been trying to
tell bright idea that I think synthesis
of phony and a confidence man I was sure
that I wouldn't be worried I think he's
a lot more dangerous quiet I don't
follow you well a confidence man it'd
just be interested in your money the
only damage they can do is your
pocketbook can be fatal
so I said to him I said listen I think
i'm getting sick of this TV every night
I mean you know we can do the same thing
in the life club well good morning Jenna
darling enterprises I got two words for
you drop dead twice urban told me to
tell me dr. Cyclops is on channel nine
tonight to sing a twice already good
morning miss darling in her office now
Miss darlins in confidence would you
like to speak to his secretary oh no no
no just say to his darling I should like
to see her when she is done yes was it
something else mr. Nathan we're going on
what a character a regular to identify
crime in the bow good morning may I see
is ordering please he's a real wedding
wonder what his game is ok you know
Morton thinks he's a crackpot I heard
him telling Cooper so open eyes really
has the execs fired but what that's just
it they don't know so anyway vectorizing
good morning her dining good morning
good morning I couldn't get away any
food is it important mcdonnen do you
remember the big cat assured your last
week no what about well I want you to
look at him come quite different yes
incredible it's a mark a gut you're
young and yet can you realize what that
means you're accepting again their home
life to live over how did you feel I
think perhaps you'll be able to find out
for yourself is starving today today
will be the first injection
you
mr. Gleason of accounting on line three
what is it reason I sent you a memo
misters interest has carte blanche to
order anything it requires make out a
check for the full amount sue Mary can I
talk to miss elaina's still hey listen
Gleason just got a bill for twenty three
hundred dollars
enzyme extracts
yes yes yes we are making progress this
great improvement in the tissue why is
it taking so long it's the third week
you forget my dear there's more to you
than a little kitten now besides the
difference in metabolism why not
increase the dosage wouldn't have step
of the process patience my dear patience
less tread lightly with care
you know I've been extended in the
cockpit solution of the enzymes or they
deal more powerful in the solution i've
been using in your injection oh yes and
i think i think it will the debtor
ferocious is an amount of loss that will
make estrogenic creams and all such
products old-fashioned my dear star will
be world famous bringing you two million
your rights interest are going to be a
few red faces of my advertising
department would i am right well your
own mirror will tell you that i am right
while you look at these five years
younger than you look three weeks ago
would you let me talk to the elevator
bill I think I've got it yeah I'm a
nervous wreck lunch lunch you'll have to
translate from eco I'm not very good at
that technical stuff pseudo technical
mr. Zinn trips a very capable confidence
man from what i read this letter he
claims he can stimulate the processes of
rejuvenation through the use of enzymes
extracted from wasps oh well what are
you to shower gonna do about it right
now I don't know frankly I'm getting
tired of the whole business that woman
still intent on holding back time she's
ready to fall the first pony line she
hears was well at least the fact Mary
Janice Stalin has built her whole life
on youth and beauty now that she's
losing that she's scared to death right
now she's on cloud nine with that quite
possessive but I'd hate to be around
when she comes back down there is well
maybe we can let her down easy I think
we owe her that much now what are we
gonna do we can't just let simpler
filled up her hopes and then not the
props out them under well can you do
such a terrible thing for Jim
it must be something we can do before
it's too late he's got a mighty
convincing argument very impressive to
the layman and the one he's got a record
just as impressive don't wait to find
out dance I might be right here in our
hands hey we're going to keep this
letter for a day ago suppose she finds
out it's called I'm the only one with
access to that does sure though I took
well it's a chance you have to take Mary
I think we can be finish early who knows
where he's going honey come on young
lover
you
what is Italy it is humid ton of course
it's me who did you think it was you
look so different
Maureen hmm I think your food is ready
oh yes miss darling good morning Jenna
sterling he surprises gentlemen Janet
Darwin enterprises is the birth of
stardom the book widespread publicity
campaign in the history of the cosmetic
industry our slogan will be returned to
you with Janet stop when its distance
from arrive there will be a present of
you and all questions regarding the
rejuvenation process will be referred to
him that'll be all for now gentlemen
it's amazing fights one of you may look
far I sent that will be all for now
gentlemen oh not you Mary wait a movie
wonderful it's a miracle a wonderful
incredible miracle what's so worried
about you we really thought you were a
game we even went to plotting out how to
rescue you from mr. desperate silly it
seems ridiculous oh no how old do I look
tell me oh how old do I look Oh 23 maybe
22 that's how old I was when I started
Janice darling enterprises do you
realize with them I'm back where I
started 18 years ago but what it took 18
years to accomplish okay it's like a
dream
years ago a bunch of cracks were
treating people with monkey glands
seemed to work for a while and the
deterioration you think that will happen
to Jan I could just get inside of his
lab run a breakdown on what he's using
mrs. Inca
Ezra
ladies gentleman I don't care what I got
we'll find him all right sooner or later
we find them all time is bible miss now
every hour he's gone it means more than
you can possibly imagine well you
haven't given me very much to go on no
home address no former employer no phone
this is just like starting from scratch
mr. centric wasn't a conventional
employee he didn't go through a regular
person uh-huh you say he came here about
a month ago well how did he come here
miss darlin he just didn't walk in off
the street did he maybe one of the other
drawers so that's what she meant what
who met Charlotte
lett has been taken and you think you
know who took is that right by secretary
instead you got an address handy it
might be better if I busted in on our
cold this way she'll have a chance to
prepare a story I know it I'm doing all
right Larry Janice tanner before I went
to lunch I made a duplicate copy of mr.
Hendricks letter I was going to take
that with the building mr. Cooper at
first but then I thought that the
original would be better have you got
the copy yes it's my dad get that copy
in a Tennyson 946 West seventy-third
Street Manhattan that's right get right
on it Jerry and check back with me as
soon as you can
yeah oh you're sure he's our boy uh-huh
central emergency mm-hmm right well it
looks like we've got him the John Doe
down a central emergency auto accident
there's no identification on anybody was
wearing a lap smock and fills in folks
description Mary got my coat on might
get a cab downstairs head injury general
contusions of the body he's had a severe
injury and there's definite brain damage
just how much we can't tell us yet how
long really don't know it's hard to say
miss talent who's the best man for this
kind of injury well there's several top
specialists get the best I'll take full
responsibility yes mr. I don't know I
think it best we wait it's been three
days since the accident Chad and no sign
of improvement he's still in a coma you
heard what the doctor said he may never
regain consciousness and even if he does
who knows how badly his brain has been
damaged
well I'll give it another 48 hours it
doesn't regain consciousness by then you
can take over the laboratory Oh Janet
incredible right in front of our noses I
can't have used it all I could run a
qualitative unknown
well the dream always goes on a fridge
right in the middle of a good program
I want this to be the biggest
advertising campaign in the history of
cosmetic editor every newspaper magazine
in the country will be flooded with I'm
you look returned to youth with Janice
Dobb excuse me miss starlett what is it
under I think we should be a little
conservative to start cosmetics or one
thing medications another we liable to
run into trouble yes Oh advertising copy
will be cleared through your office too
touchy business you know max is right
miss Darla don't have to take an emotion
I was one thing understood very clearly
now gentleman Janice darlin enterprise
is going to bring the most fantastically
saleable product ever developed by
Martin cosmetics to the public and I
don't intend to be restricted by
timidity while a part of my own staff is
that clear are you all ready just a
little
can I get you something come on I have
some aspirin at my face
I hope you all for now check
you
hi sweetie gee I sure hope they give the
girls working solved first crack about
new stuff matching being 18 again I
guess if it can take 15 years off
darling you can take 10 oh you mean
change places honey this is Maureen
you're talking to yeah well if I were
you I take a double dose then maybe
Irving wouldn't watch television summer
so who says he looks at it I can't
imagine what else he does freak it said
Cooper flaminia mr. board meeting this
morning the best darlings having a fit I
pretty push you know where the starlings
offices suite number one lobby does
Duchess the Flatbush yourself how'd you
like to have this phone wrapped around
you here wise guy that's more like it
sister
sweet number one what is it is there
anything I can do yes it's a business
districts room ready uh-huh the nurse is
fixing the emergency equipment now and
the ambulance is due any minute be sure
to let me know when it arrives Oh Mary
please before you go could you think you
could work that thing Oh that'll be all
thanks
we had a room freshman made over four
used in interest and it's Warren has a
room of joining your so there will be
someone near you at all times when
you're feeling better mr. center there
are a few things I'd like to discuss
we'll do everything we can to make you
comfortable misters interest I couldn't
spend the night here in my office so if
anything develops something important
but I'm sure couldn't make right now the
main thing is to get you back to help
take good care of these marks yes sure
is funny about old coupe this is one day
of work and you're ready to call mr.
Cruz well he's a pretty conscientious
guy I need to be felt sick or something
he's called in we were just having a
little coffee klatch miss Carlin we were
talking about mr. Cooper what about mr.
Cooper well how dismissing the meeting
this morning nobody's been able to reach
him all day I wouldn't worry about that
Scoob has been here long term probably
hear he's been trying to take a day from
seven on there that's what I've been
trying to tell mr. Lane oh by the way
miss tellin how is mr. Zinn trip
Oh fine the few days we'll start the
layout I'm ready when you are what
listen hey Bill don't go getting any
ideas about the boss for me don't be
silly I just wanted to know that I'm an
eager member of the team until she is
looking a lot younger these days and Sam
you think then that would give you any
of those treatments you know break the
launches to
what okay what lie back now just had a
bad dream lie down now this horror was
son look like a nightmare factory tell
mr. green that personnel is his
responsibility have other things to
think about than worrying whether the
night watchman walked off the job what I
just did miss darlin into green fields
that the watchman never left the
building his lunch pail and his raincoat
is still in the basement I don't want to
hear anything more about it she swears
she heard a scream from one of the other
floors that's a pretty cool that she
convinced him he was having a bad dream
oh maybe they both wear that's not funny
anymore Mary there's something going on
in that building I'm going to find out
what it is have a look around Cooper's
lab for one thing after that I don't
know oh it's teddy this is crazy we can
really get in trouble I won't tire
but it is important for it John will be
a memory
Tim Burke you've got to help me
something's happening something's
happening to me I can't control it try
to think the last ten times the extract
you you were experimenting with before
the accident well this is n trips
notebook Mary no come his experiments
with Jan well had a cooper get hold of
it only coop would show up Mary look
Cooper spies don't you get it he's gonna
go out without his pants i'll leave that
fight behind you still fell where in the
building i bet a year's salary on he's
dead and the night watchman mommy you
must let the one more injection one more
you've got to make more
is he asleep I don't know extension if
anybody knows what's behind all this
it's him
her coat purse and everything else is
still in that she wouldn't want without
her purse Oh get out of here I don't
like it core well there's nothing to be
alarmed about mr. Zinn turbine bill Lane
and this is Miss Donovan miss Collins
secretary started the journey what about
a cat must Warner the church must not
there anymore injection it was darlin in
danger terrible danger of farmers take
it easy if you're still pretty weak Mary
didn't get down on the fall
there's no answer Oh miss Donna is that
you Larry we're in the building
something happens there let me talk to
how long will our this is lame why are
you and Mary still in the building by
now a stylist I was sold on to a motel
you must not hold you back to central we
won't let anything happen in his
dominance Oh what's going on down there
Stan your office I'll be right up
keep an eye on them through my my
upstairs oh no 36 stay in touch take it
easy you do not understand miss darling
she's in danger I must warn my father
here you go for Jana when you get up
there call the police you can't get
outside on this bowl
what its next please would you please
call the police was full look I don't
have time
I'm sorry had to do that there's not
hyper in stereo male is this in fact
dancer now gone crazy sure mr. centerthe
how you just relax and take it easy
everything will be alright we'll take
care of them whether or not understand
your do not understand that girls from
the center upstairs jizzing then sugar
must stop at the whores escalate okay so
the cops get here with all your fool you
fool miss darling boy killer and terror
body to shreds Stalin kill Mary miss
Darlene is not that human being in your
longer the infant's of change she'll
destroy the girl as a fiddle was with
the store innings and then the powder
remains then bill found mr. Zinn flips
notebook and Cooper's desk there's no
mistake we've got to call the police
memo now marrying a just getting a
little excited who could possibly want
to hurt mr. cool
Oh
it's not only mr. Cooper whatever
I don't you worry Mary
you
I go later I can't wait am i next step
Liberatore she's going to look up the
stairs
you
Mary