Holly Holly
what time is it now
just 10 minutes later than when you
asked before
do you think you'd get here in time
he'll be here any minute take it easy
John you really have to tell him tonight
yes tonight I feel that it may be my
life's now you know you're going to get
better are they what's become of your
passion for call scientific frames there
is now hurry I believe my uncle's
expecting me I'm Leo Vincey yes I can
see that hi Vince come along in my name
is holly Horace Holly retinoid confounds
your English fog our ship was the whole
day late well thank heavens you're
you're here in time time what's all the
rush your cable said catch fish boat
greatest adventure in the world what's
all the mystery you'll hear all about
that from your uncle does one thing my
cable didn't say John Vince is dying
good lord what of radium poisoning hmm I
haven't seen the old man since I was a
kid he never quite got over aus out of
the family going American why'd he send
for me there's no time to explain that
now every minute counts come along in
I'm sorry I couldn't get here any sooner
never mind that my boy there's no time
for explanations now come closer Holly
did you ever see such a striking
resemblance extraordinaire and already
noticed it look at that potted Holly to
another length
does resemble me at that or should I say
that I resemble him that is your
ancestor of a dozen generations ago
really John Vincey in the 15th century
well I must say we vince's have a way of
looking like each other have no time for
explanations now my boy I'm a man of
science I'm not superstitious if I were
I might imagine that your resemblance to
a man dead nearly 500 years is fates way
of showing me that you will find again
what he discovered what is that sir the
means of overcoming Man's enemy man's
enemy my enemy your enemy the enemy of
all living things careful that is what I
mean leo that is the swinging march of
Man's enemy time bringing death
invisible relentless dead i guess nobody
can stop that who knows a lot of men
have believed that they could sponsor
delenn who searched to the Fountain of
Youth all those fifteen cents alchemists
who try to discover the elixir of life
but what connection is all this with me
or John Vincey over there on the wall
that's what your uncle's going to tell
you how they get me the box listen to me
carefully Leo I haven't time left to
tell you more than once Uncle John I
don't think you should exactly is please
what I'm going to tell you is his secret
handed down in our family from father to
son the first John Vincey there did not
go on his last great adventure alone his
wife left their son in England to go
with him for five years they vanished
from the world then one night in a town
in northern Poland the woman Hill
starving dying collapsed at the door of
an Englishman d he took her in and heard
her ravings of hardship and fantastic
terror that woman was John Vince's widow
before she died she became more coherent
begged for someone to write a letter to
her family in England here is the letter
dictated by that dying woman almost five
centuries ago
here's it is something of a puzzle
doesn't she tell what happened to John
been see ya so he was killed because he
refused to abandon me does it give any
idea where they went to not much
mentions the land of muscular Russia a
or Siberia or Kim chapke all known as
muscular in the 15th century the place
where he was killed was far far north
she escaped with our English 7 they fell
in with some natives who guided them
back across a glacier over what she
calls the shugal barrier their death
struck again Holly reading then a great
Beast sprang on our guides and killed
them all my servant Giles kill the Beast
but died of his grievous wounds so I was
left alone but what about the discovery
you spoke of what they find read on in
this strange land we saw the flame and
he who stands are in comes forth
unharmed to triumph over death but John
Vincey died there why if he found this
this flame because he was murdered but
you are scientists do you really take
all this seriously seriously come my boy
i'll show you how seriously coming to
the laboratory where Holly and I have
done our life work in the beginning I
was as skeptical as you then Holly and I
years ago in this very room began our
efforts to reproduce John Vince's
life-prolonging flame we fail with our
researchers and radioactivity Candace
far enough to make us believe that
certain element really exists an element
to preserve like yes 17 years in this
room there's one other thing we ought to
show him John yeah can you make out the
inscription it means here burns the
flame of life that is the sole
possession Vince's wife had left she
sent it to the son she never saw again
it's also mysterious it doesn't make
hence this thing's gold not an unknown
element to be sure it's gold it's only
the symbol of the flame of life John
dance if I don't you understand I'm
afraid I don't flame destroys life and
thousand volts of electricity will
destroy land but increase the frequency
and you may safely take a million volts
through your body in the radiation from
this unknown element this flame of life
maybe a million degrees hotter than any
fire we know or it may be as cold as ice
that's too much a coal flame did you
ever hear of a man being burned by
x-rays or radium did he feed himself
being burned no no more than I did
myself this flame of life been say is
pure radiation the most intense and fame
like radiation in the whole universe
radiation from what from the unknown
element do you really believe such a
thing exists we no longer believe we
know it exists our experiments prove it
that's right they also proved something
else this element cannot be artificially
produced only nature only God can
produce it but we're in a glacial region
of volcanic character that's largely
guesswork isn't it no not if the family
legend is true and I believe that it is
I believe that John Vincey found that
flame and that it still burns somewhere
remote and mysterious offering eternal
life that's why I send for you
yerevan see the life starts Holly can't
do it alone but he'll go with
Jonathan's he was an explorer it's in
your blood the lover of adventure don't
look upon this as a deathbed wish if you
should try
if you succeed I shan't be but I hope
that somehow I don't know and somehow
share in your triumph and you say here
burns the flame of life
Uncle John John John
let's hook this chap has some tea I'll
take mine with a big reindeer steak yeah
Ghana final Nolan hospitality nothing
the world like it they come in
northern hospitality a come here Castle
scientist a too Margalo well I am below
I thought you were some of those
infernal wandering Kantos can't take any
chances with him don't we know it stayed
with the tribe of them last week
planning to stay here tonight i take it
we hope so come 20 miles today come in
do it sit up full of it there's a big
stew on the stove just about already
plenty to go round better that hey how
about stop up you we eat or don't we
oh that's my daughter Tanya sit down I
guess thank you very much now in gents I
understand you want to do business with
me we heard you had the post-fight the
stuff country we thought you might be
able to help us get some natives to go
on where do you want to go did you ever
hear of the shugal barrier oh yes I've
heard natives talk of it they lost we're
on our way on your way well over the
sugar over here crazy why you will never
get a native to guide you there will Pam
well that ain't the point they're afraid
to go I tell you why because no one who
got over ever came back so far as I know
why didn't he come back what lies beyond
the shoe more of the same I suppose of
course the natives have tales about it
what did I say I never paid much
attention to their foolishness I can
tell you you can what is it the natives
say the beyond the sugar there are
terrible dangers they say ah yes go on
what it's just a sort of legend what is
the legend a long time ago they believe
a woman came out of the country that
lies far beyond the sugar what sort of
woman a white woman she told them that
she had escaped from a strange place
strange and if a man finds the way there
he will never die the catch in that is
he dies before he gets there holy
attract on you you gag too much weight
is there anything in the story about
fire aflame anything you can connect
with this no I don't think so what's
that
Gold ain't it yes it is cold I see well
now you begin to make sense so that's
what lies beyond the sugar no you don't
understand gold isn't what we enter
stood in suppose I could get a few
natives to go on how much could you pay
them anything they asked that's liberal
enough money no object a lads no one can
say old jug more ever let a white man
down I'll get natives to go I'll run the
outfit myself and you needn't pay me a
penny how's that for another what what
about those dangers you talked about
well I'll be frank with you gents I
figure it's worth some risk to be a
partner in what you're after I dare say
that's absurd you can't be a part in
what we're looking for I said a partner
you try to keep me out of this I'll fix
it so that no native in these parts will
come within a thousand miles of you take
it or leave it hannya yeah
I tell you against Doug more you're
crazy you can't take a girl I'll stop
growing about it I'm sick of hearing it
but we don't know what we getting into
what's your idea then leave her here
alone with no one around for 400 miles
except a lot of wandering shan toes we'd
like to get even with me anyhow we want
somebody to cook I dare has anybody
taking the trouble to ask you what what
you want to do I want to go there you
see she wouldn't leave a poor old pas if
there were any place to leave I wouldn't
have come along think you'll be all
right I'm on come along let's go don't
push it coo coo legit
aww
look I may leave their way over the show
go Barry what do you think let's hope so
we followed that cliff for a week
without finding a way through it anyhow
it will be a shelter from the wind and
the dogs can't go on without a rest
hurry up with that food Talia it'll be
ready as soon as I get it sorted out I
wouldn't mind being thought out myself
lil this is no place to camp that Doug
more says the dogs need a rest I don't
like it sitting down here under this
wall of ice it's it's dangerous what's
the matter with you now what's dangerous
hey uh oh all of it you heard that
several times lately in this narrow
place any noise Mike Scott vibrations
which might cause an avalanche merely
shouting my doing Oh pipe down who's
lived in the north for 20 years me or
you lecture yourself out of that
Professor you hurry up with that grub I
still don't like it
mmm smells good taste good too snow
rabbit and the ones i shot I'll fix that
you don't have to help me but I want to
you think having me along with some
useless oh we couldn't get along without
you I wish you really meant that I do
honest of course I can cook that will
not only that but there's another reason
your father if it weren't for you I
couldn't get along with him for a minute
but with you here I find him at least
terrible I know
it isn't very nice to meet you I can't
blame you but I understand he's your
father you see I was brought up by the
Russian sisters interruption makanga
broke up about a year ago and then he
came to me to the trading post he said
he was my father I began to understand
what's all right really but it isn't all
right when we get back from mr. Abati
chip now a girl like you ought to be
treated if I have a daughter like you
don't you think I'd love her and sure
that I do which of course I would I
don't see how you can help loving why
you're yo Incy Wincy Holly Holly what's
up the natives have just come down from
the glacier freaking something about a
white man let's go up and see what it's
about okay oh show us away main goal and
come on
Lord Carey what a beast Polly what is it
unless I'm barn it is a saber-toothed
tiger think of it man that's a new one
on me saber tooth tiger they've been
extinct for thousands of years
everything in all known parts the world
yes but here they must be preserved in
that ice for for four or five hundred
years it has to kympton this place you
look for that man's dressed Holly the
servant a faithful servant who was with
John Vince's wife but the part was they
remember pi Jolie all right he killed
the Great Beast but I to the wounds who
gave him and she escaped alone remember
Holly we found our way the weight of the
plane look at stiffs color chain round
his neck there's a rip canvas bag it's
cold as ice ain't so thick and with this
X don't be a fool you heard what Holly
said about any vibration causing an
avalanche all the professor's is a lot
of things
come on let's get out of here
Oh
hey Bob that make you fool
as new hoop for the others you know that
I know no sedges no food and no way back
and no way forward Holly look this was
covered by the glacier it may lead
through the barrier Tanya
at least this is a shelter from the wind
interesting formation yeah there isn't
more light oh look yet you've had a
tough time
lil de italia come quick
look
there's our way our way we're what are
you talking about don't you understand
that fumaroles volcanic formation one
hour ago ice facial ice and now volcanic
heat I get it what Uncle John talked
about we could never get through of
course we can listen Tanya when I wanted
to leave you at the Trading Post what
did you say what I said I wanted to go
all right come on
south of course
phosphorus to that accounts for the blur
that's the last stop how we rescue him
you
look there's more like yes another
update
just a minute Leo him a chance to serve
their friendly
try your lingo Tanya holiday now Goomba
like thick we greet you my friend
I go down
now go duh thank you now go down
citronelle what does it mean good day or
how are you all greetings or something
of the kind don't judge them by the
looks of us probably a very friendly
people show me your confidence in them
you know what it means Tanya no just an
average the saga cast an so right quick
I
coo coo
you
varna burger hey seemed awfully pleased
to see you stuffy
thank you thank you now go down there
see I was right there just kind
hospitable simple people I'm not sure
they are so simple
they are do realize what they're eating
some sort of melon is a tree melon
something like papaya Warwick what of it
tropical fruit here in the Arctic it
means there's some sort of fertile
country some of you on these caves maybe
what Philippines this doesn't look so
good to me not yet sir the 70 of work
steady on your study what's up now I
told you certainly a welcome
I don't like this mountain it's most
interesting
come with me
but a Scot
he will right now Tara
navika fujiya you guys suck custer pacu
pensa que ha Shamu tape gonna far Malaga
but I do Zico not the car hey I thought
steady nails Leo you are hurt mother
call Holly watch him wait please Oh
gentlemen my friend him very sick no can
walk you get out out let him ride Oh
Holly I'm trying to tell him that Leo
can't walk any further you old idiot
can't you see if yourself he's hurt
better he you already do happy Holi he's
dying no no Tara bad concussion I afraid
do not be afraid he will not die but but
how can you know English I have a wise
teacher who knows all thumbs Total core
was wait wait who who was your teacher
what is this place where are we going
what what's gonna happen you will learn
your faith from Hashem okay
cyberpower
sorry
I don't I don't
I said it Sinclair what is this place
country of course Kenya figure you're
seeing something that nobody ever
dreamed existed aren't you interested
I got off
I
and then
that mountain there scares in a great
dog what is it who's the pulse of Russia
would kept hard in the heart of the
mountain
you
cunhada here I salute them
cigana kacamata see me cum so Noland in
Greece speaking English then the
strangers may understand returning from
the journey on which you sent me they
passed a place where well the peoples of
the caves i weary of those people there
i found these strangers fighting for
their lives the cave people would have
killed them take my order known these
many years there any stranger must be
brought to me unharmed have not their
fathers and their fathers fathers taught
them that my word is law they await your
judgment o Queen they shall not go
unpunished what is your name street
hello o Queen welcome Holly though you
are not here
don't understand why should you what do
you know the mortal dreams immortal
memories
but who I I am yesterday and today and
tomorrow I am solid longing and hope
unfulfilled I am haha whatever she she
who must be obeyed I am I but you speak
my language how is that I learned it
from a countryman of yours long ago what
set you mean have been another
Englishman here in your lifetime boo how
long ago Seether the strangers are
well-treated finale I will decide later
what they should do it the other one the
other a young man wandering a fight I
thought you
it's not enough I should wait and hope
unending years
my Lawrence disobey my commands but give
you leave to think contrary to my will
nearly
you
John Vincey jumping
my my dearest
Tina
mom
lari take him to my chamber before
bidding dawn
Gingka let's pursue
please let's go with
who are you you are his work no I'm
nothing to him but he needs someone he
will not be alone
did you dream i was watching while you
sleep i dreamed of a man dead for
centuries and you called me by his name
dreams running memory the endless flow
of time
who are you
ok
Thea
had I known you were coming you would
have been welcomed like a king
over my friends tix be strong
but Tanya the girl who was here in my
palace
vaguely someone brought us here and you
said
it's all foggy know
are you
you do not remember
how can i I've never seen you before I
was so sure when you came at last you
would remember
I'm so sure you could not forget
I have some enslaved to 10 later you
will hear my judgment on those who dared
attention
wait tell me how is it you speak my
language and still do not understand
I said Tanya what's what's the meaning
of this where'd you get that outfit from
the old man Palala he said I was to put
it on and look as well as I could I
wonder why he cares how you look good
young baby please how is Leo that you
really soon discover for yourself come
if he's well we'll go back to his own
country oh yes why of course he will
then I hope you soon you've been enough
credit
Tanya and Holly glad to see you how are
you it's just what I was gonna ask you
but there's no need listen L I think
I've got some big news for you leo are
you sure you all right how do I look Oh
me to squeeze you and try my strength
I dumped oba lolly about the flesh she
summons you sit near the throne go ahead
King ah come on the Bothan you alone you
to come with me well there's healing not
Stella
there are mob is to be seen today
stranger shares the throne where I am a
scarce approach
I haven't you Holly that you may live
how justices needed out in court
prisoners stand for
you
you otters of darkness how you try my
patience
point out those who reckless enough to
their hands
you
well I'll point out those I'm sure
those two men them
and this
this man I believe he was the leader
that's all before our Romans men
attacked you that's all I'm sure they
will die what they should be put to
death but I don't want that would you
spare
Christian
I'd almost forgotten
remember in the marketplace of Jerusalem
we spoke of a man who taught mercy and
forgiveness man who died but others
might live
the death could be get life
I understand hopefully
Falcon zdorkin up I mean
Paco
comments mp4 displacement I decide I'm
not afraid of you cutter there is an end
my indulgence come away yes hobby go
with I'm the one who spoke out of turn
we don't want these fellows Bridget just
because we had a fight women punish him
if your life but but not fat
do you think I'm cruel for the sake of
cruelty then why do you torture how do
you think I rule it's not by force by
terror my empires of the imagination
still I beg you stop this
cisa block yo yo
thanks that makes me feel a lot better
all of us and don't hold anything
against tonga what is that girl too
nothing I I feel responsible for
may I do you mind if I go now I'd like
to tell her everything's all right go
then
yes the prisoners are they to be turned
back the caves now kill him ohh ohh
kill'em mecanim
when I could kill my fears so easily
he's wicked I tell you that would be too
hard on Tanya she's strange and
wonderful laughter all she didn't go
through it she would have killed him
except for you listen ill I've got it
got what they're going to find out
everything we want to know through you
good idea huh what is there to find out
except how to escape in this horrible
place you should have seen bellotti when
I showed him this all the stuff his
forehead on the floor frightened out of
his wits said it was she secret well why
didn't you tell me all in good time we
don't know the secret yet but i'll wager
pounds depends that you're the one
person who can get it from her lale
please don't go to her don't you worry
Tanya Holly I'm going to get to the
bottom of this if she knows where the
flame burns we are going to find it leo
hard to be kept waiting when one is
weighted support you must have known I'd
come you think blind chance brought you
here I came because of an old story a
woman escaped from this country told of
a strange adventure and died she left
this for her son
this woman was the wife of john d'ampton
John Vincey died five hundred years ago
how can you know his name
linkback far back o my beloved you will
you can another life the far-off
forgotten place this place and my voice
uttering word you've out remember to
endless time think your voice you were
you the same always do always offering
all wanting
you mean we I can't believe I have no
memories i will show you how to look
across the Miss time
that one moment out of all the features
that one instant when I felt myself
beloved
who was that man you do not know that
can't be I dare not believe
you will be
come
do you wonder whose feet worn away this
rock once the stair was new and level
bypassed here day by day see my sandals
are eaten off the salt stone now in a
moment you will remember that otherwise
I I see myself
swept by the tide the pan back tomorrow
centuries ago you were someone else as I
was this man here no no I'm my life and
you can do all through the years I've
learned here where your body weight but
now
you are reborn and my morning is empty
you're coming is the sign of my cookies
forgiveness for what I know why you've
come to call stick the flame of life
even as I the younger so many lies ago I
took the burden of immortality upon my
shoulders and worried through
unbelievable years darpa the loneliness
through which they shun a single like
fixed and unwavering hope of love
that's why I waited waited for a bride
whose passion for life of his fierce of
my own okay Jonathan and I loved you for
one moment you were mine in your turn
for me I had not come alone I'm in my
jealousy I I killed you
again we see me longer than before I
knew you must pretend your love of life
must be stronger than me
now you're here nothing should stand
between us I'm not Jonathan see Oh take
away my eyes that darkness utterly
shuttin him and still my ears would know
this is found of your unfuckable voice I
could only remember if you forgot me
and that woman who held you in spite of
me you've forgotten her as well yes I've
forgotten she wasn't beautiful she had
no wisdom such as mine it could never
quite leave
I have forgotten everything with you
Grayson no not now then we too are made
of different place until yours I am
cannoli
today in the whole Kings the priest
makes sacrifice and gratitude for my
enduring youth then you shall come with
me and share like
sale that's a lil what did you find out
I've seen John Vincey what I tell you I
saw him now be reasonable jaundice has
been dead for four five hundred years I
I tell you I I throwing I again Holly it
was I myself I won big at a time you
mean a mummified body it looked like you
no no Holly I saw myself lying there are
you trying to make me believe in
reincarnation rats you knew before that
you were the image of Jonathan see we
both knew that she has been waiting for
me to come back she says I am John
Vincey leo don't listen to her let's get
away while his time golly she is going
to show me the flame what do you hear
that Tanya but why didn't you say so in
the first place when
when do we go you are not to see it but
you said I said she promised me the
secret well then I see only you yes ah
you can't stay here you'll go back the
way we came you and Tanya as soon as the
temple ceremony is over you'll be
protected then I go to the flame clear
don't lose your head use it I haven't
lost my head I found memories you can't
even imagine I've seen strangeness
Beauty power yes immortality and I can
share it but only I those are her turns
what man would say no be fair very well
I'll take Tonya back with me but let me
tell you one thing leo you're a fool and
you die your father like your ancestor
John Vincey
I'm sorry don't think of me think of
yourself I am thinking of myself to live
forever it's it's what all men have
dreamed up what's the years it will be a
thousand years if you're going on being
cruel and selfish he's a thousand years
of that any better than 70 but people
would change broker has she grown good
yes did she let John Vincey escape would
she let you escape this it was me
Tanya
you're not tempted as I am think of it
never the grow never to feel age I can't
give it
you will live here miss this tune who
was young with health it will never know
where age no grief that isn't the kind
of love on you what is it you want
just two people to live together and run
each other to laugh at little phrases
and sometimes cry of the big ones to
shame whatever comes along to grow old
together then someday when one is gone
to hope to be together again
that isn't much to offer is it compared
to kingdoms and power and glory that
will never change
hey Lindsey Hashem otep sends me to tell
you that the festive of the sacred well
will begin at the setting of the Sun you
and Holly will be guided to the Hall of
kings and Tonya really may not come no
woman may view the ceremony at the well
with the maidens of the temple I don't
want to see any more ceremonies I'm
going to talk to Holly again
Tanya
Jackie
I'm sorry I they wouldn't let me pass
and I had to see you well you you are
sending us away you will return your own
yes I know Leo told us
but please
what is it you want black layer moves
sendhil away to send him away are you
mad please he came here following a
dream a dream men are followed since the
first son's voice fathered her he'll own
horn men is realized that me and you
asked me to send him away
to send him back to you and your little
mortal love no no even if he never loves
me I have to make you understand it's
not for myself I'm fitting for him love
to you
but can you were the world you live in
offering will last longer than a
miserable human life after the festival
and hold kids
will be slaves waiting without a wall
guide you in safety the world
go if you see on my anger
then if you won't send them back well
when you let me stay here where I can
see him sometimes what harm can that do
what can it take away from you you will
have everything he will have him I shall
have nothing if you take away being near
him I'm taking nothing away from you
that was ever yours he has been mine
since my last handed talking with you
why are you afraid of me fraid
you aren't and now I see why because I'm
human and you are not because I'm young
and you know love belongs to the young
your magic makes you seem young but in
your heart your old old you were young
once like me but now you're old and it's
too late for love forever you will never
love you I know that now keep him here
makeup came over your slaves and savages
love you
she came here from his arms
the sacrifice within the hour in the
whole of kingdoms
you shall sit beside you on the throne
and watch her die
did not know who can be blamed if she
wanders away an unconfined st. mango
search show concern for his sorrow all
the while knowing that he watched her
die and she can avail sorry
so that's got unique stock or Donna
honey real McCoy photo boy a job that
sauna what are they doing she's come on
sensors an offering plate foolishly to
destroy him too if you could heal he
knew your fate but could we do let him
try to save you it will be set upon by
soldiers at please it would die with you
but you shall not know
you
ha gustado humor
by me
you
the happy festival for Gore happiest of
all for me
that girl they're bringing in what does
she do carey school of my gratitude the
gift enduring life carries today how you
should see
not death
is this a human sacrifice is the
immemorial custom of the people of Cole
is that can't be
who is that girl
who is it the Tanya
it's tanya
you
you found my temple became the dangerous
way
here's what you thought so the flame of
life is left from the earth since time
began what does the flame or anything
else matter now I have what no power you
have to give I bought nothing you have
to give
he thinks he loved you now
i do wait wait for what for you to grow
old until then you will be cared for as
my stairs then he he would bathe in the
plane with his eyes he will grow old
withered ugly and it lasts repeal
details from you should be standing by
sad unchanged and if I won't go in the
flame
you have no choice if you refuse the
girl shall down you mean if I refuse to
go into flame you'll have a kill oh they
are and I know I'll always love you Tony
no no trust me believe in my love I'm
ready normally oh it's a trick how do
you know you won't be burned alive I
stand in the plane and come fro unharmed
then will you follow I will
don't think you can go and punish
forever somewhere there's a power that
won't let such wickedness and cruel they
go on your hair will fight your eyes
will lose their practice your cheeks
will wrinkle your limbs will wither and
I didn't I the years and lock
I call upon the plain most are the most
with preserver of life of youth and
beauty
you
your eyes with their brightest
your cheeks were rigged
your limbs will wither
you
I decide the year laughs at time
how do you believe I spoke the truth I
love
I can see you clearly eyes play my list
happened eight years
God pity on a shame
you
remember long ago the garden in the Sun
ok
did she kind of dark
audience leaves it would have guide you
the gold someone will be safe
she told me
greatest secret in the world we were
turning our expert
she's taken to the ground from withered
creature incredibly Oh and so she died
terribly and fitter food even as her
lips look maternal I but though she was
dead the power of her golden symbol
reach out and held a safe and so after
incredible adventures we escaped to the
outer world and thus we lived through
called the story in this manner suit it
seems as though it couldn't have
happened why no one could believe it
unless had been there with us now that
was safe in this friendly world do you
know I feel sorry for her we never shall
now what well it did happen I sometimes
think that her bathing in the flame a
second time was an over exposure to that
terrifically powerful unknown element
and sometimes I think the search such a
human immortality was never meant to be
and some greater power than she reached
out to destroy her after all Holly
perhaps there is no real flame of life I
think the news what yes right here yeah
in this fireplace the flame in any
fireplace in any home where two people
live and love each other