I'm looking for a place where the dogs
don't by killing don't cry and
everything always goes just right
maybe it's just over at you
you
maybe this go let the end of this ring
and maybe is just a maybe is just over
you offer him maybe
Mavis go let the end of this dream
and maybe and maybe it ain't I'm
striving for 10
well it's an always
and all night long that girl is always
my sure me we don't maybe it's so are
you down the line
neighbors go let the end of history
maybe is speed
and maybe it ain't
you
maybe but I don't want to go in there
why not well what if there's bug I don't
care if it smells and there's bugs
running around if we're getting back in
that car again tonight you're driving
okay well look
hey do it hey I'm sorry I'm sorry take
it easy take it easy take it easy our
map and get I'm out of the car okay it
was just an honest little mistake I got
into the wrong car looks exactly like my
car let's look I said I was sorry okay
all right college boy get into you lady
I swear I'll kill you now don't think I
mean don't even think it move yeah yeah
a sound explodes in my head I want my
mother's arms to make me safe
oh come here jackpot come on out come on
my my don't you look pretty my dogs
didn't even bark at you cuz I know
you're a weaselly piece of shit now what
do you have for me it's in the trunk get
out of the car look I got Nikki I got
your TV a beautiful TV and the car trunk
is full of stuff didn't have any trouble
getting this car did you oh no trouble
slew no trouble I promise not went real
smooth black and white TV shit I mean I
thought it was called the sign said free
color TV in every room what the fuck am
I supposed to watch on black and white
dragnet okay I'll take it back to the
Harmony motel I own the fucking hotel
okay I got you a Lincoln Continental you
didn't know net and I got a real nice
present for Pearl a nice little
overnight case with the perfumes and
women's under apparel Oh Lord look what
weasel brought me baby oh can I keep him
please can I go slow you gotta believe
me man I mean I didn't know nothing
about no baby
thank you lock up hey no trouble slew no
trouble stealing the car just a pile the
junk black-and-white TV set and a
fucking kid well I got an idea first I'm
gonna fucking kill you they're not gonna
burn the black-and-white TV set and then
I'm gonna feed the kid to the Hogs
sounds good to me no this is my baby I'm
not going to let you do that you won't
let me come on give me baby pearl I want
her to baby come on perv you know just
be all right don't you give me the baby
you lay one hand on this time sue honey
and leaving you I mean I knew it
you started this oh where in the hell do
you think you're going asshole I'm going
harmony the fuck you are you've got work
to do across the border I want Charlie
pee out here tomorrow and I want you to
start walking walk want me to walk
you're lucky you're not fucking dead now
get moving now ok ok ok I'm walk it what
seat walk me walk walk it now
you
yummy sunny yellow sun sun Oh Sonny Boy
Roman loves you so much that's like it
yeah right here come on baby come on
come on Pearl Juliet baby get up same
spirit that fine kid is mine
hi Paul hi Sue I hope I'm not
interrupting the rag on your head won't
get you the clan I'm here on business
shit i heard you had a car for me to
dispose it shit we're going blue
back off whoo whoo
oh my does it work I like that I really
like that it's not for sale but she is
tell weasel I want to paint it black I
want new plates are and i've owned it
across the state line by friday lied
you're the boss blue so honey have you
offered our guests to drink get off my
back pearl when's the last time you
leave by pearl what have you there I
didn't know my beautiful pearl blossom
was with child I've been keeping it a
secret shame of being an unwed mother is
just too much to bear I ought to kill
you lock the kid oh you hey slow so come
on take it easy you're missing one of
the biggest joys of life I only meant
that I only meant that I think you make
a wonderful father college boy right
grabs me by the lapels right he's acting
real tough so I grabbed my gun out from
under warr he's not looking in and I
pull that to his face I click and I say
okay son of a bitch get into the move
get get get get get get get get I go
into the room I close the door BAM I get
him Sam right here see right here right
between the eyes guy thought he was
tough he was nothing hey older done I'll
weasel oh look who's here his doc bender
how you doing not put any more monkey
parts and unsuspecting patients the doc
here is famous slu told me you had your
picture on the front page folks at the
goddamn New York Times yourself hey I'm
kind of sure you don't go talking down
to one of lose men slough doesn't hire
man what it's in your pants pocket what
your piston my god damn pistol is in my
coat pocket man me and smooth on this
goddamn town me and slew man has almost
brothers I miss god damn right hand man
man be putting flowers on Your Grave doc
oh ho hold it just a minute that I see
no reason to tell Slough about the good
doctors indiscretion let me give you a
piece of advice because i like it doc in
harmony you're allowed one mistake only
one rule is the citizenship exactly
bitch do you think I'm right there at
your door there's so much more waiting
for you
madigan here hello
hello flu can you hear me 27 TV sets two
refrigerators want me to do making model
on all of these and one baby boy he's
not for sale one baby boy retail value
10,000 bucks get rid of them pearl get
back here and has no decency decency
what's okay well we got company stirred
up a little dust in you afternoon
officer you uh lost your way honey nope
I believe I'm in the right place oh
lordy somebody must be in trouble I'm
looking for three individuals must have
taken the wrong turn they did I'm told
he took a shortcut through harmony maybe
you ought to talk to sheriff Madigan I
thought I'd go straight to the top you
sure you want to do that they were
traveling with a six month old child how
old's your baby miss that ain't her kid
she's just sitting with him pearl he'll
be gone by nightfall mind if I look
around I wouldn't dream interfering with
the law pearl take this boy around will
you its inventory day
ya wouldn't happen to have a receipt for
all this stuff no we picked it all up it
of swap me seem is suing near kind of
junk collectors I wouldn't call that
baby their junk ma'am find anything yet
now sweet hair drink from me drink from
your mommy Oh stay away from my house
will get away from me slew you get away
from this baby my kids stay away from me
boob chilly help please leave my son
the ground trembles his hands hold me
tight a warm red liquid covers us both
now I am his
where the dogs don't fight and children
don't cry and everything always goes
just right and brothers doing fine maybe
it's just over that hill maybe it ain't
maybe there's gold at the end of this
ring and maybe it's just a maybe it
ain't Oh cake time later for the king
mask time
it's okay for me go flew home thank you
I got something special for the kid make
a little room greedy little bastard like
father like son father cut loose my
tongue he praised it for my birthday a
gift of silence this'll make you purr
Carl she put my voice in your freezer
for safekeeping you've been aight sweet
cake god damn pearl look at him hmm Jed
métier
you
father teaches me games of strength and
love I taste the dirt from the ground
till the rope across my back and my
mother's warm breasts holding me close
you
this game makes me stronger giving me a
scan of farmer so hard that even fire
can't harm me
you
yes we nice Lou says you're almost a man
so mom take good care of you gonna be so
handsome yes sweetheart I heard some
sounds coming from over here are you
experimenting with something uh it must
be close to feeding time flew Sonny Boy
daddy's got a surprise for you little
bastards hungry feed him a chicken
you're the boss my watch
give it back I wanted that I'll get even
with you for this cop car
so we got trouble could be big sure will
be turned down a cold rainy what kind of
trouble it's the mayor it's getting
greedy wants more than his share duh
that's something about cornering matadin
well it don't look good town officials
speaking out against you could give the
people ideas this town's mindless lands
mine nobody better dare give me any
trouble by the way me as your brother
Lloyd me yeah yes shame
why don't you just relax
go without Slough in his enterprises we
wouldn't have a time but man if the town
joined forces we understand but folks
seem content the leap things as is the
help who's there
holy shit who are you come on speak up
break it injuries gets a lot around
these parts come on move it I said
you
can this beat me this pitiful thing I
see trapped in this mirror
that'll teach you to double-cross me you
bastard it'll rot your brain papas come
to take you home get did good real good
I'll put it on put it on
did you
these bars are stronger than bones
colder than the flesh now I have tasted
the blood of a man I have pleased my
father sounds like Jesus you cry huh
sweat smells like female teardrops
anybody see what happened looks like a
mountain lion got him Oh worse looks
like Mara won't be having a Christian
burial well that's a damn shame you sure
it was a very grave situation sir why I
sure do hope our fine citizens of
harmony walk softly yes I sure do hope
so otherwise the consequences are rub
how shall I put it Dyer
yeah extremely dire listen don't you boy
to go eating everything in sight I
promised I'd bring the leftovers to my
son sunny boys on a diet or slow down I
want him hungry but he yes pearl don't
cross me man it's heartless boys and
trainers on his own money is gonna be a
champion I want a mean lean and hungry
pearl this is delicious I mean there is
nothing like good home cooking bad boys
kids come of age it's time to move leave
harmony weasel weasel time is not
blessed you with wisdom when a man
reaches a certain age its type of change
no more petty theft no more two-bit
refrigerators fuck it we're going in for
the big bucks when going into the art
world art world why not we drive across
the state line in the California we got
Bel Air Beverly Hills we got a kid who
can eat his way right through their
golden gates and we got this town to
protect this Slough we get us a whole
mess of bel-air shit yeah what are we
gonna do with it steal from one and sell
it to the other plano fingerprints on
that high class shit
class lacks whoo fifth time few practice
runs Charlie p and then you deal with a
shark I always knew I'd prosper in the
artistic community you're truly a man of
vision a vision mommy love you you know
hi want an ice cream are you doing in
here
yeah fuck it bye
hate it here
don't ya
no I'm gonna get out of here one day go
to LA
ah
you
this fuckin suburbia gives me the creeps
got no taste look at that
can i watch slim you know the kid work
solo yeah well one can only hope is neat
and tidy about this experiment I do have
an i do have a scream of stomach real
nice church got their father thank you
you're welcome to come in we're here on
business no time for prey well I'll be
in the rectory in case you change your
mind
father son Holy Ghost hahaha we're here
business side boy is what I want you to
do
Getty backtalk my son
what are you doing come down boy come on
who did that to you
stop it you think he's right in the head
hmm Sonny Boy what the fuck is wrong
with you haven't you heard slew our
weasels take him to reading books not
well I figured I ought to since we're
all artists now you know what's an art
book got to do with my kid well lots of
them was off in their heads and one I'm
meme chopped 20 so I figured that maybe
Sonny Sonny boys my kid I made him what
he is any no fucking painter
did
there's something flowing in me now
taste I've never had
blood of a good man
you know why you heard one of the
prospectors and harmony stumbled across
some gold nuggets now I was thinking of
that why of yours is my fucking town the
people alone yes I'm talking about a
hermit some lonely old prospector nobody
will ever miss my Sonny Boy could happen
for dessert boys got a good appetite I
got this whole town under my son one
mysterious killer and you'll see how
nervous you old age is making you
cautious you're the boss
I'll think is such a good idea hey
freeze wait a minute wait a minute hey
you've lost it did she swore Aviv
adventure I never cross flew before or
not we're simply going to borrow the
creature that's all anyway once and airy
don't you my little bit this isn't right
why have they come for me when father is
away
I just burns too many thoughts fill my
head I don't know what's right anymore
good boy Sonny Boy don't give me the
boat stop the gold Danny Boy give me the
gold come on give me minute god damn it
Charlie p needs an attitude adjuster
that's for the moon just wants to play
oh I'll play with him come on sure cool
come on Shawn baby that's it come on
babe we'll get you this time I'm gonna
get you distance right here it's right
here god damn Charlie Strong Hey look
dominica my goddamn phone shit boy you
got a set of choppers go quick damn boy
look at that got my goddamn some more
carrots let's just call it it okay it
grabs my tongue man Pam takes it off
just clean as a goddamn whistle just
like that for us you gonna let me have a
look at what let you put a monkey dick
on it
I don't think I'm gonna be the one
having the funeral doc sound me there's
just a little bit of screaming out on
the edge of harmony almost like somebody
getting themselves killed you should
call your friend the sheriff why tell us
you thinking like your dick longer
drinks are on me since when do you pan
for gold since the same thing that's
right we took sluice secret weapon out
for little gold all right so your whip
my ass a real woman should be seen and
not heard what did you do hold up some
tourists huh what's new about that lady
we don't need a rifle yeah guns are
passe that's right now on we use secret
weapon tell you one thing ain't no
goddamn
their eyes pierced deep into me hurting
me
my dad different from all
you wouldn't turn on his own people
what the fuck get up your little shit
when you get two children a boy where
did one the holy man I ask a question
who see this he's been outside
sweetheart he's at that age you can't
expect to keep a young man all the time
hey get my clothes Mitch
ah
you
Oh
any boy leave her the fuck alone
somebody cut his tongue out you know
that well maybe he did it eating some
glass or something and it's obvious it
doesn't take good care of it alone max
you know this one's out of all our hands
you finished it just patch him up I'll
notify flu I let my staff out the back
way
you don't understand a word I'm saying
duty
shut up here why did he run away so much
just don't understand children maybe we
ought to steal the kid of wife whatever
you say sweet huh as long as my baby
comes back who cut your tongue and you
read right
they want you blood
he's in no condition to be moved
who's there
now you get the hell i hear you son of a
bitch
rania master
you
what do you want
hey thirsty huh okay
hey have some
huh
it's good
cookies you like cookies huh sugar sugar
is good
having a good time huh yeah me too I
like tea time company dropping in on me
it's nice cozy
oh that's nice you don't want to give
this to me give me that now take it easy
that's right boy that's a good boy come
on give it to me give it to me good boy
you son of a bitch
there he is
the tongs up in arms weasel and I will
attempt to save the child Saturday on
whoever wins my friend
how much pain can I stand
how much hate you should leave me alone
yeah the monster it's a blood bag do
something sure you are the monsters you
let it happen now you good people are
gonna have to pay the price
you
so hard dummy
it's like this
see
ok
go ahead fight
slow
you don't know nothing do you
you know you never talk to me why
why
are you shy
that's okay you know I get like that
sometimes too believe it or not
you like me tell you
scary huh
get on listen you I raised you like I
was raised what have I got a wider
fucking pervert no water it's time to
sober up i've read so good people upon
me what the sheriff oakshire do love you
Sheriff they sure do
how about some police protection yeah
now come on folks just take it easy
you've got some monster yet he wants us
to take it easy there ain't no monster I
say we can't wait any longer I say we
hunt that thing down and kill it tonight
what do you say Danny wait for me look
he's just scared oh shut up rose you're
not man enough to do the job Sheriff
stop will you wait a minute can't this
this isn't some animal you're hunting
it's a human being go home doc yeah two
dogs and cats talk damn about harmony am
i right yeah and I'll help you find uh
the monster he's lying I'm not lying
look see there I'll tell you everything
you want to know about him cuz I know it
I mean I knew him when he was like a
little baby okay in her I watched him
grow up and become a man
get up you son of a bitch get up you
almost got your father in the shitload
of trouble what do you think I'm running
here a stud farm you can't say pearl I
didn't raise you will bullshit come on
boy
Oh
get out
come on get the ambition it's in the
pyramid
oh it sir you guys are gonna sneak in
there and dirt guys and just burn the
whole thing down what are you saying I'd
be a real tragedy if that house were to
burn without saving some of its
furnishings you're crazy huh
I was always a bit too fond of trinkets
fire Flula try to burn us out we're
gonna Bernadette we either I don't want
to die tuck it down get your ass
together come on Oh God Debbie you tell
Nick never could hit for shit I guard
the front door
here's mom will take care of you what
are you something's gotta get out of
here so we got crazy gonna die in here
come on come on Sonny Sonny we gotta get
out of here we gotta get out
you
where are they
they're gone
max not even a hint I'm out of practice
willing to go for it
ok and now all we need is a monkey well
kids good luck to both of us
you
sorry you can make it in life without a
voice want to make that clear I mean
it's easier with one but it's not
absolutely necessary so open open
so whatever happens
well we're trying our best
hmm
hey
huh all right come on come on Sonny easy
easy easy okay come on Sonny come on
easy take it easy sorry hey kitty honey
take it easy try to get Oh
No
here's the next bend couldn't leave well
enough alone lighten up willya this is
supposed to be a celebration for me
operations a success it is i'm still a
drunk and he's
mentally then shoots everybody's crazy
max his just shows more when I got us a
case of the postoperative blues Oh run
some tests anuman keep mine the wraps
you
I have words now but what good are they
the pain doesn't stop and I wonder
Who am I now i'm looking for a play
where the dog don't fight human don't
cry and everything always goes right
maybe it's just over that you
maybe a day
may let us go let the end of this ring
maybe it ain't I'm searching for a lane
well man can stand
without sucker
someplace when no one else is a rather
be someplace else
I whatever
maybe just over you follow him
Merrill's go let the industry
and maybe
and maybe eating
I'm striving for a time
well as it always
all my lawmakers all the time
sure
why
maybe so are you down
neighbors go let the end
I'm
maybe is
and maybe you're a
and maybe
you