teenage mom station the wallet home the
cost on the stair the vampires bite
everywhere and if there's a full moon
tonight
spiders people crawl boys and goons
having a ball Frankenstein's right click
and even the mummy are sure to end up in
somebody's of me
take a fresh vote some toadstools and
weeds and out of all round the young
ones she breeds makes in seven legs from
the paint legged piece and then the
heroes set for a cannibal feast
you
sit around a fire with this couple
groove of being in a werewolf on each
side of you this cannibal orgy is
strange to behold and the lattice story
ever told
the mary syndrome so called because it's
only known occurrence is among the
descendants of one Ebenezer Mary a
progressive age regression beginning
about the tenth year and continuing
steadily throughout the victims lifetime
it is believed that eventually the
victim of the Mary syndrome may even
regress beyond the prenatal level
reverting to a pre human condition of
savagery and cannibalism many
authorities do not accept the existence
the very syndrome incredible but true
nevertheless I know only too well of
course there's no Mary syndrome anymore
it was extinguished forever from the
human race that fateful day 10 years ago
Oh
holy
can you send me where the very house and
I'm from the marrow there is any such
place we don't know anything about it
Oh
you
in a better home and better all please
say yes somebody phone
hello and down
Oh
hello cut cut a big fat sun-dried might
spare and now the spider gets to give
this bug a big thing
Virginia Virginia are you crazy now look
what you've done
Elizabeth Virginia
Elizabeth tilia Elizabeth
Elizabeth Bruno Virginia hurt somebody
real bad you are a hater Elizabeth how
many times have I told you it's not nice
to hate
Oh
one beautiful
delivery I trusted you I left you in
charge not my fault I didn't do it she
did she was playing spider
no I like you a job Virginia within you
you come here right now
we're home now we're all now
Virginia now you stay right there he's
gonna sit down you to Allah
not children I want to tell you
something and I want you to listen very
very carefully you remember last time
when those two children climbed over the
wall and Virginia almost caught them in
our spider web will that got people to
wondering about us and that's bad your
daddy wouldn't like that Virginia I
can't be here all the time you know that
I have to take Ralph into the city to
the doctor once in a while in Virginia
you were supposed to mind your sister
you are not supposed to play spider
anymore now you never never can play
spider gift oh wow what have you got
there something that man well give it to
me that's it
thank you
this is from a Lloyd
oh lord what is the boom something bad
isn't it how many times do I have to
tell you just because something isn't
good doesn't mean it's bad must be
something very bad nothing is very bad
he's going to come here and bring other
people
daddy wouldn't like that what are the
people they want to make they want to
become your legal guardian as the only
other known surviving heirs of the
estate of titus w mary isn't that daddy
yeah on the 14th
the days are hoarding
children
we've got to keep some secrets today
you
you what do you want bad for hurry up I
want to watch something me here not to
post I'm continental net
you
I'm coming in Twitter and Martha I'm
coming uncle Ned
well Emily I mean I wish it kind of
bigger if you don't like my driving
review free to take a trolley now wait
just a minute this was not my idea I've
never heard of a merry family what is
that there are cousins darling it's
behold just unique all right I mean you
know all right but remember that it was
not my idea okay of course not darling
you don't have ideas baby teacher
brothers
what in the world makes you think this
is the right Road got to be
oh there you see
so this is it I don't see any sign of
what's his name the lawyer obviously he
hasn't arrived as yet the caretaker he
probably went to meet him in a horse and
buggy
I did well go on up they'll be along any
minute why don't we let somatic ate it
chicken well I just don't like it you
know just right for barging in on nobody
the chewbacca sue I just remember we're
trying to avoid that expense it's
possible well
I'll leave that up to you
what happened you saw goes right don't
be funny it was it it was awful it is a
baboon well let's not have a complete
double dot fit
what's going on here why are we stopped
they're blasting up a headset one last
Easter with a new highway way not I
suppose yes sir they won't be long sir
mr. Hawkin painted locker mr. Brunelle
for folks Peter brutal just plain Bruno
sir come on buddy let's get this car out
of here
oh I do this off so nice to see you here
and the young miss ya I fucker all right
good to see in a boy be this is my sexy
miss more ha get the rest of the truck
let's go in and take a look at the place
oh yes I I've been away from the
children too long already he you just
follow me and I'll show you where to
park your machine I bet if I may ask a
favor please please treat the children
tactfully you see they're not accustomed
to changes and they might act wild if is
encouraged
now ladies this is your auntie Emily and
your uncle theatre Elizabeth and
Virginia there's two pretty names for
two such pretty young ladies this is mr.
and yeah Wow where's Ralph well Virginia
Wow
ah he's all right emily is it too big
kid yes it's like you say sir he's just
a big kid nothing here Bruno you don't
see me realize just how serious all this
is now these children are obviously in
need of qualified professional care when
you say so there's a great dealing what
you say sir but I gave their father
solemn oath that I'd never allow their
unfortunate nality to become the object
of public scrutiny nonsense today's when
we hit our insane behind walls of shame
went out with without old car of yours
they're talking about us for tenure fine
now but mr. shocker and off to a dying
man that can't be taken lightly Bruno
what do you mean by melody I mean
watching backward kids is it well no
it's in it it's more than a retardation
it's sort of a regression a progressive
deterioration of the mental faculty
rotting of the brain so to speak it
begins in late childhood and progresses
rapidly are ultimately resulting in
physical deformity rather like the last
stages of Croesus really that bad if the
merry family or at least this branch of
them have been afflicted for generations
and I'm sorry to say sir I I think this
is the last generation on a shame
photo you mean all three of these yes
sir the unfortunate result of inbreeding
I never mind that now Bruno we can go
into all that at the proper time God
said yet I would like to know the
whereabouts of certain other members of
the merry family the two sisters of
titus w mary and brother named i believe
medric Mary if lie alive well you might
say so sir come on Bruno don't beat
around the bush are they around or not
they're talking about Uncle Ned I know
well it became necessary to put them in
a a a more private sort of an
institution my good man are you saying
that you that the family chauffeur has
been in sole charge of this entire
estate and these minor children I never
thought of it that way sir you see I
promised the math yeah yeah yeah we know
all about that listen chakra it's been a
long trip I'd like to get cleaned up and
get off my feet for a while we can go
through this out to dinner you know yes
this dinner time matter of fact bruno we
intend to spend the night oh no sir
that's quite impossible why why we're
not prepared for guests it seems to be a
difference of opinion as to who is the
guest and who the host here you do have
food in the house don't you yes sir you
see our diet is very up there hey but I
suppose we could find something
yes that I suppose we could haha
I smell a bug
black history
proud of you Virginia you're doing so
well Ralph is ready bring out oh thank
you Elizabeth brain right down but if
there's no doubt in my mind and we have
here an absolutely clear cut prima facie
open-and-shut case great now all I was
in their worth in dollars and cents well
that's a little difficult to tell at
this juncture perhaps with an audit that
this is more skinny scheduled be alright
hey mr. shoppers of course this is only
the visible part of the iceberg so to
speak with more information we can
project the curve hey I route every way
look at Ralph you get all dressed up for
it we had to be cute
ladies and gents good this
Oh laughs thank you were jigna that was
very good Virginia so you go right ahead
but hurry up hurry up I willing I'm
remiss force oh yes I'm Spanish shall we
that some of that there we are just sit
wherever you like whoo-hoo we're not
very formal here at that very hot we
haven't had guests in a long time no
it's been a long long time i might add
it it's a great pleasure you can sit
down now rau
Oh
when a friend one affair
Barney came back naughty venison you
didn't tell me Virginia we're waiting
for you
set your charity please
watch watch well that's rabbit obviously
not bad Bruno looks done to a turn thank
you sir I hope you enjoy it you know
we're very fortunate to have leaked
forget you see we're vegetarian
vegetarian it's there we don't eat that
thing good lord man why on her master
don't say that you made a promise there
was no idle whim I assure you the master
knew of the grave danger the dangers yes
Bruno what is that supposed to mean well
the last two believed he should know
that the eating of flesh would hasten
the progress of their condition now I've
heard everything wait a minute Bruno now
you may like that old story about the
lion cub who's actually tame is how he
gets his first taste of fresh meat right
I'm afraid it's even more serious than
that sir
well whatever that is a rabbit or what
ever I pass looks good to me hey I'll
car haha thank you sir Kelly on oh and I
must tell you all you are Ralph here to
fight for providing it all right good
for you out hey I'll have something else
thank you we call these ah a rare treat
our favorite dish we call it the souffle
fungi what mushroom shocking oh it's
mushroom a real staple they grow
profusely on the ground and did Ralph
own no no Virginia provided these you
see she has an uncanny knack for picking
only the non poisonous one the whites
locker-less that arm to stop
Thank You uncle pier Thank You Uncle
Peter a sloppy you certainly can't say
that up the light on this how if you
don't feel up to the heavier fair
perhaps you'd like to try some of our
fresh garden green yeah I might try to
sell it
hey
allow me this thing isn't dressed
isn't Ralph a vegetarian too oh yes but
Ralph's allowed to eat anything that he
kept every this is very good you know
what your mission as I told you our diet
is very upset but it's most help that's
great I think everybody ought to eat
like that oh we have our delicacies too
but they're not in season right now oh
no no sir I you wouldn't want any of
that oh my god
or to think about spending the night now
Emily you couldn't drag me away mate
good show my dear I'm with you oh it's
like I told you sir if there's nothing
more to say Bruno not now let's make
things easy on yourself we want to be
fair the sisters can move in together
and you and them well well we might do
that oh no no it's quite impossible it's
too dangerous hey you see this is an old
building is the wood is rotten you did
you'd have to know your way about in the
dark nonsense the next thing you'll tell
us it's haunted oh oh no nothing like
that he means they're vampires oh yes
and we're wolves are you horror film fan
miss Morris oh yes I love it Dracula
Frankenstein and the mummy of The Mummy
I love the money the way he walks that's
great that's great oh and the Wolfman
there's going to be a full moon tonight
you
Oh
uh mr. shocker I mean if you don't need
me anymore tonight I could just as well
stay down there's an end in the village
and as I see it there are only two rooms
anyway it Peter if you took the car do
you think you could find lodgings in
this morn yeah i saw a motel coming in
here fine fine good idea just be sure
you have her back on time young man busy
day ahead you know for work Thank You
mr. house welcome children some of our
guests are going to stay the night would
you come help me prepare the room yes
Bruno got it
he spiders
we have lots of spiders
do you like spiders mr. house oh sure
yeah I love spiders would you like to my
spider with me Virginia sure I'll play
spider with you maybe tomorrow i'm sorry
mr. how that we couldn't accommodate
everyone but but i'll be looking forward
to seeing you tomorrow me too Bruno okay
thank you very much good night kids
wellness Morris we should be getting an
early start I like that very much mr. al
this is the sony setup I've ever seen
there is something terribly wrong here
and I intend to find out exactly what it
is
say it's a still early miss Morris
perhaps you'd like to have a drink of
that in the village that the limo
mention I like that very much mr. half
oh and maybe a sandwich if you don't
mind
are you going to get back good night I
used to be
and of what you know those people
hey
you're not yourself stay you should they
don't like spiders
I now
that little man looks just like a big
fat fuck definitely
you know what I liked it
really not thanks spider
Beth
coming to tuck you in daddy
nighty night daddy
I'll see here this won't do this is gone
quite far enough thanks
beyond the bounds of rodents
and rotate
I don't know what you people are up to
here but
i'm going to call in the authorities
there are laws right there are proper
procedures
now come right back in the same brutal I
or even have to please don't hate me I
didn't mean to do it she made me do it
she really did when he was fine when he
was gonna tell he was going to tell on
his Bruno yes Elizabeth he was running
down I don't you worry Virginia I'm not
gonna hate you
I knew this was coming from day it's so
soon and you really and truly don't hate
me I promised your daddy I'd never never
hate you it's kiss you gotta hate him
Elizabeth I told you it isn't nice to
hate children I I've got something I
want to tell you I want you to listen
very very carefully a long long time ago
I I promised your daddy that I take care
of you and Ralph forever and an hour and
then came this mr. Schmucker he was a
nasty mean man he wanted to take you
away where Oh Bruno would never see you
again but
you hurt mr. sucker he can't do that now
but soon there'll be more mr. stalkers
and they'll be nastier and meaner than
he was and you won't be able to hurt all
them because there'll be too many of
them they can't take me away from you
Bruno they can't make me go away you
won't let them wear you Bruno I promised
your daddy I wouldn't I knew you
wouldn't I'm not afraid well we didn't
have much time anyway pretty soon
Ralphio beat leave the joint uncle Ned
and Claire
thank you
we want to stay here forever and ever
Bruno with you and we open up on this we
will I promise forever and ever we will
you know I know where there's a nice new
toy it'll do a wonderful thing I can i
yeah and you can stay up late just to
see it can we haha I have to call it a
little ways to get that it'll only take
me a little while please don't go every
no it won't take but a few minutes and
i'll be back now Elizabeth I expect you
to take care of your brother and sister
and see that they don't get in any
trouble when you do that will Bruno
ok
Carter
haha
ow
you
and
haha
muck
yes
and
ha
hey Liz hey are you really a wolf and
Wolf Man fan and oh yes I think that's
how every man should be like a wild
beast
No Vacancy again that's the last one end
there is another town for 50 miles I
guess we should have said all that time
it's a village in I didn't realize how
late it was getting it was Catholic
you've taken away the glasses what was
that I know I remember exactly how many
listen I don't there's nothing we can do
except go back and spend the night with
moh locker
who studies aren't supposed to eat other
spiders camel spiders do
you know Bruno doesn't sound like you
know oh no it's Uncle Peter that pretty
lady they'd come back Virginia you must
have heard anyone else gonna really hate
you he will not anyway I like Uncle
Peter he's not like that bad man all the
same dope hell on earth good day the big
tail course L town and I thought it'd be
others give me
they're coming all we do we'll have to
make a plan
somebody's happen about good I hope it's
not that route oh wow it's just a big
kid do you really think so sure
you
Wow hey listen sis miss Morris Roger to
have to spend the night here after all
it's all room at the end as they say
good evening Uncle Peter
I used to ruin all about no no he's away
oh you coming here do come how about
that Emily see you around really no
means it's tears anyone all right when
is mr. brewer will get back he'll be
along by and by now I'm completely you
make yourself right at home Virginia
dear you may entertain our repeater
while I take care of this pretty lady oh
that's all right shall I I'm sure was it
but I was what to do you really think
sell sure where some emily is very easy
to get along with but she's asleep oh
well that won't be necessary and we'll
have daddy's room it's really very much
there you go see oh dear little bit
really very kind goodnight
she in the morning mm-hmm myself a nice
and this way
I'm glad you came back I like I like you
too
you're a nice lady I like to do right
away do not like those others Virginia
likes you too and Ralph we all like you
and I'm competed
you never tell no matter what grown up
you never tell I know you would I pretty
lady pretty name
and the big black spider goes round and
round and wraps the book all up on her
Virginia what happened when the spider
gets above all wrapped up in a web aha I
won't tell ah all right Alex take the
previous game oh we're almost done hey
Virginia
hey what's a spider what's the spider do
now what oh yes now the spider does
please and make it would rock so that is
useful basement Virginia I think we'd
better play another game I'll compete it
feel like that pretty lady yes yes I do
do you like me where is mr. Brunelle
come back guna won't hate me promise
spiders black box
but I guess folks don't like spiders
that much I like spiders I like spiders
I do Wow stuff I have to sting you now
can you wear my mistress locker locker
wow I have to go away from
but I'll be right back
but
are we gonna do with a rock can't let go
what do you mean what are we going to do
with her don't even know you made this
plan and you have enough time to finish
it
she riddles just like a big squiggly bug
in a spider web uncle Ned could make her
quiet no we would be very mad anyway
Ralph like this safe
we mustn't hurt her chef's makers life
now spiders very close she very cleverly
dreams the vital juices from the bug
bite
and that makes the bugs stop squiggling
would that make her stop squiggly help
me find something sharp
color should we let run out who's just
enough to make her quiet they're out
come play with their better
away
no I live in here but your bed rather
take in your hand a little paint tied me
up
you
haha
that late Ralph Ralph will be all well
very soon I brought that wonderful
surprise I promised you let's see what
is it ah this is a secret surprise
Oh sir I don't know how you got yourself
into this predicament but I suggest that
you leave the premises as quickly as
possible right hand yeah we're if I were
you I'd hurry sir
we're gonna do Bruno well it's gonna be
a big flash and go by Oh
rookie
uncle me
yes it was quite an amazing experience
but for me anyway a lot of good came of
this being the only survivor naturally I
inherited the wealth of the Mary's which
later turned out to be my best more
important than that though my wife
that's our daughter Jessica
suny man go outside now we'll all right
Jessica dear sure come back into valve
if it starts raining again live alone
and so the mary syndrome was
extinguished forever with the family
that carried it my own branch of the
family being rather distant we never
suffered from the curse
you