major Bradbury to communication bridge
major Bradbury to clear com forced to
main inch we're home forced to main
major broad prior to communication
bridge major primary to communication
bridge
why do you need me commander Clark we
have entered the very heart of the
Haunted star but we have been unable to
find the secret fortress of the enemy
yet count zarth Arn we must stay alert
we should be in the very vicinity of it
we must only locate this phantom planet
and then fly back and inform
headquarters of his position others will
come and destroy it we have a very
special person on board and we can take
no risks
what is it like the planet we're
approaching nothing but I see snow a
barren desert of whiteness scan it with
our computer waves the enemy's weapons
may be hidden beneath its surface we've
already done it with no results
absolutely none under alert happening
subsonic indicating force field I can't
make it out
you
ah looks like the cops as for chief of
the Imperial police i order you to
surrender at once feed stella you Kate's
mother I am police robot l you have the
right to remain silent if you give up
the right name first you gotta catch me
you dirty cop government for space
let this star muddy stays together
what's our chances forty percent total
disintegration thirty percent molecular
ignition twenty percent gamma
contamination you're very reassuring I
assume that means we have a ten percent
chance of making it not really true
pretend structure collapse to the sense
right all right just people in course
and get ready to reenter nor series
ready when you are
we've done it we've done it not quite
look a neutron star if it gets a hold on
his little cautious
blood is a new course so that cup can't
find us even as you speak it's been
taken care of there's the border of the
Haunted stars and we traveled one second
father we would have round up right
beside them what in the universe is that
it's a spaceship no it's a large their
powers totally down maybe they're
wounded too weak to send a signal I'm
gonna have a look
you
what's the radiation level no the hull
isn't damaged I'm going inside
is everything all right yes wait a
minute there's someone here
he look like he's hurt pretty bad but
he's alive I'll try to get him back to
the hip I'll help you bring on the board
he's dehydrated suffering from
exhaustion but the launch was full of
supplies everything he could have needed
he's also in shock he keeps talking
about monsters red monsters he wants us
to alert someone urgently who the
emperor of the first circle of the
universe
it's the element the cheap officers of
the Imperial Navy I'd say red hot
potatoes for small-time smugglers on the
run like us well what do we do you go to
prison Stella star your leap through
hyperspace didn't fool us you're freaks
betrayal is easy to follow and you are
completely surrounded by fighter ships
this time you won we surrender I won't
be in next time Stella star don't worry
we'll get out of this
my lord yes what is the telerik they
found one damn survivor right now the
Imperial shuttle ship has taken him to
their medical center but his brain seems
to be thoroughly damaged he will be of
no help to them to find the ship mm-hmm
come to me golems I have a simple task
for you you must not fail me the dreams
of a central operating system of
Imperial Justice hereby sentence you
actin of a lion vigor to do 220 years
hard labor in in the prison's manner CC
be calm the third as for you still a
star having considered it all the
arguments studied all the video you
Hades the accusations we condemn you to
force cleaver for life in Europe penal
colony of Nocturne the second this
session is here my adjourned
from the radium in the furnace move
let's go will you step it up with that
radium when you move move down those
stairs in the burners all right five
minutes of rest move quickly now
prisoners get back to that pose let's go
come on quickly now I've been it is for
12 straight hours the radiation will
burn my skin off we're not slaves
doesn't work if you don't want to taste
of the burning of their energy booster
but there must be a way to escape it
will be away you know he loves heaven
you thought could only succeed and you
who's feeding the fair but over feed it
with what energy then a gun rate could
be enough planning an escape this is
what you want to get lady
yo
you
you can drop the rifle ray now turn
around you I bet you never expected to
see me here and you too poor Stella your
escape efforts have been wasted okay
I've lost again take me back to that
hell of a prison you don't understand we
were sent to free you your sentence has
been cancelled have you both gone mad i
alway have logic and emotion circuits no
room for craziness well I've been
assigned to a top secret Imperial
mission we must now leave and said act
and free get ready for blast-off
countdown seven six five four three two
one blast-off
this the prison planet c-come rectums
being held
there he's yours my gift to you
when I lie to you a dios chapter on your
way my friend you only have two hours
look it is the Imperial flagship
machan you are gonna meet some real
royalty
easier there is his holographic image
his highness the Emperor the first
circle of the universe I come to you
because my faithful robot Hill has told
me that you are the only one who can
save us you know you must be the best
pilot in the whole galaxy and you actin
the best navigator is Dylan our galaxy
is split into two warring factions our
own and the one ruled by the evil count
zarth Arn from the League of the Dark
Worlds recently begun to receive
troublesome reports from our spies among
the league they are informed us that the
count has created a weapon a new
limitless weapon a weapon so vast so
huge that it would take a whole planet
to conceal him that is why we sent the
mission ship did they find the planet
the ship came so close so close to
discovering the count secret and it was
suddenly attacked by a horde of unknown
monsters we had assumed it was destroyed
they lost all hope until you found
launched from that ship and now was the
utmost secrecy
you must sail to the Haunted stars you
must find that shit find the cunts
secret planet and destroyed
there's something else when you complete
the mission search for the commander of
that missing ship he was my only son
here's the point where the ship was lost
now calculating the amount of pressure
of solar wind the attraction of nuclear
orbits the amount of fuel left in the
launches tanks as opposed to their full
capacity three series of spatial
coordinates come out the first
possibility is the original also known
as the world's asleep but this system is
still within our galaxy and we should
have found it by now the same also
applies to the light center vozim it's
only the third possibility remains the
heart of the hundred stars an unknown
planet named uraeus well shall we be in
our search let's go the distance we must
travel is enormous by using hyperspace
what would normally take two months to
reach we should do in two hours
everything ready ready right every time
I go in a hyperspace I get nervous
prepare for re-entry to normal space
look the Haunted stars we've arrived
we can meet you by using the space
shuttle Thor and I'll wait for you there
hidden in that Canyon so they were ready
in case of another surprise attack of
the count that sounds fine with me is
there air out there yeah yeah you can
breathe all right let's go follow me I'm
sure you can operate the shuttleship the
controls are easy he'll watch your step
right here
you all right yeah let's go
don't you think we're a little low I
haven't been programmed the walk on
water don't be silly relax el it's
beautiful come water makes me so nervous
everything makes you nervous
it's the launch left lane
taking it easy shuttle the starship we
are wailing Mel Roger
my seatbelt stuff Oh L come on take it
easy on coming look at that amazing it's
almost buried the impact was tremendous
I doubt if anyone could have survived
the nuclear exhaust ports have been
gutted by far we better look around
what's that
seems to be a planetary artifact well it
certainly is an antique looks like some
sort of laser sphere this planet is
inhabited we must be very careful we are
in the evil counts domain these stars
are extremely far and remote even for
him probably they've set up a fully
independent kind of civilization we're
wasting time we better start looking for
their missing crew come on let's go this
way
look Amazon's on horseback I hope
they're friendly we'll soon find out
take my revenge kill him
you'll pay for this
let's kill you
stop there's no escape take your hands
off of me let me go let me go get your
hands off of me let me go green Corellia
this is the spy we captured she came
through the forbidden see you're a spy
as the men from the launch were too but
nothing is going to stop the count
anymore even if you had passed by this
world you'd never be able to discover
the counts planet two packs of murdering
guardians are there to watch and protect
it from intruders and now put her into
the mind-probe now
release her a blaster queen I mean it
come on now don't you people mover your
dad you mean a treble and I'm gonna
clean up your sinuses real good lady you
stand there wait does it or don't you
follow us here behind you come on let's
go hell you're terrific I didn't know
you had it in you
where's the release mechanism it's
jammed take cover
there goes the last shot full power come
on let's go hurry hurry guardian take my
revenge kill them
whoa run for your life they're a narrow
passage in the rocks come on still up
bro
you
watch out you big bro
we better move the Amazon air fighters
will be here soon
oh man the laser cannon
oh seven
okay get ready here they come Spectre
seven fire on the approaching ships
power is up to home battle speed
you why don't you come back now yeah
they comes back two three
you shut your pussy for the ride attack
attack
alright we've got them
one more there's one more we've got him
watch out on the right we're down from
six to five get ready
the two I'm God God more to the left six
we got it we're holding
now p ships approaching for the night
all right we won we did it I found the
positions to both the third launch I am
the mothership the mothership is closest
so we'll check it out first it's here on
the third planet the next solar system
I've never been there what's it like red
fogs high winds low gravity the air is
breathable and the atmospheric
conditions are stable however the entire
planet is covered with ice and snow and
you must be extremely careful when the
Sun sets the temperature drops thousands
of degrees and in an instant everything
freezes over sounds like a real garden
spot but you know what I say I don't
care
what a terrible crash no one could have
survived you see any sign at the end
percent if he's in the middle of all
this I don't even know if his own mother
at recognize him
then it's all over there's no hope of
ever finding account secret fortress
there's still the third launch it's
probably lost out in the stars who knows
anyway it's useless to raise false hopes
it's been too long this galaxy is wild
and hostile come on now let's go back to
the shin we'd better hurry we've run out
of time and our power pack reserves are
nearly finished let's get rid of them
it's going to be a long walk back my
feet are already hope it's time like
these and I'm glad to be a robot
well I'm just refining my powers and
what's your problem ship's computer huh
is everything all right with Stella and
ill I'm not worried about them I'm just
waiting your waiting's over at last Thor
you have some good news for me yes
excellency I've killed the alien
Pathfinder and taken over the ship what
up still a star and that teen policeman
this planet will take care of them
excellency good and I await your
immediate arrival soon I will join you
as your prince of darkness
l how much further we should be closed
just a few more radiance ship's computer
why aren't the main engines firing there
is a malfunction malfunction where is
now that's exactly why I'm not letting
you in soon you'll be dead now be gone
from this planet Joe where's actin actin
is dead and I'm leaving to join counts
are thorn as the Prince of the League of
darkness
Thor a traitor I cannot believe it I
cannot fuck my logic circuits anymore
you fooled me too it's no use we're
gonna freeze maybe not maybe i can say
let's stop here now you are down in the
snow placer ok not give me your hand so
i can monitor your temperature i can use
my energy to keep your heart working
you'll be in a state of suspended
animation well as an opponent I always
knew you a program to never give up
which was infuriating but now that
quality must be best you're the most
faithful companion a woman ever had and
I to respect you Stella you are the
nicest you would mean I have known now
maybe it's a good time to use your
ancient system of prayer and hold it
works for robots as well goodbye my
friend goodbye for now Stella
you
you were expected here hours ago I've
been delayed by a malfunction I don't
tolerate malfunctions or inefficiency in
my realm how long will the delay be I
think a very long time you shouldn't try
taking off without asking me first this
time I'll make sure you're dead
fish you all right actin this is it say
goodbye and what shut up put down the
guns and stop no one can survive these
debts these deadly rays will be your
death
el el dia rain me this is actin I've
taken over the ship do you read me her
pulse rate is 16 she may survive if you
can use your powers and bring her back
slowly careful now close the hatch
look it is working she's going to make
it
come on Stella
what's wrong the main engines will not
fire Thor must have tried everything
what are we gonna do now so we get out
of one mess just to find ourselves in
another not necessarily what do you mean
we are stuck even the transmitter is out
of order we can take off immediately
take off how the ship is not operating
sickly because I borrowed this reactor
then you knew about Thor yes I did so
you see into the future all these years
you never told me think of all the
trouble I might have avoided you would
have tried to change the future which is
against the law so therefore i can tell
you nothing let's find a third lunch act
on you are something else yes time is
running out let's go
we're arriving that's the planet demonia
there in barren land and vast emptiness
will find the third launch ow
something's wrong everything had stopped
what's happening power failure
my circuits my circuits are feeling
we've been hit by an energy beam
oh you let me help you the attacks over
you'll be all right I thought I was good
we just survived an attack of the most
powerful weapon in the entire galaxy we
have yeah he counts argon watch out Oh
what about Al don't worry about him he
just got a few wires crossed I'll have
the boy ready to ride the Sun up just
keep the ship on its course I'll fix him
up now we will do in fact Don's
calculations are correct we should find
the launch this way in a crater just
over there
no me don't say it don't say it I know
steam makes you nervous no no not really
why should I be nervous there is nothing
to be afraid of around here
looks totally read but it's definitely
the third launch I better go down no I
insist time for a little robot
chauvinism you stay here be careful L
you do not have to worry about me
ah
Oh
relax take it easy i put you down there
you're free
that was a little too close for comfort
come on come on
a rest here this is safe
who are you
this is an energy shield mask and the
amount of energy is limited then I fear
were lost you put yourself in great
danger just to save me where are you
from my name is Simon I'm the only
survivor from the wreck of an imperial
mission are you really we've been
searching for you up were these damned
haunted stars what the Emperor's orders
were to find the counts phantom planet
and to destroy it so you know about the
monsters yes I do well it's useless we
did not succeed in finding a planet
either and now there's no time left the
cave men will be waiting for us
alright stay very close very quiet oh
this way looks safe is waiting
why
you
worst
yeah I acton thank God you got here in
time you must have known all along by
the way this is Simon the only survivor
from the Imperial mission we owe you our
lives now maybe with your help we can
still find the cals phantom planet at
school board your ship and continue on
at once there's no need to continue have
you gone crazy that's our primary
mission to find the planet and destroy
it I know but we've already found it
think about it then you'll understand
that this is the counts planet I
remember what the Amazon Queen said
planet occupied by two packs of evil
defenders well the first we met one in
space the red monsters in the second
right here the troglodytes and there's
no question about it this is the planet
this that's incredible who is here and I
didn't even realize it there's no way
you could have any way we must proceed
at once and destroy all that machine
right right
there's the door that'll take us to the
machinery this is the count secret
domain the very heart of the Phantom
Planet from here he planned to control
the entire universe this is incredible
where is everybody everything is set in
our destiny soon you'll know all the
answers
this will take us through operation
headquarters
after you my dear here's the nerve
center of the entire operation this is
unbelievable fantastic pre-programmed
computers they can run forever all these
power modules what are they for this is
the force that projected the red
monsters into space then this is the way
they produced real monsters no not real
the monsters never existed these
machines discharge mental projections of
monsters in our brains incredible images
of monsters designed to drive men insane
with fear this kind of weapon counts
earth Arn can take over the entire
galaxy but why didn't they finish us off
when the red monsters were attacking us
suddenly they disappeared this machine
controls how long the attack will last
it's all done automatically program for
a certain amount of time usually the
amount of time is enough to drive most
people insane but we're not like most
people there's the control panel
now destiny must take its course no we
can't allow this to happen let's destroy
it at once
you've been very lucky and clever you
survived every trap that I laid for you
then I realized that your success would
become my triumph how much time is left
captain alpha squadron to go my lord you
here in less than an hour's time all
that will be left of this planet will be
ashes and cosmic dust forever then you
will be among the dead the Ebro will
make you pay for this the Emperor I
forgot to inform you that the Emperor
will be blown to pieces along with the
rest of you yes I told the Emperor that
we had found you on this planet he's on
his way here now at top speed you'll get
here just in time to join the fireworks
I'm sorry your highness you've lost
highness forgive me Stella but in the
beginning I didn't know whose side you
were on and afterwards I didn't know how
to tell you yes he is Simon son of the
Emperor and heir to the throne you two
ought to prevent them from leaving this
room at all costs you will stay with
them until the end kill them if you have
to
now it will be just a matter of waiting
an hour goes by quickly we've got to get
past those golem yes but how have faith
and never give up hope
Oh
we're now approaching damen dear all
cream into landing stations all crewmen
to landing stations
don't worry don't worry you and the
prince will live act and you've got to
get up we must get away from here I
shall remain here please get up please I
no longer useful at this time you're
talking nonsense you can heal yourself
in no time at all no I must obey destiny
acton will carry you go it's your duty
you must live I can't I can't leave you
you're the only human like friend I've
ever had I don't understand you never
die Stella Stella I've accomplished the
mission yes but my others are coming
even as I speak they'll rescue you don't
worry
I'll live forever now go go
father
we must leave at once 48 seconds left
till the explosion we've got to get out
of here it's true father the counters
mind the planet with nuclear charges
we're all about to die you know
something my boy I wouldn't be Emperor
if I didn't have some parts of my
command Imperial battleship alt the flow
of time
in the space of three minutes every
molecule on this planet will be
immobilized but after the third minute
the green ray loses its power time will
flow once again and everything will
explode three minutes are not father
boys
now the count believes that we are dead
that our armies have dispersed sand that
we have no leader he is supremely
confident that he can overcome us with
the greatest of ease well then now is
the time to surprise him we will attack
his headquarters before his fleets can
join him if we succeed in this we could
save billions of lives gather together
all our legions there and order the
attack
Oh
you
your highness yes elric an entire space
fleet is approaching this fortress what
calling all our forces immediately we
will wipe out the Emperor completely by
sunset I'll be the new emperor and I
will be the master of the whole universe
enemy are riding with no pills
got the fucker talking where are the
constellations point on it we're
approaching their position now
you
now let's give the Emperor a great
reception put in use a mightiest weapon
the doom machine send it off towards the
Emperor's capital world and destroy the
impreza filial planet it's over we're
finished we've lost no no they're still
away there's one solution left I'm
afraid we're forced to use it what
star crash fourth dimensional attack yes
if we can re-enter space at the precise
moment the impact of surprise upon the
contrib is so overwhelming that he
cannot halt us before that there is no
weapon powerful enough oh yes there is
the floating city flowing city yes yes I
know although we destroy its hope its
future I'm afraid we must sacrifice it
by setting it towards accounts fortress
it's our only way
now you must help me both of you go and
direct its course
all done yes my lord now set the doom
machine against the imperial space
station itself how long will it take 15
minutes and set it in motion I wonder
wipe out the Emperor from the whole of
the universe yes my lord Eric yes my
lord when do we reach the floating city
less than two minutes right I'll check
the docking listen right everything
checks out okay look a floating city
already evacuated the technicians have
already set the charges and freed the
atomic engines if everything goes
smoothly i'll try to eject myself as
soon as i re-enter space but surely i'll
come with you no no no it's more
important that you stay here to rescue
me once this is all over all right I'll
stay but I cannot let you go alone in
fact their best scientists have spent
the last few hours reconstructing an old
friend of yours L you can't keep a good
robot down this is incredible they
rebuild you but how you look marvelous
very carefully and they use the latest
components I feel like a new machine go
now quickly the survival of our galaxy
is in your hands it's so nice to be
turned on again and how allow me same
old chauvinist robot
you
this will take us directly to the
control room we have a lot to do in a
very short time
get ready to ease out of orbit this
doesn't make you nervous does it I have
never flown a city before well leave it
to me
build up maximum energy we must sleep
through the very heart of the stars
prepare to transit eight degrees okay
I'm ready
my lord eccentric a floating ship is
about to crash into us what so dad yes
my lord destroy the floating ship
approaching us it can't be done it's too
close there it is dead ahead all right
the count fires we've got to evade them
systems prepare for full power
let's lock in these control a little bit
out quick let's go I am come back you
bulls you cards come back I think yes
sir rebel you'll be destroyed stay with
me at all let's get out of here oh there
won't be enough left for me to put back
together you can bet on that circuits
don't fail me now
you
we going it's Simon Simon we're over
here Stella Stella
Stella Simon hmm Stella hmm Simon hmm
that's so well it's done it's happened
the stars are clear the planets shine
we've won
Oh some dark force no doubt will show
its face once more the wheel will always
turn
but for now it's calm and for a little
time at least
we can rest
you