this is the lettermen General Hospital
at San Francisco California those
outside these gates war is over a thing
of the past for those behind these gates
there's a Grimm heart that a fight still
going on take one case the case of Eddie
rice aged 33 listed from Los Angeles
1943 holder of a Silver Star but today a
name and date number a medical fire of
five years in charter a hospital bed a
victim of amnesia in mind with a blocked
out past where were you born Eddie who
are your parents any brothers sisters
where did you go to school what's your
trade profession are you rich poor got a
girl married I don't know I don't know I
can't remember
I just can't remember dr.
you had me open what did you quit for
did the best we could a tea it'll just
have to stay there that final unless you
want your name on a headstone that's
travels to deepen your brain scar tissue
has growing all around it believe me we
tried yeah I guess you did where do I go
from here Eddie there are two kinds of
amnesia psychological and organic
psychological form is temporary it can
be cured through psychotherapy yours is
organic it's permanent that piece of
steel in your brain has blocked out your
memory which doesn't leave me much of a
future doesn't of course it does
physically you're normal and healthy
you've received a maximum medical
benefits completed training courses that
they can fit to hold down a job and face
life no address no next of kin nothing
enlisted from Los Angeles
intelligence ran that down for us
remember oh sure there were a lot of
people named Riesling but not this Eddie
rice but Army Intelligence didn't mow
Los Angeles lawns as a kid Eddie didn't
trade at the corner market didn't work
with people in a factory in an office as
you might have done now if you went down
there and ran into somebody who knew you
just one person yes
I ran into just one person who knew me
one guy would come up to me and say
Eddie Eddie rice have you been where
have you been that's said Eddie and then
they'd tell me about someone else I used
to know and I'd meet somebody else and
another
sure it scares you to go out into a
world you don't remember but you're here
now it'll be a new life a new start find
yourself a place to live get yourself a
job get going
get going any
Eddie you know it's a small world Eddie
we came down here to pick up a little
one thing and we run into an ill of
another a lot of us thought you were
dead yes and those that didn't hoped you
were what are you doing in town I'm just
in from San Francisco I didn't ask you
that he asked you what you were doing in
town I came here to look up some people
funny I had a feeling that was it
Anderson one of them Anderson maybe I
think you're lying Eddie I don't think
you're gonna look up Anderson all
Merrick do you think he's gonna look up
Anderson no Joe not Anderson uh tell you
what I've got a car and nothing to do
for a while let's go see Anderson
together any objections no objection
stick around Kelly may still show let's
go
honorable discharge of Edward rice
what's the gimmick if you'd put away of
black Jack's long enough maybe I could
get it through your heads that I don't
know what you're talking about haha you
got yourself a sense of humor Eddie you
think you come back here with a dumb
look on a silver star that changes a
no-good heel but I'm trying to tell you
that you don't have to tell us anything
about yourself we got it all down in
black and white read it regarding we
didn't dream it up possession of a
weapon with intent to kill suspicion of
murder riccardi Eddie recording
it only looks like I better get out of
here I've got to get out five years ago
we hustled you out of town for good now
what are you here for you gotta play
ball anytime you need more time to find
out about yourself ricard is just
playing dumb captain put him in the
locker I'm finding out about these
charge papers if their ponies will pin a
real one on it just another lieutenant I
guess maybe I didn't want the army to
know about Eddie riccardi the only
friends I have no me is Eddie rice I'd
like to keep it that way that's probably
the first honest thing you've ever said
pick up your things be Eddie rice in
some other town but not here we can't
hold you but you step out of line once
we step on you love us anything
different about him Williams nothing
riccardi stays in town there's got to be
trouble I don't know got a strange look
about him send to Washington for a
complete report on Edward rice that's
Silver Star you really do something to
get one yeah lighten the pawn shop for
two bits
Nina my sweet my beautiful lovely all
right Nick let's keep it all business
how is it this time Petey suspicion of
robbery get him up before they start
shifting him around Haiti him he
wouldn't steal his own shadow that was
Williams Jack to get him out of the way
I wouldn't know bailiff a
thousand-dollar inflation it's the whole
trouble these days Alexander he unhappy
Nick keep your mind on your business but
Vince worried about his huh sure
beautiful sure forget I mentioned it
take my advice you leave town I've got
things to do gnatios boy you're on your
own Kelly never showed odd will hear
from him
one of the usual fronts you have a lot
of jane doe's Nick he was one of them of
course there's a big difference between
the Florida oranges in the California
oranges at least that's what the Chamber
of Commerce and for dessert and the
chamber commerce in California says
orange juice please yes Eddie oh I
thought it was you from across the
street
hello
that's the only thing you've got to say
well there's a lot more I could say but
but you let's see
Nancy Morgan Donna Murphy no you don't
look like Nora Murphy would you come
back for Eddie the man has a right to
come home Esme my cars across the street
I'll take you there sure thanks
good to know you're back Vince should he
you ought to know
thanks for the lift
coming in who said this was the end of
the road who's complaining not me
checking in long I don't know you alone
yes Edward right San Francisco 304
I'll throw the stuff in the room d right
back you say so
hello hello this is Nina I want to talk
to Vince he's busy not too busy for what
I've got to tell him look let's not keep
hurry as a secret it might upset your
whole future put me through to him
you talk too much another treatment
Kelly any any second break Spence
I need you to do business with you talk
you live all I want to hear is your
anger with Joe Williams give me a
cigarette Danny and relax
I'm trusting you Vince sure sure Kelly I
told you we'd turn you loose you
understand how a guy feels and he's been
kicked out of the organization I know I
shouldn't have been a sucker and told
Williams about that about the silver
dollar I get that what'd you tell him
about this nothing nothing much really
Vince what did you tell him Kelly really
Vince nothing important just a little of
distant mad about the about the slot
machines and the take but i I've phony
the figures honest I did these fingers
at pony why'd you get
snatched him out of your safest Williams
was waiting for him there's gonna bundle
me out of town bring me back to the
trial but I was gonna duck and never
would have found me it's a truth Vince
hello hello Nina
you sures him I was with me first I saw
him outside Police Headquarters talking
to Joe Williams when I drove into the
car tears you checked in under the name
of Eddie rice room 304
you still want to take that trip Kelly
you don't have to worry about me vince
da big mouth Kelly you think what he's
got may be contagious very catchy what's
your opinion duck very definitely what
can I do the consultations in agreement
jelly you're dead oh you Kelly when you
get to where you're going have him give
you a nice even burn don't I'm just fry
on one side
I'm side of audio again but has there
been any sign of the girl yeah thanks
don't you believe in knocking on doors
who are you what do you want
so that's why even hold up Eddie rice no
wonder i couldn't get a line on you are
you back sightseein mr. rice supposed to
be a free country freetown open to
anyone added me in it you didn't waste
much time picking up with the cops why
should it worry you about me talking to
Williams you've got me confused any only
a sucker would lock back in town after
deal you pour some things that fella has
to find out for himself not about you
and me I've been saving this for five
years everyone in life has his Bible
this is mine I take it out and read it
every day are you to remind me of a guy
I grew up with could shove it around
with used to take a lot of reps together
some people would call a guy like that a
loyal friend he was
until he to new a dirty stool pigeon and
let me take the rap for him
Eddie riccardi my good friend who sold
me out to a cop named Joe Williams don't
mess up his face too much I ought to
kill you ready but you're not worth
taking another rap far in 24 hours
disappear otherwise I might be tempted
to change my mind Jim sameer
you
why didn't that girl come back
what did you know about me why don't you
bring me here
Vince
we're in Vince kill me
maybe I deserved it
maybe dr. Kimble oughta know
better tell him
I'd better call him hello I want to put
through a call person-to-person Dr
Kemble Letterman general hospital san
francisco kem ble thank you
you
hello dr. Campbell let me expect him
back till tomorrow nevermind I'll see
him personally
forget about Union Station take me to
seven Braxton Avenue
wait
it's early Nina a little drink for a
nightcap won't hurt you that's what you
think you could make me forget that
thousand i drop tonight Nina I can
forget a lot of things Lou you for
instance good night just a minute baby I
like a little receipt for that grand
that's better ouch that's your receipt
good
go ahead take a good look you came to
tell me how girls welcome you back
you've said it so goodbye I want to know
what you had to do with me in my life
and this December the 24 1943
Christmas what I'll never forget
only one of your presence
sure I told Vince Alexander your back I
work fine
this clipping
why couldn't you testify the truck oh no
routines I've heard them all listen to
me I'm just out of an Army Hospital with
a piece of steel in my head and no
memory to go with it I'm here to find
out about myself and I'm getting answers
the hard way I don't know you Vince
Alexander or anybody called Eddie
riccardi all I know is one person Eddie
rice me you're the last person i can
turn to please believe me help me
that's a very touching speech
you lost your memory you don't know why
I couldn't testify in the trial you've
forgotten how you use me to make sure
Vince would go to prison so you'd be set
free but if you're back to your old
tricks again I've got bad news for you I
tore up your raincheck three years ago
I'm not your wife at him
now to the station back to the hotel
you act like a cop the just lost two
convicts maybe I have take a look at
these fresh out of the photo lab sharks
don't talk the fingerprint spell Kelly
coroner said he was dead two hours
before he hit the water too bad with the
information Kelly had for us we could
have put Vince away for a long stretch
what's eating you Joe I was a smart cop
I put Petey way to get him off of
Kelly's tail and this is what happens I
feel like I killed kelli mccarty think
he's tied up in it walking back into
town that day could tie him up in
anything the case my baby all yours now
what I figure we shouldn't keep it a
secret truth is
you
only six days in the week now how do you
like that the card must have fell out it
was there yesterday Nick who's Jane Doe
please lieutenant I don't look at the
point certificate lots of people don't
use their right names with me a buck is
a book I don't ask questions before I'm
through Nick you'll be answering a few
it's getting so you can't tell her that
I anymore without having the cops jump
on you this town's going to the dogs
Simpson to me p to get that cat off a
death I was just saying sales anomie
could stand a vacation you want us to
blow town that's just what I don't want
Coco set you up and stay quiet well sure
Ben sure anything you say
well Danny
come in come in Joe pull up a chair and
rest your feet I hear you've had a busy
day I figured you would I was saving you
for last should I relax or colin Meloy
that spends on how nervous you are I
always thought nervous guys bit their
nails now let me see Nick was a little
bit hazy about to Jane Doe was I thought
you might be able to tell me never hurt
a girl then there's PD and how certain
people got to know where and just when
the bail amount now nobody knows
anything but we'll find him we've got
all exits out of tone plug and I got a
hunch he'll be real cooperative you see
him I don't think he knows anything
about this Kelly he's gone and gotten
himself killed just like Kelly you never
know what you'll do next that goes for a
lot of guys take you and then again take
Eddie ricciardi you boys forgive and
forget me back in business again you and
ricotta get a lot in common why don't
you ask him at the moment your number
one and it won't be any manslaughter
charge and out in two years I put you
away this time it'll be for keeps you
get all the answers figured out energy I
might have sooner do you think so sorry
yeah I never had a complaint you call my
old boss he'll tell you my bringing in
five hundred a night at the gambling
tables was a small Bagatelle Oh mr.
Alexander I just came in looking for a
job and I was telling us Martin get rid
of her since we need some new talent ok
ok come back at eight tonight she tell
you what to do you know any still in
town yes mirror honest II late last
night till I give him 24 hours to get
out no I changed my mind I wanted to
stay I want you to make sure he does
stay my jobs to work the tables for you
here dancin I don't even mind setups
like the one with PT er other deals like
that but fence stay out of my personal
life listen you and Eddie dropped you
who picked up and get help we'll give
you a job everything you got Vince
Alexander I won't do it Vince forget
heady when I get through with him but
now you're gonna meet him I want you to
make sure he does stay in town
well it'd be five years make you forget
that easily I told you in five years you
can forget a lot of things something for
the lady Rob Roy please the same what
made you change your mind let seeing me
again
you know finding out I was married to
you kind of threw me was even something
the boys the hospital used to rid me
about they had me fixed up with a wife
and four or five kids didn't know how
close the gag came to be true you still
don't believe me do
maybe this will convince you was any
rice that rang your doorbell last night
call dr. Campbell Letterman's hospital
in San Francisco you tell you the whole
story
that's cigarette case Oh doesn't it mean
anything to you
should it
suppose I did believe you then what then
I try and make you forget that Eddie
riccardi was ever in your life you think
you can do that Eddie rice can
Eddie leave town
now you're talking like Vince maybe I
was yesterday don't ask me why I would
go mean I don't frighten easily you can
take that message back to Vince tell him
I'm staying that's what he wants you to
do that's why I'm here to keep you from
leaving I'd hate to disappoint Oh ready
don't be stubborn I know Vince he
doesn't do anything without a reason
neither do I stay dead get yourself
beaten up again or kill do anything you
mccarty very interesting
Scotch over water hmm blue something
jelly tell alena martinet he wants to
see Eddie who just Eddie wait here
what do I need thousand might bring you
look thousand give me a foul
character called Eddie's outside wants
to see you and he here get rid of him
that's not what Vince had in mind
alright come on
six nine 12
it's nice layout inside of be able to
pick up some fast money you're crazy to
come walking in here maybe I'm just hard
to convince my dressing room respect
I'll be back before the wheel stops
turning
yeah okay thanks
so she wanted to get rhythm wonder if
that Dean is trying to pull a double
cross get down the Golden Horn and pick
up Eddie riccati find it with Nina just
him just him I get around to hear later
I started to leave but I kept thinking
about everything you told me but I've
left had been all the things you said I
was so on stay and I'm taking you out of
here Nina we could have a decent life
together got it all figured out you're
not taking me anywhere you pushed me
into this life and I like it my top bait
around here staring nice fat pigeons to
the gambling tables I'm one of Vince's
chi now and I'm keeping my life and my
job just the way they are no matter what
I have to do come on
thanks
now how about some champagne
excuse me for a minute honey off her god
I gotta call my wife
well it was homicide yeah Bart uh-huh
yeah thanks a lot what's exciting
I said what's exciting I don't you want
to wake me up Barnes casing the Golden
Horn for bison tale tells me ricardio's
walking Oh trouble maybe I can think of
plenty of reasons why there might be
Freddy your eyes you'll hear from you
later
hyah come with that Kelly report men
just finishing that for you okay I'll
wait somebody must have believed that
old gag about an apple a day yeah but
they didn't know it would kind of murder
on him he fight an appetite
psychological creates a false hungry
well here you are Joe taking the home
now thanks a lot man see you tomorrow
okay see you tomorrow
yeah i'm interested Neddy ricciardi not
in what's going on in there we don't
know from riccardi I do open up
honoree
yes miss Marcal Williams homicide may I
come in please come in said he was just
picked up by daddy where you take him
you'll hear from the letter
you know Williams I'm not used to cops
with insomnia what's on your mind it
won't take long daddy picked up that
you're riccardi where are they you're in
an awful right Oh was asking questions
all right let's start over Eddie was at
the Golden Horn with Nina Martin
suddenly he wasn't there anymore so so I
don't mind waiting oh well we kill a
little time this might interest you
and after we pick up riccardi we're
going down to police headquarters you're
gonna have a manicure on me you know
you're gonna look awful silly when I get
through with you if I'm wrong I'll
apologize say hello nothing more hello
bears we're at the shop do we stay or
bring riccardi up there tell him you'll
be down okay coke
what now
jesseman Eva's coming up in the
department
you
car 94 94 to control par Claire
frequency for that's not emergency
control for 294 go ahead car 94 to
control for notify the Homicide Bureau
we have found the body of lieutenant
Williams in his car at Sepulveda and
sunset
you mean you left son thanks I had a
little accident backup up the side road
I have to go to town get a tocar anybody
killed no luck at all tonight hop in bet
you thought I wouldn't stop to yep it I
didn't know it's late see that's where I
Fuji cup the orders pick up anybody
anytime greenacres auditions policy lift
today maybe a custom of the borrower
pays off to most people remember the
nice things you do for a while they're
living we sure don't get any complaints
about our service from them after
they're dead a family that is that
accident hurt you any
got imagine sure
fabulous of everything wonderful news
many customers
finish with Joe stuff yet still working
on it it's too bad
Joe's wife she liked him in that suit
too
lite-on ricotta yet nothing captain keep
trying is the last one who might have
seen Joe okay Ellie riccati yes Williams
was right after all a cardio rice Silver
Star and a dumb look doesn't change a
no-good heel attention all units
attention all units be on the lookout
for the following describes suspect
Eddie rice white male America 190 power
dark Robin your phone like cops and do
them a favor where to find a dead cop
and the guy that did it and what happens
the first stop is Nina Martinus I
wondered he before the cops can then
they can have him for a present and
alive
Eddie get those lights huh Eddie what
happened you certainly did a neat job of
tying me into a murder Joe Williams was
killed tonight you I don't know last
thing I remember was being slugged over
the head at Penn Selig's Andy's I know
you think I haven't got time to think
all I want is a few bucks your car and
you and my sight till I get out of here
ready you've got to believe huh believe
you like you believe me give me the keys
hey this is why I turned on you tonight
to get you away from Vince the keys are
in the car you go i'll try to stole them
all and get a bullet in the back of my
head how do you got to trust me it's
your only chance quick a garage
where you get out go to the city before
it's too late but my fingerprints all
over the gun and all over Williams car I
wouldn't last long enough to walk at the
nearest police station if I did what
could I tell them now out you want me to
go home and wait for Vince to come back
again that's something any record it
would tell me to do not Eddie rice all
right
stop
keep your lights off in the motor
running
now you've got a gun what next then as
for any killings saw him in the middle
I'm gonna be a clay pigeon for Vince
Alexander he can't prove anything dead
that would make Vince very happy
something I wouldn't want all that
happen so any place we gotta go someone
you could trust a puss up for the night
I need time maybe there is it's wrong
chance you don't think you're gonna get
away with this do you we're staying here
tomorrow stay away from that phone but
rings let her keep ringing get rid of
anybody who comes to the door I'll be
right behind you in case you have the
wrong answers what about the girls place
there and gone get a teletype out in her
car immediately have it rebroadcast
every half hour I want roadblocks at all
these points i want the airport railroad
station all bus terminals put under
24-hour surveillance I want every hotel
and flophouse notified they're in this
town somewhere and they're not getting
out one other thing we picked up Ricard
his fingerprints in that gun shop he's
got a gun now don't give him a chance to
use it all right stop moving the police
tightness dragnet about the city today
riccardi escaped just as the police were
ready to close in on him after they
received an anonymous phone call which
led them to discover the murdered body
of one of the men today every available
man
well will it start and get out of here
you couldn't arrange to drop dead before
then hazel you've got to believe us
Eddie didn't do it he should still drop
dead come on
Oh
give me a couple clean towels
it's pretty bad I'll have you out of
here in a minute we'll find a doctor go
to the police Eddie go to the place
you're karna garage yeah well your keys
in that purse take care of
thanks I'll have the doctor come right
in the moment of return
I'd basically
you're far away
five years a lifetime
beyond that a blank
they do it
when it's been a different kind of a
play it's being pushed back to Eddie
riccardi this the whole past that keeps
me from being like other people now all
that's left is wondering what it would
be like if they'd only been on any rice
might have just met you for the first
time
Eddie rice Karen Hampton
you're good
you've taken away destroyed
when the baby wants this morn hours
don't matter 77 ounces a boy dr. her
shoulder
I can't treat gun wounds she'll have to
go to the police emergency hospital I
don't think so I'm sorry I've got to
report this to the police dr. that
report to the police it'll wait if you
want to pull that trigger go ahead
Police Headquarters please put that gun
away I said I was going to call the
police Reese headquarters this is dr.
Stacy 93 chestnut street send an
ambulance on the squad car how bad is it
she'll be all right you better leave
hey I'm scared I'm scared take it easy
you'll be all right not for me for you
listen I'm leaving you for a little
while I've got an idea it might work
something very important you knew all
about me the people i used to know the
places I went think for me go back five
years who was there just one person give
me the answers quick what you say is my
only chance the only chance I've got
only one left us PT can't be trusted
well I find him not here tell me to
three places on Main Street for an
attorney to ran in front of it coke
never had a chance that he sure didn't
miss coke took three went right through
its breakfast lunch and supper anybody
come around ask any questions none i
couldn't answer bin get back down and
keeping company but the police that's
exactly what I want tell him I'll
riccati broke in your apartment found
cochlear pulled his gun and fired I do
what I told you just that all right
Vince take our back he's gonna find a
doctor somewhere and if it does wherever
think you'll dump the girl stop looking
for a hideaway get going spread the news
I got a personal interest in Eddie
riccati I don't need them to happen to
him until I get that unless the cops get
him first you're through with him Doug
yep he was a fine specimen would have
had a long life but this hadn't happened
I'll send you my report in the moon I'm
sure you don't mind coming downtown miss
Downes well I I thought not what you're
fine it was them all right riccardi left
the doctor's office about 30 minutes ago
another fight communications are
blanketing the whole area I go county
jail hospital still out whether she's
playing it safe or just not talking keep
melon they're miniature comes out I want
to know any idea lots we need ricotta to
explain some of them if he lives that
long
hello I'm looking for Pee Dee Messina
yeah where to find him
nina said three or four places I must
have hit 20 in every answer the same no
a shake of the head frightened face they
knew where i could find what I was
looking for but they wouldn't talk they
were scared
but plants appreciate the fact at least
I called you I let him stay it's another
rap another rap I get life you've got to
appreciate that and I'd appreciate it if
you'd tell me where to find PT right now
sure ready sure
ocean boulevard 20 says
who's that who is it Eddie Eddie
recording Oh ready boy are we cop in the
city's out gunning for you maybe you'd I
can't leave but I got a few more years
left open the door PT you're dead if you
don't you didn't think I'd leave you out
there in the cold is Eddie five years no
see make sure I got a hot fire burning
on the other yeah you need a pal ok sure
I need a friend PT oh look a friend will
you you put that mouthpiece away some
however I still believe they go off and
Samson I cut you you remember my cat all
right he's not feeling too good again
you stay careful nothing will happen oh
sure Jerry yeah you're throwing a PT
remember the objections to my moving in
with you I'll be gone tomorrow next day
me turn away practically my own flesh
and blood relax
ready nothing's too good for you about
some food BTW i haven't eaten all night
oh you haven't changed a bit always
hungry you'll tie it up with Vince what
I do a little powder and on the side job
your job there nothing big I'll
telephone
okay BTW hi I got a special customer
yeah yeah hold on how about sending
something over he's tired hungry a pot
of coffee and a sandwich turkey tongue
egg salad combination yeah yeah that's
right you got it
you see Eddie everything's just like old
times you say so p d yeah I'm gettin
kind of sleepy you just make yourself at
home food will be along pretty soon
Vince has gotten to be a big man the
last five years I'm really get pretty
tired Brendan why don't you bring me up
to date people I'm really awful tire
friend how long will it take Vince to
get Eddie Eddie you you embarrass me
I'll kill you if you don't give it to me
straight p Eddie Eddie don't talk like
that samsung sick I'm telling ya Eddie
what are you telling me how long 5
minutes 10 15 minutes 20 minutes come on
about 15 minutes Eddie min switch on the
spot he sent word to all the boys glow
Eddie take me with you you and me was
always been you just stay in the front
of me and keep your mouth shut and you
won't get into trouble oh well sure
Eddie you got nothing to worry about for
me just stay my friend
you're tired you can go home now you
friend want a ride not tonight
280 this will get you a thousand
take care of PT
ready let's get out of here go ahead pt
thanks Eddie hey coming
Eddie you hear me we can make a break
cover for each other I got a place you
and me Eddie start up again just like
old times
I get money Eddie
big money
baby come back
riccardi alexander will give you three
minutes to come out we're gonna start
counting at the end of three minutes if
you're not out we're coming to get you
this is your last chance Eddie there's
just you and me left now No Deal Vince I
know your guilt go Williams okay no
deals
we want you riccardi alive alexander if
you're in there not wounded bring
riccardi out you ricciardi if you're
alone come out with your hands in the
air here's where you and I part company
you're gonna get paid off and fuck
thanks for bringing him out Vince now
drop your gun I said drop your gun Vince
yeah you take what I got first Anderson
all police officers hold your fire don't
be crazy Alexander have been enough
people killed give yourself up no
bargains Anderson you wonder karti alive
I 10 what guarantee have I got that you
won't kill riccati you don't be sensible
Alexander if we let you out now we'll
get you later you'll be dead before
morning you got 30 seconds to make up
your mind Anderson I go or a car he gets
it in the back stay down Eddie don't
move
cuz he did he will be if we don't get
him to a hospital
that taxi driver must have really gotten
to you and I heard he did asking for a
thousand dollars reward and all the
questions you want to ask I call Dr
Kemble from San Francisco we know Vince
killed Joe Williams we found his blood
on Joe's clothing it matched up with our
lab files yours didn't and hazel told us
the truth about coke I'll just get well
we'll finish our business leader Nina
she's fine in the waiting room
you shouldn't kiss a guy like that when
he's sick in bed I've been waiting
outside all the time wouldn't tell me
anything that's afraid
sorry we'll go away will find that crazy
world of you sure there's only one thing
you'll always be Eddie right for the
rest of my life I have the docs word for
it
you
I