yeah
my name is sergeant Joe think working a
24-hour shift out of homicide and this
is my workshop
the part of town that everybody knows
about that nobody wants to see the
tragedy is a deeper the ecstasy is
wilder and the crime rate consistently
higher than anywhere else
Skid Row might be
yeah
the most terrifying period in the
history of might be big and little
rundown floral shop called my snakes
good morning miss achieve a house things
today
this thing is yours mr. Merson my
sister's not Stanley in little rock
I can saw what happened pick up long
enough
who knows how that's nice but you would
like maybe as usual some flowers for the
funeral
you forgot and never brought I thought
possibly yeah
because i always give you all my funeral
business and maybe you should possibly
give to me a little cut ray look at me
mrs. Shiva
but am I philatelist I sell on Skid Row
nothing but cheap carnations and I
should give you our corporation I can't
even afford water for the flowers to my
throat I would be giving a cut
I grabbed site well with that guy from
the back
excuse me miss issue with this that
Seymour a nice boy
why don't you want to see look here I
got a new customer brand new in the
yellow vest i should let me clean up boy
but i can't eat enough for chase them
out right away
flowers places the springtime motionx
hello hello dr. father
what can I do for you listen much Nick I
haven't got much time send me over to
gladiolas and the fern
excellent that's two dozen glass one
potted fight no no no mush Nick to
gladiolus and one for you want I should
sue gladiolas in the part with the
fights
no one fern one piece all together three
pieces
I need for my waiting room in there
thank ya
what a feeling for how good i'll drill a
bigger hole
you mean you want to crummy gladiolus
among crummy find what kind of a
decoration is that this is my flower
budget for the week
moosh unique who can be a dentist on
Skid Row
alright excellent also see more right
away my argument science
make it snappy no you are going to get
it
whoo-hoo-hoo you are going to get a look
see my friend of mine now
we were talking from the funeral flowers
a little
you call me mr. Mushnik know i was
calling john d rockefeller for to make a
loan on my rolls royce sorry I said it
now let's see mama
you take two glad yours will cut in nice
and easy
you'll take one . wrap them in a package
and you'll take them to dr. far right
already
now what can I do for you sir my name is
person
excellent i am gravis mushnick that's a
good one who's gonna get my rose up he
can you need to come over here
you would like maybe some orchids for
the nice go
no i think i'd like to come a dozen
carnations our nation's can find on
these numbers you dropped it when your
share of bad luck bad luck she called
you should have so many people thought
you would have somebody gonna tell you
about the carnations
you wanted the ground yeah First Nations
you should see what that see Morris
well here are your carnations make our
rep and applause all right i'll meet him
here
why not
of course what else they are all right
well I'm not sure
well yeah that's okay you know those big
places different pretty flowers
expensive flowers when you're racing for
looks and smells you're bound to have
some food bag
I think he's a little out-of-the-way
places such a thing baby clothes
look don't knock it until you try it huh
what happened this is what I was trying
to tell you before
look on him everybody look at the
quality of his work
I ask you when I fired him where is he
going to get such another good job on
fire
no I'm elected you president from the
United States
yes you are fire grab it you can't do
this ok
I didn't mean you didn't mean you've
never been
you didn't meet at the time you put up
the bouquet but to get well card and a
funeral parlor and sent the black
lillies did the old lady and the
hospital you didn't mean it
but this time I gravis mushnick need it
means it
the team is the most i always try to do
what's right and i'm crazy about flowers
I like flowers almost as much as Audrey
does excellent your fire
why don't you give me
I reckon I give me a chance to quit I
gonna quit or a brave boy you're fired
that ain't fair mr. much Nick you know
what I'm doing
i'm working on a special surprise plant
just for you
I'm going to plant like you ain't never
seen before excellent i can't even sell
the plants i got my shop out you
now wait a minute he's got a new kind of
plan to look at I don't look on flowers
mr. yellow vest
I got the ancestors in the flower
business for 200 years but I got one
shop on Skid Row one stinking shop
I don't even like flowers you're honest
and I mean look I mean in our shops all
over the world and I've noticed that the
places that the most weird and unusual
plants for the best business today
what is this a tangle all right
explain me more well I remember one
place and a whole lot coming with poison
ivy
people came from miles around to look at
that wall in a statement by the owner
got rich
no he scratched himself at Devon in
center so that was my cousin Harry
all right all right you go home and you
get this fancy schmancy plant and you
bring it back here and if mr. yellow
vest about says it's a draw you still
got a job if he don't doubt you go to
body right
our you'll like it you'll see
yeah
radio que si que you've been listening
to use it for all in the lids our next
selection is entitled czekam serenade
yeah but my already spent your tongue
and you no sympathy for your poor mother
laughing at her and marking the realness
and she's got one foot in the grave
I mean all you never mean come on look
at my town
are they all look the same to me did you
stop adapter mountains and get the
results of my tests yeah he said there's
nothing wrong with you
I'm not dr. Mallard he's one doctor I
thought would tell the truth he said you
should be playing fullback for the ramp
he wants me dead I'll bet he's assistant
coroner
well I got a good and i know i know that
my daughter is coming back I can feel
every morning after breakfast
yes when you take those great what you
have announced surprise for me open it
up and see
dr. your saddles famous tonic
wait here to be taken internally or
externally for pain and the writers
morelia headache if hit by a truck call
your position
alcoholic contact 98 prevent see more
you never know what is going to do for
me
oh I can feel that surge of warm help
going through me already
what's wrong I got to get my sweatin
hurry back to the shop
you mean that lousy wait out in the
kitchen yeah mr. Mushnik doesn't like it
he's going to fire me
apparently my hearing is going on Me
State impression
it's your job security it depends on
what Muchnick thanks for laughing
it looks worse than it did this morning
when I went to work I wish I knew what
to do with that will be asked me I'd
pitch it out in the trash
I don't like my house cluttered up with
rotten vegetables look what I got a
hurry can I bring you anything
oh yeah yeah bring me the evening news
they're running at a self diagnosis
contest
the winner gets to go to Mayo Clinic
haha right walk by and see the rosy and
your dog
330 really nice and I will
and put this on my bill
here it is everybody
it's your is different it looks
delicious but don't you think it's kind
of stale hasn't been feeling too well
you call that a fancy plan it looks like
it never spent an LT day and its entire
life
I don't care I like it anyway you you
like even skunk cabbage plant this
anymore
well i'm not sure i got the seeds from a
Japanese gardener / on central avenue
he found them in with an order he got
from a plantation next to a cranberry
farm fine fine you don't even know about
this display and you're growing
well I gave it a name what watch you
gave it a daddy named you can't even
mention it
well I named Audrey junior me that's not
exciting thing anyone's ever done to me
like shit
I don't think it's so much i should keep
on spending ten dollars a week on your
salary
he named it after me I know and if they
keep it there name is Mick Foley because
i'll be in jail for non-payment of taxes
are you crazy
who you you that's probably the only
place of its kind in the world but you
realize of see more complex that thing
back to help you have people coming in
from all over you think so you fuck i
know so you watch it
that's all I'm saying on the subject
sighs I've got to get on my wife's
making godliness with dinner
good night i'll see you tomorrow
crazy about social flowers he's a nice
man
maybe he knows what he's talking about
maybe it's not so stupid
I'll tell you what I don't I'll keep
your and his dumb Bell Jr for a week if
you can I sit back down to you about can
stay if you can
your boat fire chief Thank You mr.
Muchnick feel fat
see more
don't waste your pity on me Audrey I'm
not worth it
who stands you're not everybody
yeah i know i think you're fine
figurative of a man and I know that I'd
be junior will be the sweetest thing in
the whole wide world
well I don't know I've given it every
kind of fancy fertilizer and a comic
plant food and distill mineral water you
can buy it just gets sicker and sick
don't worry you're gonna be an Appaloosa
glendale pasadena burbank
good night see more night I three
yeah
what's the matter little plan
haven't I done everything I could for
you
my group you're the first little plant I
ever tried to grow and if you die I
don't know what I'll do
please don't die I'll get you some water
okay
yeah
gee you opened up just like you do every
night at sunset
I wish I knew how to make you grow here
let me move this out of your way so you
can breathe out what happened
how come you won't go black you like
black
you must be kidding
we'll see
yeah
what I'm doing for you
I would have bought it well I guess it
just no accounting for people's taste
yeah
boy you can hear more easily
beautiful isn't it delicious isn't he
got the two dollar raised
what happened to your fingers these
things I so how come all of a sudden so
wonderful 5 b's once on each finger and
bees
he said I was getting a two dollar
raised correct my very excellent see
more and be what did I do now that you
know what you did
oh boy look at that bro
it's almost a foot wall . it grows like
a cold sore from the lift
hello young 50 ladies what did get out
of this wishing to do for you well sign
outside about the army junior always
that would come in and take a look
well would you look that makes four
people today who come in debt to look at
it oh it sure is that just
oh my Oh what kind of plant is it's an
odd read your books that you got in
trouble with 10 be well is that all I
mean doesn't have a scientific yes of
course but who could denounce it was
like maybe device something
what we don't have any money except two
thousand dollars but that's just to
spend on flowers so we don't have any of
our home
isn't that a drag you've got just two
two thousand dollars just thought to
spend on flowers who died the Chamber of
Commerce work from pokemon high school
building a float for the Rose Bowl
parade which is made out of flour and
we're on the committee to fix the flora
and thank you song flowers
gee that sure is a mad plan wow yeah
mihir invented it he got a girl please
don damaged or the culture is tell me
how come you don't buy all these
thousands of flowers from gravis
mushnick my flowers got something the
others don't
what's that the chi Chi if your shop is
good enough to develop the Audrey jr. i
guess i can guess everything we need
yeah we'll talk it over with the rest of
the committee
we gotta run out bye bye bye girls
son a son
look on three I got the Sun gee mr. my
snake mark mr. motion they got a monster
should call me mr. motion again anymore
i want you should call me there
ok dad that beautiful
see more clever boy come over here my
son
I want to talk on you about the future
look on this flytrap
look I soon we got no more skin roll
we will be rich us I am building for you
a giant greenhouse in which you are
making impossible flowers which in turn
i am selling at ridiculous prices in my
giant new flower salon in Beverly else
you see that big sign in the sky
it is saying gravis mushnick in French
an orchestra my belly cash register and
gravel waving on in the orchestra played
end of the spring funk and i'll come out
the gun at by somebody expensive and say
they're carnations are six hundred
dollars 1,000 2,000 4,000 it's a market
my uncle moisture w I could just ask the
way to fly in Johnson tell me how much
are the carnations today the carnations
are six hundred dollars that wire and
that he can run around with his excuse
my son mrs. Shiva just . anything in the
store and it is yours
that's the cash register maybe hi
wait a minute here several dozen
carnations on the house courtesy of
gravis mushnick the bloom cool
that's my dad thanks thanks very much
only tell me why are you so happy
not only been my uncle Moses brother
thank God I have a new jersey
we should also give some flowers that
put that planting
demonic dissolution
shoot what happened to my plant that who
you calling dead who and it was so
beautiful just a few seconds ago
excellent just a few seconds ago I gave
away dozens of carnations free to mr.
sugar
I didn't mean it you have perhaps an
explanation now but if you give me a
minute i think of one
I can see it all now we are in the poor
house that big sign in the sky is
reading see more curl .
rest in peace in Arabic you got to give
him another chance
you promised me a week Mr my snake I set
up all night with that plant will be
healthy in the morning you'll see
I promise I promise
yeah
me
give me I'm all cut to pieces but ok I
can find another drop here someplace
that's the best I can them mar
but i'm already a name it e me
mar Junior I'd be happy to give you
anything i got but I got to keep a
little blood for myself for not being
worse shape than mom
I'm sorry Junior I'll go for a walk
maybe I think there's something
yeah
II need a child found bottom i got
problems of my own
each knee I'm sorry pal I'm fresh out of
blood part to somebody else hungry
I don't care what you are oh you think
it's fun up all on a sack full of food
now Junior what kind of guy do you think
I am
maybe just a snack
that looks great now . is what I call a
sell it
what do you call that area
well before the next course I think I'll
have a nice ago
all right he was like maybe a cigar
that looks like a girl what am I
thinking about better the matches
Oh would you know what I found
I'm looking for the matches and i found
that lifted money and other soldier
give your mom chicken legs
you don't have any money
so what else is no all right all right
I made a mistake after all a man is
entitled go on this is your story i'll
wait for the punch
don't get smart with me girlie i'll have
you know that in my shop in the cash
register i'm having the total daze three
seats which is summing up to more than
nine dollars
you'll bring the rest of the food then
I'll go to the shop and get the money
you are playing my favorite soul
now look here buster one of you is gonna
go down right now and get the loo
while the other one stays here until the
first one gets back if you get what I
mean
05 in this fence ish min see restaurant
you're holding hostages right all right
excellent you eat up Audrey
I'll be back in a flash with the cash
like it
yeah
- big charlie
well
yeah
haha
the flash now right
bring me whiskey rom wine gin bourbon
God try
tequila sake Manischewitz did you bring
the money
don't mock me with the money i got to
get drunk how
what for damn take it from me anything
bring me everything crème de means
everything you got ok
what happened don't panic Oh gross i
could handle don't ask why don't you
tell me maybe I could help help you
couldn't try and eat something it will
come your aggravation
my own shop order you wouldn't believe
it should break up
tell me all right i'll tell you tomorrow
right after i am telling the police but
must make didn't come to the police if
he had that might have been the finish
of the unhappy story
it was not
ok
yeah
tell you you wouldn't be interested in
selling a happy just to this place after
we talked to the committee and they said
we could use your father on the float
and guess what i'm going to feature
Audrey's you out on this picture you can
put you how the people that need it out
you talk to people and we're gonna have
the big part of it open so she can send
the grave with your credit center should
be so cute
oh you can just hear the girls all my
night job now
see more talk on me to think what do you
want to talk about dead plans is that a
nice subject for the talk
plant the plant is great it's it's four
times bigger than it was yesterday I saw
how come to plan does not so big
I don't know but look at all the people
out there
the only been open i have power we
already done seven dollars worth of
business
85 that looks to bore you gave this plan
to fence in a more gradual you but I
want to know right now what they're just
people call it
well it's a cross between a Butterworth
and a Venus Fly train is flytrap and
both of the habits of this Venus flytrap
well the book says he eats insects and
eat some three times in its life and
then it's foreground excellent
and how many times is this money once or
twice
you don't remember well this is kind of
an unusual type flytrap
that is a possibility I may never eat
again I don't see how it could get any
bigger then you think it don't need any
more flies
yeah
my tooth is just killing me all right
excellent
you run along to the dentist I'll take
care of things here
thanks but we've got to order more
flowers
making lots of money
yeah
I want you to keep your fill of the date
that be
then why you snivelling daughter and I'm
glad I heard you I'm glad I'm glad to
see more
am I got a bad tooth now I thought this
was the man's well sing off from back
you bad dog you get in there you are the
young man ruined my gladiolas own shadow
guess what my to stop tearing is I know
shut up & open up huh does that hurt
yeah good you haven't felt anything yet
you can cut our hair
Seymour was the dentist and you were me
up like that to look at
that's the lag might but don't worry
it's going to be an easy one see more I
won't even use novocaine a broken mirror
in my mouth don't tell me about it
stupid just swallow it
I let's sing see more
so you'll have this one and this one and
that one and I have to have this one
time only 12 single who is the dentist
here you or me are you practicing
dentistry without a license
alright see
oh don't look at that would you look at
that
see more I didn't know you were an elk
you know I can't for the assistant so I
get this ready
instant mix doesn't last very long but
it tastes good
e alright see mom
stay away from me sing all nighter kill
me
a duel haha
ok
it starts off huh
just a minute
yes I see it is
I you can come in now
my name is Wilberforce Wilberforce what
just Wilberforce
my first name is will be my last name is
for soup
I don't have a middle name well you have
an appointment may be no but you were
very highly recommended to me by one of
your patients and this is as she by do a
lot of undertaking for her relatives
well as you can see i have a customer
now and I'm all booked up for the rest
of the day so you have to come back
tomorrow
all I couldn't do that I have three or
four abscesses a touch of pyria nine or
ten cavities
I lost my pivot tooth and I'm in
terrible pain
I can help you today oh that's all right
I'll just wait outside
the patient came to me with the large
hole in his abdomen caused by a fire
poker used on him by his wife he almost
bled to death and gangrene had set in
I didn't give me much of a chance there
were other complications
the man had cancer tuberculosis and
leprosy and it touches the grip
I decided to operate my my patient just
left
if you could come in now oh goody
I didn't see the other man leave
he went out the back door you know most
people don't like to go to the dentist
but I rather enjoy it myself
don't you get it I mean there's such
there's a real feeling of growth of of
progress when that old drill goes in
I mean I'd almost rather go to the
dentist than anywhere wouldn't you
yeah now I don't know became it dulls
the senses
this is gonna hurt you more than ilysm
is oh goody goody here it comes
oh my god don't stop now
well I made a lot of holes and not going
to fill it up with this his silver stuff
aren't you gonna pull any well I'll go
on
well your mouth
yeah
well dr. far it's been quite an
afternoon
I can truly say I've never enjoyed
myself so much i'll recommend you to all
my friends
thank you by my now
yeah
take it easy track you know what do you
think I'm carrying here my dirty laundry
yeah
I'm coming I'm coming already
this should be enough for anybody
welcome by dr. far we may have been a
crummy that just but you were a nice
fellow
I never meant to kill anybody in my
whole life I've killed two in the last
two days
he asked for coming at me with that
knife all unvoyage dr. far one thing
else in the morning
yeah
ok
major money Frank House why Frank
not bad Joe glad to hear kids lost more
than yesterday
lost 18 that happen playing matches the
brakes a song and a strange one here
railroad people say the last one of the
best detectives the other night well
done with the arts is watching the
refrigerator cars refrigerator cars
I Steve's what happened don't know
vanished let on tracks loose know
anything else
Dennis farm and missing clothes but in
office where skid row ideas not check it
out
yeah
now we were on the case officer ranks to
leave me
my name is think sergeant Joe faked
I don't think
- oh boy look at that everybody
oh my god ain't it something yeah i
think that you see larger you don't have
to kiss me
don't you like me to kiss you yeah but
you don't like to kiss me I should night
nobody else ever did well I do like to
do you do you really do you like to kiss
me
I do would you like to kiss me again ok
the blend
oh boy you kiss good Audrey well I guess
they just have a good kisser haha hard
is it to do
would you like to go out on a date with
me some night Fred most sure what seemed
like any time tonight
ok Oh what about the plant
we got the last of flowers for the float
for the Rose Parade
I can't talk to you now girls took on
all three
we got the last with the float ok let's
take a look at it ok
I what's cooking look at my plant my
large one
yeah
mr. shaver what's no I got terrible news
nike think it's just a little boy
oh that's too bad I didn't happen he was
playing with matches
would you like to buy maybe some flowers
about 57 foot well I'll get them for you
look at my plan I'm looking and then
grab as much labour government motion to
grab this isn't that's my name
just want to ask you a few questions
questions asked me just ask your
questions and I didn't do it
do what whatever ever see this man man
see pictures are done
why you so nervous got a guilty
conscience know why sure that i receive
this man man see the baby picture
dr. slob so you know my dentist state
heat maybe did something disappeared
blood in his office the other man - but
the railroad tracks and few spare parts
of that the hot doctor five is minded
easy
you know who knows not me what do you
think he doesn't know anything
ok much me if you hear anything about
these men call our office which would
all be led to cooperate with the police
for City terrible what happened to you
for Frankie
those are the breaks
all right Seymour now you tell me if
that plan is finish all grown up
he's finish all growing up you wouldn't
get your father probably came we did
it's a figure of speech look I can't
stand anymore that plant
it's growing me out of house and home
then going to grow anymore I promise
how can you be so sure three times
already
who I mean what did it eat this time but
about a million Japanese beetles so
don't need no more for some kind of a
commitment
guys I think it's important excellent
by the by I understand you want to take
all three out on a date tonight
that's very good with me because i am
staying to keep an eye on that mature
gonna plant
we can't go tonight remark i just
remembered i don't have any money
well that's okay we could take a walk
along the ocean is something I got a
great idea
we can eat dinner at my house my mom's a
great cook
oh boy i'll call later and tell her
oh you like
I neither like nor dislike anything my
goodness
I happen to represent the society of
Simon flower observers of Southern
California
how about that tell me who created this
magnificent blue
I did me and put my journey and be seen
more crowd . with a que el boy girl boy
raised in the coffee can
this but tell me mr. crowd . it is this
a freak or canmore be raised from the
seed we should live so long I don't
think they're going to be any more missa
wish to anger
mrs. Hortense pushed Wanga I think this
is going to be the only one mrs. fish
swinger wish to anger wish to anger
that's probably an adjustable anyway
at any rate i have the honor to tell you
the more curl . that you have been
selected to receive the annual trophy of
the Society of silent flower observers
of Southern California a trophy may
search is justice
but tell me when do you suppose those
large buds will open
well according to what the book says
about the plants that I crossed they
should open day after tomorrow with
sunset
ah very well then I shall return at that
time to present the trophy
good
mark
oh I'm gonna get a trophy
I'm so proud of you no trouble to put it
on the right
oh boy don't look at me I'm a terrible
sight
I'm a complete Sea Hag she always says
it but it's true
I haven't been feeling very well lately
oh gee this is my mom went perfect curl
blind modest is already full quite
she's my girl hi Audrey you have you
here and I could eat a hair Oh what's
the grind down and I'll go get the first
course 2013
you're going to take your sweater
never mind that
that's what will not try this
it tastes like cough syrup
dr. friends called syrup a toast
so I be doing you know Audrey senior
yeah
you clocking you tonight I keep an eye
on you I don't let nobody get near you
so I don't have to like it but little
flavoring
what do you guys think you should look
good by candlelight
do I really see more yeah your yard
try to smell the difference is different
kind of oil isn't it
cod liver oil wonderful for the colon
and that's awful power top
ok
yeah
opportunities
I didn't get it may I i I'd it all right
one talking plans we got no hungry and
other fine kettle of fish
who would you like to have tonight
you look very nurse we not only got a
talking plan we got one that makes it
smart cracks will you listen to me your
botanical bomb food you wouldn't get not
from gravis mushnick starters
excellent you would unpopulated all Skid
Row
well you can forget about it
you wouldn't get fed from gravis
mushnick tonight
good night
yeah
I kind of like this jaan mein it taste a
little bitter
it's because it's made of chinese herbs
and its flavored with akram elias and
epsom salts or another cooking a whole
world like my mom
that's what your old man said before the
last ran out of me you know if you're
going to be married you're gonna be a
good cook
maybe you could teach me music Mary
he hasn't asked me yet go ahead and pour
ce mark Guiliana to get married here
boys got to go out and play around a
little bit
go out and i'm makin have a bowl team I
don't want to have a go i want to be
with Audrey know anymore
you promised you wouldn't get married he
bought me an iron long you've been three
the four years more than eight easy it
ain't easy some
yeah
here black has 13 jan 13 2 with
superstition
yeah
thank you come on their own truth mr.
i'm old and sick i wouldn't even apply
come out in the light i could see it
no it's not true
please please i'm only good obvious
wishing to get one month to kill me
where would you hide the body
don't worry I'm not going to see with
you and I should try to further I
something I never tried anything in my
life
i wouldn't try anything now you want my
money take it you want I should go out
and students are more that's all right
though i'll do it
thank you very much like your brand of
hospitality will excuse it is more on
hold four slots
we got about 30 bucks here
come on now where's the rest of it I
wasn't here this afternoon
it's all about 30,000 people in here
they must have spent the money where is
that in the world money that came in to
look on the plants a big connection or
three junior plant don't try to slow me
Jim 30,000 square didn't commit just
look for a plan i wanted but if that did
it
I don't got no money honestly believe me
okay let's try this one two three four
eyeing up no more money honest
all right try the other way around five
four three two
alright alright already ok big bad we're
in the plates
play
the big plans or richer
inside the big leagues
that's right inside how do you get it
open
just knock
yeah
in there in that inside in the bottom
I don't see anything way inside
yeah
what I did
I don't care about you got a date with
all three tonight I am no more sitting
up with that no good news plant but gee
mr. must make you don't have to sit up
with it anymore it's all grown up now
excellent smart guy how do you know it
don't be hungry no more
well because of the night you are
staying then the matter they're coming
in they're going to give you a trophy
and then after that we are getting read
once and for all for that plan
getting rid of it why don't ask why the
end into the garbage can
Aloha oh yes mrs. Shiva boy wonderful
class
that's all right on three I've got other
plans even more wonderful way I know you
will figure out what we're doing tonight
yeah we're going to place full of
beautiful flowers
you have to stay here yeah well never
mind we'll have a picnic
it'll be just like going to the country
oh boy
azalea for the armor and the 9000 yellow
months for the fruit for the border and
I the roses for the front right around
the bag
what do you mean you're going to a
picnic at night with their full chord
girl don't you like Audrey mom she's out
after your money
I don't have any money oh she's a smart
one
she latch on to young people get someone
then goodbye fortune but I've reason on
his girl and never trust a woman who
still healthy probably had a bad called
a couple of weeks ago
Oh cold a puny cold why don't you get
yourself a real female with something
decent like when I mean you Cleo sister
or gold stones
maybe she could catch something like
that the only thing she'll catches you
and should take you off to some shady
sanitarium
leave me the chiropractors and faith
healers
I know when I'm not wanted Oh
g ma don't feel sorry for me
despite a nice web le somewhere curled
up and wait for the end of please don't
die - I get back with your ma I'll take
care of you I'll always take care of you
I promise
y GOG I never tasted food like this
before
peanut butter and jelly families that
butter and jelly what is a cure
nothing it's just the food what good is
it if it doesn't clear up pimples or
shrink your sinus tissues or something
just being silly see more summer
what do you want to be well I want to
grow things if I had a lot of money i go
to the South Seas where they grow the
most fabulous plants in the world that
sounds exciting
yeah I'd like to go to the South feet
- there's no reason why you couldn't go
would you take me with you see more
oh I couldn't very well go without you
our treat why not
because because I'm in love with you are
in love with you to see more
what'd you say
how I was just kidding I'm I didn't mean
why did you
you didn't even say that we just like
that I said it I said it
I'm looking right at you ventriloquist
you know what of entropy me
what do you feel all right well i don't
know i'm not sure
stop all this nonsense and kiss me i'm
dying from on some concrete something
that you forget about me
I'm sorry idea of me to gauge
you can't control yourself i'm going
home right from Charles and Audrey
please wait listen to me listen all the
nonsense i want to hear anymore you're
not
you tell me that you love me and then
you have like a complete idiot
please listen Audrey I'll be able to
explain everything soon
why can't you explain now because so
many things are so important
I want to marry you but I got to take
care of mom
well that plant in there is going to
make it all come true tomorrow they're
going to give me a trophy and I'll be
famous
I'll be a big botanist and then we can
go to the South Seas just like we
planned it all doesn't have anything to
do with what went on in there when
you're ready to come to a sense of see
more then i'll talk to you tonight see
more
yeah
I'm getting pretty tired of you I I
don't care what you need
look what you've done to me you not only
made a butcher out of me but you throw
my girl away shot bring on the food
don't tell me to shut up you shut up
hooray for a bunch of little seeds who
fit your high-class fertilizers and set
up all night with you when you were sick
nobody else would have done that for you
do you think anybody else would have
brought your human beings to eat it done
right they wouldn't
well I've helped you and you've helped
me now shut your trap and go to sleep
i'm tired
crowd fine
your I sleep
open your eyes now you will do as I say
follow me yes master you will go out and
find me some food
yes master i'll be gone waste no time
yeah
ok
and
yeah
my name is Leonardo fly
how's the rain on the roof bar
Master is hungry
yeah
hello
I got to find food from master food i
gotta find from master for master i
gotta find food
maybe I can help who are you my name is
Leonardo applied
I love you
Master wants food at the El go
wait the night is young so we master
doesn't eat goat
well what kind of food to see like
that's more like it
kiss me
what's the matter don't you like me to
Boni - Roni
nobody ever told me that people beef is
better than field
you're such a dodo what do you call this
chopped liver
haha
Master would like more fat speak for
yourself John
my name is Seymour
my name is Seymour that's my name too
are you interested are you just wasting
my time
I never thought anybody would volunteer
do you volunteer
sure I do all right if you sure you want
to volunteer
all right my place or yours I don't care
well flip a coin I don't have a coin
flip anything silly
well there's a rock
whether drive with
yeah
the search was narrowing and we knew
that soon we would have the killer
not that we had any more clues then
before we have to tell achieve something
I had that feeling in my bones that the
mystery was going to its climax
I was determined to be on here alright
out out nobody is in today we have a
special occasion for see more control .
which has invented a big plant
so I want everybody should please stay
out of the way we can I tell you this
business situation being a conductor in
our ever losing door i'll be glad when
this day is finished it's a celebration
they're presenting my son with the
trophy you know what he's gonna run away
from home
please don't look at me that way Audrey
I want to talk to you
I'm sorry Seymour don't understand you
I'll explain everything after the
ceremony your police what are you doing
here and there was something going on
here this even just always come by and
keep an eye on things
look we don't need no eyes kept on
running everything fighting fighting
power you visit arrived and sunset is
almost upon us
welcome ladies and gentlemen we are
honored for to have you still working on
the disappearances
we think they were murdered look here
young man that's no way to talk at a
time like this
let me see your time ya know what you
got
just the facts ma'am trench mouth and I
know I had it back and not mine but I
heard that looked into Frank
whatever you say Joe that mr. cowboy
the Sun is going down now and you do
think those bugs are going to open
I hope so because if they don't mr.
grill boy
we shall just have to present the award
at another time
always starting to hold on
yeah
first that is
isn't that the will come
yeah
what do you think Frank are all there
Joe
yes you're right mr. probably how do you
explain this
that's right officer he didn't mean to
kill them at my looks like they're
getting away show guess you're right
let's schedule
ok
oh now the flow to be perfect yeah
yeah
ok
you wouldn't find him here with the
toilets let's go back
yeah
start here at plant you messed up my own
life
I feel like you've never been before
yeah
better to give up Jersey you wouldn't
find him tonight
fuck the doors open Frank
he was such a good
Molly same heart
I didn't mean it
yeah