I have been hurt by others and I will
hurt their I will make them suffer like
i have suffering the words of a sadist
one of the most disruptive elements in
human society to have complete mastery
over another to make him a helpless
object to humiliate him to enslave to
inflict moral insanity on the innocent
that is his objective his twisted
pleasure
strange-looking place but I thought fuel
pump how long you think it'll take you
to think has to be replaced take about a
half an hour they have the part you
should have one with all these wrecks
around here it's back highways good for
time but have car trouble you got
problems we've had to happen I'm glad it
happen where it did and what it did I
didn't much relish the idea of being
stuck in those waffles they were lucky
another few miles we'd have been in
desert is it what you thought mr. Stiles
I'm afraid so can we still make the game
I've got 40 miles to go 1201 game
doesn't start til 130 we can still make
it or they have the pardon l if they
don't explain stuck wasn't sunday big
order one from lancaster people had run
this place
hello
you see when a player swats that's
what's the wall Doris bat the player
bats the ball gonna pay back the ball
and it goes over the fence that's a home
run I know but if no one can make him
out why does he have to run around the
bases because he has to that's the rules
he must touch every base would you like
a coke thank you
somebody could run off of the whole
place and the owner would never know it
so get sure from the looks of things
nothing right here worth taking it's a
wonderful game business that's all
everything is so dirty and greasy all
work isn't white code word miss page I
was in the army I had my fill of this
repairing tanks this prim and proper
shoulda known me then Doris page is a
sweet girl led the good math teacher a
little on the proving side perhaps my
boy am I the dead class calls him his
ice packs there was no reason why man
should have to run around the basis when
they can't get him out isn't that a
woman for you never seen a baseball game
and already she's changing the rules you
should go to a ball game with my wife
for I still think that's a silly rule
ever gonna see any baseball today
where's the guy that runs this place
hey what about some sorta
they must be around here someplace
doesn't seem likely they'd go away leave
everything wide open perhaps around in
back lovely hey anybody here hello
hello the pump has already been stripped
off that Chevy we might be a business
we got ourselves a fuel pump if it's any
good will that work on our car take a
few adjustments but you get a stelae
I'll borrow a few wrenches and will soon
be out of here just dial's of many
talents a fine young man be a lucky
woman that looks it hi mr. Oliver I do
believe you're playing cupid again
you're only young once miss page
where mr. Oliver you sound like an old
man well 52 yesterday I'd say you'd had
a fine and full life a nice home a
lovely wife two hands and children Carl
jr. graduates from West Point in two
weeks wife and I are going back to the
graduation guy really takes careless
I'll look around and see if I can find
it somebody I don't want to shock you
miss page but I'd rather not get my
shirt dirty oh really mr. Stiles I'm not
that stuffy I don't know Tata the same
school for over a year and it's still
miss page of mr. Stiles do you think
getting dorset sound a lot better I know
on its he'll be dead and Doris
just a snake in they shed this time of
year I can't stand snakes most people
can part of the country's loaded with me
equant I hear they get to be as much as
nine feet long I was certainly wrong
wasn't fine hello hello anybody here
hello
Doris
bed hello
hello
you never know he's the same history
teacher from old lancaster hi he really
cuts loose today he'll really be in his
glory with his red plan I know Edna told
me last night that he hadn't seen in
place since they left Cincinnati she
said ever since he got the tickets are
something going on here that just isn't
right settings for for the kitchen table
2 plates eaten from and two plates
untouched why still warm except for a
cat there's not a sign of life the
sooner we get out of here the better off
I'll feel
you
well
just keep working mr. because he gonna
fix your car dislike you intended young
man you have no right to take our cups
yeah what if I don't fix it you'll fix
you down right misty you better not take
too long either supposing i get a pic
what happened then mean my girl go away
Bobby how do we know you'll keep your
word looks like you're just gonna have
to take it ain't you missed it
ok
you
give me a wallet
there's not much but you're welcome to
it but we'll only school teachers young
man yeah that Judy we're only school
teachers we don't like school teachers
do with Judy Jesus think there's so much
smarter than everybody else
you have our money isn't that enough
what else do you what I'll just keep
working mr.
teachers used to call Judy dumb
make fun of it send a home from school
cried
they're a pretty good-sized boy I wonder
how tough you be without that gun oh you
wanted in real big talk is ain't you
mister all right big chocolate hand over
your wallet come on
piki there you pick it up
you real big man in front of your lady
friend I'm not sure we're just how big
you really are for down that gun and
I'll show you how big you are I'm giving
you three seconds mr. to do what I say
I'm saying you pick up that wallet one
to do with his head
uh yeah you put it on the fender or do
you want the good huh you up again
undefended
big man and I get you got you too big
you really was started working
may I get some water this poor man is
being blinded by his own blood
don't you even have a decency to let me
care for this man what kind of a person
are you do you enjoy hurting others
seeing them in pain now how can you be
so inhuman
how is he all right I know it must hurt
Cashner's cheek isn't too bad that's a
cuddle reside what stop bleeding he
might bleed to death known outdoors you
can't be that what do you think you're
going the man needs help he's gonna get
it if you want this car fixed
he's going to be all right Doris
you're lucky Carl a little more to the
right you wouldn't be here if we can get
you some water in the shade we can stop
the bleeding what about muddiness man
get the shade mm-hmm how can you be so
cruel you get back in that car he won't
be needing nothing
oh by all means enjoy your lovemaking
but the least you can do is allow a
suffering man a little water carrying on
like that one you're no more than an
animal
you got your dirty hands off me you
leave her alone ago out the car fixed
and he won't fix it unless you let us
get some water there's a pump by the
house you can working in a car mr. and
you who here
shoot if they move Judy if I hear a shot
your girlfriend is dead don't get no
ideas Judy don't know how to use a gun
I wonder I wonder why he changed his
mind ed I don't like this I know
something else you won't like Carl
remember reading last week about those
brutal killings and Arizona
you
you please let me by
why are you putting us through this
torch you have our money and you're
taking our car isn't that enough you
keep your dirty hands off me you think
you so much better than me you kind all
think that way you called me in human
all right I apologize I shouldn't have
said that now will you let me go call me
an animal I'm sorry I'm sorry I said
those things now can I go you're sorry
but you still think it you think I'm
dirt you think Judy's dirt you'll always
think it so you don't think no more your
kind means nothing yeah yeah nothing
what are you scream maybe the big talker
come and help you maybe miss pretty good
good still think she's so much better
than me he's a few to be touched by dead
huh goody good food to taste it taste
the dirt tasty
it's good to do thank you so much now uh
she
one being touched by to it
ok
yea what did he do to you John all right
Tolliver it's hard
get back to work you want that car fixed
you can do it yourself jaffna be the big
man again you're the big man Tibbs
that's name isn't it Charlie Tibbs the
big man who killed seven people made
them get on their knees and shot them in
the head paper calls you a thrill killer
must be a real thrill to wipe out a
family of five how many thrilled to be
ahead since you're left Arizona what
about that people here did you kill them
too how long do you think you can keep
getting away with his son The Lost bound
to catch up with you sooner or later the
law has ways of handling murders please
don't antagonize him anymore what's
going to happen to you Kenny but it was
about to get I'll blow their brains out
listen big man you get back to fixing
that car you gonna be a big dead man
fast
all of a sudden everybody's becoming a
big talk didn't kind of breathe
nobody wants to talk no more Judy
I want to get my goody bag
judo give me a soda
just little target practice
shake bottle
they're going to do something terrible I
just know it
you
get it
were there what are you gonna do shut up
move that's far enough down on your
knees on your knees seeing is how you
like to talk go ahead and come talk all
you want as soon as I finish this you
gonna be through talking
school be out for you teach
better start talking mr. the time's
running out you can't shoot me like this
for no reason for nothing surely blowing
my head off can't give you a thrill
is it money you need I have close to
twenty three hundred dollars in the bank
tomorrow you can call my wife sure give
it to you all of it you and your
girlfriend could have a lot of fun on 23
hundred dollars she sure is talking a
lot different than he did a while ago
ne2d you have a father told you would
you want someone doing this to him hmm
think of your own father in my place or
yours save your breath on her mr. I'm
the only thing in the world she has her
old man is dead and her old lady's a
drug young lady can't you realize this
is wrong you love him don't you you know
what it is to be around someone you love
and who loves you I have loved ones to
daughter a little older than you sanober
is age
please I beg have you talked to your
boyfriend tell him this is rock tell him
please my god Joe there with you any
feelings at all
at you understand look at him squirm
Judy they all alike is this yellow
illegal
you
you can wipe out an asthma hit like this
not like this can you watch and you
can't let him do this maybe he'll listen
to you talk to him and dog to him pick
somebody do something lemme won't take
the car don't let him do it if you want
the car pick maybe the big man was to
take your place he says one more would
he will what about it big made you feel
like talking
maybe miss good good was to take his
place
i guess nobody wants to take your place
mr.
schools that teach you though not me hey
shut up bruegger's do you coward that's
me course you're gonna get us bull shots
I don't get why did you go ahead and so
forth you gon gon shoot
in another couple of minutes I'll have
to pump out shut up it won't take very
long to put it another car I said shut
up you're gonna need that card out I'm
the only one that can fix it I'd waiting
too long
Judy go get me a soda and then fight you
Edna whole anybody be able to tell his
sons graduation Doris believe me I feel
as badly as you did nothing can bring
him back we rely we've got to think of
ourselves now do you think I wanted to
stand there watch him die what could I
do what could anyone have done you can't
reason with that kid he wants blood
doors and nobody's gonna talk him out of
it don't you understand what we're
dealing with he's a psycho Doris well
should I have taken his place without a
major feel better what would you be
saying to Carl if it was me lying over
there
forget it it's a shame after the way I
didn't was nothing we could do
why don't we just run high we use only a
few yards from here he cut us down
before we got five feet I had died
running before I get on my knees like I
can still see I'm drinking
maybe a car come by and stop your doors
maybe your car will pull it pull in they
won't know you kill them in us too
please maybe the police will pass by
they do patrol this highway they will
they will sure
you find a way to make them stop it
Doris miracles do happen but you can't
count on I'm sorry now listen I gotta
try to find out how many more shots he
has left or if he has reloaded or not
how will we find out four shots we know
that leaves four he probably shot the
people here to there must have been to
remember what Carl told us about the
settings in the kitchen yes two bites
eaten from and to place untouched Tibbs
musta surprised in wild reading never to
fright tea while those tours stuffing
themselves be shot then that leaves two
shots I certainly didn't walk here from
Arizona maybe shot someone else and if
he hasn't reloaded
go ahead and talk miss it he talked all
you one you thinking somebody's gonna
save you why should I fix a car if
you're gonna kill us anyhow you fix it
does that let you live a little longer
like back there I know G was stolen if
you want to pitch a guy you die right
now you want this car tips who are you
fooling well you can kill us but you'll
be stranded that's a road in it well
there's a road there's cars somebody
will pick us up they Oh is hair said how
he got here from Arizona sailor pig he
says I've already taken daddy's a real
lover Judy suppose you shot him too nah
I just cut his throat why haven't you
still got his car ran out of gas last
night is she asking a lot of questions
mr. did you wait and ask all you want
how does it get here a farmer picked
yourself his old crate broke down up the
road apiece bed I was beginning to like
that old codger shoot him too he sure
prayed when he wears duty remember he
reach for the sky and talk to the lordy
Lord then you shot him yeah right
between the eyes
what about the two people you shot here
did they pray to you must think I'm dumb
mr. don't know nothing you gotten
bullets can't all you want i can count
to you know i only fired seven shots
nobody got one bullet left unless i
reloaded how many pull this to ahem left
you to be mad come on no open its gold
hmm come on maybe the guns empty come on
Miss time giving you chance come on come
on mr. you'll get the good what's the
man your friend
you had a chance mister you should have
taken it you ain't gonna get no more see
I yella be our duty friend of an empty
good Big Talk
they're getting ready to do something
you Oh
please they're coming with style I told
you they would
they were coming after you they're
coming after you you hear me you you
you're not going to kill anymore yours
getting back back or to you right now do
the same oh over there but out flat out
stop
you go get another one you find out what
noise new MIDI friend dies she brought a
site she needs one noise you slit her
throat
hi whoa son
sure a scorcher sure is
don't recall having seen you around here
before son friend of the family just
talked to Milt son in town about an hour
ago funny being the talker he is didn't
mention anything about visitors uh he
just left for I got in
Lancaster huh yeah didn't working in the
car coupon trouble mine went out only
last week you know Jenna costs over 30
bucks to get it fixed boy what a crook
that guy was look something locks 45
clip
where is melt I'll back someplace
well you can get more parts out of a car
than the factory put in it yeah here can
get out
I told you to keep quiet sure know what
I told you
get moving
Oh
I told you nobody could help you you're
gonna have every officer in California
looking for you they don't scare me
nobody scares me I'm gonna give you a
choice big man you die now or you fix it
god I'll give you 15 minutes to fix it
why should I fix it you'll only kill us
when i get done i'm giving you 15 more
minutes of life mr. if you don't want it
I'll blow your head off right now there
is two it's one o'clock you got until
115 you started working
mmm
who'd ever believe something like this
how could he shoot two officers they
were two of them to love them Judy give
me that gun
15 minutes what are we going to do all
units all units be on the alert for to
Arizona murder suspect believed to be in
California possibly driving a green 1958
Ford sedan license number marry Nora for
693 suspect hitch a ride with the driver
of this car a sailor and route to san
diego the sailor was found murdered two
miles east of needles approximately
ten-thirty this date tips Charles a male
Caucasian age 20 light brown hair blue
eyes height 61 wait approximately 180
pounds fair complexion wearing Levi
jacket and pants when last seen this
suspect is armed and to be considered
extremely dangerous in company with
suspect number one is Bradshaw Judy
female Caucasian age 18 black hair blue
eyes I'd approximately 54 weight
approximately 100 pounds dark complexion
wearing a yellow flowered dress when
last seen
hey it's lonely that radio collar cum
two minutes earlier gods do something
looks like we'll have to run part
would closer
getting funny I got an idea it may not
work but at least it's a chance it's
obviously doesn't know much about cars
here don't look but I get the pub that
I'll ask you to get the car and started
leave it in neutral I'll race the motor
from here when I give you the first
signal uh I'll scratch my shoulder when
I do you shift into drive and push down
on the brake got that yes
i'll give you the second thing huh a
wink hold on tight because i'll be
pulling the gas pedal to the floor board
i'm gonna try to lure him in front of
the car yeah it's just a chance we might
not hit him but we can t least start him
and they give me the few seconds i need
let's just pray this doesn't kick out on
us what if it does
rotten fort
so chance we'll just have to take
you got 11 minutes
Doris
damn it
I can't fix the car with you starting it
member
this is thick woods bringing you music
from Dodger Stadium as we do every
Sunday preceding the ballgame talking
about baseball all those red hot
Cincinnati Reds are in town riding a
nine-game winning streak it's going to
be Bob Perkey going for the red and
Sandy Koufax for the Dodgers that should
be quite a pitcher's battle they're
still plenty of good teams to be had so
if you're not doing anything come out to
Dodger Stadium and see exciting National
League Baseball it's a beautiful day for
a ball game time is 1pm still time to
come on down and now stay tuned for
Dodger warm up
hmm we could just get them away from the
car long enough to you think all those
people laughing and belly so happy
that's I don't want to die don't want to
die oh I don't
four minutes
Doris get the car and started so I can
see the puffles pressure Doris get in
the car and started just a minute you
want the car to run I want to live those
extra few minutes now I have to check
the pup for pressure alright but it
better run good
started up
you ain't got much more time two minutes
how does it feel when your budget uh
right now
I think you yellow-bellied yeah what is
more words
get up
I said get out
move
you will think I'm stupid you tried
something
xochitl something I get nothing we're
pretty good at for the seconds ago you
muster did something like this pup has
been in a wreck Carver who knows how
long now sometimes they get clogged too
don't hold the pressure I should take it
out and clean it you eat that Thun for
this if not warning pressure needs to be
cleaned your time agent it won't take
very long we take your nothing out do
you think you're fooling me don't you
take it on earth about cause don't you
nothing right there that's a carburetor
the cock had written letters gas in it
all you gotta do is prime it now I seen
that done so you private
go on a gas pump over there
doors get in the car and started when I
tell you to nobody gets netcom at me why
gonna prime it somebody had to pump the
gas pedal just never you mind you just
put that gas in that cadre
Wow
ah
finally I I'll find you find you
you
Doris wrong
birth
Oh
doctor
you
ah
Wow
rookies that again yes I lined up once
more follow outside a curve ball just
missed the outside corner barely took
ball one strike was apparently say
incidentally there lives a good seats
here for you fans who enjoy the Dodgers
the Redlegs you're close by won't you
come on down you'll enjoy it here at
Dodger Stadium of gorgeous day shirt
sleeve crowd everybody having a
wonderful time okay we're set to go the
bases loaded bottom of the first inning
Ron fairly up their perky the great
pitcher of the Red Lake set to go he
faces him he has his sight there's the
windup dub hitch fairly belts it oh what
a Robeson back back back