Hi, babe.
- I have something for you.
- What is it?
- Just a little something.
Here you go.
Oh. Johnny, it's beautiful.
Thank you.
- You wait right here.
- Mmm.
- I'm gonna try it on right now.
- Mm-hmm.
Wow. You look so sexy, Lisa.
- Isn't it fabulous?
- I would do anything for my girl.
- Oh, hey, guys.
- Oh, hi, Denny.
- Wow. Look at you.
- It's from Johnny.
Anything for my princess.
- How much was it?
- Denny, don't ask a question like that.
Nice to see you, Denny.
I'm going to take a nap.
Can I go upstairs too?
Denny, I think I'm gonna join him.
I've got some candles upstairs.
You always think.
All right. I'm ready.
This is so great. I can't wait
for you to get it off of me.
Oh, yeah.
- You're in for it.
- Oh, yeah.
How much you pay for this dress?
Don't even ask.
Ooh.
Ouch.
Stop.
Stop. No, stop.
Get up.
Denny, do you have
something else to do?
I just like to watch you guys.
Oh, Denny, Denny. Denny boy.
Denny, two's great,
but three is a crowd.
- I get it. You guys wanna be alone.
- That's the idea.
Fine. I have homework to do anyway.
Bye, lovebirds.
- Bye, Denny.
Come here.
Oh, Lisa, you know. Oh, yeah.
It'd be a shame
Living in this world without you
There's nothing I
wouldn't do for you
You are my fantasy dream come true
When I see your face
It stirs up my emotions
Your style and grace
It inspires my devotion
There's nothing I
wouldn't do for you
You are my fantasy dream come true
Oh, oh
And I will stand in
the way of a bullet
I will run through
a forest of flames
I will climb
the highest of mountains
Just to show you I love you
I will
I will stand in the way of a bullet
I will run through
a forest of flames
I will climb
the highest of mountains
Just to show you I love you
I will
I will, I will
And I will stand in the way
of a bullet
I will run through
a forest of flames
I will climb
the highest of mountains
Just to show you I love you
I will
I will stand in the way of a bullet
- Oh.
- Mm.
Did you like last night?
Yes, I did.
Can I get you anything?
- Mm-mmm. I have to go now.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Hi, Mom. How are you?
I'm fine. How are you?
Hmm?
Okay. Let's go to the couch.
And we will sit down.
Now...
what's happening with you?
- Hmm?
- Nothin' much. Do you want some coffee?
What's wrong? Tell me.
I'm not feeling good today.
Well, why not?
I don't love him anymore.
Why don't you love him anymore?
Tell me.
He's so... boring.
You've known him for
over five years.
You're engaged.
You said you loved him.
He supports you.
He provides for you.
And, darling, you can't
support yourself.
He's a wonderful man, and
he loves you very much.
And his position is very secure.
And he told me he plans
to buy you a house.
That's why he's so boring.
- Well, what are you going to do?
- I don't know.
I don't mind living with him.
Well, you can't do that.
Have you talked to him about it?
No.
- I don't know what to do.
- He's a wonderful person.
And he's getting a
promotion very soon.
He bought you a car.
He bought you a ring, clothes-
whatever you wanted.
Now you wanna dump him.
That's not right.
I've always thought of
him as my son-in-law.
You should marry Johnny.
He would be good for you.
- I guess you're right about that.
- Of course I'm right.
I know men.
I wasn't born yesterday.
I'm glad you're listening
to your mother.
Nobody else listens to me.
You're probably right
about that, Mom.
Well, I'm glad you're
listening to your mother.
Listen, I've gotta go.
But you remember what
I told you, okay?
Mm-hmm.
Bye-bye, now.
Thanks, Mom.
- Hello?
- Hey, baby. How you doin'?
Oh, hey. How you doin'? Yeah,
I'm very busy. What's goin' on?
I just finished talking to my mom.
She gave me this big
lecture about Johnny.
- We'll talk about it later.
I told you I'm very busy.
- We'll talk about it now.
Whenever you say we'll talk
about it later, we never do.
I can't wait till later.
I wanna talk right now.
You owe me one anyway.
Okay. All right, what do
you want to talk about?
She's a stupid bitch.
She wants to control my life.
I'm not gonna put up with that.
I'm gonna do what I wanna
do, and that's it.
What do you think I should do?
Why do you ask me? You've been
very happy with Johnny.
What do you want me to say?
You should enjoy your life.
What's the problem?
Maybe you're right.
Can I see you tomorrow?
Okay. All right. How about noon?
- I'll be waiting for you. Bye.
- All right, see ya.
- Hi. How you doin'?
- Hi. I'm fine. Come in.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
It's hot in here.
- Do you mind?
- No.
I mean, the candles...
the music, the sexy dress.
I mean, what's goin' on here?
I like you very much, lover boy.
What are you doin' this for?
What's the matter?
Don't you like me?
I'm your girl.
Johnny's my best friend.
You're gonna be married
next month. Come on.
Forget... about Johnny.
This is between you... and me.
I don't think so.
I-I'm leaving now.
Please don't leave.
I need you. I love you.
I don't wanna get married anymore.
I don't love Johnny.
I dream about you.
I need you to make love to me.
I don't think so.
Everything's gonna be fine.
I promise.
Oh. Oh, yeah.
Your touch
Pulling fire out of me
Like a wave crashing on the sea
Your kiss
As gentle as a summer breeze
Your love is what I
need to set me free
A rose
Is what
You are
To me
The smell
Of wonders
Oh, so sweet
- You are
- Oh, Lisa.
- A rose
- A rose to me
- To me, to me
- To me
- You are
- My rose
- My rose, my rose
- Baby
- Baby, baby, baby
- You are
- A rose
A rose to me
- To me, to me
- Yes, you are
- You are
- My rose
- Baby
- Yes, you are
Oh, yes.
You are my rose
You are my rose You are my rose
God. Why did you do this to me?
Why?
Johnny's my best friend.
Didn't you enjoy it?
That's not the point.
I love you, Mark.
Look, you're very attractive.
All right? You're beautiful.
But we can't do this anymore.
I can't hurt Johnny.
I know.
He's your best friend.
Hey. This'll be our secret.
Mmm.
- Hi.
- Can I help you?
Yeah. Can I have a dozen
red roses, please?
Oh, hi, Johnny.
I didn't know it was you.
- Here you go.
- That's me. How much is it?
- It'll be $18.
- Here you go. Keep the change.
- Hi, doggy.
- You're my favorite customer.
- Thanks a lot. Bye.
- Bye-bye.
Yeah. Deliver it.
555-4828.
Half Canadian bacon
with pineapple...
half artichoke with pesto,
and light on the cheese.
Thanks.
Who is it?
Denny.
- Hey, Denny. How are you doing?
- I'm fine. What's new?
Actually, I'm really busy.
Do you want something to drink?
No, thanks. I just
wanna talk to Johnny.
You look beautiful today.
- Can I kiss you?
- You are such a little brat.
I'm just kidding.
I love you and Johnny.
Okay, okay. Johnny's gonna
be here any minute.
- You can wait if you want.
- Mm, I gotta go.
- You'll tell him I stopped by.
- Of course I will.
- Bye.
- Bye, Denny.
Hi, babe. These are for you.
Thanks, honey. They're beautiful.
- Did you get your promotion?
- Nah.
You didn't get it, did you?
That son of a bitch told me that I
would get it within three months.
I saved them bundles. They're crazy.
I don't think I will ever get it.
They betrayed me. They
didn't keep their promise.
They tricked me, and I
don't care anymore.
Did you tell them how
much you save them?
Of course. What do you think?
They already put my ideas into practice.
The bank saves money, and they
are using me. And I am the fool.
I still love you.
- You're the only one who does.
- At least you have friends.
I didn't get any calls today.
You're right. The computer
business is too competitive.
Do you want me to order a pizza?
- Whatever. I don't care.
- I already ordered a pizza.
You think about everything.
What's the matter? You all right?
It's just a lousy promotion.
You know what you need?
You need a drink.
I don't drink. You know that.
Don't worry about it.
It's good for you.
You must be crazy.
I can't drink this.
If you love me, you'll drink this.
You're right. It tastes good.
I know. I am right.
Don't worry about those fuckers.
You're a good man.
Drink, and let's have some fun.
Mmm!
Oh!
You have nice legs, Lisa.
And you have nice pecs.
I'm tired. I'm wasted.
I love you, darling.
Come on. Make love to me.
Come on. You owe me one.
I love you, Lisa.
I love you, Johnny.
Mm.
I see you walkin' by, yeah
I hear your lullaby
It seems to reel me in
Yeah, yeah
You really got me good from
From just one little look now
All my mind can do is spin
I'm goin' crazy crazy
thinkin' about you
Crazy, so crazy about you
Crazy, wantin' you with me
I'm goin' crazy crazy
thinkin' about you
Crazy, so crazy about you
I need you here with me
So, I'm organizing a party
for Johnny's birthday.
- Can you come?
- When is it?
Next Friday at 6:00.
It's a surprise.
- Oh.
- You can bring someone if you want.
Well, sure, I can come, but I
don't know if I'll bring anybody.
Oh, that jerk, Harold.
He wants me to give him
a share of my house.
That house belongs to me.
He has no right.
I am not giving him a penny.
- Who does he think he is?
- He's your brother.
He is always bugging
me about my house.
Fifteen years ago, we agreed
that house belongs to me.
Now the value of the house is going
up, and he's seeing dollar signs.
Everything goes wrong at once.
- Nobody wants to help me, and I'm dying.
- You're not dying, Mom.
I got the results of the test back.
I definitely have breast cancer.
Look, don't worry about it.
Everything will be fine.
- Mm.
- They're curing lots of people every day.
I'm sure I'll be all right.
Oh. I heard Edward
is talking about me.
He is a hateful man. Oh, I'm
so glad I divorced him.
Look, don't worry about it.
You just concentrate on getting well.
Well, at least you have a good man.
You're wrong. Mom, he's
not what you think he is.
He didn't get his promotion,
and he got drunk last night.
And he hit me.
Johnny doesn't drink. What
are you talking about?
He did last night, and I
don't love him anymore.
Johnny is your financial security.
You can't afford to ignore this.
Yeah, okay, Mom.
Can I just talk to you later?
You don't want to talk to me.
I just got done talking
with a client...
and I have to get
ready to meet him.
- Can I just talk to you later?
- Okay.
I will see you later.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
How much time do we have?
I don't know. Uh, couple hours.
At least.
Well, let's have some fun.
Did you, uh, know...
that chocolate is
the symbol of love?
Feed me.
Yum.
That's delicious.
Arms up.
Chocolate is a symbol of love.
Hello?
What are these
characters doing here?
- They like to come here to do their homework.
- What homework?
Mom, this is Michelle's
boyfriend, Mike.
Mike, this is my mother.
- It's a pleasure to meet you.
- Mm.
Uh-huh.
Oh.
All that shopping wore me out.
- Hey, Lisa.
- Hey, Denny.
Denny, this is my mom.
Mom, this is Denny.
How many people come in and out
of this apartment every day?
This is worse than
Grand Central Station.
- I just need to borrow some sugar.
- Help yourself, Denny.
I also need a cup of flour and
a half a stick of butter.
- Doesn't your home have a kitchen?
- I'll come back later.
- Tell me, what does Denny do?
- Johnny wanted to adopt Denny.
It's really a tragedy how many
kids out there don't have parents.
When Denny turned 18, Johnny found him
a little apartment in this building...
and he's paying for it until
he graduates from school.
Johnny really loves Denny even
though he doesn't say it much.
He's, like, a father figure to him.
I told you, Mom.Johnny is very
caring about the people in his life.
And he gave Denny his own
set of keys to our place.
Please, don't hurt Johnny.
Now, if you really don't love him,
so be it. But you should tell him.
I forgot my, uh, book.
Oh! What-What's this?
Oh. That's-That's nothing. Really.
Homework.
Don't worry about it.
If I were a burglar, you
would be my best friend.
Look, I don't wanna talk about it.
You know I worry about you.
- Oh. I have to go home.
- Okay, Mom.
Bye-bye.
Oh, my God.
Hey, Denny.
Chris-R. I've been lookin' for you.
Yeah, sure you have.
You have my money, right?
Yeah. It's comin'. It'll
be here in a few minutes.
What do you mean
it's coming, Denny?
Where's... my money?
Okay. Just-Just give
me five minutes.
- Just give me five.
- Five minutes?
You want five fuckin'
minutes, Denny?
You know what? I haven't
got five fucking minutes!
I'm gonna ask you again, Denny.
- Where's my money?
- I don't have anything.
Where's my money, Denny?
Where's my fucking money, Denny?
- What did you do with my fucking money?
- I swear to God. It's coming.
- Where's my fuckin' money, Denny?
- Put the gun down.!
My fucking money.!
Where's my fucking money, Denny?
What's with this guy? Get off!
You're fuckin' dead, Denny!
What's going on here?
Somebody help!
- Let's take him to the police.
- You're fucking dead!
Denny. Are you okay?
- What did that man want from you?
- Nothing.
Oh, that was not nothing.
- Tell me everything.
- You have no idea what kind of
trouble you're in here, do you?
- I owe him some money.
- What kind of money?
- Everything is okay. He's gone.
- Everything is not okay.
Denny, that is a dangerous man.
Just calm down. He's going to jail.
- Denny, what kind of money? Just tell me!
- What do you need money for?
Mom, please! Denny's
with me and Johnny!
A man like that,
with a gun. My God!
Denny, look at me in the
eyes and tell me the truth.
- We're your friends.
- I bought some drugs off of him.
Things got mixed up. I
didn't mean this to happen.
- Denny!
- And I don't have them anymore.
- What kind of drugs, Denny?
- It doesn't matter. I don't have them anymore.
It doesn't matter? How in the hell
did you get involved with drugs?
Were you giving them to him?
Selling them to him?
- Where in the hell did you meet that man?
- What kind of drugs do you take?
- It's nothing like that.
- What the hell is wrong with you?
I just needed some money
to pay off some stuff.
How much do you have to give him?
- This is not the way you make money.
- How much?
Stop ganging up on me!
Well, it is time somebody ganged
up on you. For God's sake!
A man like that! Where in the hell
did you meet a man like that?
- It doesn't matter.
- It matters a great deal.
A man holds a gun on you. You almost got
killed. You expect me to forget that?
You're not my fucking mother!
- You listen to me, little boy!
- No, no! No, don't!
Somebody had better do
something around here.
It's okay.
Are you okay, Denny?
- I'm okay. I'm okay.
- Are you okay?
What's okay? He's taking drugs.
- Come on, stop. It was a mistake.
- A mistake. That he takes drugs.
- Let's go home.
- Come on. It's clear.
- What's clear? I am going to call the police.
- Mom, stop.
- It was Denny's mistake. Just stop.
- Let's go.
- Why did you do this? You know better, right?
- I'm sorry.
- Why?
You know better, Denny.
You almost got killed.
I'm sorry.
It won't happen again. I promise.
Denny, you know that
Johnny's like your father.
And we're your friends.
We're gonna help you.
Let's go home.
I miss you.
I just saw you. What
are you talking about?
I just wanted to hear
your sexy voice.
I keep thinking about your
strong hands around my body.
It excites me so much.
I love you.
Is Johnny there?
He's... in the shower.
I don't understand you.
Why do you do things like this?
Because I love you.
You just don't care, do you?
No, I do care.
But we agreed.
It's over between us.
I understand. It's our secret.
But I still have feelings for you.
- You just don't care.
- I do care.
I have to go now.
I'll see you later, darling.
- Don't call me that.
- Okay. Bye.
I did not hit her. It's not true.
It's bullshit! I did not
hit her. I did not.
Oh, hi, Mark.
- Hey, Johnny. What's up?
- I have a problem with Lisa.
- She said that I hit her.
- What?
- Well, did you?
- No. It's not true. Don't even ask.
- What's new with you?
- I'm just sittin' up here thinkin', you know.
- I got a question for you.
- Yeah?
You think girls like
to cheat like guys do?
What makes you say that?
I don't know.
I'm just-I'm just thinkin'.
I don't have to worry about that,
because Lisa's loyal to me.
Yeah, man, you never know.
People are very strange these days.
I used to know a girl.
She had a dozen guys.
One of 'em found out, beat her up so bad she
ended up in a hospital on Guerrero Street.
What a story, Mark.
You can say that again.
I'm so happy I have you as my best
friend, and I love Lisa so much.
Yeah, man. Yeah, you
are very lucky.
Maybe you should have a girl, Mark.
Yeah. Yeah, maybe you're right.
Maybe I have one already.
I don't know yet.
What happened?
Remember Betty? That's her name?
- Betty?
- Yeah.
Yeah, we don't see
each other anymore.
She wasn't any good in bed. She was
beautiful, but we had too many arguments.
That's too bad. My Lisa is
great when I can get it.
Aw, man. I just can't
figure women out.
Sometimes they're just too smart.
Sometimes they're flat-out stupid.
Other times they're just evil.
It seems to me like
you're the expert, Mark.
No, definitely not
an expert, Johnny.
What's bothering you, Mark?
- Nothin', man.
- Do you have some secrets?
- Forget it. Forget it, dude.
- Why don't you tell me?
- Is it some secret? Tell me.
- Forget it. I'll talk to you later.
Well, whatever.
- Hey, Johnny.
- Hi, Denny.
- What's wrong with Mark?
- He's cranky today.
Girl trouble, I guess.
- What's new with you?
- Not much.
- Still goin' to the movie tonight?
- Oh, sure. We are.
What kind of movie
are we gonna see?
Well, we'll see-
Denny, don't plan too much.
It may not come out right.
All right. Let's toss
the ball around.
Okay.
Gotta tell you about somethin'.
Shoot, Denny.
- It's about Lisa.
- Go on.
She's beautiful.
She looks great in her red dress.
- I think I'm in love with her.
- Go on.
I know she doesn't like me,
because sometimes she's mean to me.
But sometimes, when
I'm around her...
I feel like wantin' to kiss her
and tell her that I love her.
I don't know.
I'm just confused.
Denny, don't worry about that.
Lisa loves you, too, as a person...
as a human being, as a friend.
You know, people don't
have to say it.
They can feel it.
What do you mean?
You can love someone
deep inside your heart...
and there is nothing wrong with it.
If a lot of people
loved each other...
the world would be a
better place to live.
- Lisa's your future wife.
- Denny, don't worry about it.
You are part of our family,
and we love you very much.
And we'll help you anytime.
And Lisa loves you,
too, as a friend.
You are sort of like her son.
You mean you're not upset with me?
No, because I trust
you, and I trust Lisa.
- What about Elizabeth, huh?
- Well-
- I love her.
- Mm-hmm.
When I graduate from
college, get a good job...
I wanna marry her and
have kids with her.
- That's the idea.
- You're right.
Thanks for paying my tuition.
You're very welcome,
Denny, and keep in mind...
if you have any problems,
talk to me, and I will help you.
- Awesome. Thanks, Johnny.
- Let's go eat, huh?
Come on. Let's go.
Let's go, huh? I'm starving.
So, how's Johnny?
- He didn't get his promotion.
- Oh. Is he disappointed?
Quite a bit. He got
drunk last night.
- And he hit me.
- He hit you?
He didn't know what he was doing.
Are you okay?
- Well, I don't wanna marry him anymore.
- What?
Johnny's... okay, but I
found somebody else.
Lisa. This isn't right.
You're living with one guy, and
you're sleeping with another guy?
I'm doing what I wanna do.
Well, who is he?
His best friend.
And he lives in this building.
I can't believe you're
telling me this.
It's Mark, isn't it?
Lisa, you know what?
You're just thinking
about yourself.
Somebody's gonna get hurt.
You've gotta be honest with Johnny.
I can't do that.
He would be devastated.
If you care so much for
him, why cheat on him?
Look, I really don't
know what to do.
I love Mark.
I don't have any more
feelings for Johnny.
Johnny is so excited
about this wedding.
- I know.
- You've got to tell Johnny.
No guilt trips.
You don't feel guilty
about this at all?
No. I'm happy.
Something awful is gonna happen.
Please don't tell anybody.
Don't worry. You can trust me.
Your secret is safe with me.
Hello, Michelle. I heard you.
What secret?
- It's between us women.
- Hi, Johnny.
Did you get a new dress?
Um, well, I guess I'd
better be going.
Uh, I'll just talk
to you guys later?
Excuse me.
Lisa, remember what I told you.
- What's she talking about?
- It's girl talk. I just told you that.
I never hit you. You shouldn't
have any secrets from me.
I'm your future husband.
You sure about that?
Maybe I'll change my mind.
- Don't talk like that. What do you mean?
- What do you think?
Women change their
minds all the time.
You must be kidding, aren't you?
I don't wanna talk about it.
I'm gonna go upstairs and
wash up and go to bed.
How dare you talk to me like that?
- You should tell me everything.
- I can't talk right now.
Why, Lisa? Why, Lisa?
Please talk to me.
Please!
You're part of my life.
You're everything.
I could not go on
without you, Lisa.
You're scaring me.
You are lying! I never hit you!
You are tearing me apart, Lisa!
- Why are you so hysterical?
- Do you understand life?
Do you?
Don't worry about it.
Everything will be all right.
You drive me crazy.
Good night, Johnny.
Don't worry about it.
I still love you.
Good night, Lisa.
- Hey, Johnny. What's goin' on, man?
- Hi, Mike. What's new?
- How you doing?
- Um, actually, Johnny...
- I-I got a little bit of a tragedy on my hands.
- Uh-huh.
Yeah. Me and Michelle, we
were-we were makin' out.
Uh, at your place.
And, uh, Lisa and
Claudette sort of, uh...
walked in on us in
the middle of it.
- That's not the end of the story.
- Go on. I'm listening.
We're goin' at it, and, um, I get
out of there as fast as possible.
I get my pants, I get my
shirt, and I get outta there.
Then about halfway down the
stairs, I realize that I-
I have misplaced-
I've forgotten something.
- Mm-hmm.
- Uh, my underwear.
- I know.
- So, I come back to get it,
and I pretend I need a book.
I'm lookin' for my book. I reach in,
put the underwear in my pocket...
and sort of slide out real quick.
Claudette-She saw it
sticking out of my pocket.
She pulls it out, and she's
showing everybody me underwears.
You must be kidding.
Underwear-I got the picture.
- Yeah. I don't know what-
- That's life.
- Hey, Johnny. Hey, Mike.
- Oh, hey, Denny.
- What's up, buddy?
- Wanna play some football?
I gotta go see Michelle in a
little bit to make out with her.
- I'm sorry.
- Come on.
- Come on. Football.
- You think I'm-All right. Whatever.
- Let's go for it.
- I'm goin' out.
- All right.
- Yeah. Sorry you had to see that.
- I'm not sorry.
Your turn. Almost as much as I was.
- Studying, right?
- Come on, guys.
- I don't study like that.
- He doesn't.
- Denny, what's up?
- What's up, Mark?
- Hi, Mark.
- Catch it.
- Not too much. What about you guys?
- Uh-
- He's just tellin' us
about an underwear issue.
- Dude, it's-
- Underwear? What's that?
- It's embarrassing, man.
I don't wanna get into it.
- Underwear, man?
You okay?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- You sure?
- Uh-huh.
- Do you want to see a doctor?
- No. No, no, no.
I'm good. I'm all right. I'm fine.
- I'll take him home.
- Why don't you take him home?
Mike, listen. If you need anything,
call me. Anytime, all right?
- You gonna be all right?
- Yeah.
- See you guys.
Let's go home, Denny.
You look really tired today, Mom.
Are you feeling okay?
- I didn't get much sleep last night.
- Why not? What's wrong?
- You remember my friend, Shirley Hamilton?
- Uh-huh.
She wants to buy a new house...
and so I asked Johnny if he could
help her with the down payment.
All he can tell me is,
"It's an awkward situation."
I expected your husband to
be a little more generous.
- He's not my husband.
- I know.
But Johnny is part of our family.
Mom, I don't love Johnny anymore.
Ohh.
I don't even like him.
- I had sex with someone else.
- You can't be serious.
- You don't understand.
- Who?
Who is it?
- I don't wanna talk about it.
- You don't want to talk about it.
- Then why did you bring
it up in the first place?
- I don't know.
You don't know.
If you think I'm tired today,
wait till you see me tomorrow.
Coming to the party?
Sure. I suppose so.
How can they say this about me?
I don't believe it.
I'll show them.
I'll record everything.
I don't understand women.
Do you, Peter?
What man does?
- What's the problem?
- They never say what they mean.
And they always play games.
Okay, um, what do you mean?
I have a serious problem with Lisa.
Um, I don't think
she's faithful to me.
In fact, I know she isn't.
Lisa? Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure. I overheard a
conversation between Lisa and her mother.
What should I do, Peter?
- This is Lisa we're talking about?
- Yeah.
- I don't know what to say.
- But you are a psychologist.
Do you have some advice?
It's a complicated
situation, Johnny.
I mean, you're my friend, and I don't
wanna get between you and Lisa.
But look, if you want to,
you should confront her.
I can't confront her.
I want to give her a second chance.
After all, she's my future wife.
You know what they say-
Love is blind.
You got a lot of faith in Lisa.
Sometimes life gets complicated.
The unexpected can happen.
When it does, you just
gotta deal with it.
Did you hear the door?
Yeah. I did.
- Oh, hi, Mark. Come in.
- Oh, hey, Johnny.
Hey, Peter.
We're just talking about women.
Women, man. Women just confuse me.
I have a girl, but she's married.
She's very attractive.
It's just... It's driving me crazy.
Why didn't you mention this before?
Is it anyone I know?
- No, man. You don't know her.
- Can I meet her?
I don't think so.
It's an awkward situation.
You mean she's too old, or you think
I would take her away from you?
Huh?
No.
I have my own problems.
Tell me about your
problems, Johnny.
Peter, you always play
psychologist with us.
Look, I'm just your friend,
and I'm just worried about you.
Lisa's teasing me about whether we
are going to get married or not.
And we didn't make
love in a while...
and I don't know what to do.
You never really know. I mean-
Look, you should tell her
about your feelings. Okay?
You shouldn't hide 'em.
You two have been together forever.
- You can work out anything
as long as you talk about it.
- Not always.
People are people. Sometimes they
just can't see their own faults.
I'm thinking of moving to a bigger place,
man. I'm making some good money.
You should tell her the truth.
You're doing this for your girl, right?
You're right, Peter.
- Is she getting a divorce, Mark?
- You guys are too much.
Hey, are you running Bay
to Breakers this year?
- I am, sure.
- No, I'm not doing it this year.
Chicken, Peter.!
You're just a little chicken.!
Cheep! Cheep-cheep-cheep cheep!
Who are you calling a chicken?
I just don't like all the weirdos.
There's too many weirdos there.
I-I-I don't mind.
Mark, do you remember the one
with the big tits? The blondie one?
- How about the one with the
bridal gown, with the sign?
- Oh, yeah... "Can you marry me?"
I thought I would
take her up on it.
- I never ate so much.
- The barbecue chicken was delicious.
Rice. That was cool.
You guys prove my point-
You're both weird.
You guys wanna play cards?
No, we can't. I expect
Lisa any minute.
Come on, man. Who's the
king of the house?
You gotta establish these
guidelines before you get married.
How did you ever meet Lisa?
You never told us.
That's a very interesting story.
When I moved to San Francisco with
two suitcases, I didn't know anyone.
I have-I hit Y.M.C.A...
with a $2,000 check
which I couldn't cash.
- Why not?
- Well, because it was an out-of-state bank.
Anyway, I was working
as a busboy in a hotel...
and, uh-uh, she was sitting...
drinking her coffee.
She was so beautiful.
And I say "Hi" to her.
That's how we met.
So, what's the interesting part?
Well, the interesting part is that on
our first date, she paid for dinner.
- What? No tips from your job?
- Whatever.
Do you guys wanna eat something?
Hey, guys. What's going on?
- Oh, hey, Lisa.
- Hi, Lisa.
- Where's Johnny?
- In the kitchen.
I gotta go.
I didn't mean to chase you off.
Wish you'd stick around for a while.
I gotta work early.
See ya.
- Did you get your wedding gown yet?
- No. I've got plenty of time.
Are you sure you have plenty of time?
It's only a month away.
It'll be fine. What are
you so worried about?
Everything's okay.
Johnny doesn't seem very excited.
Is there a problem?
There's no problem. Why do you ask?
I just want you and
Johnny to be happy.
I am happy.
Look, Denny, I need to talk to
Johnny. Okay? I'll see you later.
- Okay. Tell him I said hello?
- Yeah.
Hey, Mark. What's up?
Oh, hey, Peter.
It's a good place to
think up here, isn't it?
What, man? You wanna
put me on the clock?
What the hell is that?
You want some? It's good, bro.
You know I don't smoke that stuff.
You look depressed.
I got this sick feeling
in my stomach, man.
I did something awful.
I don't think I can forgive myself.
Tell me about it.
I just feel like-like running...
killing myself.
Something crazy like that.
Why are you smoking that crap?
It's no wonder you can't think straight.
It's gonna screw with your head.
It's none of your business, man.
You think you know everything.
- You don't know shit.
- Wait a second. Who do you think you are?
You're acting like a kid.
Just grow up.
Who you calling a kid? Fuck you!
Just chill out, Mark.
I'm just trying to help.
You're having an affair
with Lisa, aren't you?
- Am I wrong?
- What?
What are you, nuts?
Sorry.
I'm sorry, man. Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Let's just talk about your problem.
- You sure you're okay?
- Yeah.
Goddamn it, man. Fuck!
Why do you want to
know my secret, man?
Well, you're right.
It's Lisa.
I don't know what to do, man.
I'm so depressed. It's all her fault.
She's such a manipulative bitch!
- How the hell did you let this happen?
- Fuck!
You know this is gonna ruin
your friendship with Johnny.
What were you thinking?
All right, you want my advice?
Sometimes life can
get complicated...
and you've gotta be responsible.
So you don't see Lisa again, and you
definitely don't sleep with her again.
Just find yourself another girl.
She's a sociopath.
She only cares about herself.
She can't love anyone.
Whatever, Peter. Come on.
Oh, thank you. Yeah. Thanks a lot.
Oh, hi, Denny.
Nice tux! You look great!
You look really handsome.
- Your wedding picture's gonna look great.
- Oh, thanks.
Hey, Peter. Come on in.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey, Peter. Come in.
- You look good too.
- Sit down.
- Whoa!
- Whoa.!
Hey, guys.
- You like it?
- Yeah. It looks good.
You look great. You look
like a baby-face now.
You guys wanna play some football?
In tuxes? No. You gotta be kidding.
- Come on, Mark. Let's do it.
- I'm up for it.
- Johnny?
- Ask Peter.
- Come on, Peter!
- No, I don't think so.
- Please?
- Nope.
- Come on!
- No.
- Cheep-cheep-cheep-cheep!
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
Catch, Johnny! Whoo!
Yeah! Nice snag!
All right, Peter!
Here we go, Mark!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
- Ohh!
- Yeah!
- Catch, Mark!
- Go.
Go deep!
Gee, Peter, you're clumsy.
All right, that's it. I'm done.
Great idea, Denny.
I'm gonna get a slice of
cheesecake and a bottle of water.
I'll have a large peanut butter whip
with extra whipped cream, please.
- All right.
- And I'll take some cheesecake and a coffee.
Okay. Have a seat. We'll
have that right out for you.
Hi. How you doing?
What would you like?
- Can I get a bagel and an Americana?
- Great. Sure.
I'm gonna get a slice of
cheesecake and a bottle of water.
Sounds good. Have a seat.
We'll have that right out for you.
- Hi, Susan.
- Hi, Johnny. How are you?
- Good to see you. What would you like?
- Hot chocolate, please.
- What size?
- Medium, please.
- How about you?
- I'll have the mint tea.
- Medium also?
- Yeah.
Go sit down. We'll be right there.
I'm so tired of girls' games.
What happened now, Mark?
Relationships never work.
I don't know why I waste my time.
What makes you say that?
It's not that easy, Johnny.
Well, you should be happy, Mark.
Yeah, I know. Life is too short.
- Oh, thank you, Susan.
- You're welcome.
How 'bout somethin'
like cheesecake?
- No.
- Not today.
It's real good. All right.
- How was work today?
- Oh, pretty good.
We got a new client, and the
bank will make a lot of money.
- What client?
- I cannot tell you. It's confidential.
- Aw, come on. Why not?
- No, I can't.
Anyway, how's your sex life?
I can't talk about it.
Why not?
- Take your time.
- Oh, God, I have to run.
- Already?
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
- It's on me.
- See you, Mark.
- You wanna go jogging?
- Sure. What time?
- Golden Gate Park, 6:30.
- Right on.
- All right? See ya.
- Okey dokey, pal.
What's going on here?
I like you very much, Mark.
Come on. Johnny's my best friend.
Just one more time.
I couldn't picture
Spending life with anyone but you
And we wouldn't be here
If it weren't for all the
things we've been through
And my heart wouldn't beat if
Oh, yeah.
If you didn't come and save me
With your love
You are the reason I breathe
You are my everything
In your eyes I can see
Baby, you are the one for me
I can't imagine
Sharing love with no one
in this world but you
It's so exciting
When you're here with me
And I am here with you
My heart couldn't beat if
If it wasn't for your
warm and tender touch
You are the reason I breathe
You are my everything
In your eyes I can see
Baby, you are the one for me
Even though at times
It's been hard
We've conquered winds and storms
And our hearts will always be one
Until the very end
Very end
Ohh
You are the reason I breathe
You are my everything
In your eyes I can see
Baby, you are the one for me
You are the reason I breathe
- Hey.
- Hey, Johnny. How's it going?
Really good.
- What's going on, Johnny?
- Not much.
Oh, yeah!
Throw it, dude. Throw it.
- What's new with you, man?
- Not much, man.
- Catch this!
- All right!
Whoo-hoo! Whee! Ooh-whee!
Boom!
Oh! Oh, yeah!
Catch this, Johnny!
Right on, man.
- What's new with you, man?
- I'm doin' good.
- How's your work?
- Things are good.
Try and catch me! Come on-Ohh!
Ha-ha! I got you!
- Oh, man!
- There you go!
Who is it?
Delivery man.
It's me, Lisa. Come on. Open up.
Come on in.
Hey, Mark.
Wow. So, uh, you gonna be ready?
How do you mean that?
I'm always ready... for you.
I mean for the party.
We have plenty of time.
All I have to do
is put on my party dress.
- Come on.
- What are you doing?
Nothing.
You're so beautiful.
- Hurry up. I have to open the door.
- Wait! Hang on. Hang on.
Come on in. It's open.
Hi!
I brought the stuff.
I knew I could count on you.
Hi, Mark. X-Y-Z.
What are you talking about?
Examine your zipper.
You guys are too much.
So, what can I do to help?
I gotta go.
- Come on and help me move the coffee table.
- Okay.
What was he doing here?
Ah, he just brought by
some take-out.
What about his zipper?
Leave him alone. He's a good guy.
Did you tell Johnny yet?
No. Mark's his best friend.
Tricky, tricky.
You know,
I really loved Johnny at first.
Everything's changed.
I need more from life
than what Johnny can give me.
Suddenly my eyes are wide open...
and I can see
everything so clearly.
I want it all.
You think you can
get it all from Mark?
If he can't give me what I want,
somebody else will.
Lisa, you're sounding
just like your mother.
You're being so manipulative.
So what? You can
learn something from me.
You have to take
as much as you can.
You have to live, live, live.
Don't worry about me.
I have everything covered.
Your point of view
is so different from mine.
Look, I don't wanna talk about it.
People are gonna be getting here soon,
and we have to finish.
Lisa.
I don't see what the big deal is.
Doesn't everybody
look out for number one?
Don't I deserve the best?
I couldn't do that.
You're too much for me, Lisa.
You know, you're not
such an angel yourself.
Yeah, but we're not
talking about me, are we?
Stop it!
Are you trying to ruin my party?
- Live fast, die young, man.
- Yeah, you're right.
- Yeah. That's the idea.
- Yeah!
Catch me! Come on!
I'm looking at this property
in Sausalito.
How are the loans like these days?
Pretty good. Yeah.
You'll be qualified.
- You serious?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
- When can we meet about that?
- We can talk about this tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
- Yeah.
- I can come in, like, in the late afternoon?
- Absolutely. 8:00?
Really? Right on. That's great.
Bye, Lisa.
Oh, hi, Claudette.
- Oh!
- Bye!
- Uh-huh!
- Hello, Mom. How are you?
I'm okay. How are you?
I'm fixing the apartment for Johnny's birthday,
but I'm really not into it.
Oh? Why not?
'Cause I'm in love with Mark,
not Johnny.
And here I am planning his party.
It's not right, Lisa.
I still think
you should marry Johnny.
Now, you can't live on love.
You need financial security.
But I'm not happy.
He still thinks
I'm gonna marry him next month.
He's a fool.
You expect to be happy.
I haven't been happy
since I married my first husband.
I didn't even want
to marry your father.
You never told me that.
Well, it's true.
All men are assholes.
Men and women use and abuse each other
all the time. There's nothing wrong with it.
Marriage has nothing
to do with love.
Johnny's okay, I suppose.
Actually...
I have him wrapped
around my little finger.
You should be happy then.
But I don't love him.
Don't throw your life away just
because you don't love him.
That's ridiculous!
You need to grow up,
and you need to listen to me.
Okay.
Mom, I'll see you at the party.
- I just need to be alone right now.
- Mmm.
Bye-bye, my precious.
Surprise!
Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday to you
- Hey. Oh, wow!
Happy birthday, dear Johnny
Wow. All right.
Thank you, thank you.
- Happy birthday to you
- All right, I'm blushing.
- Cheers!
- Happy birthday!
Thank you. You guys pre-Hey!
- So, were you surprised?
- Yeah, I'm surprised. That's right.
Well-
Thanks a lot again.
Thank you. Thanks. Hey!
Wanna drink this one?
Yeah, later. Later.
- Later?
- Yes.
That's, like, the third time
you've told me that joke tonight.
Now, listen, have you given
any more thought to-
- I know you think I'm awfully bold-
- No, it's okay.
Well, you know, I don't
want to be a pest...
but we have to help her.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I'm just f-
Okay.
That's what friends are for.
It's up to us, as her friends...
to give her a little
boost when she needs it.
That's all I had to say.
One of my little speeches.
Hey, everybody, let's go
outside for some fresh air.
Yeah.! Yeah.!
Yeah.
Wait.
I have something I wanna show you.
Oh, really?
So, uh, what do you
want to show me?
It's a surprise.
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
Everybody's here.
No, they're not.
They're all outside.
You devil. You planned
this all along.
What's going on here?
Why are you doing this?
I love him.
I don't believe it.
You don't understand anything.
Leave your stupid
comments in your pocket!
Do you understand
what you're doing?
You're going to destroy Johnny.
He's very sensitive.
I don't care.
I'm in love with Mark.
How can you do this?
You make me sick.
Hey!
Thank you, honey.
This is a beautiful party.
You invited all my friends.
Good thinking!
You're welcome, darling.
- You know how much I love you.
- I do.
It's getting really hot in here.
- Why don't we go back outside.
- Uh-huh.
Okay.
Hey, everybody! I have
an announcement to make!
We're expecting!
That's great!
Hey! Thank you.
Lisa, I have to talk to you.
You have got to be
honest with Johnny.
I agree with that.
Look, I'm gonna tell him. Okay?
I just-I don't want
to ruin his birthday.
When is the baby due?
- There is no baby.
- What?
W-What are you talking about?
I told him that to
make it interesting.
We're probably gonna have
a baby eventually anyway.
You're not gonna tell
Johnny, are you?
Lisa, are you feeling okay?
Because this is just
getting worse and worse.
I feel like I'm sitting on an atomic
bomb, waiting for it to go off.
Me too. I mean, there's no
simple solution to this.
Don't worry. You guys worry
entirely too much about me.
We're not worried about you.
We're worried about Johnny.
You don't understand the psychological
impact of what you're doing here.
You're hurting yourself.
You're hurting our friendship.
I am not responsible for Johnny.
I'm through with that.
I'm changing.
I have the right, don't I?
People are changing all the time.
I have to think about my future.
What's it to you?
This is going to pull us all down.
It's gonna shake up
our group of friends.
It's gonna destroy our
friendship, Lisa.
I don't think Mark
really loves you.
I don't wanna talk about it!
Lisa, you're gonna have to face it.
I, for one, am gonna have a hard
time forgiving you if you don't.
Hey, everybody! Let's go
inside and eat some cake!
That's a good idea.!
I don't understand you, Lisa.
- Mmm!
- Mm-hmm.
- Lisa looks hot tonight.
- What do you mean, "hot"?
- Sorry about what happened.
- That's all right, darling.
I'll-I'll help.
Whose baby is it? Is it mine?
No, of course not.
- How can you be sure?
- Just stop asking me stupid questions.
- Who the hell do you think you are?
- Just shut up!
What are you doing?
What's going on here?
- You really don't know, do you?
- Maybe I know more than you think I do, Mark.
- Shit! All right?
- What do you want from me?
Huh?
Stop! Stop! Stop it!
All right. All right!
Okay, folks everything is fine.
The fight is over. I'm sorry, Mark.
Yeah. Me too.
Lisa, can-Can you
clean up here, please?
What are you doing?
None of your business.
- You're my future wife.
What are you doing, Lisa?
- Leave her alone, man.
- She doesn't want to talk to you.
- Since when do you give me orders?
Since Lisa changed
her mind about you.
Wake up, man!
What planet are you on?
I think you should leave right now.
Don't spoil it. We
were just having fun.
Don't worry about it, man.
Don't touch me,
motherfucker. Get out.
- Stop it! Stop it!
- Leave my girl alone!
You two are acting like children.
- Son of a bitch.
- You're gonna ruin the party.
If you'd keep your girl satisfied,
she wouldn't come to me.
Get out of my house. I'll kill you!
I'll break every bone in your body!
- Stop it!
- I'll kill you, you bastard!
- You couldn't kill me if you tried.!
- You betrayed me!
You're not good. You're just a chicken.
Cheep-cheep-cheep.!
- Johnny, chill out! It's over!
- Shut up!
- Cool it! It's over!
It's not over.! Everybody betrayed me.!
I'm fed up with this world.!
I cleaned up the kitchen,
sweetheart...
so you don't have
to worry about that.
He still won't come
out of the bathroom.
Sweetheart, he's upset.
Now, Johnny is a sensible man.
He will come out. You will discuss this.
Everything is going to be okay.
I just think I should be
alone with him right now.
I understand, sweetheart.
I'm going to go home now.
- Bye-bye. You call me if you need me.
- I will.
- Thanks, Mom.
- Mm-hmm!
You can come out now, Johnny.
She's gone.
In a few minutes, bitch.
Who are you calling a bitch?
You and your stupid mother.
- Hello?
- Hi, Mark.
I need to talk to you.
- What's going on?
- Don't worry about Johnny.
He's just being a big baby.
You know, I love you very much.
I love you.
Why don't you ditch this creep?
I don't like him anymore.
I know. He's not worth it.
Why don't I come up there
and be with you?
Sure, baby. Come on up.
I want your body.
You got it.
- I'm on my way. Bye.
- Bye.
Who were you talking to?
- Nobody.
- We'll see about that.
We'll see about that.
Hello?
Hi, Mark. I need to talk to you.
What's going on?
Don't worry about Johnny.
He's just being a big baby.
You know, I love you very much.
You're the sparkle of my life.
I can't live without you. I love you.
You little tramp.
How could you do this to me?
I gave you
seven years of my life...
and you betray me.
- We'll see what else we have on this tape.
- No! Stop.
You little prick.
I put up with you for seven years.
You think you're an angel.
You're just like everybody.
I treat you like a princess,
and you stab me in the back.
I love you, and I did anything for you
to just please you.
And now you betray me!
How could you love him?
Why don't you just
ditch this creep?
I don't like him anymore.
I know. He's not worth it.
Why don't I come up there
and be with you?
Sure, baby. Come on up.
I want your body.
You got it.
Everybody betrayed me.
I don't have a friend in the world.
I'm leaving you, Johnny.
Get out. Get out!
Get out of my life!
Why, Lisa? Why? Why?
You bitch!
You bitch! You bitch!
Screw the whole world!
I don't need them!
You little tramp.
I put up with you-
Why? Why is this
happening to me? Why?
It's over.
God, forgive me.
Everything'll be all right.
Good night, Johnny.
Wake up, Johnny! Come on!
Is he dead?
My God. Mark, is he dead?
Yes, he's dead.
Yes, he's dead!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
I've lost him, but I still
have you. Right?
Right?
You don't have me.
You'll never have me.
You killed him.
Mark, we're free to be together.
I love you.
You tramp.
You killed him. You're the
cause of all of this.
I don't love you.
Get out of my life, you bitch!
- What's happening?
- Don't look, Denny.
Johnny's dead!
Wake up, Johnny! Please!
Please! It's not right!
It's not right.
Denny, he's in a better place.
Leave us!
Both of you leave.
As far as I'm concerned, you can
drop off the earth. That's a promise.
Just leave! Both of you!
Leave him, all right?
Let him be with him!
Why, Johnny?
Why? Johnny, why?
Why?
- What's happened?
- Is everything okay?
I heard a shot.
- Someone fired a gun. I smell smoke.
- What's going on?
Call 911.
Is everyone okay?
Your touch
Pulling fire out of me
Like a wave crashing on the sea
Your kiss
As gentle as a summer breeze
Your love
Is what I need to set me free
A rose
Is what
You are
To me
The smell
Of wonders
Oh, so sweet
- You are
- A rose
- To me
- You are
- My rose
- My rose, my rose
- Baby
- Baby, baby
Yeah, baby
- You are
- A rose
- To me
- To me, to me
- Yes, you are Yes, you are
- To me
- You are
- My rose
- Baby
- Baby, baby
You are my rose