you
wake up wake up constable
coming coming coming
good evening I mean that must ensue I am
the BBC as you can see and hear was the
last news on this the third or is it the
force anniversary of the nuclear
misunderstanding which led to the third
world war here is the World War here it
is the last recorded statement of the
Prime Minister as he then was who had
just succeeded his illustrious father
into office I feel I am NOT boasting
when I remind you that this was without
a shadow of a doubt the very shortest
war in living memory two minutes 28
seconds up to and including the grave
process of signing the peace treaty
fully blocked the great task of burying
our 40 million dead was also carried out
with great expediency and goodwill you
know this great country of ours often
sticks in the mud of past searches out
and holds up to the light of the
mistakes of past ties man damn him heide
the butcher I shall tell the world look
at that another chat butchered oh the
horror who the horror I can't look we
eat our hot tub with the canker of
racialism and death east of Suez and I
am forced to ask have we forgotten the
bomb the Prime Minister head as you all
know just returned from the 449
disarmament conference and was greeted
on the steps of another 10 x marks it
for a chairman has invited me kindly in
hey can't see very much at the moment
but there will be some pretty hard
you may be sure that's all thank you
very much thank you ah Lord former BBC
television off the cuff while we're
waiting for statement I like your hat I
do do you do use it until you it's the
latest early warning hat it gives you
that extra four minutes in bed I never
wanna hurt him better be the Catholic
person for long time and I would know
where to begin is this your cousin it is
I'll comment from lobster not leaders
there's no a lord snowdon is the woods
are full of them Prime Minister is
coming up Prime Minister can you say hi
Kenzie I can say without any fear of
contradiction erotism pretty tough agony
thank i say we have finally fixed the
rent of lumberton at an undisclosed via
carve a 100-yen pounds per week this
lease means peace in our time that I'm
afraid was the end of the news our next
scheduled program will be on August bank
holiday when Charlton Heston will
wrestle His Holiness the Pope for the
sportsman of the year title until then
all walk backwards in the long shot
while good night it give god save mrs.
ethel stroke long live mrs. ethel stroke
god save mrs. ethel sroka 393 a high
street leytonstone good night yeah hey
come out of that television change it's
your turn for the telly news there is it
you're the district but you didn't
action here's that choice everybody
request let me do this polishing the
poor oh yes
tonight japanese invasion forces of Riek
singapore oh yeah ah I didn't quite
catch the name are you a doctor doctor
besides no boots I don't wear them and I
don't travel in it don't be sharp with
me on them my car kennington and
districts do laundry I am no that's not
me I've left the space for advertising I
am other side Lord portan identity I
type the title for the suture person who
found himself on hot tub the psychiatry
old army sir I think he had to do with
all of that but the table lamps were
knitting should we all got one I don't
require surgery I shall decide that
thought now you want it privately or my
national yes but yes I wanted privately
on the national health
yo man it's night father the last bar on
the circle line I think I'll have a
smoke one of these days you'll not come
back who brought back by the health
visitor smoking you know yet you persist
you know that I don't approve of your
leaving the compartment she doesn't get
enough exercise on the hill after all
it's been how long's it been it's been
since dead what'd she say yeah shinsen
managed very well mr. chalky bars I like
my women shall be built I think she
supposed to try to keep her weight down
oh I wish there was more speak to her
own age on the circle line she could
perhaps smoke with riff damn fast happy
fella no shit always at it
you
yeah there's a limit to what I'll do you
know yes then let's go as far as i can
tell me yeah no I'm pissing well I'll
get you soon oh no you have been a bit
off color there's a hell was why I'm not
eating anything why's that but I can't
get the stuff look I had this mounted
this very morning 18-karat pelvis well
tell me about it oh well things were
going swimmingly until that well until
they drop the oh well now there you know
oh that's the fella yeah did the noise
keep you awake oh I step to it all right
yes in fact when I was in England still
a beard albeit in a club chair third
world war took place huh I didn't get a
chance to join the regiment neither did
I I was standing by ready to face the
enemy whoever they might be and I
couldn't find them tell me do you know
who was the enemy I haven't the least
idea I thought dr. I thought you might
give me breakfast as a proscription
against malnutrition ah yes well can
take come 30 milligrams a vague on toast
and get it made up at any restaurant oh
good i'll have it made up in boots it's
more hygienic in bottles yes yes yes but
will it will it will it cure me huh my
first impulse is to cut and run thank
for having the thought is no more than
simple salvation the doctor I i feel it
is more your Thornton we must have a
photo okay yes we do sit down again yes
yes it's inside and out meet up please
Oh skin is very white in my bones for
wife dr. looks since this thing drop
this is routine there's some that's the
Pharaoh I I had terrible mortgage fears
and I think I made turn into a bed
sitting room ah ah that's that probably
atomic mutation man's a lot of the
dividers how can I take for it three
guineas what take three guineas your
rent granted I don't want rent I
I want to make sure i I've demand a
second opinion yes well that is your
privilege of course but I can tell you
that there's no evidence of dry rot in
his worm but keep well wrapped up and
try and keep out of overdrafts she gets
later and later every night sometimes
morning well perhaps she's had more than
one she's at don't offer doesn't if you
ask me I'm gonna get her father don't
leave me at night
you
God what's this likely story those are
my daughter's little hairs outing up
there's a simple explanation sir yes and
I'm going to give it to you what class
of person to you I'm top drawer to put
it mildly you expected from the gutter
but I don't believe it's about my my
turning
who can say she say sorry sorry sorry
that's not nearly enough enough under
the circumstances actually sir I'm a
commuter chap you know backwards and
forwards forwards that witness how gay
doesn't get boring I'm really dare you
see such things and do them well I'll be
interested in joining your party I'm
sure you can use other pair of hands
will keep your filthy computer hands to
yourself y'all the seams of your
trousers when I can see them she'll need
a nurse
what is it you want one what you mean to
say we'll be looking at me without
regard to my condition you're not well
enough to have a condition dear she want
to potty i won no such thing I wanted to
opinion my opinion in my opinion you
need repointing but are you putting off
the evil hour what you really need you
see is a full-scale conversion to Maison
it it's true oh I expected is still try
not to worry love it's just simple off
and the council will give you a girl
your balances you don't realize do you I
don't want a bathroom now what you want
anything yeah here we are just being for
nurse my god I've dropped a brick
I said I believe in the new world where
we are going up is where we're going on
man and don't you forget it you can't do
that that's public property that's right
lastly you come to kill me how long
please three years collect me collect me
I've been here dead since the morning
raid I'm afraid this far too much to pay
my friend will pay if you can find and I
no friends left Roger is this your trunk
me my name's not roger it's adam rogers
name is not on the lid cost you
twenty-five shillings Oh Fred I had any
money sir I shall lend you some take
something use
okay me lukkage girl copy arrested his
veins gone
I hear a rumor sir the Pope's now
allowing co-receptors for all occasions
except during sexual intercourse
okay look here can't you get more
horsepower keep moving keep moving say
you're safer on the move
what hmm I shan't I shall not keep
asking you to keep moving sir you will
not you'll do your duty young man I wish
to speak to your superior I expect to
turn into a bed sitting room very
shortly automator in which particular
ice be obliged to stop somewhere
preferably r street council better oh
well where can I stop the car stop
anywhere says you very well know we
don't want to stay in one place long
enough for the enemy to have another
charter does do is it not until I
preemptive strike is launched do sir
have we not stop that as England not
should have struck back three years ago
if if not before I think we did sir
these things take time you're not look
you know you well sir absolutely refuse
to handle bit until I turned in your bed
sitting room and you are not that I
guess fully damn you man do I do i do I
look like a bed Citigroup it's not for
me to say sir I should you stop your
novel to be knocked down without the
option what I don't want to turn into a
bed sitting or I I don't can't have a
lord turning into that sort of thing
longleat Woburn Abbey a place for the
takings are considerable that a big city
three pounds ten a week another
hey I'm getting better and better every
day you live hello hello no no no I'm
should gonna give me it's coming from
every day in every way I'm getting
better he's your big bust stingy / girl
her age what did you do that lift Buster
special he seemed soon my nipple she's
just turned out more on that one mmm
father's very observant he was in the
call she wouldn't talk about me in front
of Alan he doesn't want to know about my
Brussels no I do I do so we still pier
40 hope all this family talk isn't
boring you know a little bit of it he'll
expect you like little dance now to
reaction the best of you
I'm get it forever yeah do you know
about it so my just like I was glad when
I met in you got it all over I'd named
the end was such a relief if only I i
used to say for Christ's sake drop it
didn't duck and only when you were very
tired he's on a bad lad oh there you are
what did I say what I said later he said
you another bad one yeah I want to treat
me just as if I was your father hated my
father well then you're gonna say mean
mq fun love you Nana yes well treat me
like him then Oh uncle can I have six
months of sweeties please of course you
may what a good polite boy you are
radiations rising still I mustn't
grumble too much
oh hello how they dropped it yet huh but
haven't dropped yet boy where are you
I'm a regional seat of government coming
to your quick I'll sue have you seated
and governor has he seen you don't you
huh who are you first of all yeah they
popped it yeah it did have they drop
walk you know do you we found to know
you're relaxed won't you still close the
end Olga mixed up in the black eaten LBJ
there's a fella fruit LBJ how is proud
to regionally serve him haha ok nope
until me let me guess Herod's lead all
this on you know parents they very good
of that yeah expect I talk too much good
listen I don't listen I'm gonna get my
head with all about him have a good
people of on you know I shot to myself I
had to they came at me they try to get
in with a massive Hannah's in gas
Presley were telling inning for Sutton I
said kitchen escape let me see this you
see oh who did you shoot another day my
wife shot him dead of course I married
again don't know me or talk to us
darkness Wallace very much in love
course it led to marriage she doesn't
seem to mind hi honey no you shot at me
I'm a medical practitioner hey have the
proof the kind of the proof yeah fresh
evidence is comfortable to who is
responsible we have I will I will I will
where are we you all forgotten
Paddington don't you know you London
haha family life that's important let me
brother did didn't you have a daddy and
a mommy there's no my brother handsome
there you could have had one each I'm
sorry to have to rest eps my legs feel
like Larsen would
well thank goodness I caught you on your
rounds doctor what are you going to do
for me what hmm g six of these pills one
every half mile oh but I can't do that
only live a mile away this is Hyde Park
isn't it yes will you have moved whether
I'll tell afraid no I'll tell you what
I'll take the long road home that's the
ticket spinning I don't know what to say
to your doctor say doctor how much will
it be doctor how much will there be
there will be 18 first walked in his
mark down to three and six in the last
bargain budget
are you kept in a few Marty yes I just
signed a show at one ah luncheon ah
would you care to join me yes saturday
Saturday
if this is regions park than Bob large
must lie to the south
what i have here sir your wife's death
certificate oh thank you oh dear there
well it was a lovely way to go but
Mummy's alive I'm afraid not dear makes
me feel all funny to read it no no tell
them no holla no pull yourself together
I am together we are I want you to call
me after and come to me for every little
plaster mum's a nice I thought I will
steer by rights I should be but how can
you tell if it's here in black and white
give it to me I shouldn't should I
they're only upset us a reason you were
to meet him I'll put it somewhere safe
with all the others the health cards
look mrs. Burton there's nothing wrong
with you nice going boy it's your wife
being alive assumes the all the troubles
I'm sorry oh I'm sorry we don't want to
cause any trouble now listen none free
don't argue with a nasty she's she's
bound to know best what's best for us do
I flygon or anything the one of the way
I'd like you to look at it is this
and may have lost the wiser but you've
gained a certificate I expect you've got
the set now if you can't be careless
with I do hope we haven't been careless
with our papers birth marriage death and
school mom got escort can you let me see
them all before you send them off I
would just like to hold them all
together
not much is it zero did we've all been
so much happier since that
well at least I didn't still keep Jeff
that's the star but style
Oh
I can hear them silly in the slot calf
heaters on the Lord's legs belgravia
i'ma spank their period before I turn
well I know I may even now be in the
province issue to someone kindly sent me
on the right road to Belgravia a guide a
guide I freehold or a guide lovely
evening a splendid meal yes careful an
after-dinner drink if you have a try
what were you doing before this step I
was in the Army actually I'm a captain
oh I see what regiment oh we didn't know
I mean to the Official Secrets Act but
from what I could make it my cap badge
it with the Household Cavalry did you
have to be a householder good good lord
no no I did help the Commission know the
household that we are referring to is
the backing palace household we did all
the cavalry for them did you they're
splendid all destroyed of course when
they dropped you know god save our
gracious Queen long live our noble Queen
kaze no tenderly no no no we don't sing
that any longer you don't know we were
using now that God should save mrs.
ethel stroke of 393 a high street
leytonstone Oh of the 20 people who are
known de vive in England she stands next
in line to the throne hmm I say all I
could still be connected huh it'll like
to have the phone I've under got the
bells boy try be mad the door they drive
me mad man all right hey
whatever keep moving it and the pooper I
have the proof the proof of germ warfare
boy get the weapon jammed you see the
dip the weapon to the germs and the
later survive the you know uh huh huh if
it survived at you see you come down
with the measles uh Jake me madam which
one of you ordered a business telephone
both of me huh last at last I shall
convince the world with my documentary
vice hello from the world hello hello
folks at walls every get dem equation
model but this is the top you'll be
getting madder just let me have the
borrowing of it why he is the Bella
Godiva me my dough see Maria sugar two
telephones install we whip the bills are
you hello I'll show you in ready color
is he talking about jump haha that dirty
fuck kick your ass rotten bills Martin
captain and dr oh just a moment
hello darling what are you doing
sleeping how are you well let me have a
photograph of adventure Oh give him my
regards yeah bye bye Gregory Gregory
have you seen my Nigel oh it's getting
late my humiliation now what have I done
with my defeat of England medal Your
Majesty I'm sorry that I failed you I
tried to catch the thing before it hit
the palace but one of your corgis with
me God put your back into it my first
wife died you know sorry to hear that I
got my certificate the other day you'd
have want another woman like me
you remind me of my first wife that's
funny you see I never met easy will you
do for me what my first wife did Doris
tries but she she can't coordinate you
see will you do it for me well as long
as we get it over quickly before daddy
misses me see these move it move it your
worship your melon I didn't know that I
haven't Oh get out just let her leave me
alone that was my best in the servants
hello
call the roll alum all the figure
present penelope the well-known fiance
yeah Alan here mother mommy we're all
here it's at one mapa that's all we ever
had one mother mummy all right now when
I say wave I which Walter wave wave
hello hello young Alan hello blimpy
mommy all right that's enough I demand
an explanation Oh which was the night
fault Oh mother don't worry mother we
look after
one more stop madam and I shall be
forced to endorse your license you
wouldn't want us to use our special
password you hello o Lord Fortnum and
you've changed well keep moving and
where are you I'm number 29 hold a set
place how do you forgot so you can bring
some furniture I'm freezing I shall come
at once if they try not to look
conspicuous or you'll be knocked down
without the option react fiend get your
hand out of my drawers I know mother
I'm over here so you are I'd recognize
you anywhere my heart I must say it
suits you please don't do this I'm not
well it's me captain Bill's Martin and
I'm your doctor come in dr. did you
bring some furniture
I say this is you yes tell me the worst
where am I yeah your number 29 called a
secretary yes I know that but what Bubba
ah that's pretty bad news I'm afraid
pennington quick put a card put a card
in the window no comments no children
and definitely no colored children don't
know rod is he looks like he's come to
stay Molly a doctor everyone thought
like you this world will be much heavier
place breathing in how's Walter isn't
button properly for years Oh soon fix
that I go to wash you somewhere you
married oh not a moment and I would
advise against it against it
survivors of the third crackers quick
march hey it stopped burma reunion and
hop dinner I was fine the Albert Hall I
should be out till dawn no I got right
up and don't take any rent that's got me
to be come on I do let's get the
furniture
thank you my dear as you chaps their
electricity it's the lifeblood of
civilization without electricity
civilization as we know it could not
survive so I in 10 we've gots help to go
on pedaling this bicycle until we've hit
this vessel based on 46 and one God's
just victory over the forces of evil
it's not raining in the road to Mandalay
oh yeah it is sick no coloreds Daniel
have you not yet finished with my poor
bruised body you that black man's woman
it's hardened I clear in my condition
and what is your condition I'm a
cupboard will nobody close my doors I'm
Lord Fortnum of element who are you oh
hi mrs. fritton well madam in view of
the ghastly circumstances in which we
both found ourselves i suggest we speak
only when spoken to and hold our towns
very well if you think so
Mummy Mummy let's sleep here for a bit
make a look again when it's light low
you
I will say this for him I can't really
say anything for him except is like a
sheet of white paper I hadn't seen a
sheet of white paper for years I could
draw a face on his poor suit crumpled
fashion with little stitches on the
edges and I'll say this for him trendy
boy you can say as lapels a crumpled and
he has got a knows who knows it used to
be and I say this for him he's always
here whenever his feet I he is toes
event upwards but he's straight flat
stupid as a son
I will say this for him and he has got
twirly hair but you do get the whole
thing now to stroke he's nobody else
Oh
let's check your ruler to deter juicer
carry on can't head 22 inches ah taking
my measurements chest 22 inches that's
right that's the hammer get it all down
inside link George isn't right right sir
well do you know thank you very much I
think ah that my children you want more
damage months of course they're little
bit young my word what I Eddie trunk
keep booing they're gonna let me know
then who are you they are I must say the
seemed rather impressed with my inside
leg excuse me sir but it was a 22 isn't
it yes I believe it was I'd say not many
of them left you know like shake you by
the hand yeah I ward but not until I've
referred it to the Minister of Health
kite right I'll be to care for you and
business then hmm looking for a partner
in no I am a partner of course who is
your partner yeah I don't need 1 i'm
just partner and company yeah i see ya
isn't that your daughter I say it is
chop a little thing we'll bill Chang
Gail thank you been going on some time
18 months hey indeed indeed hell I'd I'd
like your permission to call upon your
daughter often starting now
yeah I'd like a bit more off here for
caulking ah yes that's much better I no
wonder you hippie types you know such as
that never won fair lady anything else
mm-hmm
but daddy I love Alan love love is a
four letter word it's come for that
serves ball cat is a three letter word
right hahaha you're gonna make a favor
son-in-law be my ambition for yours now
look here mr. Ferris you can arrange
this thing over our heads you know Gotye
captain Bill's Martin as a man of
substance of property if not more
moreover he's a partner a fitting
son-in-law her future prime minister who
is I am you don't imagine they gathered
my measurements for nothing to her show
me a 22 inside leg and I'll show you a
future Prime Minister it's well known
fact I expect mrs. ethel stroke yeah
consider my credentials any day now that
trunk of yours get rid of it
it's not my trunk he tied his thumbs up
a string and exposed himself for a
limited parenting camberley was that
user a post-war gestures rose over
destroyed the string
you
I love some poles you know dearly loved
us to be married here Oh Vika may be
requiring your services soon happy once
and I yeah I'm not surprised I wouldn't
leave it too long if I were you chubby
little fame n shake my patient you know
well if you'll excuse me I'll just go
into a minute and kids screwed up a bit
I can't go through with it what having
this monster well no one else can have
it can they
then it must be it must be well just
slip into an our wedding dress no no no
no wait a minute darling go behind the
screen oh really darling you've watched
a lady undressed before today haven't
you haha course Tommy now go behind the
screen with you the wish mother could
have been alive to see it oh just a fool
oh I've considered a new economical
combined marriage and divorce ceremony
three pounds one shilling Catholics
extra oh no we couldn't afford the
divorce just now she had to be satisfied
to the wedding later on of course when
I'm earning well then they recover the
annulment cct instant God kicks out good
luck
a line up there would you join hands
please good good and now put a good book
oh and the naughty game people are
cooker in the pot and change and later
upon the ground and we're a quitter and
II Ripper oh that's all the Bible I know
Slade each Atlas lover but if you prefer
the old twit verse nothing on still
recall it mm-hmm do you Bill's Martin
take this girl to be your lawful wedded
why now is expecting her to ask me that
questions it so happens I do and you
Penelope take this lawful wedded man to
be your husband I do and do you promise
Penelope Rose Fred and to cherish your
eyes burn in sickness and in health in
trial and in ordeal and in all our only
I say look here there's still some
decency left come on down lick it up
shit out and finish that way I now
pronounce you man and wife on your mom
get out of my bedroom you're peeping tom
this alternate the drinkin you've got
two hours my god when was my last be
religionist excuse result BBC television
when did you first decide to become a
politician good then I'm afraid I didn't
say would you like to try again it began
when I measured my inside leg one day as
we all do and I found that I was very
well equipped good heavens Penelope hey
daddy but your promise to captain Bill's
mouse in your stuff come down at once I
married you this morning daddy so you
did that's all right then get it all
wife sent you along did you well it did
occur to me that I might review the
circumstances love it yeah I can't keep
away you'll learn to love your fertility
test I've always had a very good win
those room well my wife oh well best
thing the best thing to do is talk dirty
among yourselves what you can't come to
that too click through the dirty books
do you get my socks on my love I live
downstairs kiss it some boiling water oh
yeah
ah did you pass your fertility test some
ID an error huntsdale you see lights
viewers in the critical moment where's
my bride she should be able to tell sit
down son your bride is in labor oh god
daddy I need a drink what do you have a
boy y'all have a larger more than the
border we know nothing well I think I'll
wander along to the saloon car
love you
I knew as soon as I grasped the test you
a friendly in my right hand none of your
cheek and impotence
not gonna have
evening we're looking for a man are you
indeed inspector there aren't many of us
left you know we're also looking for a
bed sitting room don't we all we are on
the trail of a foul and grisly murder I
says noting that the first post-war
murder things are looking up for you in
popular fiction yes we've had a pretty
thin time that recently what with 40
million dead we haven't been able to see
the woods with the tree but this is
murder not glory
they're also looking for a chunk if the
inspector doesn't mind me saying so and
when we find it we'll know why we're
looking for doing very well would you
like to see the birth which still got a
few tickets left let me go she needs me
oh no what she has need of his medical
science are you don't that's what ought
to be friend cock fighting I am I am
hang it up there I think it might do
better on the wall oh she regulated
minor sure your night raritan nope nah
never that is the manual yeah honey it's
his turn to be Prime Minister I know I
know I always knew my inside leg would
lead to power their Martin rules you can
be a hand wheel get rid of my own
tongues which actually not need
down there
a lovely dome that is Ren isn't it no
it's not rendered sir looks a bit cloudy
but I don't think we're in for any rain
sounds a little dropping off a balloon
suddenly Sheldon oh we have this new
system instead of moving the baby out we
move the furniture Eve oh excuse me Oh
what are you doing to my penny we should
all ask ourselves is it really necessary
for people to leave the womb nowadays
that's where most of the trouble seems
to start in this wicked world my god is
monstrous it may well be but you must be
prepared to love your monster oh we had
to submit medicated wallpaper here
perhaps you'd like to choose a pattern
to suit your womb
aim income a free bag daddy fish said
who's been sleeping in my poorest and
the mama bear said that that's no
porridge that was my wife waster tell
him tell him pleading jinx it there were
three and Darcy ah sergeant sup man
they're coming over the wire we're so I
can see no one whatever son put these
glasses your eyes with you no sir
doesn't submission son I can see nothing
whatever son 90 Roger to the boats are
no sign of the animator yeah huh are you
the plug officer what was in charge of d
a nuclear deterrent in the last atomic
war I am he bad news he has been
returned to sender and it's free and
mind and pay on it in Chinese dollars
have we got a reply I can't help that
might you didn't reckon with the
chickiepoo post office little bit late
now yes 65 million pound it costs to
develop that bomb Oh pity about the
three and nine we could have won eula
damnable red la
dad will get a nice surprise dad sorry
we're late home dad I had the baby don't
you think it looks a bit like you sir
long day rape damn it I can hold my
tongue no longer what how dare you r
delta how dare you take advantage of our
feathered friend nice piece of shit
compromised internally in front of my
own daughter close my doors at once
can't we go into this in the morning i'm
all in me hey well captain but be gentle
with me
no nothing edible yeah you know ever
since they drop the good ones and become
quite extinct younger strange actually
wasn't the Russians and Americans who
dropped it there gratz was render killer
killer surf video oh I don't know here's
it's just the time oh sit you down what
what is it darling chicken no it's daddy
oh oh never mind don't take it too hard
huh we let his perch from our bird dream
Franklin be gentle pools how did this
terrible danger after his career in
politics he said he wanted his body to
be left to silence and you've learned
some of his perch
what my actually think so father father
I who this will mean a by-election 14000
hey mamas we've never had it so good
you
no I am
Oh
my word it's a good job to Minister
defense had a sense of humor when he
invented these masks mind you I was
thinking I don't be the human face fits
the modern mean you don't know if I'd
mob way in the early burly of post
atomic living out of a bloke's mouth on
top of his nut she see doesn't then when
he's late work all yesterday sardis
breakfast and reset they need it already
office huh do you think we've come to
the end of it all
oh please God not again fuck we'll just
have to keep going what for because
we're British British what a lot of used
that is he don't even knows won the war
we've run out of food no medicine more
eating our parents British
and another thing if I have my white
part of a box genitals on the end of his
finger it were a glove of course yes you
don't want the frost to get any day huh
and you think how Andy it would be in
them non corridor train she can likely
that the wind and then where would you
put a woman's equivalent well I'd uh I'd
have that up here on my shoulder see oh
then she couldn't get right by a midget
it's supposing they stood on each
other's shoulders room please you've
read a new dad no no it wouldn't work
out of the question how do you mean
picture to yourself crowded train young
man gets up to give a seat to a young
pretty girl she doesn't notice at first
and then excuse me miss ah dear your oh
dear indeed put the project tickets at
wenatchee way
isn't it look a bit off to you take him
inside a fucking compartment fucking
yeah turn around darling pardon pardon
me rubber please go wait
brother yes is it the killer father
right nothin just like the old days hey
is it hey look hey you'll enjoy this it
was horrible a little gassed
Oh
my baby
my poor baby it's dead now look Holly we
all know that rucca mistake it was our
thing as we made it Alan I it was the
only thing I ever cared for it now oh no
I'm darling we might someday make
another bright shiny yeah I'll treat up
chilly chilly here with milk oh yeah Hey
look he's already gonna hang of it no
died why don't we adopt this one mmm
there we are pleased his rattle diddams
want his rattle in didn't want his
rental whistle yes darling his first
words piss off piss off
the rubber is the end of us my friends
the end my friends is in sight Carrie
little Rupert inside me for 17 months
rather than let imagine to this wicked
world stretch and repaired his way round
hold on brothers r on the rubber will
get you wherever you high the rubber is
come stretch brothers and repent we've
provoked the hand and the foot and the
elbow and the mean and the taste am I
mean Miriam thanks why he chipped the
ball pumped the ball hmm honda bond
stop stop in the name of the Lord yeah
it's god it's good he's come back on us
good our God night for a systolic affair
he's a he's a socialist you know what
leave us come ha he's eating
conservatives yeah hold on a minute you
don't sound like God you sound like old
fort them I i also do impressions save
us Lord God from the dreadful death by
radiation savers oh god from the
temptations and perversions of the
rubber save me and I'll give up being an
atheist goody God gives me back my baby
yes well I has indeed in the fullness of
time we see what we can do good oh well
um that's not God that's Lord Fortnum
the well-known bed sitting room what
what lies in Buell's Martin that's God I
recognize the voice a large brown
substance has come to our attention
Bill's darling say something my god
Nigel and Ally you left me on the left
luggage rack the 17 pound seven
shillings to pay bills Martin but apart
from that there are no further charges
against you provided that you have the
immediate funds about your person that
is it is is it another do I knew there
was something in there going to be
another mummy I expect you may be
wondering why I've invited you all here
this afternoon I've just come from an
audience with her Majesty mrs. ethel
stroke and i'm empowered by her to tell
you but in the future clouds of
poisonous nuclear fault will no longer
be necessary mutations will see cine de
and furthermore I'm the bringer of glad
tidings a team of surgeons at the
village hospital have just accomplished
the world's first successful complete
body transplant the donor is the entire
population of South Wales and the new
body is functioning normally I myself
saw it sit up in bed wink and ask for a
glass of beer all in all I think room
peace prosperity and stability when the
earth warburton fourth of you the lion
will lie down with the lamb and the goat
gives sacked to the tiny beam at times
of great national emergency you want to
find that a new leader tends to emerge
here I am so watching
keeping everybody that's
you can come with us mr. this is mimis
each element
I have great news the country Great
Britain is a first cast
god save mrs. arrow stroke
I street leytonstone good night