I finished the test man so if it's okay
I'd like to know my grade I mean right
now Miss bloomquist right now I really
studied hard but you can tell that for
my answers can't you of course you can
that's good just keep grading like that
and then you'll have to just keep going
the right answers on the wrong ones
that's right you see I have to pass I
studied so hard now I want my grade
71 past now you have to die
hot the one have a new mac you ask for
hawthorn are you getting off or not
oh yeah I'm sorry sorry
I listener I didn't mean to hold you up
well you seem to fit the bill young man
what's that the kind of strong stranger
i said i needed in the bullet and i put
up in the supermarket your little old to
read the one I had tak stuff downstairs
you know for a while I didn't think
anybody was coming around but thank
goodness you're here yes ma'am I'm here
oh you can just put that any place
I suppose you're wondering what goes
where is that it yes that's it well it
really doesn't matter it all has to be
packed away 27 years of clutter so it
doesn't matter where it goes as long as
it goes you could start filling the
boxes and be sure to get everything
because i'm leaving here good the term
here ends day after tomorrow and I'm
retiring little early i might add if
you're looking for canes and dentures
this is the messiest part of all and i
kept putting it off I suppose I was
hoping that some of the faculty ladies
my friends but come and help me oh well
it's the end of the term everybody's
busy
oh just a moment I'd better take that
with me but I hear about the weather
over there this time of year is you know
I'm sorry i've been talking in riddles
i'm planning on living in England for a
while you know the place where English
Lit teachers are supposed to go when
they die hey think I wonder if this
works oh now that's bad luck well just
don't tell anybody no man there's no one
to tell
what about these uh no no just leave
those and this little book I'm I'm gonna
leave this here
that's what he bought sergeant an
examination book i rang up a big eight
cents how come you guys let a maniac
like that escape we don't know he's a
maniac mr. and if you've got a complaint
write it down and mail it in sure sure
guys like that really bugged me you know
with mental patients even if they are
prisoners they don't like to use the
word escape half the time these people
just wander off yeah but this guy sure
seemed to know where he was going I mean
yesterday he comes directly to this town
nearest one to the hospital and then
right to hear the first stationery story
had hit I missed it
are you sure he didn't say anything
about where he might have gone from here
I told you all he said was he needed an
example and had to go someplace to take
a test oh and thank you that I do
remember you know for a weirdo that guy
struck me as being very polite excuse me
ma'am were you saying something well
nothing momentous I was just asking if
that twine I bought is all right if it's
strong enough and if these things will
get all the way to England she's okay
it's good and strong you know I've been
talking so much about myself I forgot to
ask you your name oh it's Raymond
Raymond what just Raymond know in a
schoolroom that's practically all you've
got is your first name when they call on
you it's always yes Raymond or uh
Raymond would you please give us the
answer that's right isn't it ma'am oh
he's just the first name like teacher is
a last name maybe that's the education
gap in the metal shell you're a very
conscientious worker thank you speaking
of school where did you go high school
at it different places I never got to
graduate though oh that's too bad yeah
yes it was too bad well a high school
diploma and everything believe me
you know ma'am I think this twine is
gonna work out really good that's nice
she's still out in the hall talking to
mr. McDonald oh here she comes I miss
bloom quit as you no doubt know I
apologize for being late but you'll
still have the full hour to complete
your examination as you know your own
English that teacher vizitator is still
home he'll then I've been asked to give
you this makeup test for her I
understand some of you failed the test
and several of you missed it because
illness mrs. Taylor told me that all of
you will definitely pass force if you
pass this test this time so good luck
now before we start look over your
questions and see if you have it
are there any questions
well if there aren't any questions
please begin
no questions
no questions well that's why I have to
die
you
I'm sorry but that's the way it adds up
61 I'm afraid you didn't pass but it's
not fair I didn't understand the last
two questions I thought they were
awesome for extra credit please miss
bloomquist I raised my hand I didn't
understand the instructions I want you
to explain to me I was mixed up and you
wouldn't give me a chance to tell you I
gave all of your time for questions I
was to reading please miss Blue Goose I
just have to pass well there's nothing I
can personally do about it but i'll ask
mr. Pattison to reconsider mr. doesn't
even like me he won't do anything
Raymond are you all right what's the
matter oh I just I just felt a little
dizzy that's all well it is getting a
little late you probably starved that's
what it is I'm afraid I talked too much
and I held you up too long so I'll um
I'll just pay you now and I can finish
up all these things tomorrow
it's two hours at two dollars an hour is
that right I think it was more like an
hour and a half now
oh are you serious everybody except Paul
Newman and he's sending Steve McQueen
now don't look so surprised Mary
Bloomquist what you really think your
last week after 27 years and nobody was
gonna give you a party well I you may I
just a moment and we can't forget this
little formality oh thank you thank you
because it's a special celebration for
you thank you very much goodbye Raymond
goodbye rain oh come on guest of honor
where the hotel my beer the Florentine
room of course we had to tell them you
were really a European princess so you
have to speak only Hungarian right I'll
certainly try oh but I can't go looking
like this you listen to me Mary
Bloomquist it's not for nothing I spent
the last 30 years teaching the kids
about that brilliant organizer of
campaigns good old Julius Caesar behold
you
this is a fine way for me to act in
front of my kids kids I say Louise how
old are you anyway I'm afraid that I
preached the 30 mark now mr. Lindquist
and she's released and no I'm turn I'm
sorry but you're in need and your charm
right but it was very decent of you not
to change your last name you know you've
made this a lovely occasion for me
leaving your families and all coming
down here tonight
you know these are my beloved enemies
the faces in the seats behind the desk
it's just not the same
give a lady a going-away party and and
you give her some gifts and too much to
drink and you've got to hear what's on
her mind and was on my mind
as I finally decided to leave office is
that something has happened to our kids
let's face it let us place it there not
reaching out for us like they used to
like you used
oh I know it's these ferocious hostile
times I suppose but it's just not the
same and it is nice has been going on
for a heck of a long time if anybody
probably noticed it's almost ten years
ten years
you know I bet I know but you all just
been thinking about that your sawstop
school mom is gonna continue talking for
another 10 years dismiss boy girl
you
well I think it's safe now don't you two
talk you know we haven't had a decent
conversation in almost 10 years I was
just talking about
there's been nothing since you've been
back we didn't even have a talk 10 years
ago that's that goodbye note by the
conversation stop
you know I was thinking about to this
day
I have something you gave me a book of
poems I remember do you Alan you
remember you remember everything all day
yeah but that oh yeah that was a day to
take stock day of great decisions I
decide I remember that too I decided
that you had no intentions of divorcing
your wife but you didn't know that but
for sure you didn't oh yes i did it was
you that didn't know and then there were
their goodbyes and have a happy summer
have a happy life
did you
I think so I'm glad of that
hey I tried to make the whole thing as
easy as I could you mean you transfer
then you came back didn't you I wonder
why Oh which brought it because you knew
you would be the head of the department
did you wipe here no one of my kids is
having a party I can only come for a few
minutes themselves I I just came to wish
you all via Hajj merry happy England
happy everything youtube you and yours
you haven't changed
but I have I have
you know I had to pack today and I
needed help do you know what I had to do
I had to post a notice in the market and
on the bulletin board help wanted well
the kids are all busy now graduation end
of the year so i told myself
I wonder why I told the waiter it didn't
want a drink
oh but there was a young boy who took
the job and no but he wasn't a student
now and he was a handyman or something
oh thank you kind sir I think but he was
a young person
and someone clearly with a problem so
vulnerable I wanted to reach out to him
so badly and I I just couldn't do it I
was so nervous I kept thinking about how
late it was and how I wanted to get rid
of him
which is what I want to do with you now
go
you
Oh
I help you
there people waiting
I'm sorry no i don't i'm sorry
I have time to read over his fire while
I was waiting for his sergeant but you
know there really is nothing here to
give you the slightest idea where it
might be tonight wonderful would you
like me to tell you what I do know it's
the best offer I've got right now we're
a couple of guys working after hours
service of the public without anyone in
overtime pay Michael Scott beautiful we
had some dealings with his fellow about
10 months ago song of intent to kill
thank you my pleasure he got into an eye
or what some woman in a bar watch this
stuff for years now well it really
doesn't matter it doesn't tend to
murderous intent to murder but it all
started on such a trivial thing they
were arguing about what president was
elected in what year did you believe it
and then this this man of yours he had
mad at something then he almost cooter
so look at the motions you know he put
the case in the calendar when I asked me
psychiatric examinations I knew which
way I was gonna go he was remanded to
the state's mental facilities tanjung
further determination of the defendants
mental capability to stand trial
and that's where he stayed until the day
before yesterday or whenever it was
that's what it was you didn't mention
any previous record well there wasn't
any I mean there's no next of kin
there's no no anything you don't like
your orders I'm watching my weight not
just stand in line wherever he is and
whatever his name really is or isn't I
think somebody could be in trouble mr.
rotor huh somebody usually is I went out
to the hospital day for a while not long
enough to really do the job but I did
find out that they had diagnosed him as
a paranoid delusions of persecution
usually accompanied by potential
violence concerning maybe some teacher
you once said at least the doctors
thought they got that far a woman they
figured middle-aged maybe I could apply
to that woman at the bar and a couple of
other women at the hospital though they
told me he was dasol most of the time as
a matter of fact he spent a lot of time
in the library which by the way was the
last place anybody saw him before he
took off I missed connections with the
librarian today I'll check her out in
the morning could be that something in
that library set the guy ha
do you realize how many calories one
peanut has well please don't tell me
that this is supposed to be the happy
hour I think you guys are gonna catch up
with this fellow pretty soon paranoids
don't spend too much time covering their
tracks and neither do hurricanes
you
hey you drop something
oh thank you
thank you very much
stress is there any chance to let us out
of school early today yeah we've all got
really big plans for tonight mm-hmm who
hasn't Harold don't tell me they're
finally going to let you out of here
today
it has to be today well fall for one
thing he was allowed to do what we are
doing right now to to walk from the main
building to the library you see we hate
to tie them down we we try to let them
do what they want ples how they like
grow a beard to have an identity you
ought to hide one yes he certainly was
hiding something and I certainly didn't
find out what you can't win them all doc
poor twisted brain talking about winning
as far as I can tell he never won
anything ever in his whole life not even
the right to walk around loose yes I
usually kept an eye on him all right
it's hard not to if a patient decides to
hate you you mean he got violent no he
was always very polite too polite I
thought the haight was there all the
same just under the surface yeah do you
have any way of looking up the records
to see what sort of books he checked out
well I don't have to look it up it was
the same book every day a textbook high
school English junior level the standard
used in the state oh it's a missing too
by the way well he dumb he take that
book and he study it for a while and
then he dead go over there and browse I
suppose now that's all I can tell you
maybe something happened over there set
him off thank you
hello you're dr. secare Ian's patient
aren't you I'm dr. Abel do you come here
often there was a young man here two
days ago perhaps you remember him his
name is Raymond
and I'm Raymond structure I wonder could
you tell me what Raymond was looking at
here it might help me to help him
there I appreciate that very much but so
many newspapers here perhaps you could
tell us which newspaper where he used to
live very very used to never do you know
the name of the place where he used to
live well that's too bad because it's
possible to draymond is in trouble makes
me feel bad because I like him I like
him a great deal I take it you like him
true you do don't you
he opens the door for me he even holds
my chair that's why I can't God what
tell on him
he shouldn't have done it I told him
people would get mad well I won't get
mad I promise you I won't so tell me
please please tell it what did he do he
tore out a story from the newspaper he
was reading that won't get any more
trouble with no that won't get him into
any trouble and you helped him you
helped him agreed to you I do like him
I'll take it from your doctor I'd go
back to work why co2 when it's chilly he
even goes and gets my coat
you
well the last class is over school's out
goodbye well thank you alice i hope you
have a nice vacation thank you goodbye
mr. Lucas I really enjoyed the class
thank you nice trip thank you very much
for your nice vacation so uh
you
I
excuse me I'm not talking my locker
locker oh excuse me
you
I don't get too
and I had to get it San and maybe this
is my last chance you sound so funeral
Alan that's an improper word to use
venereal but it's one semantically
sophisticated person to another how is
it possible to be fun Ariel about
something that's been dead for ten Mary
cut it out and listen for a minute will
you it was stupid of me to transfer back
to the school Mary very selfish that's
why you're leaving isn't it not because
of the kids because of me me the
proximity in a constant reminder oh
you're a dear Alan you really are I mean
it you really believe that it's still 10
or 15 years ago what is it aren't the
girls giggling as much when you tease
them between classes uh the mind I'm
sorry about that you had nothing to do
with my lead this is what I'm running
away from maybe it started with you but
before you or after you what really
mattered to me was I wanted to be a
teacher and I failed at being a teacher
for too long
goodbye Ellen you sure you know I just
trying to let me off the hook or
something I put in a request for an
early retirement two and a half months
before I even knew you were coming back
here well thanks you were trying to save
a little of my pride weren't you I just
wouldn't let you why Mary are you all
right by the way the girls don't giggle
as much oh if I were a girl I'd be
driving you crazy
Alan I came to finish miss bloomquist we
didn't need to yes I did I mean I have
to well that's very sweet of you Raymond
but it really isn't necessary yes it is
I mean you gave me that extra money you
know oh well I could use the help and
the company too I suppose I've been
putting all these things in this box and
oh there's the twine left over from
yesterday I'm sure they'll be enough I
figured it would be well I'm very glad
you're back Raymond I wanted to come
back miss Beatrice one two three four
hello testing testing one two three four
that's for tomorrow what was it you said
to me yesterday that you didn't graduate
from high school because of a test
that's right I needed a 70 still one
failed test they're usually ways of
repeating the course Oh Raymond please
forgive me if I'm getting too personal I
was just talking to you as if you were
one of my students you're not very old
you could be in one of my classes
I was living with my uncle on my aunt on
account of I'm an orphan I never got to
know anything about my mother I always
kept asking how wouldn't you Oh your
uncle is that your mother's brother we
moved a lot a lot of different states so
I never went long anyone school I mean
well at least he made it possible for
you to go no that was on account of the
welfare money we're above my uncle when
he would talk to his welfare people and
tell him that he had a nephew living
with him to went to school that's how he
got the welfare money so I just packed
my clothes and cleared out I didn't need
all that hollering and getting hit all
the time I'm talking about the time when
I didn't get a 70 on that makeup test it
wasn't just that one course I didn't do
so hot in the other one yeah that
principle he never liked me in the first
place so I just dropped out of school
packed up my clothes and pair it out I
told you that already died yes yes you
did um put my uncle would have kicked me
out anyway on account of losing the
welfare so I wrote him a couple of times
some greeting cards that i bought in the
PX I thought maybe my dad we're liking a
little bit better maybe she'd be sorry
because she always called me dumb uh you
said the PX were you in the army that
was a lot of rotten people there to not
only in the army everywhere since see
you
I could have gone on to school but it
was just that at one test just that one
what is that you have a textbook
ok
no wonder it got so quiet the band's
gone home oh I guess we're ready to go
to know we can't go yet miss bloom quest
we haven't finished with this something
else to be tighter everything looks done
to me you're a very conscientious person
right and I admire that well I have to
go to so I'll just go get my things
I never told you what happened after the
service today oh it was was just a lot
of moving around it's hard to keep all
eyes straight how do you expect me to
remember all i had anyway Raymond
they're never the last place that why
not so dumb that hospital with that dr.
Abel where they stuck me after what
happened at that other place that bar
dr. Abel big deal he's a big liar that's
try to tell me I'm wrong about badges
bluest eye dairy try to tell the pocket
dr. Abel be telling the truth when he
says he can make me feel better after
what was done to me I was done to me in
this very room
when I got treated so rotten when I got
all messed up for my whole life and when
I got cheated by you but few miss bloom
I will wait a little longer to make sure
nobody's here and then you're gonna do
it again let this stop you when they
took right gonna do it's fair my makeup
test from English Lit sure june twelfth
1961 right in this very same room that's
it the makeup test I passed fair and
square I got a 71 I deserved a 71 and
everything has happened since all the
stinking things terrible things they're
all your fault it's all your fault
he usually does that pulled my chair
when the dinner bell ring please don't
hurt him now look young lady don't worry
go and enjoy your dinner no he didn't
tear that out
I figured this out this morning this way
i can see but it doesn't show up me
outside you didn't know I was that smart
did you no no no this isn't right her
mouth wasn't covered until near the very
end I'm not till the very end I didn't
plan this you know I saw it all happen
lots and lots of times okay if you
scream nobody's gonna hear you so don't
scream
I'm sorry you're scared i can tell i am
i've been scared lots of times okay okay
now you're gonna go get me my test paper
it's in a folder marked s I'm keeping my
eye on it all along that box nice and
tie it up we have a whole series of
tests for every course it's been some
time since I used any of them we
switched them all around and mix them up
and over the years I don't know which
test it was I do miss Bloomquist a guy
remember certain things question number
one John Ruskin
are you s k I n tetek fallacy and give
an example from work by john ruskin see
it's the test that starts like that
and you better find
ok go back to my desk go ahead you know
what to do check the time I have one
hour check the time 720 ok wait
ask
no any questions ask it are there any
questions are there any questions no
miss Bloomquist bloomquist what an ugly
name ask it again are there any
questions any questions no not this time
I don't have to wave my hand at you for
nothing do you remember that Miss
bloomquist do you remember that well now
it doesn't matter because I learned
which questions are optional and which
ones are I learned that much
okay wait
two minutes two minutes went by when I
was telling you that two minutes all
right you have an extra two minutes okay
okay first question describe the meaning
of pathetic fallacy and give an example
from a work by john ruskin do you think
I don't know that
you'll see i start at the school for 27
years as Bloomquist future plans other
than the extended trip to England are
indefinite ass courts he will miss most
miss bloomquist said next year's classes
the students i'll never get to see I
think that must be the item you're
referring to sergeant yeah thanks now
look I'm gonna call your police
department and tell them what I know I'd
appreciate it if you'd call to and read
that clipping for confirmation and do it
right away please I'm not a feeling that
this miss bloomquist might need
protection maybe you're right now that's
right miss bloomquist keep checking the
answers the right ones and the wrong
ones
okay there they are the last two
questions those are the ones i didn't
get to answer because you wouldn't give
the instructions to me Raymond how did
you remember these last two questions
when you didn't get around to the last
time
I didn't remember that but I read the
book believe me I read that whole book
and the whole point is that this time I
knew that they weren't optional and
there they are both both answers The
Rime of the Ancient Mariner was a poem
written by Robert Browning it was told
by a wedding guest who stopped to talk
to this old sailor it's about a curse
that was put on the ship the wedding
guests once sailed upon because somebody
killed something Charles and Mary lamb
wrote many plays that were put on by
Shakespeare in his Theatre to answer
Part B Shakespeare's Romeo and Juliet
was about a boy and a girl who loved
each other the girl was very nice the
two of them only wanted to be together
nobody understood that they were just
happy together so they ran away to some
place that was like cave that's where
they got killed ok now you finish miss
bloomquist I get five points for this
one and five points for this one and
then I can add that on what I had and
I've got a 71 a little while ago Raymond
you said that you had thought about all
of this a lot you'd imagined just add it
up and something else about what would
happen later at it Adam and it doesn't
do me I want my braids don't get art
talk you like a teacher again this is
exactly how I must talk to you because
that's what I am if you're going to hurt
me if you got to do something to me I
haven't anything to lose perhaps I'd
tell you the truth anyway I'd like to
think so but Raymond these answers are
wrong
I'm gonna tell you what you did right
and I'll also tell you what you did
wrong that's what studying is all about
not the marks it's getting to know and
what's interesting and very encouraging
is that you were almost right on both of
these that's very good considering that
you were trying to teach yourself
I passed
you can that's what matters you can I
can't
it's too late
rosary unit 12 boarding on the residence
of one married Bloomquist 4125 ingram
place resident unseen be on premises no
sign of disorder better check out right
away
this is the book standard text high
school English junior level authorized
by state department of education this is
the right book and you can't tell me
that it isn't and I studied it hard well
I'm sure you did Raymond but this book
is supposed to be used by students and a
teacher and you look things up every day
I took it and I studied it how this book
goes right back right back where it
belongs
you
I
waiter run now miss bloomquist
you
I know you're in here miss Bloomquist
if they got done I'm not so dumb
what's better on the wall I just tripped
intelitan Talbot don't start screaming
at me I know a lot I studied real hard
all summer I mean what's fares therapist
Bloomquist it's Bloomquist Raymond yes
ma'am you know the rules of the school
students must be courteous now rudeness
and shouting will not be tolerated this
is a classroom and you will remain
seated Raymond yes ma'am now go to your
seat and the lesson we'll continue this
isn't a classroom I said sit down it's
dark classrooms aren't dark don't
interrupt just sit down and pay
attention we're going to study Romeo and
Juliet
I knew this wasn't a classroom
were you trying to trick me I'm not
trying to trick you we must go back to
the classroom and you will walk not run
do you hear me you will follow me with
proper decorum
go to your straight you know where it is
wait
I don't need to sit down
why should I listen to what you say miss
Bloomquist
didn't listen to me when I raised my
hand and asked you for instructions
about what was optional or what wasn't
and I had a right to know you didn't
listen to me you're right I didn't
listen and you deserve an explanation I
had a friend rady a man and that day
just before the test I broke off with
him when you raised your hands are just
looking out the door I was feeling very
sorry for myself 71 I tell you again
that the answers you gave on the tests
were wrong but I was wrong too because I
didn't give you a chance to understand
what you were supposed to do the wrong
my wrong was the worst one because I'm
the teacher and you're the student and
I'm a adult and you're just a boy it
isn't too late you can still pass that
test I'll teach you everything you have
to note right now please go to your seat
due to your seat braman
go to your seat
Oh
smokeless we saw light since you see a
classes in session now if you don't mind
as a beginning let's start with the
first question you missed The Rime of
the Ancient Mariner was written by
samuel taylor coleridge c 0 l-r c g he
now there are a couple of very
interesting things about mr. Coleridge
he was a very famous man a very
important man and he was worth studying
and one of the things that I think is
very interesting is that Coleridge never
finished school
and another thing after a while he went
to live with a doctor because he was
very troubled about things terribly
mixed up am I going too fast no it's not
you man
to tell you the truth I'm kind of slow
getting things i always get him sooner
or later of course we only have to get a
start tonight and then i'll come and
teach you at that oh well that place
where you live well you might have to
come a lot because like I say I'm a
little slow I'll make you promise I'll
come and teach you every day if it's
necessary that is until sep tember and
then I'll only be able to come on the
weekends because you see I might change
my mind about retiring of course then
I'd have to be here monday through
friday teacher but to complete the
thought on mr. Coleridge he felt that
people were really helpless in trying to
fix their own lives but as I always tell
my
I don't agree with that I did
you