hi hi yeah of course no I was lying it's
kind of weird it's a nightcap
oh my god that's so good can I try that
yeah of course it's definitely not bad
it's pretty light nice but it doesn't
compare with that yeah that's like so I
will ya so delicious Franken who's in a
nibbler yeah Nick 140 is this like the
first time you've done this this
internet dating is like the first time
I've done this so yeah I just had one I
like met a guy at a bar for drinks does
it not say if there's an awful actually
oh it was awful okay we're getting
somewhere what happened uh well you know
nothing but like I was there early I I
just got that really whatever I was
waiting for him and he was like 20
minutes late and then he shows up he's
wearing a popped collar and I was like
not a few that's it yeah totally I mean
if you would have been wearing a popped
collar I would've been out of here also
know it um but yeah that's the extent of
my internet dating dating you're you
you're filming me yes sorry i'll try to
remember your profile I try to make
those basically I've been working on
this one thing for like two years and
I'm like totally stuck with it though so
more like stressed and cranky about it
up ah fuck you so don't want to talk
about aside from that much less
stressful project I'm working on is this
music video for my friends band cool
yeah okay here's my stock question um
what kind of music do you like
what that is so lame that's labor that
should ask me what I do for what do what
do you do how is it so ladies make fun
of you at lunch Eva wherever I am 2dr
211 whatever I get appointment whatever
um second site listing fans you're not
going to know any of them what how do
you know that no no I might know more
about bands than you did it the hard way
to answer questions the stupid ones okay
what's the last thing you listen to oh
okay have you ever heard of a band fo
curry yeah totally really no I totally
happen I can't be right i would have
been so excited they're so good sorry so
Apple curry just broke my heart I was
like oh my god it's heard of them okay
so there's no but now there's this
opportunity for you to share that with
someone absolutely they're like a velit
actually are you on the line chirp we're
have you heard of it the lion's share no
I'm not on it and I
both those things well it's like a bit
torrent site you download like movies
yeah I know I know what you're talking
about you have to be invited though so
if you give me your email i could invite
you wow that's tricky i don't know if i
want to do that why i don't know if
we're at that level yet mark you're just
giving my room fine so then you're
you're about Apple curry again Nick what
my name um OH as in the letter got it
and Rep like nicorette like the gum or
ET te why'd it go let go so I'm gonna
send you my last time but ok and you
have to download a poker I will I will
why wouldn't I do the head that's what I
was like oh I want to check that and
you're like yeah what if you forget who
would they are ok um Apple curry is the
name of the band sorry does it hurt no
take this a little bit is there anything
else you want to put down their favorite
color yeah just so i know i didn't just
write your whole profile so i could look
at it whenever I want um ok cool awesome
um
so how long have you known you wanted to
be a filmmaker I'm just curious cuz like
I still don't know what I do yeah I know
you like I know I don't know um we had
my dad's big clunky VHS camera like it
was bigger than us like you did like I
feel like every families yes um and we
decided to remake ghostbusters cool yeah
it was totally awesome um it was weird
cuz all my friends were really into the
whole you know pretending being in the
movie thing but I like really enjoyed
being behind the camera huh and that was
something I knew I liked more than what
they were doing so I always add that's
it like I always just ended up being
there so awesome I guess I mean yeah
I've never seen Ghostbusters what it
really yeah i mean like this there's
plenty things haven't seen i'm not i'm
not seen but and ghostbusters this morn
of them all right that I can't all right
that that needs to be rectified
immediately like now I think I'd rather
see your version of ghostbusters is this
is this is way bigger than just me it
was a cartoon too right yeah it was a
cartoon it was with you got it you
haven't seen a movie we need to watch
ghostbusters right now
like for real I don't know there is a
blockbuster all the way to my house is
there pull it out there they might in
fact have a copy of ghosts questions
that we can then watch at your house
you
and they don't have it seriously
seriously where you what Holly foot
there was a collector series two
should we ask me to have a look in the
back yeah do they have a packet I mean
they might have actually
I don't know maybe they have it at like
me I don't know i would buy it i would
buy another copy just for this occasion
yeah i don't i don't see anywhere inside
know where you could sell dvds i don't
know what do you think
lion share lion share some one word it
uh doesn't it's not gonna matter search
awesome um is downloading ok I take
about an hour maybe two hours do you
wanna drink
oh is this it's my favorite little
opener see I can't I can't deal with the
hell yeah cheers yeah took ghostbusters
yeah the Ghostbusters downloaded by
listing mm-hmm and to me seeing it for
like the millionth time yeah it's a
pretty good job though it's like super
chill i can wear whatever I want I can
like it just hang out I don't know
that's a good job that's cool man do you
have a title ah record label do stuff
girl that would be my title I think
that's a pretty awesome title you win
yep it's embarrassing what's if you
don't hug oh yeah sure oh you're not
actually done oh I could have one too
late now that's a pretty satisfying
sound there's a like there's a mess huh
it doesn't oh there you go it's cool
they just fell over I don't I can't look
I'm not gonna move again that's okay are
you sure yeah it's me I'm sorry you want
me to leave all right I've had enough
it's about that yeah it's almost time
for ghostbusters it should boot mm-hmm
almost and just feel you're watching do
that you're gonna keep on pressing yeah
totally so much pressure
you
hey
yeah I'm just gonna go get a cab because
I'm really late but the subways that way
so okay cool yeah um he wasn't a lot of
fun last night yeah me too cool um what
are you doing this weekend I don't know
yet a friend of mine is coming in from
out of town I don't know what's going on
with that but I i can let you know if
you wanted to like pick Taylor something
yeah yeah cool that's great yeah uh yeah
yeah tons of fun and I'm definitely send
me that any time to that thing I want to
check out appleberry right definitely
all like chat with you on laughs oh ok
yeah
just tell when the music / working man
how is it take to get from the fucking
door
hey man hey how'd it go by alright man
what you guys waiting all night to do
that all night so she fucking put it in
her butt yeah man that was like the
first thing we did in there you know
some sarcasm yeah well are you gonna see
her again ah I don't know hopefully
breath is here where with us come on
that sir shit don't mean is there
something you want to tell us we're
gonna camp out here all night oh my long
you guys know what happened then I said
I was a good night right look at that
face he wants to tell us but he really
can't you that's not fun fun you don't
want to say anything I can deal I can do
change he's changed you know I'm just
merely a friend who's really concerned
about my friend getting action but if
you don't want to tell me anything
that's cool by me I'm over here with my
little Nintendo my internets all right
I'll be fine I like it by myself that's
the that's the song that's the deficit
second track yeah all right awesome oh
yeah that's a good one you gonna make
the video for ya hopefully if you still
want me to do i do want you to do it
yeah yeah totally I I just want you to
you know listen to it I'll listen to it
i'll try to get some ideas you know it
is the beginning of bear meeting season
what no I mean bears I mean they're just
just trying to mate now existence but
some bare fact bare fact what are you in
third grade was Oh perfect there's look
there's a direct correlation between you
know bears and no next site are you
looking at this is my wait no that's
really nasty that's gross it's very much
look I'm just saying is a direct
correlation between the Bears and you
and us and you know means his honey
season man spoke to me
can grab it yeah what are you guys doing
tomorrow tomorrow night specifically um
I think I might see the new James Bond
movie with my dad it's a heartwarming
experience on that no it sounds good I'm
gonna be playing at stain if if you're
free um I think I might actually end up
seeing that girl again hopefully I mean
that's awesome and if you looking for
something to do you can bring her and
tell her to bring some of that hot honey
with her yeah perfection I don't know
man I I'm kind of reluctant about that
idea that he's pretty terrible Gracie
like what if she what if she didn't have
any friends and she's just gonna end up
going home with you or some other
stubbly scurries yaris know when does
this ever happen why this always happens
it's true man like guitars like nature's
pussies Backman Fairfax you it's bare
fucking fact I'll even wash you thinking
do you do that equals ting ting ting
yeah all right all right maybe I'll see
you tomorrow maybe ah Maddie have fun
with your pops mm-hmm later dad tell me
how the movie goes right yeah all right
let us later goddamn door you gotta fix
this shit know what was that about
anyway yeah dad I said it was fine okay
we could just probably sketch another
showing another time look good Oh even
if is still playing mm well um there's a
show coming up in with my friends now
you don't know him dad you don't know
him his name's Bruce he's in the band
and he's playing the show he really
wants me to go so I mean you know
oh no nothing really unusual she seemed
fine yeah well me what'd you expect dad
dad dad I'm fine okay I mean I got paid
last week all right well when I go to
show how they just give me a call that
day and then maybe we can see if we can
you know find another time to go see it
or just just give me a call we'll see
what happens okay all right now love you
too
mm-hmm oh god what have I started yeah
we got to put the put a stop to that as
soon as possible yeah right its Mary
chicks just Oh drive one point funky
left on I 278 okay Thank You yeah we're
gonna be waiting we're gonna be like no
doubt about it we're gonna walk in and
Gracie's gonna be like oh thank you
everybody that was our last off that's
haven't realized
hey dick kerala I thought of calling
what's her face but I didn't I was like
yeah it's too soon do you watch project
runway uh oh really oh hi well I mean
the girl have a massive crush on ya is
the winner so I kind of perked up my day
a little bit did you did you celebrate
her victory with Jane oh yeah actually
Jane was the one that got me out to the
show got us your contestant ya know ya
remember one has a contestant yeah well
you know those situations where you have
a girlfriend date they have a TV show
they have to watch I basically watch
whatever she watches and she watched the
project runway so I started watching
Roger project project of the way I
started watching project runway but yeah
she has all these shows she needs to
watch so I i watch them it's like I have
any shows i'm going to watch I'm like
the complete opposite of that I like
like I'm even worse than her I need to
watch like pretty much everything
not necessarily project runway but you
know I mean yeah it's sure it is true i
mean i did get into lost because of you
yeah that's what happens again this
shows because of other people yeah I
don't know these are always things that
I just discovered on my own
you
rolled out those welcome arms hold me in
close don't let me go to the form of the
brightest star
I'll be okay lost in your swing
that's how hard today you know I'm like
I was looking at that thing over there
with a giant George yeah I did the
cyborg sent back from the future to give
us democracy yeah it's fine hey
everybody my name is bracing it's like
Tracy with the beat I'm gonna put the
song that I haven't really a name yet I
just read it last week yo what's that
what's going on okay I like your shirt I
like your jacket thank you thank you
Claire bag and ours combined will be a
totally suave what can do yep there's
the shoes whoa I was in my early in this
picture before I thought they got his
throwing up blood but apparently is
fired but if you go over here it looks
like a stripping blood oh I'm chica I
don't know who goes about that is it's
sort of like some guy who owns a place
has his friends decorated or is it just
people do it and then so I recently
started a netipot school
I believe is right don't you want to
feel just the same everything you find
everything you want will leave me behind
gonna fit inside what we define
everything what we can hard and it's so
damn easy to ended I think ajikko up in
a counter you know I mean like everybody
the people think they'd totally original
stuff we're just ripping on someone else
you know that's true I mean Kurt Cobain
seven you made out it smells like teen
spirit she was basically trying to make
a really good pixie song right yeah
totally I never heard that but i can see
that like I'm sure like when the Pixies
were making their songs they were like
oh let's make a really great talking
heads song yeah that had a flyer out for
their bassist and it's like someone that
has the influences of Peter Paul and
Mary and hüsker dü and then that's how
like the basis during the band The
Pixies yeah that's crazy it's in the
basis the girl mmm deal that's crazy I
don't know Marty Buffy what's the part
above you what are you talking about hey
Marty public I'll make a song called
sounds like a dog's
everything about just walking away from
it take a break like what am i doing if
I take a break from this and I don't
have anything else that I go back to
when I'm not doing this like this is my
break so if i take a break from this
ecology you should stop buying these
shitty lighters and got like a fucking
Zippo you know I see the mic off in
boonton shit like that yeah I'm look to
the fucking man ladies of shit ah fucker
terrace you're a terrorist nothing just
explode yeah yeah yes it did
that's fucked up love the thing like pop
in your pocket god damn it I hate my
artistic life crunch it ignites my old
pan
but you know
I'm not six feet under I'm just six me
just dreaming you and the way you were
okay hey Wow
I
can we take this car place grab me off
I promise
you sue
I
I don't know something came up and we
just didn't go I don't know what hmm
yeah i know most important to me too i
mean if it was so important to him yeah
yeah I know Mom no mm-hmm okay look mom
I have to go to work so would be ok if I
just called you back later all right
yeah no sir Hanlon no I'm I'm sorry okay
okay mm-hmm I love you too bye bye
yo ass fuck you up hey nice pajamas what
so you're gonna get up fuck no ok you
know some nice days three o'clock you
know yeah so forgive all to shit your
shit i'm going to go to work I'll catch
you later
love find a boy's love
I
you
thank you
goes down beside me
comparing notes of fine
she was
hey
you
anytime a dad called me recently oh yeah
uh-huh put it back down he want to go
see another new Bond movie but on hmm
well we kind of blew me off the first
time so when you want to go see it again
I blew him off and I kind of feel like a
dick about it why it's comic this old
tradition where I can't find the thing
by the wait for this and nothing for
anything this is your hose you're not
well you are a day but you're not being
a dick right now sure yeah
I should put a little more um no I put
enough I kept in mind here spicy thing
thank you like the school a bit more
right I have this going on over here
yeah just you can even put it away I
don't know okay hello oh my god you're
such an asshole what I go like it do you
want to put the food yeah yeah I do
actually okay yeah well um you can mmm
and besides it makes her cum tastes
awful what I thought it makes your cum
tastes awful my cum tastes awful it's
the spices it's not your tongue tastes
lovely usually but not well I know what
not to expect you I'm gonna take a shit
and I'm going to think about
there
yeah I mean I'm just here for the
weekend like a class on Monday so I'm
back to the grind no that sucks yeah i
mean that's okay it's like it's nice to
be back in school again doing a
something yeah yeah totally like I kind
of wish I was back in school again cuz I
don't feel like I'm doing it yeah I mean
it gives you definitely purpose right
that's what you're paying for yeah play
my thousands of dollars yeah so like i
mean i have to pay like over seven
hundred dollars in textbooks where I
don't have seven hundred dollars right
she already gave them right thousands of
dollars oh yeah right it didn't cover
nice looks though that's ridiculous I
mean you're already paying them to like
spend that time to give you all that
information yeah it's like the education
hey that's your pain or not Brian you
owe me that and then i will learn yeah
yeah it's totally backward um that's
backing your past backwards I don't like
to think about that of the weekend my
relaxing time this is Jane time this is
Jane time okay cool ask your world just
a part of Jane time yeah yeah two of us
yeah um Matt was telling me about this
thing that you're doing with Gracie the
video thing oh I was like I'm doing you
know I got the signal yeah totally um
Matt signal I get those all the time
like every day yeah um you know he's
like oh I have this song that I want to
put out on youtube in my space and stuff
just to get more stuff out there to use
like oh you know if you could do a video
so I was like all right yeah sure of
course oh yeah I guess I'm it I'm really
like worked hard at all I guys like no
ideas for it whatsoever
I mean I'm sure I think of something
like hopefully I always thought your
stuff was really awesome no thanks sure
yeah mr. I mean like when we were in
school like I was always really really
impressed okay yeah sure okay I'm like
oh right totally you know that though
you know that Alan I don't know yeah how
it is like with me I'm just like I don't
know food's ready kids
Oh too much too much too much doing what
fuck did you do waters not gonna help
him oh my helpful look what am I
supposed to do what what are you doing
what are you Elsa base this stuff like
you know that I'll be a solution that is
d that's what I Bob okay you know what
Fairfax you're retarded you to know with
the fucking bear fact he was saying it
and then he's got me thing it and I just
did not think that one was gonna want
what is this on me like this on TV or uh
so on next computer actually seriously
mm-hmm next computer hooks up to the TV
yeah next the man with the plan oh cool
you'd better my curtains now uh yeah
it's just you know it's a work in
progress you know it's gonna take some
time sometime you do that shit all the
time yeah well I mean it's so usually
just stupid shit you know I can't just
will it out of nowhere when I was
something important yeah for you will be
important
you mad at me oh but why so my cum
tastes funny there thank you hey fucking
back you guys really gotta stop with
that I'm gonna kill myself oh god I'd
love to stop doing that before I'd kill
myself wait fuck this we're going to do
a blind taste test Nick I want you to
beat off into a cup we'll do a Pepsi
challenge see what she says I kind of
already did that so I was waiting for
you to ask oh really yeah I mean it's
been here for a while though so all
right you probably have a bit of an
advantage is probably a little bit more
fresh let's fucking do this right now
you guys are so fucking gross that's
disgusting I've been remiss for a long
time so I've been a matter of time I've
been doing these taste test yeah that's
exactly what in me that was the one
thing I respond it didn't hey what are
you doing out here uh
I really uh you know smoking the
apartment while you were there yeah yeah
I guess yeah it's me yeah that is you
can you like drink out here is that ok
is there like public consumption or
something whoa what do you mean I don't
know that sounds stupid uh I can you do
that I just got dive-bombed by a moth or
so actually that looks like a monster be
it's it's nighttime you're not supposed
to be here oh my god it's right there oh
jeez
this is really not giving you points in
the masculinity department right now I
don't step on it oh no i'd rather have
it like stab me know it my jangle there
oh yeah sure
that was quick
it's much better sure
I my teeth stained yeah a little bit
really just a little bit i knew i was
gonna be like no it's fine all right
you're losing teeth points fair enough
maybe just wondering you can do what you
want haha I'm not responsible if he
catches you yeah
so I'm talking about this internet
though um there's really sadly nothing
to tell unfortunately so is that why
you're sit down cuz she hasn't called
you look down really come on alright
maybe I'm a little down I guess do you
think I could maybe have a cigarette
really all right thank you one of my
lighters exploded the other day like
seriously that habakkuk speed yeah
apparently it's just this thank you sure
sorry you didn't explain it to me like
what why are you sit down I don't I
still don't really understand it's about
the girl it's not about that's it am I
creatively constipated like all the time
oh okay disgusting what constipated us
you know I don't like toilet humour or
language okay here's underwears nobody
now it's just like it's like I know that
things will be fine eventually yeah so
if things are going to be fine later
they're gonna be fine now mm-hmm fine
later
you get that from somewhere or something
what is that maybe yeah I do feel better
cool
are you going to your dad soon yeah
you're gonna be back for lost this is a
new one yeah it's the new season fuck k
set the DVR it's already said that you
said it once and it remembers I'm not
gonna make it in time we're going out to
my dad's birthday dinner sir it's your
dad's birthday Friday but I'm I mean
we're just celebrating tonight Oh
perfect what is this it's uh it's a
screener copy of quantum of dollars yes
serious yeah totally you know it's like
they give it to the critics so I mean
it's kind of like a bootleg but yeah
shaky cam corder type it's a real DVD oh
dude Thanks no seriously like this one's
a lot like my dad's gonna love this I
mean like I owe you great man yeah and
don't worry about it I mean if you want
to like have sex with my girlfriend or
something just like go ahead well I mean
how do you know I already haven't good
point good point you sure the DVR set
it's it's definitely sad don't worry it
is it's good alright cool watching today
is a good day yeah motherfuck when I get
back I'll take care of it later stop as
you know I want to hear no I defy her
plan for me hey Bracy it's Nick what's
going on man you still want me to do
that video right okay cool man um cuz I
got a bunch of ideas for it turns out so
um the yeah yeah no I did why what's up
well I mean what why does anybody put
music on the internet so people can hear
it
um what I did um you were selling it at
the show so I you know you're already
disseminating it to random people so I
didn't it didn't even cross my mind how
is that different well dude I mean it
sounded pretty damn good to me i did i
wish i had no idea that you that it
wasn't a finished product yeah i guess
we'll talk to you later man later
hey Eva it's nick it some 20 25 on
Thursday and I was just wondering if you
were doing anything tonight because my
friends band which I told you about is
playing at this place and of course
you're all into new music and shit so I
thought you might like to come along I
guess if you get this before this
evening give me a call back and maybe we
can I don't know get something together
all right hope to hear from you soon bye
it didn't fucking record it's not my
fault i said it is I did everything I
was supposed to do I can't I mean you
know the technology that's what it wants
a fucking time morning yep no well
actually we don't have time warner's not
bad well fucking Skynet fucking
cablevision I don't know I think maybe
the show was just so awesome the DVR
shadow I mean what what little piece of
technology knew I wasn't going to be
home so sabotage yourself so I kind of
watch the show principal the matter mr.
fucking principal this is why we should
not have thrown another fucking VCR the
only quality not what happened you need
quality you don't prefer quality I can
TV shows well I mean I was gonna get it
off the internet you know with great
quality and no commercials but if you're
not into that so well me if you're gonna
do it and then by all means do it I'm
just saying like when you need your fix
doesn't matter right you're the great
fuck fuck fuck did you watch it I
watched it yeah okay was it good it was
you know I don't even put even tell me
all right but I got it I just have to
save this no don't don't don't don't all
right it was awesome how was the movie
then watch it but I did give it to him
and he was actually really happy about
that good a thing I made his night
excellent thank you no problem the fuck
is this what the fuck is patches on the
radio fucking apple curry I don't
believe this oh it's that band i was
listening to that one time where you
were like oh who is it sounds like oh
it's apple cart you look great you
fucking leave me this and what you know
i don't even listen to the radio yeah
actually is about to ask you about that
why are we listening to I don't know my
ipod was no i don't know what i did with
it under something somewhere okay
machines fucking machines yeah it's
hiding from me I fucking hate this song
that it's not that that they always take
the worst song on the album and make it
the single i will never understand that
i mean i know i'll just tell people that
you're in first and your wicked on the
ground I'll garner you enough seen funds
right great yeah just make sure you
don't show them this song
you find it yet uh not yet one sec it's
not working my name is not working and
it's being weird it's not working Shh
don't worry I'll get it for you this is
fucked this is bear fucked it'll be all
right
who is welcome
Oh
close time that we go
minus son
the young
you're so moany
what you say
they're just fine
young I believe
where's your say
from
hi Lee
is everything
Oh
me
shut up
I'll see you
was
I
nah
e
you now
to watch you feel
and consume me
okay rubber this would live yet so I
enjoy the kind of worked on it from
something that happened my friends
inspector
its back
swimmer to
oh shit
small
give it up for Dominic back down the
gums and then get is kicking up the base
and then please say thanks for making
rounds night hey yo what's going on man
fucking crazy shit yeah i know i think
it's like the biggest crowd you had yeah
it's pretty crazy some crazy shit danger
it's insane yeah no joke oh well you
know how you put our my demo online yeah
yeah well somebody from a demo label
they downloaded it long story short I
think we're getting Sun dude holy shit
fuck yeah it's all city crazy i I'm Eric
you know that dude don't worry about it
obviously over town yeah you're fine I
told them that we shot a video and and
they want to see it so we've got to get
working on some luck relations yeah
thanks a lot
Thanks yes I'm freaking out yeah I'm
figured it's clearly out bring it up and
just go in I a girl dude I met a girl is
also a chair for me she I think she she
must have downloaded some our music
offline I don't really know how but she
ended up coming to one of our shows we
talking after she's got offered a
psychic reading Maddie yeah you love you
honey hey so this is what I'm thinking
doing at your place my place a bar so we
can talk we should totally go to a bar
but you better maybe yeah go with diner
or something that would be great I'm not
really i really don't have to that's it
come on there's no need for that I mean
I really did have fun with you laughs
like yeah I didn't know he was your
friend right all right no it's don't
worry about it look it's not like you
know we were in a serious relationship
or anything we were always only that one
night I mean I of course I did have a
lot of fun that night too but well yeah
the net
have you heard the new apple cart
haven't been into that much since I got
like really
yeah no I heard them on the radio apple
commercial yes thank noon woman it's for
the new ipod I which you know probably I
don't know such as death or something
Thanks can do ever
blow dry your hair blow-dry your hair
cheese grater that's no shoes I
temperature indicator they've pulled me
back him / bernal fro from from the
godfathers it's one of those moving
pictures you know like that that's sexy
one juicing is from Sarah Sarah cos
Jessica's Parker's sexy town please
we're gonna move with it here mm-hmm and
you ever notice when like old people
come in because like never remember the
title the movie they want to say mm hmm
well i kind of whittled it down to like
a couple basic rules um first off if the
word uh it's in front of a title it's
just totally a minute or they added if
it isn't there they also do this thing
where they plur eyes and deep low rise
movies so transformers is it becoming
like ah five seniors for the transformer
pickle i transformed i change from this
woman came in once and she was like give
me three seniors for failure to launch
and there's no movie even close to that
darkie all I fucked it up you said
failure was federalize yet she asked for
full throttle I'm sorry but she's like
anyone for full throttle so she went
from failure to launch the full throttle
somehow they won't have to do it like
flying some kind of permit bottling
anything but did you like the wrong yeah
I all right forgive me I'm give me a
thumb okay ghostbusters all right to
seniors for the break ghost bust that's
breaking the rules you're not following
the rules don't you know the rules you
just do whatever you want it's like jazz
the foundation just keep going hey
that's awesome they totally do that now
it's true it's like um what's the fee
say it's like a total it's like a polar
back back to shut up it's a bear fat
yeah you can't have that joke that's
it's my job so you wish I think that's
my joke anyway those little thing
hey baby boy coffee's up if you want
right see you had a long night last
night yeah it was pretty long yeah
where'd you think of braces new
girlfriend she's knife yeah slammin body
hey did you happen to download lost
you're my man with a hook up soon
fuck what fuck that sucks oh yeah you
just knew it was gonna end this way
though well come on man I'll make her
wrong well uh we'll call it the bare
bears don't share sure they do sure they
do how they don't they don't share
that's it dude fuck all right well what
did i doing why insure me there's me
there's a night okay okay not a bear
anymore well thanks yours a baronet
let's see line share bare facts we've
got tiger beats we get hey let's write
you a song
you
back in 20
26 it was easy to forget it was simple
answer in with all the chemicals in my
blood strength all that
I spent two sleep I couldn't build my
own machine that would have kept my man
murray's from slowly disappearing
cries and cheers we faced our fears
every day on that TV screen last time I
looked away I forgot the meaning in my
little tree
you