you
hello hello dr. Tracy yo this is dr.
Tracy this is david Harmon I don't know
if you remember me but I was in your
class next year ah yeah yeah yeah David
um it's a little bit early isn't it uh
what I do for you well I remember you
talking about UFOs all the time and how
was one of your favorite hobby yeah yeah
yeah I'm mom that's one of my interest I
know this will sound weird but I just
saw a UFO okay okay describe it to me it
was like a big fireball that came out of
the sky if we were right over me and
light up passing trees okay was there an
explosion not exactly I don't know it's
hard to describe but I've never seen
anything like it in my life I know it
was gonna plan or anything I think it
might be a meteor where were you at
where'd this happen um right outside of
Harley bill the town I live in yeah
that's about five hours from here I know
but I really think this is something
worth checking out um where can i meet
you if you take out to 27 off the
turnpike and follow it to the left it'll
bring you right to where i am right next
to a big field okay ah stay by the side
of the room you're the field i'll give
me time make a few phone calls I'd be
there about six hours from now ok don't
worry I'll wait for you great ok we'll
see you about six all right
you
ah
mom we hurry up with my eggs I'm making
yours now cow nice and coffee mouth no
coffee ain't no good Annie it makes you
nervous shut up JJ what's the truth it
makes you nervous mom I'm gonna be late
okay Carol I'm moving as quickly as I
can legs wait for what huh you heard
what I said what the hell are you late
for I'm gonna be late for the prom here
your age don't you get snotty with me
girl now where the hell you're going
love your business where I'm going yeah
as long as you're in this house it's my
business sure for God's sake she's 25
years old please don't treat it like it
shut up I know what you're doing I'm
gonna meet that Michael Smith kid I told
you before his old man's I jerk and I
don't want you to have nothing to do
with that family oh just because you
tried to cheat Michael's father out of
some money and didn't get away with it
he's a jerk huh oh you're the jerk and
everyone knows it Harold please Oh mom
everybody knows dad's a liar and a cheat
not to mention a drunken bum Jo good
face
yeah just she didn't mean what she said
you know she didn't mean it Michael's a
nice young man you upset about what you
said JJ please go after your father he's
acting crazy he's got hurt your sister
what can I do mar he's got a gun you
know how I get JJ Montague 40 thanks
would you please go after your father
now okay but I don't know what I can do
dad's in a pretty nasty mood please do
what you can get going
god I hope JJ could stop your father dad
won't hurt Carol I hope not I hate him
my girl
my god what's that we look at that boy
ain't that something ha what is that
thing and what kind of man was that
don't think it was any kind of man JJ
but he don't matter this thing here
could be with a lot of money but what is
it more what's it for oh it's for
something JJ I'm sure that go home get
the wheelbarrow shovel we're gonna take
this thing with us golly boy
you
Thank You Man don't do that to me don't
do what I'm serious don't scare me like
that and get that smile off your face
it's not funny hey come on it was only a
joke yes some joke you should have seen
the look on your face you're just lucky
I didn't kick you what with my crazy
father chasing me out here with a gun
and they are you scaring the hell out of
me are you serious no I like to tell my
i mean about your father with a gun I
thought I heard a shot it with him he's
been drinking again as usual I don't
care this is the fourth time he scared
you with a gun Michael you know how he
is he's been that way his whole life
that's his problem I want you out of
there now you don't have to put up with
this Michael I can't go I can't leave
mom and auntie here all alone with him
they've got JJ to take care of him
Michael I don't want to leave you I love
you then we'll leave together and if we
have to we'll take a knee and your
mother with us no I don't want us to
start things off wrong look I want us to
get married and have a normal life but
if we run away from harley bill things
will never be right ok Carol but I know
one thing if that father of yours scares
you like this again I'm gonna beat his
face in
David the SIA I agree back to come on
where do you think this thing came down
I hope you all think I'm making this up
David I wouldn't be here but if you're
on the level i warded this thing go down
well I want beyond those trees i run the
distance it's gonna be a couple miles
any trails going back that away well
looks like we're going to be doing a
little hiking by the way does anyone
else know about this no not that I know
you mentioned anyone I'm a people in
this town would understand something
like a meteor well maybe more than that
David after you called this morning I
checked it several my sources in the
scientific community and found out that
something with the rather unusual mass
did come down what do you think other
people are gonna be looking for
thankfully no I talked her friend of
mine over the Air Force Base and
according to him they've already chalked
this one up as a meteor that burned up
in the atmosphere oh really but there is
something we don't be concerned about
that is we're losing daylight fast I'm
go get going okay you'll be the way
right
hey watch what you're doing boy don't
worry Paul okay
Michael I don't know maybe she went to
you cool down before you talk to him
Carl I'm talking to him now yeah but
Michael something's going on over there
and I don't think this is the right time
for a confrontation no Carol now come on
let's go what is this thing where did
you get it dad where's Carol shut up I'm
busy JJ get this thing in the garage
just a minute out out wallet hey you
pull one more stunt like this morning
I'm taking care away for good Michael
please you're just gonna make things
worse yet gone ok man I'm going you just
leave Carl one ok the heck is that thing
not a your business Punk kept moving JJ
wait a minute JJ what is that and where
did you get it well we found this green
man in the woods and Paul shot at it and
it dropped this way sir shut up JJ I
don't want nobody knowin about that now
walk it up
ah Franco so just pulled up
I'll bet it came to see that thing from
the Green Man any Montague I've told you
there's no such thing as a green man hey
really glad you could make it hey lucky
you look pretty today ain't nothing like
you know us this thing you call me out
here to see better be good it is ragged
is you say it's worth a lot of money
you'll fetch it well are we ever gonna
get to see this great discovery jure
sure I'll get it for you right now JJ
Oh
what in heaven's name is that he did
something else oh it's something else
all right
what the hell is it Joe don't know what
it is but I ain't never seen nothing
like it and it come from a green man
Green Man oh for God's sakes Frank let's
get out of here wait a minute girl I'll
do the thinking here I never seen
nothing like this before yeah and
wait'll you see what it does all right
good good and I'm real anxious to see
what this thing does and JJ found this
little switch on it you got to turn it
on with a pole give me the pole JJ but
you can't get near this thing when it's
on
well that's something huh and I'm
telling you Frank it was this weird
green man I know it sounds crazy but it
was
I pause telling the truth Frank I seen
this thing to Frank honey we gonna stay
here and put up with this put up with
what we ain't lyin Vicki you know I
think there's something to what you say
and I'll tell you why now Tom Gibbons
told me this morning that he saw a
fireball fall out of the sky all right
so let's say there is a green man and he
dropped this this year thing he did he
did I you say this thing is worth a lot
of money and you're probably right but
you know what Joe this green man would
be worth one hell of a lot more money if
we got it to the right people I never
gave that a thought hot damn franker
right all we got to do is hunt the space
manner blow a hole through no no no we
got to get this thing alive now look I
know certain parties in the city that
would pay big bucks if we could get to
this thing before the government boys do
no no we we got to go out and we got to
catch this bird alive it ain't gonna be
easy just so thrilled us I got it all
figured out you are you and we can go to
town and get some of the boys to help us
it's better to have too many than not
enough yeah but they're gonna want some
of the money sure will pay the boys a
little slice but we're talking big bucks
here Joe and I paying off some of the
boys
we're going to put a dent in what me and
you get yeah you're right JJ lock that
thing back in the garage and guard it
with your life I don't say nothing to
your mom or your sisters oh I ain't
going to paw don't worry Frank sweetie
do you really think there is a spaceman
you think I'd be getting involved here
if I didn't stop your worrying fucking
you'll see we're all gonna be rich well
that part of it does appeal to me all
right all right enough talk now let's go
get some helpers before this spaceman
decides to go back to the moon keep an
eye on that thing what here
my fall in a corner
here
look what just walked in who is that
that's Frank custom
patrasche didn't mean him Thank she's
trash too hey guys hey Frank Vicky well
if it ain't Joe Montague what you been
up to Joe nothing good that's for sure
y'all see what we've seen out at Joe's
where you shut up how many times do I
have to tell you how sorry Frank hey
Frank what are you gonna have I'll take
a whiskey I got my own she ain't drinkin
no I listen everybody hey Joe and me we
got a proposal for some of you what kind
of our proposal a business proposal
Giddings if you'll shut the hell up and
give me a chance to talk what you got in
mind Custer ok here's the deal and Joe
and me we need a couple of good men to
go out with us tonight and do a little
hutton you're gonna hunt at night yeah
this is something a lot different than
regular old hun that's right Alice and
we don't need no women hey no crap Frank
what's the deal all right now Joe and me
wheeze onto something big I mean real
big big bucks kind of big now what we
need are some guys with guns to go out
with us tonight out around Joe's house
to hunt something out in the woods what
are we looking for Frank a bear some now
this ain't no fair is it something
unusual something special hello I'll
tell you guys all about it tonight at
nine o'clock where we all meet over joes
house all right now wait a minute Frank
what can be worth so much money that
you've got a hundred night yeah it don't
sound right the minish wouldn't I look I
know we got something here worth big
bucks and I ain't going to share with
the whole world just those who comes and
helps us now if you go out to joe's
tonight you'll find out what it is and
you won't regret it Neela we got
something good here as flicking she
knows that's right I thought a job a
woman did not tell you I don't want the
whole world knowing about this huh all
right who's gonna go with us and be it
on this hmm and who wants to be on the
big bucks I'll go with you tonight
anyway good that's one I'll come out to
juvie just to hear what you got to say
yeah me too but I ain't promising i'm
going to the woods though I know one hey
now there's two more smart man all right
now I need a few more who's coming what
the hell it's better than staying with
my old lady count me and Frank and I can
bring my uncle too good that's it and we
got enough men now that's it the authors
closed I don't forget we meet at nine at
my place and that's right bill old buddy
and you guys don't forget to bring your
guns hello we meet at nine o'clock sharp
at joes
ok
where the hell is your brother I don't
know he's outside somewhere
ah what's wrong with him your father's
weird I hate him she was my father I
hidden to JJ I tell you thrown on the
ground you hear me boy or window and
ayman um ahead where's the wrong thing
ha the Green Man jump me it must have
took the thing what do you mean it took
the thing how in the hell could you let
it do that I told you to lock it in the
garage I was getting ready to pawn then
I heard a noise back here so y'all just
come back here like a fool and let the
green man take it damn you boy now
you're gonna make me look like a fool
the Frank of the guys we can get that
round thing back to nightfall when we
catch the green man yeah sure if we
catch the damn thing you better pray we
catch it we're all turn you over to
Custer and let him deal with you
ah tell you what David we're losing
light fast let's say we call off the
search today and pick it up tomorrow you
don't think I was lying do you I mean I
know this thing came down around here
David David I believe you all the way
just that we've got to find some
fragments if there are any well how
about you but I'm hungry let's see we
head into town and get something to eat
yeah I guess it does sound good all
right
mom that going hunting no way I I don't
know what he's doing don't worry
yourself about it I'm not worried about
him I'm worried about JJ if I know he's
going to yeah keep on talking
hey the boys are here just like they
said man is straight I tell you just ER
we're gonna be rich man yeah but you
know Joe we got to catch this bird first
I've been thinking I think we ought to
let some of the boys take lead now let
them walk in front because we don't know
what we're dealing with here and there
ain't no sense in us get neither blowed
off
hey customer waiting hey right right we
know Joe and me was just getting our
plan set we still don't know what we're
hunting hey I know you don't know bill I
know you don't know that's why I want
you to meet out here at Joe's before we
go out well then what the hell is what
I'm about to tell you is going to sound
a little bit unbelievable but it's the
truth you know me and I wouldn't lie
about something like this neither would
Joe
what we're going to be cutting out there
some kind of creature look look I know I
know what I'm saying I know it sounds
crazy but I'm telling you there's
something out there and it ain't human
we can bring it in a lie we're all gonna
be rich
just hold on it I don't customer money
you ain't the most reliable men in town
what I do know they're crazy enough to
drag us out here for nothing you're damn
right now look I've seen that thing I
even shot at it well I know it's out
there well I'm gonna get my shot we're
about the rest later yeah I'll go with
her okay what's this thing will look
like it don't matter what it looks like
it don't look like us and that's all the
caps listen Joe and me are going into
the woods we're going down to ebony the
road follow us yeah
we're gonna look for ma hey how about a
game of Scrabble I hate Becky
I got quite a jukebox piloting solar's
new song okay hey Roscoe give me another
great gonna slow down big you Frank's
gonna get mad if I'll let you get
overthrown Franco didn't get mad at
nobody cuz we're gonna be rich
yeah nice place David yeah it's not much
but foods here father David how you
doing you and your friend want some
menus a big great idea and can I get a
vodka martini shaken not stirred on the
rocks with a twist of lime know how
about here sure can good for you David
yes large I know you don't believe it
but you'll see Frank expect you'll see
where's my cap it's a big secret without
are you really son of your iced neck
Frank and Joe are up in the woods and
they're gonna catch this space name that
keenya spaceman when you talk about his
face man from Mars or David do you know
that woman yeah he Johnson see if you
can get her over here okay hey Vicky
Vicky come here oh hi Davy Harmon you
sure are growing out quick Oh once your
seat
by a dream you're a true gentleman now
don't even know your name this is dr.
trace is one of my college professors
and we're so glad to meet you Becky hey
Vicky heard you say that Frank's on the
woods what's he doing out there ain't
supposed to tell nobody you can trust us
we wouldn't tell anyone would we David
no not a word of it no no Frank might
get mad at me if I tell you hey if we
don't tell Frank he can't get mad right
yeah I guess you're right okay so what
what city good to up and Herndon you
know where the old Barkley shed is Joe
Montague seen a green space man there
this morning and he and Frank are gonna
catch it and sell it for a lot of money
your son or not yes very good idea she
means fun waiting for hostile eviction
yeah thanks big simulator yeah we're in
another driven by Frank
all right guys listen up I figure the
best thing is to fan out a straight line
maybe 5 10 feet apart well what if we
see something you yell out and you let
the rest of us know that's what are you
scared Thompson get off me come on
Thompson cool down yeah save your fight
for this thing we're looking for okay
okay I'm hey don't you think we ought to
get moving I I real important guys you
see these ropes me and Joe we're going
to use them to catch this bird alive so
you just shoot the scarit okay now
remember we fan out but stay close all
right boys let's go
hey what's that what is it look don't
lose it ain't gonna get away from
oh shoot oh shoot animistic got it
corner oh my god it's shiny it's not
kidding hell with this let him have it
Oh wittle eyes hey Joe for good if you
ain't gonna stop them okay though you
and me and Jay Jake still carry out our
plan come on
it's incredible David it's actually
happened to realize that an alien life
of an alien life-form has finally come
to earth can't believe we're those fools
shooting at the creature dr. Tracey and
her shooting back it must have been
provoked David
you
Frank custard he's bad news it rate the
biggest scientific event in the entire
history of the world was being lassoed
by a bunch of rednecks well well come on
let's player man I got him all right
let's go go to poteau get him in here
come on hold him in there oh those what
do they think they're trying to
accomplish we got we got
damn we did it frankly city we've got
this out of an engineer we gonna be rich
men Joe rich man where are the others
what about the men that died yeah he's
right hey wait a minute wait those boys
were friends of mine too I feel real bad
about them but we all of us taking a
chance out here and us we got lucky this
green man's gonna bring us in a ton of
money Yeah right but what are you gonna
do better dead bodies oh he just can't
leave him laying out there we ain't JJ
we ain't we're gonna take this bird back
to Joe's place and lock him up good and
tight and then we'll come back and bury
those men proper okay boys will put him
in the back of Turner's truck and then
we'll take him back to chose how I'd do
it I knew it I knew it David do you know
where this jose houses sure that's Joe
Monaco the older guy his place is up by
meadow lake good we're gonna follow them
and keep an eye on this creature that
God they don't harm it
I know Joe we did our part out here
tonight you better make sure that bird
don't get loose don't worry Custer my
paw always does a good job well he
better JJ because if he don't we're
gonna hold you personally responsible
boy now look you better keep your mouth
shut about what went on out here tonight
don't be worrying about us keeping our
mouths shut you just make sure we get
our part of the cut yeah what is our cut
we risk an awful lot to catch this damn
thing hey don't worry about your cut
Thompson I'm going into town tomorrow
and I will be talking to my contact now
let's get out there and bury them dead
man I asked you where makes no
difference we got do that those guys are
dead they will feel nothin nohow after
we touched this gun out we're going to
have to check on that spaceman yeah and
make sure he's tied up good entice
JJ where you gotta figure out how these
things work well when we were fighting
the spaceman this thing seemed to power
the gun I think you're right Joe I
demand to know what's going on i'm going
to call a cop you do that and i'll put
your lights out for good I knew there
was a green man I saw in the garage
where'd it come from JJ I am sure Annie
but Paul thinks it's gonna be worth a
lot of money you're a damn right and
another thing I don't want you to say
nothing to nobody about this and that
goes for all of it john montagu I have
had it you're fooling around with
something you don't know anything about
come here I wanted to talk to you from
death illicitly I know you can come
crazy I have thinking the garage could
be worth a lot of mine John Montague I
don't know where that green man came
from but I don't think that's right that
you haven't tied up like that I'm kind
of a spaceman Custer totally do you know
what this leaves us don't want you
having anything to do with custody he's
a prominent rock no no you don't know
what you think I'm doing what I want
that sighs come on Annie
okay JJ let's figure this thing out
let's put it down here on the floor okay
careful of that switch I've got
something here for Oh does it should
fire they need hot this gun listen it
sounds like it's getting ready to fire
let's just shoot it into that stairway
JK this is a crave shoot another one for
dad but the Russians would pay a million
dollars for this
looks clear David guess now's as good a
time as any I hope nobody catches us
yeah me too
but look if someone does find us I'll
stall you get a lot of yours best you
can write and I'll get the sheriff ready
yeah
ok
open slowly
the most incredible over my life
I feel sorry for
grab that rope get a tight
okay stand up back away slowly see what
he does
Frank well nervous as a whole gonna
grill you got good news I hope sure do
Joe I just got back from town seeing my
contacts it took a lot of convincing but
they're going to come out and take a
look at the spaceman and when they do
you and me are gonna be too rich dude's
house the great Frank damn it the right
outside it's Custer and Joan on you I
don't think we have a choice David tell
her we're going to do with this door
open or make the 44 give our friend back
your imagine sure hope to hell he knows
how to run ready yeah what the hell hey
I got my gun right here
hey
soccer Tracy no right no he's just a cat
at all so he's still witness
I
hey God you scared sorry I didn't mean
to do that look I saw everything that
happened my father has that creatures
gun again is healing okay i don't know i
think it is David you've got to come
with me i'm supposed to meet Michael and
I know he can help us I don't know I
don't feel too good look I know what
you've been through and I understand how
you feel but we need help and right now
Michaels our last chance okay come on
Michael Carroll where have you been
you're really late what's David doing
Michael you've got to help us why what's
wrong is you're fun no it's not that
Custer shot dr. Tracy he's dead what
it's true Michael where's Custer now
I'll break every bone in his body Custer
is dead the alien that creature that
came here she killed Custer that space
man saved my life that's it I told you
before we should have told the sheriff
about this thing forget that Michael dr.
Tracy didn't think the only was hostile
he thinks he just wanted to get his gun
and equipment back I saw my father
taking spaceman Scott and there's no
telling what he'll do Cal we shouldn't
be fooling around with this thing
Michael we've got to get those things
back to the spaceman it'll probably
leave us alone if he gets the gun back
all right I'll help you but we better
get your mother and auntie out of the
house before I go in that's gonna be
really hard that'll be there all right
talk to him tonight and plan on sneaking
him out in the morning then we'll all
meet back here at eight o'clock okay
meanwhile try and think of some plan
some way to get that gun back from your
father I'll help out too great David we
better go just remember Michael I love
you
Oh
what the hell's wrong Wow haha what's
wrong what is it thought that space man
was in the house I damn there guy
Wow
at all
pendle hey hey hey anybody here JJ where
is everyone
Oh
I don't want to go what tired of this I
just move away Oh Danny come on no come
on you're gonna be late will you just
leave her wonder when they're gonna get
here here they are come on Annie what's
wrong with Annie she's upset about this
let's just leave her alone okay here's
the plan first thing we have to do is
get back to the house to find out where
Joe is it'll be up to you to get him
outside okay once i get him outside you
grab them I don't know I don't like this
whole thing JJ we're not trying to hurt
that we just want to get the weapon away
from him will you stop being such a wimp
you say that but Dad can really put up a
fight when he wants to don't worry JJ I
think we can handle them fuck is
everybody ready yeah right let's get
Annie and go okay
come on come with us we really really do
need your help
Joe where's Frank oh lucky come on in
this Frank Joe never showed up last
night that's not like Frank hey little
fight hey man we're gonna drink here
where is he Joe is fine Carolyn uh let's
go look Frank Frank are you in here well
let's have a drink Vicki will figure out
where Frank is I don't want a drink
where's Ethel where's this your family
Joe who knows who cares it somewhere
come on sit down hill what look drink
with me all right I'll sit down Joe I
want you to tell me where Frank is I'm
really worried about him I don't want to
drink Joe I want you to tell me where
Frank is good old Frank yeah you know we
cut that space man he got away but we
had him it's Frank trying to catch him
again he's still out in the woods yeah
right yeah right that's it he's out in
the woods oh where Joe take me to him
please I could do that would you Joe
yeah you know you're a pretty
good-looking woman fucking Joe I just
want to see Frank
any little kids first time no yo just
take me to see Frank Oh get your hands
yeah
come on baby you don't need friggin cut
me now George Frank tell you
Oh
you
man this is better with far he's passed
out cold
okay you guys stay here and whatever
happens Joe wakes up stall him keep him
here we've got to have time to find that
creature don't let him come after us you
ready yeah wait a minute Michael I'm
going with you no you're not you're
staying here there's no way you're going
we've got to get moving all right let's
go come on let's go
it should be over this way as well saw
the fireball come down firewall pull out
front over the fireball on a4a saw it
you must spin that spaceman ship over
there huh yeah what I let's go
I'll only ask this once where my
elephant to you've been out of it shut
up woman JJ look at me boy I'm asking
you where to step down from the space
line oh you gotta understand Carol
Jeanne here she took it out
wait do you hear something
sounds like somebody running no it's my
father
ah
okay hold it right there
that's it
don't nobody move now if you pump with
that gun down the ground
music
y'all back off