I was crying
hey Martha and Martha what time is it
930 Jesus why didn't you wake me cuz
it's Saturday
Harry what's a breakfast what is pancake
later i'm working oh hell little bastard
been bugging you again don't call him
master pardon me how single go down and
get the paper what you wait till after
breakfast I want to look at the ads I
don't spend another day driving around
looking at places we can't afford I can
go by myself it'd be silly to leave here
do you think the roads are cleared I'll
be all right sorry I got mad at you
Harry watch a watch a tie what's this
mmm that smells good ya ain't eat all
night careful Ani don't throw anything
away just just put them on the desk
there how are you look terrible eyes are
all red oh you take good care of your
daddy don't you baby you just remember
to eat those oh you're hungry huh hey
Paula decode hey here you go man
hi is this where build Schmidt lives yes
we're friends of his from the Army well
hey is he around bill would like to say
hello to it yeah you went to get a
newspaper he'll be back in a second why
did you come in its color yes that's hey
sorry I'm Antonio Rodriguez the blond
guy that's my clicks on sergeant
Nickerson maybe you've heard bill talk
about it he never talks today's at the
island there is wide huh hey Sarge I
introduce you this is uh I'm sorry
Martha hello why don't you come in and
sit down
No
bill won't be long mm-hmm that's a boy I
got friends visiting you yes you do
hello hello sergeant hi sunny I looks
like you struck it rich how many acres
you got 170 wow that's a lot huh well
it's Martha's father's we're just
staying here like caretakers free rent
her old man pretty well off he's a
writer maybe you've heard of him Harry
Wayne he writes muscly westerns oh yeah
I read his books I'd better read a dozen
josephson had a whole stack we hardly
ever seeing honky where he works at
night most of the time he sleeps all day
we couldn't afford this place on what I
make
are you in I thought he'd leave that
what no what kind of job you got oh it's
in our plant near here that makes
helicopters yeah I know I know that's
funny and then the same choppers we used
in Vietnam and I swore I'd never go near
the army again have anything to do with
it but that's where the work was so
that's what I'm doing what's his name
how are your cute little baby
tired we've been driving all night oh
you want to bed No
I tell you if I could just lay down it's
so cool there for a while I'll get you a
blanket Hey ok found a dozen I didn't
know anybody had so much space sure uh
I'll go with you
oh whoa hi Camille now is that your
place too yeah Wow terrific it's her old
man is that a lake out there hun upon
huh wow you're lost dog is that well
that's the neighbors
fighting who's a good quarter Rico
this one's too heavy to be a fighter
he's a lover shut up bye everybody
wouldn't have a dog at this fight but he
won't bother come go home who the hell
is that with him just different from the
Army there's another one up here ah you
can walk on it besides you the foot
stick I thought you drain the water and
put her covering them in the winter no
no you leave the water in this one then
in the spring it has to be drained
painted filled up again sounds like a
lot of work yeah there's a company does
it all everything taken care of huh yeah
goodbye we can visit you last summer we
could have all SAT around here
sunbathing we're busy you know
they threw the confessions out just like
you read about in the papers failed to
inform the career defendants of his
rights I got done that two years ago
what about Riley he's still it didn't
confess see boys he's pissed off yeah
I'm glad to see you but I want what I
don't think you're so damn glad to see
you what did you come here for I don't
know I'm not even sure whose idea it was
the Sarge and I were both 11 work they
gave us all our back Peyton you believe
that for two whole years we decided what
the hell why wait for transportation we
both want to come back east so we got
the car Jesus water bump we broke down
in some dump outside Philadelphia last
night and we had a weight while a guy in
an all-night garage put a new head
gasket in and I don't know we started
drinking and talking about you how did
you know where I lived Sarge hide your
address I'm his lawyer in case you had
to testify in the appeal I told it all
the first time yeah I know anyway here
we are why
I just wanted to tell you what did I
forgive you anyway no hard feelings no
talking about it last night we figured
you must be worried thinking about what
we might do right right so I wanted you
to know that as far as I'm concerned
bygones are bygones as far as your
consent yeah
he gets a little fussy sometimes all
right I can't sleep any nevermind awful
dad what nothin
do you want a newspaper to me no se yeah
you got coke sure
we're the guys I think you're still
walking around thank you do you think do
you think I could I use your oh yeah
sure it's it's upstairs turn to your
left you'll see it thank you
you
go
and you scared me you in Vietnam with
Bill yes ma'am what did like you who
watch television sometimes well let's
just like it is on television did you
like it I get nobody likes it I meant
the countryside of his annoys a dream I
don't know I guess it yes after why you
just don't notice didn't feel ever tell
you about it never talks to me about
Vietnam he is involved in some kind of
trial their court-martial yeah you and
your friend won't stay for dinner this
is really too big for us i'll just put
in more potatoes maybe we can there they
don't know my father's with him once you
go down to meet him he'll like you he
was a sergeant to in the Second World
War we never took any prisoners on
Guadalcanal Ellen wasn't time we're
outnumbered four months that's something
you guys don't know about and even dare
go into the bushes to take a leak one of
them to be waiting for you and we didn't
have the weapons you guys got hands
rifle bayonet anyway you got one was
alright how's your beer holding up there
bill fine baby we need a little more
wood huh even later when we had ice
cream in movies they used to come and
sit in the back and watch the bastards
and admire oh no I don't think these
Kong North Vietnamese whatever the hell
they are have the guts the Japs did
whatever the hell they are they keep on
fighting over there you don't know what
your friend is and who isn't that there
are no sighs book your own so in the end
it's easier to shoot everybody bill
doesn't believe in fighting kid you
should have gotten yourself a job in the
hospital patching up guys who had the
guts to get themselves shot at I got
shot at by an old man civilian he was
scared to death you shoot back sure over
his head what I heard him that's it god
damnit look at him
damn look at that poor son of a bitch
spread some newspapers by the fire huh
damn it's a mountain top there he is I
told that son of a bitch to keep his dog
off my property it's all tied up all the
time I couldn't find any alcohol use
whiskey for Christ's sake June almost
all the way through any legged dog what
the hell am I gonna do with a
three-legged dog I told him next time
this dog came on my place I'd kill a son
of a bitch to the doggies oh shut up you
can't hit him with a pistol and damn
well try need a rifle yeah i know i got
a shotgun but at this range it was just
tickling we got a rifle in the car
six point five millimeter yeah I'd
Swedish it's not pretty but it'll do the
job great Daniken yes they're gonna do
your father alright gotta stay I could
take anybody out on a terrible can't you
shoot the man's dog well I can't look
max the one who picks the fights yeah
he's tough let's go
you need something to rest it on not in
this range I don't even really need the
scope can't you stop them legally he's
within his rights and that's what came
after you once remember what the hell
didn't you shoot it then perfect Tony
don't miss
nice-looking dog you want to bury him
very heavy shit the dumping right at
that son of a bitch's front door and let
him do something about it
those the men aren't they what men we
have to tell me that we're just supposed
to look for supplies well by the third
day we hadn't found anything and
Nickerson was beginning to get edgy so
we get to this village was Mart friendly
on the map but Nickerson decided to get
everybody out and search the huts four
arms so we lined them up while he and
Tony look the place over they thought we
were gonna shoot them all and I think
Nickerson almost did he was so angry
about not finding anything well in the
last Hut girl was hiding Nickerson
pretended he thought she was a VC and he
told one of the old men in the village
that we were gonna take her along as a
hostage what'd she look like she was
young 15 or 16 pretty I guess that's why
she was hiding us that's what her mother
said at the court-martial
a couple of miles at the road nificent
took her into the tall grass someone she
made this look
after a while it was like yeah it was
like mac down there it was just just
whining and then Riley went next and
josephson and Tony and then never
waiting for me to do it well I couldn't
move I mean it didn't take any thought
any bravery I I just couldn't walk
Nicholson he looked at me for a long
time you know the way he does he just
looks that hit her rifle in his hands
then handed the rifle to josephson he
jerked his thumb towards the grass and
and you turned them in when we got back
to camp
no it's too late I I should have stopped
them what's the point of punishing the
master wizard criminals have to be
punished the Vietcong do exactly the
same thing everybody does every day
everywhere everywhere why blame these
guys they were my friends they will my
buddies
let's go home boys
found all three four Higgins hell would
they come here for well it wasn't just
cuz they loved the scenery Tony said he
wanted to tell me that he didn't what he
said he want to tell me there were no
hard feelings in his side shit no
Harry's raid i was working i knew they
were Jerry's in there I take a grenade
at pull the pin go up along with it boom
come on in call the police well what
would I say that I'm afraid of these
guys aren't you maybe yeah yes yes you
know something I am I've thought about
it every day since it happened but I
can't do it to them again did they don't
even know why they came here you know
that that's what Tony said they're like
stray dog don't call the police yeah but
when I bus in the morning our meetings
of pigs isn't boy when you need on this
police car
yes way to football games on heroin how
much done your sliced not I don't give a
sh sure that's fine hey mr. Wain I'm in
the other one is the way it's done
that's a boy
hey kid got simple enough yeah but no
was on yeah yeah yeah come on cough hey
the fields in good shape there seems to
be only one soft spot near the 50-yard
line thanks kid move it now yeah old
Comstock just in time it's a good high
end over end a beautiful food to go
hello bitty he's at the 50 don't let him
sing off of pete's sake
why don't you erase the myosin glasses
in here so we don't have to keep running
back and forth come on give this my head
back go go go 25 yards now let's go
there you go it's gonna be the right let
me inaudible in there often enough the
other team is gonna come down with it
for now let's go have another food last
week
history doesn't throw the ball away
again in this situation he goes to
raider football is a great game without
her elemental cause it's a conflict
that's what life is about please you're
happy if you make it no its life against
death I can Vietnam will see just one
corner of it above the surface within
your metaphors loot a football field one
teams got one color jersey and other
teams got another color that's really
soon but the world is set up the same
way communist on one side that's on the
other you'd face that look at Vietnam
and that context should understand it
but we'd like right now Europe is
stabilized even more power is shifting
in Asia what num is the fall courier
that's what they tell us
and you'd better believe it soldier
Danny had a job with his coach during
the timeout so we'll see what he comes
up with now
the ball is spotted on the tuna
how's your uh Roger beer holding out
there uh I'll never get like sex very
much ginger get that kid what the hell
am I gonna do with that three-legged kid
dude come on referee is out of bounds I
she was out of bounds I let's see the
playback hey ton i watch football I
notice one thing what's that then how
many Puerto Rican guys plan did you
notice that yeah why is that oh well
there are plenty of Puerto Rican
baseball player I don't know yeah it
stars but not footboard Rodriguez are
too small afraid he'll need to write
these 18 Chili Peppers your racial
difference he cuts back in
racial difference isn't that illegal oh
I can't play because they're too small
not because of Puerto Ricans some people
are just naturally it's smaller than
others like oriental ain't no goddamn
slow petting cuda Tony just an example
Christ's sake
I was in college that's what it was all
about football everybody wanted to play
football even the guys you never saw the
guys have spent most of their time in
the library secretly they wanted to play
football you know why football players
got more pussy not that anyone got a
hell of a lot but the football players
got more those days guys your science
could play college football if he was
tough
15 Wow big Pete Smith me was just giving
away to each other didn't even have to
ask work nicely there's no challenge to
know when am I always gonna play
football asselin while his friends once
if they wanted to watch the game that
looked at his impose some fat-free where
the hell's bill lap stairs Jackson's put
down hard at 36 I think Danny under
through that when a little bit let us
give second interception of the day the
fourth turnover I soon they act already
do get away later nobody cares anymore
she's much looking girl Martha that made
no getting this stupid solid bits
laughs they was nice smiles all the time
yeah broke his arm
nice all right look I was hanging yea
baby's all right I always one of the
grandson I don't even know what this kid
is see my grandson is that but I should
say to people
and
Colin games to Murphy the freshman
you can't watch it Peter seems ready to
try for the extra point to make it 28 yo
it's a lot old bill his hair is getting
a little gray you remember how he'd look
when he first got over there like a
little kid
oh god damn very reason cuz I gotta get
to the city Jerry tongue yeah where are
you gonna go I gotta go see if I'm
getting a job our son d let's go give
you a job on Sunday there's a guy I can
talk to well they fit on being a given
Giada waterville like it yeah I wish you
guys had stick around a couple of days
speaking purely selfish you understand
it's great to have somebody to talk I
bet you'd like to use that rifle again
there's some there's a moon tonight and
there's a thigh no in town a cop Fred
Holly he's gonna be cooling back in my
woods yeah I told him I might be out
later we could all go how are they got
two bedrooms upstairs they're not using
right bill yeah they're empty
Bryce what a weirdo you see that I shot
that bear and now look at it
Martha what time is dinner as soon as we
get the table set what's the matter
nothing golly harry wants them to stay a
couple of days Oh Harry of God don't
have a girl stay anyways it's Harry's
look it's as much mine as this Harry
because it's mine it's yours and if you
don't want them to student you just tell
them to go yeah some kind of trouble
Vietnam you know about we were here
what happened I was leaving him patrol
with an a woman of Vietcong had to shoot
it can take on patrol with her something
time to see huh he turned you in for
that well we had a little fun with her
first cuz that's what made him an didn't
touch her no I thought it was a half
clear
there's salad at the icebox I know I'm
surprised you didn't slit his throat I
thought about it thought about her love
wasn't stalking thing was he gonna get
me
dinner's on the table
do you want a car very sure okay Mike
I alike Mike career still moving you got
it Tony how about you little rat he
likes it burned we forgot the 10 pitch
like it isn't anything I hardly felt it
come on let me wash it no hold still you
can need some stitches like myself
Harry please don't read anymore I think
you've had enough that thanks quite a
guy isn't he did did he tell you what
build it what Phil did to them yo Harry
just scratch well I remember one time is
Phil peanut captain trying to make one
of them talk took him out and bolt he
cut off his his hands one by one and
dropped from the little wire Harry be
quiet mm-hmm many's arm what it'll Watsa
the sharks eat them
Harry I Ashley's boys time stay a couple
days thanks mr. Wayne but I really gotta
get back I think my being booked him
yeah he did well or talk more about
tomorrow afternoon I I have work to do
in the morning huh my cap
I think so
thank you very much
Harry you forgot your glasses think I
make it you're sure my fleet to death
I'll check on him later
he's a very interesting guy you think so
yeah he's been through it I'm really
couldn't stand him neither could either
his other to us well yeah I would want
to be buried
Deverell about it good baby toys now let
me make you some coffee before you know
y'all have coffee we're gonna drive you
just take a few minutes please sit down
that is nice around here this summer
yeah
great ciao mas is a great cook dama hell
you know you like creamed corn
come on oh yes it took her a woman to
get angry I want you wait till he's
hungry how'd you know I don't you got
his vegetables
yeah I can roll Bigfoot
good for you how's the said he wants to
go to bed so goodnight everybody how am
i huh
the 90 needle
let us say good night to hell
kind of job you look the hell you used
to interesting cars yeah yeah I think
I'll get myself a job in a garage just
to get experience
the most important tool in any garages
the steam cleaner now I know this guy
named Fellman he has a place in garage
near the river Geico
a guy comes in there with a knock in his
car now he doesn't know a thing about
cars filming who comes over and starts
shaking his head transmissions about
ready to fall out he says bill I mean
it's a good thing you decided to bring
it in now you see the transmission
something that everybody knows about you
know I mean I mean you tell the guy his
vile if this is shot well he gets
worried he's not even sure his car's got
valveless to split the transmission you
gotta have that right anyway the guy
comes back the next day Feldman shows
him a shiny clean transmission only
self-defense it's the same man the only
difference this is a filming worth it
all with the steam cleaner you are me
Nessus okay now rebuilt transmission
right underneath it all maybe can't
stand I Lisa what's the matter with all
that back pay maybe filming we let me
find his place
hell I don't even know this garage is
too
Tony does all the driving you fly one
mind if I have little Willy you think he
drank the whole thing himself when he
wakes up really famous writer here is a
lot of books and other people buying
them it's like a compulsion with him
when he gets going sometimes he stays up
the whole night riding pretty good books
long time ago they used to be first two
or three wrote really good serious books
now he's full of anger and self-disgust
and books are empty the good stories
full of dramatic events and flashy
characters easy to read enjoy reading
them myself but they're meaningless
I liked what he said about there being a
book and Tony and me
he'll tell me what you did
is it true sure whatever you say
mother what meet you everybody was doing
what pickled me I pick on that girl baby
she young bill says she wasn't how the
hell could I tell she was hiding from us
see the proof she had a damn good reason
to hide it's a lot of crap what do you
think of me a conduct a uniform
different nobody else over there Justin
your husband cost me too damn good
here's the fair he did Buster God we
hanging on he's not your husband is he
hey what kind of regimen is that anyway
huh you pitch morality my living with
phil has nothing to do with morale
you're in morality yours I see you can
just leave it I can't judge you you make
all the rules you see what's right
what's wrong what someone else is
immoral that's the only standard you can
have you how about your father huh you
don't get that Terry see some guts out
to see the woods Italy's problem I'm
sorry he's upset but it's an emotional
problem and it's a lot different from
seeking some with a bandit bayonet is
that what Bill told you sorry did the
shooter we couldn't take any prisoners
patrol that was orders Final Solution
video nothing can justify what you have
to justify otário das white become here
stead in stockade and we were heroes to
the boiler out there 10 bill he got
shipped out a combat area pretty fast
didn't he he wouldn't there would have
been any case why you get shot going
either way have you boarded a fraud look
you got a few things in woods you get
locked up for peacetime what you think I
am some kind of hoodlum this does an
honor student in high score on how does
a damn good soldier that's more he was
glad
well you got it safe here you don't know
what you've been there do you been shot
at
what would you do live I can take it
till you gone to a village head handing
out candy bars to the kids and then you
seen your best buddies legs blown off my
mind because the pp you gave the candy
bars to forgot to tell your Charlie was
in town
that happened
it happened you're rich now I haven't
been there I can't imagine it I can't
wait to get that first thing you notice
sweet city people way to walk around
spending do you have any point the whole
city's gonna stay warfare just like over
that really warp a cocktail at the
Avalon hey
never much one of those piece brains
curious I why
I don't know look like somebody I'm
washing up peace parade interior design
I used to wonder over there
what kind of people want to those things
I always thought their long-haired freak
swing was like Indians
bill asked me to marry him once before
the baby was born he was he's gonna do
me a big favor
you ryona Karachi
dance
you
my uncle's got a restaurant that other
tomorrow night 130 a street I can work
that for a while something
responsibility I've been wanting to
invest what's that 200 good at the other
time
hey Sarge let's get the hell out of you
this one out
you
oh that's nothing I said that's enough
you better go now the day you said you
really want to go
when you
sure
with the matter with you
I
oh shoot him
you
you'll be okay
lady you are nuts you think you can
change the rules in the middle
well
you
you will