how the hell are you doing okay sorry
girl i'm just trying to coordinate
trouble I'm not gonna hurt you just
relax just like mom what do you think
all right just want to show you come to
the lesson
inhale it my kids out of here after the
old man comes up with the ransom not
before them sajan have to worry about it
big daddy's going to be having to pick
up a girl in a few hours I mean I'm
gonna have company she's one of your
kind he'll you mean my pad oh don't get
upset I didn't hear anything by I mean
she's black she's the wife of an African
president helm but damn what'd she use
well that doesn't matter we're gonna be
here for a few days so I'm get a little
friend damn hands up for me you sorry
bitch I'll see you later
[Music]
good morning sweetheart any calls yes
then by the name of David McLeod called
you said it was coming over to see you
this morning David cloud I wanted that
same cloud
yeah good he says he's an old friend of
yours that must be him I wonder if he
still with the CIA the CIA yeah when I
first started out in Harlem as a
detective Davis CIA men helped me out of
a couple of really rough spots I wonder
if any of those rough spots had anything
to do with girls so I wonder where you
get such a dirty mind having committed
some zeros
uh yeah mr. Freeman
ok
hello listen I'm wondering about the
check his cassette haha
yes not healthy yes you may I'm David
McLeod is they are content oh yes he's
expecting me you can go right in thank
you thank for looking here hey the guy
from Harlem just like those hands tato
fine you never when we split football
together it's my remember how
quarterback he caught the winning
touchdown pass each score Oscar please
sure does that became you talking about
that's the one but that's not quite
story that's good tell me what can I do
for you personally introduce my father
here Paul Benson Paul hey you're my
partner speaks pretty highly of it
doesn't yeah well you know he'll you
wanted a great stuff I think you're
hella guy but no bullshit Jim that's
quite all right what you guys have seen
so what line of business brings you to
Miami
Oh still with the CIA a person from an
African nation will be meeting secretly
the Secretary of State they arrived
today but he apply on tomorrow from
Washington DC how come the meeting will
be held in Miami instead of Washington
our clients life is in danger and we
assure that fallen Powell's will be
trying to prevent this meeting what I
can't understand Dave is why the CIA
doesn't supply the security why do they
want me something just doesn't seem to
fit paid it's simple it's very possible
that there could be a leak in the CIA
someplace somewhere but we're not taking
any chances this person from my African
nation she's the wife of the chief of
state and we're thinking that you will
check in old as man and wife
hands off she's the wife of a chief of
state hey now that would take everybody
off guard let me ask you a silly
question don't say it we don't need an
international crisis you want to know if
she's cute yes but remember
international repercussions yes she's
cute hey now how do you get there I'll
remember the good old days Hong Kong
Bangkok dirty old man yeah but getting
back to business just how much do i get
for this little number there's two
thousand dollars in it for you hey
that's great for 24 hours service that's
not the head in fact for that kind of
dough i don't care if the lady diplomat
is 80 years old we have two agents
airport now picking up mr. Shanti we
have precisely 30 minutes to get to the
hotel lobby where she'll be wait a
minute if I'm taking this case I have to
pick the hotel have your agents draw her
through the towers the desk clerk will
tell her where my room is I'll be
waiting there will be registered as a
mr. and mrs. Connors that's a little
irregular but I guess we have to do it
as you say look I'm going to worry about
the security of mrs. Shanti let me do it
my way the desk clerk of the towers is a
personal friend of mine and he'll handle
the situation for me gentlemen I think
I'd better get to the hotel and make the
necessary arrangements and I suggest you
get in touch with your agents and tell
them what the change of plans good luck
out don't worry it's gonna be an easy
case I hope so well you're ready for
problems you can reach me at this number
cancel my buttons for the rest of the
day ok
prices went up
it's been so long you can need this back
then I'll take care to know thanks
thanks a lot I'm sorry about that little
number this isn't sean day but it was
necessary for security purposes you're
supposed to be my wife for 24 hours my
name is al and we're registered as mr.
Ellis's al Connors hey wait a minute you
don't mean of course not it's just for
security purposes in fact the suite has
two bedrooms I'll be staying over here
you can take that one I'm just your
personal bodyguard now hey you know I
really feel miserable today I'm in pain
all over you show me to my face off with
pleasure man
did you say we're not feeling well yes
i'm in pain all over I understand that
plane for so long you know I really can
use a good massage okay I'm called from
Zeus good can I change into something
more Connor
hello yes I would appreciate it if you
would send him to suits to suite 304 for
my wife for about five minutes that's
fine thank
[Music]
ah
Oh
huh
Oh just melt on the zoo she's here ready
you
what are you doing at the window oh I
was just admiring the scenery it is
beautiful listening yes I guess it is
she's ready I'm going okay
hi how are you I'm terrible bad back huh
terrible you know I really need my back
is killing
oh this really feels good I feel much
better already
ah
[Music]
how do you feel much better you do good
work now what are you doing in here just
admiring you um I really don't feel
comfortable about men being in the area
while I'm doing this if you don't mind
how would you leave around please sorry
things but I enjoy watching it's been a
long time you know all right you peeping
tom you may remain
so do you feel much better now yes much
better good
ok I had a good evening I
you tried you go to my room right yes
the bill will be charged Sheeran thank
you bye-bye
some parties around here I had to do it
for security purposes I didn't know that
you had such a beautiful line that's
right I can't believe they're paying me
for this
princess you could never guess how happy
I am to be here yeah that's your it's a
good thing you don't bring your own
ma'am along on trips like this hey wait
a minute that's just leave my husband
out of it I'm starved how about you have
us some food does it matter of fact I
was just getting ready to ask you the
same thing why don't we go get a bite to
know the security purposes we have to
eat here oh I've had it up to here what
security it's not that bad I'll call
room service and get something
oh yeah this is suite 304 we'd like to
have to New York strip steaks glow them
yeah we'll have bring a bottle of scotch
Jamie
the President must be a previous
interesting position yeah interesting
for him but boring for me boring yes
he's always gone out of town someplace
and there's nothing for me to do round
health a lady as lovely as you always
has something to do yeah like watching
television all the time oh come on
should we get a little bit paper about
him you mean say you don't have anything
on the side no extra curriculum step I
have to return to my country hand back
to my husband and we don't have very
much time doing
this hey wait a minute just because i'm
bored doesn't mean that i'm hot to trot
now where does a burner pick an accent
like that well when I was very young in
the red how'd you become the wife of the
president oh that surprised me but he's
fantastic but a little boy yes so many
worrying fun Oh Harlem oh wow oh I spent
six month and how did you like it oh yes
fantastic I had the most voice but
there's too many detective said khloe's
dear well I didn't know this you weren't
looking but i'll let experience in
Harlem I should be very lucky to have
you for my bodyguard baby you don't know
how lucky you are column is the
experience playground for all people
interested in becoming protectors oh
yeah that must be room service I need
the door oh I hope so I'm starving so on
Oh
oops
you can put the tray over there gee I'm
glad the food is here
yeah how did you know it was a man
nobody I'll be eatin SS Chris tree I can
smell the New York strip steak a block
away but the worst is yet to come sure
he's got somebody's getting there fast
and get on some clothes
Oh
[Music]
who the hell is panda to do this
now that was a blank that time the next
one it's gonna go right through your
throat I can't subpoena you to do it I
can't tell you kill me if they find out
okay you got three seconds if you don't
tell me I'm gonna kill you right now all
right all right all right all right I
work for Victor you tell big death then
nobody who's with a guy from Bob you did
oh my god what happened where do we go
now don't worry about I'm thinking we
could say fuck this game I'll call his
office no I haven't heard from a mr
McLeod well if Al's checked out the
hotel I'm sure he had good reason to
well listen if you're leaving your
number I'll have him call you when I
hear from
how's that 685 4932 ok don't worry I'm
sure he's all right I'm sure
everything's fine ok ok I haven't called
ha
I thought you had forgotten me oh you
know I never forget you baby who is she
I'm sorry let me introduce you to them
this is Ashanti princess this is Joanne
how do you do ok Elvis de story will
explain everything princess please
excuse the squirrel on the joint college
today
okay buster you better explanation look
detective sometimes get weird
assignments keep talking I'm listening
I'm this lady's body guy I don't have
safe place to take people trying to kill
her
I can take it to my place or another
hotel would be too risky I think your
place to stay place to be ok alright
you've convinced me you can stay here
but how long are you going to hide the
scroll in my place just for tonight
okay if you really dig me just trust me
okay I'll be ready in five minutes
what have you spent the night hotel
prices
I'm
you
famous no everything's been taken care
of well he was a pleasure to meet you
princess but I gotta warn you about this
playboy detective I didn't know I had
such a reputation thanks for the warning
hmm well by now
are you comfortable feel free to make
yourself at home here thank you very
nice place
did you want something to drink yeah
I'll have a great idea blackman Ephixa
beautiful show me one boss the bar is
quite over there
i'm going to give David McLeod call
they he asked me look we ran into a
slight problem at the hotel and I had to
split for safer place yeah everything's
cool everything's all right they yeah
yeah she's here with me the meetings at
ten o'clock tomorrow morning you want me
to drop her off you're gonna pick her up
how about about nine thirty nine o'clock
that's cool is the penthouse apartments
screen 1500 feel right don't worry
everything's cool man i'll see you
tomorrow morning okay right right right
okay fine do you need any help no just
fine you're right with you I gotta make
another call sure
Pal Connors office whats new puss again
hell I was worried about you your friend
MacLeod called yeah everything's under
control you can go home now yes I'll be
in tomorrow as usual okay so goodnight
now and remember don't do anything I
wouldn't do sure boss that leaves me a
lot of leeway oh I almost forgot you had
another call a guy I'm working for the
CIA he wanted your address did you give
it to him yes boss did I do the wrong
thing now that's right you did the right
thing it'll work out okay boss but
please be careful okay ahhhh
what
that's just what the doctor ordered if
you're meeting with Secretary of State's
at ten o'clock tomorrow morning they'll
be picking you up around nine you should
be a pretty safe answer but I feel
starving think I understand Oh doing it
sorry
how did you buy
you still having those aches and pains
in the body
my body still aches all over
you know I used to be able to once
myself come no seriously turn around you
guys do for you
out of this bill that feels good
I have flush it do you oh
bunny got for those bad guys so strong
you know there's a slight problem that i
forgot to mention to you this apartment
only has one bedroom ah beautiful but I
haven't finished talking yet oh I got it
you sleep on the floor and I'll take the
way come on you gotta be joking that's
not fair okay I was just joking work
then let's not waste any time
you know character Sam thank you so much
and begin filling bellboy
well quite an experience yourself my
sister
listen why don't you get out
why so fast
are you some slow change
wow what a change
you are
Allison's classes
[Music]
oh good morning Casanova you look tired
I had quite a night believe me I don't
think I'm taking any more babysitting
jobs oh so you're large enough turns out
to be babysitting totally owns got my
damn head blown off it's a matter of
fact babysitting can be a lot rougher
than you think baby yeah what's up for
today yeah nothing I'm free I think
about 15 minutes i'm splitting for the
rest of the day the rest of the day well
it's only about ten o'clock what's going
on thank you give me about 15 minutes
you find it yeah
good morning good looking yeah can I
help you I don't know I think you can I
came here to see how in Congress can I
have your name in the nature of your
business sweetie I got an answer for
both of those questions you got two
questions I got one answer there are
your damn business sir you don't have to
use that kind of language in just a
minute I'll see if he/she
well I think that goof off dead yours is
about to be ruined the hell are you
talking about there are three dudes out
there that are demanding to see you they
wouldn't tell me who they are or what
they want hey Dad you think that
difference is fake it he better see a
lobster's guys from Big Daddy's game you
want me to tell them you're not in so
I'm ready for those bums anytime they
want to see me big daddy wants to get me
the game can be played two ways have us
do 10 min as a matter of fact I better
take me to safety having connect
who your boss
you gentlemen can go me thanks good luck
it thanks babe
you wait here
while you wait take care anything that
needs taken care random
I better see
hello ma'am man they called me and you
promised aid of me I'm Harry the ball
just well I'm al Connors it's my
pleasure to meet you I had a lot of good
news about you this is my son Larry then
what can I do feed each other but first
stops boss just put the gun away we
gonna make a deal we're not here to
waste you man
I see thank you
I can't even see the daily office them
but two reasons two very important
reason to me and my happiness one it's
kind of personal but but I gave you
reason why I cave is because because I
know what you can do you say that
happened between for being a Saturday
night L did you know about that that's
supposed to be top secret top secret and
my business on him the street in this
jungle he's supposed to know everything
that happened twenty four hours a day as
a matter fact I've here's something you
should know big daddy gay them hoodlums
and my boys have been fighting for a
long long time over favor property that
brings in millions of dollars each and
everything that sounds like a problem
between the two of you not mine just
suppose just suppose I got you involved
with the problem and offered you some
serious but not only in the type of
money you make sit behind that death I
need some serious money sorry gentlemen
you've come to the wrong place I don't
deal with hoodlums let's go dad will
need little Joker why I found muscles
for myself down sister did you say
sister that's right out I don't like to
get sentimental Albert's he is talked
about his sister was my daughter they're
right my daughter Wanda Big Daddy's
kidnapped what is the case of kidnap and
that's another matter I'd be interested
in taking the case but there's one thing
if you don't level with me
you're gonna pull me off the case that's
an automatic thing you do and understand
it okay okay why are you doing when you
get off the night baby can I have the
same come out well you and I going down
here to the disco tonight you know how
work we gon dance get together two
beautiful people why do you see one
beautiful
hey you know life is beauty still with
you and I together everything people you
see well coming from
can I guess all right that's right
anyway how there's the man man to man if
you take this case Bailey I'll pay you
anything you name or nothin you got it
okay so fill me in on the petitions I'm
not going to just fill you in with words
man I'm going to prove to you what I'm
talking about lady good stuff on you got
five hundred thousand dollars worth of
stuff right there and you got a quarter
million dollars in cash right there now
that's not good at you and I don't know
what street you live on baby I suppose
you want me to make the delivery and
pick your daughter up right it all has
to be done how this afternoon it's got
to be done this happen you exchange and
the cop has to take place at the same
time since we don't make the trade I
don't know exactly out but here's what I
do know you got to go to the bodybuilder
spots on 106 and third street and you
mean a guy better about the name of Jim
I know the place but what I can't
understand is why you want me to do the
job why don't somebody in my
organization do the job do you realize
the helmet we're talking about life and
death everybody's too upset I thought
man he is talking about my daughter I'm
gonna need a picture of it I wouldn't
want to pick up the room I guess you're
right about that is the pizza pie little
wonder you found out that she's right
beautiful
yeah because she is incidentally this
little job is gonna cost you 25 big ones
you didn't say anything not usually his
five g's for starter it's all there you
don't have to count so if you were that
what do I take her wonder I don't tell
you that I've got the money the coke and
picture of your daughter there's one
more thing I need what is that out
that's all the information you can give
me on this big daddy felon who is it
when you say who is he you talking about
what he looks like and way hangs out
nobody knows now that's one thing we
can't tell you much fun her did you
people ever see Big Daddy the only thing
I can tell you he's about six feet two
inches tall has long curly hair and man
you took my son muscles he got some
muscle on him and he always wears fans
and runs muscle that's the only thing we
can tell you if I think that nobody ever
sees him that's true in fact he has a
reputation of never pulling any of his
own stunts he always said his cheap
bombs dirty looks like I'm going to have
to pay this big daddy fellow no visit I
think I've been just started what I love
that that's music at night by the way
how I get in touch with you how do you
get in touch with us don't you worry
about that you get in touch with you
see ya all right
positive well I'll just hoping that all
right my man all right here to get out
of here good looking you can it's a kill
business heretics give you wait a minute
wait a minute that's money honey wait
just a minute you give this to him so he
can family what haha what we're looking
for my name bro
it's not a little fox something wrong
don't you think hey shut up bitch what's
your problem how have any problems I
think you won't have a problem hey eat
shit shit is what it was he had yours
here you think what stay on your heel I
like just what I see but I don't like
that Oh glad you like it hey black
beautiful that looks like pubic hair
that's okay too trash you should you eat
your damn self will you just cool it are
you cookie the light what's your problem
i have a problem it's your hand off of
me look bitch look you better listen
better keep your damn mouth shut
something's gonna happen to you might
not like it Oh
oh you're a nice squeeze me handle damn
it's almost one o'clock and went away
the hell gym is i don't know i love you
hear the treatments hopeful quiets I'm
breaking my store yeah he's right
nothing is that is high for me hey calm
down hey I got to bother you anymore
just cool let's talk about this look
I'll make you a deal you give me a
little action i'll let you go how's that
sound hey Chucky no day although I know
you're not gonna let me go I know what's
going on yeah that damn big daddy would
do me and if I did let you go
canal I'm looking for jail Jim you're
finding my up in the sauna just cut up
the stairs there and take a right
I
put it away
taking a dog
understand your gym that's me who you
want my name is out I think we can do
he'll kill what nigga certain chick I'm
looking for I've been told you happy
when you talking about their little
black bitch one that's the one there's
the money in the merchandise but I can
get the money and the merchandise I just
have to know where to deliver it well
there's a midwife about a mile south 141
/ children road movie did the four
o'clock i won't bring the money and be
there on time oh wow just remember goal
you see the girl to me in the pit hood
are you know anything copy that make
sure to catch it
and everything going on just this plan
[Music]
that cat bathroom
check out me
well let's get this over with
hey grab this sure hey that wasn't too
cool I was cool to hang god I think I'm
gonna blow you away I'd like your phone
away never get blown way before that
hurt I didn't think that was too cold
what are you laughing about you heard
that's why you need to reverse the neck
Oh
[Music]
oh shit I didn't want to anyhow i'll hit
you didn't he damn chill try to you now
just playing with a bit okay hey just
wanted to see if you were a little
scared that's all no I'm not scared of
you right now what are you shaking for
huh you make a difference you know I
better check those ropes see you in doc
please maybe we can go nowhere
[Music]
I ropes tight enough now that bros not
to baylor i have been any of that dark
leave a long time yeah I wonder if
Michael is take turns at least you
interested
[Music]
everything all right no thought required
four o'clock forgot to take the kid to a
mailbox about two miles down the road
it's only you know 130 we got plenty
time all right it was Matt he's inside
with broad alone I told you to keep your
hands off that shit hey what can I say
man she looked horny get out of here
come on get hotter here all right I'm
going home damn I'm tired of being
around you're chilling nothing I'm gonna
take a walk no problem just don't go
through the fog we got working it sure o
Canada
whatever happens
I say
Oh
yeah I hear what time is it now
that's been taking the whole full-time
much receive you punch
whoosh it is huh
six clearview
you
all the right there
so make more
just raise your hand slowly
oh it's you again yeah me again
[Music]
what the hell am I getting out of here
well if you can hold onto for fly have
you gone they don't have a fuck hot pan
yet he'll am I going to get out of here
you just be cool come for a clock can be
long gone just play a card room telling
for carp fish yeah yeah well uh someone
go check on a few things don't do
anything stupid fear smart nigga oh no
take them down are you crazy hey lady
stupid
okay make a mistake now I'm telling you
hello honda
you are one art
you look like you know not of shit I had
to go through to get see pick one I was
protecting her astra the hell you were
hey I'm trying to make a big mistake now
I came here I'm protecting her schreiber
hey ask him an Oscar hey come on now
that we can partner for supper we do
clapping o'clock is it easy put the gun
please please go away I want you to take
a message the big day sure sure anything
hey tell him he's next yeah
that's getting all aliens
[Music]
did you kill him I don't know
ooh you are I want to thank you for
saving my life don't worry about just my
job get it I guess oh I want the hot to
go home man I think that's why I'm in
this mess now I don't want to go home
all right come on
[Music]
you
I'll don't say a word I know detectives
sometimes get weird assignments huh you
just give me five minutes and I'll be
ready wait a minute let me introduce you
to him oh who cares hey yo late yes
she's just okay should be Irish sorry to
a hotel no it's much safer much sit on
glass
[Music]
what I can't understand is how your
father got into drugs if he was doing so
well in gambling as you said well I'm a
foster to the drug business he knows yet
gavilan it only made his money out of
the woods bono had this water p
I
well how long do you want me out this
time mr. private eye it's just for
tonight incidentally have an illegal
package yeah forget up at some other
time oh I couldn't care less pick it up
when I want a baby wait wait Oh get
yourself a hotel room the next time
there won't be any always made good bye
nice knowing you whoever you are go get
mad
[Music]
vas harm you gonna try he didn't get too
far
pretty tense which relax makes upcoming
say sháá might be well this see
clothes in the closet look to him they
did something to fit you sure she
wouldn't get mad she might bitch about
by the way why don't you give your
father brother ring we take a shower I
know you're okay because I'm sure they
worry about it I don't want to talk to
them now give me the number
[Music]
37 30 Petrie sure you safe now
yeah let me speak with mr. Herriot of
all tell me it's al Connors
[Music]
Harry yes me she's fine yeah but I can't
bring it to you right now no no
nothing's wrong she's fine but I just
can't bring it to you right now she
doesn't want to see you
look Harry it's a long story all right I
tell you once just be in my office
tomorrow morning at ten she'll be there
I'll have it it right ok ok Harry just
be cool okay see you mama right
ah
well
so I never look like that man you not
enjoyed some thinking I can understand
why your father got into the drug scene
he was doing so well in gambling as you
say well really he was forced into the
drug scene so he made you want to beat
well he got to be a biggest dude in town
you're right too many people OD on the
hard stuff I promised my father that the
first dealing he had with drugs that I
would leave home and do you know that
two weeks ago he bought in a big
shipment and that's what I decided to
split naturally I'm assuming that that's
the opportunity that big daddy needed to
kidnap you he doesn't want your father
in the business he doesn't need the
competition at all i'll never go back
home i can understand how you feel but I
think you'd be a lot better off at home
with them right now then you would be
away besides you may be the influence
that they need to get out of this drug
shit yes I know my father brother need
or want to talk to right now oh just try
to move well besides all that I'm glad
you came down here tonight but you must
go back to them tomorrow I've already
spoken to your father and made
arrangements for us to meet with him
tomorrow morning in my office I'm not
just asking you to attend you will be
there well I promise I'll be there but
unless you own world
understand we come
okay got an idea I'm not look soft music
dancing maybe a few more drinks thing
we'll just forget about this whole with
deal that light
[Music]
I suppose up you need this yes you will
I just a fashion
whoa
you mean I've been missing this all this
time
get from and we go real damn it man I
told you to coin by that name sorry plus
that guy alcohol is the detective
another number of us again he's got the
girl is get the ransom to get everything
and now you didn't tell me this what did
you tell me yesterday couldn't help it
you left me tied up and fill up the guy
though this outcome is probably just try
to split I got a plan no my I don't have
the headache anymore well you don't have
to worry about me you know I have my
pills with me if I need them are you
gonna cook the greens tonight oh they're
already on i'll be home at five o'clock
i haven't had a good meal in a good
laugh oh I'm gonna have to go my boss is
here good morning mama yeah i'm back by
how many times did I have to tell you
this business phone
hi yeah I want you to meet wonderful
wonder this is soo hi how you doing
award listen Wanda's father harried a
ball and her brother Larry will be here
at any moment now I want you to have him
to come to Martha systems again are you
talking about those guys that were here
the other day listen I'm not asking for
a commentary hey yeah if they excuse my
father brother sometimes it just don't
half good man well there's reasons for
everything I'm sure they had one come on
yeah I'm a very nice office thank you
you know you're really very pretty this
morning it's a matter of thank you
really turn me up one day you're gonna
make some man very happy person can I
hope that person might be me you want to
make a woman really happy say your words
yeah I did a great job business are you
in trouble family reunion uh-huh but man
you process happiness to the parent of
every film what happened well I got your
back haha but without giving a breast
man that's great hahahaha where's my
money you wait a minute as far as you
would concern the bread is being turned
over to the Big Daddy game I could buy
that you did your job and you didn't
will but the main thing is where his
mash she I can't give it to you Harry
it's on the way to please ladies you
crazy you me to tell you to give up on
shut up man you have to be using your
goddamn mother when I hope there's no
check no objection don't crack ass
nobody tells every seat don't all right
all right all right all right maybe
you're right maybe you're right here's
what you do you get a check in the mail
airmail special every first thing in the
morning it's not necessary just what I
promise matter of fact is you
first in time if you want to be Robin
without take the money but when I take
the money I'm gonna give you some advice
there i will give you some advice you
better look up your big daddy ko begin
on your kiss for your blankets all i can
say is I know better thanks and good
luck come on let's go home ballet all
right heart feel friend
how's everything wrong no everything's
fine listen we'll have closed the
officer for a few days once you get a
couple of bucks for old thousand take
them home with you what's happening
nothing don't worry about it just do
what I tell you okay get the bosses
hell is there anything wrong I don't
understand what's happening no
everything's fine I'll Hamid office just
a minute I'll see if he's in there's a
man on the phone who says he's big day
and you may as well face him now she got
some you out yeah maybe he's right
perhaps I should talk to him now watch
that man
kind of speaking yeah I want to talk to
you too man be at the seventy-ninth
Street marina in one hour but they caddy
this is between me and you so come alone
don't worry about you don't worry babe
everything's gonna be fine but I've have
to go right now if anything should
happen to me destroy all my boss but
help hello I'll call his office Oh
Rhonda I'm so glad you called l got a
call from someone calling himself big
daddy and he's got something about
meeting him at the seventy-ninth Street
marina
that cat
[Music]
I'm glad you showed your black bastard
you know you got a big mouth and I can
back it all up cuz you're a dick don't
you think that's a little premature
either does big one you move you're dead
I'll take the big then give me this
you'll need this do what the man says
you know Connors I could use a man like
you in my operation for what kidnapping
dope
murder maybe that's not my thing Philip
L is your thing Connors what's your
price we all have a price big daddy you
can't forward
I put it to you this way cuz people
don't turn down my office handling
it's the first time for everything this
ain't your first time kindness when I
wouldn't be too sure about that
I could help it began shut the fuck up
Jim I didn't even know that one else we
found two people column in the bushes
over there I suspected you friends with
it how'd you find out I was in one of
those yeah so hit me to this bullshit
you get it just in time Connie's you
fucked up my whole organization but I
want to know one thing the true that
niggas are like dogs they only fighting
packs I want a piece of your ass if
you're not it go on yeah catch it just
like a right now Wow wait a minute it's
not necessary i'll talk to you in e they
get did you hear that sound of your
bullshit look there are times when a man
has to do things I don't want to keep
the gentleman waiting
fig that I want your guarantee Khanna's
when I kick your ass I'm gonna get out
of here alive he's got my word
you can do it fuck fuck
alright but yeah are you okay yeah
yeah are you all right
yeah yeah
lr you are yeah yeah I'm finding what
you wanted to do with these guys
I don't think I might have any more
problems out Big Daddy
what were the hell are you going I got
just a couple of more of those since I
gotta wrap up on this case and what mutt
what would that be
man are you thinking what is you better
be bound a new suit brother Brett haha