grandma sometimes I hear you still
ticking coming near me in the dark
grandma oh dear and wondrous electric
dream
grandma I remember the hour and day of
your birth when did it all begin that
terrible week our mother died but week
the world ended for me my brother
Timothy at my sister Agatha
I was the oldest and not supposed to cry
you
of all of us I big Agatha took it the
hardest
Agatha
well now we
you can't all mo all the time here's to
us now that's the spirit Henry no need
to fear Aunt Clara is here what a
surprise you don't think I'd stay away
at a time like this do you Henry my
goodness just look at all these gloomy
faces now I'm going to have this place
running like clockwork in no time Henry
Agatha you've got a spot on your dress
all right all right Thomas I want to see
those vegetables disappear and Timothy
oh I do believe you need a haircut well
now let's have a big smile for your
auntie all right well let's not all say
hello at once
Oh
how could his mine mine too I'll be give
it here why just a hunch
what are you doing see no now yours
Aggie there Agatha has more sense than
the rest of you that's right dear you're
just like me Oh daddy listen now yeah is
he a machine that gives love that's
preposterous it's five-pointed right no
huh let's go get one nothing's ever
gonna be like having mom back
you
this is it this place
hmm now wait don't run a boys boys now I
wouldn't I wouldn't go on down there by
over you Tom Timothy
here over here man till Cheney women
makers of robots from time immemorial
all shapes sizes colors especially Danny
we've already come too far now this is
madness
hello hello oh my goodness hello Tom
Timothy Agatha and this must be your
father welcome welcome take off your
coats who are you we go Fanta Cheney at
your service I believe you're looking
for something in a grandmother oh well
the boys got all carried away imagining
impossible things sign of great
intelligence that is she really electric
I mean can she walk and talk my grandma
who can sing shocked and tell bedtime
stories Timothy no machine can do that
even if it could it wouldn't be like a
real person oh no I think you might be
surprised Abigail Agatha the only limit
to what a machine can do is the limit of
one's own imagination you see this key
take it outside I ities with this key
you and you alone can bring your
electric grandmother to life my name's
Agatha and I don't believe in electric
grandmother's but if I did where would I
put the cake well that's for you to
figure out when the time comes My dear
after all I can't be expected to tell
you everything can I now look here just
what kind of a business are you running
here my business my business is
fulfilling dreams oh well excuse me but
I I think that sounds like a lot of
mumbo jumbo oh thank you I see you're
strictly a practical man I I believe in
what I can see in here in touch if I
tried to sell a stock to a client
without even explaining well allow me to
explain my terms you see all our
grandmother's are made to order on the
premises and I said to families select
families i may say for a 30-day trial
basis if at the end of 30 days any
of your family is dissatisfied with your
grandmother she's returned to the
factory under no obligation to you
whatsoever now even a practical man like
yourself has got to admit you've got
nothing to lose hmm well yes then shall
we proceed yes huh hi Jews and Bill
first we have thin grandmother's from
grandmother's she shouldn't be too fast
but not too bony either and shit out of
whack should feel kind of squishy it's
bushy
that one there hey where'd she go oh you
have to be quick Kennedy shadows don't
last long shall we go mrs. grey can't
wait to see what she's gonna look like
no then perhaps the young lady has some
idea about the color of her
grandmother's hair oh I see you wish to
leave the choice to the board
I like that ah
could it be wrong of course
that one the blue know either one no the
brain could they be this car it's my
favorite Marvel my grandmother's eyes
just that color I remember she used to
read uncle wiggly to us criminy I
thought of that in years yes
done
and her voice
say your name Timothy Oh shout it now
you're Tom Tom Tom bread oh come on
Amanda your turn this is ridiculous well
even more ridiculous not to try don't
think Henry Henry any hello it's her
that's what grandma sounds hello my god
come along mr. Panda Cheney yeah all
these choices they really go together to
make one electric creature well seeing
is believing as I'm sure you're safe
perhaps I will why can we get on well go
home ask me no questions I'll tell you
no lies one of these mornings you'll get
a surprise so long so a robot now Clara
listen if it was only up to me I
wouldn't have on the last straw Henry
bye
by word it's a sarcophagus is it ours
our very own must be a mistake it's too
beautiful look it has my name on it
indoors Wow
let's get the cables off the top grab
the end of that oh yeah
curiouser injury
cute
Timothy you're in your pajamas it's 20
degrees out here you'll catch your death
oh my goodness you're all in your
pajamas oh well get get get get mouse
help me up oh wow I suppose you haven't
had your breakfast can know we were so
excited about the hell am I hurry up her
you get into the housing get through and
calm Agatha Timothy oh I don't know how
the world you ever got along without me
I'm Jackson fried ham french toast my
favorite I've had that food for but a
small French restaurant near leader
mango in Paris 15 years ago how did you
do that huh
knelt orange juice Agamemnon Agatha oh
I'm so sorry Agatha oh I'm afraid I have
a terrible weakness when names are
concerned me you've got a clock inside
you okay what for well to hear what mr.
Shakespeare cozy inaudible of noiseless
would have time Shakespeare jours well
that ends well act 5 scene 3 bad 5 scene
3 oh my goodness it eight o'clock
already this is a school day for you I
want to go to school I understand home
with you what kind of a grandmother
would I be if I had to get away with
that come on finish up
hey looking know anything
you
milk uh-huh thank you I wish I had hair
like yours what that color oh I never
take it out of this bun so Audrey but I
what see ugly
would you brush it for me yet
your hair is so beautiful mine oh no no
yours is beautiful oh I'd so love to
brush it and braid it for you no you
can't do that only my mother I'm sorry
Agatha
use this thing
anyway string snooker oh it's hopeless
Tom Timothy give me that please
no wonder you can't work it and got
enough string I know fly probably
holy Toledo it's fine Wow Agatha boys
hand me the clothes send them up to be
washed by the clouds and dried by the
wind
I don't think that's so great
what on the chicks can you do that
Timothy you'll wear her out no he won't
I'm a living instance of immutability
mr. Darwin might put it I can't get over
the things you know Darwin Shakespeare
Plato machine-made to teach it's one of
my most important capabilities Agatha
aren't you cold over there I'm all right
well tell us what else well I store up
everything say or do so years from now
when you're married the children of your
own that's a billion years away the
memory of everything you said and did
will still be here okay what was I
saying at three-thirty today careful
Todd
muffin break it open
holy Toledo it's flying the pets kind of
be the greatest thing I've ever seen
nine o'clock bedtime for Timothy and
Agatha Gemma could you sing me sir mr.
fana Cheney promised me a grandma who
could sing songs all right just one and
then I want you asleep Timothy Timothy
never you fear trouble won't trouble you
now that I'm here I know the secrets
that grandmother's no trust me to love
you and help you
you
grandmother's know how to keep away hard
go off to sleep with your head on my arm
dreams will bring happiness all the
night through I'll be here waiting to
help them
you
I love him I love you you'll never go
where grandma will you of course not
I'll be here forever and I'll always be
here when you need
you
goodnight Agatha sweet time
I wish I had your talent for getting
along with the children you do you all
see good night phyto said we were all
like cave dwellers we ever came out into
the sunlight would be to dazzle to see
anything have sleep give me the splendid
silent son with all his beams fool
dazzling did you see that no Walt
Whitman Oh Timothy cross your teeth huh
second my fourth work forgot to cross
your teeth and 6 x 124 is not what you
think it is I get what a few and Matt
could I see that no don't pay any
attention her grandma she's a horrible
grouch you shut up Agatha don't speak to
your brother that way you can't tell me
what to do
Agatha I want to talk to you Agatha your
dinners getting cold
you
you can get them to love you but I never
will never just a machine just a machine
haha you swine ah Oh triumph triumph
father wins fair and square no one no
throwing snowballs near the house oh I
can't believe how the boys have changed
since you've been here and so of you me
well I feel wonderful it's true now if I
could only bring Agatha around oh she's
afraid and that makes her angry it's my
task to discover the source of her fear
hmm sound so reasonable reasonable is if
I understood what that meant anymore I'm
talking to this machine as if she were a
real woman often I feel you are a real
woman well sometimes I wonder what sort
of a human being I am to be so much less
understanding than a machine oh now
that's not sense I'm a machine and made
up of you and Tom and entity and Agatha
and everything you ever say or ever do I
shall put away in treasure always I'm so
used to thinking of machines is cold and
inhuman machine is what it does good
machine does good things bad machine
does bad thing glad some clothespins
please see I have time time for your
children to tell me their dreams to say
what they want to be and I shall run
ahead on the path and help them be it
even Agatha I truly believe you can do
almost any
Oh
what happened Agatha
Agatha
hey wait wait wait why did you do that
why Agatha what do you have against her
tell me um Timothy Agatha come in here
please sit down please there's something
I'm I'm very sorry to have to tell you
what well you remember our agreement
with mr. penta Cheney 30 days have gone
by so fast what your father means to
tell you is that I let's go back to know
why it's something that we didn't know
it's something I didn't do I failed to
make all of you happy what satisfaction
was guaranteed you it's you send her
back somehow did the scrap heap oh no
Timothy I mean it daddy Timothy a
bargain is a bargain as long as one of
you is unfulfilled as sad
uneasy because of me then I must go
please I have to but you said you'd stay
forever and ever Timothy don't make this
harder but that's what she said she
promised she lied don't you see she's a
liar chiseling just like who I
yeah all right but I don't think well
it's alright it's alright it's alright
no no it's alright it's alright
no dear not like I'm not you're not no I
can't die see and it wasn't no why what
when she said she'd never go away you're
not like her not like mom no dear you
always be here always cross her No
your help
that was it all a little horse you
thought I'd imitate your mommy go away
and never come back now you see I can't
be killed I'll always be hearing me now
do you believe yes even you and Tom and
Timothy are old and childish and smaller
I'll still be here for you
you
grandma what did you mean about when we
get old I never ever gonna get home oh
no haha Oh soon you're way off you'll be
weighing high school colleagues million
billion years away haha a million
billion years okay all right who's king
of the hill
you
Oh Tom you will write you from college
you promise
the biker oh ok maybe so proud of
Oh Oh Agatha by so fast
well back to the factory dear
oh I shall have so much to talk so much
to share of course I'll be there for the
children ever they sleep Oh
you
well we didn't eat grandma for many
years but then we used to play kingdom
and Red Rover so many other games it's
hard to believe the things i found
myself doing with them setting off
fireworks on the fourth of july and the
snowball fights the boys told me how to
play tom and timothy army and i must say
i got quite good at it the things one
learns from them yes Agatha taught me
the most I think here listen this is
when she was just a little girl I love
you so pretty no sometimes I almost feel
that I feel so do I sometimes I forget
the difference between loving people and
paying attention to them there is a
difference isn't it I think so grandma
Tom 00 young you look oh uh oh no I'm
just the same what about the others
Agatha she became a doctor a good woman
and Timothy Timothy help build a
permanent base on the moon me I I spent
my life writing books 16 of them has
that much time pass too much too much
and now my time has come round again has
it husbands wives families we three
outlived them all in the same old house
you you come then you be there of course
when when ask me no questions I'll tell
you no lies but one of these mornings
Oki Kenji even remember to nob eggy what
is it what do you think you don't go
Agatha Agatha never you feel trouble
won't trouble you now that I'm here I
know the secrets that grandmother's no
trust me to love you and help you to
grow gramma I love you oh grandma come
play with us will you brush my hair
grandma demo come on let me help oh no
me
grandma I love you turn about round
about sharing our day
teaching each other in so many ways tell
me the best that you dream you could be
I'll be a sunlight and helps
turn about round about sharing our day
teaching each other in so many
tell me the best that you dreamed you
could be i'll be the sun life that helps
you to
you