[Music]
yourself
it's been almost a year now jumped us
last night
us in the Atlantic you an ocean liner
lost at sea
my a lighthouse without its keeper just
a flicker of light for a heart by
starlight you navigated your way back to
me prepared this failing light of mine
soon thousands of ships also lost at sea
sailed into port was a weird dream but
we promised each other honest that's
what matters in the end waiting for you
on the other side for me come back
loving letter-writing husband back
PS how the fuck do I work the washing
machine possible girl
[Music]
water right
ok
and
[Music]
so
[Applause]
you know this isn't exactly healthy
right in any meaning of the word how
many accidents
for
it'll be a hundred and one dollars in 89
sir I'm sorry your cards been declined
credit cards comes Oh
try this one this one
I'm sorry sir
you
try this one maybe it's this one for
sure
there you go perfect ok I wasn't sure
are you sure all right why would I don't
know I just
I'm all right
alright
ok
asus
ki okay yeah I'm all right listen just
wondering if you could take my hospital
shift tonight
what come on scooters got something
planned tonight I'm not a first shipped
like all they can handle see here I know
it's hard but this is the fourth time in
a row that i've covered to shift i'm
exhausted i've been working all night is
going and nursing okay Charlie first
truly said to ask you
great your listen you gotta stop water
on your front of the store they're
giving me shit about her i will i'm
serious neck
yes ma'am I cross my heart ok stay out
of trouble
Oh remember to talk to dad alright yeah
they're so sometimes i wonder what
people see when they look at me and look
at my eyes they know about you
the other side of that ocean is the same
for you out there in that desert and the
heat
maybe they look at you all they see is
the soldier fighter now head to the wife
and you know hit the other half hint of
me
let's be on the face beyond the eyes and
in the heart of person truth home miss
you
[Music]
right
that come on I know you're in there
please talk to mom and dad they just
want to know their son is alright and if
you're not just let us in literally call
me please
ya know your mom trying to just that
we were
[Music]
ok
[Applause]
yes I hello um I need to see the doctor
last thing
oh yeah no I don't actually have an
appointment I have an equality an
emergency
now there's this pain in my stomach
I'm sorry so that work by appointment
only this isn't the walk-in clinic
I know but my family doctor I figured it
just asking quickly
where's Nancy she knows me and she
doesn't work here anymore sir on the new
receptionist
oh ok alright maybe you could ask the
doc for just a minute and see if you can
see me it first place you are not
allowed to do that as I said work by
appointment to link these me ma'am
please
something is wrong with me I can't
breathe properly unconscious and I'm
sweating too so if you could just I
don't know maybe you'll get the dark
right before you appreciate I'm sorry
sir i'm not allowed to do that actually
said we are by a point the power of
nature of these images have struck a
chord with world and seeing if you have
more tragic all i can do see another
triangulating guerrilla attacks from the
other side of the car you're right okay
drama and I've been pointed okay all the
time for which day sir which which they
mistake today we're all booked up today
sir I fine nevermind good for God's sake
lady to change the channel things I mean
people got enough shit to deal with
walking into a place like this point
would like to invite you would
[Music]
excuse me yeah on your ally is Alice
Colin she's my sister she works here
oh yes i think i just saw her a few
minutes ago back still being over there
is hard for everyone but freaking tell
them all right tell them when i leave
Ellie please
alright fine can I help with your hand
what night don't let this this is fine
this is ok know how do you want me to
write in the description think I can do
that
well fine no matches I could lose my job
not to mention that those pills aren't
the answer here probably making things
worse
what I can get someone to talk to i go
through properly give you something that
will help
yeah yeah I don't know you won't call
that
no no he came to find me
I don't know I think he wanted to refill
of when it sells prescriptions noted to
have it out
you're kidding me
please your new I've been here every day
for a month
Gina always let me step out I'm not
Dennis and you're not allowed to stay
past visiting hours and those are the
rules
that's my father in there what is wrong
with you people you working this this
hospital and you can't be a little arm
more bhai you know my sister Alice
Callahan remember she's okay so i'm
alright it's just the rules no I know
I'm to just frustrated
yeah I'm sorry I have some frustration
issues
frustration she's yeah i'm not that
quick on my feet you tonight okay I'm
back I'm sorry fine i just thought maybe
I could help
thank you just this damn hospital stuff
and when I tell you all right then
yeah I just panicked a little bit okay
Ciera
wait what are you doing here
oh my sister works here and then I just
needed some advice on something
yeah you know maybe it's the diet maybe
what about you
that in a coma
oh I'm sorry my brothers and I he turns
talking to him I think it makes them
feel better about you he likes singing
but I can't carry the team to save my
life for any life peers sorry I just I
talk much like now I'm sorry I'm
scrambling no it's okay um I know how it
is you do we all got our things
sure
got my girl war
we are better things
yeah listen if any of the other nurses
give you any trouble just find Alice
Callahan child
thank you so much yeah you're on you
so what would you like to talk about
today pop the weather is nice it's on
four
okay Gwen got a fairly good son beat
don't you go get some sleep
snake alright
you've been talking to debt
been trying
[Music]
looks like your team in the playoffs
called it the pitch going to be good
game too
[Music]
I mean
yeah Ellie
limits
[Applause]
I'm sorry Allie it's just I thought this
was it
you're gonna have to open up trying
you're always easy one kiddo
come on you in there told if you're in
there Colorado for the damn door
my old man's been good to you man you
always right I'll be waiting
you can't hide forever
[Music]
even now or continue every minute we
don't want you and costs every day
[Applause]
thank God didn't take that's right
aiming at her right now
[Music]
on
hey hey wait wait and slicer but no no I
listen I just need a refill on this
again I'm sorry but we upload come on
look you could just maybe if you could
just go back there and help me out i
really appreciate it it's just one reap
the computers are already shut down
you'll have to come place 24 hours on
the signs please don't make a scene
sorry tired the prescription counter is
not open all night
it's been a long and hard day and I'm
tired I just want to get home i wish i
could help you but I can't won't help me
once the computers are down for the
night that down for the night there's
nothing i can do it
please just listen move for like five
seconds okay I'm having a really bad
week here you know I'm having one of
those of locked my keys in my car time
we only I haven't done that actually but
the thing is I need this reef film okay
if you can't help me if you can fill
this up I'm gonna lose it you
threatening me so what
no no no not gonna lose it with you i'm
going to use it with me
what's your name Ali I have a sister
named Ali I Valley please
um I can't keep my shit together without
these I need this refilled I'm asking
you man to man
human-to-human help me out
please so i can't fill it i can
recommend something with the bloody
counter by God for your fucking
prescription so
you're mean ok that's it I'm calling
security
boom
hello this is still so again I can't
hear anything us babe are you okay
hello so they are you alright
hello everybody
well what is it
hello so hello hello
[Applause]
look at this fucking asshole what did
your friend leave you what I like a
little girl should be ashamed and public
at that you know people got bigger
problems in you what real fuckin
problems get some real issues to what
we're going to do so I'm sorry I'm sorry
[Music]
other man to respecting team at a
24-hour local supermarket the two
teenagers were waiting for ryan when a
man is like you want to attack them from
behind injuring what you're putting the
other next Tyler in critical condition
the attacker is the largest the police
that were beyond the description at the
moment
[Music]
looking for Nick Tyler he was brought in
here last night I would pull out one of
his friends were attacked by some
bastard
well only family members are allowed on
this unit
are you family yeah family
[Music]
sorry kid doing nothing but what are you
doing
ah do you know this boy is he gonna be
all right how do you know him but he's
gonna be okay hope so you're not looking
so good
I gotta go tank before please before one
you called that I asked you not to any
called him he just wants to talk to you
doesn't matter i gotta go from the
matter is your parents scared to death
call it's making one sick say you care
hey it's here
what's wrong I don't know
[Music]
ok
I
[Music]
get lost on this bullshit
I didn't ok got his plate Nick are you
okay what's going on Nick what happened
in my parking want
why did that guy attack ii is true
chased him off your ok he's here he's
gone he's gone
ok maybe five
[Music]
kitchen get to get his niece what
getting good picnic in this bed put our
brother in that bed care I care if I
thought you turned him and I cheer you
on and be happy for you not to bring
scooter ya sister still work at the DMV
yeah we got his plate charge of dinner
plates not even kind
what are you trying to get him yeah yeah
give me some paper I'm going to check
ok
away
[Music]
and see your school
wanna see a spark
[Music]
ok
[Applause]
a mac
I got you now hot you think you can hide
from you son of a beach just forget my
family's have this for telling look I've
been really catch up with you but this
is not a good talent here asshole
I'm carrying my old man's got you a lot
of slack or your wife being over in the
service and all
even I had respect for that you going to
use RP you're going to use our sympathy
started look I'll get you the money I'll
catch you the goddamn read your fucking
right you will friday
we came back using that gives your when
you talk too long we chased him out of
there
you think you heard that kid you think
you've heard that before I can't maybe
this this whole thing with Sylvia away
just for you just need some help from as
I think he's not interested and help
from us you gotta you gotta help with
that and some you can do it you're the
only person is even remotely close to
that can't be responsible for him
sure no it's alright i'm in a while you
want no no i'm sorry i really be a
you're doing great kiddo didn't grain
and calling the house you what calls and
it feels like he's going to say
something they just hangs up damn it I
gotta go i love you okay i'll be too dad
sure you're okay
[Music]
where's the other guy what's-his-name
alley
hello no he's not here at the moment can
I help you in some project that's good i
yes yes can I need a refill on my wife's
painkillers you do that
of course surgery you have some idea yes
thank you
you'll be ready in 15 minutes all right
I'll just browse thank you
when right you
I'm sorry 80 corner that ok how's your
dad
someone beat up my brother is now
recovering the same hospital
what
some asshole attacked him and started to
be quiet little harder
I'm sure make asked for it but him and
my dad please
you're reading on a prescription yeah
listen I we are due for a break
we got to talk to someone
ok
[Music]
I'm sorry sir but the car didn't go
bucks
no no no this this one works sorry
missing a diamond sucks
we'll just say you worked
it's okay
we all deserve a break sometimes
we do
ok
tell me about your life
her name is Sylvia
one calls herself she enlisted signed up
for the war happen parents are well off
we got married young 21 she was plenty
young mistake that worked out all those
marriages that only gets better you know
anyway she got called out a year ago and
here we are
heart wasn't that bad at first just
steadily got worse
ever since I was young I've had this
thing where if i can think of something
bad could happen at this very moment
then there's no way that it could
actually happen more specific i am
imagining this bad thing
greater the odds are against it actually
happening
that's fucked up yeah I now right
to break still wrote that on my arm just
before she left
I don't know what it means to is always
doing shit like that difference is this
time I gotta too beautiful to see
something ridiculous
it's what they call stress rash
never had it before I have them all over
oh yeah watch this
[Music]
all got our things
well gotta things
look we're trying to get off sometime
ya think so i want to show you something
something that helps me okay
[Music]
it's the soft white noise
exactly
[Music]
I've got to get back to the hospital
didn't he ride we can thanks
[Music]
I hope bomb your brother and your father
end up ok i hope your wife comes back to
you
[Music]
[Applause]
ok
what scooter trying but is that this is
the DMV paying for that creepy asshole
see it when you're right trail isn't
soon
now i know i don't use all right but ok
[Music]
I need to go find charlie
for God's sake or Mac yeah not ready
I don't understand why do you have to be
ready I don't know I haven't been able
to since since you left
why are you doing this why do you have
to make this your responsibilities dad
asked me to and because mom's worried
not trying to put you in the middle of
this am in the middle of it I didn't ask
to be the fuck up you know are you
talking about this is about you being
responsible for your life so others
don't have to worry but still say this
is me at my best but you're not okay
that's why there's an eviction notice on
you want to help you
you can't help me Alice
there you are
DMV registration we got this Punk
[Applause]
Matt Callahan waiting for Charlie let's
go get you see this i'm in the middle
meal is a fucking okay with you
[Music]
so hot but wait well like what was
happening I can't hear anything
damn it's still just tell me you're all
right thank God thank God huh
I was so worried so what's going on
what's happening
come on you I'm fine home
I'm perfect I was have you been getting
my letters letters so good to hear your
voice
so what
hello hello
[Music]
when this is this is not a good time
going
how did you know where I live what's
wrong
when I thought you were my friend
I thought you were a good person her
mother and then through your teeth you
lie to me to my feet don't I don't you
goddamn tiny I can fight it in you
didn't know he was your brother and it
was an accident when I can't do this
right now i wanna i was hot but
something has happened and I have to
have to arena or you just don't want to
know a priest just
[Music]
hey I'm sorry you're a bad god man you
did anyone
no no I'm sorry I'm sorry
oh no just please i don't i don't know
oh that's when can you just come back
later
I have to find out about Sylvia i'll be
here tomorrow I promise where Charlie
Charlie I think I think you sick or
something
one that her neck hurt my brother yes
I'm sorry sorry doesn't cut it ask have
have to go see about self-taken Charlie
for God's sake Charlie please Quentin
sorry Gwen
[Applause]
I didn't mean to hurt you did he set
things to me and I snap it was my fault
what he said things ok about my
girlfriend your girl hope you have a
white God movie I I need to go got a
wife serving the portrait hell out of my
way
why would you tell me that look I know I
did you wrong
ok but I can't do this right now
hey fuck you fuck you I decide when it's
time okay look I'm not trying to skip
out on this man alright but I have to go
find out of my wife is okay
he's obviously not well right now
Charlie look at him
ok way get out of my way home
your big man that was that right what do
you want from me seeing you you don't
even want to do this
you deserve a break
alright
what i understand you need this so let's
just get it over with that ok I don't do
that shit that reverse psychology shit
is not gonna get you out or not i
understand you need this so let's just
do but then i have to go find out about
my wife fuck is this
please come on just hurry
it's okay
you can do it
great
[Music]
I
Holly nothing okay what color
no no I just wanted to talk to speak to
Mac dad and done you need to figure out
a way to see yourself likely have to
he won't talk to me I want to be his
sister I have to find that again and
that means saying no to you
I'm sorry dad
no more
[Music]
dad
are you
that is mom's sick I will system let me
yeah yeah i am sorry i will just let me
know what
no dad this is not a good time
come on dad please just not now open the
door please
I'm not leaving until you what the hell
is this a good shake back this is what
is this
open the goddamn door
[Music]
oh no look bad though you're stronger
than this
Jesus Christ please can we just do this
tomorrow right
ok when I what's happened to do
oh it's a bad time
I'm not leaving you what's going on back
you gotta tell me I want you to know I'm
not going anywhere
old Mac please get out of here please
that would you just go just go would you
just go which you can just go just go
just go just go just go to school all
right
[Music]
take me
you sure about this
[Music]
I gotta do this
right yeah
we all got her things
[Music]
and see your spoor
wanna see
[Music]
my
wanna see
[Music]
[Applause]