you
I
Thanks so on can be singing along
hello Molly meron great day isn't
morning when did you get back just now I
saw Santa the whistle stop he didn't
seem to know me and no wonder you look
like a mendham is it linked it better be
Saddam married are pictures of breakfast
only coffee my you're just like my
chinny you never eat anything in the
morning she isn't surprised to see you
what brings you back from Chicago money
money you look like you're rolling in it
don't let this code for you Molly main
can cover a lot of things I can i sell
the hot we do all your some rent don't
wait well I never wrote to ask you
because I never needed it till now you
sure it didn't did you lose your job no
I gave it up Oh Molly can I see you for
a couple days of course is your house
I'll have kitty moved out of your room
in a jiff no no don't wake him up it's
too early well he's here right now he he
hasn't left town as he oh no you know
Kitty is always up to Ashbury looking
around looking for what well you know
Kenny always on the go right now I bet
he's working on a big deal
I'll say three me too how many I'll take
three I'll take five
one dime my mom
raise your nickel
that sounds like the train from Chicago
she's thanking someone he's not
expecting no one I'll see you queen king
and three deuces you haven't won a pot
all night Barker cards are against me I
don't know you did pretty good when you
brought your own deck you're not doing
so good yourself with cards or anything
else meaning what well Lou got a letter
from an old friend of yours no one cares
last time I listen she called girl who
had me look her up she's doing all right
for herself shut up you want to see the
hotel she living in strictly class yeah
who'd ever think a little Mary would
wind up wearing mink wind up keeping
that big trap yo shut you hear me forget
a Kenny she's no good for you that's
what I like about you you gonna blend
your nerves morning miss Elaine uh-huh
what happened to you his tongue slipped
you have to bar in a mess don't clean it
up getting my job I'm a bartender hella
nice boy sometimes I'm not too sure
shooting off your mouth again huh oh you
hit me when I wasn't looking forget it
one of these days is gonna swing and
miss shave yeah
thanks
I am armed now you listen to be Kenny
I've been telling you you've got the
stuff to staying out all night and I
haven't been talking just to hear myself
either mom you're getting fat guess what
I'm not good at guessing anymore Mary's
back cops on the stove be sure you hot
oatmeal
Mary
hiya beautiful hi Anne
gee I missed you what's been so long
where did you get this it's a present
from who oh yeah owns a department store
we almost got married
two lovely Mary from George that come
with the coat no there's more than one
department store in Chicago you know big
stars in ashbury what did you come back
here for maybe I came back to you you
chump sure it wasn't somebody else euro
tellu lens I answer this letter that's
more than I got for you you never got
anything for me go ahead and say it I
never asked anything from anybody know
what's not loving New York before my
love friend something special
I suppose you've been pretty busy since
I've been gone and I'm gonna be kept
busy
I
my life you opened a restaurant in
Chicago you slam you buy you not only
the best cook which a given be the best
looking girl at ashbury uh-uh watch how
long that's gonna cost you an extra
dollar now you know Mary 30 years ago I
don't say them in Chicago without haha
hiya folks Oh Artie you remember Mary
don't you any money come on my apple pie
hey my I couldn't eat another bite
adjust at dinner just take a little
Cayenne hiya folks hbu Mary from Lou
glance why should I put it oh gee red
roses they're nice huh
well along
you know can have been seeing about for
you some of those wives strawberries
this year they make such nice sauce how
about thinking you summer huh let Josie
do it I am NOT going to spend my day off
picking berries what are you doing
that's so important that's no way to
talk junkie well no one ever said
anything about him doing a single lick
of work no he can go to Ashbury every
night and spend the money you're giving
drinking and chasing around she's right
you want to quit that kind of monkey
business we have that sort of a family
no sorry you should make any to do same
around here waiting for a job to come to
hero's you're the best time to start
looking for a job as eight o'clock at
night if you do a good job of looking
you can't get home to morning and the
best place for looking is every beer
join a pool on Main Street that's
telling him you shut up same Beach if it
wasn't for any given you back to job
jujube sir never you mind son don't pay
attention to your father Josie is just
blowing off steam come on Ernie let's go
if you gone to town ready and give me a
lift okay Carrie why Kenny I thought
you're gonna stay home tonight I've got
a date
wait a minute Ernie I'll go with you 30
thanks daddy
where are you going not where you're
going
brandy a drink
you shouldn't have come in here they get
it give me a break you're only asking
for trouble let me worry about that
I
hello no thanks for the roses I've been
expecting you why you sitting in the
dark I hadn't noticed it was so late
what hair shines in the light video
don't wear a ribbon anymore that's what
struck me the first time I ever saw your
own changed a bit in two years lo have
you
I came back
wine there in to sell a house that's why
where's a little homesick how would
anyone were homesick for this town still
can't get him out of your blood I
couldn't Chicago
I wanted to see what he was like again I
did
he'll never change I could have told you
that two years ago wouldn't have helped
two years ago I eat his guts the
arrogant way he walks around like he
owns the town and he hasn't got the
price of yesterday's newspaper
come here
just look at that he knows the way I
feel about a meeting has the nerve to
come in here tonight
you
still love me friend
what's the matter aren't you glad to see
me you didn't come to see me thought we
had a date for last night remember
hello kids up hello you can talk that on
that hello Mary
give me 50
going
might as well
well he's back remember Kenny
listen to me Kenny I tell you there's
nothing for us here Chicago's a big city
we can make out there what'll I do in
Chicago dig ditches well what are you
doing here playing cards all the time
the town your friends your family
they're all poison for you Kenny at
least there you'll have a chance you'll
meet new people something will turn up I
know it will too many Lou lenses there
I'm gonna mention me this is a private
party and just thought I could do
something for you sunny yeah you can
give me a cigarette anything else now
you can light it
now you got all you want you'd better go
I don't want your hanging around here
the next time won't be so sociable if
you said that with a smile and a sound
better let's go go where I'll take you
to your house and swing down the hammy
hold it very funny no you asked me to go
to the Wilton Club as the office till go
sure take your hand off it make up your
mind if you're going with him or me my
mind's made up now beat it sunny
Danny stop it stop it Kenny I'm through
Kenny I'm through wasting my life trying
to change you I'm leaving this town for
good Kenny you whistle them
Kenny duck
come on snap out of it in let's go to
get in Berlin have a drink just the two
of us
what you went to town got a cigarette no
matter when you find no excitement
listen to that rooster crow keep set up
all night long can't even hear the train
whistle my gold coming out of here and
my back is killing me Duan won't pop
I'll take over next you will find a cent
to that box answer that
how you Kenny how you get low how about
a gamma casino yeah I don't feel like it
ah just a couple of hands I can never
sleep until daylight
no I like it in here trains passing by
down here cause up there full of life if
we're always alone I feel safe to you
know working in the nightclub and living
in the hotel he's always around always
watching me just because they once got
in a jam the police don't know what he
does he never says nothing but I know is
only waiting for me to make one wrong
move who's a mean guy that way you don't
take ten of diamonds I sure surprises
you marry only I figured she would be
coming back to you of course after she'd
call though it would be kind of hard on
her to come down to your way living
especially was an important guy like Lou
nuts about it did you see him take that
50 bucks why he'd spend that light we
would 50 cent you know that makes a big
impression on a girl did you throw that
deuce
as if it wasn't for Lou I'd be happy
will be better for you too we both
wouldn't have a thing to worry about
Carter sticky on me I forget a new deck
never told you how I got no trouble
today I lost my nerve that's what I like
about you Kenny you got plenty of nerve
well it's three weeks to the ashbury
annual fair jeweler first that's a big
day for Lou he makes plenty of money out
of those concessions as cheery he made
over fifteen thousand dollars I know
because I drove him to the train and
when the show closes he takes the money
to a bank in detroit and the train for
Detroit has to be pried from here see
now if the diner signal box let her
forget her flight the train who wouldn't
get back to Detroit would give me or
your toddler brings him oh it can be
easy done all I have to do this I Drive
do up here your old man's rheumatisms
bothering him again that's why you're
here see now I can wait a few minutes
that's all a guy with nerve needs then I
Drive nikara I know we're pleased to be
waitin
as far as anyone knows who never comes
back from Detroit
trade the Detroit always on time
one so good
and with
whoa
one
was the minority good to have you home
one night your new hire beautiful swell
hi folks all day I'm here will you guys
know
well Josie get the new dress meri badi
Farah yeah where Mary get the money
what are you doing home tonight
lunetta tried to me feel are you doing
luetta drive to mayfield ken let's go
outside sure
have you got a cigarette yeah
Thank
what happened to George well he's in the
bottom sure that's a good place for
you see a lot of Gitmo don't you now and
then for you now by the good guy buys me
dreams rocking drinks but he's a good
guy once get low gotten a lot of trouble
no got him out get low and be around
today maybe he's got something out Lou
that guy that brought the red roses who
don't keep him around for laughs either
go if you would get low will you are you
telling you this Alou thank you why do
you keep seeing blue
what about me Mary what about us us can
this is all the restaurant
you think you can get anything you want
that way don't you there's something the
guy don't give up without a fight you're
wrong Kenny you've got the wrong slant
on everything you're hurting everyone
your father your mother your sisters me
you've always told me that no matter
what I do what I feel and I'm always
wrong maybe you're right Mary but I'll
be right too
I'll take those Mitch sure Kenny
yes
well Kenny we're all set for the big
fair and we're gonna start right on
schedule only two more days now this
one's gonna be better than last year you
signed on a whole carnival yes sir this
fair is gonna make someone a rich guy
that's good beer and that's my beer
hello honey sit down take care of my boy
with you you got left on his mind poor
mommy Kenny you like attention huh I'd
like a little more from you
lately you do seem to have a lot on your
mind a lot of Mary what about Mary the
whole town's laughing at you you trying
to compete with Lou lens you know you
don't stand a chance
why don't you quit beating yourself down
Kenny
once again
remember remember when we all fall and
then we saw
war
when you're here
oh let's not play games Kenny what do
you think you're going you know where
and you can't hold me by closing a suit
King stay a little while longer that's
all I'm asking let's stop kidding each
other Kenny the sooner I leave the
better will it be better what have I got
with you
you get what you give when I needed you
most you walked out on me now you're
walking out again I never promised you
anything before but I'm making you
promise now we will go together
go where anyway
the long walked anywhere
this time you're right
I
Oh many
go ahead Kenny sure what you do ah sees
it a knockover clay pigeons
I'll bet you can't hit that light up
there
Daniel Boone that's me buddy want to
lose out about your 50 cent
then
she's against the law to shoot electric
bulbs
your money out what's matter you lose
your nerve
we're big long here without how do you
feel now oh I feel one will have enough
what will have another integer weight
which is right I've gotta keep awake
you're so good to me Sam I mean oh let's
go to the week oh this is terrible nerd
he'll have to take over the whistle stop
you'll ruin our whole evening you she
comes
Sam you want to be a seat where did you
get the money get less than buy him
drinks get low I didn't know he had to
work tonight oh so you didn't know that
he has to work you didn't tell him huh
well all I gotta say to keep your big
nose out of other people's affairs you
go on run along children Kenya take over
the business stop
and while i lick you to death make sure
you my mommy or so poor idiot yes I am I
here miss Mars getting very generous
with the beach family he's a good guy
looks like you're it tonight can't be
helped couldn't it someone has to take
over
naturally it would be you come on let's
go watch the kid
I
and
backing up my
Oh
when
Kenny would you like them
Oh
hitting a collar on me for just a second
I'm in a hurry what do you want I'll get
the captain to the lady will you make me
there I'll get lost with you all right
but when Mary tells you the same thing
don't come crawling back to me
get back home please stand back Terrace
no shooting gallery yeah so long hey you
ready to what's the hurry you don't know
mr. trendy sit down
will you sit down
as a man lucky
no let's go
where's my car what it was here a while
ago and person left the keys in this
again now who will steal your car no he
just went off by itself welcome to you
Carlo Mary took someone will take the
station where did you hear friend had an
accident too bad
come on we'll get in
you didn't have to leave it there I
could have walked molly was worried
you'd be late I still got another time
matter what you want me to drive you
down what gave you that idea somebody
who had enough time you certainly left
in an awful hurry
how come you're so quiet tonight I
haven't been London safe
and never stopped you Gavin before
most down
well you are just in time thanks wait
Kenny what for that's something I want
to tell you later later maybe too late
I'll be back on the afternoon train via
what are you doing here where's where's
well it's just as I expected the
father's drunken his sons probably
getting drunk it's a fine family I'm
marrying into you better take the train
Ernie
great night this turned out to be
I asked you a question get low what are
you doing here
I talked to Kenny with you I keep him
company sometimes play a little cod
well the cards
see come on let's go this wouldn't have
been your lucky night anyway
what are you doing what's the idea you
can get out now now Kenny what was going
on between you and get on tonight you
seem to figure it out for yourself I'm
hoping I was wrong
this time we're ride huh Mary I can get
up
well only one more month to the big
moment irony yeah I'm counting the days
Oh Annie gee whiz honey it's our wedding
out of funeral same difference hey do
you think I should invite little ends
mom I don't know why you're sure just
because Mary moved over to his hotel is
no reason why he has to go play she goes
you know go nowheres without him since
the bear Kenny Kenny come eat your
supper
I saw Fran at the hospital today she any
better when the doctor says she won't
pull through tough break for the kid
she would love to see you Kenny
alright alright you're going to be real
nice to her aren't you well he didn't
think I was gonna go and fight with it
did you well I don't know what to expect
from me after the way you treated Mary
or bottle it well there isn't anything
Fran would have done for you Kenny and
you know it oh why don't you stop
she mustn't stay long she's a very sick
girl but
thank you my friend
made you weren't coming
never would have had the nerve to ask if
Josie and told me how you felt about you
taking over fun we get ahead together I
know I won't go through
I'm not scared I'm happy we got you
Kevin you care about me stupid Oh
yeah sure
what should be happy darling
after a while
there are some nice girl and settle down
that's the way I want it Kenneth honest
don't talk like that friend you'll be
out of here in a couple of weeks and
will will
don't take it so hard candy it'll work
out all right
look at me
look at McKinney
Josephine I'd kid
mustn't late joseph no she she was
described
Oh
I'm sorry too fair should have been
different sorry for everything look at
yourself you're all broken up never
thought a woman could do this to you how
does it feel kitty how does it feel the
love someone it doesn't give a darn
about you
nerd stupid it hurts doesn't it give me
all the while i loved you i was at
scared too i can see now you're nothing
to be afraid of nothing good will ever
happen to you because you're no good not
gone down here chillin
you
we're the boys out nobody showed up
tonight I hear your sisters getting
married Kenny yeah you want to see the
trial by court this morning down a
Miller's Brooke it was that big and I'd
wait hurry up will ya tonight's my
birthday you wanted artistic don't you
of course and don't rush me oh hey Teddy
lay off there will you thanks Joe hiya
Kenny fist fight now that's the place I
have a bar the steel mill really gets a
man of faith I've never been the
Pittsburgh give me a double coming on
how come you drinkin alone on a Saturday
night I'm getting exclusive haven't you
heard give me another one
why don't you break down and go see if
any not a bad idea
we'll call it mr. it will get midgets
from all over the world little midget
why I'm telling you do with the greatest
idea since Noah's Ark I haven't do
better than bad why I'm telling you Lew
will make a fortune well ball over the
world but I have another idea we're a
South African will buy it whoo well what
are we celebrating remember this is a
private party well tonight I'm buy it
well you have I'll get back I don't want
to smell the liquor on your yeah like
the smell of this don't you good old
green cabbage buys everything doesn't it
Lou you must be penny drunk to get
enough to walk in here again you know I
don't think he likes me I don't like you
I don't like anything about you I'm
going to tear you apart for that don't
Kenny please go home get him out of here
hey don't you touch it are you trying to
do here thinking you're not beaver boy
can't go home
isn't that drunken I know it isn't let's
finish our drinks
I think you'd better drink alone
I've still got no use for the guy but
now that he's working and all set we're
bound to run into each other why not
live in peace you really mean that rule
sure I never made a bug holding a grudge
all that swell low why Ken ain't such a
bad guy you got him all wrong all right
he'd be just tickled s to shake hands on
that we'll get together soon you better
go down and open up sure anything you
say just give me the word
your knee Josie any kind of just me
waitin there's a church or your apron
mom oh go ahead get gonna make sure
you're not leaving I won't be you'll
even be late for your own wedding I'll
be worth waiting for Oh many cars you
wolf hey you never smile Mary why did
you win that oh I borrowed it from a
waiter the Wilsons life well i hope the
ceremony don't take too long yeah hello
who get lows for you for me
yeah oh uh huh what now we'll we're on
our way to church I don't know without
fly
hey Ken I had a talk with Lou the other
day yeah how is the old bachelor he
wants that you should be friends Lou and
me that'd be a gruesome twosome nah no
kidding I think it's a good idea for all
of us Mary I'd like it to come on
why are we stopping here for what he's
waiting for us upstairs we'll be late
for the wedding oh it won't take a
minute now do it for me Kenny all you
have to do is to shake hands all right
but only one shake
he's dead
my gun I gave it to the fair probably
get here hope you get three guesses
we got to get out of here what for can
you not then put it on to us come on
you
looks like it's always off on another
Street
I think we lost them
they don't give a better a break
they catch it
let's hit for the river road
they must've got the tank get off the
road
when they get you in the arm what are we
gonna do while they're out the hot we
can't move till next see red
I think we better be moving Kenny where
to your guess is as good as mine
Oh what's the use
left eastbound Freight can you make it
we can't stay here
Kenny wake up wake up
when they're Detroit I got a friend here
that keeps the roadhouse I hope she's
telling members
you can come around
we got to make a jump for it now try and
land on your right side
no did he
yeah alright well now take it easy
see how it is yes man hello Estelle
who's your plane well we just arrived
this morning what's the matter with him
always dude I don't want any trouble
around here maybe it's got the wrong
kind of friend how can I tell Oh buddies
with me auntie yeah that's just what I'm
afraid of well alright let's get him to
bed in here you've got to have a doctor
don't you suppose I can see he's gotta
have a doctor hmm my fav prohibition
you were pretty smart getting me to run
away I'm gonna fix you and then Lou
would you guys you what did you do you
had it all figured out first the whistle
stop now this how much it Lou pay you to
get rid of me all you don't see I was in
on this to you I don't think I know if I
had the strength it
I didn't I couldn't I couldn't I
couldn't
I didn't do it
but
I didn't do it yep
mm-hmm
a friend of mine
ok
you know where it is what's the matter
with him all we lift in the bathtub yeah
step on it doc I'll put you upstairs
well there's no rush I won't be back for
a while not running out on him are you
you know I wouldn't do a thing like that
Estelle you uh need any money no just
luck
where you been all day oh I have to see
a lot of people I like suffering stove
for you hey Mary I can't stand it no
longer married kitty you must know what
happened to him and you gotta tell me
well Molly Kenny's gotten to just about
the worst trouble he's never been in I
knew it Ida feeling all the time what
does the police want here where is Kenny
did he get hurt what did he do married
you didn't do anything he must have
gotten panicky and ran away so it's just
as bad but you must remember Molly Kenny
didn't do it do what do what hold up the
Flamingo room
that wasn't Kenny vittal was talking
about the sum of the B shop chased up to
the forest that was Jimmy Walker I went
to the police they don't believe he did
it they told me it would be so easy to
clear in this we could only get him back
we've gotta find you we got to swing it
Lou they're losing money and everything
google call him on the telephone moves
down enough already go to bed we can't
do anything until morning anyway I know
why kids in this mess everybody's always
been Josephine because he's more of a
man that any of them ever will be I'm
not begging for his mind he won't let
him put him in jail for something he
didn't do a good world
back
Detroit oh he'll be all right I left him
with a friend of mine in a Roadhouse the
o bohemian rue 21
you know who put the finger on it don't
you yeah
Oh Ethan the kind of a day but when he
comes out of it you he's got his head
I'm going back
I'm not going back I just stopped by to
give you the word
you can't beat it now you got it you got
it anymore
but Kenneth my friend I never mention no
wrong you never get him any pleasure
and now you're running out of him when
he needs you
yet love a good guy always buying any
dream always looking after anything
alright
run away
none you know you coward
sure
the place
Oh what she just get low get low hello
take it down yes
lool he framed the whole thing
here
you
certainly gotta hand it to you anyone
else would be flat on his back two days
with that arm was get low he'll be back
where'd he go he didn't say you better
get to bed how can I get a lift ashbury
at six in the morning who's the girl
don't think it's only used Sela this
woman stuff ends up at the kick in the
teeth for everybody you don't know Mary
Mary Betty Jane a man can love anyone
I know
it's always her
I am beautiful
you