you
we interrupt this program for a special
bulletin here now is sandy hill
seismologists at Caltech now report at
least three separate seismic events
tonight each in the northern hemisphere
with earth tremors of magnitude 8.5 and
above the first location is believed to
be in the Thunder Basin area of Wyoming
that's about 200 miles east of Casper so
far we have no reports of casualties the
other two sites in Europe and Asia have
not been identified but stay tuned at
eleven o'clock news for further details
we now resume our regularly scheduled
program
we interrupt this program for a special
report from evening World News in
Washington here now is chief national
affairs correspondent sander van toker
good evening a meteor shower which
appears at this time every year erupted
into a massive cosmic event tonight as
pieces of an enormous asteroid plunged
to earth reports are just coming in but
it appears that at 824 p.m. eastern time
the near-earth asteroid known as 6645
venturi hurtled from space and broke
apart striking the earth had three
separate points around the globe
aftershocks were felt from come jhatka
island in the Aleutians to santiago
chile in all three cases the meteorites
hit deserted rural areas leading wide
impact zones scientists say if any one
of them had struck near an urban center
the results would have been catastrophic
we begin our coverage with correspondent
Pamela Barnes outside mount palomar
observatory in the mountains east of san
diego sandy as this story first broke
the report suggested that three massive
earthquake struck worldwide the initial
shock waves registered within minutes of
each other at Caltech the best image we
have right now is this infrared shot
from a kh-11 reconnaissance satellites
the crater is 2.4 kilometers wide more
than a mile and a half across the red
you see around the rim is a section of
scorched earth from a wildfire that set
the grasslands ablaze at the moment of
impact correspond abri Walker was
vacationing in Wyoming when the meteor
hit she came in with the first fire
crews and we go to her above the crater
I'm told we're having trouble with the
feed from Wyoming so we'll bring bri
walker's report to you as soon as
possible in the meantime we go to Barry
Steinbrenner of affiliate KTM L in
Casper Wyoming with fires from the
meteor crater raging out of control
units from the third Air National Guard
wing were quickly called in to
extinguish the flames more than 10,000
people living west of Thunder Basin are
being evacuated by National Guardsmen
amid fears the fires may spread
and there are numerous reports of power
outages both north and east of Cheyenne
this is Barry Steinbrenner Katie ml
Action News Casper Wyoming I'm told
we've now contacted correspondent Bree
Walker she now brings us pictures of
what is being called impact site alpha
located 60 miles north of Grover's mill
Wyoming Bree can you hear us sandy as
you well know I've covered my share of
disasters the LA riots Hurricane Andrew
last year's floods in the Mississippi
even mount st. Helens when she blew but
nothing I've ever encountered could have
prepared me for this let's give you a
look from the choppers camera mounted
below what you're looking at now is is
the crater itself a massive inferno is
the only way you could describe this in
fact one of the firefighters I talked to
said temperatures we r 1200 degrees
Fahrenheit and above any human being
within miles of this impact would have
been incinerated in seconds and we came
in through the smoke and haze along the
craters east rim the scene of
devastation below was unbelievable with
dozens of state troopers and National
Guardsmen surrounding the impact site
when the asteroid hit it touched off a
massive fire storm that destroys much of
Thunder Basin we're told that chopper
you see down below is flying a team of
hazardous materials specialists from the
Department of Energy we expect that
they'll be checking for a radiation or
any potentially deadly chemicals that
might still be off gas
the site and sandy sandy we're just
getting word that there may have been
some survivors along the Thunder Basin
National Grasslands we're gonna go over
there now for a look the two other
pieces of this gigantic meteorite came
down first in the Gobi Desert of China
along the southern edge of Mongolia and
minutes later in a mountainous area of
the pyrenees about 20 miles south of
lords in southern france now tentatively
known as impact site Bravo Lords was the
site in 1858 of a fable visitation by
the Virgin Mary it's been a mecca for
religious pilgrims ever since but
tonight as correspondent Paul Whittaker
reports the mood there is one of fear
the churches are full here tonight with
religious pilgrims giving thanks but not
because they came to this holy site
because they're alive only hours before
the asteroid fell in the mountains to
the south hundreds of people were still
on the snow-capped peaks after a long
day of recreation and skiing when it did
alternately fake English or name he was
in the elastic to his label car off the
mountain akula just as I heard started
to shake it p olice channel in his
friends and they looked at the sky Huey
fireball streaking across the sky did
yet to miss I mean this woman Silva
chenard also survived but when she got
down she discovered her husband
jean-paul was missing little ladonia dis
omnipony whiskey young Queen um I he I I
took down the cable kind Saul said here
he wanted to ski down for the last one
of the day ironically today was their
third anniversary French rescue teams
are combing the mountainside for skiers
jean-paul chenard a bitter twist to an
already frightening turn of events the
French have an expression plus i chose
Lucilla mem shows
the more things change the more they
stay the same but tonight is the lucky
ones celebrate happy to be alive one
senses these people will never be quite
the same again Paul Whittaker reporting
from Lourdes friends little is known
tonight about the third impact site in
China it is correspondent Denise Wong
reports in Beijing the communist
government has put the country on a
state of alert sandy it's just after ten
fifteen in the morning here in Beijing
since Xinhua the Chinese news agency has
reported that the third asteroid hit at
929 a.m. beijing time it struck at 105
degrees east 45 degrees north along
China's border with Mongolia while
little more has come from the government
here reuters has just released this
aerial photo taken by the French
satellite agency SPO tea from 12 miles
above the earth the crater is almost a
mile and a half across Denise that's
almost identical I repeat identical to
the Wyoming impact site what do you know
about casualties well sandy jinsong is
in a remote area of the gobi desert with
no rail lines and few highways in or out
as a result it may be days before the
full damage from this third impact site
can be assessed we'll be back to you
Denise as soon as there's more I thank
you we switch now to the Johnson Space
Center where Matt Jensen is standing by
sandy the NASA scientists who tracked
these enormous asteroid sometimes refer
to them as killer rocks as such one of
the first questions we asked was how how
could an asteroid of this magnitude have
come so close to earth and not be
detected till impact in July the comet
shoemaker-levy 9 struck the planet
Jupiter in a series of massive impacts
equal enforced to two million hydrogen
bombs these events were monitored
worldwide through the enormous I of the
hubble space telescope orbiting the
earth scientist had known for months
that these events on Jupiter were about
to take place in fact they were actually
able to predict the precise moments of
impact dr. Kurt Loudon was one of the
NASA scientists tracking shoemaker
leading well what about it doctor why
the surprise this time well first off
there are at present some 2,500 near
asteroids magnitude 1 mile and above
that could intersect with the earth if
only I'd had a fight about ten percent
of them and those have all been on
benign trajectories until tonight yes
where you see if an asteroid is coming
directly towards the Earth it's very
difficult to see it until it's literally
on top of us dr. loudness is Santa van
Oakland Washington do I understand you
to say the earth is at risk for more of
these asteroids well not to sound
alarmist but one of those rocks came
down on a big city well well what dr.
let's just say what maker oshima seemed
like a three-alarm fire thank you that
was dr. Kurt Loudon at the Johnson Space
Center in a moment we'll be joined by
dr. Carolyn Jaffe evening world news
science editor but first some rather
startling developments from
correspondent Bri Walker sandy we're
told now that at least three men
perished in the fire storm touched off
by the impact from the meteorite
believed to be sheep ranchers who
releasing grazing lands from the nearby
Thunder Basin National Grasslands what
you are seeing is live and edit it's
hard to believe but only miss camping in
these hills this was lush green grazing
land leased by the government serpents
now it's all just ash and char you can
see the bodies of dead animals scattered
everywhere Bree you should know you
should know your signals breaking up
what what there let's get a closer look
Oh God it's all I know yes the
helicopter is over Thunder Basin
National Grasslands you have the picture
Billy god it's a human that me to go get
her come on Billy I have no idea how
anyone could have survived this but that
is a human being it appears to be
a child it's a child we're moving in
what you're seeing re walker or
cameraman Billy done now you're not
seeing it I hope you will they're moving
in there they are that's breathe moving
in on what appears to be a survivor
movies moving toward the church she's
moving toward the child there she is
cameraman William Dunne behind her it is
definitely a child okay it looks like it
is a little girl cannot tell you what
she is saying you can see she appears
badly burned how she survived never know
apparently we've lost our signal that's
just extraordinary to think that anyone
could have survived so close to that
fire zone it appears the child was
trying to say something something
incomprehensible she obviously was in
shock we'll try to get back with
correspondent Walker to learn more about
that little girl's condition in the
meantime we'll give our affiliates a
chance to break this is Santa von ocher
in Washington
here once again is sander van ochre if
you're just tuning in all of us
witnessed a remarkable rescue tonight
after three fragments Magi a'n't
asteroid fell to Earth causing untold
damage worldwide an evening world news
crew was flying over one of the impact
sites when they saw something moving
correspond abri Walker and cameraman
William Dunne found a survivor a little
girl you still don't know who she is or
what she was saying at this moment our
helicopter is flying her to Mercy
Medical Center in Casper Wyoming and
will get word to you on her condition
just as soon as we have it joining me
now is our science editor dr. Carolyn
Jaffe sandy in the grip of a story like
this it's a reporter's job to hold back
remain dispassionate and yet when you
look in the eyes of that child you can't
help it be moved I understand you
prepared a report on just how powerful
these meteors can be that's right sandy
the philosopher George Santayana once
said that he who forgets history is
destined to repeat it well the three
asteroid fragments that rain down on the
earth tonight weren't the first and most
likely they won't be the last the crater
at Winslow Arizona more than half a mile
across an enormous hole caused by an
iron asteroid just 60 metres wide that
hit more than 50,000 years ago in 1908
an object the same size exploded a few
miles above the ground near tunguska
river in siberia the shockwave with the
force of 15 hydrogen bombs incinerated
millions of acres in an impact area that
would have spread from Maine to the
Carolinas if it had hit the Northeast
but both of these were just BB shots
compared to the big one known now as the
KT event scientists now believe an
object in the order of seven to ten
kilometers wide impacted 65 million
years ago along the Mexican Yucatan
Peninsula a month after impact the
debris from the giant crater covered the
earth in a dust like cloud that blocked
virtually all sunlight billions of
life-forms were killed within weeks and
ultimately the dinosaurs that had ruled
the world for 140 million years perished
and sandy of an asteroid even one half
that size were to hit the earth today
the death rate could easily match that
of the Black Plague which wiped out half
the population in Europe during the
Middle Ages or the question I've got to
put to you is how real is the threat to
the earth today I'm afraid it's quite
real two years ago NASA scientists
calculated that the odds of a person
dying from a near-earth asteroid were
about 1 in 20,000 about the same as
being killed in an airline crash and
that's what they assumed until tonight
you see the dangers increasing why is
that astronomers at NASA's JPL say there
is a 20-percent likelihood that because
of the meteor shower tonight we can
expect more of these Earthbound asteroid
forgive me I apologized but they're
ready now for that report from NASA and
we go to the Johnson Space Center where
correspondent Matthew Jensen is standing
by Matt sandy the men and women who
tracked these giant near-earth objects
have been working nonstop to analyze the
data ever since the first impact at 724
central time we were inside the
Operations Center where we regularly
follow the shuttle flights then just
moments ago some data came in from
NASA's big radio telescope at Goldstone
in the Mojave Desert and all reporters
were asked to move behind this wall of
glass they say a statement is imminent
but right now we're watching and waiting
we'll be back to you Matt but first for
an insight on what may be happening we
go to correspondent Warren only at
Goldstone Warren sandy this enormous 70
meters steerable antenna is part of
NASA's Deep Space Network used to track
spacecraft when a comet or asteroid is
identified by widefield telescopes like
the one at Mount Palomar the data is fed
here and the space debris as they call
these killer rocks is then tracked with
precision now the scientists who work
here are normally rather cool
understated people but about an hour ago
when the data on 6645 venturi was fully
analyzed this marine ella copter made
scheduled for landing a pair of MPs
raced inside they emerged minutes later
with one of the scientists here and they
rushed him aboard the chopper no word
yet on the side of his name or his
position with NASA sources say he was
flown to nearby edwards air force base
for a trip by jet to the Space Center in
Houston weren't what could have been so
important that they couldn't have linked
up with Houston by phone or a
teleconference another good question
with no answer from here sandy one
source says that the scientists
involvement may have something to do
with the asteroids trajectory both
before and after it broke up thank you
very much we've just received an update
from correspondent Denise Wong in
Beijing there are no known casualties
near the third impact site designated
charlie however the impact is said to
have damaged the tinction hydroelectric
dam 40 kilometers to the south power
outages have been reported throughout
most of Liang Shan province and the
Chinese government is requesting
emergency generating equipment and Red
Cross assistance for the estimated 7.5
million people now without electricity
or running water doctor we've just
gotten word on the condition of that
little girl found wandering near the
Wyoming impact site we go now to evening
World News correspondent Bree Walker
standing by at mercy medical center in
Casper the little girl we found at the
scene was badly burned she's an
intensive care now being treated for
exposure and second degree burns doctors
have sedated her and they say she's
resting comfortably meanwhile the Macomb
County Sheriff's Department has set up a
special hotline to try to find out who
the little girl is if you can help
here's the number 1 805 554 818 Bree
Walker evening world news Casper Wyoming
there's more now in the fate of another
victim French skier jean-paul soon are
after combing the area near the second
asteroid impact site French rescue
workers came upon Jean Paul June are
huddled in a snow cave near the base of
Mount vigne men will have an update soon
from correspondent Paul Whittaker in
southern France sandy in this era of
home video where people seem to shoot
everything I
us this was inevitable we've just
received tape from KW BF our affiliate
in newcastle wyoming some 80 miles from
the impact site it purports to show
asteroid fragment alpha streaking across
the sky as it roars towards Thunder
Basin I'm told it was shot by Chris
O'Neill the father of three from
Newcastle the voice you're hearing is
mr. O'Neill's on a reason Oh Tyler you
look great please Gary Joshua gosh
that's an ugly map buddy great come on
doesn't shoot him on it every time to
tell them what you're gonna say what is
that get the kids in the house the tape
was analyzed by the FAA and apparently
that was the Alpha fragment from 6645
venturi we're gonna watch it once more
as it comes into the camera's lens get
the kids in the house sandy were happy
to report that no one was hurt and the
children went on to trick-or-treat with
one incredible story to tell well thank
goodness for that there's new
information on that scientists rushed to
Houston to confer with NASA officials he
is dr. Avram Mandel an astrophysicist at
NASA's Jet Propulsion lab sanding
sources say dr. Mandel visits a Space
Center here in Houston at least once a
month but this is far from a routine
trip in fact we've just learned that
he's flown here not on a conventional
carrier but in the jump seat of an air
force f-16 with a maximum airspeed of
more than 1,400 miles an hour the flight
time from Edwards to Houston should put
dr. Mandel on the ground some 22 minutes
from now sandy correspondent Robert
Moreno has just flown in from Denver and
he is at the edge of impact site alpha
apparently the police there have just
changed the ground rules Robert all the
news crews here have been asked to pull
back from the immediate edge of the
crater the official reason is safety
state police saying that there have been
aftershocks as with the impact but none
of the press
on the ground here was felt anything and
there's been stepped up activity at the
crater by NASA scientists we shot this
video only moments ago sandy as you can
see dozens of investigators from net the
Pentagon have been flown into the site
which is now beginning xem bola sequel
airbase you can see a chopper below
landing carrying additional troops armed
with assault weapons why the government
would need firepower like that at the
site of a meteor impact is anyone's
guess we're told among the personnel
being moved to the site is a team of map
makers from the US Geological Survey in
addition the FAA is now established a
no-fly zone immediately over the crater
they've made it quite clear that anyone
violating this restriction would be
fired upon so if these are the last
pictures you're likely to see for a
while sandy had impact site we're going
to have to cut away a statement is
imminent from the press room at the
Johnson Space Center we go now to
correspondent Matt Jensen after a
virtual blackout since the first impact
jail Powell NASA's director of community
relations is about to speak now
mr. pelvis can you have a have a short
statement there will be no questions at
this time let me just say from the
outset that what we're about to show you
is based on findings that are
preliminary at best she didn't get that
the findings are not I repeat not
definitive data just analyzed by the
space center's computers suggest that
the asteroid 6645 venturi was
approaching the earth on him on a
precise trajectory for impact at 90
degrees north latitude when it broke up
over the polar ice cap the three debris
segments that split apart linens the
following impact points zero degrees
longitude near Lord France the other two
sites were at 105 degrees west and
Wyoming and the same longitude east in
Mongolia here and here all three sites
were located at 45 degrees north
latitude what their that is all we have
at this point broke up over the North
Pole and came down in a perfect pattern
that is correct made no conclusions at
this point well what are the chances
that a random asteroid would hit and
break up and fall with such precision
I'm feeling Rebecca dr. Ephraim and OH
is being flown here on an Air Force
fighter jet what about it well you
couldn't have gotten him down here any
faster if you'd shot him from a cannon
so what's your point well according to
his bio he is a founding member of Seti
does that mean extraterrestrials were
involved like I said at the beginning
there are no questions they'll do
nothing
there you have it sandy back during the
Watergate they would have called that a
non-denial denial this isn't like NASA
ever since the Challenger disaster
they've been one of the most open
agencies in the government that's right
sandy but as soon as I mentioned city
Powell shut right down seddie was
originally a NASA program yes but just
last year their funding was cut most of
the scientists here are members of Seti
and as you know sandy assedi is an
acronym it stands for the search for
extraterrestrial intelligence these are
scientists who are dedicated the belief
that there is life on other planets our
continuing coverage asteroid fire from
the sky will resume after this evening
world news continues its coverage with
dr. Carolyn Jaffe and sander van ochre
for those of you just joining us we're
tracking the story of a large near-earth
asteroid that broke up over in the North
Pole tonight and collided with the earth
that three sites in the United States
Europe and Asia we'll have more on the
damage in a moment but first news on two
of the survivors correspondent Paul
Whittaker begins with this live report
from Lourdes in southern France sandy
rescuers are bringing skier jean-paul
Shannara down from the mountain where
he's been stranded since the asteroid
hit earlier this evening we've been
getting reports that his condition is
critical he's semi-comatose and
suffering from frostbite and
third-degree burns getting him down off
this mountain has been an incredible
task as you can well imagine and and his
wife Sylvia is clearly relieved that
he's been found alive she's going to
accompany him to the burn center and
nice we're gonna follow this story and
we'll get back to you as soon as we know
more this is Paul Whittaker evening
world news reporting from Lourdes we
switched on a mercy medical center in
Casper Wyoming where corresponding abri
Walker is standing by Bree sandy a woman
called here to the hotline just moments
ago and said the little girl is her
daughter
sheriff gave few other details but did
issue a statement confirming the
identity of a little girl as
eight-year-old Kimberly Hastings of
Corrales New Mexico apparently she had
been missing since last Friday no one
knows yet how she got this far north
Corrales is almost 400 miles from where
the asteroid hit doctors say she is
still in critical condition tonight yet
she is one lucky little girl with a
mystery over little Kimberly's identity
cleared up we shift now to a larger
question how is it that an asteroid
could break up and fall to earth with an
almost geometric precision my colleague
science editor dr. Carolyn Jaffe has
found one astronomer who believes he has
the answer you were looking at the sieve
tranquility a vast stretch of craters
created over the centuries when
asteroids pockmarked the lunar surface
this shot of the moon was taken through
a 158 inch cassegrain reflector
telescope the man operating it is dr.
Robert Pearlman a caltech PhD and
astronomer who has personally identified
a half dozen major comets dr. Perlman
what's the significance of tonight's
event well you see in in astronomical
terms tonight's event coming so close to
shoemaker-levy 9 is really unique in
recorded history we understand that you
actually have a photograph of 6645
venturi taken just before it broke up um
this was taken at an elevation of 12,500
miles above the pole now four minutes
later when we attempted to take another
plate the asteroid exploded dr. Perlman
sander van ochre Oh mr. von ocher I
understand you're the co-chair with dr.
Avram Mandel of SETI the search for
extraterrestrial intelligence I am well
doctor what do you make of the
announcement by NASA the asteroid
fragments struck and precise order well
it just confirms what we've been saying
for years I mean with with 200 billion
stellar systems in the Milky Way galaxy
alone the existence of intelligent life
beyond Earth is undeniable perhaps but
why jump to that conclusion in this case
just because the asteroid fragments hit
at the same latitude uh
that's a very very good question let me
see if this yes yes uh can you see this
yes we can alright 6645 venturi
approached the earth on a dead center
trajectory for the North Pole the angles
of the three impact sites a B and C are
exactly 45 degrees huh the odds against
that happening in nature or something
like go tens of the 58th power so what
are you saying I'm saying that what
we've seen tonight is unnatural could it
happen at random not a chance oh thank
you doctor that was astronomer Robert
Pearlman executive director of the
American observatory in Kitt Peak
Arizona we need to point out for our
viewers the danger of speculation at
this point because of the breaking
events tonight we're bringing you
information that's live and unedited
that's right sandy and viewers should
keep that in mind as they watch this
next report from Barry Steinbrenner of
affiliate KTM l in Casper Wyoming a 39
year old crop duster pilot identified as
Dwayne Thomas Haskell was questioned by
local law enforcement and Air Force
officials tonight and later released
after reporting a UFO the alleged
incident occurred as he was landing his
plans some 40 miles west of crash site
alpha here Benson while
I ask you about the UFO mr. Haskell
already said all I'm gonna say party
said I told him a pussy ball I know but
why were you in there so long Gilly much
luck since Haskell refuses to talk we
tape this interview with sheriff's
deputy Hanson Peters the first official
to speak with Haskell he told me that he
was just coming down at around 6 45
after Dustin all day anyway Haskell was
shaken I mean the man was terrified he
said he was just coming in when this
thing appeared on his right hand side
and if all him a few hundred feet as he
landed and then it streaked across his
windshield than the thing took off
straight up like shot at this point the
pilot Haskell is in seclusion we checked
with the FAA to see if there was
anything unusual on radar and they had
no comment this is Barry Steinbrenner
Katie ml Action News Wyoming well we've
just learned that mr. Haskell has sold
his story to the National Enquirer
though he denies it the full purchase
price is believed to be upwards of 100
thousand dollars well was there really
something up there tonight we took our
cameras outside just moments ago to get
reactions do I believe in UFOs
I don't know I like aliens I like that
theory I have no doubt that he's a UFO
um I definitely definitely don't think
it's you have what's he done that to me
is just humans arrogancy to think that
everything can be explained with
scientific data and information I mean
for years we've always assumed that
there's no life on other planets broke
why would I be there I'm not surprised I
don't know i I really don't i don't
believe in aliens all right did you know
the White House has been noticeably
silent in all this the president's out
of the country at the g7 economic summit
and for him that may be a blessing but
there's at least one segment of the
administration willing to comment on the
alleged UFO incident we go now to
national security correspondent Mark
Minetti at the Pentagon here with me
tonight is a deputy undersecretary of
defense for advanced technologies dr.
Norbert Hazleton now doctor with NASA's
announcement of how the asteroid
fragments came in I suppose that talk of
UFOs was inevitable absolutely they all
come out of the woodwork at times like
this i granted the the crop duster
report has yet to be confirmed but what
about the findings of dr. Robert
Pearlman he's a respected scientist look
there's an irresponsible segment of the
scientific community that seems bent on
proving the existence of little green
men and that's fine the problem is is
that the US has been trying to establish
contact for decades to no avail seven
separate unmanned probes have been
launched toward the edge of the galaxy
beaming messages from Earth there have
been more than a thousand US Space
Shuttle own since the 1950s another 2400
by the Russians twelve men landed on the
moon and returned without sightings we
wanted to find them there was nothing
what about the geometric pattern of the
crashes I mean how could something so
precise simply be attributed as a
natural phenomenon well I've got just
one answer for you snowflakes hundreds
of trillions of fall to earth every year
each with an intricate geometric pattern
and no two alike nature is precise in
its randomness and that is the
fascination of it thank you doctor back
to you sandy with these allegations of
UFO involvement we shouldn't forget the
real story here that the more than 2,000
near-earth asteroids still uncharted by
NASA represent a significant threat to
the earth two years ago during a
football game in Peekskill New York fans
observed this meteorite streaked through
the sky where it almost destroyed a
residential neighborhood in 1972 an
alert photographer in the Grand Teton
National Park caught this object as its
streaked across the sky at 33,000 miles
an hour with an estimated weight of 1
million pounds it narrowly missed a
campground with thousands of people and
in 1989 an asteroid half a mile wide
narrowly missed the planet the earth had
been directly in line with that giant
rock only six hours earlier you're
saying that we were only six hours away
from catastrophe that's right I in fact
after that near miss a congressional
report concluded quote had the asteroid
struck the earth it would have caused a
disaster unprecedented in human history
doctors you know government officials
continue to insist that tonight's
asteroid hits were of natural origin
there's a growing segment of the
population who cents something more and
joining us now is Terrance Freeman
author of the recent bestseller
messengers from beyond mr. Freeman
welcome glad to be here sandy I'm mr.
Freeman you've long been a proponent of
the theory that intelligent life has
visited earth before correct oh there's
no question there are ancient cave
drawings showing figures and space
helmets the pyramids the enormous
figures on Easter Island even the circle
at Stonehenge were all built at a time
before we had the technical skills to
create them i'm sorry mr. freeman but
you seem to be denying all human
achievement on the contrary men
women accomplish these things but they
were guided by forces on high it's
axiomatic you can trace the benchmarks
throughout history they come every few
hundred years and we are long overdue
well there are plenty of responsible
scientists who would argue that these
asteroids are long overdue you know
there's a dictum that scientists are
taught to follow it says that when you
are faced with an enigma the best
explanation is usually the simplest and
most logical one in this case asteroids
not a Leo got interrupt you both we've
just received a disturbing report from
correspondent Robert Moreno he's now on
the ground near impact sine alpha in
Wyoming Robert sandy two events in the
last 10 minutes a foot asteroid impact
in a chilling new light first our new
friend about a but doesn't aircraft were
forced to land when an intense radio
signal be coming our navigational system
then after we hit the ground began to
hear that noise in the background a lot
of pulsating hum coming from the
direction of the meteor crater the
decimals increased minute by minute to
the point where you almost have to
scream to be heard Bob can you get any
closer to the right crater can you get
any closer to the rim of the crater
right hi
oh you're the sound of rich as we move
towards the greater it seriously the AP
is reporting that state police units as
far away as Casper Wyoming have been
picking up that same loud hum on their
radios and there's this statement just
in from NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory
quote a persistent audio signal of
unknown origin on the edge of the FM
band is being emitted from the vortex of
the crater unquote in other words that
apparently benign piece of space rock is
charged electronically and sending out
some sort of signal Matt Jensen has more
from Houston officials here at the
Johnson Space Center have confirmed that
similar radio signals have now been
detected emanating from the Bravo and
Charlie impact sites in southern France
and in the Gobi Desert of Mongolia
there's no official word from NASA but
sources here say that the signals could
be natural in origin the result of what
is being described as quote a pulsating
charged ion field which developed during
the parent asteroids flight through the
atmosphere we repeat at this juncture
the word is that the signals are of
natural origin back to you there's some
activity at the FAA's air traffic system
command in Washington DC we go there now
with correspondent Mike Curtis Caroline
I'm standing in the aviation command
center where authorities have now
confirmed that signals emanating from
the asteroid sites have begun to disrupt
commercial air traffic with me now is
facility manager David case David are
you able to shed any light on this
situation for us well traffic has been
disrupted across the country but as you
can see on the screen behind me the
problem is most acute at O'Hare in
Chicago Wayne County Airport in Detroit
and
New York City hubs Newark JFK and
LaGuardia Oh mr. case this is Carolyn
Jaffe 45 degrees north is the very same
parallel where the asteroid fragments
struck yes ma'am you have any comment on
that oh no I'm afraid to have nothing to
say about that at this time if you'll
excuse me I have to get back to work
this is my Curtis reporting live back to
you Caroline thanks Mike in a moment we
hope to have more on those mysterious
radio signals we stress again we don't
yet know the full significance of all
this but one thing is clear an event
that began some ninety five minutes ago
with few human casualties has now grown
into an international air crisis
affecting thousands our continuing
coverage asteroid fire from the sky will
return in a moment here once again our
dr. Carolyn Jaffe and sander van ochre
for those of you just joining us now we
are following an ever-widening crisis
touched off by the impact tonight of a
massive meteor that broke up and fell to
earth radio signals from the three
impact sites are affecting air traffic
worldwide and faa officials are
recommending that people fly tonight
only if it's absolutely necessary we go
now to one of the city's hardest hit
correspondent Ernie Anastos is in New
York they come here to Times Square as
they always do in the world is in
trouble the Cuban Missile Crisis the
Kennedy assassination the war in the gun
all recorded up on that side when you
want to take the pulse meat of the
planet few places can give you a reading
like New York ever since the meteor
shower started several hours ago things
we take for granted have been affected
officials at Newark Airport are
reporting delays of up to three hours
the situation is worse at LaGuardia and
the two runways at JFK have been
completely shut down all new york-bound
air traffic was diverted to Boston and
Hartford as interference from the three
impact sites continues to scramble radar
the only planes moving at LaGuardia were
outgoing flights the resulting gridlock
at airports has produced massive traffic
jams this is the Holland Tunnel tonight
and as you can see traffic backed up
with thousands leaving the city by car
others abandoned their vehicles and
rushed into the tunnel trying to get out
of the city on foot New York City 911
emergency center is overloaded now and
running on backup generators at this
hour the police and fire departments
have called in all off-duty personnel
during the crisis and finally hundreds
of people of all denominations Jam st.
Patrick's Cathedral tonight for a prayer
vigil conducted by Terrans cardinal
O'Connell so sandy here we are at the
foot of the tower where the ball drops
every New Year's Eve and if we get stood
here last December 31st looking ahead to
1994 I assure you that no one would have
predicted this Ernie Anastos evening
World News New York as money markets
open now in Asia there are reports that
trading has been suspended on the Hong
Kong and Tokyo markets scattered power
outages have been reported throughout
Europe and Asia but for the most part
people are staying calm just watching
and waiting to see if the unthinkable is
possible could intelligent life exists
elsewhere outside our solar system and
if so do they have the capability of
visiting earth dr. sandy America is a
country that thrives on conspiracy the
very word cover-up is part of our
national lexicon and for close to five
decades now tens of thousands of
Americans have been convinced of two
things that there is something out there
and the government doesn't want us to
know
the UFO era began in 1947 when a sheep
rancher in Roswell New Mexico found
fragments of what he said was a flying
disk later the Air Force called it a
weather balloon but a secret government
report made public years later described
the recovery of four tiny bodies from
the Roswell crash site and ever since
then there have been hundreds of
reported sightings however the air force
shutdown Project Blue Book concluding
quote no evidence has been found that
any of the UFO reports reflect a threat
to our national security well there's
science fact in their science fiction to
help separate the two we go now to a man
who spent years studying the threat from
these massive meteors arthur c clarke
the noted author of 2001 and dozens of
other books was recently nominated for
the Nobel Peace Prize he joins us now
live from his home in colombo sri lanka
dr. Clark thanks for being with us my
pleasure dr. Clark as far back as 1973
in your book rendezvous with Rama you
wrote about the threat from near-earth
asteroids isn't that right that's
correct there are those who believe
tonight's impacts may have some
connection to extraterrestrials what's
your view well I believe there's plenty
of intelligent life out there in space
actual visitors very unlikely despite
the claims of the UFO enthusiasts why is
that well we've been sending out radio
radar signals for 50 years they know
fill a volume of space hundred
light-years across but we haven't had
any reply well UFO advocates would say
that you have had replies but that the
government just isn't telling and
nelson's I'd give any sorcerer gate
about 24 hours to unravel and apart from
the broadcast transmissions nASA has
made attempts to send messages to any
possible civilization in space using the
Voyager space probes I understand you
have a copy thereof the discs they sent
out on Voyager 2 yes the record like
this carrying pictures and messages from
the peoples of Earth
from the United Nations well if they're
out there and we sent them a beacon so
to speak why wouldn't they answer I'm
afraid is a function of time and space
the distance between advanced
civilizations may be thousands of
light-years so even if they were
traveling the speed of light it might
take them several millennia to get here
but just for the sake of argument say it
was possible all right then the question
is why bother to come here for the earth
to be chosen we must assume ur are the
special not looking at the primitive
state of our civilization I think that's
very conceited so what are you saying
well as a much bigger issue at stake the
need to protect ourselves against rogue
asteroids which are very real and pose a
much bigger threat to earth thank you
dr. Clark that was scientist and author
arthur c clarke speaking to us from sri
lanka we go to lurch france where
correspondent Paul Whittaker has an
update on the condition of jean-paul
June are the French skier who survived
the second impact i'm here at julian
airport near lords france where just
moments ago doctors airlifted jean-paul
chenard to the colon bear Burn Center
and nice we spoke to shun arts wife
Sylvie just moments before the departed
what is your husband's condition please
he he was trying to tell me I don't know
maybe are you survived I just don't know
that jump on it strong and you will not
give up if you double money in the
meantime Air France has suspended all
flights in and out of Rome where these
bizarre radio signals threatened to
paralyze one of Europe's busiest
airports this is Paul Whittaker evening
world news Julian airport near Lords
France Wyoming police have widened the
area of evacuation to some 200 miles
around impact site alpha we're about to
go live to correspondent Robert Moreno
near no I'm sorry we're not going there
were not we just received word of an
unscheduled briefing at the White House
correspondent Mike Curtis is standing by
Mike sandhya formal briefing had been
scheduled for eleven pm tonight to
coincide with local news broadcast but
moments ago the White House press corps
was summoned here for what's being
described as a high priority briefing
thrust secretary Barbara Schiller that
must be her now
yeah earlier tonight following the
impact of three meteor fragments
President Clinton directed NASA to begin
around-the-clock monitoring of all
near-earth asteroids with a potential of
penetrating the atmosphere at
approximately 9 17 p.m. the Air Force's
geodes tracking stations at Skaro New
Mexico Maui Hawaii and Diego Garcia and
the Indian Ocean detected the presence
of what appears to be a second asteroid
at 65 meters or 200 feet in length it is
on a trajectory almost identical to the
path of 6 645 interi the radio telescope
at Arecibo Puerto Rico locked on and
they confirm that the object is heading
toward the earth at an airspeed of
32,000 miles per hour the expected
impact in the area of the polar ice cap
is some five minutes from now at 952
p.m. eastern time the President and
Joint Chiefs of Staff ordered units of
the 388 Fighter Wing from Hill Air Force
Base to you in Utah to a full alert a
pair of f-16 fighters from the 18th
Space Surveillance squadron were ordered
into the air on a defense condition to
status the planes are armed with hawk
optically guided missiles capable of
destroying the asteroid before impact
these missiles are tipped with two
kiloton low-yield nuclear warheads the
the f-16s are expected to be in target
range at approximately ten sixteen is
four minutes from now
Mario yes Barbara how can the president
possibly justify the use of nuclear
weapons uh well a panel from the
National Academy of Sciences met tonight
and their conclusion was that if the
asteroid penetrated the ice cap then the
consequences to the Earth's ecological
balance could be absolutely catastrophic
what about the radio signals jamming air
traffic how will that affect the f-16s
launch uh it is our understanding that
the traffic is affected only long the
45th parallel yes yes Michelle did the
president consult Congress the President
did speak with leaders of both houses
organ see and what about other world
leaders Russian president Boris Yeltsin
and chinese premier deng xiaoping have
been informed both leaders have
expressed their consent as has the
chairman of the UN Security Council let
me just wait let me just tell you one
other thing and that is that the missile
hardware that is to be used is identical
to that which was deployed so
successfully in the Gulf War that's all
there's word just in that the event will
be monitored live at the Johnson Space
Center they're deciding whether or not
to give the media access to the feed but
NASA which has been quite quiet
throughout much of this crisis now seems
to be opening up Matt Jensen's live in
Houston why the sudden turn around sandy
no one here wants to openly break ranks
with the White House or the Pentagon but
there are a number of scientists who are
unsure about the use of nuclear weapons
among them dr. Kurt loudon who we spoke
with earlier dr. what is your concern
simply this with an incoming projectile
moving at 50 times the speed of sound at
close quarters air engagement may be
quite ineffective also the prospect of a
nuclear burst over the ice cap may
produce consequences even more dire for
the Earth's for the Earth's ecology
ladies and gentlemen the point being
dead deal will be monitoring US
Strategic Command off at Air Force Base
Omaha Nebraska we will be listening to
the voice of Air Force launch control
officer major Scotty powers you will be
allowed to stay that was Dale Powell the
director of community relations here for
NASA he has just told the press that we
will be allowed to stay here in the
Operations Center where they will be
monitoring the f-16s so we'll be back
when the missiles are ready to be
launched doctor there's late word from
New York where the United Nations
Security Council has gone into special
session correspondent Ernie Anastos is
outside UN headquarters excuse me could
you tell me why you're here tonight to
let the world
snow that if we are being visited the
asteroids represent some kind of contact
in the world should respond in peace
ambassador what action will the council
take in the event of the unthinkable and
these are indeed extraterrestrials we'll
try and formulate an agenda for
receiving them personally I don't care
if it's asteroids or aliens the most
important thing is to keep our families
safe keep our home safe they come to
Brooklyn will know what to do and I come
down here with my boys from sweet
college vicar maybe we could find us
some slack some heads why so hostile you
kidding me I got a brother flies for the
elephants now these things are messing
with a track we got to stop the two
fighters that took off from Hill Air
Force Base in Utah will be designated
interceptor one and interceptor too we
go back now to Mission Control at the
Johnson Space Center sandy we're at
t-minus 52 seconds and counting gear
you'll be seeing three pictures up on
that active matrix display on the
furthest screen is a feed from the
tracking station at Socorro New Mexico
showing the incoming asteroid the middle
screen will be a graphic showing the two
f-16s and the asteroid in relation to
the North Pole and the image on the far
left is from a camera mounted in the
cockpit of interceptor one thi minus
thirty second that's major Scotty powers
we're fourth launch control office able
warheads manatee confirm lock-on
guidance Roger radar like to clock
prepare to fire then egress lift cleared
to fire in three two one and gate
come on home boys ten seconds to calm
down hey said because I sit I to judge
by you're losing video on India wanna
come to you guys we have a nice it seems
like a water direct hit on the asteroid
that there's to do you cause some
concern here that we've lost my image of
the cockpit you got me say again okay
now Joe do you want in the detail in via
ones in detail what happened to the
image your own no comment today we have
with you the pilot people are watching
here John now we come in hey Louie one
India to do you have to let us know did
we lose pilots on this or not with a
pilot shot down at 10 16 p.m. some four
seconds before the asteroid was
destroyed the transponder signals from
the two f-16s cut off the radar screens
at the same time the sounds we've been
hearing from the craters were heard I
f-16 the to pirates Air Force Captain
Charles Wright Kaiser 32 and Major John
pastor alley 36 both of Hill Air Force
Base are missing and presumed dead the
nuclear submarine USS Houston which
surfaced at the polar ice cap has
reported seeing debris consistent with
the afterburner of an f-16 search teams
are racing to the scene from gander
Newfoundland now to the Pentagon where
the Air Force is about to conduct a
briefing on what they're calling
defensive engagement with the meteor the
post-mortem will be having by deputy
under secretary defence Norbert Hazleton
Lucien Alexander US Air Force chief of
staff let me say at the outset that we
are deeply grieved over the loss of two
outstanding Air Force pilots but they
gave their lives so that we can stand
here tonight and report a near-perfect
mission profile I want to stress that
the warhead loads were extremely low
yield any trace radiation should
dissipate in the atmosphere within a
matter of day radio signals from Wyoming
France and Mongolia have ceased once
again there is every reason to believe
that what the people of the earth
experienced was a natural phenomenon
general Alexander get up general
Alexander how can you attribute this to
natural phenomenon but we all saw the
glow inside the cockpit just a lens
flare at air speeds like that with the
light conditions over the pole the
cockpit array throws off a number of
video spikes okay but wait what are what
about the trajectory all right come on
6645 venturi and the same asteroid the
latest one they were on the identical
path not surprising it's not surprising
it's quite possible they were both part
of the same source asteroid the pieces
simply split in deep space and came in
online only one thing ladies and
gentlemen if there was ever an argument
for jump-starting the anti-missile
defense shield this is it we were lucky
tonight good shooting great hardware the
next time it might be a different story
next
that anti-missile shield the general was
talking about of course is the Star Wars
system a favorite of President Reagan's
put on the Shelf when President Clinton
came into power sandy the air force f-16
jet carrying dr. Avram Mandel has
touched down in Houston he's about to
arrive at the Johnson Space Center in
Houston and Matt Jensen is there life
Matthew yeah Carolyn any minute now that
door behind me will open in a man who
has been something of an enigma and all
this will arrive and speak with her any
comment imagine over there do you have a
comment the action of the Pentagon is
frankly unforgivable there is a force
behind these asteroids that is clearly
intelligent the fact that they chose to
land first in unpopulated areas
demonstrates clearly that they meant us
no harm the radio signal was acting
nearly as a sort of transponder to help
steer the second vehicle in a second
vehicle this is very people the entire
notion of a flying saucer is a fiction
it's a fiction they took the form that
they wanted to take they came in the way
that they chose to come in peace at
first what are you saying doctor but I'm
saying is that we have made a
pre-emptive strike people we have just
declared war
it's clear that dr. Mendel is quite
emotional and as soon as we have details
of his meeting here we'll be back this
is Matt Jensen evening world news at the
Johnson Space Center an evening world
news telephone pole suggested more than
two-thirds of the public now believes
that the asteroids are connected to
alien life-forms it has been a night
filled with charges and counter-charges
but we would be remiss as journalists if
we didn't separate fact from allegation
to the best of anyone's knowledge at
this point the giant meteors that came
to earth tonight were of natural origin
all right um with the radio signals now
silent Robert Moreno is live from faith
Wyoming town less than 50 miles from the
impact site alpha Robert I'm here in
faith an old religious community dating
back to the mid 19th century the town is
well outside the evacuation zone there
were no reported casualties or incidents
after the nearby impact then after the
meteor explosion at the North Pole
Wyoming Edison detected an unusual power
surge here they sent a repair crew out
to inspect and when they got here this
is what they found sandy the streets are
deserted everybody has vanished men
women children cats and dogs and cars
are left in the middle of the streets
and except for the National Guardsmen
there isn't a soul here the town is
completely empty frozen in time the
sidewalks are strewn with trick-or-treat
bags as if the children had simply drop
them as they left
I don't know what else to say it's eerie
air national guard sergeant Leroy digs
told us he was a forward recon in Desert
Storm but that he never saw anything
like this it's like they got swallowed
up we did a full house to house check
for radiation toxic emissions we got
nothing I'm telling you there's no way
to explain this the rescue workers are
even using motion detectors set to pick
up the smallest movement but there's
nothing in a town where 3,000 people
live work and go to school everyone is
simply gone as soon as we have any word
on what happened here we'll be back but
for now this is a ghost town this is
robert murray no faith wyoming a rather
sad note from france Paul Whittaker
reports from outside the coulomb be a
burn center and nice where it's now
morning it's 643 a.m. Greenwich Time
here's sandy and doctors have just sent
word that Jean Paul chenard the French
skier they plucked off the mountain has
died he regained consciousness briefly
before succumbing to injuries sustained
when the asteroid hit and doctors were
able to get a recording of his last
words here fearing that it would be
exploited by the tabloid press his widow
Sylvie has requested that it be released
to the network's
Sean's thing
evening world news continuing coverage
will resume in a moment continuing our
coverage in the aftermath of three
enormous meteor fragments that struck
the earth tonight we go first a
correspondent Mike Curtis at the FAA's
air traffic system command in Washington
DC radio signals from the three impact
sites may have stopped but aviation
authorities report ticket counters jams
at airports nationwide this is
baltimore-washington international most
airlines report delays of up to three
hours as dozens of flights are being
diverted there sandy this is a
continental light market unfortunately
the people at this end of the terminal
are able to get out because these
flights are still taking off authorities
say it may be morning before traffic
returns to normal this is my Curtis at
the aviation command center Washington
DC meanwhile correspondent Warren only
has news on the final words of French
skier jean-paul shuna he's outside
NASA's Goldstone facility in the Mojave
Desert Warren Carolyn in this breaking
story that seems to take a different
turn every minute we have just learned
that the last words of John Paul shoe
narp are being analyzed here by NASA's
computers they're checking for any
similarities between shoe NARS
incomprehensible speech pattern and that
of eight-year-old Kimberly Hastings who
of course is found more than 6,000 miles
away we'll have more on this when we get
it now back to you we have an update now
on little Kimberly Hastings the
eight-year-old girl found wandering near
impact site alpha Bri walkers and mercy
medical center in Casper Wyoming Bri
finally some good news to report as
little Kimberly's condition is upgraded
from critical to stable doctors are
still not able to get through to her
verbally so there's no way to know what
if anything she remembers from the
asteroid crash as to how she got to the
impact site when Donna Hastings her
mother arrived at the hospital does
moments ago she was mobbed by media
the answer to that question how to cure
linkage from wildin daddy I got a court
order keeping away being care about it
this come on Sonya with the phrase
thanks fellas more three days ago she
went off the daycare and you just up and
took her from me but why so far from
home come on we're in here was gonna go
to Canada give it a network right you're
the one who's found Kimber sandy dr.
Robert Pearlman the astronomer we
interviewed earlier has done a computer
analysis of the first three impact sites
he's joining us now live from his lab at
the American Observatory in Kitt Peak
Arizona dr. Perlman can you hear me yes
thanks this is a 3d model of 6 645
venturi as it came to earth it breaks up
an appoint some 6500 miles above 90
degrees north latitude which is the true
north pole you can see the three
fragments falling to their impact sites
designated alpha Bravo and Charlie as i
connect the trajectories you will see
what looks like a diamond shaped pyramid
with its apex above the pole the angles
on impact are exactly 45 degrees forgive
me dr. Perlman but that looks remarkably
like the line drawn you showed us
earlier what's so new about this model
well it will become relevant when I show
you this now this is an exact
reproduction of a pixelated message that
was sent out in 1973 on pioneer 11 here
you will see symbols for man the solar
system the DNA double helix which is the
basic molecule of life and a figure
representing the Pioneer spacecraft
itself you will note the upside-down
pyramid now watch
it's unmistakable the asteroid fragments
represented a symbol they were using the
descent vectors to send us a message
that's an intriguing theory dr. perma
but I'm sure you'll agree it's subject
to debate of course we've invited dr.
Norbert Hazleton to join us he's deputy
under secretary defence and if you don't
mind he has some questions not at all
fire away dr. Hazelton dr. Perlman if I
understand you correctly you're saying
that aliens visited earth tonight and no
no I said it was possible come come you
brought in pioneer you've matched a
couple of triangles what are you saying
well if you put it like that point blank
yes it sounds improbable but consider
what happened tonight the pattern of the
impact sites the radio signals survivors
speaking in tongues an entire town
missing forgive me doctor this isn't
some Trekkie convention there are
millions of people in the world right
now panicking needlessly yes and I would
like to know how much that has to do
with the hair-trigger responses the
Pentagon der if you can show me aliens
in those triangles i'll give you the
second gunman on the grassy knoll listen
you know as well as I do that the
scientific community is divided on this
but you people you people see this as an
opportunity to hotwire Star Wars and it
shouldn't come down to that there is
much more at stake here you're damn
right there is gentlemen I'm sorry but
we've run out of time you've just heard
from astronomer Robert Perlman and
deputy undersecretary of Defense Norbert
Hazleton and now to recap the earth was
rocked tonight by three separate
fragments from an enormous meteor that
landed in the United States Europe and
Asia a second meteor on a direct path
with the first one was shot down by us
planes using nuclear weapons over the
North Pole the two pilots in that
mission perished after radio signals
from the three meteor fragments began
jamming air-traffic World Wide Shut
unrest grow cotton a number
the some speculating that the asteroids
may have a connection to
extraterrestrials that issue has
fractured the scientific community while
the sole survivor of the asteroid impact
in Wyoming an eight-year-old girl
remains hospitalized unable to speak
President Clinton is now jetting back to
Washington aboard Air Force One he
scheduled an address to the nation when
he lands at andrews air force base at 11
16 p.m. eastern time me sandy but dr.
Avram Mandel the SETI scientists rush to
the Johnson Space Center has just
emerged from a meeting with NASA
officials he's talking with reporters
right now and we pick up his comments in
progress no no I'm way past that why do
this here because I'm no longer speaking
as a staff scientist at NASA effective
at nine-thirty 2 p.m. central time I
resigned my position as a concerned
astronomer and most importantly as a
human being I can no longer associate
myself with the government's handling of
this ongoing crisis look we were given a
gift tonight people we had a visitation
they came in peace and we answered them
with two thousand tons of TNT at the end
of a nuclear warhead yeah what if this
had been Jesus or Buddha or Mohammad or
or a profit of old I mean haven't we
learned anything from history but we all
know that we have the most violent
planet in the galaxy but why in god's
name why did we have to take it to them
look dr. e you're upset what do we do
this to run hello I I wanted to do this
the right way to deal that's why I flew
out here I tried to plead with these
people have didn't do any good dr.
Mendel you mentioned before that this is
an ongoing crisis what did you mean by
that you don't know no you mean they
haven't told you anything look the
doctor is clearly disturbed hola be
don't you do this this is not respond
saying I am responsible to myself now
I'm so sorry I'm so so sorry in
approximately 10 32 p.m. eastern time
the radio telescope hit tongue at
Goldstone Mojave received a signal Air
Force tracking stations locked on as
well there are three asteroids of a
magnitude of two miles each and above
that are on a trajectory with earth they
are headed directly toward three of the
earth's most populous cities Beijing in
the People's Republic of China Moscow as
well as Washington DC what our cities
doctor I don't know I can only guess and
that is that they are the capitals of
the only three nations on this planet
who have a first-strike nuclear threat
the the asteroids are expected to hit
sometime around 1052 p.m. eastern time
that's it's nine minutes from now we
declared war against them people we did
it and now they've just decided to
respond so may God have mercy on us all
our coverage of this continuing crisis
will resume after this from now on we'll
stay on the air continuously until this
crisis is over as we count down now to
the moment of impact the mayors of the
nation's ten largest cities have all
imposed curfews looting is widespread
amid fears of food shortages as the
crisis deepens meanwhile the radio
signals that all three impact sites have
resumed this time they're affecting not
only commercial air traffic but radio
and TV signals across the globe in many
countries telephone service is out the
reaction in this country has been panic
hopefully everything's gonna be okay but
I just don't know what I'm gonna do when
it happens well as a as of right now I'm
not really frightened because I mean I
really I haven't seen him and I mean
they haven't really come after me but
they start coming after me yeah we'll be
hungry scared I gotta get out of here my
family's waiting for me now it ben de
ligar if idea I'm not a religious person
I haven't been to mass in years but I
came tonight sandy there are reports of
panic worldwide as fears begin to mount
as you can see here the French police
are having no success in trying to calm
the people who are rioting while in
Washington and other cities around the
world the fear is being expressed in
candlelight vigils and other peaceful
gatherings no one seems to know what to
do or where to go no place is safe as we
realize the magnitude of this crisis
people take to the streets in different
ways but one thing is clear racial and
national boundaries are disappearing as
the world reacts to a greater danger the
best advice anyone can give at this
point is to get inside a building move
to the basement and stay there in the
event broadcast stations lose power turn
to the emergency broadcast network at am
640 or FM 10 2.4 we begin with a series
of reports from evening World News
correspondence
his paul collingwood in moscow it's 640
in the morning he ran red square is
completely deserted even during the
darkest days of the Cold War when the US
nuclear arsenal was aimed at this city
you never felt such palpable fear this
is not a religious country but this
morning the churches and synagogues are
filled this is Michael Curtis reporting
from Washington a city normally
associated with great power but tonight
all anybody really feels is powerless
some people have gone home to be with
their families some are in transit
trying to get out of this city but a
group of people have gathered here to be
together at the feet of a great man who
once saved this Union perhaps in the
hope that he might somehow do it again
what would you do if you were told you
only have seven minutes to live or maybe
it's just a strange attraction we have
for witnessing natural disasters tidal
waves great fires or this asteroids
falling to earth whatever the reason is
all we can really do is wait and watch
and pray this is Denise Wong reporting
in Beijing where an eerie calm has set
in after hours of fierce fighting
between riot police and angry student
demonstrators now people simply want to
be with their families and we can
understand why all services a reported
shut down hospitals are overflowing
there's word of a massive fire raging
through Shanghai with no apparatus or
firefighters to stop it if this is your
last day on earth you want to spend it
with the people you love Denise Wong
evening world news in beige
you know Carolyn a time like this you
can't help but feel for our
correspondence elsewhere you know Denise
Wong has got a husband and two children
up in San Francisco yes the threat is
imminent of course to the cities that
we've just mentioned but if the
asteroids hit Earth as feared the entire
planet will be impacted Matt Jensen is
standing by as he has been all night at
the Johnson Space Center Matthew Carolyn
as you can see behind me many the
scientists here at the Operations Center
have gone home to be with their families
of the few that remain dr. Kirk loudoun
doctor we've been told that if even one
of these asteroids impacts as expected
the effect worldwide could be
apocalyptic could you elaborate yeah
just like the KT event 65 million years
ago if an asteroid one mile or larger
strikes on land it'll throw up enough to
breed to create what amounts to a
nuclear winter yeah we can see the
screens behind us you can see the three
asteroids as they proceed on target they
are now some 11,000 miles from Earth but
closing fast with five minutes and
Counting until the asteroids break the
Earth's atmosphere late word from the
Pentagon that there's a plan in place to
meet them head-on general Lucian
Alexander is Brittany reporting Air
Force Space Command and the US Navy are
preparing to counter the threat of
nuclear weapons directed by the most
advanced guidance system each carrying
10 independently targetable re-entry
vehicles they'll be launched from the
Trident submarine USS Ohio in the north
sea and from fe Warren Air Force Base in
cheyenne wyoming the Soviets and the
Chinese have agreed not to respond for
fear of an all-out nuclear exchange this
peacekeeper and Trident d5 devices will
hit their targets and take them out with
surgical precision and minimum
collateral damage
can nuclear missiles be against UFOs we
still have no definitive proof of alien
life forms there's every likelihood that
these asteroids are the result of a
meteor shower of massive proportions the
point is either we cut and run and we
stand it right we're now DEFCON 1
t-minus three minutes encounter no
Carolyn in the midst of a story like
this when you're talking about millions
of lives being affected I can't help but
think of one Kimberly Hastings in
Wyoming we go now to Bree Walker at
mercy medical center in Wyoming with all
the hope in this room just moments ago I
don't quite know how to say this shortly
after we spoke to you little Kimberly
Hastings collapsed and went into cardiac
arrest a crash team rushed ended but
they at 851 p.m. little Kimberly
Hastings passed away and whatever it is
that she knew about that asteroid went
with her we are now less than three
minutes from the first impact and the
people's republic god I just want to say
something to uh Lindsay my little girl
she's six she had it and she had a tooth
out last week the tooth fairy brought
her a silver dollar honey I want you to
know that mommy loves you very much I
went you and Daddy you hold each other
real real tight I know how much I love
you both I'm just gonna finish up here
and we're all gonna be together real
soon Carolyn you don't have to stay here
you don't let some
let's just see it through you sure we're
now less than two minutes before the Air
Force launches its peacekeeper missiles
will be live via satellite with
correspondent Denise Wong in Beijing
paul collingwood in Moscow and Mike
Curtis here in the nation's capital and
now for the launch phase we go to Matt
Jensen at the Johnson Space Center sandy
the radio signals at you here and that
are coming through our headsets are
coming off the feed from impact site
alpha the sound is ear piercing I'm
gonna have to do the rest of your pear
phone it's okay mapping we can hear you
now the asteroids have now been being
designated x-ray Yankee and Zulu that's
xyc in a few seconds you'll be able to
see them hurtling down towards Earth at
four to five thousand miles an hour the
missile exchange will be monitored by
tracking stations in Maui Socorro and in
Diego Garcia attention all stations
status green alert that voice you're
hearing these amateur scouting Ohioans
the launch control on combat crew
initiate execute launch command on my
mark in 10 seconds his voice is from the
US strategic command offutt air force
base in Omaha arrived four three two one
launcher closure open missile away you
loose ones Beijing is target one impact
respected at 40 seconds per mile zero
interference is too strong do you see
anything at all oh you're breaking up
sandy
I'm going to have to take a header off I
think you re good I saw anything see and
yet I can't tell you I'm impact / China
t minus 15 with wealthy audio that I
assume that's a pic of her husband
graylen and her two children Keisha and
Mallory I said before they all live in
san francisc Denise please hold on where
he can 21 we've lost contact with Denise
Wang in Beijing Matt Jensen can you tell
us the status from where you are well by
the cheering behind me i'm sure you can
tell we've had total incineration on
x-ray but it is far from over yet
interest we believe the first asteroid
has been destroyed we go now to Paul
Collingwood in Moscow Paul what should
look like where you are nothing so far
SEC has done the sick piercing signal in
my headset sandy for the record I'm a
four-year correspondent we're all proud
of you Paul and your collar and tomorrow
would have been my 28th birthday well I
love you mom and dad 65
three two one sandy what happened this
should have impacted by now Paul it
looks like we've destroyed truly I am
390 engine hi Curtis of the link is a
little sandy it's really it's impossible
to see anything tonight it's a it's so
overcast all night long impact over
Washington into my god fortnight now
network now I see it it's so bright and
it's coming in fast big guy got the
counter it's it's getting too close
sandy why aren't they shooting at this
thing now
how does it feel out there it's this
fabulous it's like the day the wall went
down yeah happy birthday Paul happy
birthday oh thank you soon Thank You
Denise we're gonna go home I'd say
you've earned it thanks for a job well
done thank you very much have a very
good day have a good day reaction from
around the world is typical of this live
footage we're seeing right now
well before we sign off correspondent
Warren only has some information for us
from Goldstone sandy the scientists here
have deciphered the speech patterns at
Kimberley Hastings and John Paul June
are here's the feed now 147 member
states we committed that's the recorded
message we sent up in Voyager to Sandy
there's a report from the johnson space
center Matt Jensen is there with a comes
to us live mad Carolyn as you can see
the elation in the room behind me has
stopped people cheering and celebrating
and then it was if a balloon would burst
quiet permeated the room and nobody
seems to be giving any indication why
now what is it now what do you see just
tell him tell us what you're seeing Matt
the count what sick and wonder well
what's the Tama man's name I'm told his
name is Patrick Patrick Patrick just
move the camera to the screen show us
what you're seeing on the screen Patrick
you read it over show us what's on this
track trajectories no there's too many
there's too many to calculate now look
for a success was to transport got me
taking friends mrs. you coming Elizabeth
do you copy the vector code 95 Mexico
signals used in Mexico City respond 7
these change frequencies and copy mexico
city now is teacher in caracas london do
you read me this is negative london if
you're there please add a guru anchorage
reports judo is rev respir our spice
fishing Russia is astonishing I'm
capitulation is left our support any
mirror sir you can hear the sound of my
league of nations before russia car oh
please come obviously we'll stay on as
long as we can and will keep feeding you
the signal from the Johnson Space Center
as long as possible with all the
missiles in all the power I could only
leave you with this thought from
Shakespeare before dear Brutus lot in
your stories selves or just came in at
Edinburgh is bendable iterated weird
capital she hasn't run in Washington
this is you like Washington I you read
through door buzzed washington this is
Houston control please come in come in
Washington this is Houston control
Washington come in
you
now