Mosfilm Studio
START Creative Association
Leonid FILATOV
in
ZERO TOWN
Starring
Oleg BASILASHVILI
Vladimir MENSHOV
Armen JIGARKHANYAn
Evgeny EVSTIGNEEV
Alexei ZHARKOV
Pyotr SCHERBAKOV
E.Arzhanik, T.Khvostikova,
Yu.Sherstnev
Can you take me to the hotel?
You should have a pass here
for Mr. Varakin.
No? That‘s not possible
I just ordered it.
There's no pass here for you.
Dammit.
This is Varakin. I'm at the
check-point but there's no pass.
I explained it all half an hour ago.
Varakin,
from the Moscow engineering works.
I've come to talk
about the air conditioners
you supply us with.
OK.
I'll wait.
What kind of lousy place is this?
Mr. Varakin, please go through.
Hello.
Ninochka! Order this right away.
I've settled it with the boss.
What's your business?
What's your business here?
I'm from the Moscow
engineering works.
It's about the air conditioners.
I'll tell him you're here.
The man from the Moscow
engineering works is here.
- Send him in.
- Go on in.
What can I do for you?
Well, what do you want?
I'm from
the Moscow engineering works.
Our director called you
about the air conditioners
you supply us with.
We supply you with air
conditioners?
Yes, for 15 years now.
Excellent. What else do you want?
We want you to change
the back panel.
What for?
Well, we're no longer
financially subsidized
Our technology's changed
and your panel doesn't fit.
We called you, sent schematics
and you asked us
to send someone down
to figure this out and so I came.
We'll get this sorted out.
Just let me find the chief engineer.
Nina!
Where's she gone to?
Excuse me,
your secretary--
She's sitting there stark naked.
- What?
- You know, undressed.
- How d'you mean?
- She's got no clothes on.
She's sitting and typing
like it was perfectly natural.
Oh yeah?
The Party Executive Committee called.
They want you to call them back.
I've got someone here!
- So she's naked?
- See for yourself.
Well, so she is.
So, where were we? Ah, yes,
the chief engineer...
Put me through
to the chief engineer.
- We don't have one.
- What happened to him?
He died 8 months ago.
You don't say!
That's real bad luck!
What did he die of??
He drowned in the river.
This complicates
your business a bit.
Tell you what...
Come back
in two weeks.
I'll get together
with the chief engineer,
and we'll sort things out
in no time.
ENGINEERING WORKS
Yes, I did put a call through.
Natasha! I got all settled in.
Everything's OK.
No, I'm not ill, why?
There's nothing wrong with my voice.
I'm leaving today.
No, I haven't.
I don’t understand it myself.
It’s crazy.
I'll tell you when I get there.
It's very funny.
I'm leaving today. See you.
Dammit.
I'll order without the menu.
I'm in a hurry.
Whatever you have for starters,
And what kind of soup do you have?
We’ve got solyanka today.
And I'll take some kind of meat,
not too fatty.
- A ground beef patty.
- OK.
Mineral water and tea.
- And for dessert?
- Nothing.
- Our cakes are fresh.
- No, thanks.
We're not taking orders,
this is our break.
Your tea and dessert.
I didn't order dessert.
Don't worry.
It's a present from the chef.
- What is it?
- Cake.
Bon appetit.
Our chef baked it specially for you.
He likes the look of you.
There he is is peeking out
from the kitchen.
It happens sometimes,
a person just takes
a liking to another person.
- Give me the check.
- At least taste it.
Bring me the check.
Just a little bit,
or else the chef will kill himself.
Stop talking nonsense!
So you weren't acquainted
with Nikolaev?
No.
You'd never met before?
Never. I've never been
in your town before.
I’ve got an evening train.
I just went in to eat.
That’s all there is to it.
The waiter did warn you
that Nikolaev
might kill himself
if you didn't try his cake?
Yes, but didn’t take it seriously.
It was all so crazy.
It's absurd.
His work-mates describe Nikolaev
as a restrained,
well-balanced personality
an active member
of the teetotalers' association.
If I'd known it would turn out like
this, I'd have eaten his lousy cake.
Well, OK. Sign here
and you can go.
I have read the above
and it is a true record of my words.
We'll call you if we need you.
One sleeper to Moscow.
Tickets are all gone.
- A seat then.
- There's nothing at all.
- Where's the station-master?
- He won't help you.
Where to?
The nearest railway station.
I can't go any further.
No entry.
- Want me to turn round?
- Is it far to the station?
A kilometre and a half.
Then I'll walk.
Thanks.
- Hello.
- Good evening.
Can you tell me where
the railway station is, please?
There isn't one.
This is our regional museum.
They told me there was
a station near here.
Never has been.
This is a nature reserve.
Would you like
to see the museum?
- How can I get back to town?
- You can't.
No buses at this time.
Then how do get around?
I live here beside the museum.
Come to think of it,
not far from here lives a lady
who sometimes drives
into town in the evening.
I can find out
if she's going in today.
Yes, please.
Anna, it's me.
Are you going to town today?
I've got a nice young man here.
Would you take him along?
Thanks! It's all settled.
She'll pick you up in an hour.
Meantime, why not look round?
30 kopecks a ticket.
Where are we going?
The exhibit starts 28 meters
below ground level.
Did they dig the shaft
especially for the museum?
No. They used to mine coal
here in the last century.
They came across an ancient
burial site while they were digging.
The merchant Butov,
a great lover of archaeology,
bought up all the land
in the area to continue excavations.
That's how the museum
came to be founded.
This way, please...
Where’s the light?
The most ancient relics found
in our town
go back to the first fall of Troy.
This sarcophagus contains the remains
of the Trojan king Dardanus.
Wait! How did the Trojans get here?
Professor Rottenberg has proved
that after Troy fell,
some of the Trojans went north
and founded
the first settlement here.
Here's an inscription.
'Dardanus, son of Hellen,
grandson of Priam'.
The same inscription is
on the shield found by Butov
beside the sarcophagus.
Let's go on.
The 2nd cohort of the 14th
double legion of Mars.
- Wait! Are these Romans?
- Correct.
Their disappearance without a trace
en route from Britain
to the Caucasus
was reported to Nero
by the legion's commander.
The cohort's re mains
were discovered by Butov
while they were digging
the second shaft.
Nonsense, the Romans were
never on Soviet territory.
The sculptural portraits
were created
using Professor Gerasimov's method.
Let's continue with the exhibits.
The bed of Atilla,
on which the leader of the Huns
violated the queen of
the West Goth in front of his horde.
Professor Rottenberg found
traces of semen on it,
from which he derived
a genetic fingerprint.
He fed the data into a computer
and he got an absolutely
accurate likeness of Attila.
Our town's
first rock'n roll dancers.
Smorodinov, Secretary of the town's
Young Communist League,
who had them expelled from the YCL.
The pistol with which Urusov
shot the False Dimitry II.
And here's the impostor's head.
How'd the head get here?
When the pretender Dimitry
was killed,
Marina Mniszek
had her husband's head embalmed.
Marina Mniszek's lover,
the Ataman Zarucki,
lost the head at cards
to the Uhlan Beletsky,
who was killed
during the siege of the Kremlin,
and the head went to Fyodor Kuzmin,
a soldier from our town.
But he's not here. Let's go on.
Here you see
the Kievan Prince Vladimir
at the moment
of Russia's acceptance
of Christianity.
The famous revolutionary Petrov,
from our town,
a member of the 'Black Repartition'
group
who was betrayed
to the Tsarist secret police
by the head of the combatant
Socialist Revolutionaries,
the stool-pigeon Azef.
Azef's mistress, Lady N.,
an actress at the 'Cafe Chantant'.
The monk Julian,
ambassador and spy in Russia
for the Hungarian king Bela IV.
Another representative
of our town, Burtsev,
superintendent of the hotel
'Florence' in Moscow.
In 1918 the anarchists
had a conference there.
This is Burtsev.
Here he is going in the door.
The Ataman Makhno himself
took part in the conference.
Here he is talking with the
commander of the
Jewish Army battery,
Abraham Schneider.
Gavriusha, the commander
of the Black Hundreds,
who said he would hack down
his own mother and father
if Makhno ordered it.
Our town's first Stakhanovite
hero, Yegor Bykov.
This apartment belonged
to the railway worker Kuridze.
Joseph Stalin spent a night here
in November 1904
when he escaped from exile.
Next morning he proposed a toast:
'Soon comes the dawn,
soon the sun will rise,
This sun will shine for us'.
Zinovi Peshkov, Gorky's adopted son,
natural brother of Sverdlov,
Ambassador to China, in the 30's.
And who's this?
That is the president
of our writers' organization,
Chugunov.
On March 10, 1938
his first poem was printed:
'Sentence of the People.'
'Bayonets of the guard,
We're in the October Hall.
'The judge's bench,
the prosecutor's steely phrase:
'So, how much did you take
from the Germans,
'To betray your homeland yet again?
'The malice in their eyes
flickered and faded,
'The accused did not look
at the hall...
'Yes, we added glass into butter,
'Yes, I ordered
Gorky's assassination...
'I took money for spying
in the Reichswehr.
'Terror, sabotage,
betrayal, venom...
'They sit there like captive beasts,
reciting in turn:
'Chernov, Yagoda,
Rosengoltz, Bukharin.
'The human features
fade away
'And monstrous, devilish mugs
'You come to see
before you.'
In 1949 Chugunov
was accused of cosmopolitanism
for his novel
'Kuchelbecker's Fetters'.
In 1956 he was rehabilitated.
The first chairman
of our Revolutionary Committee,
Mikhail Zverev, who took part
in the liquidation
of the imperial family.
Here he is at a meeting
with construction workers
from the White Sea-Baltic Canal
and their supervisors.
He's the one with the accordion
on the left
of the camps' political
police chief, Berman.
At this meeting
the deputy head
of the OGPU Yagoda said:
'The OGPU labor camps
are pioneers
'in the cultural assimilation
of remote regions'.
Another native of our town,
Academician Fomin.
In 1934 he discussed
with Khrushchev and Kaganovich
a project to erect
a magnificent Commissariat
of the Heavy-Metal Industry
on Red Square.
Mayor Sokolov
was also born in our town.
While providing air-cover
to an Anglo-American convoy in 1942
he engaged ten German planes
in combat. He shot down six of them,
and though fatally wounded,
he landed his own fighter safely.
Antonina Petukhova,
known as 'The monkey',
the first citizen of our town,
to be arrested in 1957
at the youth festival in Moscow
for interacting with foreigners.
'Dreams', a composition
by our sculptor, Troitsky.
Where's Anna?
She's usually very punctual.
Maybe she's changed her mind?
Well, you can sleep here.
Where?
Our electrician lives close by.
He has a large house.
Maybe I could leave right now?
You won't get anywhere now,
it's 15 kilometres to the road.
Come on, I'll arrange
a bed for the night.
Please help yourself.
How'd you end up in these parts?
You a tourist?
No.
Help yourself.
I asked the taxi driver
for the nearest railway station.
That's in Perebrodino
and this is Perebrodovo,
so the taxi-drivers get confused.
Was the taxi driver young?
- Yes.
- I see.
Oh, Lady of the House! I think
the potatoes are probably burnt.
- How about a glass of vodka?
- No, thanks, I don't drink.
Homebrew!
You'll never leave our town.
What?
You'll never leave.
You'll die in 2015
and they'll bury you
in the town cemetery.
I can see the gravestone
with the words:
Alexei Varakin:
1945-2015.
To our beloved father
from his daughters Julia, Natasha,
Tamara, Zinaida.
Special brew.
What are you doing here?
Get off to bed!
Ten o'clock,
and he's still hanging around!
- Good night.
Don't forget to brush your teeth.
To our meeting here.
Excuse me,
but where can I lie down?
- You sleepy already?
- I'm sorry, I'm very tired.
But you haven't eaten anything yet.
Thanks, but I'm not hungry,
just very tired.
I'll show you the way.
Here's a towel.
Make yourself comfortable.
- Who's that?
- I don't know.
When we bought the house,
Victor found it in the attic
and hung it up
- Good night.
Excuse me. Someone's come for you.
Hello, my name's Anna.
I couldn't get to the museum,
I had a flat tire.
I can take you
to town now if you like.
Could you take me to Perebrodino?
- To the railway station?
- I have to get to Moscow.
There are two Moscow trains
that stop at Perebrodino.
Great.
Are you upset about something?
Upset? Not really. More surprised.
Has anyone ever foretold
your future?
No.
But I have read
that in the 16th century
Nostradamus foretold
the rise of Hitler.
Someone's following us.
They want us to stop.
Mr. Varakin?
Please get into the car.
We've got new information,
we have to check something out.
Do you recognize this person?
- That's me.
- That's correct.
This photograph
was found among the papers
of the deceased chef Nikolaev.
How did he get it?
That's what we'd like to know.
You said you didn't know him.
I didn't.
Then how do you explain this?
'To my dear father from Makhmud'.
What?
It appears you're Makhmud,
the chef's son.
This is crazy. What son?
What Makhmud?
Expert examination indicates
that your signature
and the one on the photo
are identical.
There's some misunderstanding.
I never laid eyes
on that chef before.
My father is
Mikhail Alekseevich Varakin.
He's never been a chef,
he's an engineer.
How do we explain that a photo
with an inscription
in your writing was
in the possession of Nikolaev?
I don't know.
Perhaps you met the chef
some time or other?
I swear I never met him before.
I have to ask you not
to leave the area.
What? But it's all a mistake!
Don't worry, we'll sort it all out.
I have to get to Moscow.
You must sign a declaration that
you will not leave this town.
You can appeal to the public
prosecutor if you wish.
- Alexei Varakin?
- Yes.
This is the town prosecutor here.
Come down, please,
we have a car waiting for you.
Hello, Alexei.
I know what it is you wanted
to see me about.
A strange business.
It's a misunderstanding.
I've nothing at all to do with that
business. I just happened to be there.
I have to get to Moscow. Urgently.
Alexei!
Were you never tempted
to commit a crime?
- What for?
- Just for...
...the sake of doing
something criminal.
You know, steal a stereo,
attack a policeman.
Why should I attack a policeman?
The policeman's just an example,
that's all.
Imagine,
I, the public prosecutor here,
dream of committing a crime.
I spend all my life
punishing criminals,
but in my heart I really envy them.
A paradox
worthy of the novelist's pen.
I'd love to do
something absolutely crazy,
that no one would ever expect of me.
But let's get back
to the business in hand.
You want me to allow you
to go back to Moscow?
Yes.
Don't you think
you might have been a witness,
not of a suicide, but of a murder?
- What?
- Yes, a murder.
But I saw him shoot himself.
That's just it, you didn't see that.
Remember how it happened.
Your tea and dessert.
I didn't order any dessert.
Don't worry.
It's a present from the chef.
- What is it?
- Cake.
Stop. Why the jazz?
I don't know.
Probably they were rehearsing.
There's never been
any jazz in that restaurant.
But they did play.
Maybe they were only pretending
to play, miming to a record?
But why?
So you wouldn't hear the shot,
from the kitchen.
The first shot in this tale.
I don't understand.
Even if someone killed Nikolaev,
why set up this whole farce?
I'm not saying someone did kill him,
but it's possible.
The whole business
looks absurd enough
to make you suspect
a premeditated murder.
But maybe that's
what they were counting on.
They had to convince you,
a bystander,
that you had witnessed a suicide.
And they did.
I have to get to Moscow.
You evidently fail to appreciate
the seriousness
of the Nikolaev case.
It affects the interests
of the State.
Since the times
of the Mongol invasion
the main idea uniting us,
which inspired generations
of our forebears,
is the idea of statehood.
A great and mighty state
is the ideal
for which the Russian
is willing to suffer,
to bear any deprivation.
Ready, if need be, to give his life.
This is an irrational idea,
not the pragmatic European striving
to extract the maximum
of personal profit.
It's the idea
of the great Russian spirit,
of which your own individuality,
and mine,
is only a small subordinate part,
but which repays us both
a hundred times over.
This feeling of belonging
to a great organism
inspires our spirits
with a feeling of strength
and immortality.
The West has always striven
to discredit our idea of statehood.
But the greatest danger lies
not in the West,
but in our own selves.
We grasp at all these incessant
at fashionable Western ideas,
seduced by their obvious
rationality and practicality,
not realizing
that just these qualities
give them a fatal power over us.
But never mind,
in the end our own idea
always comes out on top.
Our revolutions have all finally led
not to the destruction,
but to the strengthening,
the reinforcement of the State.
They always will.
But not many people realize
that the present moment
is one of the most critical
in our entire history.
And the case of chef Nikolaev,
which appears so trivial
at first glance,
has a profound significance.
So there's no way
you can leave town.
What do I have to do?
Nothing.
Just one request:
if anyone should ask,
don't deny that you are
the chef's son, Makhmud.
Varakin?
How'd you like a bit of fun?
What?
My friend and I
are just dying of boredom,
I thought you might like
a bit of fun.
Who are you?
We'll cook the dumplings,
you bring the wine.
Leave me alone!
Please yourself.
Who is it?
I’m here with a request…
The writer Chugunov
wants to see you.
What for?
It's very important for you,
let's go.
I'm not going anywhere.
Please come.
It's has to do
with your father Nikolaev.
- Alexei Mikhailovich?
- Yes.
Pleased to meet you. Chugunov.
Please come in.
You witnessed the suicide
of the chef Nikolaev.
The point is that Nikolaev
was our town's first rock'n roller.
It all happened
in the Zhdanov House of Culture
on the 18th of May 1957.
Look.
It was It was a typical party
for youth.
You know, young people dancing
and enjoying themselves.
We still don't know
how Nikolaev came to be there.
He was already 27,
a senior lieutenant in the police.
But he was there.
Look, there's Nikolaev in the hall.
See what happens now.
The waltz breaks off
and rock'n'roll starts up.
They are confused.
You can't tell
who's changed the music.
Now watch Nikolaev.
This was a great scandal.
The biggest since the revolt
of the the Social Revolutionaries.
Now look at this young man.
The Secretary of our Young Communist
League, Nikolai Smorodinov.
The next day he expelled
the dancers from the YCL.
Nikolaev was sacked from the police,
and the girl Shulakova was
thrown out of the medical school.
She took acetic acid.
They saved her life,
but her vocal chords were burnt.
She could never speak again.
Nikolaev got a job
in the restaurant.
He was resigned and calm.
But I knew that sooner or later
he's try something and I wasn't mistaken.
Only he could turn his own death
into such a circus.
You know, the prosecutor thinks
that Nikolaev was murdered.
And do you know that our prosecutor
is that same Smorodinov
who expelled Shulakova
and Nikolaev from the YCL.
This is all very interesting but...
What's it got to do with me?
Well, today is the opening
Of our town’s Nikolaev rock'n roll club.
I'd like you
to speak at the opening ceremony.
Me?
Why me?
You're Nikolaev's son.
Okay, let's get up on stage,
it's time to begin.
Thank you for coming.
Hello, Nikolai Ivanovich.
Well, are you going to speak?
What can I do?
This is all so crazy.
What can I say
about a man I've never met.
Say what they usually say
in such cases:
He was a good man,
and all that stuff.
But I'm supposed to talk
as if he was my father.
Alexei Mikhailovich,
we're waiting for you!
Dear friends! Today our town sees
the opening of a rock'n roll club!
Yet another great victory
for democracy!
Through the periods
of Stalinism, voluntarism,
subjectivism and stagnation,
we have preserved
the passionate desire to dance
like we want to.
The first to dance rock'n roll
in our town
was the chef Nikolaev.
The first always has it rough.
But then comes the second,
in the unstoppable process
of historical logic!
Allow me
to introduce Nikolaev's son.
Ladies and gentlemen!
I must be honest and say
that I didn't know
the famous man very well.
Life decreed that we would
rarely see each other…
actually only once.
He was a very good man,
a good chef.
I had some soup and beef… not bad at all…
Can you dance rock'n'roll?
Well...
I used to in college.
Dance some then!
Yes, do!
Rock!
Let's all dance.
Silence, please.
He could never
have shot himself.
He didn’t have the guts.
Now watch how it's done.
We want to see Varakin.
- I'm Varakin.
- Can we come in?
Yes, please.
Sit down.
'My name is Lydia Shulakova
'and this is my son.' That's me.
What can I do for you?
'I am the Lydia Shulakova
'who danced rock'n roll
with Nikolaev,
'for which I was expelled
from medical school,
'and then drank acetic acid
and lost my voice.'
I remember Chugunov
told me about you.
'I have a few things
which belonged to Nikolaev.
'They mean a great deal to me,
'but I want you to have them.'
Thank you.
But if they mean so much to you,
perhaps you will keep them?
'Thank you
for being so much like him.
'You have kept our ideals alive.
'I want to dance with you.'
Good evening.
Ah, there's Alexei Varakin.
Stepan Ivanov.
Pleased to meet you.
Our town's mayor.
And this is Lydia Shulakova herself.
Pleased to meet you.
I've been looking forward
to meeting you.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for helping.
Things are a long way from finished.
That’s true. A lot has to yet be done,
but we've made some progress.
True, but the rehabilitation
of rock'n'roll
is of great political significance.
We can't be satisfied with that.
We're not satisfied.
The hero of the day.
Why did you come here?
I came to see Alexei on business.
If it's business, come on in.
Why'd you make such a fool
of yourself, Nikolai?
Turn it up, Victor.
- You'll destroy Russia.
- You're destroying her!
That's enough, no more of that!
Will you be with us long, Alexei?
I have to get to Moscow.
- Can you help me get out of here?
- You can't leave now.
Can I have a word
with you in private?
By all means.
Could we talk right now?
I'm ready.
Maybe we could go out
into the corridor?
- Hello.
- Hi, Pavel!
I was walking along and I saw
these girls outside your door,
so I invited them in.
We called you, remember?
We made meat dumplings and
brought some beer.
- Meat dumplings? Great.
- How could you be so stupid?
Leave me alone.
Okay, let's have a beer.
To progress.
I won't drink to that.
If you won't drink to progress,
drink to your mother.
I'll drink to that.
What'll we do with the dumplings?
We don’t have any plates.
Here's a spoon.
Eat them from the pot.
Alexei, would you help Tamara
exchange her room
for one in Tbilisi?
Only if it's a three-way exchange.
We can't let Tamara
go off to Tbilisi.
We need our beautiful girls here.
No, seriously,
I see you're a Soviet Deputy.
At the moment I’m not a deputy,
I'm merely a man in love.
That didn't take long.
By the way, Stepan,
we don't have a chief engineer.
We wanted to sing for you.
Let me sing a song.
- Just sit down.
- But his voice isn't bad.
'The Sokolov choir
at the Gypsy cafe??
'Was famous in its time.
'And the Sokolov guitar
'Still rings in my ears
'Always money, money, money
'Always money, gentlemen.
'Without it life is rotten,
'And just a waste of time.'
Mind if we join you?
- Who are you?
- We're in the next room,
here on business from Kiev.
We heard you singing
and thought we might drop in.
- We've got beer.
- Where are you from?
We're from here. I'm the mayor.
Our public prosecutor,
the director of the factory.
And this is Chugunov, the chairman
of the local writers' association.
All local townfolk.
Varakin isn't.
Ah, yes, Varakin,
the son of chef Nikolaev.
A fine gathering.
Are you going to listen or not?
- We’re singing and you’re talking!
- You're singing nonsense.
Then sing yourself!
That’s enough.
- Okay, Nikolai, go on.
- You're not listening.
What song would you like, Alexei?
Me?
'The night is bright,
above the river
'Brightly shines the moon,
'And the blue waves
'Are edged in silver.
'The woods are dark and silent and
'Among the emerald branches,
'The nightingale hides,
'But sings no thrilling song.
'In the light of the moon
'Brihgt blue flowers have blossomed,
'Stirring in my heart
'Restless dreams.
'On this moonlit night,
'Beloved, darling friend,
'Think of me again
'And love me as before.'
Let's go to the oak tree.
Alexei, we have an oak tree
that Prince Dmitry Donskoi
once sat under.
That's right, let's go.
This oak is 1200 years old.
In pagan times it was sacred.
Anyone who pulled off a branch
became the leader.
But to hold on to his power
he had to protect the tree.
So of course sooner or later
someone killed him,
tore off a branch,
and became the leader himself.
In civilized society this custom
outlived itself.
Prince Dmitry Donskoi,
and later Ivan the Terrible
both pulled branches off our tree.
Since the 1917 Revolution
it has been protected by the State.
- Can we have a little branch
for a souvenir? - No way.
A tiny little one.
Let her take one.
Well, if the town Soviet
says it's okay...
Dammit.
It's rotten.
We should’ve watered it.
Now that one's off,
everybody take one.
- This one's too small.
- That's a good branch.
Can I take one for my brother?
Run for it!
Run!
What?
Run, I tell you!
Which way?
Written by Alexander Borodyansky
Karen Shakhnazarov
Directed by Karen Shakhnazarov
Camera: Nikolai Nemolyaev
Sets: Lyudmila Kusakova
Music: Eduard Artemiev