MOSFILM
MOSFILM CINEMA CONCERN
PRODUCTION COMPANY
OF ALEKSANDR LITVINOV
With financial support from
the Ministry of Culture
of the Russian Federation
The Russian Military-Historical Society
Present
ON THE ROAD TO BERLIN
Based on the story by E. Kazakevich
“Two in the Steppe” and
the war diaries of K. Simonov
Starring:
Yuriy Borisov
Amir Abdykalykov
Producers:
Aleksandr Litvinov
Karen Shakhnazarov
Screenplay: Evgeniy Nikishov
Go!
Directed by: Sergey Popov
Director of Photography:
Shandor Berkeshi R.G.C.
Designers:
Sergey Fevralev
Irina Ochina
Composer: Roman Dormidoshin
Costumer: Gyulyumzhan Bejshenova
Make-up: Sofia Bulychyova
Go!
Sound: Olga Serdyukova
Editor: Olga Kolesnikova
Director:
Natalya Lyashchenko
Executive Producers:
Olga Golomovzyuk
Maksim Zolotov
Project Idea and
Artistic Director:
Karen Shakhnazarov
The Southern Front 1942
Air! Everyone, head for shelter!
Air!
- Why did you change?
- What are you talking about?
Why did you change your clothes,
you fasсist? Why’d you change?
Just leave me alone.
Hit the dirt! Fasсists.
They’ve got us surrounded! Run for it!
- Give me back my rifle.
- Get back!
Why’d you change clothes, fasсists?
I recognize all of you anyway.
Why’d you change clothes?!
I’ll kill you! I’ll kill you all!
He almost caused a panic, the rat.
Take him away.
Lieutenant! Are you shell-shocked
or something?
No, sir. Lieutenant Ogarkov,
assigned to the 114th division.
Do you have a weapon?
Yes.
- Here.
- Is it loaded?
- Yes, sir, it’s loaded.
- Then why didn’t you shoot?
The evacuation will end at 5 PM.
- You’ll answer for this personally.
- Yes, sir!
Do you know why there aren’t
any craters from shells in the road?
Why?
Fritz’s orders - don’t bomb
the roads or highways.
Then they can use them themselves.
Comrade officers! You need to leave
immediately for your divisions
and deliver these orders.
Thousands, even tens of thousands
of lives depend on you!
Ogarkov?! Our divisions are next
to each other.
We can ride together
as far as Pavlovsky farm.
Yes? I’ll get the horse.
Look over there.
- What’s your name?
- Sergey.
- Why don’t you have an orderly?
- They didn’t give me one.
How can a communications
officer get by without an orderly?
Say something happens to you
on the road, who will help you,
make a report to your superior officer?
You head to the right here.
See you.
Look lively, hold your position.
Turn around - more to the left.
That’s it.
Let’s go, guys.
- Is this Aprelevka?
- No!
- Do you know where the 341st division is?
- What division, damn it?
The Germans have broken through
our defense. Get out of here!
Dig in deeper, deeper. Don’t slack off.
Comrade Captain, I’m a communications
officer. I have an order,
I need to deliver it to the division.
Look here, we are here.
The Germans broke through here.
The division you need
is located in this area.
There’s nothing else I can tell you.
Belousov! Damn you, I told you
to the left! Well, that’s the direction.
- Sir!
- Bring those branches over here.
Brace the mounts!
Tanks from the right!
Turn your weapon around!
Aim for the one in front.
Take your positions.
- Set your sights at 20.
- Shell.
Аn armor-piercing shell. Load!
Fire!
More to the left,
Belousov, damn you!
Why are you sprawled out!
Load.
Load! Fire. Fire, I said!
Aim constant. Three rounds,
continuous fire.
Go higher, higher, damn it!
Load!
No retreat!
Back!
Back, I said.
Go back, damn it!
Why are you lying here!?
Germans! Run, run!
Back, I said! Back everyone!
Back, I said!
You’ll all be court marshalled.
Bitches, back I said! Cowards!
Back! Back!
Your full name.
- Ogarkov, Sergey Leonidovich.
- Age?
- Twenty years.
- Rank?
- Lieutenant.
- Position?
Communications Officer at
the staff headquarters of the Army.
Education?
Ten years in school,
then the military chemical college.
Did you know what order you
were taking to the division?
- Yes.
- I'm talking about its content.
Did you know the content of the order?
- Yes, sir!
- Then why didn’t you deliver it?
Well, I couldn’t get through to them.
There were tanks, well,
many German tanks.
And the division had probably
crossed over beyond the river.
I don’t know, and I couldn’t
get through to them.
Who was your father, Ogarkov?
Why was? He’s still alive.
He’s an engineer. At a factory
in Gorky. Why the past tense?
Ogarkov and I split up
near the Pavlovsky farm.
- How was he acting?
- A bit cowardly.
But I thought it was a lack
of experience, he’s still young.
- And how old are you?
- Twenty-two.
They hadn’t given him an orderly.
Still, he was a bit cowardly. After all,
he was right by the staff of the division.
Tonight the enemy broke through
our defenses in a few places.
A move to the rear is complicated
by the loss of the communication.
Orders for the re-deployment
were sent to all divisions.
As for the 341st division...
It seems we’ve lost them.
Seryozha!
What are you up to, you scamp?
What did I say about coming here?
Having considered
the investigation materials
and heard the explanations
of the accused and witnesses,
The Military tribunal decrees:
For exhibiting cowardice,
desertion and betraying the oath,
we sentence former Red Army
lieutenant Ogarkov Sergey Leonidovich,
in accordance with statute 193,
to the highest extent of the law –
death by firing squad.
Corporal Dzhurabaev, strip the condemned
man of the signs of his rank.
Come on out.
Come on, what are you waiting for?
Take off your coat, you won’t need it.
Comrade Lieutenanat,
and maybe this at the same time?
No rush.
Hands behind your back.
Get a move on. Go.
Go in.
Hey! Open up.
I’ve got something to say.
Hey, open up. I’ve got...
I need to explain something to them.
Hey.
Open up.
Open up. I need to explain...
Open up, I need to explain it all.
Open up!
You don’t have the right.
I’m a Soviet citizen. Do you hear?
Hey, brother,
are you here?
Stop. Who goes there?
Comrade, I need to give
the condemned a copy of the sentence.
I’m the secretary of the tribunal.
The corporal of the guard
must be with you.
The corporal of the guard is
at staff headquarters in the village.
Don’t you know who I am?
The corporal of
the guard must be with you.
Svetochka, what brings you here?
That guard of yours.
He’s a complete idiot. A dolt!
That’s the way he is.
Woudn’t let his own mother through.
Right, Dzhurabaev?
I need to give you a copy of the sentence.
Here, take it
and sign for it.
There.
Thank you.
Listen, don’t worry,
there’s still hope because the Military
council has to confirm the conviction.
They can’t enforce it otherwise.
Maybe you’d like to write a letter?
I’ll mail it for you.
I didn’t bring the convict any grub,
cause I figured they would’ve already…
Dzhurabaev,
- your boots aren’t too tight are they?
- No.
As you wish. Or I could try
to rustle you up some new ones.
No.
The conviction must be confirmed
at the Army staff headquarters.
Do you hear?
If anything happens to this man,
you’ll answer for it.
You see, Dzhurabaev.
You’ve got quite
the reputation for being sombre.
Go on.
I’ll bring you relief in the evening.
Guard the convict like he’s the apple
of your eye, got it?
Sveta, please, sit down.
He’s just a sentry.
He’s the kind who would
take him out and kill him.
What? No.
You know, I’m always worried about you.
You women shouldn’t be here
in the war, you understand?
This war, they’d shoot you and
wouldn't even notice that you're a girl.
They’re fascists, after all.
You understand?
Get out.
Move.
Move, move!
Stop!
Just shoot me already!
We’re leaving!
- Give me your rifle.
- No.
- No, it’s forbidden.
- I’ll shoot him.
Let’s leave.
Go to sleep already.
I won’t run off, I promise.
- Why don’t you say anything?
- Because you’re the enemy.
Ogarkov!
Stop! Lower your weapon.
Who are you? Your documents.
You’re also trying
to get through the blockade?
You’ll go under my command.
- No, It’s forbidden.
- Why?
I’ve got orders. We’re to go
to Army headquarters.
Why?
Even rhynos are smarter than you!
Why couldn’t we just go with the Captain?
Nobody asked for me to be let go.
We could have simply gone with
the Captain, on the same road,
side-by-side, in the rain,
but with the Captain
who knows the way and how and why.
Any idiot should know the Army staff
headquarters is not in the blockade.
Or do you not understand that?
Why don’t you say anything?
Can you understand what I’m saying?
Go on, be silent, you dolt.
I’ll escape from you all the same.
I’ll knock you out,
take your rifle and run away.
- Go in.
- Sure, sure, of course.
Let’s sit a bit and wait for the Germans.
Close it, sure, close it.
You think that’ll keep
me from running away?
You fall asleep and I’m gone, understand?
I’ll dig my way out and run away.
Or maybe through the roof.
Go ahead latch the door.
Nail me in,
get a log and barricade me in.
I’ll still run away.
We’ve got to find a place to cross.
Let’s swim across.
No.
What? Can’t you swim?
Are you serious? You can’t swim?
He says, I bet you can’t swim across
the Volga. I says, you’re on.
In an hour I was on
the other side. An hour.
And that was the Volga not this…
That was the Volga.
- Do you know how wide the Volga is?
- Quiet.
- A cow.
- Will you kill it?
Why would we kill it?
Mom said that the Germans would
come and kill her. Our guys, too.
- And you’ve hidden her here?
- There’s nowhere else.
- I see. Is there a place to ford here?
- No.
There used to be a bridge over there,
but the Germans blew it up.
- Any boats?
- There’s a raft.
A raft?
- Would you show us?
- You’re really our guys?
Really.
Then maybe you could
take the pilot with you.
He’s wounded in the head and the leg.
We bandaged him up, well Nina did.
Her mom’s a medic.
She knows how to do it.
- Has he been here long?
- Three days already.
He moaned a lot the first day.
We all thought he’d croak.
Mom says that if any Germans find him here
they’ll do us all in.
Help me.
This raft won't carry two people.
Misha and I tried it once,
but it tipped over immediately.
- You know how to do it?
- How?
Put one guy on the raft and
the other will swim alongside holding on.
Then it’ll work.
Look. Let’s do it like this.
I’ll go with the pilot,
I’ll take him to the other side.
I’ll leave him there and come back
for you,
and together we can cross, OK?
Come on.
What?
You’re afraid I’ll run off?
OK, look.
This watch was my Grandfather’s.
My most prize possession.
Look, read it. There it says - Ogarkov,
that’s my Grandad. Take it.
That’s it. Let’s go.
You… what?
Yeah, I could run off, only how
then could I drag him there without you?
Do you get it?
Or do you think that
I’d leave him there?
You think I’d leave him?
Well, say something. Answer me!
He’s ours, isn’t he? Isn’t he ours?
The current carried us away.
Come on.
Stop, stop!
They’re ours, they’re ours!
- Our guys…
- Halt! Hands up!
Guys. I’m one of us! Hey, guys,
we’ve got a wounded pilot over there.
Your guy’s in bad shape.
He doesn’t even moan anymore.
Guys, help me. Let’s move him.
We’ll tend to the wounded later.
For now, anyone who can
hold a weapon, we’re going to battle.
I’ve got my own orders.
Break through the ring and get
the people out with minimal losses.
- Can’t. We’re going to Army headquarters.
- What are you harping on about!
The staff headquarters is back
there in the rear! Here I’m in command.
And anyone who can carry
a gun tomorrow is going to fight.
- Comrade…
- Drop it!
Attention!
In accordance with directive 2-6-0,
you and your prisoner are under
my jurisdiction
until we’ve broken through the blockade.
And then go wherever the hell you want!
- Got it, private?
- Yes, sir.
They’re prepping
the pilot for his operation.
They said gangrene has set in.
They’ll have to amputate his leg.
- Wanna smoke?
- No, I don’t smoke.
Well, I do.
Were you a Komsomolets?
Yeah.
Go,
you have to go get your weapon yourself.
We’re going to break through the blockade.
Go.
Here, take it, soldier,
a rifle sling, a cap, sign for it.
Listen… Sign here?
- Here.
- Don’t you have any boots?
No boots. We’ve got foot
cloths and buttons. Need any?
- No.
- Then sorry, buddy.
- Comrade.
- Five… six.
Is your watch any good?
- Like it?
- Yeah.
- It’s a trophy.
- Do you collect them?
What of it? I’ve got a right.
- Next.
- And for me more broth, guy.
You want zilch? Move on.
Next.
What’s with your shoe, soldier?
You going to attack like that?
Or you do not go in attack?
Head over to the supply tent.
I’ve got a pair of boots
left in just your size. Run.
We were allocated to the third company.
- We’ll move out soon.
- I’ve got to get boots. Just a minute.
Hey, guy. Was it you who brought
the pilot to the infirmary?
- Yes.
- Could I have his parachute?
It’s all torn and covered in blood, it is.
Once he wakes up, ask him.
Well, he…
when he came to after the operation
and saw he didn’t have legs,
he shot himself in the mouth.
Third company!
Fall in to two files!
So what about the parachute?
Faster, double time. Look lively.
Lively!
Line up! Attention!
Right face!
Forward march!
To the assault!
Forward! Hoorah!
Forward!
- Brother!
- Yeah!
- Hey, brother. Why are you lying here?
- They’ll kill me.
Well, so what if they kill you,
it’s war. Get up.
No, they’ll kill me.
If you’re lying down,
they’ll definitely kill you.
Harder to hit a moving target. Get up.
- They’ll kill me.
- Look, I’m standing up, you get up, too.
Load. Fire.
- Forward, brothers! Hooray!!!
- Hooray!
A sniper!
Stop! Where are you going?
Don’t! The sniper will see you and shoot.
- Forward, guys.
- Hooray!
Ogarkov!
Ogarkov, are you alive?
Damn if the directive of
the Soviet tribunal
was fulfilled by the Krauts!
I brought him.
Well, about time.
So, comrades, lets’ put the artillery
in the background.
That’s good.
Backup a bit. Now to the left.
Ready.
Here we go...
Say cheese.
Got it. When the paper comes out,
I’ll send you the picture.
Thanks. We sure gave it
to them, Captain.
- Well, yeah and how!
- We are fearless people.
You and I are fearless, Dzhurabaev.
And you know, everyone who came out
of the encirclement will get medals.
What’s wrong, Dzhurabaev?
We need to go to
the Army staff headquarters.
Ogarkov,
can you write?
Write what?
Can you write a letter?
Where?
To the staff headquarters?
Wait, we will be with you soon?
No. I need to write home, to my mother.
What do you want to write?
Write that we’re fighting the Germans.
She knows that.
From the war you need
to write something heroic.
What?
Heroic. Say, write that you’re a convoy.
- A what?
- A convoy.
You are conveying me, you are fulfilling
a very important order.
No. They’ll think it’s bad, that
I’m serving in a prison, not the front.
That’s because you need to write
to your father, not mother.
The father will understand.
My father died
at the front.
In ’41.
Write about the steppe.
What?
The steppe here looks a lot like at home…
the steppe… and the wind…
Comrade soldiers, I’m lieutenant
Prisyazhnyuk, the commandant of the town.
Your documents.
Again, private Dzhurabaev,
you're free to go.
- Head back to your unit.
- Can’t go back. I have an order!
- I need to go to the staff headquarters.
- Back off!
- I have more than enough to do!
- Comrade commandant,
the tribunal papers
need to be confirmed.
Private Dzhurabaev, I tell you again,
you’ve completed your mission. Go.
Comrade commandant, I can’t.
I’ve got an order.
In conditions of war
I can decide such questions myself. Clear?
Ishenko!
Escort the private to the exit.
Sit down, granny, sit down.
I’ll call you.
I’ve got no time right now.
Go straight ahead.
Attention!
Ready!
Load!
Aim!
- Ogarkov! Ogarkov!
- At ease!
Comrade Lieutenant,
I’m to take Ogarkov to the commandant.
Who’s Ogarkov?
Aim.
Fire.
You now owe your life to your Kazakh.
If he hadn’t brought that paper…
Take it.
This is your citation for
the order of the Red Star.
What happens now?
I don’t know…
Let the staff headquarters decide.
Shoot you or give you the award.
Ishenko!
That’s all. Escort him out.
What made you decide to save me?
You never finished the letter.
You don’t smoke.
Yes, I don’t smoke.
- Hello.
- There are two of you?
I can find a place for two.
Come.
Take it.
Maria!
Everyone is ours. Here take it.
Maybe you’d like to sleep?
No, thank you.
My husband was killed last
year right at the beginning.
He was stationed
at the border, in Bessarabia.
He was a lot like you,
a city boy,
from Maikop.
- Hello, Aunty Masha.
- Hi.
Here.
- Thank you.
- When you come back -
drop by
if you remember.
Get up, get up.
- Are you alive?
- Yeah, everything’s OK.
Check the personel.
Anyone wounded?
A soldier’s wounded. Call the medic.
Get a medic here.
- Quick, quick.
- Go away, go away.
- Let us help.
- How?
Now, now.
Get your hands off him!
- Get your hands off him!
- Calm down.
Now, now, now. Hold on.
Give me a rag.
There now, hold on.
I’ll take care of you. Hold on.
- Here. Will this work?
- Now, now,
hold on.
Get out.
- Where can I wash my hands?
- I’ll show you.
Now, now…
- How is he?
- He won’t last an hour.
Hold on, hold on…
Boots…
Boots, what?
- for the German…
- The German… what?
- Boots…
- Boots… Hold on…
- Don’t give them away…
- I won’t give them away… Hold on.
What was his name?
Private Dzhurabaev.
And his first name?
You’ve got blood on your tunic.
I’ll wash it for you.
That’s Mikola, our neighbor.
He says, he’s not going across the river.
He’s done with fighting.
I found this in your tunic.
Are you Ogarkov?
It’s you they’re going to shoot?
Yes.
And he...
he was taking you
to be shot?
Yes.
Well, so that means now
you don’t need to go there.
Yes, I could choose not to go.
But you’re going anyway?
Yes.
Let’s move!
C’mon, open up!
No sleeping, sentry.
- Good health, Comrade lieutenant.
- What?
Don’t you recognize me?
Ogarkov?
So you…
How?
Are you going to the staff headquarters?
Yes.
Then we’re both going the same way.
- Well, what’s over there?
- Still don’t know.
What’s there to know, geez!
He came himself.
Of his own will. Formalists.
And he fought. In the encirclement.
Did you make the inquiry?
I did. Don’t get worked up.
Nobody’s gonna shoot him just yet.
I’m coming!
I’ll call you from the nearest telephone
station, I’ll find out what’s up.
- You’ll be here?
- Where else would I be?
- Vanya!
- What?
He wrote a letter.
He asked to have you mail it.
Germany
- Is it going to be much longer?
- A couple of minutes.
Kopylov, you were supposed
to be at your position a half hour ago.
I want everything ready so the column
can head out in five minutes.
- You understand? Carry it out.
- Yes, sir.
- Ogarkov.
- Good afternoon, comrade Colonel!
So now I'm just a colonel for you?
Don't you recognize me?
Sinyaev!
Hello!
I’m so happy to see you, you old devil.
I didn’t know what kind
of sentence they’d give you.
I got wounded
and then was in hospital.
Wait! Just a minute, wait.
This is the third year
I’ve been carrying it with me.
Kopylov? Look lively.
- Here, take it.
- What’s this?
There inside, look.
Comrade Colonel, everything’s ready.
We can head out.
Alright, fairwell, Sergey.
Starring:
Ogarkov - Yuriy Borisov
Dzhurabaev – Amir Abdykalykov
Sinyaev – Maksim Demchenko
Maria – Maria Karpova
Crew:
Director – Sergey Popov
Scriptwriter – Evgeniy Nikishov
Cinematography – Shandor Berkeshi R.G.C.
Composer – Roman Dormidoshin
Scenic design – Sergey Fevralev
Irina Ochina
Director – Natalya Lyashchenko
Costume design – Gyulyumzhan Beishenova
Makeup – Sofia Bulycheva
Sound director – Olga Serdiukova
Director of editing – Olga Kolesnikova
Executive producers:
Olga Golomovziuk
Maksim Zolotov
Irina Zolotova
Producers:
Aleksandr Litvinov
Karen Shakhnazarov
© Mosfilm Cinema Concern, 2015