Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Paramount News
brings you special coverage
of Princess Ann's visit to London.
The first stop on her much publicised
goodwill tour of European capitals.
She gets a royal welcome.
Thousands cheer a young member of
one of Europe's oldest ruling families.
After three days of continuous activity
and a visit to Buckingham Palace,
Ann flew to Amsterdam,
where she dedicated
the new International Aid Building
and an ocean liner.
Then she went to Paris,
attending many official functions
to cement trade relations
between her country
and the Western European nations.
And so to Rome, the Eternal City,
where the princess's visit
was marked by a spectacular parade,
highlighted by the band
of the crack bersaglieri regiment.
The smiling young princess
showed no sign
of the strain of the week's
continuous public appearances.
At her country's
embassy that evening,
a formal reception
and ball in her honour
was given by her country's
ambassador to Italy.
Her Royal Highness.
His Excellency, the Papal Nuncio,
Monsignor Altomonte.
Sir Hugo Macey de Farmington.
- Good evening, Sir Hugo.
- Good evening, Your Highness.
His Highness, the Maharajah
of Khanipur, and the Raikuuari.
I'm so glad you could come.
Thank you, madam.
Friherre Erick af
Massinsjarna-Bergenskiold.
Prince Istvar Barlossy Nagayavaros.
How do you do?
Der Fürst und die Fürstin
von und zu Lucktenstichenholz.
Sir Hari Singh and Kmark Singh.
The Count and Countess
von Marstrand.
Good evening, Countess.
Good evening.
Senhor e senhora
João de Camões.
Good evening.
Hassan El Din Pasha.
How do you do?
I hate this nightgown.
I hate all my nightgowns,
and I hate all my underwear too.
- My dear, you have lovely things.
- But I'm not 200 years old.
- Why can't I sleep in pyjamas?
- Pyjamas!
Just the top part.
Did you know there are people
who sleep with absolutely nothing on?
I rejoice to say I did not.
Listen.
Oh, and your slippers.
Please put on your slippers
and come away from the window.
- Your milk and crackers.
- Everything we do is so wholesome.
They'll help you to sleep.
I'm too tired to sleep.
I shan't sleep a wink.
Now, my dear, if you don't mind,
tomorrow's schedule,
if that's your preferred
pronunciation, both are correct.
8.30, breakfast with
the embassy staff.
9 o'clock, leave for the
Polinari Automotive Works,
to be presented with a small car.
- Thank you.
- Which you won't accept.
- No, thank you.
- 10.35,
inspect agriculture organisation,
who'll present you with an olive tree.
- No, thank you.
- Which you will accept.
Thank you.
10.55, the new Foundling
Home for orphans.
Laying of cornerstone,
same speech as last Monday.
- Trade relations.
- Yes.
- For the orphans?
- Oh no, the other one.
- Youth and progress.
- Precisely.
11.45, back here to rest.
No, that's wrong. 11.45,
conference here with the press.
Sweetness and decency.
One o'clock sharp,
lunch with foreign ministry.
You'll wear white lace
and carry a bouquet
of very small pink roses.
- 3.05, presentation of a plaque.
- Thank you.
- 4.10, review special guard of police.
- No, thank you.
- 4.45, back here to change...
- How do you do? Charmed...
Stop!
Stop, stop!
- It's all right, dear, it didn't spill.
- I don't care if it spilled or not.
My dear, you're ill.
I'll send for Doctor Bannochhoven.
I don't want him.
Please let me die in peace.
- You're not dying.
- Leave me!
It's nerves. Control yourself, Ann.
I don't want to.
Your Highness!
- I'll get Doctor Bannochhoven.
- It's no use.
I'll be dead before he gets here.
- She's asleep.
- She was in hysterics 3 minutes ago.
- Are you asleep, ma'am?
- No.
I'll only disturb Your Royal
Highness a moment.
I'm very ashamed, Doctor.
Suddenly I was crying.
To cry is perfectly normal.
It's important she be calm and
relaxed for the press conference.
Don't worry, Doctor,
I'll be calm and relaxed.
I'll bow and I'll smile,
I'll improve trade relations and I'll...
There she goes again.
Give her something, please.
Uncover her arm, please.
- What's that?
- Sleep and calm.
This will relax you
and make you feel a little happy.
It's a new drug, quite harmless.
There.
I don't feel any different.
You will. It may take
a little time to take hold.
Just now, lie back.
- Can I keep just one light on?
- Of course.
The best thing I know is to do
exactly what you wish for a while.
Thank you, Doctor.
Oh, the General! Doctor, quick.
I'm perfectly all right.
Goodnight, ma'am.
- Goodnight, ma'am.
- Goodnight, Doctor.
- Bet five hundred.
- Five hundred. How many?
One.
- I'll take one.
- Three.
Four.
Two for Papa.
- 500 more.
- Without looking.
500, and I'll raise you 1,000.
- Two pairs.
- I've got three shy little sevens.
A nervous straight.
Come home, you fools.
Look at that, 6,500.
Not bad, that's ten bucks.
One more round and I'm gonna throw
you gents right out in the snow.
I gotta get up early.
A date with Her Highness, who'll
graciously pose for some pictures.
What do you mean early?
My personal invitation says 11.45.
Could it be because you're ahead?
- It could.
- Works out fine for me.
This is my last 5,000 and
you hyenas are not gonna get it.
Thanks, Irving.
See you at Ann's in the morning.
- Ciao, Joe.
- Stay sober.
All right, a little seven-card stud.
So happy.
How are you this evening?
Hey, hey.
- Wake up.
- Thank you very much.
- No, thank you.
Charmed.
Charmed too.
You may sit down.
You'd better sit up, or you'll
get picked up by the police.
- Police?
- Yes.
2.15 and back here to change.
2.45...
You know, people who can't
handle liquor shouldn't drink it.
"If I were dead and buried
and I heard your voice,"
"beneath the sod my heart of dust
would still rejoice. "
Do you know that poem?
Whadda ya know?
You're well read, well dressed,
snoozing away in a public street.
Would you care to make a statement?
What the world needs
is a return to sweetness and decency
in the souls of its young men and...
Yeah, I couldn't agree
with you more, but...
Get yourself some coffee,
you'll be all right.
Look, you take the cab.
Come on, climb in
the cab and go home.
- So happy.
- Got any money?
- Never carry money.
- That's a bad habit.
All right. I'll drop you off, come on.
- It's a taxi!
- It's not the Super Chief.
Where are we going?
- Where do you live?
- What?
- Colosseum.
- Come on, you're not that drunk.
You're so smart, I'm not drunk at all.
- I'm just being very happy.
- Hey, don't go to sleep again.
Where are we going?
Where do you want to go?
Where shall I take you?
Where do you live?
Come on. Where do you live?
Come on, where do you live?
Colosseum.
- She lives in the Colosseum.
- It's the wrong address.
Look, for me it is very late night.
My wife... I have three bambino,
you know bambino?
My taxi go home,
we go home together.
Via Margutta 51.
Via Margutta 51!
Here is Via Margutta 51.
I am very happy.
A thousand lire. Mila lire.
One, two, three, four mila.
- OK.
- For me?
OK. Now, look,
take a little bit of that.
Take her wherever she wants to go.
Goodnight.
Oh! No, no. Momento.
All right. Look, when she wakes up,
she'll tell you where to go.
Momento.
My taxi is not for sleep.
You understand?
Look, pal, this is not my problem.
I never see her before. OK.
Is not your problem,
is not my problem.
What you want?
You don't want girl, me don't want girl.
Police. Maybe she want girl!
Stay calm, stay calm. OK.
So happy.
I ought to have my head examined.
Is this the elevator?
It's my room!
I'm terribly sorry to mention it,
but the dizziness is getting worse.
- Can I sleep here?
- That's the general idea.
Can I have a silk nightgown
with rosebuds on it?
I'm afraid
you'll have to rough it tonight.
- In these.
- Pyjamas.
Sorry, honey, I haven't
worn a nightgown in years.
Will you help me
get undressed, please?
OK.
There you are.
You can handle the rest.
May I have some?
No!
- Now, look!
- This is very unusual.
I've never been alone with a man
before, even with my dress on.
With my dress off, it's most unusual.
I don't seem to mind. Do you?
I think I'll go out for a cup of coffee.
You'd better get to sleep.
Oh, no. On this one.
You're terribly nice.
Hey, come here.
These are pyjamas, they're
to sleep in. You're to climb into them.
- Understand?
- Thank you.
And you sleep on the couch. Not on
the bed, on the couch. Is that clear?
- Do you know my favourite poem?
- You've already recited it.
"Arethusa arose
From her couch of snows"
"In the Acroceraunian Mountains. "
- Keats.
- Shelley.
Keep your mind off the poetry
and on the pyjamas.
- You'll be fine.
- Keats.
Shelley. I'll be back
in about ten minutes.
Keats.
You have my permission to withdraw.
Thank you very much.
- Well?
- No trace.
- Did you search the grounds?
- Attics to cellar.
You must swear not to
speak of this to anyone.
I must remind you that the princess
is the direct heir to the throne.
This must be classified as top
crisis secret. Have I your pledge?
- Yes, sir.
- Very well.
Now we must notify Their Majesties.
- So happy.
- The pleasure's mine.
Screwball!
Holy smoke,
the princess's interview!
Eleven forty-five!
Oh, sh!
Hi, Joe.
- Morning, Joe.
- Hello, honey.
Mr Hennessy has been
looking for you.
Uh-oh.
Thanks a lot, hon.
Come in.
- Looking for me?
- Just coming to work?
- Who, me?
- We start at 8.30 in this office.
- We pick up our assignments...
- I got mine last night.
- What assignment was that?
- The princess, 11.45.
You've already been to the interview?
Sure, I just got back.
- Well, well. All my apologies.
- It's all right.
- Interesting.
- No, just routine.
Did she answer
all the questions on the list?
Of course. I've got 'em
right here somewhere.
Don't disturb yourself,
I have a copy here.
How did Her Highness react to
the idea of a European Federation?
- She thought it was just fine.
- She did?
- She thought there'd be two effects.
- Two?
- The direct and the indirect.
- Remarkable.
Naturally, she thought that the indirect
would not be as direct as the direct.
- That is, not right away.
- No.
Later on, of course, nobody knows.
Well, well.
That was a shrewd observation.
They fool you, these royal kids.
They're smarter than we suspect.
How did she feel about
the future friendship of nations?
Youth. She felt that
the youth of the world
must lead the way to a better world.
Original.
By the way, what was she wearing?
- You mean what did she have on?
- That's usually what it means.
- Is it too warm for you?
- No, I just hurried over here.
Naturally, with a story
of these dimensions.
- Did you say she was wearing grey?
- No, I didn't.
- She usually wears grey.
- Well, it was a kind of a grey.
I think I know the dress,
it has a gold collar...
That's the one. I didn't know
exactly how to describe it.
I think you described it very well,
in view of the fact that
she was taken violently ill at 3 AM,
put to bed with a high fever,
and has had all her appointments
for today cancelled in toto!
- In toto?
- Yes, Mr Bradley, in toto.
- That's pretty hard to swallow.
- In view of the fact you just left her.
Here it is, Mr Bradley, all over the
front page of every paper in Rome.
All right, I overslept.
It can happen to anybody.
If you ever got up
and read a morning paper,
you might discover little news events,
little items of general interest,
that might stop you getting
immersed in such a gold-plated,
triple-decked, star-spangled
lie as you have just told me.
If I were you I'd try some other
business, like mattress testing!
- Is this the princess?
- Yes, Mr Bradley.
It isn't Annie Oakley, Dorothy Lamour
or Madame Chiang Kai-Shek.
Take a good look. You might
interview her again some day.
Am I fired?
No. When I want to fire you,
you won't have to ask.
You'll know you're fired.
The man's mad.
Giovanni, it's Joe Bradley.
Now listen carefully.
Hurry up to my place and see
if there's somebody there, asleep.
Aha. Si, Mr Joe.
I look, you wait.
- Mr Joe?
- Yeah. Tell me.
Giovanni, I love you! Now listen.
Yes, Mr Joe.
A gun? No.
Yes, a gun, a knife, anything.
But nobody goes in
and nobody goes out.
OK.
You still here?
What would a real interview
with this dame be worth?
- Are you referring to Her Highness?
- I'm not referring to Annie Oakley...
- How much?
- What do you care?
- You've got no chance...
- If I did, how much?
Just a plain talk on world
conditions might be worth 250.
Her views on clothes, a lot more.
- Maybe 1,000.
- Dollars?
I'm talking about
her views on everything.
The private and secret
longings of a princess.
Her innermost thoughts, as revealed
to your own correspondent,
in a private, personal,
exclusive interview.
Can't use it, huh?
I didn't think you'd like it.
Come here.
- Love angle too, I suppose?
- Practically all love angle.
With pictures?
Could be. How much?
That particular story would be worth
five grand to any news service.
But tell me, Mr Bradley,
if you are sober,
how you are going to
obtain this fantastic interview.
I'll enter her sick room
disguised as a thermometer.
You said five grand?
I want you to shake on that.
You realise she's in bed
and leaves for Athens tomorrow?
- Yes.
- I'd like to make a little side bet.
Five hundred says
you don't come up with the story.
- What are you looking at that for?
- Just want to see what day it is.
- It's a deal.
- Now I'd like you to shake.
You're into me for about $500 now.
When you lose this bet,
you'll owe me $1,000.
You poor sucker,
I'll practically own you.
You practically have for a couple
of years but that's all over.
I'm going to win that money and buy
a one-way ticket back to New York.
Go on, I love to hear you whine.
When I'm back in a real
newsroom, I'll think of you,
sitting here with an empty leash
and nobody to twitch for you.
So long, pigeon.
- Signor Bradley.
- Everything OK, Giovanni?
Si Signor Joe.
Nobody come, nobody go.
- Absolutely nobody.
- Swell, thanks a lot.
Oh... Giovanni...
How'd you like to make some money?
- Money?
- Yeah.
That's the stuff. I've got a sure thing.
- Double your money back in two days.
- Double my money?
I need a little investment
capital to swing the deal.
Now if you'll lend me a little cash...
You owe me two months rent
and you want me to lend you money?
No.
Tomorrow you'll be sorry.
Your Highness...?
Your Royal Highness...?
Yes, what is it?
Dear Dr Bannochhoven...
Oh, sure, yes, well...
You're fine, much better.
Is there anything you want?
- So many things.
- Yes? Well, tell the doctor.
Tell the good doctor everything.
I dreamt and I dreamt...
Yes? Well, what did you dream?
I dreamt I was asleep in the street,
and a young man came,
he was tall and strong.
He was so mean to me.
He was?
It was wonderful.
Good morning.
- Where's Dr Bannochhoven?
- I'm afraid I don't know him.
- Wasn't I talking to him just now?
- Afraid not.
Have I had an accident?
No.
Quite safe for me to sit up, huh?
Perfectly.
Thank you.
Are these yours?
- Did you lose something?
- No.
Would you be so kind
as to tell me where I am?
This is what is laughingly
known as my apartment.
- Did you bring me here by force?
- No, no. Quite the contrary.
- Have I been here all night... alone?
- If you don't count me, yes.
So I've spent the night here with you?
Well, I don't know that
I'd use those words exactly,
but from a certain angle, yes.
- How do you do?
- And you are?
- Bradley, Joe Bradley.
- Delighted.
- You don't know how delighted I am.
- You may sit down.
- Thank you very much.
What's your name?
- You may call me Anya.
- Well thank you, Anya.
- Coffee?
- What time is it?
About one-thirty.
One-thirty! I must get dressed and go!
Why the hurry? There's lots of time.
No there isn't, and I've been
enough trouble as it is.
Trouble?
You're not what I'd call trouble.
- I'm not?
- I'll run a bath for you.
There you are.
Here we go now.
There you are, that does it. All right.
Give me a little slack, will you?
Irving! Why don't you answer?
It's Joe. Can you
get here in five minutes?
No, I can't come now, Joe, I'm busy.
Oh, no.
Joe, I'm up to my ears in work.
Get into your next outfit.
What kind of a scoop, Joe?
I can't talk over the phone.
This whole thing
might easily blow sky-high.
It's front-page stuff,
that's all I can say.
It might be political or
a scandal, I don't know,
but it's a big story.
I need pictures.
But I can't come now, Joe, I'm busy.
And I'm meeting Francesca
at Rocca's in half an hour.
- Don't understand.
- Don't understand?
There you are.
I was looking at all the people.
It must be fun to live in a place like this.
It has its moments. I can give you
a commentary on each apartment.
I must go.
- I only waited to say goodbye.
- Goodbye? But we've only just met!
- How about breakfast?
- I haven't time.
It must be a pretty important date
to run off without eating.
- It is.
- I'll go with you.
That's all right, I can find the place.
Thank you for letting me
sleep in your bed.
- That's all right. Think nothing of it.
- It was very considerate of you.
You must've been awfully
uncomfortable on that couch.
No, I do it all the time.
- Goodbye, Mr Bradley.
- Goodbye.
Go right through there,
and down all the steps.
Thank you.
- Well... Small world!
- Yeah.
I almost forgot.
Can you lend me some money?
Oh, yeah.
That's right,
you didn't have any did you?
How much was it you wanted?
I don't know. How much have you got?
Suppose we just split this fifty-fifty.
Here's a thousand lire.
A thousand!
Can you really spare all that?
- It's about a dollar and a half.
- Oh.
I'll arrange for it to be sent back to you.
What is your address?
Via Margutta 51.
Joe Bradley.
Goodbye. Thank you.
Double my money, eh?
You tell me how?
- Tomorrow.
- Yes, tomorrow.
What a wonderful hair you have.
- Just cut, thank you.
- Just cut?
- Well, then... Cut so?
- Higher.
- Higher? Here?
- More.
- Here!
- Even more.
Where?
- There.
- Are you sure, Miss?
- I'm quite sure, thank you.
- All off?
- All off.
Off!
- Are you sure?
- Yes!
Yes!
Off!
Oh no, no.
That's a nice camera
you have there. Nice...
You don't mind if I borrow it?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org