I came here to tell you a story.
I don't like stories.
But I'll listen anyway.
Greetings, Comrade Chenkov!
You'll see.
Alright.
Satisfied?.
I'm satisfied.
Comrades...
Our sister has rejoined us.
Russia will rise from the ashes...
of the greatest war the world has ever seen.
And the world will hear us!
...will hear.
Welcome back to our family, sister.
...sister.
Russia has changed.
But our lives will not be wasted.
You're to meet an agent, NATO uniform,
at a plane here...
Tail number N182SL.
Final instructions will come from him.
That's it.
After this, we go dark.
Radio silent.
Have you heard from Orlov?
Yes. Last word was ""go."'
Congratulations, Comrade Chenkov. You made it.
I tried many times, but...
My loneliness was my only friend.
I was a class ahead comrade.
The brightest of any of Orlov's stars.
And now it's my honor to launch the attack.
Excuse me.
Part two of our plan.
Kill nine million people...
Enrage a billion Muslims.
America will suffer a painful death.
Let me join you.
All these years right in front of me
and I never knew.
Let me join you.
I want to be with you.