I came here to tell you a story.
I don't like stories.
But l'll listen anyway.
Home to Grozny?
Greetings, Comrade Chenkov!
You'll see.
All right.
Satisfied?
I'm satisfied.
Comrades...
...our sister has rejoined us.
Russia will rise from the ashes...
...of the greatest war
the world has ever seen.
And the world will hear us!
Will hear.
Welcome back to our family, sister.
Sister.
Russia has changed.
But our lives will not be wasted.
You're to meet an agent,
NATO uniform, at a plane here.
Tail number N1 82SL.
Final instructions will come from him.
-That's it.
After this, we go dark.
Radio silent.
Congratulations, Comrade Chenkov.
You made it.
I tried many times, but....
My loneliness was my only friend.
I was a class ahead, comrade.
The brightest of any of Orlov's stars.
And now it's my honor
to launch the attack.
Excuse me.
Part two of our plan.
Kill nine million people.
Enrage a billion Muslims.
America will suffer a painful death.
Let me join you.
All these years right in front of me
and l never knew.
Let me join you.
I want to be with you.
Our father has decided that...
...the time has come...
...for you all to start your new lives.
To prepare for our next attack.
Can l help you?