Salt-Unrated DC
North Korea
two years ago
Please let me go home.
Please, I'm not who you think I am.
I'm really not who you think I am.
Please. Please. I'm not a spy.
You are a spy.
I'm not a spy.
Please let me go home.
Try again.
I am not a spy.
I am a businesswoman.
I work for Rink Petroleum and Gas.
Please call them.
I work for Rink Petroleum.
You are here to sabotage
our nuclear ambitions. Yes?
I am not a spy! I am not a spy!
Try again.
I am not a spy.
You are a spy.
Don't lie to me!
I am not a spy.
It is through the grace and munificence
of our glorious Dear Leader
that the Democratic People's
Republic of Korea
has pardoned
the American imperialist
for her hostile acts
against our socialist nation.
Keep your head down.
Don't say anything
till we make the swap.
In case Kim Jong
here changes his mind.
Exchange.
Right face!
I don't understand.
You don't
understand what?
All the rules say to leave me,
that one life
is not worth blowing
operational cover.
You got that right.
If we have to
lose someone for
the greater good, we will.
So why did you do it?
Well, I didn't do it.
He did.
Once he found out where you were,
there was no stopping him.
He petitioned the Senate,
the State Department.
We didn't need the publicity
so I figured we better do something
or he's gonna invade this
goddamn rice-paddy republic
himself.
You okay?
Yeah.
Hey.
Good morning.
Happy anniversary.
You want me to make you breakfast?
How about pancakes?
Your cooking?
You're joking. You like my cooking.
Germans don't joke.
Burt likes my cooking.
Get your bugs off the table.
They're spiders.
They're bugs.
Fold the next layer back
as you did the two before it.
Turn the napkin over.
Fold both sides back,
and over one another
about a third of the way.
Check for symmetry
and press the fold down well.
Are you doi ng this
on company time?
And insert your favorite silverware...
It's my anniversary.
And I want it to be perfect.
But that is not sexy.
No, but it is utilitarin.
And utilitarian is the new sexy.
I ran the trace. First name Usam,
last name Utsaev.
Any verifiable hits?
One.
Hey, Francis, do me
a favor and stick that
in the safe till tomorrow.
Mata Hari here's
got a big night tonight.
Yes, sir. Right away, sir.
"Sir"? Do I look like a "sir" to you?
From head to toe.
I'm surprised he didn't call you
"Your Majesty."
I like the ring of that.
I think I'd prefer "Your Majesty."
Was I ever that young?
Younger.
Walk me out.
How did the Oval Office briefing go?
Oh, you know.
The usual.
President wants to know
what's happening in Russia
the day before it happens.
How about you?
I heard that interview went well.
Fingers crossed.
You sure about this?
You know, once you start pushing
paper, there's no turning back.
I had the strangest feeling
when I was out last time.
I was homesick.
Homesick?
Can't you take something for that?
Sir! Sir!
We got a walk-in.
A defector, 10 minutes ago.
Here?
I guess he's not buying our cover.
Did you get his bona fides?
He's Russian.
He says he's FSB
but won't give us any more.
He's a strange guy.
How's his English?
Passable. Not great.
But if it got down to
the subtleties of English nuance...
Ted, Mike's gonna be waiting for me.
Yeah, and I got a plane to catch.
Come on, Salt.
No one can sort out a nutjob
from the real thing faster than you.
I got 25 minutes.
I got 26. Let's go.
Yeah, okay. Well, we'll decide
when we know more.
Who called Counterintelligence?
Not me.
Hey, Ted.
We're crashing the party.
Peabody.
Salt.
Please remove the hood.
Microphones are on.
Checking levels.
Bseline recorded.
Neural scan is up. Ready to go.
Ev.
Mm. Yeah.
Commencing audio
and visual recording.
Testing earpiece.
Interview has commenced at 1442.
You're married.
A husband must be a distraction
for a female intelligence officer.
Well, we're here to talk about you.
So, what is your name?
My name is
Oleg Vassilyevich Orlov.
I have cancer.
I'm moved.
A defector with cancer.
Are you selling secrets for chemo
or are you afraid of dying?
If I have gained anything
by damning myself,
it is that I no longer
have anything to fear.
Russia is also dying.
But unlike me, she's not dead.
Oleg Vassily Orlov,
shows up in 1993
in Novosibirsk Oblast, Siberia.
He was on Victor Barisovsky's
staff there.
He checks out as FSB, Ev.
Scan says he's truthful
on the cancer.
Prior to '93?
Russia was once strong, poWerful...
Nothing.
He doesn't eXist.
And she Will be again
when things have been set back
on the correct path.
I have somewhere I need to be,
Mr. Orlov,
so if you wouldn't mind
getting to the point.
I came here to tell you a story.
I don't like stories.
But I'll listen anyway.
In English, please.
Others are listening.
1975.
The Cold War.
In a gymnasium in Grozny,
a Soviet Olympic wrestler
named Sasha Fyorodovich
Chenkov
meets for the first time
the only female chess grand master
of her era;
Anka Nurekyova.
Within a month, they Were married.
And within a year, a child.
One month more,
the child was back
in the same hospital,
sick with fever.
And within days after that,
the child suddenly was dead.
Yes, a child Was dead.
And, yes, a child was buried.
But the Chenkov baby Was alive
and became the property
of another man.
A master spy Who had
devised the greatest plan
a Russian patriot
could ever invent.
A plan to destroy America.
It had all started
with an American named
Lee Harvey Oswald.
In 1959, he emigrated to Russia.
Three years later, he returned home.
But the man
who came back to America
was in fact a Russian spy
named Alek.
On November 22nd, 1963,
Alek became the first success
of the neW program
and a hero of the Soviet Union.
The spymaster Was now
given the go-ahead
to create many more like Alek.
Scores of agents,
males and females,
to be substituted for Americans.
I pledge allegiance to the flag...
At an abandoned monastery,
Chenkov and other boys and girls
learned English
long before they learned Russian.
Drilled in idiom,
idiosyncrasy and
ideology.
And by methods of rigorous physical
and psychological programming,
the spymaster
made warriors of iron.
Unquestioning and unbreakable.
Who crossed first?
Who crossed last?
You're killing me, man.
When does the good fairy come in?
Never.
It's a story without hope.
Chenkov was matched with the child
of a visiting American family.
There was an accident.
The family died.
Chenkov was sent to America
to live a complete lie
and to patiently await the day
to attack from within.
Day X.
The long-awaited mission is here.
Chenkov will travel
to New York City
to kill the president of Russia
at the funeral of
the American vice president.
Chenkov is KA 12.
"KA."
Cold War legend.
Highly trained
Russian sleeper agents
inserted into American society
to sabotage and assassinate.
Supposedly they'd wait years
to strike. Decades, even.
Mm. Supposedly.
What, you don't believe in moles?
I believe in moles, all right.
Just not the bogeyman.
Especially if the plan is
to kill their own president.
This guy's selling smoke.
Wrap it up, Ev.
So a Russian agent is going to kill
the Russian president? Is that it?
Mm-hm. Okay.
Thank you very much.
And what would you like
in return for that information?
I simply wish to help you do
what you need to do.
You're good.
The KA program
is brilliant bullshit.
But I'm officially off duty,
so you can tell the rest of your
little story to one of my colleagues.
Salt.
Yes?
The name of the Russian agent
is Salt.
Evelyn Salt.
My name is Evelyn Salt.
Then you are a Russian spy.
Truthful.
So far the fMRI scan registers truthful
on everything he's said.
Ted?
Call Protective Services,
make sure they find my husband.
I need to get to the phone.
Not after the neural scan.
I can beat that thing
five times out of six.
I am trained to, and so is he.
I need my phone.
I need to call my husband.
Let me call my husband.
Let me see it.
There's a reason he mentioned
my wedding ring, Ted.
They don't just blow up their cover
they blow up their whole cover life.
You know that.
Do you remember Henley's wife?
Yes, I do.
Speaker.
Please leave a message
after the tone. Thanks. Bye.
Honey, it's me. Please call me
as soon as you get this.
Okay, sweetheart?
As soon as you get this.
Godspeed, Comrade Chenkov.
Someone interrogate that
piece of shit. Someone
who enjoys getting answers.
Look, Ev, try to stay calm.
I'm not a goddamn Russian spy.
I didn't say you were.
Let's go up to my office,
we can sort this out.
No, no. We gotta go to
a secure location. Now.
All right.
Doesn't get any more secure
than this.
Ev? Five minutes.
Call Protective Services, find Mike.
I will.
This is bullshit.
Give us a sec,
we'll be right in.
I know we're heading
into your jurisdiction.
I'm just asking for five minutes.
No.
If I have to. You can't have
five minutes. I have to talk to her.
She's scared. Don't you see that?
I don't care.
There is a mole
in Russia house, Ted.
There is a mole. I am sure.
Please step in the elevator.
--Russian president, okay? So I'm
gonna ask you to step out of my way.
What the hell is that?
Sir.
I gotta pee.
Where do you think he went?
No one saw him coming
out the front.
Jesus Christ.
Here he is again.
No sign of him so far on the street.
It's two minutes ago,
before lockdown.
Anything clean on him?
We just got a match, sir.
It's May Day, 1981.
There's Brezhnev. And there...
Orlov.
That's him.
He used to be a heavyweight
once upon a time.
Get that photo out.
Every ticket counter,
airport, train station,
taxi dispatcher,
the whole nine yards.
Get me Medford on a secure line.
Yes, sir.
Top-right screen. Is that live?
Where is she going? Track her.
No one may leave the building.
Rink Petroleum, Security.
Yes, you have a woman to your left,
behind you. Evelyn Salt.
We lost the visual on her.
Damn it. Where'd she go?
We are on security lockdoWn.
Dave? It's Evelyn, is Mike there?
No, I'm sorry. He left after lunch.
Hey, happy anniversary, huh?
The stairwell.
Second floor.
What's on that floor?
It's empty, a security buffer.
Isolate and seal it.
Get her records to my handheld.
East corridor.
Notifying Metropolitan Police.
Kill the power to the elevator doors.
We got her.
Locking down all floors.
Security Protective Service
responding to threat.
All right. Get a tactical team
to meet me on the south stairwell.
Yes, sir.
Director Medford, sir.
Get me a side arm.
I'll call her back.
Shit.
Lost visual.
Where is she, Albert?
Talk to me.
Come on.
North hallway.
There, interrogation room,
bring it up.
Switch down, switch down.
Have you found him?
What the hell are you doing, Ev?
This doesn't look good.
Let's do it.
Move.
There's a tac team coming at you
in 30 seconds.
Get your panties off the camera.
Get where We can see you
so you don't get hurt.
Have you found my husband?
These boys aren't fooling around.
Please. I can't help you
unless you talk to me.
Call me when you find Mike.
SWeeping corridors
outside the elevator.
Put the masks on.
Situation is hot.
Open the door about tWo feet.
We 're gonna gas her.
Tac team in position.
Waiting for a go.
Is that absolutely necessary?
What, you want me to shoot her?
Get a medical team in place now.
We're ready.
Now.
Okay, on my count.
Three, two, one. Go.
Jesus Christ.
Where is she? Come on, guys.
Find her, Albert. Now.
Suspect has escaped.
There. Bring that up.
Stay with her,
she's crossing the street.
Pan the goddamn camera.
Back that up and zoom in.
We're looking for Michael Krause.
Freeze.
We're looking for her husband, Mike.
What the hell are you doing, Ev?
Wait, when was that?
No. No message.
Let's switch to the exterior cameras.
Michael Krause left his office
at the Smithsonian an hour ago.
Salt's apartment is 20 minutes away.
We can cover it,
but she won't go there.
She will if she's serious about Mike.
This stays in-house.
Okay.
Taxi!
U Street. I'll tell you when to stop.
Hi, this is Mike. Please leave
a message after the tone.
He's one of the world's
top arachnologists, Ev,
and as such, enjoys pretty much
unrestricted access
to the borders of North Korea.
So brush up on your bugs
and get to know him.
He's the perfect cover
to get us inside.
Mike?
Mike? Honey?
Hey, baby. Hey, baby.
It's all right. Shh.
It's okay. Where's Daddy?
Where's Daddy?
Come on. Come on.
Check for back eXits.
Go! Go!
Bedroom, clear!
Kitchen is clear.
Office, clear!
Living room, clear!
Everybody out. Sixty seconds.
Come here.
What are you doing?
She's not here.
No sign of the husband either.
Did it ever occur to you that
that Russian was lying?
Why'd she run?
I don't know.
Because you were gonna lock her up?
See it from her perspective.
Maybe her husband
is in some real danger.
Maybe, God forbid,
Salt is who she says she is.
"Maybe" is your department.
Mine is catching her
so we can find out.
Protocol is clear. We bring her in
or we bring her down.
Do you have any idea
who this woman is?
What she's done for this country?
Does that mean anything to you?
Should it?
Is your mom home?
No.
No? Can you do me a favor?
Yeah.
Hi. You baby-sit Burt for me?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah? Here's some money for food.
Hi, Burt.
What you doing?
You doing homework?
Yeah, math.
Algebra.
I hate math.
Hi. Nice to see you again.
You talking to me?
Yeah, I've seen you here before.
Yeah, I-- Yeah, I come here a lot.
You?
Oh, I'm working here.
At the museum.
I'm an arachnologist.
A what?
A spider hunter.
You look like one.
There are 40,000 species of spiders
in the world.
And that one is mine.
You discovered it.
Inside North Korea.
I named it Terrijoolsima peterbesti.
Do you get that?
No. Should I?
Peterbesti? I named it
after Pete Best.
The first drummer
before Ringo.
Best never was a famous Beatle,
but now he's a famous spider.
I got her.
She's heading north
towards the Metro station.
Ev!
She's eastbound,
in the Penn Quarter Mall.
Excuse me.
Will do. Headed there noW.
There she is.
All teams, southbound
toward the bridge. Box her in.
Circle around!
Salt! Stop!
Keep her in your sights!
Coming up behind you!
Fuck!
Keep back! Hold your fire!
Salt! Down!
Salt!
Spread out!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot, I'm innocent!
On the ground. Now!
Please don't. No!
Down! Salt! Do it now!
On the ground!
I have to find my husband.
Why'd you run?
To find my husband!
That's not a reason.
Don't shoot.
Stay back!
Last chance.
I'm innocent.
Somebody is setting me up!
Don't make me put you down.
Put the gun down!
Give yourself up!
Come on, Ev.
Do what he says.
We'll sort this out, I promise.
I gotta bring you in, Salt.
It's over. Face down.
Somebody's going to try to
kill the Russian president.
Do something about that!
That's what you should worry about.
There's nowhere to run! Quit now!
No, I didn't do anything.
Get back! No!
She's on a blue semi.
Route 1, heading north.
Get a roadblock in place now.
Metro Police on alert.
There she is. On the tanker.
Stop. Stop!
Ev!
You, my friend, have got
a mole in your group.
We don't know that yet.
I'd say she's a trained goddamn liar
and everything she's said
has been to protect her cover.
Well, why don't you tell me
how you really feel about it?
Get up on the shoulder!
Okay, take it down.
Shit!
Okay.
Ted, I know you're her friend,
but we gotta drop a net
on New York.
We gotta do it now.
Let's go!
Notify the Secret Service
on Matveyev's detail.
Tell them Salt might be
coming their way.
And if she is,
Orlov may not
be far behind either.
You seen this?
Salt spent time in Russia as a kid.
She was in a car accident with
her parents in '88. They both died.
They were teachers at
the U.S. Embassy for
the American children of the staff.
That's why we
put her on Russia
in the first place.
We need to get on a plane
to New York, tonight.
Send everything we've got on Orlov
to N.Y.P.D.
And here in New York City,
security has been beefed up
and preparations are continuing
well into the night
for the funeral of
Vice President MaxWell Oates.
Among the dignitaries attending the
service at St. BartholomeW's Church
is Russian president
Boris Matveyev,
who arrived here in Manhattan
earlier this evening.
Public transportation will experience
delays, with subway closures and...
Evelyn.
Look at me.
If there was a way,
I would kill them.
You shouldn't have come here.
What do you mean?
I don't understand.
Now they know who you are.
Who?
Evelyn.
I would accept
anything about you,
but I need to know.
So look at me. Look at me.
Just tell me, okay?
Just tell me.
I work...
I work for the CIA.
So you see, there's...
There's no future for us.
You're not safe with me.
I don't wanna be safe.
I know you,
and I wanna be with you.
I want to spend the rest
of my life with you.
Okay?
Okay. Okay.
Welcome to New York,
Miss Hernandez.
One night, a deluxe room.
Do you need any help
with your luggage?
Nope, I got it. Thanks.
I'll put these in the closet, sir?
Yeah, fine.
I do solemnly swear
that I will support and defend
the Constitution of the United States
against all enemies,
foreign and domestic.
That I will faithfully discharge
the duties of the office
on which I'm about to enter.
on which I am about to enter.
So help me God.
A solemn day here in New York City.
The funeral of Vice President
Maxwell Oates,
a former five-term U.S. senator
and Cold War warrior
whose greatest legacy
may be as architect
of the new era
of Russian-American relations.
Russian president Boris Matveyev
has journeyed from Moscow
to be an honorary pallbearer
to the man he's called
his greatest friend in the West.
What's the
security perimeter?
We're two deep inside
and we own this entire block.
And those are
Secret Service agents,
not CIA.
So relax.
That's real funny.
Didn't know you guys told jokes.
Detail, halt.
Forward, march.
Due to the funeral,
the 51 st Street station is closed.
Repeat: Due to the funeral,
What--? Hey, what's going on?
Hey! There's smoke.
Step back, step back.
Everybody, move out of the way.
Eleanor. Good to see you.
Thank you.
Boris.
Mr. President.
Hello.
Please be seated.
Stand by for president's speech.
Patrolling church exterior.
No one in or out the side doors.
Mrs. Oates.
Eleanor, Joe, Marissa, Donald...
After the president, the choir sings,
then Matveyev delivers the eulogy.
If your girl tries anything here,
it'd have to be pretty amazing.
I knew he would bring more to the job
than just his years of experience.
As vice president,
he showed the world the best
of what it is to be an American.
And today,
the world says goodbye
to a great man.
I'll check the back.
Lima Zulu 4, clear.
My friendship with Maxwell Oates
began in the unlikeliest of places:
Lima Zulu 4, come in.
Across the negotiating table...
What's your status, Lima Zulu 4?
We got two M lAs.
Lima Zulu 4 in the utility tunnel
outside the crypt entrance
and Lima Zulu 5.
I'm heading down to the crypt.
Some kind of trouble down there.
What's going on, guys?
Talk to me.
Subunits Lima Zulu 1, 2 and 3,
converge on the crypt. Repeat:
Converge on the crypt.
He made all the difference,
and for that,
he will always have
my respect and admiration.
That is what my friend Maxwell Oates
would have said.
What's going on?
Matveyev.
Get goddamn Matveyev.
Get the bomb squad in here!
Go, go!
Drop it!
Any MTs down here?
I see her.
Keep your hands up!
Shooter's at 12 o'clock.
Gun! She's got a gun. She has a gun!
Don't move!
Do not move! Do not move!
Keep your hands up!
Take her down, take her down!
Check for other weapons.
We need a medical crew
in the crypt immediately.
I can't feel a pulse.
Jurisdiction is clear.
This is New York City.
N.Y.P.D. has her.
She's going to 1 Police Plaza.
I'm not arguing jurisdiction.
We don't know yet, sir.
The shooter is CIA. I know her.
Yes, I'll be there.
I'll be on
the next chopper out.
Have your superior call the mayor.
Open up, guy, open up.
Back it up! Back it up!
Come on, guys. Keep moving.
Keep moving. Keep moving.
Let's go, let's go.
Hey, watch this guy, watch this guy.
Back up!
Keep moving.
Sir, back up!
Why? Why?!
Do you have any idea
how much blood is on your hands?
You're gonna rot in a hole, Salt.
I'm gonna see to it personally!
A dark hole!
Get ahold of yourself.
Get the door, get the door.
Get off me!
Back off, man! Back off!
That's it. Let's go.
Stand back.
Close it! Go, go, go!
Matveyev was declared dead
en route to the hospital.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
You were right about her.
She had the drop on me, Ted.
Why didn't she shoot?
Natasha.
Is that you?
Did they give you a new face?
I'm going home tomorrow,
Shnaider.
Home to Grozny?
My home is in Harrisburg,
Pennsylvania.
My favorite place there
is McDonald's on Fern Street
because it's near the river.
But I won't want to go there
anymore
because my mother and father
are dead.
Natasha,
will you miss me?
My name is Evelyn Salt.
Cop down, cop down! Hear me!
Get out of the car
with your hands on your head!
Right now! Hands in the air!
Hey, did you see that?
Hey, get those guys over here.
Get them over here to help.
Somebody help me get him out.
Help me get him out.
What college will you attend?
Princeton University.
Where will you work?
The Central Intelligence Agency.
Who will you trust?
No one.
Be very patient.
Remember your training.
Remember, you're not the only one.
There are many others.
All of you waiting to strike.
Yes.
And we will strike.
Together.
Yes.
Wait.
One day,
I will come for all of you.
Hello, Evelyn.
I'm Martin Crenshaw
from the U.S. Embassy.
We're very sorry about
your family's accident.
Rioters outside the U.S. Embassy
cheered their neW leader's words
and called on him to take strong
action against What they are calling
a state-sponsored act of terrorism
on the part of the U. S.
These riots are sparking
similar outbreaks
of anti-American protests
across Russia.
"We will strike back,"
says the new Russian president,
angrily condemning
today's assassination
by American intelligence officer
Evelyn Salt.
As the body of slain
President Matveyev is
on its Way back to Moscow,
anti-American riots
have erupted across Russia,
with bombings of U. S. diplomats'
cars in Moscow.
The Russian armed forces
have been put on high alert.
Responding to
a rapidly escalating crisis,
President Lewis has called for
an emergency White House meeting
with cabinet members, military
leaders and NA TO representatives.
Greetings, Comrade Chenkov!
When I saw you in Washington,
I almost ran to you.
You were not supposed
to get married.
Not unless it had
great tactical advantage.
I did it to seem normal.
When you escaped today, I thought:
"Even I could not have hoped
for so much."
You are my greatest creation.
You trained me well.
My husband, you have him?
I had to be certain.
But now you trust me?
Completely.
So tell me what's next.
Next, part two:
We seize control of
this country's atomic weapons.
How?
You'll see.
All right.
Are you ready to watch him die?
Give me the gun.
That would be too easy.
Satisfied?
I'm satisfied.
Comrades,
our sister has rejoined us.
Russia will rise from the ashes
of the greatest war
the world has ever seen.
And the world will hear us!
Will hear.
Welcome back to our family, sister.
Sister.
Russia has changed.
But our lives will not be wasted.
You're to meet an agent,
NATO uniform,
at a plane here.
Tail number N182SL.
Final instructions will come from him.
That's it.
After this, we go dark.
Radio silent.
You won't hear from me again,
my daughter.
Forever and ever.
Have you heard from Orlov?
Yes. Last word was "go."
Chenkov.
Do you remember me?
Did you miss me?
Shnaider?
How long have you been here?
I left Russia one year after you.
To Prague.
I've been the NATO liaison
to the White House for three years.
Colonel Edward Tomas.
And you are my attache.
Your ID.
Don't worry, we have plenty of time.
More importantly, our mission.
The bunker eight stories
below the White House.
That's where the president
needs to be.
How do we do it?
Don't worry, he'll be there.
That's my job.
I'll make sure he's there.
What's my job?
Do you remember, Chenkov,
when we were young and you
had to finish first in everything?
Had to be the best
at everything.
Though you knew you would
be beaten with a cane,
you had to finish first.
I remember.
Tonight you will finish
ahead of me again.
Tonight you will kill
America's president.
IDs, please.
Pop the hood and open the trunk.
I'll check the side.
Control, this is Hayes.
I have a Colonel Tomas
and a Major Vicek.
Undercarriage is clean.
Back's clean.
Colonel. Major. All clear.
You know the drill, colonel.
Shrapnel. A Serbian landmine.
They've spent more time looking at it
than the doctor did.
Step through, please, sir.
Turn around.
Thank you.
Step through. Arms out.
Patience is key.
I've been coming here for two years,
others have been here longer.
What others?
I don't know.
But you were the best of us
and I was the least.
There must be others,
here to finish what we begin.
Colonel Tomas.
Good to see you again.
Major Vicek.
Pleasure.
You'll have minutes to preview
NATO's point of view
before the meeting.
Now, Ted, your Russian
CI agent, Salt.
What can you tell us about her?
We think she may be a Soviet plant,
inserted years ago in preparation
for something the KGB called Day X.
A day marking the start of a large
strike against the U.S. and her allies.
This should be
the president now.
You have a big job, Chenkov,
but you can do it.
You still haven't told me
what your job is.
Home.
I'm going home.
Down! Take cover!
Get the president!
A gun! He's got a gun!
Get back!
Are you okay, sir?
Yes.
Goddamn it.
Geronimo is SOP, downward mobile.
Help, over here!
Get a medic! Get a medic!
I think I saw her.
You saw who?
Salt.
I think I saw her in the corridor.
The other NATO officer.
She's here.
Check.
Clear.
Move.
Go!
We may have a visual
on a second assailant. Evelyn Salt.
Repeat: Evelyn Salt on premises.
May be dressed as a NATO officer.
This is not a drill.
The White House is under attack.
If you are near an exit,
please proceed outside
in an orderly manner.
This is not a drill.
I need this hallway cleared
to the left, now!
Command, this is Jenks. I need
the PEOC bunker up and running.
If this was authorized
by the Russian government,
it is an act of war,
and we will respond.
If you are near an exit,
please proceed outside
in an orderly manner.
This is not a drill.
Clear!
Let's go, sir.
Alpha team!
Move, move.
Close it.
Please proceed outside
in an orderly manner.
This is not a drill.
Go, go.
Geronimo approaching
bunker door
in five seconds.
Clear.
Any chance she could follow?
My own men couldn't
get through that door.
Yeah, well, unfortunately,
she isn't one of yours.
Okay, go.
Stay until it's shut and sealed.
Geronimo secured.
Get me Director Medford.
Yes, sir.
Sir, I think we need to
seriously consider the possibility
that today, right now,
could be the start of Day X.
Mr. President,
Director Medford is up.
Marion, what's the situation?
It should be coming up
on one of your screens.
What you see there
represents temperature drops
in mobile missile units in Siberia.
It means the Russians are deploying
their missiles to the field.
And that's been confirmed
on the ground, Mr. President.
Mr. President, I strongly
recommend we go from
DEFCON 4 to DEFCON 2.
At least at our forward bases.
Do it.
And since the Russians
have deployed,
we need to look at
our own nuclear attack options.
It's not on the table,
it's not a deterrent.
Thanks, Marion.
We'll come back to you.
Sir.
The outer portal door is jammed.
No response.
And we just lost the feed
from most of our security cameras.
We're blind down here
and no one can enter this facility.
Command, our eyes are down.
We have a PEOC
outer security door malfunction.
Get out there now.
Seal this room.
Down that corridor. Secure it.
Victims are being taken to
George Washington Hospital.
Reports are coming in that there
are casualties at the White House.
This is President Howard Lewis.
Proceed with authentication.
Y es, Mr. President.
Ready to commence authentication.
Zulu.
Tango.
Echo.
Seven.
Niner.
Juliett.
X-ray.
Sierra.
Seven.
Alfa.
Mike.
Charlie.
Whiskey.
Five.
Six.
Tango.
Authentication codes confirmed.
It's all yours now, Mr. President.
God be with you.
Attack options and targeting
under your control, Mr. President.
Anders and Nablo,
what's your location?
Is the camera outside
this door working? Put it up.
Officer Dryer, what's your status?
Officer Dryer, come in.
Federal Communication Commission
is activating
the Emergency Alert System.
Who the hell's that?
That's her. That's Evelyn Salt.
She's in. Go to DEFCON 1.
Give me your side arm.
No, sir. Only Secret Service possess
firearms in the president's vicinity.
Screw protocol.
We got an enemy agent.
Protocol is protocol, sir.
And dead is dead.
Behind me!
I'm the national security advisor.
Not anymore.
Sit down.
Who are you?
My name, Mr. President,
is Nikolai Tarkovsky.
And unless you do
exactly as I say,
I will be the last person
you will ever see.
Shall we look at some
selective attack options?
Go to hell.
Selective attack options ready.
Ted?
Emergency action message
released by...
Congratulations, Comrade Chenkov.
You made it.
Why didn't you tell me?
I tried many times, but...
My loneliness was my only friend.
You weren't with us in Russia.
I would have remembered you.
I was a class ahead, comrade.
The brightest of any of Orlov's stars.
And now it's my honor
to launch the attack.
Excuse me.
Selective attack targets acquired.
Tehran.
Mecca.
Mecca? T ehran?
Part two of our plan.
Kill nine million people.
Enrage a billion Muslims.
America will suffer a painful death.
Permissive action links initiated.
Missiles arming.
Nuclear command
posts airborne.
Let me join you.
ICMs set to
maximum yield.
You know, when you first came
to Langley,
I didn't think I'd be able
to do it.
I didn't think I'd be able to
resist the temptation
to say something.
Then you met Mike and,
well, things changed.
Let me join you.
All these years right in front of me
and I never knew.
Let me join you.
I want to be with you.
The man
we thought Was dead has made
a resurrection that is miraculous.
President Matveyev is alive.
We 're going to Russia.
What you are seeing
are live pictures of
Russian president Matveyev
arriving at the airport outside
of MoscoW. This is astonishing.
According to his doctors,
President Matveyev's
mistaken death
is attributed to
a temporary paralysis
from a toxin
derived from spider venom.
A recap for those Who may
not have been following
the events of the day...
At least I was rig ht.
I had a feeling we'd lost you
back there in North Korea.
I could see how moved you were
by Mike's little white-knight routine.
You were supposed to
recruit him, Ev,
not fall in love with him.
That's why I told Orlov
to pick him up.
By the way, how is Mike?
Orlov is dead.
Well, that's good news.
Saved me the trouble.
I had to practically twist his arm to
get him to blow your cover at the CIA.
You see, he wanted you
to come out of this thing alive.
But you needed somebody
to take the blame.
I'm the patsy.
And I'm the hero.
Congratulations, Ev.
You're about to become famous.
Identity confirmation requested.
Identity confirmed.
Minuteman lll lCBMs' batteries
up to poWer.
Authorization, 9 percent.
Go!
Permissive action links initiated.
Trident submarines
at firing readiness.
Permission to launch.
Get down on the floor, now!
I said now!
Launch sequence aborted.
Systems restored.
Move, move, move!
Show me your hands!
Get down!
What is your name, sir?
I'm Theodore Winter, CIA.
Help the president.
Mr. President.
Mr. President, can you hear me?
Hold still.
EMT's on the way.
Make sure they got body bags.
At least seven.
She's wearing a vest.
I'll meet you in five minutes.
I wanna get cleaned up.
And I want her alone in a room.
If there are other KAs out there,
I want her talking.
She won't talk. She's trained not to,
no matter what we do to her.
If we're gonna
find these people,
we gotta do it.
Somebody already did.
At least some of them.
Barge on the East River.
Twelve dead, including Orlov.
Who did that?
Don't know. Forensics are on it.
I'm gonna get cleaned up.
I'll be right back.
Well, sir, you're injured.
Why don't you have a seat?
We'll take a look at you.
Are you okay?
Pretty good gash there.
Looks like you got a piece
of glass in there.
She killed someone else.
It's Winter. It's Ted Winter, sir.
You better get up here.
Check him. Check him!
Checking vitals.
I'm not getting a pulse.
I'm not getting much.
Sit down.
She's yours for 15 minutes
during the flight.
Give me your hands.
Then she's the FBl's.
Hey.
Why'd you kill him?
Because somebody had to.
What?!
By this, I take it you think
everybody is who
they say they are.
You knew something
was wrong the moment
Orlov walked in.
So did l.
We just didn't know
what it was.
Winter did.
Winter?
You expect me to believe
that Winter was gonna
launch the missiles
and you saved the world?
I would like you
to believe that, yeah.
That's a big accusation.
Well,
he's dead now
so he can't defend himself.
I guess you'll just have to
decide for yourself.
How many more like you
are there?
Like me?
None.
Like him?
More than you or I
can handle alone.
You really think
a trained Soviet agent
couldn't kill the Russian
president at point-blank
range if she wanted to?
Or you, for that matter.
I could've killed you
at the funeral
and I didn't.
You surrendered to me
because I gave you no choice.
You know better.
I had a choice.
If I did believe you,
and I'm not saying for a second
that I do, but if I did,
nobody else would.
Well, maybe you can
think of a way around that.
They took everything from me.
I'll kill them.
ETA, four minutes.
Bullshit!
We are approaching the Potomac,
heading due south and west.
Go get them.
Salt!
Circle back! Circle back!
New U.S. President Joseph Steppens
announced today
that with the death of
Natasha Chenkov,
known in the U. S. as Evelyn Salt,
all elements of the terrorist group
have been eliminated.
The announcement came
during his Moscow
peacekeeping visit
where President Steppens paused
to lay floWers
at the site of the 1974 plane crash
that killed his parents and sister
while on a tour of Russia.