(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(WAVES CRASHING)
(CHOIR VOCALIZING)
(SERENE ORCHESTRAL MUSIC)
♪♪
Now, I know what people
mean when they say,
"I wish I knew then
what I knew now."
(CHUCKLES)
Ain't that the truth?
Probably save me a whole
lot of pain and suffering.
That's for sure.
But I guess in the whole
scheme of things,
it's part of God's plan,
and alls we can do is
just roll with it...
(TENSE HORN MUSIC)
'Cause when it comes
right down to it,
God's running the
whole show anyways.
There ain't nothing we
can do to change that.
(ALARM BLARING)
Believe me. I've tried.
He'd say go left,
and I'd go right.
He'd say slow down,
and I'd smash on the gas.
Wasn't trying to hear
nothing he had to say.
Maybe that's why I had
to go through all this.
Maybe that's why things had
to happen the way they did.
Go, man. Go.
(ALARM BUZZES)
Someone once told me
that God sometimes needs
to use extreme measures
to deal with extreme
circumstances.
Guess I was one of those
extreme circumstances.
Sometimes I feel
like God took me
all the way around the block
just to get me next door.
I've seen and
experienced a whole lot
in my short time
on this earth...
loved, laughed,
cried, won, lost.
Through it all, I
can honestly say
I don't have too many regrets.
It's been a long,
long road, man.
Let me tell you.
Better yet, let me show you.
Let me take you all the way
back to the beginning,
when life was a little easier.
Well, sort of.
Look, y'all really need to
tighten up y'all money game
and stop playing around,
start thinking about
your future, feel me?
Yo, Miles, what's
there to think about?
We make money,
then we spend it,
and then we make some more.
(LAUGHTER)
Y'all think this
is a joke, man.
Yo, this ain't no game, man.
Look, I spend half my time just
looking at all the angles,
covering all my tracks,
so I ain't got no problems
with the IRS or nobody else.
What, you think I
don't get noticed?
Young dude in a $300,000 car,
$1-million home,
and mommy, daddy ain't
nowhere in sight?
Write a check, man.
(LAUGHTER)
Man...
Use a credit card once
in a while, you feel me?
All right, now, let's
get this money.
All right, man. Check
this out, Miles.
Say no more, partner.
I feel you, man.
I'm in it to win it.
Here's my cash right here.
Let's do it. What y'all got?
Get it poppin'. Yeah.
Holla.
Not light. Not light.
All right, it's all here.
It's looking good.
So listen, man, we gonna
come back here tonight,
chop it up, have a few drinks,
celebrate a little bit...
you know, do what we do.
Y'all go ahead and get
out of here, man.
I'll see y'all later.
Wik, you looking a little
light, too, over here, man.
You sure this is 75?
You crazy.
(GRUNTS)
Is that you, Caesar?
No, it's me, Ma.
Miles?
What a surprise, baby.
What are you doing here?
I just came by...
put some paperwork
in the safe.
I'll be right back, okay?
All right, sweetie.
Ah, what you cooking on?
Oh, some spaghetti.
Looks good. Mm-hmm.
I've always wanted
to go there.
What? Sandals Resorts?
So why don't you go?
Sure. Like it's that easy.
We're not all millionaires
like you, mister.
(LAUGHTER)
Stop it.
So how you doing, baby?
I'm good.
In fact, I'm extra good.
Extra good, huh? Yeah.
Well, Mr. Extra Good,
when are you gonna give me
a grandchild, huh, mister?
There you go talking
about these grandkids.
Look, Ma, I told you,
don't be expecting no
grandkids anytime soon.
You need to come
to church with me
and find yourself a
good woman there.
Church, huh?
What, Miles?
You act like you weren't
raised in church.
I took you every Sunday.
Yeah, I was bored every
Sunday too, though, Ma.
I mean, I'm sorry, but
the music was horrible.
The service was gloomy.
All those painted
pictures in the glass
and them spooky little
statues all over the place?
I don't know.
Miles...
I mean, really,
think about it, Ma.
Why do you think I really got
up on Sundays to go to church?
'Cause I knew we'd go to
that brunch afterwards,
and you know I
love that buffet.
(LAUGHS)
You go light a candle for
that one, Miles Montego,
because if I have to
start making you go,
you know I will, okay?
Mm-hmm.
You know that I will.
Uh-huh, I know.
Because you have a lot
to be grateful for.
I guess.
I tell you what, though.
What?
If you find one of those
nice young ladies down
at your church...
Mm-hmm.
You give them my number
and tell them I'm
down for whatev.
Whatever, huh? Whatev.
Love you, Ma. Love
you too, honey.
All right, I'm gonna
go on and go,
but tell Dad I said hello,
and I'll holler at
him later, okay?
Holler?
What is "holler," Miles?
See you later, Ma.
(SIGHS)
Have a seat, gentlemen.
You know what these are?
These are time and
expense sheets
for the Montego case,
and you guys spent way
more time and money
than I ever authorized.
Sir, we believe very strongly
that this crew is
one of the biggest
operating in this region,
with ties with several
other states.
This guy lives in a
house that's worth
more than all of our
houses put together.
One of his dozen cars
is worth more than all
of our cars combined.
He wears what we make
in a year on his wrist.
So we're working on this one
around the clock, Chief.
Well, you ought to
stop right there,
'cause that's your problem.
You're working around the clock.
Now, "around the clock" costs
this office a lot of money.
So what now?
We're gonna put a
price tag on justice?
This conversation is over.
I want a full progress
and status report
on my desk by the morning,
and I'll decide whether
or not to shut it down.
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪ ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Yeah-ah ♪ ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ All you rappers gonna wish ♪
♪ I never got in the game ♪
♪ 'Cause when I get
my first hit ♪
♪ Everything fittin'
to change ♪
♪ The whips and slang... ♪
(REVERENT STRING MUSIC)
♪♪
(TIRES SCREECH AND SQUEAL)
Come on. Come on. Out
of the way, man.
(DRAMATIC INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
♪♪
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SIRENS WAIL)
Got to be kidding me, man.
You in a hurry today, son?
You wouldn't believe
me if I told you.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Drivers license, registration,
and proof of insurance.
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
All right, gentlemen,
listen up.
Shh. And ladies.
Let me tell you
what we got today.
First up, we got Percy Taylor,
aka P-body.
He's the muscle of this crew
that we've been keeping
an eye on for some time.
Next up we have
Martin De LaFuente.
He is best friends with
the leader of this crew.
You can be sure wherever
you see the leader,
you will see Mr. De LaFuente
not too far behind.
Next we have Taylor Delmonico,
better known as "Wikki."
(LAUGHTER)
I know. I know. I
agree with you.
He's got a stupid name,
but don't be fooled.
He's just as dangerous as
the rest of this crew.
Next up, Chris Mayor.
Now, this guy is the number one
moneymaker for these guys.
Don't let his baby
face fool you either.
Last but not least,
we got the leader of this crew,
Miles Montego.
We have reason to believe
this guy is the biggest
drug trafficker
in all of northern California,
which is exactly why we
want to nail this guy.
He's smart, he's rich,
and he's good-looking,
but I don't necessarily think
I'd want him marrying
off to my daughter.
(LAUGHTER)
All right, listen up.
All kidding aside,
this entire crew
is considered to be armed
and very, very dangerous.
The way they work is very
tight and efficient,
and they do not like anyone
coming between them
and their money.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
To the money, baby!
ALL: To the money!
(THUMPING CLUB MUSIC)
Yo, let me get another
round of those.
Yo, Miles, let me holla
at you right quick, dog.
What's happening?
Yo, man, check this out, dog.
I know you don't like to hear
this kind of stuff no more...
and I get that dog, I do...
but your boy Jesse,
he owe me a whole
lot of loot, dog.
He been giving
me the runaround
for, like, the past two,
three weeks, homey.
All right, Marty.
This is the last time.
Like I told you before, man,
I don't want to hear nothing
about no what, when, why...
none of that, you feel me?
I feel you, boss. I'm
serious about this, man.
(PHONE RINGING AND BUZZING)
Nick.
How you doing?
I'm doing good.
I'm hanging in.
Not as good as you.
You got to learn to leave
some of that cash around
so we can make some.
Aah, stop it, man.
Anyway, look, it's the
Fourth of July weekend,
and I got a real great group
of people coming over.
I got steaks from Argentina.
I got lobsters from Maine.
All I need is for you
to come by and hang out
so I don't feel like I
only know old people.
Sounds good, Nick.
You know what?
I think I'm gonna
take you up on that.
Yeah? So you gonna come by?
I'll probably shoot over
there in about an hour.
Okay, good.
I'll see you in a
bit, then, okay?
All right, cool. Okay, good.
♪ 'Cause I'm ready
to give right now ♪
♪ And I'm ready for
love right now ♪
Yo, Miles!
My youngest and coolest
friend in the world.
You made it, man. Yep.
Hey, everybody, I told
you I got cool friends!
This is Miles. Man,
get out of here.
I'm trying to get like
you when I get older.
Old? Who you calling old?
Yeah, you putting
on a little, man.
I'm putting it on.
(LAUGHS)
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So who you with?
I'm solo today. Solo?
Well, just don't let money
run your life, Miles.
Otherwise, you're gonna end up
like these guys out here.
They look like they
doing all right to me.
I'm serious, Miles.
I'm asking one of these
guys to pass the chips,
and he wants to ask me
what the market
closed at yesterday.
Come on, man. Get a life.
I used to be the
same way, Miles.
But my career almost
cost me my family,
and it got to the point
where me and Karen...
we didn't know each
other anymore.
She said the only thing
that kept us together
was answered prayers
from her church group,
so I had to commit to going
to church every Sunday
as a family and one
date night a week.
I never figured you to be
a religious guy, Nick.
Well, we really don't like
that word "religious," Miles.
It's kind of like the
word "margin call"
in the stock market.
I'd prefer "man of faith."
All right, guys,
food is ready.
Oh, let's eat.
So can we all gather around
and have a word of
prayer before we eat?
First, I'd like
to thank you all
for coming to our home today.
We are so thankful and blessed
to have such wonderful
people in our lives
and so happy that you were
able to come over and join...
Honey, could you, um,
get to the prayer?
I mean, this is not the Oscars.
Everybody's starving.
(LAUGHTER)
Well, I was just about to
thank my wonderful husband
for putting this all
together, but...
I guess I'll just get
straight to the point.
Dear Father, thank You
for this glorious day.
It's easy to believe in
You, to have faith in You,
when we're blessed with
such beautiful weather,
such delicious food,
but most importantly,
for the friends and
family that we have
joining us to
enjoy this today.
For this and more,
we give You thanks.
Amen.
Amen. Amen.
ALL: Amen.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
Oh, that's Vanessa.
She goes to Bible study
every week with my wife.
Hmm.
Bible study, huh?
Mm, Bible study.
She come over a lot?
Come on.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
Miles!
Hey, ladies, how y'all doing?
I'd like to introduce you
to some of my girlfriends
from Bible study.
This is Shari... Hey, Miles.
Maylin... Nice to meet you.
And Sarah. Pleasure
to meet you, Miles.
You as well. And then
there's Vanessa.
Hi, how are you? How are you?
I'm good. Miles is
a very cool name.
Thank you.
Uh, can I get my hand
back before I call 911?
Rm 50'!
It's cool.
Hey, Dad, watch this!
So how do you know
the Halston family?
You know, Nick's my
broker and my money guy,
so we hang out
from time to time.
So young and into stocks.
So how do you know
Nick and Karen?
We actually all go to the
same church and Bible study.
Okay.
So you go to church
on Sundays, then?
Yes, Sir. Every Sunday.
So, uh, what was
your religion again?
I guess I'm "Christian,"
but, you know,
we don't really like
to call it that.
Right, right. You like
to say "men of faith."
Or in your case, it would
be "woman of faith."
Exactly, so you know exactly
what I'm talking about, right?
Well, yeah, doesn't everybody?
What church do you attend?
Oh, well, right now, I'm
kind of in between churches.
Between churches, huh?
Yeah.
In between churches.
All right, well,
what was the name
of the last church
you attended?
I really don't remember,
but I'm sure I could call
my mom and she, you know...
You are so playing with
me right now, Mr. Miles.
All right, you caught me.
But I do go to church on
Easter Sundays with my mom,
and on Christmas, I mean, if
that counts for anything.
Look, I grew up in
a Catholic church,
but, you know, I don't know...
I never really stuck with it.
I think I just didn't feel
comfortable in my church.
Well, you should find a church
you do feel comfortable at
and stick with it.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
Wow, I guess we shut this
joint down, didn't we?
We sure did.
So you think somewhere
between school
and saving the world,
you could make a little time
so I could see you again?
Please, Miles, my life
is not that serious.
But yes, I'd love to.
Great. Hold on.
Give me your phone.
Okay, here we go.
(CAMERA CLICKS)
I got a good idea.
How about we not play
the "who can wait the
longest to call who" game?
Yeah, I don't like
that game either.
Okay, I got a better one.
How about we play the "who
can call who first" game?
Ah, see, I'm into that.
I'm into that, too.
Yo, it's definitely
time for me to go.
Yeah.
So, uh, I guess I'll be
talking to you tomorrow?
Soon?
Not if I talk to you first.
Yo, we in San Jose,
not San Francisco.
Yo, you good?
(LAUGHTER)
(LAUGHS)
Good morning, Vanessa.
Mmmmm.
See what she talking about...
(LAUGHS)
Good morning, Mr. Miles.
Look, I know it's
a little early,
but, you know, my Sundays
start when the sun comes up.
Just wanted to say
that I really enjoyed
meeting you yesterday,
and hopefully I look forward
to hanging out with you again.
Well, have a blessed
day, Mr. Miles Montego.
By the way, I win the game.
(LAUGHS)
Peace.
(MURMURS INDISTINCTLY)
(PHONE BEEPING)
(PHONE VIBRATING)
Hello?
Well, aren't we quite the
busy bee at 6:00 a.m.?
(LAUGHS)
You're awake? Ain't
no question.
My days usually start at
5:00 a.m. anyway, so...
5:00 a.m.? What are you?
Like, a Baker? Nah.
You know, I deal a lot
with the east coast,
so the time difference
gets me up.
Okay, big shot.
So how about it?
Want to come to
church with me today?
You know what?
I got a gang of stuff I got
to get done by tomorrow,
but I'll definitely
take a rain check on it
if that's all right with you.
Of course.
Yeah, anytime.
Well, I actually got
to run right now,
but maybe we could talk later?
How about we leave the
maybes out of this
and just get together
after we done doing
what we both got to do?
Not only does he get to flaunt
all that money around town,
but he gets the
pretty girls, too.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
Is that a little jealousy
I'm sensing, McDaniel?
Oh, no, it's not jealousy.
When I slap the
cuffs on this guy
and he gets 25 to life
while I'm home all warm
and cozy in my bed,
that's when you'll
see some jealousy.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
You live here by yourself?
Well, yeah, unless
there's some roaches
I don't know about.
Miles, this place
is beautiful.
Thanks, babe. I'm
glad you like it.
Like it?
I love it.
So how many bedrooms
does it have?
Uh, last time I
checked, eight.
Eight bedrooms for one person?
Now, why would you buy a
house with eight bedrooms?
I needed some extra
closet space.
I'm playing. I'm playing.
You so wrong.
I'm joking. I'm joking.
Oh, even the kitchen is sick.
You cook?
I do a little something.
You know, maybe you come
over one night and...
put something
together for you.
Okay.
So this big house,
for one person?
I don't use all this space.
I usually end up sleeping on
the couches half the time.
(LAUGHS)
Yo, I always pass this place,
but I've never
actually eaten here.
Yeah?
I hope you're hungry,
'cause the food
here is amazing.
(PHONE RINGS AND VIBRATES)
Oh, my goodness.
No, I know. You got to get it.
I got to take this one.
I'm sorry.
Yo.
Hey, what's buzzin', cousin?
T, what's going on, man?
What's happening?
I'm just trying to make a
dollar out of 15 cents.
You know.
So, hey, did you fire
off that package?
Oh, yeah, man, that
should be on your desk
by tomorrow morning,
probably around 10:00.
Man, I like your style, Miles.
So you all locked and
loaded on your end, right?
Oh, yeah, for sure, man.
Everything's set up just the
way we planned it, man.
I got y'all hooked up, man,
so I'll see y'all in
a couple of weeks.
One love, baby.
What do you make
of this, Brian?
You ever hear of
this guy T before?
Can't say that I have.
Where'd the call come from?
Cell phone outside of Ohio.
Could be one of his clients,
maybe even a connection.
That would be my guess.
This is good, right?
Yeah.
Real good.
Do you have to go?
'Cause I would
totally understand.
Oh, no, no, no. Know what?
Matter of fact, let me turn
this phone off right now
so we can enjoy our dinner.
Don't you dare, Miles. No,
no, it's okay, really.
Yo, it's clearly business.
Like, I would never
ask you to do that.
You know what? That's dope.
I mean, you know,
a lot of women,
they'd be like, you know,
"You're being rude,"
or, you know, "Could
you turn that off?"
Anyways, so did
the stock market
get you all of this...
the house, the cars,
the jewelry...
or did you, like, run into
some amazing family fortune?
Actually, I like
to keep my hands
in a lot of different things.
You know, right now, I
got a string of shows
that I'm doing right
here in the Bay.
Matter of fact, I'm
doing three shows.
I got one in Frisco,
one in Oakland,
and I'm doing one right
here in San Jose.
Wow, Miles, that's...
that's exciting.
You know, I was
thinking, um...
I don't know... maybe
you might want
to come hang out with me
for a couple of the shows.
You ain't got to go to all
of them, but you know...
Mr. Miles, are you asking
me on another date?
Why, I think I am,
Miss Vanessa.
I'd love that.
Well, then it's a date.
Look, Miles, I really had
a good time tonight.
You know, I really did, too.
I'm not just saying that!
Me neither. I had
a great time.
Yo, I still cannot believe
you spent all this money
on this big house
to live in it by yourself.
Really? I don't know.
Well, maybe one day,
I'll find somebody
to, you know, fill it.
I mean, does it really
make a difference
if I get the house first
and then find somebody
special to share it with?
I guess not. No.
Silver convertible, huh?
Yep. And?
You want to hear
a funny story?
Sure.
A few weeks ago, I'm driving,
and I come to this stop sign,
and I look over at
the intersection,
and I see this convertible,
but what really caught
my eye was this...
this beautiful woman
that was driving.
I mean, she had, like,
long, beautiful black hair
kind of like yours.
And she was wearing
these shades...
these really hot shades.
I mean, I was on her.
I felt like I had
to catch her.
So I... you know,
I get in pursuit.
I'm holding up traffic.
I'm bobbing and weaving
in between cars.
Anyway, to make a
long story short,
I get pulled over
by the police,
but you know what really,
really bothered me?
What?
Was that I didn't get
a chance to meet her.
I didn't get a chance
to know who she was.
What kind of car did
you say this was?
Um, hmm.
A silver convertible Sebring.
(TRIUMPHANT STRING FLOURISH)
(STRING-HEAVY PUNK MUSIC)
Oh, my gosh.
What? Oh, my gosh.
Yo, he's in the store.
The guy you just met?
Yes, he's in the...
Miles? Where?
Don't say his name so loud.
He's gonna hear you.
Girl, he is so fine.
Ooh, he sure is.
I so hate you right now.
Well, don't just stand there.
Go over there and talk to him.
We all know he
didn't come here
to buy a Jesus bumper
sticker for his Bentley.
BOTH: Go.
Hey, you. Hey.
What are you doing here?
You know, I was in
the neighborhood.
Thought I'd stop by
and surprise you.
Well, I am surprised.
I love the spot.
What kind of store is this?
Thank you.
We are a faith-based
product store.
Okay.
So I guess there's a
pretty big market
for this church stuff, huh?
That's right.
Aw, they look really
cute together.
She looks really happy.
Yeah, I know.
Her last boyfriend
was such a jerk.
We have, like, a
bunch of T-shirts
and, you know, books, and CDs
that are Christ-like themed.
Stuff like that.
And these are all
Christian artists?
That's right.
This dude right here looks
like a real rapper.
Come on, Miles. He
is a real rapper.
He just, you know,
raps about the Lord.
Nah, nah, nah. That's
not what I'm saying.
I mean, look, this dude
looks like a gangster,
and the music that was
playing when I came in
made me feel like I
wanted to stage dive.
(LAUGHS)
Yo, you never listened
to Christian music?
Nah.
I mean, well, you know,
my moms used to play,
like, Elvis Presley
gospel albums on Sundays,
but other than that, nah.
Well, yo, I am about
to hook you up
with some really, really
hot Christian music,
hold on a sec. I'ma
get you some CDs.
Okay.
T-bone...
Bone-a-fide.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
What you got for me?
All right, so I hooked you
up with some really hot CDs.
Trust me, you have to
listen to this, Miles.
You're really gonna like it.
If you say so.
How much I owe you?
Consider it a gift
from me to you.
Okay. I love gifts.
Oh, look, look, I got
a birthday party
that I'm going to tonight.
You want to go?
A party? Yeah.
I might be able to,
you know, swing it.
All right. How
does 7:00 sound?
All right, cool, you
pick me up at my spot,
and then you can meet my family.
Meet the family?
This is getting
serious now, huh?
Oh, please. They don't bite.
Sure about that?
Yes.
All right, I'll
see you at 7:00.
Oh, my gosh.
Mad cute, right?
He's gonna meet my
parents tonight.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Seriously, is someone
gonna get that?
(SCOFFS)
Hold on.
Have Mercy!
I got to call you back.
Hi. Hey, how you doing?
I'm Alyssa.
I'm Miles.
I'm here to pick up Vanessa.
Figures.
Vanessa, somebody's
here for you!
Mom, have you seen
my phone charger?
Hey, you must be Miles.
Hi, I'm Julissa, Vanessa's
younger sister.
Do all you guys
yell around here?
You're killing me right now.
Yeah, pretty much.
Loud as can be.
Well, it was nice meeting you.
You too.
Hello, I'm Miguel
Leon, and you are?
How you doing, Mr. Leon?
I'm Miles Montego.
Wow, Miles Montego sounds
like a secret agent name.
Man of mystery.
Well, sorry to disappoint,
but no mystery here.
What you see is what you get.
Honey, this is Miles.
He's here to pick up Vanessa.
On.
You're Miles?
Uh, yeah, last time I checked.
Nice to meet you, Mrs. Leon.
And what church do
you go to, Miles?
Wow.
Well, um, I'm kind of looking
for a new church right now.
On.
And what is it that you do?
Honey, enough
drilling already.
Well, I just want to know
who our daughter's
hanging out with.
All right, well, I see
you've met everyone.
We're gonna head
on out, you guys.
Good night. Love
you, Dad, bye.
Good-bye. It was
nice meeting you.
(HEAVY DANCE MUSIC)
♪ I want you to
possess my body ♪
What's happening?
Could it really be?
Is it Miles Montego?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What up, baby?
What's happening?
Montego, wait a minute... I
thought you left the country.
You lucky you
showed up, homey.
I was gonna go straight
to your house from here.
You know I wouldn't have
missed that for nothing, man.
Appreciate that.
Fellas, I want y'all to meet
my new lady right here.
This is Vanessa.
Vanessa, that's Chris. Hi.
That's Wikki, Percy, and
this one right here,
that's my right-hand
man, Marty.
Hey, Marty.
It's such a pleasure
to meet you guys.
You know, Miles talks about
you guys all the time.
Yo, let's go inside
and get some drinks.
Man, let's do it right.
Come on.
Thank you, baby. Yeah.
Don't let me see you
around here again!
You all right, baby? Yeah.
Miles!
Bootz, man, you always
up to something, man.
What's going on?
Nothing much, man.
All right. All right.
What's up, big homey?
Good to see you, man.
Looking sharp.
♪ Abracadabra ♪
♪ Fill me and
possess my soul ♪
♪ Your life is so beautiful ♪
(LAUGHS)
Hey, what's up, Miles?
Hey, Jerry, what's
going on, baby?
You what's up.
Hall-of-faming it this year.
You know how we do it, man.
Definitely, man.
Congrats to you, Jerry.
Really, man. Really.
Hey, thanks, Miles.
Oh, Vanessa,
this is Jerry Rice,
one of the greatest receivers
to ever play the game.
Jerry, this is my girl, Vanessa.
I know who he is.
Pleasure to meet
you, Mr. Rice.
Oh, "Jerry," please,
and it's my pleasure
to meet you.
I want to wish you
guys a good night,
but also, Miles, I don't
want you to forget
about those tickets
for that show.
Oh, Jerry, come on,
I got you, baby.
And, Vanessa, it's
really nice to meet you.
Pleasure meeting you.
Yo, babe, you know Jerry Rice?
Oh, yeah, Jerry's
a good dude...
Babe, my dad is gonna trip out
when he finds out
I met Jerry Rice!
Hey! How are you?
Ladies, I want y'all to
meet my baby, Vanessa.
Vanessa, this is Nicole,
Jasmine,
that's Simone,
and this is Shanice.
Nice to meet you guys.
Hey, yo, what's good, Chico?
Let's have some shots, man.
Ah, not tonight, Marty, man.
I'm driving.
Not tonight? Man, it's
my birthday, homey.
I mean, that's why we
all here celebrating.
I mean, just one shot, man.
All right, maybe later.
Psh, man, I remember
that one time
he was hanging out the window
with guns blazing
like a madman like...
(IMITATES GUNFIRE)
Hey, Vanessa, you
don't even know.
Miles Montego?
You're sitting with
a real legend, Ma.
I seen my man...
Let's go get that shot on me.
Yeah, yeah.
♪ Supersonic, cybertronic ♪
♪ All up on it ♪
♪ No need for that
gin and tonic ♪
So, Vanessa,
is everything they say
about Miles true?
About what?
You know.
Oh, wow.
Um, I'm not trying to keep
you girls in suspense,
but I wouldn't know.
You mean you two haven't
slept together yet?
Look, we're just trying to,
you know, take it slow.
That's all. Nice and slow?
Are we talking about
the same Miles here?
(LAUGHS)
So what, y'all
trying to make me
look like a psycho or something?
She ain't trying to
hear all that, man.
Does she look like
she's impressed?
Do me a favor. Tone it down.
Tone it down, man.
Just saying, man. Just saying.
You went out there, talking
all that stuff, man...
I'ma finish his drink.
Wow, that was...
quite an evening.
Babe, I am so sorry.
I thought they'd act
way cooler than that.
You don't have to
say you're sorry.
Everybody has a past.
We all do.
Yeah.
You know you can talk to me
about anything, right, baby?
Yeah.
Look, I got a past, baby.
One I'm not
particularly proud of.
And if you were to
hear about it...
I don't know, I...
I feel like you might not
want to see me no more,
and that kind of
scares me, babe.
Miles, what's the matter?
Look, I know this great
little restaurant.
Great coffee.
Best pie in town.
I mean, if that's all right.
Sure.
Let's go.
What's wrong, Lydia?
Please go to sleep.
Sleep?
How can you sleep when
our daughter's out
with that... that...
That boy.
He's a boy, Lydia.
Well, I got a really bad vibe
from that so-called
boy, Miguel.
He doesn't seem her type.
According to you, she'll
never have a type.
Please go to sleep.
(SIGHS)
Now, promise me you're
gonna have an open mind
and not freak out on me.
I promise.
What'd you think about
my friends tonight?
They looked like gangsters
and drug dealers.
That's because they are, V.
I mean, they're not,
like, Mafia or anything,
but they live that lifestyle,
and to be honest, I used
to live just like them.
In fact,
they all used to work for me.
Work for you?
Doing what?
Here we go.
Thank you.
Folks, let me know if there's
anything else you need.
Yep. Thank you.
Work for you doing what?
I used to be a drug
dealer, Vanessa,
and those guys
you met tonight,
that was my crew.
I mean, basically, we was
into any and everything.
Wow, Miles, I don't...
I don't even know what to say.
Look.
I don't talk about it
'cause I'm not proud of it.
I mean, I don't
know how I did it.
I don't even know why I did it.
I just did.
But I can honestly say
I'm a better man
from all of that.
Wow, Miles.
Well, about your
friends, baby,
the Bible says that bad company
corrupts good character.
You really think
this is a wise idea,
still hanging out
with these guys
when they do what they do?
Those are my friends, V.
I mean, those dudes...
they're like my family,
and I can count on
them for anything.
Look, I've been trying
to tell these guys
there's other ways
to make legal money.
I mean, I spent the last
two years of my life
just trying to wash and
shake all that off.
Shake it off, huh?
Look, I'm not this
perfect guy, V,
but I'm trying.
Miles, that was a mouthful.
To be honest with you, babe,
it almost sounds
like a testimony
of someone who's had their
life turned around by God.
Thank you
for even wanting to
share that with me.
Am I okay with it?
I don't know about all that.
Does it make me want
to pull away from you?
No.
If anything, it...
makes me want to
get closer to you.
Would it be wrong to say
that I'm falling
in love with you?
No, baby,
'cause I'm falling in
love with you, too.
(BOTH SIGH)
Well, since you just had
the floor, Scarface...
Oh, I'm Scarface now, huh?
Yeah, it's my turn now.
Baby, do you know what
"equally yoked" means?
What do you mean, like
eggs or something?
No, silly.
In the Bible, God refers to
our spirits as equally yoked,
so in order for you and
I to be equally yoked,
it means that we have
to feel the same way
about each other and God
and put Jesus in the center
of this relationship.
Now, do you think
you can do that?
I mean, it sounds like
a whole lot, babe,
but I care about you enough
to give it a try.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
Good morning, sunshine.
So it's the big
weekend, eh, Miles?
I hope so.
So these are your events?
Yeah, well, you know,
I got a few partners,
but yeah, for the most part.
Well, we'll say a prayer for
you and your shows tonight.
Thanks, Mr. Leon.
I appreciate it.
(FUNKY DANCE MUSIC)
♪♪
Tams, what's going on?
How we looking?
Everything's great.
The groups are checked
in to the hotel.
Sound check's going
on right now.
You got yourself a sellout.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh! 'My
(LAUGHTER)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
♪ Gave you my money ♪
♪ Gave you my time ♪
♪ Why you want to hurt me, girl? ♪
♪ Are you serious? ♪
♪ I'm just curious ♪
♪ Why you want to hurt me, girl? ♪
♪ Just because you're
not for real ♪
♪ Why you want to hurt me, girl? ♪
♪ Just because you're
not for real ♪
♪ Why you want to hurt me, girl? ♪
♪ Never ever had another ♪
♪ Put the pedal to the metal
and burn rubber on me ♪
♪ Charlie, oh, no ♪
(LAUGHS)
Look at you.
"Yo, I'm Miles Montego.
"Ain't no question.
"What?
Oh, hold up."
Who that supposed to be?
You.
That is not how I act,
talk, or any of that.
You were amazing today.
Amazing.
Like, honestly, I
was so impressed
with just the way the
whole show came together.
Really? Yeah.
I'm glad you liked it, baby.
Loved it.
Well, we should get some rest,
'cause tomorrow's
gonna be a long day.
Yeah.
(GROANS)
Where are you going?
Oh, see, you can
lay back down,
see, 'cause, Mr. Montego,
you have the sofa tonight.
Me?
I have the King-size bed.
(LAUGHS)
Love you.
Don't forget to
say your prayers.
(SIGHS)
Oh, boy.
(FRENETIC DANCE MUSIC)
♪ My God is awesome ♪
♪ He can move mountains ♪
Baby, these are mad hot.
You like those? Yeah.
What about these?
Oh, I'm into that, too.
You like them? Yeah,
those are really hot.
I'll take them in every color.
Yo, we should take
a little break
and actually get
something to eat.
Yeah? You hungry?
I know a spot up here.
It's nice.
Key word "break."
I'm not done.
I'm not done shopping.
Ain't that something? Miles?
Celine.
Where have you been?
I've been calling and calling.
I just... I been
rippin' and runnin'.
You ready, babe?
Oh, I'm sorry.
V, this is Celine.
Celine, this is Vanessa.
Oh, how do you do?
Fine.
Celine's a old friend of mine.
Really?
Okay, well, babe,
the kids are ready,
and, you know, the
jet is waiting.
Wheels up at 6:00.
It was nice meeting you.
(CAR ALARM BEEPS)
For real?
Kids waiting?
Wheels up at 6:00?
Where'd you get all that from?
I watch the E! Channel.
Did you sleep with her?
Yeah.
I shouldn't have even asked.
So why did you?
Women.
(FUNKY DANCE MUSIC)
♪♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
Get out the car, homey.
Get out the car!
Don't do it.
Open the door, Jesse!
Get out.
Miles, don't...
Miles, don't do it.
Miles! Lock the
door and get down.
Oh... my!
Come on, punk.
Ya! Yo, yo, ya, ya-
(GRUNTS)
Get up, homey.
What's up, Dag?
Get him, Miles!
Back up.
Is there a problem here?
Jesse, is there
a problem here?
Man, just shoot him, Miles!
Shoot this punk!
Nah, nah, nah.
Ain't nobody gonna
get shot tonight.
What we gonna do is, Jesse,
you gonna get in your car, and
you gonna get out of here.
You hear what I'm
saying to you?
Get in your car and
get out of here!
This ain't over, punk.
See you around, homey.
Let's go, man. Let's go.
Meet me at the spot,
and make sure nobody
follows y'all.
(TIRES SCREECH)
Baby.
Baby, are you all right?
Are you okay? Babe!
No, I'm not okay, Miles.
Who were those guys? Were
they trying to kill you?
Look, baby, just relax.
Just relax. It had
nothing to do with me.
Look, I was just trying
to defuse the situation.
That's it.
It had nothing to do with you.
It was between Martin and
whoever that guy was.
So what am I supposed
to do, babe, huh?
Leave him out there alone?
Let some dude come
blow his head off?
Is that what you telling me?
Don't think so, baby.
So you're just willing
to give up everything
including your own life
for something that had
nothing to do with you?
Yeah.
And they would do the
same for me, baby.
Look, a few years ago,
this whole thing would have
turned out a lot different.
I was just trying to get us
out of there safe, baby.
That's it.
Really?
Would you like to tell me
why there was a
gun in your car?
Babe, it's like I told you.
Whenever I do shows like this,
there's always large
amounts of cash around.
You know that! You see it!
Look!
What do you want me to do?
Listen, I know this whole
situation and everything,
it's all new for you,
but you got to
understand, babe,
when it comes to protecting
you, my family, my friends,
I'll do anything, babe.
You understand that?
I thought I was
gonna lose you.
Come on, baby.
Really, Miles.
I don't ever want to feel
like that again, ever.
Promise me I won't
ever lose you.
I promise.
I ain't going nowhere.
You understand me?
Give me your hands.
Heavenly Father, we
come before You.
We thank You, Lord, for
getting us through
a hard day of work
but most of all for
protecting us.
Lord, we ask that
You would continue
to show Miles that You are
always there with us.
In Your name we pray.
Amen.
Whoo! Yeah!
Happy Birthday, baby.
Smile. Thank you.
Love it. But you guys...
you guys really didn't
have to do this.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Now, Miles, we got you
a little something.
We hope that you'll
not only use it
but enjoy it as well.
Wow.
I mean, y'all really don't
have to do none of this.
This is too much
for me right now.
Go on, Miles. Open it.
I know! Hurry up.
Okay, okay.
Let me... let me open this.
Get out of here.
You guys got me my own Bible?
Look, it's got my name
on it and everything.
Let me take a picture.
Love it.
Miles, you need to
understand something.
We have done everything we can
to raise all of our children
in the ways of the Lord.
Now, the Bible says
that we should pray
for our children's spouses
from early in their lives.
Well, we have been praying
for a godly man for Vanessa.
Miles, are you that godly man?
I don't know.
How come I can't I figure out
who you really are?
Bet she has no idea.
I see you're working
late again.
I told you we had a
solid case, right?
So if they're working late...
We got to be working late.
If there's something there,
you'll find it.
This ain't for me.
Babe, after church tomorrow,
you want to go to the movies?
About tomorrow...
I don't think I'ma
be able to make it.
(SHORTS)
What's the matter, babe?
You all right?
No, Miles, I'm not all right.
Look, just tell me
what the problem is.
There is no problem, babe.
I just got some things I got
to take care of tomorrow.
That's all.
We all have a lot of
stuff we have to do.
You're always gonna have a lot
of things you have to do.
Look, I'm gonna put
aside the fact that
my entire family
is expecting you
and that, hey, I'd
actually like you
to come to church with me,
and what I'm really
concerned with
is what the real issue is.
Why don't you just tell me?
There's nothing to tell.
Really? There's
nothing to tell?
Look, I'm not even buying that.
What is so bad about
going to church?
God don't want somebody like
me in his church, okay?
Ridiculous.
What are you smiling about?
Look, babe, I'm not trying
to belittle your feelings.
Look, I'm sorry,
but you're just so off.
Like, so off.
And to be honest, I'm
a little relieved
'cause I thought
you were actually
keeping something from me...
something ugly.
Well, don't be getting
all happy just yet.
I haven't told you
why I feel this way.
It doesn't matter.
God doesn't care about what
you've done in your past
or what you're in the
middle of right now.
He just wants you
to come as you are.
You sure about that?
I'm positive.
Look, the Bible says,
"What causes a man to
gain the whole world
and lose his soul."
Baby, I don't want you
to lose your soul.
Once you really get to
know God and His Word,
you'll see that that book
is better than life,
better than the cars,
better than the money.
For a man like you,
even better than...
Better than what?
Look, please, better than sex.
(LAUGHS)
Yes, I said it.
Yeah, this must be a
great book, 'cause...
Hey, watch what you saying.
Ain't too many things...
Hey, we're talking about God.
Better than anything.
Don't get crazy.
♪ I love you like
Sunday morning ♪
You ready, babe?
I guess. It's crazy, though.
This is like a sold-out show.
This is the best
show on earth,
and it's free.
♪ Of the feeling that I get ♪
♪ It's a Sunday kind of love ♪
♪ Like a classic gospel song ♪
♪ You just have to sing along ♪
♪ I wish that every
day was Sunday ♪
♪ Oh, happy day ♪
♪ The darkness gave away ♪
♪ To the light that shine ♪
Come on, babe, let's go.
♪ Everything will
be all right ♪
♪ It makes me want
to say thank you ♪
Hey. Good morning, Vanessa.
How you doing today?
I'm good, Jerry.
Jerry, this is my
boyfriend, Miles.
Hey, pleasure to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
This is Jerry.
Hey, I'll seat you
with your parents.
Follow me. Thank you.
Am I supposed to tip this guy?
No, baby, he doesn't get paid.
He's a greeter.
This is his way of
serving the Lord.
♪ I love you like
Sunday morning ♪
♪ It's a Sunday kind of love ♪
♪ Between the two of us ♪
Hi.
Hey, Mommy.
Hey, Miles, good to see you.
Good to see you too, Mr. Leon.
How you doing, Mrs. Leon?
Good morning, Miles.
♪ I wish that every
day was Sunday ♪
(SOULFUL ORGAN MUSIC)
♪ See, I'm so glad the
troubles don't last ♪
Who's that?
That's Pastor Galley.
He's our worship leader.
He's a pastor?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
ALL: ♪ The troubles
don't last ♪
♪ I'm so glad ♪
♪ So, so glad ♪
ALL: ♪ Troubles don't
last forever ♪
♪ If it's a song You want,
Lord, I'll sing it ♪
♪ And if it's an offering,
You know I'll bring it ♪
♪ 'Cause You are worthy ♪
♪ So, so worthy, worthy ♪
♪ Worthy of all praise ♪
♪ Lord, my life for You,
I'm gonna live it ♪
♪ And every ounce of praise ♪
♪ I'm gonna give
it to You, Lord ♪
♪ You're so worthy, worthy ♪
♪ Worthy, worthy
of all praise ♪
♪ And as I sing ♪
♪ I will sing of
all Your glory ♪
♪ Tell the world Your story ♪
♪ Of Your strength,
Your power, Your love ♪
♪ And as I live ♪
♪ I will build my
world around You ♪
♪ I'm so thankful,
Lord, I found You ♪
♪ I forever will pray ♪
Babe, everybody doesn't
have to see that.
Oh, my bad. My bad.
Here.
How much are you giving?
I don't know. About that much.
That's not enough?
(LAUGHS)
Babe, that's plenty.
Let me explain how this whole
offering thing goes later.
♪ And as I live ♪
♪ I will build my
world around You ♪
♪ I'm so thankful,
Lord, I found You ♪
♪ I forever will praise ♪
You smile and behave.
You heard me?
All right, I'll see
you in a little bit.
Amanda, what's up, baby?
Pastor Galley, how
are you today?
I'm wonderful. How are you?
Fantastic. It was
an awesome worship.
I loved it. I had a
great time, too.
The Spirit was really
moving, right?
Oh, it was in me.
It was everywhere.
I'll see you on
Thursday at rehearsal.
Don't be late. Yes,
I'll see you there.
All right, Ma. See you.
Hey, Pastor Galley.
Vanessa, how are you, Ma?
Pastor Galley, this is
my boyfriend, Miles.
Miles, Pastor Galley.
Miles, you got some
church in today, huh?
Yeah, it wasn't what
I was expecting,
but it was good.
That's right. That's right.
So you really, like,
a pastor, huh?
I mean, like a real pastor.
As opposed to, like, an
imaginary, cartoon pastor?
(LAUGHTER)
Nah, that's not
what I meant, man.
I mean, you don't really
look like a pastor.
I don't, huh?
So what's a real pastor
supposed to look like, Miles?
I don't know, man. I
mean, look at you, man.
Clothes, your jewelry...
You're kind of tight to death
yourself there, Miles.
Yeah, but I don't drive
no Lambo, Pastor.
The Lambo, huh?
I recall pulling
into the parking lot
and passing a four-door
black Bentley
that I've never
seen here before,
and I'm assuming
that's yours, man.
Yeah, but I ain't no pastor.
True that, but the last
time I read the Bible,
it said nothing about
style being a sin.
Kind of goes back
to that old saying
that you cannot judge a book
by its cover, you heard?
Yeah, I dig.
So what made you want
to be a pastor anyway?
Well, God had a calling
on my life, Miles,
and as much as I tried
to avoid that call,
I couldn't avoid it anymore,
and here I am.
He's got a calling
on your life, too.
On everybody's life.
But you got to
answer the phone
when He calls, you dig?
A calling, huh?
A calling. I tell you what.
We'll talk more about
that in the future.
I'd love to see you around
here a little bit more.
All right.
You have a blessed
Sunday, Vanessa.
Such good worship
today, by the way.
Praise God. Miles...
Pastor. It was a pleasure.
Pleasure's all mine.
Hope you two brought
your appetites,
because your Mother cooks
enough for an army.
It looks good too, Ma.
So you got Miles
to go to church?
Mm-hmm. Just this Sunday.
I cannot believe this.
Vanessa, you are an
Angel from heaven.
You just don't know
how hard I've been
praying for this boy.
Whoo, you and I both.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, let's say grace.
Dear Lord, thank
You for the food
we are about to receive
for the nourishment and
health of our bodies,
for our wonderful son, Miles,
and for bringing the beautiful
Vanessa into our lives.
She is truly an
Angel from heaven.
In Jesus' name we pray.
ALL: Amen.
Now, Vanessa, honey,
don't you be afraid to
crack the whip on this...
(LAUGHTER)
If he gives you any trouble,
you just let us know.
We'll straighten him out.
All right, I like
the sound of that.
Let's eat.
(SWELLING STRING MUSIC)
♪♪
Man, what took you so long?
Sorry, big dog.
Sorry? Let me tell
you something, man.
Don't ever have me waiting
like that ever again.
You hear me? Yeah, I hear you.
Man, here.
125k, man, nice and neat,
just like you like it.
All right, here, man.
Get out of here.
Get out of my car.
All right.
See you soon, Martin.
Yeah, whatever.
Got you.
(ENGINE RATTLES)
Babe, I got a question.
What's up?
Have you considered, you know,
taking that walk of faith
during the altar call?
Babe, I ain't
gonna lie to you.
What?
I'm still trying to figure
this whole thing out.
I mean, I know there's a God,
and I'm supposed to act a
certain way and everything,
but to be real, babe,
I'm still researching this
whole salvation thing.
I mean, I just don't
want to dive into it.
Does that make any
sense to you?
Yes, it makes perfect
sense, babe.
I get it.
I will say this, though.
What will you say?
I feel real good
when I'm in church.
Yeah? Yeah.
I mean, it feels like
everything's moving
in the right
direction, you know?
But then I get to thinking,
if God is this all loving,
all seeing, all being God,
then why does He allow
things to happen
like rape, murder,
war?
Like, that part I don't
understand, babe.
I see you clearly have been
giving this a lot of thought.
Well, yeah, I mean,
just the other night,
I'm sitting in bed, and I'm
watching this program,
and this Muslim
speaker's speaking,
and he's talking about
the book that they read,
the Koran.
Okay.
He's basically saying that,
you know, they believe
that Jesus existed
but that he was
only a prophet,
and then he started getting
into all these scientific facts
that exist in the Koran
that, you know, scientists
didn't even discover.
I thought it was...
I thought it was really,
really interesting.
All right, well, how
did it make you feel?
To be honest?
I don't know,
it's a lot to swallow, babe.
All right, well,
whenever you're ready.
Whenever you're ready.
Hopefully sooner
rather than later.
Merry Christmas, everybody.
ALL: Merry Christmas.
What a special time
of year this is.
To think that God
would become flesh
and dwell among us,
that ought to fill
our hearts with Joy.
(LAUGHTER)
Vanessa, honey, it was so
nice meeting your family.
Thank you. You're
all so beautiful.
And with such pretty
daughters as you three,
it's no wonder your father
turned to the Lord.
Man must spend a lot
of time on his knees.
Amen.
Look, Mom, Dad, me and V
want to give y'all a
little something.
We know y'all been
trying to, you know,
get away for quite some time,
so we got y'all something
we think y'all might like.
Wait a minute,
son, what is this?
Open it up.
Okay.
(GASPS)
Sandals Resorts.
Look at this place.
Oh, my gosh, it's the one
we saw in the commercial.
Thank you.
Look at this, honey.
Son, this is beautiful,
but you shouldn't have.
Aw, come on, Pop.
You and Mom been trying
to get away for years,
so this is our gift to you.
Baby, I love it,
and I'm so glad to finally
get to go to Sandals.
Sandals, here we come.
Merry Christmas, Mom.
Oh, Merry Christmas.
(PHONE VIBRATING)
Listen to this.
"How much more pleasing
is your love than wine,
"sweetness as the
honeycomb, my bride.
"Milk and honey
under your tongue.
"Your two breasts
are like two fawns.
"I slept, but my
heart was awake.
"Listen, my love is knocking.
"My head is drenched with dew.
"I've taken off my robe.
"Must I put it on again?
My lover thrusts his hand
through the latch opening."
Now, that sounds like
late-night HBO to me.
Hold up.
If you could hear how
you just read that...
I read it how it's reading.
That's what it is.
Babe, okay, are
you trying to say
that the Bible says that
it's okay to have sex?
Babe, I don't know what
the Bible is saying.
I guess I'm just trying
to figure this all out.
That's all.
Babe, I can almost assure you
that these people that
they're talking about
are married.
Now, the Bible says you can
totally enjoy your
spouse sexually.
Now, how did you interpret it?
You know what?
I'm sorry I brought it up.
Just forget about it.
No, no. That's a good thing.
It's good that we
discuss these things.
Just forget it.
It's important to discuss
the Word of God.
Drop it.
Really? Really?
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
(HEAVY RAP MUSIC)
Y'all in trouble now.
Uncle Freddie.
♪♪
Miles, my man, man.
Marty, what's up?
What's up, baby?
Where you been at, man?
Ain't seen you
around in a minute.
Just been rippin'
and runnin', baby.
You know, rippin' and runnin'.
Hey, you all right, Miles?
Don't I look all right?
I mean, not really,
but if you say so.
Hey, where's Vanessa at?
Man, I don't know.
She's around somewhere.
She just ain't here
with me, you know?
So what, you ready to party
with your boys tonight,
then, or what?
You know what?
Let's do that, man.
Drinks are on me tonight, man.
I ain't been with
y'all in a minute.
Let's do what we do.
Let's do it.
Keep them coming all
night, beautiful.
Okay, I'll be back.
Baby, thank you.
Hey, yo, Miles, what's
going on with you, man?
For real? With what?
With what?
With you, homey.
I mean, we don't ever
see you around no more, dog,
and when we do,
it's never without Vanessa.
You say that to say what?
Look, dog, I'm
just saying, man.
You ain't nowhere near
your normal self,
and to be honest
with you, man,
me and the fellas is just
concerned about you, man.
That's all.
Look, I just need a
little vacation.
That's all. I'm good.
Look, dog, me and
you go back, man.
We go back further than all
these cats right here,
and if there's one thing
I know about you,
the only thing that can get you
off your square is a girl,
so if you need to
talk about it,
for real, I'm right here
like I always been, man.
I'm all ears, but if not,
then that's cool too, man,
'cause I got something else
that can get your mind
off that, you feel me?
Hey. Yo, ladies!
Ladies, come on in here.
Let's get this thing started.
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Come on, you can catch
me in a big body ♪
♪ S-class with chrome spinners ♪
♪ Pulling up to the
club with a brim ♪
♪ Iced and a chinchilla ♪
♪ Stacking the skrilla
in a legal way ♪
♪ Rock stadiums from Nicaragua
down to San Tropez ♪
♪ Hey, and I ain't even
got a curse in my raps ♪
♪ I keep it gully while
I'm spitting this fire ♪
♪ On hot tracks ♪
♪ My skills speak
for themselves ♪
♪ I'm like a young
LL back in the day ♪
♪ When he was rocking
them bells ♪
♪ The Sly Stallone
of the microphone ♪
♪ I'm old school like Special
K, turbo, and ozone ♪
♪ What, rep for my people
like I'm Che Guevara ♪
♪ With a derby and linen
pants plus a guayabera ♪
♪ Oh, I'm so sick they
sending ambulances ♪
♪ To resuscitate the mic
from my verbal thrashing ♪
♪ Cash advances and
top-brand fashion ♪
♪ Guaranteed to rock the spot ♪
♪ And keep the party
peeps dancing ♪
(MELANCHOLY ORCHESTRAL MUSIC)
♪♪
I got to go.
Why, Miles? Why?
God help me.
(PHONE RINGING AND VIBRATING)
Miles, it's your mama.
She's very ill.
Hurry up and get down here.
No. No.
"But if any of you
lacks wisdom,
let him ask of God"...
I'm so sorry guys.
It's Miles' dad.
Hello?
Vanessa, it's Caesar.
Hi, Mr. Montego, how are you?
Not good.
It's Miles' mom.
She's very ill.
Thank God you're here, son.
Hey, Pop, how you doing?
I came as soon as I could, Ma.
How you doing?
Hi, baby.
I'm sorry.
I ruined the trip. Trip?
What you talking
about, "trip"?
Don't worry about that, okay?
You just concentrate
on getting well.
How you feeling?
(GROANS)
She's under a lot of
medication right now.
Let's let her rest.
Don't worry, son.
It'll be all right.
Okay.
Miles, I need to talk to you.
Come on.
Well, son,
it's not good.
Not good at all.
How?
How does somebody go
from perfectly healthy
to dying overnight?
It wasn't overnight.
Apparently, your Mother
lived with this for years,
and you know your
Mother and doctors.
There's no way to know.
Your Mother always thought
that an aspirin could
fix everything.
So what do we do now?
They said the best thing to do
is to try to help her
feel comfortable.
But, Miles,
right now, I need you to
be strong for your mama,
okay?
Yeah, Pop.
Good.
(INDISTINCT PA ANNOUNCEMENT)
Miles, I'm so sorry.
I can't even imagine
what you're going
through right now.
Look,
V, I want to explain
something to you.
Miles, you don't have
to explain anything.
I know this is not
the right time.
It's not the right time.
Just listen to me.
I don't know what's
going on right now,
but I've never felt like this.
It's like...
it's like I'm feeling guilt
and shame.
It's like... I don't know...
I don't deserve anything.
All at the same time.
Then I get confused
about what I think
God is telling me.
I never feel like I'm doing
the right thing, babe.
I want you to
understand something.
Look at me.
I want you to know that
nothing happened that night.
Miles, you don't have to...
Hey, babe, just...
I love you.
I love you,
and I would never do
anything to hurt you.
Is that the whole
truth, Miles?
No question, babe.
I believe you, baby.
Vanessa.
I need you to do
something for me.
Anything you ask me to,
I'll do it.
Don't cry.
Just listen.
I need you to take
care of Miles for me.
I know there's a reason
why you two met.
God has something
special for you two.
God knew
that the only way
to his heart...
(COUGHS)
Was through a woman like you...
beautiful, wonderful,
godly woman.
Please don't ever
give up on him
if you really love him.
I do.
I really do.
Baby.
Now, I want a big wedding
and lots of grandbabies, okay?
Ma, don't do this right now.
You're gonna be fine.
No, Miles, I'm not,
so I need you
to keep seeking the Lord.
(COUGHS)
He's the answer
to all your problems.
He's got big plans
for you, baby.
Big plans.
My love.
She's really tired right now.
Let her get some rest.
It's been a long day.
(MONITOR BEEPS)
Ma.
Ma!
May the Lord now welcome Julia
to the table of God's
children in heaven.
With faith and hope
in eternal life,
let us assist her
with our prayers.
Eternal rest grant
unto her, O Lord.
May her soul and the souls of
all the faithful departed,
through the Mercy of God,
rest in peace.
Amen.
Looks like a nice party.
Have a little respect
for the dead, Brian.
You want to send some flowers?
I just don't see the point
in keeping an eye on him
while he's here.
I don't buy this.
You don't get to be where
a guy like that is
and just flip it off.
This guy's smarter than
the average crook.
This could all be
a smoke screen.
Maybe.
You believe in God, Brian?
Oh, don't go getting all
religified on me, Jason.
(LAUGHS)
Do you go to church?
Yes, Sir.
Every week,
wife and kids, Bible study,
the whole nine yards.
You do, huh?
Why didn't I know that?
You never asked.
Miles?
I just wanted to tell you
that I am so sorry
for your loss.
Your Mother was a
beautiful woman.
I saw the look on her face
and felt the warmth of her heart
when she saw you in church.
I'm sorry if I
haven't always been
the easiest person
when it comes to you.
I want you to know I'm
always praying for you.
Remember, you may not
always understand
why God does certain things,
but I can promise you
that it's all part of one
big plan for your life.
Just know that this
family loves you.
Thank you.
That means a lot to me.
Hey, Mrs. Leon.
Hi, Miles.
I hope you have an open
heart and mind about this.
I really love your daughter.
I mean, she means
the world to me.
I want to spend the rest
of my life with her.
I want to marry her.
I mean, with your
permission, of course.
It'd be an honor
to have you as part of
this family, Miles.
Do you think you're truly
ready for this, Miles?
Well, I know I got a long
way to go, Mrs. Leon...
...but no one's gonna
love or treat Vanessa
the way I can,
so, yeah,
I'm ready.
(SULTRY SAXOPHONE MUSIC)
♪♪
Uh-oh. Okay, okay.
Loving it. Look at you.
Thank you, baby.
So you ready for your
big birthday surprise?
Yes, but seriously,
you're crazy.
Come on, we could
have done something
super simple like dinner.
It ain't too late.
We could always cancel.
You know, Jimmy's
is open 24 hours.
That's what we won't be doing.
Come on, let's go.
Where are we?
You know this is crazy, right?
Who does this?
Okay, babe, is
there steps or...
Come here. Come here.
Okay. Okay.
I'm... hey.
Right here.
It's Windy.
Happy Birthday, baby.
Oh, my gosh. Are you crazy?
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Oh, my... is this for real?
Hi, how can I help you, Sir?
I'd like to see
the flight plan
of that last private jet
that went out, please.
I'm sorry, Sir.
That information
is confidential.
It's okay.
I'm Mr. Confidential.
(JET ENGINE ROARING)
Look, babe.
Look out this window.
Know what I see?
What?
I see God, baby.
You do?
I mean, only He could
have created all this.
I look, and I see a
world with no limits.
With the right
drive and hustle,
anybody could have anything
and everything they want.
It's been a rough couple
of months for me,
but I learned a lot.
Yeah?
Like what?
Well, I learned
I'm not as in control of things
as I thought I was.
I learned that life
can be taken away from
you just like that.
I learned that God is...
really and truly in
control of all of this.
But the most important
thing I learned...
What?
Is that I never
want to be alone.
I never want to be away
from you again, baby.
(GASPS)
Vanessa Leon,
will you marry me?
Miles,
ain't no question.
(TIRES SCREECH AND SIRENS WAIL)
Freeze! Freeze!
Show me your hands!
Don't move!
Put your hands
behind your back!
(SLOW FUNK MUSIC)
♪♪
Get him! Hold it!
Hold it right there! Freeze!
Show me your hands!
I got him! I Got him!
Freeze! Freeze!
Put your hands...
♪ Sitting here ♪
♪ Guess I didn't make bail ♪
♪ Got time and a story to tell ♪
♪ Started when I was
nine years old ♪
♪ Woke up and Daddy was gone ♪
♪ I started hustling ♪
♪ They couldn't
tell me nothing ♪
♪ Fronting in the hood,
trying to be somebody ♪
Y'all always trying to
blame it on me, man.
I told you not to... Shut up!
Shut up!
We in this position here.
We got to wait for
Miles to get us out,
and that's it.
We here.
(PHONE RINGING)
Yo.
Hey, yo, Miles, man, listen,
don't say nothing, okay?
Just listen.
We got hemmed up, dog.
Me, Percy, Chris, Wikki...
all of us, man.
We locked up right now.
You got to be kidding me.
Man, does is sound
like I'm kidding, dog?
Listen, and to top it off,
it's the feds that got us.
The feds?
Yeah, man.
They set our bail at
$112 million right now.
All right, what you
want me to do, man?
Look, dog, I need you to get
us out of here right now.
All right, I'm on it.
So what happened?
Man, they came at
us hard, Miles.
I mean real hard...
feds all over the
place, SWAT cars, guns.
They took us all down in
different places, man.
It was not good.
They charge you
with something?
What's the charges?
Man, the indictment had all
kinds of stuff in it, man.
Still trying to
figure it all out.
What about the spots? I
mean, was anybody dirty?
Did they find anything?
Nah, man, but I'll
tell you this...
they tore my spot
up real good,
and thank God the only thing
they found was a gun.
Mine too, man.
They left that joint
a mess, dude.
Yeah, man, them dudes
bust the door down, dog.
They act like they was looking
for bin Laden or something, man.
Man, check this out, man.
They got some of my people,
but I got my lawyer on it.
Says he won't know
nothing for a few days
till he gets the reports back,
but they was pressing
us really hard, Miles.
Pressing? About what?
About you. About me?
Man, look, this guy
told me I could get up
and leave right then and there
if I told them something
juicy about you.
Yep.
Told me the same thing.
This Agent McDaniel dude?
He got it real bad
for you, Miles.
Yeah, that's real talk, Miles.
Man, they offered to take me
right back to my house, man,
and forget like any of
this even happened.
What'd you say?
Man, I asked them if I could
get ESPN in my cell, man.
(LAUGHTER)
Yeah, what about you?
You really got to
ask me that, Miles?
After everything
we've been through?
I think they was just
fishing for something
and trying to use me
and all the fellas
as bait to get at you.
I'm buggin'.
My bad.
(SIGHS)
Just stay out of their way
till we can figure this out.
I feel you.
Man, done.
Thanks a lot, man.
Thank y'all, man.
Hustle it up, man. Come on.
So not one of these guys
gave us anything on Miles.
Not one, Sir.
I'm surprised.
I thought that little guy
Chris would have talked.
Maybe there's nothing
to tell, Chief.
What are you saying?
That Miles is some
squeaky-clean choirboy now?
Maybe.
Just get this guy.
Let's move out.
Man, Pastor, I'm sorry.
She's usually on
time for everything.
Hey, don't worry
about it, Miles.
Listen, we spend half our
days waiting on the Lord
and the other half
waiting on our wives.
Hey, don't tell her I
said that to you, though.
I won't. I won't.
(PHONE VIBRATING)
Excuse me, Pastor. I
got to take this.
Hello?
Miles.
It's Alyssa.
Hey, Alyssa, what's up?
Vanessa's been in
a car accident.
What happened?
Her car was hit by a truck
that ran a red light.
How is she?
She's not well, Miles.
She's still in surgery.
Mr. And Mrs. Leon?
Well, here's where
we're at, folks.
She has internal bleeding,
suffered severe head trauma...
she's in a coma.
Is she gonna be
all right, doc?
I mean, she gonna live, right?
Only time will tell.
We've done all we can for her.
We just need to see
how her body reacts
to the procedures and
hope for the best.
Hope?
You say hope, and
they say pray.
I mean, can we all get on the
same page here at least?
Take it easy, son.
Take it easy?
You said you've done all
you can for her, doc.
Yes, we have.
You sure about that?
Miles, please, calm down.
It's in the Lord's hands now.
"It's in the Lord's hands."
I'm tired of hearing it's
in the Lord's hands.
I heard that when
my Mother died.
"It's in the Lord's hands."
Look, I'm sorry,
but somebody else
needs to step in and
take the wheel here,
'cause it seems like
He is out to lunch.
Look, I promise you
I'll do everything I
can to save her life.
You have my word.
Look,
I'm sorry.
There's somebody I
got to go talk to.
Miles, wait.
Good.
I'm glad You're here,
'cause we got some serious
issues to talk about.
First of all, You took
my Mother from me,
and that just about killed me,
but I kept my mouth shut
and let that one slide.
I've done some bad things
to people for a lot less,
but I've been trying to give
You the benefit of the doubt.
I've been faithful.
I been going to church,
reading your precious
little book.
I even drop stacks of
hundreds every Sunday
in that little Velvet
bag they pass around.
I've changed.
I'm a changed man,
can't you see that?
Oh, my bad.
Of course You can.
You see everything, right?
So what's the problem, then?
What do You want from me?
I know I haven't made You proud.
How could I with all this
mess I got going on?
What happened?
What happened to all the things
I've been reading about?
Grace, forgiveness, Mercy?
Where was the Mercy
for my Mother?
Now You want to take
Vanessa from me?
Nah, that ain't gonna
happen, big guy.
Look, I'm a stand-up guy.
If anybody needs to
pay for they sins,
then let it be me.
Please just leave
everybody else out of it.
Just take me!
I'm ready for whatever
You got coming.
You want to send me to hell,
book the flight!
But please.
Please.
I'm begging You.
Don't take Vanessa from me.
Just tell me.
Look, whatever You
want me to do.
Tell me what You want me to do
to spare her life.
I didn't mean a word
I just said, Lord.
I'm sorry for yelling
at You in Your house.
But, God, You got to know
this is rough on me.
Just let me know
what I got to do
to make this right.
I'll do it.
I surrender, Lord.
I surrender.
(TRIUMPHANT ORCHESTRAL MUSIC)
♪♪
(SIRENS WAIL)
Okay, Miles,
get out of the car.
Get out of the car.
Put your hands in the air
right now.
Is there a problem, officers?
Turn around!
Walk backwards.
Put your hands on your head.
Down to your knees.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
House is clear.
(MONITOR BEEPING)
All right, Miles.
Now, let's just see
what you're made of.
Mr. Montego,
my name's Agent Carey, and
this is Agent Stokes.
We're with the IRS C.I.D.
You know what that means?
No,
but I'm sure you're
about to tell me.
IRS criminal
investigation division.
All right, yeah, and?
And, well, Mr. Montego,
that means that we have a
series of questions for you,
and we would appreciate your
full cooperation with them.
Do you know these guys, Miles?
Yeah, they're friends of mine.
How good of friends?
Old friends.
We went to school and
grew up together.
Why?
Is that all you did
together, Miles?
What's that supposed to mean?
It means that they've been
indicted on drug charges.
It means that we found
these check stubs
that show large payments
made from your company
to each of these individuals.
It means that this
looks like you're in
business with these guys,
and if you are,
you're in a deep mess.
First of all, I'm a
legitimate businessman.
Man, I don't have any illegal
dealings of any kind.
All right, so I wrote
them some checks.
Last time I
checked, gentlemen,
that's still legal
in this country.
Well, that depends on why
the checks were issued
in the first place.
I'm a concert promoter.
They invested in a
few shows of mine.
Do you know your friends'
source of income?
No, and I don't really care.
Well, I hate to tell
you this, Miles,
but their problems are quickly
becoming your problems.
Oh! Yeah?
What kind of
problems are those?
It's a problem
when you use illegally
gotten funds
to fund even a legit business.
That makes all of its
gains and assets
up for grabs to us.
Make me believe you, Miles.
I really want to believe you.
Look, does it look like I'm
trying to hide anything
from you or anybody else?
Miles, we're giving
you a chance here
to save yourself a long
and dirty investigation
that, in the end,
can only hurt you.
Fellas, if y'all want
to go down this road,
let's do it.
I got a CPA that handles
all my financial affairs.
I'm sure, together
with my lawyer,
they can answer any questions
that y'all might have.
So if y'all gonna charge and
arrest me with something,
I suggest you go
ahead and do it
so I can bail out and
go on with my day,
but if not,
I'd appreciate it if you
showed me the door.
You have any luck with him?
Nothing.
Looks like it's bad guys: 3.
Good guys: 0.
Why don't I give it
just one last shot?
All right.
Okay, everybody out.
Let's go! Out!
Real smooth, aren't you?
You got those guys wondering.
But I think you're
as dirty as sin.
Yeah, sin.
Isn't that what you talk about
in those sweet little
church meetings of yours?
Whatever, man.
I'm not a churchgoing man,
but I take guys like
you very seriously.
So let me give you the
raw and uncut version.
I'm gonna walk out of here.
I'm gonna give you
a few minutes
to gather your thoughts.
Then I'm gonna come back,
and it's gonna be
time for confession.
Hey.
You know confession.
(LAUGHS)
I think he's clean, Chief.
Who knows?
He just might be that
choirboy after all.
We probably should
just let him go.
(SOMBER ORCHESTRAL MUSIC)
♪♪
I'm gonna say a prayer.
Don't laugh at me, okay?
You know I'm new to this.
Dear God...
what can I say?
I give up.
I finally figured out that
You are who You say You are
and I can't do
nothing without You.
I know that You run
this whole thing
and that everything I have
really belongs to You...
including Vanessa,
even my mom.
I'm humbly asking You...
no, I'm begging You, God,
please,
please spare her life.
Please allow her to
come out of this coma
and be healthy again.
I'm here to do or say
whatever You want me
to say or do, God.
I know I don't have
much to offer.
But what I do have is Yours...
including my heart.
I want You in my life.
I want You in my heart, Lord.
I promise...
I promise to be as
faithful to You
as I possibly can.
I love You,
and I pray all these things
in Your name,
Christ Jesus.
Amen.
♪ You're my first ♪
♪ You're my last ♪
♪ You're my future ♪
♪ And my past ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ You hold the key ♪
♪ To my heart ♪
♪ Even death would
have a hard time ♪
♪ Keeping us apart ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪♪
(INHALING)
(BOTH GROAN)
(GROANS)
Mm...
V?
(GROANS)
You awake?
Hey, guys, she's awake!
Come here! Everybody come in!
V.
Good morning, church.
ALL: Good morning.
Listen, if you
have your Bibles,
say, "Got it."
ALL: Got it.
Good. James 1.
This is what the Bible says.
"Consider it pure Joy
"whenever you face
trials of many kinds,
"knowing that the
trying of your faith,
"the testing of your faith
develops perseverance
in your life."
And we should allow
perseverance
to have her work in our life,
because God uses that to
complete us and to mature us.
And I'm looking at a
family here this morning
who went through
a severe trial,
a beast of a trial,
the Leon family.
And you know, church,
remember, we all
prayed for them,
and we asked God
to do a miracle,
and God did answer our prayers,
and Vanessa woke
up from her coma,
and I tell you, I just
want to thank God.
To God be the glory. Amen.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
Yes.
Hallelujah.
To God be the glory.
Now, finally the
Bible says this,
that today is the
day of salvation,
that now is the
acceptable time
to receive the
Lord Jesus Christ
as our savior.
And I'm just going to open up...
I'd just like you to
all stand with me,
and I really sense
that there may be
someone here today
that would like to come
forward and kneel before us
and say, "Yes, I'm going
to open my life up"
"to the Lord Jesus Christ.
I'm confessing Jesus
as my Lord today."
Anyone want to come,
kneel before us
and open their life
before the Lord?
Excuse me, Pop.
Where are you going?
I'll be right back.
I made a promise to
somebody I need to keep.
♪ I surrender ♪
♪ Yes ♪
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Lord, I surrender ♪
♪ I surrender ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Yes ♪
♪ Lord, I surrender ♪
♪ I surrender all that I am ♪
♪ And all that I've got ♪
♪ Everything I am ♪
♪ Everything I've got ♪
♪ Lord, I surrender ♪
Yo, fellas, I
hope all of y'all
are in the best of
health and spirits,
and I hope y'all are
staying out of trouble,
'cause I know how y'all
like to wild out.
Ah, man, I can't tell you
how much I Miss y'all.
I can't imagine how
hard it is in there.
And as for me,
man, what could I say?
I guess God has a sense
of humor, right?
Vanessa's doing great.
She sends her love.
Man!
So much has happened
over these last couple of years.
It's been crazy but all
to the good, though,
you know?
It's a new season, man.
I finally turned
in my player card
and wifed Vanessa.
Yeah, I took the plunge.
(LAUGHS)
In more ways than one.
God has been so good to me.
Sometimes I can't
even understand it.
I mean, after all I did
throughout my life,
and He never gave up on me.
And if that ain't love,
I don't know what is.
I've even been taking
these Bible classes
just so I can understand
Him and His Word
a little better.
Good news is that you guys
are short-timers now.
Just a little ways to go,
and it's all over, yo.
Just remember what we
talked about on our visits.
God is good, and
He is faithful,
and I promise that He's
inside those walls
just as much as
He is out here.
I sent some money to
your books already,
and it should be
enough to last y'all
until you get out.
Man, I love y'all, man.
Can't wait to see you out
here in real clothes.
Steaks are on me, baby.
Love, respect, and blessings,
Miles.
P.S. You guys are
gonna be uncles soon,
so straighten up,
'cause I don't want my kid
around no knuckleheads, you dig?
Okay, Mama, look,
Daddy's about to preach.
Good morning.
ALL: Good morning.
I'm Pastor Miles,
and today...
today, we're gonna
talk about change.
(VIBRANT SOULFUL MUSIC)
♪♪
It's important to me, man.
I'm serious.
We'll deal with
Marty, though...
I mean, we'll deal with Jesse.
Here's my cash right here.
T-bone's in.
I don't mean t...
(LAUGHTER)
No worry.
Can you get out of my light?
I'm joking.
Sweep the leg.
(LAUGHTER)
(LAUGHS)
Let me get another
round of those.
Hey, Jesse, let me... dang it.
(LAUGHTER)
Hello, I'm Miles Montego.
You are?
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHTER)
Oh, "Jerry," please,
and it's my pleasure
to meet you.
But, uh... what...
(LAUGHTER)
That's what we won't be doing.
Oh, I can't dis
Jimmy's, though, right?
(LAUGHTER)
(LAUGHS)
I mean, you say hope,
and they say pray.
I mean, can we get an...
My bad, y'all.
Yes, I'd like to see
the flight Pa...
Back to one?
I'm... I'm feeling
bloopers reel here, baby.
All right.
(STRIKING PIANO KEY)
Oh, hold on. I got
to take this.
Hello? Okay, good
talking to you.
Yeah. Hi...
(LAUGHS)
Y'all embraced me,
y'all loved me,
and I... and I...
I don't know what to say.
I'm at a loss for words.
(INDISTINCT SPEECH)
(LAUGHS)
We want to speak
life over you today.
Every person listening,
we want you to understand,
no matter where you've been
or where you might
currently find yourself,
it's not over.
When God is in it,
there is no limit.
♪ Oh, it's not over ♪
♪ It's not over ♪
♪ Until God says so ♪
♪ And so I counted on y'all ♪
♪ I counted on y'all ♪
♪ You make all things new ♪
♪ It's not over ♪
♪ Not till God says so ♪
♪ Till God says so ♪
♪ So I counted on y'all ♪
♪ It's not over ♪
♪ Until God says so ♪
That's right.
♪ If you can just believe it ♪
♪ I believe, I believe ♪
♪ You make all things ♪
♪ All things new ♪
♪ It's not over ♪
♪ No matter what
the doctors say ♪
♪ Until God says so ♪
♪ He's still got y'all
in the picture ♪
♪ He will convince you ♪
♪ It's not, it's not ♪
♪ It's not ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
(RECORD SCRATCHING)
♪ Rain down ♪
♪ Rain down Your love ♪
♪ Rain down Your love again ♪
♪ Can you do it once again? ♪
♪ Rain down ♪
♪ Rain down on us, yeah ♪
♪ With Your love again ♪
♪ With Your love ♪
♪ Oh, till we see
You face-to-face ♪
♪ Let us feel Your
warm embrace ♪
♪ Rain Your love on us again ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Rain down, rain down ♪
♪ Rain Your love on us again ♪
♪ Again ♪
♪ Rain one more time ♪
♪ Rain Your love on us again ♪
♪ Your love on ♪
♪ Love on ♪
♪ Your love, oh ♪
♪ Rain Your love on us again ♪
♪ Rain ♪
♪ We need You, Lord ♪
♪ To rain it down ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Rain Your love on us again ♪
♪ Rain down ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Rain Your love on us again ♪
♪ Rain down ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Rain Your love on us again ♪
♪ Pray for the day ♪
♪ Your pain goes away ♪
♪ And for the time ♪
♪ Wasted on good-bye ♪
♪ Can't get back the time ♪
♪ But You stay on my mind ♪
♪ Forgive me for the lies ♪
Forgive...
♪ And all the tears
you've cried ♪
♪ Hope to see you
when I get there ♪
♪ Mile-high heavenly skies ♪
♪ Will be a breath
of fresh air ♪
♪ G5 ♪
♪ Nobody on my plane
'cause it's private ♪
♪ On my way to
Saint Elsewhere ♪
♪ I swear ♪
♪ I know they say the
good die young ♪
♪ And I guess that's
why I'm so scared ♪
♪ And I refuse to die ♪
♪ And I won't die ♪
♪ Until history records
my greatness ♪
♪ Amen ♪
♪ I see angels ♪
♪ I see demons ♪
♪ I hear laughter,
people screaming ♪
♪ Makes me wonder
what's my reason ♪
♪ For being here ♪
♪ And so I'm kneelin' ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Don't matter what
it looks like ♪
♪ Or feels like right now ♪
♪ My God has promised
for my good ♪
♪ He will work it out ♪
♪ No, no, no matter
what it looks like ♪
♪ Or feels like right now ♪
♪ My God has promised
for my good ♪
♪ He will work it out ♪
♪ No, no, no matter
what it looks like ♪
♪ Or feels like right now ♪
♪ My God has promised
for my good ♪
♪ He will work it out ♪
♪ No, no, no matter
what it looks like ♪
♪ Or feels like right now ♪
♪ My God has promised
for my good ♪
♪ He will work it out ♪
♪ No, no, no matter
what it looks like ♪
♪ Or feels like right now ♪
♪ My God has promised
for my good ♪
♪ He will work it out ♪
♪ No matter how ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ He'll work it out ♪
♪ My God ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Trouble don't last forever ♪
♪ Trouble don't last always ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
(SIGHS)
Hello? T-bone, come on.
They told... they told
me I was in this scene.
Come on. Come on. Come on.