KoreanDramaX.co
Well then,
why don't I make a deal with you?
Aren't you looking for your friends?
Tell me his name and what he looks like.
If you promise me that you'll stay, then I'll look for your friends.
I don't have friends.
Were you abandoned by your friends?
I'll give you one more chance.
Think about it carefully.
I am very angry this time, extremely angry.
You know how I treat you usually.
You dare to do this to me?!
What was your name?
Ah Chang.
Ah Chang?
- Throw him to the ocean for the fishes.- Yes!
- If you have any problem, deal with me! Let him go!- Boss Sakai...
- What capability will you show for killing him?!- Boss! Boss! Have mercy!
- You can't even defend yourself.- Boss!
- Bring her away.- Yes.
- Let me go.  - Move.
Let me go!
Being angry everyday is not good for my skin.
I'm betting small. Big. Small.
- Big, big, big.- Small, small.
Here, here, here.
I don't believe that I'm unlucky. I don't believe.
I'll still buy small.
I'll bet big. Small. Big. Small.
Move aside. Move aside. How do you play this?
Is this your first time to play?
Between this big and small, you just bet randomly.
- Bet randomly, is that it?- Right, bet randomly.
I'm betting on big.
- I'll bet on small. - Betting on small.
- Small! Small!- Big! Big!
- Big! Big! Big!- Small!
I won! I won!
Boss, I'm betting on big again.
I'll also bet on big! I'll also bet on big!
Big! Big! Big!
- You're something!- I won again!
Your luck is not bad.
I can't play anymore. I can't play anymore.
- I'm going now. I'm going now.- Mister, just play one more round.
- Just one round.- Right, one more round.
Just play one more round.
Come. Come. Come.
Play one more round.
- Play one more round. This is fun.- Come. Come. Come.
Just play one more round, okay?
Okay. I'll bet all on big! Bet on big!
Okay. Big! Big! I'll bet on big, too.
- Big! Big! Big!- Small! Small!
Xiong Fei, Yuan Shuai, I'm risking your life on this bet.
You two must bless me that I can win this.
Sorry. Sorry.
You can't. You can't. Go now. Go now.
Why must I enter the gambling area?
Why?!
I don't have any money now.
How am I supposed to save Xiong Fei?
How am I supposed to save Yuan Shuai?
Stop right there.
I...
You don't need to tell me where you went.
I don't want to mind your business.
Go and split the logs in the backyard first,
wash the bowls in the kitchen,
wash the vegetables, wash the clothes, and sweep the floor.
Or else, you won't have any food to eat.
Okay.
You don't know at all how tiring it was to bring you up from when we were little!
- You...- What about me?
I am the one who is tired!
You crappy person.
You totally are a big asshole!
You are the one who is a bastard.
My biggest mistake in this lifetime is to meet you!
Crappy person, look at my 'fierce tiger going down the mountain'!
Look at me hitting you!
I'm also hitting you!
I'll punch you!
What are you two doing?! What are you two doing?!
Stop! Don't fight anymore!
Stop fighting already!
Enough already. Unlock the chains first.
Da He.
Let's go, Da He.
No use. We won't be able to get out.
How will we know if we don't give it a try?
Let's go.
- Older Bro Fei.- Are everyone okay now? Let's go now, everyone.
Come with me!
Bastard! Planning to rebel?!
What are you two planning to do?
You tell us what we are going to do.
Dead fatty, you better release us now.
I hate other people calling me a fatty the most.
You even added a 'dead' word in front?!
I'll kick you to death!
I just want to call you that. So what? So what?
Dead fatty! Dead fatty! Dead fatty!
Let me tell you. Today, we all must escape out of this damn place.
Do you think you can get out just because you want to?
I'm the law in here.
The two of them are newbies and don't know any better.
It's fine for them causing trouble.
But all you others know the rules.
Yet you all are still creating a disturbance here?!
Let me tell you all. I'm counting to 5.
If you don't go back, you know the consequences.
Are you even counting? Do you think we are kids?
Will we just be scared because of that?
Scaring you?
Just look.
I'm counting now.
5!
Hey, don't be afraid. As long as we unite, we surely can get out of here.
That's right.
4!
Da He, you are their leader.
You must not retreat.
It's no use. We can't get out.
3!
Da He!
We have more people than them.
- What really are you being afraid about?- That's right.
2!
Da He! Da He!
- You all...- Da He...
Don't go!
Restrain them!
Yes!
Customer, your hooves are here.
Is it my hooves or the pork's hooves?
This is your hooves.
T-T-This is the pork hooves.
Don't laugh anymore! Don't laugh anymore!
Boss! What kind of waiter is this that you hired?
What my hooves, the pork's hooves.
He can't even differentiate my hooves and the pork hooves.
What are you doing?
- Stop right there! Stop right there!- Star Chart.
Stop right there! Stop right there!
- What are you doing?!- Give me back my item.
What item? How come I don't know?
Don't you dare try to scare me.
Stop pretending already!
Last time, you stole my Star Chart.
If you don't give it to me today, don't think of leaving.
- You really can't understand.- Hey!
- Boss.- Where are you going?
My stuff got stolen. I am trying to get it back.
You are being paid wages by me so you are my people.
Without my permission, don't think of going anywhere.
- Boss, that item is really very important to me.- I'm warning you.
My patience has a limit. Stop trying each time to challenge it.
I don't care.
Get in! Get in! Behave!
You two better behave! Do you hear me?
You dead fatty who has no conscience! Dirty thing! Stinky evil person!
Hurry and let us out!
Then just continue your cursing.
The fiercer it is, the better.
Let me tell you. Don't just look at how happily you can still jump now.
In the future, I'll put you to death.
An attempt where you already know the result, what's there to be angry about?
Such a coward.
Escaping in the middle of the fight.
The door was just right there.
We clearly could have gone out.
People like you are indeed suitable to stay here forever.
- What did you say?- What are you doing?
What are you doing?!
What?
Want to kill me?
Come. Give me a fast one.
It's better than staying in corruption with you to kill one another as monkeys played by others.
If you ask me,
the ones lock you in here aren't these shackles
or these cages,
but your own selves.
You yourselves have no more courage or hope.
Just continue dragging out an ignoble existence.
Why must Older Bro Fei and I still turn around and save you all?
We could have just escaped by our own.
But we wanted that all of you here
to live a humane life.
Yet in the end,
in the end...
Customer, please wait.
Hey.
Come. This one is good.
Boss, you tell me, is there any money lending bank at this place?
In this small place, how can there be a money lending bank?
Slower.
There isn't even a bank, is there?
None.
Here.
Buddy, are you a foreigner?
What?
I have a precious item here. Do you want it?
What treasure?
Blue-and-white porcelain.
Blue-and-white porcelain?
Do I look like a person who can afford to buy blue-and-white porcelain?
Buddy, just look at it for a while.
This is my family's heirloom.
If not because I need money right away, I won't be rushing to sell this.
There was even such a kind of treasure on this small island.
If this is in the capital,
I might have already bought it.
But I have no money now.
Buddy, you really have good eyes.
This one is worth 2,000 liang.
I'm just selling it now for 100 liang.
If you are going to resell it, you can at least sell it for 500 liang.
Don't you even want this? You really are so stupid.
If I resell that vase,
won't the money I earn be able to save Yuan Shuai and the others?
Hey! Wait!
Ha?
I'll get this item now. Wait for me. I'll just get some money.
Sure. The treasure won't wait for you.
Hurry and go.
My fishes are over there.
You wait for me there.
Okay.
I want to advance my wage.
Do you think I will give it to you?
Today, you must give it no matter what.
Then what you are doing is stealing then.
That's right.
Give me the money!
On what basis should I give it to you?
I'll exchange it for an item.
You already are this poor.
What item can you still have to give me in exchange?
Is this one okay?
If this hand can save the lives of my two buddies,
I'll cut it off for you!
Fine. Anyway, my knife has not seen blood for quite a long time already.
Take it to save your friends.
Thanks.
Hey.
Little bro, why did you come just now? I even thought you were not coming anymore.
Of course, I would come.
Where is the money?
The money is here.
- Give me the money.- Wait.
Let me see the vase first.
Give me the money first.
Let me see the vase first. What if when I was gone, you switched the item?
I was pushing your fishes so how could I have the time to change the item?
Then how about this? Let's exchange it at the same time.
Okay.
Hey, oh right. All sales are final. No returns.
Right, it's real.
Okay. I'm going now.
Where can I go to sell this?
Are you still awake?
I can't sleep.
What are you thinking then?
I don't know, either.
Random thoughts.
Thinking that there are still so many things I haven't finished.
So many people I haven't thanked.
Then just think about him in your heart.
Think about who you want to say sorry to.
Who you want to thank.
Thinking about him in your heart.
They will then dream about you.
Sleep now.
Older Bro Fei,
being your friend is my most non-regrettable matter in this life.
Although we never said any stupid words like living and dying together,
if there is a next life time,
I would still want to be your buddy.
What nonsense are you talking about? Sleep now.
Look at it. How much will this item be worth?
Where did you get this item?
Don't bother where I got it.
Just see if it can be worth how much.
We are not allowed to accept
items whose origin is doubtful.
Don't worry.
This item is definitely mine.
It's just that I'm in a hurry to have some money to use now
so I can sell it to you at a lower price.
1,000 liang? How about it?
Okay! Deal!
- Servant.- Yes, Master.
Get the money and give it to him.
Yes.
I found you two a playmate.
He will play with you two tomorrow.
Little thing...
Be careful.
Brats, I'll torment you two to death.
Da He.
Looking at you doing this thing all day but not doing it well,
I made you one.
Treat it as my payment for that bread.
Forget it.
I also don't know what I want to say.
Maybe it's some last words.
If one day, you meet people who are looking for us,
just tell them that Zhan Xiong Fei and Yuan Shuai found a treasure
and went to a very far, far away place to open a restaurant.
And that place is someplace that no one knows about.
I know that you are a good person.
Please then.
KoreanDramaX.co
Wake up.
Wake up, young man!
Who are you people? Let go of me!
Let go!
Don't move.
Are you some racketeering shop?
Are you planning to steal from me?!
Steal?
Do you know what this is?
Blue-and-white porcelain.
Do you know whose item this is?
Of course, it's mine.
Stealing an item from my, Qiu Luo Feng's, house,
you even dared to publicly sell it on the streets
and even dared to claim it as yours?
You really have guts.
I don't know that this item was stolen from your house.
But I spent money to buy this.
Do you think I will believe you?
Believing or not is your problem.
Why have you tied me up?
Are you going to kill me?
Do you want to die that much?
I don't want to die.
My friends were sold to the fighting arena.
They are even waiting for me to save them.
Then does it mean
that you stole this vase and planned to sell it to get money to save your friends?
I am saying it again.
I borrowed money to buy that thing! I didn't steal it!
How about this?
I'll make a deal with you.
Since this vase has already returned to your hands,
just let me go and lend me money.
After I saved my friends, I'll pay you back.
Okay?
If all of this that you are saying is true,
you are quite a loyal friend.
I admire you.
Untie him.
I'll temporarily believe you this time.
What do you mean?
Take this and save your friends.
Thank you.
I will definitely pay you back.
No need.
Just after 2 hours, this money will return to my hands again.
Move aside! Move aside!
Move aside!
This isn't Xiong Fei...
Hey, where are my friends?
This person has been with me for ten years.
Look at what he looks now.
If anything happens to him,
do you know how hurt my heart will feel?
Hey. What does your friend's business have to do with me?
What does his life or death got to do with me?
He was beaten up by your friends.
I told you before.
I am a businessman. Yes.
You gave me that money.
But that money is not the bail money for your friends anymore.
Instead, it's payment for my losses.
How come you are such a dishonest man?!
Even if that money was still your friends' bail money,
he ended up like this because your friends beat him up.
Someone must pay, right?
Not much.
5,000 liang.
Why don't you just go steal?
I am a businessman.
How can I do such barbaric things?
You--
Oh, right.
I still have to watch the game later.
Jeez, this competition is quite exciting.
Oh, right.
I am exactly going to watch how those two friends of yours
are going to die.
You dead fatty! You are not a man of your words!
Drive him out!
You dead fatty! How come you aren't true to your words?! Hey!
- Move!- If you want to make a bet, I will welcome it.
If you want to cause trouble, no way! Throw him out!
- Yes! Move!- You dead fatty!
You dishonest dead fatty!
Hurry and leave! Hurry and leave!
- Let me in!- You don't have money so why are you still coming here?! Hurry and go!
Hey, Mister Feng. Give me the money.
Looking at this money bag, this must belong to Mister Feng.
Mister Six told me to return it to you untouched.
Let's go.
Wasn't I right?
I just knew it. You are with them.
I disdain having dealings with them.
- Hey!- Yes.
Can you help me?
What?
Do you want me to help them fight?
I don't mean it that way.
If you can help my friends,
I will do anything you want.
Do you think I need your help for me do things?
Don't forget.
It was you who stole my item.
I not only didn't kill you,
I even gave you money to save your friends.
I can be said to have extreme benevolence and have done my utmost duty already.
I know that you are a good man.
You are not the same with them.
Then can you just be a good man until the very end?
What you are doing is called asking for a mile when you are already given an inch.
I do want to help them.
But this world has its rules.
There was one really good saying.
If one person never lost anything,
then he wouldn't know how it was to truly live.
- Hey!- I'm urging you to stop following me.
If I was you, I'd go back to my friends' side now.
At least before they die, I would still be able to send them off.
What is this that I am doing?
Even if in death, I must die with my comrades.
Today will be a very exciting and outstanding fight!
I believe that last time, everyone still remembered
that because of our power king belittling his opponents too much,
causing these two mice to have a chance to find loopholes.
But today, the power king has said that he surely will aim for redemption.
Letting these two people know what powerful really means.
Everyone, let's use our most warm applause and shouts
to cheer for this fight!
Someone! Anyone!
My stomach aches!
- Anyone!- What's going on?
What's going on?
My stomach is aching.
- It really hurts a lot.- Come. Get out. Stand up.
So painful.
Come.
You must have eaten too much.
So painful...
So heavy.
Can everyone here the sound at the viewing stadium?
Is the moment of our death just to try to please these cold, heartless, and inhumane audiences?!
What that little buddy said is right.
What is really imprisoning us?
Is it this cage?
No. It is ourselves.
Who made us become cowards?
And who made us lose courage?
Right now, I want to go out. Live like a human.
Who is willing to come with me?!
I'm going! I'm going!
Me! Count me in! I'm going!
Count me in! I'm going with you! Let's go out together!
Buddies! Come with me!
Let us go! Go!
Go and open the doors.
Hurry. This way.
Older Bro Fei, Older Bro Fei, my 'fierce tiger going down the mountain' won't work this time.
No matter if it will work or not, let's just try it. Come.
Fierce tiger going down the mountain!
Hit him. Hit him.
Today, I will knead you two to death!
The battle starts!
Don't be afraid. If we are going to die, I'll die before you.
I'm not afraid. I'm not afraid.
Stop them!
Buddies, attack!
What's going on? What's going on?
Who are we fighting now?
Da He?
Da He, you've changed your mind, right?
You said it right. Even if we are going to die here, we have to die with courage.
Let's go. I'll protect and escort you out of here.
- Let's go together! Go!- Okay!
Buddies! Let's go!
Are you all rebelling?!
Go in quickly.
They are fighting already! Hurry and run!
Run! Hurry and run!
Quickly go! Hurry and run!
Hurry and run!
Go!
Xiong Fei!
Zhan Xiong Fei!
Yuan Shuai!
Xiong Fei!
Where have you gone to?
Later, if Zi Su starts asking about it,
tell her that I've already informed you.
It's just that you've forgotten about it. Understand?
I remember already, Your Majesty.
What if Zi Su doesn't believe?
Do you still have any other way?
Your Majesty, if even you can't handle Princess Zi Su,
who else in this world can?
Reporting!
- Your Majesty, I have urgent news to report.- What is it? Why are you in a flurry?
We just received information that the royal tomb has been looted.
What?! Who did it?
Still don't know.
- Okay. Go back to the grand hall first.- Yes.
Pi Wu, you had a major achievement this time.
Just for Lord of the City, I am willing to offer my life.
Fine.
Once I use the Magic Star to
summon the magical army that the God of Heaven left,
we will let our people
to openly live under the sun.
Congratulations, Lord of the City.
For a hundred years, no one has accomplished this great cause in this underground city.
It has been realized in your hands.
That's right.
This can be considered a great relief to our founders from a hundred years ago.
Kill them! Kill...
Kill!
Retreat!
Does His Majesty really want to do this?
This concerns the lives of thousands of citizens.
Right now, the war has been going for so long.
The treasury is running out of money. We can only do such a move.
General needs only to follow the orders of His Majesty.
Afterwards, once the dynasty is stable,
General will surely be able to enjoy your achievements forever.
But how about the thousands of citizens at the downstream of the river?
This is not what you should be worrying about.
As the general in the front line, what you should think about is how to fight the battle.
Please decide as soon as possible.
Okay then.
Spread my order. Tomorrow night, destroy the dam.
Flood the enemy's camp.
Yes!
General, we had a great victory this time.
Once we return to the capital, His Majesty will surely give you tremendous rewards.
As your subordinates, we will benefit from it, too.
Shut up.
Don't you clearly know how we won this battle?
We won without fighting
and even sacrificed the lives of thousands of citizens.
What are you doing here?
You group of rebels and traitors!
Actually publicly going against the order of His Majesty!
Not giving importance to the lives of thousands of citizens!
As ordered by His Majesty, I am here to arrest you all!
Isn't this His Majesty's order?
Why did it become an order to defy the Emperor?
Attack!
Buddies, kill them to make the way!
[Xiu]
General, where are we going now?
In this world, all land belongs to the Emperor.
Where else can we go?
Are we going to wait here for them to kill us?
No. Since we have no place to settle in the above land,
but there is a place His Majesty can't control.
General, where is this place?
The underground.
As long as I can let the people of Yongzhou City live underground,
I, Lord Xiu Fu, will die without any regrets.
Lord of the City cares about the citizens of Yongzhou in your heart.
No wonder you are supported and revered by the citizens.
There is still something extremely important.
That is the formula for the medicine that your teacher, the Miracle Healer, is holding.
When I think of this Miracle Healer, I get a headache.
Lord of the City, my teacher, this old fogey,
is very stubborn and prejudiced.
But please don't worry,
I will surely do my best
to fulfill this task.
Fine.
I will wait for your good news.
Older bro, you are still treating me like a kid.
Just those soldiers that you arranged to guard me,
how can they stop a person who has seen great winds and high waves like me?
Zhan Xiong Fei!
It's the white-skin person?
Yes. White-skin person.
Lord Ma.
Lord Ma, this news is worth at least two gold bars.
Don't be too greedy.
If I need anything else, I will look for you again.
Scram.
Zhan Xiong Fei!
Princess Zi Su?
Good things actually come without any reasons.
Zhan Xiong Fei!
Ma Shun.
Greetings to Princess Zi Su.
Heaven has really helped me.
Even though I don't have a mansion,
I was able to capture Princess Zi Su.
With this bargaining chip, even His Majesty will have to be courteous to me.
Ma Shun, you have done a good job this time.
It was all to your guidance.
Is there any news about the royal tomb being looted?
I was just about to report to you about this.
This matter... seems like... it was done by a white-skin person.
I received confirmed news that
the Magic Star in the royal tomb was plundered by them.
So it was done by a white-skin person...
Lord, who really are these white-skin people?
How come they have such capability
to trespass a heavily guarded royal tomb and steal the Magic Star?
The white-skin people, also called white-face people,
is not just pertaining to a certain person,
but all the citizens who live in the underground Yongzhou City.
I see.
This is getting more interesting.
Lord, what you meant was...
Get ready to set off.
Lord, you shouldn't take this trouble. Better just let me go there first to check on the roads.
These mysterious people below Yongzhou have high skills.
They dared to plunder the royal tomb.
This shows that they don't respect the Imperial Court.
Even if I personally go,
we still might not have a 100% chance of succeeding.
I understand.
Lord, what about the Princess?
Take her along.
The princess is way more useful than a shield during emergent times.
Okay, I will prepare the horses and carriage now.
Wait.
Send someone to deliver a letter to the palace now.
Palace?
Who's the letter for?
- His Majesty. - His...
If you didn't save us in time,
we would have been doomed.
It's nothing.
Why didn't you escape when we released you?
Subsequently, you fought your way out.
I don't know either.
It could be because of the words you said at that time.
The words?
What did I say?
You said that I should live like a human being.
I didn't say you were like a monkey.
Right now, my whole body aches.
Thank you for giving this to me.
If this grasshopper can help you find yourself again,
it's very meaningful then.
Why do you want this?
Because I promised someone.
Who is it?
My daughter.
That time, our boat capsized in this sea
and she fell into the water.
Before our boat sunk, I promised to make one for her,
but...
Your daughter... must be very adorable.
Of course.
In the past, I dared not leave.
I dared not remember that afternoon.
I didn't know where to go if I was released
and how I should live.
When I dreamed of her last night, I dared not sleep again.
But I realize now that
I should continue with my life.
You are right.
If your daughter were to see you now,
she would be very proud of you.
Little buddy, thank you.
If you need my help in the future, just let me know.
I definitely will.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
KoreanDramaX.co
♫ In a rainy night, ♫
♫ I've not put away that windbreaker umbrella ♫
♫ My hand, that grasps it, is unwilling to throw it away ♫
♫ I want to be together till the end ♫
♫ Upon opening my eyes, ♫
♫ there may be only fallen leaves all over the ground left ♫
♫ There may be only those cold long streets left ♫
♫ I have you next to me ♫
♫ We agree to wait till tomorrow ♫
♫ Wait until snow and frost compromise with sunshine ♫
♫ You must believe ♫
♫ those agreements that we made at young ♫
♫ We agree to wait till tomorrow to ♫
♫ walk through the coldest winter night and ♫
♫ kiss the most beautiful spring together ♫
♫ Stand side-by-side before the daybreak ♫