KoreanDramaX.co
Older Sis, why did you lie to him that he is our worker?
Wasn't the reason that Xiao Dao dares brazenly bully us like that
because we have no men in the shop?
I see that lad is pretty good in martial arts.
We can make him stay with us temporarily,
then if Xiao Dao comes again,
he would at least have some dread.
But what if he regains his memory?
If he knows we lied to him, he will definitely not stay still!
Rest assured.
When Older Bro Ying Jun returns, everything will be okay!
He should be returning soon.
Older Bro Ying Jun has gone to sea for five years,
and there has been no news about him since.
That huge storm-
That huge storm overturned their ship,
only three people survived.
Also, there were 57 bodies that had been found.
Only his whereabouts is unknown.
This means he is still alive!
Just because he is missing does not mean he is still alive!
If nothing happened to him, why hasn't he returned after so many years?
Older Sis, I know you don't want to face the truth,
but you cannot continue to lie to yourself like this!
You being like this will only harm yourself.
Xiao Mei, I don't allow you to say such words.
I have a promise with Older Bro Ying Jun.
He said that when he returns he will proudly marry me.
He has never gone back to on his word.
He will definitely return.
This...
What stupid place is this?
What is this, seriously.
Can you stop complaining?
It's so irritating.
What? Pfft.
Sir, you say, this person called what... what, Yu Qi Lin?
What does he mean?
He asked to meet us yet delayed his appearance.
We couldn't have been cheated, right?
I hope you got cheated!
Can you shut up?
Don't make a fuss.
We will wait awhile more.
Is it you people who wanted to see Lord Yu Qi Lin?
Yes.
My master has something on and is unable to meet you.
What?
He can't come, right?
What situation is this?
Do you know how long we waited here?
Stop.
We've made an arrangement in advance with your teacher for a map to Yongzhou Underground City.
Do you know our rules?
Did you bring the money?
Open the box.
Can you give us the map now?
Hey, I am the current emperor's younger sister, Princess Zi Su.
These two people are traitor minister Ding Song and his lackey Ma Shun.
I was kidnapped by them!
You... You cannot believe a word they say!
That... This is my younger sister.
She likes to listen to plays.
She is a play addict and can't get out of it.
I don't care about the grievances between you people.
Take it.
Hey! You... You see someone in trouble and refuse to help!
You are helping the bad people to do evils!
Princess, just drop the idea forever.
No one will be able to save you.
You guys... You're all bastards!
Then that's it. We're taking our leave now.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Move!
Seems like he is really here to find someone.
Older Sis!
You frightened me.
Older Sis, why don't you go to eat but stay here alone furtively?
Let me tell you, that Yuan Shuai is really a treasure!
Not only does he know martial arts, but also cooks extremely well!
I think it is comparable to Brother Ying Jun!
Come quickly and try his fried rice with me!
Younger Sister, here. Please sit down first.
Look at this drawing.
Yuan Shuai?
Is this the brother Older Bro Fei was looking for?
You have to hide this picture and these clothes well.
Don't let him find them.
Older Sis, isn't it too much for us to do this way?
When Older Bro Ying Jun comes back then we will explain to him and let him go.
-But... -No buts.
Right now, I'm the hostess of this household.
Also, I think you've been too hungry.
Now whatever you eat is delicious to you.
Remember, in this world, no one's cooking can compare to Ying Jun's!
Yes.
Sir, look. There's a city there!
Right. This is Yongzhou Underground City of the legends.
Yongzhou Underground City?
Then do those white-skinned people all live here?
The white-skinned people of legends can only live in Yongzhou Underground City.
Once they go up to the ground and see the sunlight, they will bleed to death.
So this is how it is.
Lord, then what shall we do now?
Let's find a place to rest first.
Older Bro Ying Jun!
Don't leave!
Did you have to go?
Stay with me, okay?
We have such good hot springs.
You're so good in cooking.
We can transform this shop into something great!
Xiao Cai, wait for me.
I will be back in half a year to marry you.
I heard that on the other side of the seas, there is a place where they make spices.
I want to learn from them and bring back their secret methods.
Then when the time comes we can open this hot spring inn all over the world!
I will become the number 1 chef,
and you will have unlimited wealth.
I, Gao Ying Jun, swear that the first thing I'll do upon returning is to marry Xiao Cai!
I will always wait for you.
No matter how long, I will wait.
In the middle of the night, you come out pretending to be a ghost instead of sleeping.
Do you plan to scare me to death?
I should be asking you that.
In the middle of the night, you stand here alone crying instead of sleeping.
Who says I'm alone.
Look!
Hey, Xiao Cai,
have you ever thought about re-opening your business?
Just take care of your own things.
Don't bother about anything else.
Miss, I'm here!
- Did you bring the money? - No, I didn't.
Why do you come here if you don't bring money?
Unexpectedly, you're young with a good figure,
but you just want all the rewards without paying the price.
It was because I promised the Em--
I promised her family that I would save her,
and it has to be done with my own abilities.
So... I don't have the face to go back and ask for money.
So you're going to the Underground City to save someone, right?
Yes.
Could I trouble you to tell Granddaddy Earth?
I'm really anxious to go to the underground city.
Then when my issue is settled, I will definitely repay him with lots of money!
Then you tell him yourself.
Granddaddy Earth, please tell me the way to the underground city.
After I rescue my friend, I will definitely repair your entire temple for you!
If I am lying, I will be struck by lightning!
Countries have laws.
Businesses have their regulations.
I will take the money first then help you.
This rule cannot be broken.
Everyone who has come to beg has given me some payment.
You gods, why are you so money-faced?
Fine. I don't believe I cannot find the way on my own accord!
What kind of god are you?
I'll see you next time!
Buddy, wait!
Ventriloquy?
I say!
You tell me. Why are you, little lady, not doing anything good,
but come out to fool people like this?
I'm also dumb.
How can I, Zhan Xiong Fei, be tricked by such a low level scheme?
What did you say earlier? What you are called?
Zhan Xiong Fei.
Is your father the Heaven Strategy Envoy, Zhan Ke?
Does he have a sword called the Gray Thunder Edge?
How do you know?
It really is the Gray Thunder Edge.
So... do you know my father?
My dad's Jianghu's code name was Golden Spade.
He is the present empire's top tomb raider.
He and Uncle Zhan Ke have known each other for more than ten years.
Afterwards, when things happened to the Department of Heaven Strategy, we lost contact with your family.
Oh... Then where is your father now?
Last year, when he was raiding a tomb,
his men rebelled against him and injured his arm.
He then just retired from it.
So, do you know how to go to the underground city?
Or does your father know?
Hurry and tell me, please.
The people of the underground city are unable to come out, and they know my father well,
so he often helps them conduct trades.
You can say they know each other well.
That Princess Zi Su you mentioned
was brought there by two people yesterday.
It was me who gave them—
I'm sorry.
It seems like Zi Su was really brought to the underground city.
It's okay. It's not your fault.
Can I have one map, too?
I will go and find them now!
What is Zi Su to you?
Why are you so anxious?
She... She is my good friend.
Then when you were young, did Uncle Zhan Ke mention me?
No.
How is that possible!
We were engaged by our parents when we were in the womb with a babies' marriage agreement.
What?
You are the Baby* Elder Yu Qi Lin?(* baby in the womb)
And you and I have a baby—
B-B-Babies' marriage agreement?
Right. I only found out from my father after I grew up.
You... You... The babies marriage agreement you're talking about is the one I'm thinking about?
Right. That time we lost contact,
I also thought the heavens didn't agree with us.
Now unexpectedly, I've actually seen you again!
It is truly fate!
No, it's not fate.
This is confusing.
This...
Don't worry about that first.
Please give me the map.
I really need to save Zi Su!
Older Brother Xiong Fei!
Then that means you admit what happened in the past?
I admit... I... What?
Miss Qi Lin, things are like this,
I am just a poor person.
That... We are not compatible.
Compatible! You don't have money, but I have money.
When we are together, we won't lack anything!
You don't have to risk danger anymore, either!
- I... No... - Don't tell me you fell for that princess!
You want to be a prince, is that it?
I...
I am not thinking so much now.
Miss Qi Lin, just take it as I'm begging you. Just give me the map.
Then you have to promise me something.
As long as you don't mention marriage, I will promise you.
Fine then promise me.
If you manage to rescue Zi Su, I want to have a fair competition with her.
Okay?
No... What? Compete for what?
Okay, fine, I promise.
Just give me the map now.
Don't worry. I'll send you there!
Let's go!
What are you doing now?
I am not giving you the money for nothing.
Help me get something.
What?
The pearl powder from Toyo Bay.
Cosmetics?
Of course. I'm earning money for this face!
For the pearl powder from Toyo Bay with this little money,
I don't think...
This is the deposit!
If there is stock,
then I will repay you everything!
Was this money earned from that girl?
Let me tell you, that girl is worth a lot.
I've sold her for so much!
Where is she now?
You also know that I was just asked to come here.
It's that little boy, right?
Has he woken up?
He won't wake up in such a short time.
I've not seen such a foolish act.
He even dared drink the pirate king wine.
Okay, let's talk about that girl A Ji Ya first.
Where is she? I must take her away.
If you don't say...
Your pearl powder...
You are really being serious, aren't you?
I was kidding.
If the person is with me, I'll hand her over.
But the point is... that she was taken by Cheng Ming Pan.
She's with Chen Ming Pan?
Right.
Who changed my clothes?
Who do you think?
Do you think you got out yourself?
Boss, men and women should not get too close, how could you—
I got my waiter to do it for you.
Oh, I got scared to death.
How long have I been asleep?
You dreamt of your mother, didn't you?
How do you know?
I must have been sleep talking again.
It was not sleep talking but drunk talking.
I've not seen such a foolish drunk like you.
If you do this again, I will kill you!
After drinking so much... who can remember what he said?
I won't drink next time. I won't drink.
Right.
A Ji Ya is still in Sailors' House.
I need to save her!
She's not there anymore.
Where is she?
Don't be rash.
Listen to me.
Your friend, A Ji Ya,
is with Cheng Ming Pan currently.
Then all the more I must go save her!
Now the most important thing isn't just saving one person, A Ji Ya.
Cheng Ming Pan robbed a government boat.
If I don't hand him to the capital,
not just A Ji Ya, this whole island will be in danger!
Don't worry about the government!
I am worried about A Ji Ya!
Do you think Cheng Ming Pan will obediently hand her over?
- I heard the sailors said that he wants to marry her! - What?
KoreanDramaX.co
What are you doing?
Stop the boat! I want to get off!
You aren't allowed to! You need to stay onboard and be my wife!
No way!
I'm telling you!
Here, you have no choice!
Be thankful you have food and clothes now
because I, Cheng Ming Pan, have fallen for you!
What do you like about me?
I'll change it then.
Before I reply you,
can you answer a question of mine first?
You love him, right?
The gaze of a woman who has fallen for a man can be told!
That little pale face also loves you!
For you, even his life can be thrown away!
Don't act like you know everything!
What you said is all fake!
You want the truth!
Fine, I'll tell you.
Actually the person I like is not you,
but sometimes I think you were her.
But I know you are not her.
Because your eyes are always so cold.
But her face always had smiles.
Since you have someone you like, why don't you find her?
Why are you making things difficult for me here?
If I want to find her, I have to die first.
She's dead?
Right! She was killed at such a young age.
I killed her!
You killed her?
That time she was the great missy of a wealthy family.
I was just a poor fishmonger!
After we were together,
we decided to go to a place where no one knew us and live out our lives happily.
But good things don't last long.
Not soon after, she got caught and brought back to her house.
I thought that when she got back to her house, she'd continue living her rich lady life.
Her family also promised that they would just treat that this matter didn't happen.
But I never thought that she had gotten pregnant.
Afterwards, they said that she tarnished their family's reputation
and actually got cruelly killed by her own father.
The lady that I risked my life to protect with
actually got cruelly killed by her father just because of me and the child in her womb.
Isn't that me killing her?!
Actually, it's not totally your fault.
No! This is my fault!
From then on, I killed her whole family!
All the people in her household, whether old or young, I killed one by one.
From then on, I took pleasure in killing people!
I took pleasure in hearing the sound of their necks getting broken.
I want these cold-blooded people to accompany my wife and child in her death!
You...
Right! This is me!
Afterwards, I escaped onto this island and become a pirate!
In the end, became the captain of this ship!
Right now, it's my turn to ask you.
Does that guy love you the same way I do?
I don't know that.
But I feel that I will never love you
because you are inhumane!
Do you think that agitating me like that will work?
Let me tell you. You can have your choice.
But in here, you can only follow my choice.
My choice is...
- You can never leave this ship!- You...
I can only walk you up to here.
When you reach the underground city, you must be careful.
If you encounter anything, just mention my father's Golden Spade code name.
It should be able to help you.
I know already.
Then... I'm setting out then.
- What's wrong?- About the engagement set years ago, try reconsidering it.
- Qi Lin, that... We—- Hey!
Forget it. I don't want to hear the answer again.
I hope that it would get better one day.
It may become the answer that I want.
Here is the map.
It'll most likely be of use.
Qi Lin, thank you.
- Come! Come!- We're open!
- We're open!- Look here,
- All Seasons Hot Spring!- Come inside and take a look!
Reopening again!
An old shop reopens!
- Customer, look. Our service is very good.- There are discounts for the grand reopening.
If you have any questions regarding–
- It's really very comfortable.- Hey, our shop has reopened. Hurry and take a look.- We are giving discounts.
Look. We even have a new menu.
Hey, hot spring, hot spring. Experience it for a while. Very relaxing.
No. Not interested.
Hey. The outcome isn't that good.
What do we do?
We cannot continue like this anymore.
We must actively make a move and divide the work for it to be effective.
Let's go.
Coming, All Seasons Hot Spring!
- It has reopened.- Let me tell you that All Seasons Hot Spring is really very good.
Big Bro, Big Bro, please look.
Our All Seasons Hot Spring is currently free. Go and try it.
Just go take a look at it.
Hello. Hello. All Seasons Hot Spring. We welcome you to visit our shop.
Thank you. Thank you.
These are are newly renovated springs.
Go and take a look. They're really good.
Thank you. Thank you.
I told you, it won't work.
We ran the whole day and I'm so tired.
And also, we wasted so many papers.
What main theme? What distinction?
It wasn't useful at all.
Enough already. Stop saying it.
After all, there isn't always a good outcome just because you worked hard for it.
Yuan Shuai.
Xiao Mei, don't be that fierce.
After all, it is his first day to be a waiter here.
I don't know if what we did is right or not.
Older Sis, it's not the time to say these things.
You must know that any effort done to protect oneself will eventually be understood by others.
Right now, just with the two of us, if Xiao Dao returns to cause trouble,
then our shop might be taken by him.
If our shop still don't reopen, we really can't continue living anymore.
If we live only upon our capital, there'd be a day of exhaustion.
What smell is that?
So aromatic.
What is that?
I never smelled such aromatic little yellow fish.
What's the use of just smelling delicious?
The absolute truth is that it tastes delicious.
Try it.
How did you do it?
Older Sis, hurry and taste it.
It is so delicious that I am about to cry.
Is that great?
Let me try.
So delicious!
Yuan Shuai, aren't these just ordinary grilled fish?
How come they taste so delicious?
Maybe because you are hungry already.
But to tell you the truth, when it comes to food, I am really an expert.
This is a recipe passed on in our family.
Our family's culinary skills can't be said to be the world's number one
but it can be considered to be among the top ones.
- What thing smells so delicious? Smells delicious!- Where does it come from?
These are all mine. You two must not fight with me for these.
Xiao Cai, Xiao Mei, our first day of reopening the shop indeed isn't that successful.
It's there! There!
Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry! Smells so delicious! Let's take a look at what it is.
What are you doing?! What?
What are you doing?!
- Mine.- Don't fight. Don't fight.
That fish is mine! That fish is mine!
- Don't fight! You all stop taking it already! - Lessen the amount that you are taking!
- Everyone, stop fighting to get one already.- What are you all doing?!
- Hey, you all...- My fish!
How can you all be like this? It all got taken away.
I still haven't eaten.
Really so delicious.
- Is there still any left?- There is.
But...
- Are there still any? Owner, are there still any? - Give us one order!
Hey, Xiao Mei. I have thought of an idea.
What idea?
Hurry and give it a try.
- Smells so delicious. Wow, smells so delicious.- Just looking at it and I'm already drooling.
Never seen one like this. That's right. So fun.
Our co-villagers, the fathers and elders, do the grilled fishes smell delicious?
They do!
Do you want to eat one or not?
We want to!
Then listen to me say some words, is that okay?
Okay!
Our All Seasons Hot Spring Inn will start business again soon.
Right now, we are promoting a free hot spring bath activity.
You only need to draw a stick to enter. What stick?
The grilled fish stick.
Five sticks and we will give you tea.
Ten sticks and we will give you free hot spring bath.
Twenty sticks! Sorry for the twenty sticks. We don't have anymore additional freebies.
Because you all can only eat a maximum of twenty sticks.
Let me tell you. Everyone wants to eat.
Everyone can eat one, right?
Leave some to others. Our All Seasons Hot Spring Inn welcomes everyone!
Okay! Good!
Everyone, please pay here.
Please line up.
Come. Come. Pay here.
- Here.- I want five sticks.
Welcome to our shop.
Thank you. Thank you.
- This is yours.- Welcome to our shop.
- Please enter. Please enter.- Here. Yours.
Thank you.
- Is the temperature okay?- It's quite good.
- Come back often.- Okay. Okay.
There are all girls here. Why did you come here?
But someone wanted towels.
Then just give it to me.
Hurry and leave this place!
Go there!
Your grilled yellow fishes are here!
- It's here already.- Come. Please enjoy.
This is our best seller.
Thank you. Thank you.
There are fishes coming!
Customers, here are our grilled fishes.
- It has a special flavor.- Okay. Okay.
Your water is here!
- Not bad, right?- Is the water hot enough? Let's add some more.
Thank you.
Here, for you.
Hot water is coming! Here. Here.
Okay.
This is the hard-earned money we had for today.
Wow!
It's been so long since I saw so much money!
We must thank Yuan Shuai a lot for this.
If not for him, those customers really wouldn't dare enter our shop.
Let's give Yuan Shuai one merit.
It's nothing. Everyone worked hard.
Look. Today is such a happy day.
How about let's toast tea in place of wine and celebrate the reopening of our shop today?
You both said it right.
It's all thanks to Yuan Shuai for helping us resume our business.
From now on, we are a family that shares blessings and goes through danger together.
- Cheers!- Cheers!
Cheers!
This...
How come is like that? Never saw him. Weird.
- He really looks so different from us.- That's right.
- He looks so weird. - That's right.- So scary.
Look. Look. So weird-looking is this guy.
Owner, one bowl of noodles.
There are no more noodles.
No more noodles? Why still open a noodle shop?
There is no seat for you.
Hurry and leave!
No... What do you mean by no seat–
Waiter! Serve the four customers noodles!
Okay!
Fellow customers,
your noodles.
Owner. No noodles, no seats?
Then what are they here for?
No. You cannot be biased.
Little kid, looking at you, I think you are not some bad person.
Let me be straight with you then.
If you just weren't careful and ended up in our underground city,
I urge you to go back using the path you used to come here.
Don't carelessly lose your life here.
Look at what you are saying. I didn't come here to commit crimes.
Don't say frightening things like that.
You little brat.
I was giving you kind advice. How come you are unable to differentiate good from bad?
Owner, I just want to eat a bowl of noodles.
Don't worry. I will surely pay.
It's not a matter of money.
Let me tell you the truth.
I am not selling my noodles to outsiders.
To enter our underground city, you must have someone recommending you.
Or else, based on the rules of our city,
this... If the soldiers saw you, they would catch and forcefully banish you.
You... Do you have someone that recommended you?
Recommended...
That... Golden Spade is my friend.
- Golden Spade?- Right.
The Golden Spade that does trade with us?
Right. It should be him.
Do you... have a proof?
Proof? Oh!
I have the map he gave me.
Without this map, I really wouldn't have been able to enter here so easily.
Here. Is this okay?
Is that okay?
Sure. Sure.
It's enough that you have evidence.
Okay. Come, waiter!
- Yes!- Give this customer a bowl of noodles!
Okay!
Hey, owner.
This...
Sit.
It's fine. I just want to ask you some questions.
What do those people carrying weapons do?
They?
They are the most respected Netherworld Assassins.
- Assassins? - They also are the people we depend upon for our livelihood.
How can assassins be the people who provide for your needs?
In our underground city, only the assassins can get out.
They help the people in the world above solve different problems.
The money they earned is our only source of money here.
We depend on this money to exchange for food and items,
that's why we are able to survive here in the underground city.
Wait. How come only assassins can get out?
Can't you normal citizens get out?
Since we underground city citizens have never seen sunlight,
our body is full of dark energy.
So when we are exposed under the sun,
we will strangely bleed and die.
Are you saying that people from the underground city will die once they see sunlight?
That's right.
So tragic.
Then... how do the assassins go out?
It is because they have been training martial arts for so many years,
their bodies are stronger than ours.
But even if it's like that, they still have to drink a special medicine before going out
to guarantee that they can stay longer in the outside world.
I understand already.
Hey, right, little kid. What really is your purpose for coming here?
I came here to look for a person.
I was just about to ask you about it.
Sure. Say it. As long as I know it,
I'll tell you all.
That person is my friend.
She is a girl like me with black hair.
She should have been tied up.
Do you find her familiar?
No... didn't see her.
Hurry!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry...
Move aside! Move aside!
Hurry and get out of the way!
Hurry! Move aside!
Owner, where are those many assassins going to?
They are going to the middle point.
Middle point? What place is that?
Middle point is the place where the netherworld assassins receive their mission.
It is also the place where information is most abundant here in the underground city.
Oh, right! If you are asking around for that lady's information, I suggest you go there to ask.
Okay.
But... if you are going to go there wearing that,
you surely will be arrested and get exiled out of here.
Just think of a way then.
- Okay. Thank you, owner.- You're welcome.
For that noodle, I'll just...
This underground city is really a strange place.
Is Zi Su really in here?
I must hurry up and find her
and then take her quickly out of here.
Hey... there's another one.
How come there are so many of them today?
All are strange people. So scary.
Hey, owner. Give me a bowl of noodles.
There are no more noodles.
What?! There are no more noodles?
Let go of me! Let go of me!
My Lady Highness Princess, you better just save your energy.
With this amount of energy, why don't you just go take a nap?
You... Ding Song! You big bad guy!
You... You dared to kidnap me?!
Once I get back, I'll tell my Royal Brother to kill all your clans!
Thank you, Your Lady Highness Princess.
Hey, just be light with her.
For us, she is a treasure.
Customer, is it convenient for me to come in?
Come in.
Customer, your tea.
Please enjoy.
What are you looking at?
I just want to ask if you still have any instructions for me?
- Mr. Waiter.- Yes, please say it.
I want to ask you about something.
Wow! Just say it. Just say it.
If you can answer the question that I'll be asking,
there are still a lot of them.
Just this one is enough to make me say all that I know, to say it nonstop.
Who is the leader of this underground city?
It's of course is our Lord Xiu Fu, the city leader.
The other one will be the miracle doctor Gongsun Miao Quan.
We, the citizens of the underground city, greatly revere them.
Then recently, has your city leader left the city before?
Customer, you don't know this.
We people in the underground city cannot see sunlight.
That's why, we never went out.
Other than those heroic netherworld assassins.
Cannot see the light?
Why?
For this... you have to wait for me to clearly explain it.
Lu Yin...
I'm back.
You tell me, if one day your teacher is able to make a drug for us to be unafraid of the sun,
then we can move to the world outside.
That would be great.
Actually, going anywhere is fine with me as long as you're by my side.
You really are so boring.
You don't get interested in anything.
Of course, there is. For example, I want to be the world's number one assassin.
Then between being the no. 1 assassin and me, you can only choose one.
Who will you choose?
Of course, it's you.
I trained martial arts so that I can protect the people I want to protect.
Do you know that...
in the outside world...
I met a woman. Her name is Huang Qian Xun.
Her personality and attitude is really like yours a lot of the time.
I want to see her. But I tend to always hide very far from her.
Every time I saw her, I kept avoiding.
Because... I don't know what will happen between us in the future.
I also don't know if my heart can open up again.
Lu Yin, what exactly should I do?
Get lost! Get lost! All of you, get lost!
Hurry and move aside!
These are your fish. Please come inside.
Thank you.
This flavor is really so aromatic.
Get lost. Get lost.
It's you again!
Why are you here?
Hey, after a single shake, you changed into a chef now?
This Miss Cai is quite in a hurry.
Letting any guy just enter her shop.
I'm warning you.
Hey, don't get agitated.
I came here today but didn't want to use force, either.
So you better just stay obedient.
After I finish with official matters, I will deal with you.
May I ask if Miss Cai is around?
Older Bro Dao is here already and you don't know to come out and welcome him?
Come out, Miss Cai! Come out!
Xiao Dao, if you don't find it troublesome, then I'll tell it to you once again.
I will never sell this shop.
Even if I burn it down, I still will not sell it to you!
Okay. Okay. Not selling. Not selling.
I am not buying it, either.
I came here today is to care about your marriage.
Miss Cao, this Gao Ying Jun has already left for almost 5 years already, right?
For these past years, there has been probably more than ten lads coming here to ask your hand for marriage, right?
Shut up! What does that have to do with you?!
Of course, it concerns me.
I came here today seriously asking Ms. Cai's hand for marriage.
I believe that almost all young lads in this bay have already been rejected by you.
But I think that Ms. Cai will surely not refuse me.
- Older Sis.- Xiao Mei.
Stop trying to take advantage of my boss.
Or else, I'll let you suffer.
Xiao Cai, I am also doing this for your own good.
With such a big family business, you must have a man to manage it with you.
You don't plan to not marry forever, right?
With Gao Ying Jun dying in the seas,
and you keep refusing to get married,
if this gets out, will you end up with having a widow reputation
or some messy rumors?
Clean up your language!
Little beast, shut up!
I will soon be your master later.
Don't aim for a mile when I have already given you an inch and ask me to personally beat you up later.
That's why after thinking about it,
in this area, other than me,
there really isn't anyone else who can help you out of these troubled seas.
You better just accept these good intentions of mine.
Xiao Dao, what does my reputation have to do with you?
That's right. It indeed can be not my business.
But based on the rule in this bay, there has never been a woman who can inherit the family business.
Since you are not able to inherit your family business, automatically, you can't manage this hot springs inn.
But I am willing to be a good person and do good things to help you manage it.
That's why, I also must have an official title. Isn't that so?
Around here, who doesn't know that I'm sincere towards you?
Then rather than looking for another date, why don't we just set it to today?
Today, just officially be my wife.
How about it?
This way, as one family, we don't need to be against each other.
Pfft! A toad wanting to eat swan meat!
Xiao Mei, take Xiao Cai away first.
I'll deal with this rascal.
I'll let you taste my brush!
Who do you think you are?
You won't behave if I don't teach you a lesson, is that it?
Then I'll let you pay for both old and new grudges today then.
Buddies, attack!
Yes!
KoreanDramaX.co
♫ In a rainy night, ♫
♫ I've not put away that windbreaker umbrella ♫
♫ My hand, that grasps it, is unwilling to throw it away ♫
♫ I want to be together till the end ♫
♫ Upon opening my eyes, ♫
♫ there may be only fallen leaves all over the ground left ♫
♫ There may be only those cold long streets left ♫
♫ I have you next to me ♫
♫ We agree to wait till tomorrow ♫
♫ Wait until snow and frost compromise with sunshine ♫
♫ You must believe ♫
♫ those agreements that we made at young ♫
♫ We agree to wait till tomorrow to ♫
♫ walk through the coldest winter night and ♫
♫ kiss the most beautiful spring together ♫
♫ Stand side-by-side before the daybreak ♫