KoreanDramaX.co
Stop wasting effort.
I've sent men to block the entrance and exit.
Just be obedient and surrender to us.
You are quite nimble.
You are everywhere.
Stop giving me nonsense!
If you kneel now and beg me, you may be spared of pain.
Wait!
I urge you to clarify first my identity before making your move.
Or else, later, I might let you take the consequences.
What nonsense are you spouting?
Your Elder Jiong Ye, which is also your superior,
do you all know he is my what?
He is my father.
He's my biological father.
That's why, right now, I can be counted as your...
- What is that thing?- Young Master.
Young Master.
Aren't you all going to hurry and kneel yet to show respect to your Young Master?
Elder Jiong Ye acted against the sect's teachings and disrespected Elder Zhao Ran.
Yet you are shamelessly saying all those words here?!
Totally seditious!
Good then.
Men! Take them both!
Kill anyone who resists!
Hey! Do your Illuminati still have any rules about respecting your elders?
Look how strict the security is here.
How are we going to get out?
Hurry. Hurry.
Here.
Hey! Stop right there!
- This is an important prison area.- Let's go.
What are you two doing?
Give you a chance.
- Big Bros, I've something very good here to give to you.- What? What?
You have skills.
Who told you to belittle me?
Hurry and save them.
- Let's go. Hurry and go.- Go.
Hurry up.
Be careful!
Are you alright?
Gong Zi Xu is also with these people, right?
All of you, stop daydreaming!
Just surrender and be arrested!
Ah Ning, defending an evil one like this, you won't have a good ending!
I am afraid you won't be able to see the result anymore.
You and Elder Zhao Ran rebelled together and destroyed the reputation of the Illuminati.
Do you think that by doing that, you're going to get any benefits?
Is there any use for these words that you said?
Elder Zhao Ran said that the past Illuminati has been drowned out.
And these young children will lead the Illuminati to walk into the future.
The mighty Elder Zhao Ran will lead the Illuminati to recover its past glory!
It's not something that you ants can hinder!
Loathing the past and looking ahead at the future?
Then are people's lives not important anymore?
Then just die for the future of the Illuminati then.
Stop misleading the public here!
Take them all down!
- Older Bro Fei, how are you?- Yuan Shuai.
- If you have guts, then just attack!- Charge!
Charge!
Be careful!
Let's go!
Quickly go! Go!
The time didn't pass.
I've been walking for quite a long time and again returned here.
The time didn't change at all.
What really is going on here?
Zhao Ran?
You really made it hard for me to find you.
It turns out that you're here.
Where is the Magic Star?
Don't daydream anymore.
Stop your nonsense.
Give me the Magic Star!
Do you want the Magic Star?
You first have to get past me.
Zi Su...
Be careful.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you? Are you alright?
Hurry and find Elder Chang Ming.
Or else, the Illuminati will be done for.
But Elder Chang Ming has been in seclusion for so many years.
I don't really know where his seclusion chamber is.
The seclusion chamber is inside the labyrinth.
How come you don't know that?
A Ji Ya, there are a lot of things that happened in between these past years.
You don't really understand the real situation.
Then what should we do?
Just letting Elder Zhao Ran continue with his tyrannical abuse?
Don't we have any other way at all?
The Elder Chang Ming that you're talking about has already been gravely injured by Elder Zhao Ran;
don't know if he's dead or alive.
These three people here are the envoys sent by Elder Chang Ming.
Elder Chang Ming?
Not sure if dead or alive?
A Ji Ya!
- A Ji Ya!- A Ji Ya!
Bai Ze!
♫ I'm sorry that I'm not a doll ♫
♫ Smiling for a long time will make me tired ♫
♫ Whatever way I want to think, I think that way. ♫
♫ I'm too lazy to pretend again ♫
♫ I'm sorry that I'm not good in imitating ♫
♫ that kind of graciousness you want ♫
A Ji Ya...
No matter if we can get out of this labyrinth today or not,
there are some words in my heart that I must tell you.
I'll bear this familial revenge of yours together with you.
You hate me and blame me.
I will bear all of them.
But the remaining sins... have nothing to do with them.
If killing me can make you happy,
I am willing to die for you.
♫ that you could let go any time because you’re bored ♫
♫ as nothing has happened ♫
♫ I'm sorry that I'm not a doll ♫
♫ Smiling for a long time will make me tired ♫
♫ Whatever way I want to think, I think that way ♫
Look, Lord! Over there!
♫ I'm sorry that I'm not good in imitating ♫
A Ji Ya! A Ji Ya!
A Ji Ya!
- A Ji Ya!- A Ji Ya!
- A Ji Ya! - A Ji Ya!
Ah Ning... I'll let you die a tragic death!
A Ji Ya!
Stop them! Hurry!
Ah Ning!
A Ji Ya, we grew up together.
You are in almost all my memories.
You divided a dagger into two and gave me one of them.
I have always treasured and kept it by my side.
To invite Oldest Elder Chang Ming to come back and take charge of matters...
At this time, am I not the one who should stand out and bear that responsibility?
Wait for me here.
Looks like absorbing the powers of young children, you real are indeed extraordinary.
But what's the use?
Today, you will die here as a sacrificial offering to those dead children.
Aren't you thinking so simply?
The thousands of years of glory of the Illuminati will be revived during my time.
If you don't want to die, just obediently hand over the Magic Star.
I can give you a not-so-bad ending at the very least.
I don't know where the Magic Star came from,
but it has never belonged to the mortal world.
Do you know why this underground palace exists?
The duty to guard the door connecting the Strange World to the mortal world has long been forgotten.
I think... you and me both should remember it very clearly.
Right now, I already found clues in the Bloody Pool on how to open the Strange World's main door.
As long as I can gather all Magic Stars, I can then absorb unending power.
By that time, I can then open the door to the Strange World, rule both the Strange and Human worlds,
using the Illuminati's name to fulfill this grand ambition!
Did your brain get stuck in the door?
Can you even have these kinds of daydreams?
The helmet that the Demon King left in the mortal world was in the Bloody Pool.
I controlled myself numerous times and dared not to wear it.
But once I have the Magic Stars, it will be different. When that time comes,
using the Magic Stars' power, I can stimulate the power within the demonic helmet.
The person who will obtain all its power will be me.
The Demon King's Helmet?
Let's go.
Mister, you are...
He Cao... are you willing to serve me loyally forever?
Yes.
Since Elder Jiong Ye got sick, I transferred under Elder Zhao Ran
and became his lackey.
Right now, at this moment, it's his time to pay back everything.
Older Bro Fei, where are you going?
I'm going to look for Elder Zhao Ran to seek vengeance for A Ji Ya.
Let's go help, too.
Mister!
What's going on?
Helmet?
You don't have much time left now.
Think about if you want to obediently hand over the Magic Star. At the very least,
I can leave you a tablet inside the Three Sacred Palace.
In the past, you killed Elder Chang Ming
and then made a lie that he was training in seclusion.
And now, you're telling me that you are going to make me a tablet?
I am not stupid.
It seems that the explosion came from there.
Let's go inside and take a look. Let's go.
- Let's go.- Let's go.
This is not the place that you can enter.
Leave now, you all.
Big Bro Chong Yun!
The Magic Star!
Are you alright?
How come it's like this?
The Magic Star actually is being used to refine the Bloody Pool?!
What's wrong with you, Xiong Fei?
Be careful!
Never thought...
Gong Zi Xu.
Never thought that there'd be a person who can get the Magic Star as easily as that.
Why are you here?
Give the Magic Star to me.
It doesn't belong to you two.
It belongs to me.
It belongs to the Demon King!
How come I feel that this thing in his head is not that friendly.
My Illuminati's three elders.
Oldest Elder Chang Ming
has long gave up all his sect responsibilities
and went into the path of cultivation.
He already has no power to interfere with Illuminati matters.
Elder Zhao Ran willfully changed the sect's rules and
went against the sacred laws of the Three Gods of Illumination.
Elder Jiong Ye got tricked by an evil person
who blurred his consciousness.
Then it is just natural that the person who should be the main authority in the Illuminati
is me, the Leader of Red Clothed,
Gong Zi Xu!
That thing in your head...
Demon King's Helmet.
Demon King?
Zhao Ran, you wasted so much effort.
The Magic Star isn't with me.
You can't fool me.
Looks like... you are not really just after the Magic Star.
You also want to take the Star Chart, too.
Only with Star Chart can you find the Magic Stars.
Only by gathering all Magic Stars
can you activate the helmet's power.
You indeed are a Heaven Strategy Envoy.
You know the special properties of Magics Stars more than anyone else.
But when you arrived here at the labyrinth,
the Magic Star was indeed with me.
But right now, it's not with me anymore.
A Ji Ya, this child, thinks deeper than anyone.
She was able to follow the directions on the Star Chart up to this mountain.
it shows she has never forgotten the Hanyu Code I taught her
when I played with her when she was younger.
After all, A Ji Ya is a kind child.
And you, Zhao Ran, killed Elder Chang Ming.
You learned the Diablo Scriptures.
You are no longer a human!
You dare use such underhanded tricks to lie to me!
Playing magic tricks is my best skills.
It is mainly used to entertain people.
Elder Zhao Ran, how do you feel today?
Even if it is like this, the Magic Star won't leave the Illuminati!
However, next year on this day, it'll be your death anniversary!
My death anniversary? It should be our death anniversary!
Master, the Illuminati and the Demon World are complete opposites!
How can you wear the helmet of the Demon King?
This kind of evil item, how can it be hidden within the Illuminati?
His mind has already been bewitched by the Demon King's Helmet.
Today, all of you
have to bow before my feet!
Hold this well.
Xiong Fei!
Gong Zi Xu, wake up!
Zi Su!
- A demon exterminator?- Xiong Fei...
Mister, since the Illuminati had been guarding this place,
no one is allowed to have any aspirations towards the Demon world!
You are a member of the Illuminati!
Have you forgotten that?
I've always respected the Illuminati since young.
Every day I work hard for them.
I worked for Zhao Ran without ever complaining about it.
They have actually killed my beloved A Ji Ya!
Only when I have all the highest power in the world, the power of the Magic Stars,
can I make the people who hurt me pay!
It is time to fight now.
It is time to take revenge for A Ji Ya.
Zi Su!
I will take revenge for A Ji Ya.
Give me your life!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Why? Why?
How is this possible? This is impossible!
Go away!
I want to kill them to take revenge for A Ji Ya!
Let's go.
What do we do?
Zhan Xiong Fei, are Chong Yun and the others... already dead?
What should we do now?
This thing... shouldn't be kept here.
KoreanDramaX.co
This passage, how can it have such a place?
Jiong Ye, you come out right now!
Where have you hidden the Magic Star?
A Ji Ya...
Zhan Xiong Fei, do you think we will die here today?
It will be fine.
Don't worry.
I will look after you.
Lord Ma, it must have been a tiring journey.
Have some water.
Lord,
why will the Illuminati, an organization that claims to be leak proof,
suddenly sell us information regarding the Magic Stars?
Actually, there is no place that doesn't leak water.
As long as there is hard currency,
any place will start leaking.
I'm close to the Red Clothed left hand envoy of the Illuminati, Ah Ning.
He says, as long as you are willing to bring manpower to
help him to become an elder,
then the Magic Stars in his hands will all be given to you.
Cut the crap.
Let's all go up to the mountain.
You... have to go with me as well.
You are going up there dressed like that.
I fear it will be inconvenient.
Men!
Take him down now!
Why are you still standing there?
Left Hand Envoy Ah Ning and Elder Zhao Ran,
willfully changed the sect's rules,
broke the sacred laws of the Three Gods,
and plotted to change the sect's direction and have ulterior motives.
I, Gong Zi Xu, today in the name of the Illuminati,
will clear the sect of evil!
All you red-clothed soldiers listen!
While Elder Zhao Ran sat in the leadership position,
he has done too many despicable deeds.
He defamed our sect and disgraced the Three Gods,
but today, his whereabouts are unknown. He went missing.
Our Illuminati cannot be without a leader for a day.
So I will take over his place as Elder!
No way. No way. No way.
Elder Zhao Ran clearly was inside that labyrinth.
How can you say he is not here?
Who else has any complaints?
We support Gong Zi Xu to lead the Illuminati!
Let's go.
Where are you going?
Hey! Bai Ze, are you alright?
Where are you going, Bai Ze?
Bai Ze!
- Are you alright?- I'm fine.
This must be the Thousand Return Door.
It should be.
This is the place that your father entered.
But where is your father?
And Elder Zhao Ran?
Where are they?
There seemed to be people who have came here but have already left.
Let's just go inside and take a look.
Let's go.
This... Isn't this the room earlier?
How come it's so strange here?
Let's take a look again.
We're back again!
What ghostly place is this?!
How come it's like a maze?
No. No. No. Let's take a rest for a while.
What do we do?
We've been encircling for a long time and haven't found anything.
Zhan Xiong Fei, I'm so hungry.
If this continues,
will we starve to death here?
I don't want to. I don't want to.
We won't starve to death.
We won't. Don't worry.
Even if we really are unable to get out,
don't forget, I am the Illuminati's Young Master.
They will surely come here to save me.
Although they don't recognize me as such,
they still wouldn't be ruthless to allow a flower to be destroyed, right?
What situation has it been already and you're still making jokes.
Don't worry.
With me around, I definitely won't let you be in danger.
Bluff. Just continue bluffing, Zhan Xiong Fei.
I am telling the truth.
Even if I have to risk my life, I won't let you be hurt.
I don't believe.
Hey, oh, right. Zi Su, last time, I wasn't able to tell you
that my astrological sign is your sign's guardian angel.
I am not listening to your nonsense anymore.
Just continue making up things everyday.
Zi Su...
If... I said if...
If what?
If... the two of us really got stuck here and can't go out forever,
what would you do?
Stuck here forever?
Won't that be so boring?
How can it be boring?
I will surely do magic tricks to make you laugh.
And also, we surely would have a lot of words which we wouldn't be able to run out.
It won't be boring.
But this place is not as fun as the one outside.
The outside world is so wonderful.
There are so much delicious food.
What good is there in here?
What's the difference of me being locked up inside the palace?
It wasn't easy for me to be able to get out of the palace.
I don't want to be trapped in here.
The difference with that of the palace is it's so huge, okay?
I'm not inside the palace.
Then does it mean... you are quite willing to get trapped here with me?
You... if you are not willing, then I'm not willing, either.
If you are willing, I will then be willing.
KoreanDramaX.co
Stop! Who are you?!
Stop.
[Left Hand Envoy Ah Ning's seal]
Left Hand Envoy Ah Ning's seal?
It's good that you know it.
After seeing Left Hand Envoy Ah Ning's seal, aren't you still going to make way?
Lord Gong Zi has ordered that Left Hand Envoy Ah Ning betrayed the sect.
We are cleaning the sect of all traitors right now.
All men of Ah Ning must be killed.
- What's going on?!- I don't know, either.
There must be some misunderstandings behind this.
This is called a misunderstanding?!
Are you Ah Ning?
Creating such a mess and causing me to lose men. Is that okay?
Ah Ning is already dead!
Okay. Then you are making a deal with me in place of him, am I right?
Stop touching me.
I'll get back to you later.
Men! Take this mob down!
Wait!
We still haven't talked about the price so why are we fighting again?
Lord, he is not with Left Hand Envoy Ah Ning.
What? Why didn't you say so earlier?
What are you still standing there for?
Attack!
Zhao Ran?
What is that?
Is it the Magic Star?
Hurry and give it to me!
I told you. I won't let you get out of this maze.
What really is this thing?
What is this place?
What are you panicking about?
I can be benevolent and tell you that this is a toy box.
This toy box is the ultimate secret key of this Thousand Return Door.
In it is the whole labyrinth including all of us in here.
What I will be doing now is to
remove everyone else in this maze and just leave us two here.
And then... destroy it.
Stop day dreaming already.
Stop using child's play to trick me.
Do you believe that I will destroy this?
Then destroy it now!
I surely will!
Let's go.
Father! You are indeed in here!
Are you alright?! Father...
Zhao Ran, you dare bully my father?!
Look at my skills!
- Xiong Fei!- Child...
- Are you alright?- Of course, I'm fine.
♫ How long can my friends around me to accompany me? ♫
♫ I’m tired of hearing those comforting words ♫
♫ I’m pulled between courage and collapse repeatedly ♫
♫ I cry out to myself to hang in there ♫
♫ I’m still awake at 3 in the early morning ♫
♫ I can only expect for a good night sleep but not having it ♫
♫ If I’m not careful, I’ll be disturbed once I think about you ♫
♫ Memory has been overturned into a kind of sin ♫
♫ Having loved one very much is wrong but so what ♫
♫ Loneliness is also just a process ♫
♫ We still have next person waiting for us ♫
♫ I’ll remember those wonderful things ♫
♫ Shedding tears isn’t need ♫
♫ Thank you for your choosing ♫
♫ Don’t force myself to give blessing ♫
♫ Be a mature person ♫
♫ Having loved one very much is worth the pain and so happy ♫
♫ Having loved one very much is wrong but so what ♫
♫ Loneliness is also just a process ♫
♫ We still have next person waiting for us ♫
♫ With a little regret, I’m more complete ♫