KoreanDramaX.co
But based on the rule in this bay, there has never been a woman who can inherit the family business.
Since you are not able to inherit your family business,
automatically, you can't manage this hot springs inn.
But I want to be a good person and do a good deed in helping you manage it.
That's why, I also must have an official title.
Isn't that so?
Around here,
who doesn't know that I'm sincere towards you?
Then rather than looking for another date, why don't we just set it to today?
Today, just officially be my wife.
How about it?
This way, as one family, we don't need to be against each other.
Pfft! A toad wanting to eat swan meat!
Xiao Mei, take Xiao Cai away first.
I'll deal with this rascal.
I'll let you taste my brush!
Who do you think you are?
You won't behave if I don't teach you a lesson.
Then I'll let you pay for both old and new grudges today then.
Buddies, attack!
Yes!
Drag him away!
Don't let me see him again!
- Get up.- Stop! Stop!
Stop! Get lost!
- Yuan Shuai.- What? So does that mean you agree?
Xiao Cai, don't mind me.
Hurry and go.
Xiao Dao, if I marry you, you'll give up already. Is that it?
Right.
So many years have passed.
In this bay, other than me, who else will be willing to marry you?
Come, Yuan Shuai.
Xiao Dao, then let me tell you.
All the people here, please be my witness.
He, Yuan Shuai, is my fiancé.
We have already privately pledged to be married to each other. Soon we'll have a marriage ceremony.
From now on, I will be his person.
Do you have any question?
Zhou Xiao Cai, do you think that just randomly grabbing a person, you'd be pledged to be married?
Do you think I am a three-year-old child?
Who are you fooling?
Can someone just randomly speak about one's marriage?
After all, our Zhou family also is a respectable family.
No matter in how much dire straits we end up, we still won't need a rascal like you to prop up our reputation.
Xiao Dao, look well.
Yuan Shuai, let me ask you.
Are you willing to marry me, Zhou Xiao Cai, as your wife?
Answer.
I am willing.
Fine, Zhou Xiao Cai. You just have to do this, is that it?
Then don't blame me for not giving you any retreat path.
Xiao Dao, listen well.
He, Yuan Shuai, is my fiancé.
Zhou Xiao Cai...
Fine. I even thought you loved your Older Bro Ying Jun so much.
Looks like, you are only like this.
Everyone, just disperse.
By that time, we will let everyone attend the wedding.
We surely will entertain you all well.
Fine. You win for today.
- Move out!- Get lost!
Move aside! Move aside!
Xiao Cai, don't worry.
- Older sis...- I surely will treat you well for the rest of my life.
- you are not planning to...- No matter if the world ends,
I will still be loyal to you.
Older Sis, I never thought that you were this kind of person.
When you kill, you attack so fast that the enemy is caught unprepared. Just publicly announcing your fiancé.
You tell me. If you're that good, why didn't you just say that Xiao Dao was you fiancé?
Bullying a chef who has amnesia. Do you think it's fun?
I also was just forced to do it.
You also saw that situation earlier.
If it was you, you also would do the same.
If I'd known earlier...
Hey, Little Sister, stop saying cynical remarks.
Hurry and help me think of an idea.
If we are not able to think of an idea by today, I'll kick Yuan Shuai out.
Older Sis, is everything really clear to you?
Then kick him out. He isn't my fiancé anyway.
Based on what?
We worked hard to earn money outside and we will just give it to you?
First, you privately pocketing the reward has violated a major law of the underground city.
Second, this money isn't going to me.
When you all were still training in the assassin's camp,
didn't you eat and use the best ones?
When you have become true assassins, that is when you repay the underground city.
Can't we even use this money to buy medicine for our sick father?
Your father is sick?
Does your father know about this?
If he knew about it, would he approve of your doing?
My father was the one who raised me.
Now that I have attained achievements,
can't I even repay him?
I am not tasked to reply to such questions.
- You decide by yourself.- You...
This girl looks quite outstanding.
I'm guessing that she must be the leader here.
Maybe I can even get some clues from her.
Do you dare steal my money?
When have I tried stealing your money?
What is this?
Your money bag. What else can it be?
- He is an outsider!- Hey...
Calm down. Calm down.
I only just stole a money bag. Do you guys have to be like this?
Stop!
A few of you take him up here.
As for the rest, just disperse.
Yes.
Go. I'm returning this to you.
Older Sis. Older Sis!
What is it?
Now that our business is doing well,
tell me, what should we do?
What 'what should we do'?
Yuan Shuai.
What really do you want to say?
Yuan Shuai is currently our shop's main profit source.
Our shop's business is doing so great now all thanks to him.
You are not telling me to betray Older Bro Ying Jun, right?
Older Sis, what are you thinking?
I didn't mean it that way.
What I mean is Yuan Shuai will never keep being a chef here.
He just hasn't regained his memories yet for now.
Once he does, he surely will hate us.
Even if he doesn't, he most likely won't keep staying here to work for us.
I also thought about that problem.
But right now, we don't have a better way.
Older Sis, you have studied more than me.
Think of a way.
The books have everything but it never taught me how to make a person stay.
Based on my observations these past days,
I noticed that our customers here are not really coming for the hot springs,
nor the little yellow fish set meal.
Then what is their purpose?
Could it be that they are coming here because of us?
Of course not.
It's the sauce ingredient.
Sauce ingredient?
Right now, there are already a lot of customers asking me
if we can sell the sauce separately.
Do you know what this means?
This means that the sauce is our store's main selling point.
Recently, I have been helping him as his assistant.
I have been indirectly asking him about it.
He said that this is a family secret recipe. He cannot tell it to outsiders.
If the sauce is our shop's main selling point,
then I must think of a way to get it.
I indeed want to tell you about this matter.
We will be unable to let him stay but we must keep the sauce.
Am I being unkind for thinking that way?
Have you forgotten those words that you said before?
All hard work that one does just to protect oneself
is worthy to be understood.
Xiao Mei, it's good that you are here.
Just good. Just good. I have something to ask you.
What?
Did you feel that after Xiao Cai proposed marriage to me,
she seems to be avoiding me these past days.
You can't blame my older sis about that!
No. No. I am not blaming her.
But you also know that my brain isn't working that well now.
Did I do anything wrong that had angered her?
And also I am a little suspicious...
Suspicious of what?
Suspicious that she is just using me.
No. How could my older sis use you?
Don't you know how you wooed her before?
Don't you know that you two were already in talks of marriage before?
Don't you know how sincere older sis is towards you?
I really don't remember all these that you are saying.
Can you tell them to me?
Oh, no. Isn't he asking me to lie?
Older Bro Ying Jun, so sorry.
I can only transfer what happened to you to him.
Actually, you know older sister better than she knows herself.
Can you say it more clearly?
You even know that she only drinks lukewarm water.
There are a lot of things that you can make just right for her.
You know that she can't drink wine but loves to join in the fun.
That's why, you made grape wine desserts to satisfy her curiosity.
Actually, the most important point among everything
is that in the past, you will immediately appear as long as older sister needs you.
You never disappointed her.
So I was that kind of person before.
Xiao Mei, I will remember everything that you have said.
For Xiao Cai, I must work harder to be a better person.
Xiao Mei,
your story making abilities are way better than mine.
Not really. Not really.
You made the story of Older Bro Ying Jun as Yuan Shuai's.
Don't think I don't know.
Then Older Sister, what else can I do?
Do you want me to tell him that we lied to him?
What? Older Sister, you're feeling sorry for him now?
What are you saying?
I just feel that by doing that, we are wronging Older Bro Ying Jun.
Older Bro Ying Jun has already been–
He hasn't come back for so long already.
He doesn't know our situation, either.
Once we get the sauce recipe,
even if he regains his memories and leaves,
our days won't also be that hard. Isn't that so?
Do we still have any other way out now?
Could it be...
that I really have to marry Yuan Shuai?
Anyway, if you keep being cold to him like this,
even a stupid person can see that something is wrong.
Leader Lan Ling, we already brought the person.
Leave then.
But... this brat tried stealing my reward.
You're so talkative.
- Just a measly thief. Leave.- Yes.
Hurry and leave.
Did you come from outside?
Right. You noticed it.
You are quite good.
I don't really have some bad intentions in coming here to your place.
I just want to ask you to help me find a person.
Find a person?
Do you know what this place is?
Coming here to find a person?
I know.
This is the Middle Point, the scariest place in the whole Yongzhou Underground City.
All assassins are here.
But looking how kind you are,
you surely will help me.
Her name is Zi Su.
Have you heard of her?
If you are just looking for someone,
why did you steal the assassin's reward?
Wow! Killing one person amounts to so much money?!
Oh, so sorry. What were you saying earlier?
I asked you why you stole the assassin's reward money when you were just looking for a person.
Because... I want to see you.
- See me?- That's right.
I saw how mighty you were earlier outside.
You must be the leader here at the Middle Point, right?
I think that you surely can help me.
What made you think that I will help you?
Because...
Look. I am so handsome, so young, and I–
I'm not that handsome–
Smooth-talker... pestering unreasonably!
That...
Say it. What really is your purpose in coming here?
I already told you. I am here to look for a friend.
Her name is Zi Su.
Have you heard of her or not?
Hey.
Do you people here in underground city never really see the sun?
If you never saw the sun, then you never saw a sunflower.
If you never saw a sunflower, then you never eaten sunflower seeds.
Not being able to eat sunflower seeds at all is really so pitiful.
- You!- What you?
Going. Goodbye.
Stop!
Just leaving like that?
Isn't that making it too easy for you?
Let me tell you. If you don't want to help, then don't.
You shouldn't be like this.
Don't do things too excessive so it won't be awkward if we meet again.
Do you understand?
How about this? You agree with my one condition.
I won't go after your misdeeds
and will even allow you to temporarily stay here in my place.
How about it?
What condition?
I want you to tell me stories from the outside world whenever I'm free.
This... okay. Okay.
If we want to save this island,
then we must hand over one person as the scapegoat.
Do you think that this plan will work?
We only have this plan at this time.
We can only try.
Who should we hand to them?
Whoever stole the ship, we give him up.
Cheng Ming Pan?
Right.
The navy isn't an easy opponent.
They are unlikely to let things go if we just give them some random person.
I already told you before
that if we want this place to last long, we must stop our illegal dealings and start anew.
As long as this place continues to be a pirate bay, it will never be able to escape danger.
I know. Right now, let's first get past this difficulty.
But Cheng Ming Pan's strength is also something that cannot be belittled.
So...
how can we be able to hand him over to the government?
If we add our current strengths, we still won't be able to defeat him.
That's right.
Moreover, his sailors are well-trained for battles.
Master! Master!
Master, Da Fu is here.
Okay. You can leave now.
Yes.
Why did you come here?
Of course, I'm here to help you.
Let us then get straight to the point.
What you need is a pirate leader that can serve as the scapegoat,
while I want a captain position.
Just right, we can just get what we each want.
For Cheng Ming Pan to be able to be in his status now, there must be a reason.
Moreover, he has so many men under him, all powerful and well-trained.
I do want to hear your idea.
As long as he is not the captain, with just his individual strength,
he is at most like a grasshopper after autumn.
It would be easier to just kill him than not letting him be the captain.
Not really.
As the second in command of the ship,
I know very well how the sailors are thinking.
Our brothers have all been unsatisfied with him for a long time already.
It's just that no one is talking.
Could it be that you want to oust him?
That's right. Our ship has it's own rules.
The captain is someone that all of us chose.
Right now, the men that I can guarantee haven't reached a half of our crew.
I still need 20 votes.
How is it, you two?
Are you interested?
Just leave the rest to us.
KoreanDramaX.co
You were non-benevolent so don't blame me for being disloyal!
118, I already guessed that you would come back to cause trouble.
For the sake of your old father,
if you leave now, I can treat it as if nothing happened.
Lan Ling, since I already came, I never thought of going back.
Since you dared to humiliate me publicly today,
I must make you pay!
Stop saying nonsense and making false counter charges.
It was you who broke the rules first.
If I don't punish you, how am I going to make the others obey?
Stop your nonsense! Watch my move!
Never thought after training in martial arts,
you actually used it against your own kind.
I am not able to defeat you. I am willing to accept punishment.
Who are you?!
Stop!
Don't run!
Before you die, I'll let you see the sun once.
That's already worth it.
You crazy person!
Lan Ling.
Zhan Xiong Fei.
Let's go.
Lan Ling, let's go.
Zhan Xiong Fei!
Lan Ling, go back to the underground city!
Where is the cave entrance?
I can't see it.
Just keep walking left!
Do you think... this person can be trusted?
I can see greed in him.
When a person's greed swells, it is the scariest.
As long as something threatens the Pirate Bay,
no one can be totally safe.
Why are you so attached to this place?
Because this island...
is my home.
If you tell that to other people, maybe they will believe you.
Then just believe what you want.
Ming Zhen, I know
that you have been protecting this place.
Surviving on this island where most people are men
and even swearing with your life to protect it,
you must have your reasons.
- I won't ask but you also can't--- Don't continue saying it anymore.
Fine.
I just want to tell you.
I will forever help you guard the Pirate Bay.
Tell me.
How are we going to get the remaining votes?
Don't worry.
I already asked my men to check on it.
Master.
Master, I have already investigated it.
How was it? Hurry and say.
There are total of 73 people on the ship.
Thirty-plus people are Cheng Ming Pan's loyal supporters.
The remaining ones which we can convince can be divided into three groups.
As long as we can get them, we can win.
Please continue.
One of the three group's leader is someone who likes to drink a lot.
I really have to thank you this time.
You really were so courageous.
If not because of you, I might have–
Being a real man,
it's unreasonable for me to just look at my friend in danger
and not do anything.
But I still have to thank you.
Enough already. No need.
Then... continue telling me stories from outside.
Ah... how about let's skip today?
I am going to find Zi Su.
I'll just tell it to you when I return.
But the underground city is so big.
Do you know where to find her?
Even if the chance is too small, I still will do my best.
This Ms. Zi Su is really lucky to have a friend like you.
I'm going then.
That... I'll cook you some delicious food when you return.
Okay.
Come. One more.
Come.
Mister Feng, I heard that you don't drink.
Right. I don't.
On this island, you can count with one hand the people who don't drink.
But as the old saying goes, 'One pot of wine, one group of friends,
even the gods are envious'.
Come.
Mister Feng, listening to what you said, this wine isn't for free, right?
As long as we are able to discuss things well,
I guarantee you that you'll have never-ending good wine.
Just for a mouthful of wine, I will never do things that will endanger my life.
Don't worry. I will surely not let you be killed.
I won't do things that will offend my buddies, either.
Not only will you not offend your buddies,
it can even make you and your buddies have a good life.
Mister Feng, with you saying it like that, I am already confused.
What do you mean?
Come.
I want to ask you, what is your reason for being a pirate?
Trying to earn some food to eat.
Being exposed to the wind and sun all day,
always risking your life, who would want to do such a job?
But from what I can see, you all right now aren't that rich.
What do you mean?
For those products that you recently got, how much did each of you get?
Mister Feng, this is a private matter within our ship.
It doesn't really concern you, right?
Although it doesn't have much concern with me,
you still have to think about it well for your wine and your buddies, right?
I know. You guys are looking forward for your payment for three months already.
But how much have you received?
What really do you want to say?
Don't you want to change to a captain that can lead you all to success?
I won't do such a thing.
I know what you are thinking.
Whoever extends their hand first might be able to be the first one to get it.
Actually, it's very easy. I just need you all to raise your hands.
- Us?- Right.
You and your group of buddies.
They might not listen to me.
But they will surely listen to this.
That one earlier is for your hard work.
This one is for the wine money for your buddies.
Come, let's drink!
Cheers!
You can choose not to believe me.
Let me ask you one question.
If this time the capital investigates this matter,
will the strength of just your ship
be able to go against them?
I understand what you mean.
Aren't you just asking me to betray?
Then let me ask you a question, too.
Do you think I am such a kind of person?
I am thinking for your sake.
I can totally tell the capital that
the ship was robbed by you guys.
Then why didn't you do that?
You guys and pirate bay are interdependent.
If you're down, the bay will be in danger.
I don't understand what you mean.
What I mean is...
I don't want more people to suffer just because of his decision.
Then let me tell you, too,
that every decision he makes is for our sake.
Even if you will die, are you still willing?
With him around, we won't die.
Have you all thought about the consequences of doing this?
No need for you to worry about that.
I know your status here including your relations with the captain.
I can treat that nothing happened today.
Wait.
If you still don't want to completely be an enemy of our captain,
then don't say anything anymore.
If it was just for myself,
I can choose not to say it.
But...
Based on your actions,
it seems that you won't stop until this matter is done then.
I think you already know very well my stand on this matter.
I am urging you to stop for the last time.
Or else, I can't guarantee that I won't tell captain about it.
Are you sure that is what you are going to do?
Unless you kill me now.
What? You killed him?
Right.
At this time, how could you...
In that situation that time, killing him was the best choice.
If things have progressed to this level,
then we don't have much time left.
Once Cheng Ming Pan discovers it,
we will then attract disaster to ourselves.
Are there anybody else that we can draw to our side?
We can only try.
The hardest one to deal with is someone without any desires or wishes.
I'll go with you.
You illness isn't very serious.
- Good.- As long as you take your medicines on time,
within three days, you'll totally be cured.
Thank you, miracle doctor.
- Please be careful on your way home.- Okay.
- Let's go.- Let's go.
After three days, return here again.
Okay. Okay.
Teacher!
Qian Zhen?
I was not filial.
Hurry and get up. Quickly get up.
You finally returned.
On my way here,
all the corners here are memories.
It's good that you are back. It's good that you're back.
Congratulations, 929.
The Netherworld Assassin Camp Leader and I
have decided to promote you to be the assassin team leader.
Thank you, City Leader, for promoting me.
In the Assassin Camp, there are only five team leaders.
The next camp leader will also come from you five.
I personally support you for that position.
I will surely not disappoint city leader.
The netherworld assassins kill for a lifetime and look cold and heartless,
but you all are the heroes of the underground city.
You all use your life and fresh blood
to guard the peace and happiness of the citizens of the underground city.
Forever do not forget your duty.
Yes. I will forever remember it.
Okay.
Go to the middle person to receive your first mission.
Yes.
Never thought that at a young age, you would become an assassin team leader.
Take this.
[Duan Residence: Duan's Family of Five.]
The first mission I got was to kill all five people in the Duan family.
Not even letting an infant live.
For a newbie like me, how could I bear to do it.
Hence...
City Leader!
This is the first time that such a thing happened in our Netherworld Assassin Camp.
He didn't only affect the reputation of the assassin camp,
but he also affected the safety of our Yongzhou Underground City.
929 must have his reasons.
No matter what his reasons are,
his doings have already broken the rules of the netherworld assassins.
City Leader, please give out an order to let us arrest 929.
What if he refuses to come back?
Then we can only kill him.
You all just leave first.
Yes.
City Leader.
No need to tell me, I already know why you are here.
I beg City Leader to spare Qian Zhen.
Qian Zhen must have his reasons.
I surely will investigate this matter well.
But first, we have to catch him and bring him back here first.
Or else, public opinion is powerful enough to melt metal.
I also won't have a way to help him anymore.
I couldn't win and got arrested by the camp leader
then imprisoned.
I thought that I would surely die that time.
City Leader.
Open the door.
City Leader, please.
City Leader?
All of you can leave.
Yes.
City Leader.
Teacher.
Teacher, why did you come?
Qian Zhen, I'm sorry.
I brought you into this city yet I let you walk onto this path.
Teacher, don't blame yourself.
This is a path that I chose on my own.
It has nothing to do with other people.
If not for this matter, I initially planned to really train you well
and pass you the city leader position in the future.
City Leader, what are these words that you are saying?
I don't have the capabilities
to be the leader of Yongzhou Underground City.
Other than me liking you as a person, there is also another reason.
If I let someone who grew up in the underground city to be the city leader,
when they are in power,
they will develop desire towards the outside world.
If by that time they will do some extreme measures,
the one who will suffer are my underground city citizens.
There isn't any more meaning to talk about these things.
From now on, we can only leave the fate of the underground city to Heaven's will and to destiny.
Qian Zhen,
hurry. Drink this medicine.
What is this?
This is the Nimble Transformation Pill that I created.
I initially created it to prolong the aging of city leader's body.
This medicine has one side effect.
But this side effect can exactly be useful at this time.
What is the side effect of this medicine?
After you take this medicine, within 10 hours,
you will lose all signs of life.
But after the effect resolves, you will regain your bodily functions.
When you wake up, we will have already transported you out of the city.
Child, come over here.
After you get out, you must take good care of yourself.
It's done.
Men!
City Leader, are you alright?
Qian Zhen tried to abduct me and escape.
He has already been knocked unconscious by me.
You go over there and take a look.
Yes.
City Leader, Qian Zheng is already dead.
Qian Zhen also worked for our Yongzhou's Assassin Camp a lot.
Take some people and carry him out of the city.
Look for a place and bury him.
Yes.
I can only help you until here.
The path that you will walk from now on will depend on you.
Qian Zhen, you must go as far away from here as possible.
Don't ever return.
From now on, you are free.
After you left, I hoped that you would never return here.
But in the end, the person who asked you to return
was I.
But Teacher,
what exactly happened here in the underground city?
The prophecy of old city leader unfortunately has happened.
Lord Xiu Fu feels that he has abundant strength now
and wants to use the Magic Stars to summon God's Army.
Leading the underground city citizens to charge out towards the outside world.
He repeatedly came here to look for me
to ask for the medication to make the underground citizens be forever unafraid of the sun.
He's also coveting the Magic Stars, right?
If we let his plan succeed,
it will become a disaster for both the citizens of
the underground city and outside world.
Then Teacher, is there really such a medicine?
No.
But Lord Xiu Fu doesn't want to believe it.
To stop his plan, after careful thoughts, the only person who can help me
is only you.
No matter how sturdy a wood is, it can't win over a knife.
Did you travel far to come here to just watch me carve wood?
We came here to–
Actually sometimes, whether to become the knife or the wood,
is just a moment's decision.
Wood is wood.
A knife is a knife.
We came here this time to tell you
that something bad will happen to your ship.
You should go look for captain for such matters.
Why look for me?
Because your choice will determine the fate of all the lives on your ship.
I don't have such great capabilities.
If you've offended the capital, do you think you all can still live?
Which one is more difficult, living or dying?
Could it be that you like to die that much?
If everyone on the ship has died and only I survived,
how long do you think the sea god will let me live?
Where did that some sea god come from?
Here.
Stop wasting efforts.
I have a debt of gratitude towards Cheng Ming Pan.
I won't betray him.
Don't fret first.
Let's think of another way.
If it's still won't work,
- it's better to let me personally–- No.
If he dies,
there won't be any use at all.
If we do battle with him face to face, we both are not his match.
Da Hu Zi is very famous for being heartless.
But if we continue to drag this out,
we will become very passive.
Let me try.
Who told you to come in?
If I can convince Da Hu Zi,
you must promise me one condition.
I don't know what you are talking about.
Get out.
Wait.
Let him speak.
What do you plan to do?
I don't need you to bother on how I will do it.
But I believe that I surely can convince Da Hu Zi.
I don't know from where are you getting this confidence of yours?
KoreanDramaX.co
♫ In a rainy night, ♫
♫ I've not put away that windbreaker umbrella ♫
♫ My hand, that grasps it, is unwilling to throw it away ♫
♫ I want to be together till the end ♫
♫ Upon opening my eyes, ♫
♫ there may be only fallen leaves all over the ground left ♫
♫ There may be only those cold long streets left ♫
♫ I have you next to me ♫
♫ We agree to wait till tomorrow ♫
♫ Wait until snow and frost compromise with sunshine ♫
♫ You must believe ♫
♫ those agreements that we made at young ♫
♫ We agree to wait till tomorrow to ♫
♫ walk through the coldest winter night and ♫
♫ kiss the most beautiful spring together ♫
♫ Stand side-by-side before the daybreak ♫