KoreanDramaX.co
Let me give it a try.
Who told you to come in?
If I can convince Da Hu Zi, you must agree to my one condition.
I don't know what you are saying. Get out.
Wait.
Let him say it.
What do you plan to do?
What I plan to do is none of your business,
but I believe that I surely can convince Da Hu Zi.
I don't know where you are getting this confidence of yours.
Come in!
Older Brother Bai Ze! Older Brother Bai Ze!
Who is this?
Da Hu Zi's son.
Are you sure of this?
What do you think?
Okay.
Let's just do as you say.
If you need anything, just tell me.
If I convince Da Hu Zi, you must help me with one favor.
Sure.
If you are able to do it, I will surely help you.
I know about your power on this island.
I want you to help me find my friends that got separated from me.
Do you still miss those friends of yours?
To tell you honestly, a month has already passed.
They might have already–
Impossible!
My friends surely are still alive.
Okay. I promise you.
As long as they're still alive on this island,
even if I have to dig three meters deep, I'll find them for you.
Then it is a deal.
Let's go.
Let's go look for you daddy, okay?
Okay.
Xiao Cai!
Why have you been avoiding me lately?
I am not.
You are just overthinking.
I am not overthinking.
Right now, other than being able to see you during meal times,
for other times, you'll run away every time you see me.
Including now.
You're really just overthinking.
I am just...
Just what?
This...
Just joking.
Don't know if you do but, anyway, I do.
That is every time I see you, my heart beats so fast.
Actually, we being like this is a bit unreasonable, isn't it?
Before the marriage, the couple usually don't see each other quite often, right?
This stupid guy thinks it's real.
I really am committing sins.
If I don't continue this act and get found out,
the news might reach Xiao Dao.
But if I continue this act, what if he falls deeper and deeper?
Hey.
What are you thinking?
I was thinking that you must be tired from working today.
Tired?
I don't feel that way.
I'm quite energetic.
Yuan Shuai,
I feel that... we...
we... we actually... actually aren't...
We actually aren't like how Xiao Mei said we are.
Being in love with each other and respects each other.
And also I even know that you're still thinking of Gao Ying Jun.
He must be a very special person.
I really don't know how you were able to survive in these five years without any news about him.
Dad! Dad!
Why are you here?
Didn't I tell you to stay at home?
I brought an Older Brother.
Older Brother? Who?
When I got locked up in a cage by human traffickers that day,
it was this Older Brother who saved me.
I really don't know how to thank you.
If not because of you, I might not be able to see my son again.
No need to thank me.
All of his is our fate.
You saved my son so you're our whole family's savior.
Being a savior is too much. But...
Just say it.
I indeed have one thing that I want to ask your help with.
Say it.
It's about your captain.
You are one with them?!
No.
Although I don't know which side you are on,
I feel that you can consider the words they said.
Do you want me to betray him?
In your heart, he's indeed a good captain.
You also are a good sailor.
But a real good captain won't let his sailors' lives be in danger.
Think about it.
If the navy from the capital really come here to attack us, will you be able to take care?
Do you plan to be like them and die in the sea?
You have such an adorable child.
What will happen to him then?
But... I've followed him for twenty years after all.
Loyalty is good.
But stubborn loyalty is stupidity.
You–
Forgive me for talking so bluntly. Sorry.
No need to say it anymore. Please leave.
Okay. Goodbye.
Dad, Dad, just help him.
I beg you.
Wait!
I am agreeing with it.
Be careful. It's hot.
I don't know what Xiao Mei told you.
Ying Jun and I are childhood friends.
Whenever I remember his name,
I'll recall those wonderful times we were together.
Just thinking about it, I can be happy the whole day.
But five years ago, he went out to sea just for his dream.
I was unable to stop him
and also didn't have the reason to.
Right?
Of course, you could have tried to stop him.
But... you have no power to control what the ending would be.
You must miss him a lot.
Although I don't have a smart brain,
I can see that you're very lonely.
Being alone isn't lonely.
It is when you think of someone else that makes you feel lonely.
Then do you plan to continue... continue thinking about him?
It's not up to me.
Sorry.
It's fine.
You... you must feel that I'm stupid, right?
Being stupid is very easy.
He only needs to be persistent in the path he believes in
and he will already see the result and answer.
But being stupid is also hard.
Because the path he'll walk on is destined to be very difficult.
For every step he takes, he must suffer 10 times more pain than others.
And also, those people, who care about you,
will also be very sad.
Are you talking about me?
I am also talking about myself.
In summary, Yuan Shuai, I feel guilty towards you.
Actually, it's not only due to this,
there are also other...
other–
Why are you saying this?
I know that you must have some other intentions for choosing me to be your fiance,
but it's fine.
Since the day I woke up,
I felt that I had a new life, a very clean one.
Plus, I got to meet you.
When I first saw you, I felt that we seemed to have known each other for many years and are very close.
Anyway, it's... I feel very happy.
I'm not unhappy or hurt at all.
This... it's fine.
But... I still feel... that I'm being too cruel.
Yuan Shuai, you are very good. You are very, very good.
You shouldn't bear all of this.
Everyone must take responsibility for their choices.
These are things that I should bear.
You really are stupid.
I am very smart, okay?!
I know a lot of things.
Whatever you want, I can get it for you.
I don't want anything.
Hey? Xiao Cai, don't you believe me?
I believe you.
It's just that... I don't need them.
- It's cold now. You can drink it.- Thank you.
Should I tell him the truth or not?
Once you drink this water, you're my woman.
You are so hateful! Annoying! Hateful!
Who told you to say those words while I'm drinking water?
Xiao Cai,
I want to apologize to you.
Apologize for what?
Because I didn't ask for your permission and just fell in love with you.
But don't misunderstand.
I am only admitting my mistakes.
But... I have no intention of changing.
Anyway, I'll... no matter what, I'll still keep liking you one-sided like this.
I'm done with what I want to say. Just like this.
I'll go back to work now.
Your appearance is especially like my Shi Shi
when you don't talk.
Just like you, she also has two big eyes,
curved eyebrows, and pointed chin.
But Shi Shi is different from you!
You are always so cold!
Who will smile at you? Stinky pirate!
Who do you think you are?!
What are you saying?
Are you saying bad words about my Shi Shi?!
Fine. Fine. Fine. Your Shi Shi is the prettiest and the best, okay?
I really don't understand you men.
Why must you use alcohol to solve your problems?
What's the use of getting totally drunk?
Your Shi Shi is already dead.
Can't you let it go?
Be a good person and continue living well.
This is also something that she would have wanted to see.
What did you say?
Let go?
One term with two words. You say it like it's so easy,
as if you're just breathing.
But do you know that
every time I think about how Shi Shi was strangled,
my heart aches every time I breathe.
Do you know that?!
Let go?
May I ask if in this world, how many people can really do it?!
You are saying bad words about my Shi Shi, right?
Okay!
I'll kill you bitch today then!
Shi Shi, just watch.
I will kill all these people that say bad words against you.
I will kill all these people who have offended you!
What are you doing?!
Don't come near!
Let go of me!
What are you doing?!
Get lost!
Let go of me!
KoreanDramaX.co
Captain, oh no! Hou Zi has been killed!
Who did this? So cruel.
So cruel. So tragic.
This one died so tragically.
Throwing a knife through his brain, isn't that like opening one's heavenly eye?
This matter isn't that simple.
He died so tragically.
That's right. So tragic.
Captain is here!
Hou Zi... has followed me for eight years.
A buddy who has followed me for eight years through life and death.
We cannot just let him die like this.
Everyone here on our ship is my buddy.
I am the one who said these words.
I, Cheng Ming Pan, am a man of my word!
- How did Hou Zi really die?- We must take revenge for him!
Everybody is saying that it was that Ming Zhen.
I heard that Captain and that Ming Zhen have a past.
Someone is spreading rumors that Ming Zhen killed Hou Zi.
Ming Zhen is my friend.
I'll surely confront her about this.
I'll surely give you all an explanation!
We need a new captain!
Who? Who said that?
Stand out!
I am the one who said it.
Our captain right now is caught in a dilemma.
I suggest that we vote again and choose a new captain!
You brat, shut up.
Think about it, everyone. Before, we exerted so much effort
to steal from the government ship so we could finally be able to get some money.
If we become hostile with Ming Zhen now,
will the Captain really stand on our side and think about our interests?
Then wouldn't he have died for nothing?
I believe that everyone has already heard the rumors.
Right now, the government is really focused on going after this matter.
She and our Captain have a good relationship.
Just to find a scapegoat, Hou Zi then had to be sacrificed.
If this matter continues like this, we will all be sacrifices.
You brat better shut up first.
I have the right to talk!
If a half of all the sailors here are discontented with the captain,
we then have the right to choose a new captain.
This is also one of our pirate rules.
We want to choose a new captain! A new captain!
A new captain! We want to choose a new captain!
I agree with you all choosing a new captain.
We must not break the pirate code of rules.
Who is this new captain that you all are recommending then?
I suggest... Da Fu!
Da Fu! Da Fu! Da Fu...
Older Bro Hu Zi, who do we choose?
Let's first observe.
Da Fu! Da Fu! Da Fu...
Da Fu, 17 votes!
17 votes? Just 17? The situation is not good.
Cheng Ming Pan, 16 votes.
There aren't enough votes.
Wrong.
There are 36 people on our boat.
Minus the dead Hou Zi, that's a total of 35 people.
There are only 33 votes here.
Where are the two votes?
Who still hasn't voted?
Stand out. You cannot not vote.
- I abstain.- I also am abstaining.
Abstaining? How do you count abstaining?
How do we count that?
Just count it an abstain.
Hey, Captain! Captain!
I am announcing that our new captain is Da Fu!
Da Fu! Da Fu! Da Fu! Da Fu...
Hey, Yuan Shuai, it's so busy there in the hot springs.
Why aren't you helping out?
Although I lost my memories,
I feel that I have encountered the largest bottleneck of my life.
I know that the person who Xiao Cai is thinking in her heart is Gao Ying Jun.
I also have clearly told myself that I don't care about this.
But how come I still feel sad?
When it comes to love, it's really not up to oneself.
The more you try to console yourself, the more it means that you are affected by it.
Right now, I feel my limbs are so out of energy.
When I wake up everyday, I feel that I can't even stand stably.
When I wake up, I feel that I am not cleaned no matter how many times I take a bath.
Oh, right. There are also auditory hallucinations.
Is it like when you see people in the streets passing by,
- you feel that they are stronger than ten more times?- Yes.
Do you suddenly realized that you have so many bad traits?
Yes.
Is your mood so unstable?
One moment you're happy and the next moment, you feel down?
- You can't even take care of your own life anymore.- Yes.
Oh, my god. How come you are so accurate?
Doctor, please tell me what illness I have!
You still need an old doctor like me to cure you.
Please check my pulse.
The source of your illness is with my older sis.
How come upon just mentioning my older sis, you become listless?
Because I feel so confused.
It's like I didn't consider her feelings first yet I disturbed her.
Then did she reject you?
That's the strange part.
I initially thought that when you love someone, being good to her is your own thing.
But thinking about it afterwards, it seems to be not like that.
If I really don't expect to receive anything in return,
how come I am so sad now?
Just thinking about it, I really am such a hypocrite.
Did my older sis really not give you any reply?
None. None at all.
What did she tell you?
Tell everything to me exactly like how she said.
You must tell me each word.
She asked me if I was tired.
Thinking about it now, she seems to be quite concerned about me.
Those are just courteous words.
What else did she say?
I couldn't ask. Neither could I stop him.
That is what she said.
She also said, 'right?'
Ying Jun and I are childhood friends.
Whenever I remember his name,
I'll recall those wonderful times we were together.
Just thinking about them, I can be happy the whole day.
But five years ago, he went out to the seas just for his dream.
I was unable to stop him and also didn't have the reason to.
She also told me a lot of stories about Gao Ying Jun.
That's right then.
What?
Are you stupid?
What is the position of Gao Ying Jun in my older sis' heart?
The fact that she was able to tell you the most wonderful memories in her heart
means she treats you as a confidante.
Think about it. Who will talk about one's most hidden weakness and despair to some stranger?
No matter in what tone she said it.
What you said is quite reasonable.
When she talked about stopping him, how did she said it?
I couldn't ask. Neither could I stop him, right?
That's right then!
Talk properly. What right?
Not only does she treat you as a confidant,
but she also wants to get your reply.
I answered.
I told her...
Of course, you could have tried to stop him.
But... you have no power to control what the ending would be.
What? Did I say anything wrong?
That's not the reply she wanted.
It'd have been better if you said nothing.
What else did she say?
She even said, "You really are so stupid."
You indeed are so stupid.
She already said that you are stupid.
Why are you still dwelling about replies?
That is her reply.
What did she reply about?
You can't look at a woman's reply superficially.
You must try to understand it oppositely.
If she tells you to leave,
it means 'come back, hug me tightly.'
If she says that 'this item is too expensive, I don't want it anymore,'
It means 'thank you, I want them all.'
If she asks you if your heart has her or not,
it means to not say anything; just kiss.
You think about it yourself.
How about this? Let us put it in a simpler way.
What does she mean by saying that I am stupid?
What it means is she doesn't know how to face you.
She also is very confused.
Then it means... I still have a chance?
Of course.
And also, a very good chance.
In a few days, it is my older sis' birthday.
You are on your own. I'm going now.
Xiao Mei! Xiao Mei! No...
what I mean is Older Sis Xiao Mei.
Let me tell you. Don't let me prepare some birthday surprise for you.
Older Sis Xiao Mei, look if there is anyone else here who can help me.
If you don't help me, I will end up so tragically.
There are three major tragedies in life.
First, so poor that you don't have a way to do evil things.
Second, so hungry that you don't know what to eat.
Third, so sleepy that you are unable to sleep.
You haven't even experienced any of these major life tragedies.
What is there for you to be tragic about?
- I'm going now.- Hey! Hey!
Don't go. If you leave, I will really be kneeling.
Kneel then.
I'm kneeling.
Xiao Mei, help me...
Help me...
Xiao Mei... Older Sis Xiao Mei!
Wrong... Older Bro Xiao Mei... Help me...
What I am doing is step by step trying to get my older sis and Yuan Shuai together.
This wasn't my initial intention.
I just wanted the recipe for his family sauce.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
I'll help you.
But what should we make?
Then what should our first step be?
A birthday surprise
is just some kind of tricks but we must add more sincerity.
My older sis is a person who has gone through ups and downs.
She might not feel moved with such things.
Come.
KoreanDramaX.co
I've waited for this day for so long.
Come in.
How about it? What is the feeling of being the captain?
This time, it's all thanks to you.
- Hey...- Don't worry.
As long as you follow me, you surely will earn.
Don't say that. This captain position can be anyone.
But there are some captains that when they eats meat, I can only drink soup.
With you as the captain, when you eat meat, I also can eat meat.
What you said is so right!
Looks like there are a lot of stories behind this.
Did you hear it all?
Men come quickly!
Enough! Stop hitting! Stop hitting! Stop hitting!
Break up! Break up!
Let go!
Just because you didn't get voted as captain,
your innate personality has surfaced!
Let me tell you. It's not me who stole your captain position.
It was decided by votes by the whole ship members.
- Drag him away!- Yes!
Go! Go!
How are you ?
Crazy dog.
Xiao Cai, in here, I want to tell you, happy birthday.
These aren't some courteous words.
Because from the moment I first saw you,
I already know that you are hiding some things in your heart.
You must be very tired, painful, and sad.
Maybe I am just fated to meet you,
but don't have the luck to be with you.
But I really don't want you to keep living a life like this.
If you keep immersing yourself in your memories,
then how will you be able to take a step towards the future?
So promise me. Walk out of it, okay?
Oh, my–
- Older Sis, don't be like this.- Let me in.
- Let me in!- Older Sis... Older Sis...
- Just get in later. Just get in later.- Let me in.
Older Sis, the meals haven't been prepared yet.
Once the meals are ready, I'll just call you to eat.
Older Sis, just go back to your room first to rest.
I know that you are making some birthday surprise for me, isn't that so?
I am not stupid.
You two have been acting weird since this morning.
I already warned you not to make these messed up things and make me unhappy.
You know that I hated these ceremonies the most, especially birthday presents.
Older Sis, we didn't prepare any birthday presents.
Not birthday presents.
There are really no birthday presents.
Older Sis, just go back first.
There really are no birthday presents.
It's just a normal meal.
- It's true, Older Sis. Go back first. Try getting more rest.- Especially ribbons and candles,
so old-fashioned.
Older Sis, just go back to your room and rest.
I'll just call you later when it's time to eat, okay?
- Let me in. Let me in.- Jeez, Older Sis.
Older Sis, didn't I already tell you?
The meals are not yet prepared.
- Just go back first.- If you still don't open the door, I won't be polite anymore.
Older Sis!
Look. Look. Such good flower vases.
Look at one. Look how good they are.
Lord Ding?
It's really a coincidence.
Never thought I would meet you here.
I previously went to look for you.
I also have returned the hiring money.
I know. Ma Shun already told me.
You people from above ground are able to live here so leisurely.
That's quite a surprise.
If you have money, you can make anything happen.
It's the same above ground or underground.
You said that you are going into seclusion.
Why didn't you go find a beautiful place
and instead come to a forever sunless place like the underground city?
You surely have something to do here, right?
Nothing.
I just visited an old friend while passing by here.
A lone assassin who doesn't even blink when killing people will also have a friend?
Lord Ding, you really are making jokes.
But... how come Lord Ding is here in the underground city?
Only that item can make me personally attend to a matter.
I still remember that you owe me a favor.
I indeed said so.
But... if Lord Ding is asking me to find the Magic Star,
I am afraid I won't be able to do so.
This time, it doesn't concern the Magic Star.
I want you to help me with one thing.
Since we were fated to meet here,
let's look for a place and have some drinks.
Come with me.
If my guess is right, this Magic Star is in the hands of Lord Xiu Fu.
I just need you to help think of a way for me to get near him.
I can get the Magic Star on my own.
The past city leaders have all lived inside the city leader palace.
It not only has very tight security, but it's also a very mysterious place.
If you just recklessly enter it, you surely will not have any success.
Even for me, neither can I guarantee 100% success.
Lord, what I don't understand is
since this Lord Xiu Fu has been living all his life here in the underground city,
he totally has no plans of going out.
Then what is his purpose for getting the Magic Stars?
Lord Xiu Fu feels that he has abundant power now
and wants to use the Magic Stars to summon the God's Army.
God's army?
What?
Nothing.
Do you have a way or not to let me get near him?
Looks like there is only one way.
Tricking them.
Tricking them?
You even are able to come up with such an idea?
Such a despicable method, will it work?
Just relying on trickery, of course, it definitely won't work.
But with the Magic Stars, it might work.
If I haven't guessed it wrongly, Lord Ding,
you most likely have more than one Magic Star now in your hands.
I really never thought... I really never thought that someone would still help me at this time.
It's not the time to say these things.
Hurry and go!
What are you doing?!
I am already not the captain
and you cannot be the captain's wife.
Hurry and leave with me.
Hurry and go!
Oh, no! Captain, he has escaped!
- Who?- Cheng Ming Pan has escaped.
Are you still waiting for me to catch him personally?!
Aren't you going to lead some men to chase after him?!
Yes!
Go! Useless!
Reporting to city leader, an outsider is requesting an audience.
We here at the underground city never make dealings with outsiders.
I won't see them.
Send them out.
But... they say they have news about the Magic Stars.
They know about the Magic Stars?
Okay. Call them in.
Yes.
Bring them here!
Greetings, City Leader.
No need for formalities.
Who are you two?
A person who wanders the world, no need to ask for our origin.
Since you were able to enter the underground city,
it shows that you aren't just some ordinary people.
Now, you actively want an audience with City Leader
but you answer in puzzling ways.
Aren't you giving importance to City Leader?
City Leader, please don't be mad.
We both have no evil intentions.
I heard that you know about the Magic Stars.
We are wandering shamans that passed by this area.
We suddenly sensed a mysterious energy.
Such energy is like a spirit from a worldly king.
So we can't help but to come in and take a look.
If we have caused any disturbance, please forgive us.
Spirit of a king?
Your words are quite interesting.
Then please continue saying it.
From time immemorial, only regions where heroes are born will have such spirit.
I came after it up to here and saw that this spirit is different from other places.
What is the difference?
It isn't floating, dispersing, spreading or leaving.
Just go straight to the point!
Are you saying that I'm not qualified to be the city leader?
Not so.
The spirit of a king is with a person since he is born.
If its origin isn't from here,
then there can only be one explanation.
Continue.
That is because of the Magic Star.
Magic Star? Continue talking.
I can sense the power of the Magic Star.
Or else, I wouldn't have come into this underground city either.
Okay. Then let me ask you.
Do you know what the total amount of Magic Stars is?
There are clouds in ancient times, five stars of different colors,
including yellow, blue, crimson red, green, and black.
You really got them all right.
Fine. Then can you tell me
where the other Magic Stars are right now?
These...
I still am not able predict.
I need to carefully calculate it.
If you can help me find the other Magic Stars,
I surely will reward you handsomely.
Thank you, City Leader.
Informing City Leader. I have a mirror
which can show you the whereabouts of the object you show it.
I hope City Leader can hand over the Magic Star in your hands so I can shine my mirror on it.
City Leader, do you not believe me?
City Leader.
In our underground city, nothing bad can happen.
Yes.
Men! Bring out the Magic Star.
Let the shaman appreciate it.
Mr. Shaman, what did you see?
City Leader, this mirror is telling me
that the Magic Star is just in this underground city.
- Okay already.- What are we going to do now?
Don't follow me anymore.
If you follow me, you'll just get into trouble. Go now.
Stop! Stop! Stop...
In there! Hurry! After him! Stop!
Stop! Don't run!
Stop! Hurry!
Stop!
Hurry! Hurry!
Jumping from this high, he surely would have died.
Let's go. Let's go.
Xiu Xiu, so great. This is... What are you making?
Dad,
you tell me, is there really a sun in this world?
Of course, there is.
Then... will the sun talk with me?
Xiu Xiu, very soon, I'll take you above the ground.
You'll then see the sun and what it looks like.
You will then know if the sun can talk or not.
You always say it like that.
Come. I'll let you see some good stuff.
Here. Look. Is it beautiful?
Wonderful. So beautiful.
This is called a Magic Star.
There are five of them with five different colors in total.
I initially have one plus this one.
Then, we have two.
When we have gathered all five,
I can then take you to see the sun.
Really?
When have I lied to you?
Careful. Careful.
City Leader, were you looking for me?
Xiu Xiu, play on your own first.
I'll just talk with this uncle for a while.
Yes.
Come.
Xiu Xiu has been like this for these past years.
It was really hard on City Leader.
If not because Madam in the past...
Don't mention past things anymore.
With the help of miracle doctor Gongsun, Xiu Xiu
being able to survive is already not easy.
So the reason that you had always refused to do cruel moves
against Gongsun Miao Quan is this, right?
Pi Wu,
someone told me that the remaining Magic Stars are here in the underground city.
No... City Leader,
you aren't suspecting me of taking these Magic Stars and not giving them to you, right?
You don't need to be that nervous.
We cannot totally believe the words of the Jianghu wizard.
But we also can't totally not believe it.
Xiu Xiu.
KoreanDramaX.co
♫ In a rainy night, ♫
♫ I've not put away that windbreaker umbrella ♫
♫ My hand, that grasps it, is unwilling to throw it away ♫
♫ I want to be together till the end ♫
♫ Upon opening my eyes, ♫
♫ there may be only fallen leaves all over the ground left ♫
♫ There may be only those cold long streets left ♫
♫ I have you next to me ♫
♫ We agree to wait till tomorrow ♫
♫ Wait until snow and frost compromise with sunshine ♫
♫ You must believe those agreements that we made at young ♫
♫ We agree to wait till tomorrow to ♫
♫ walk through the coldest winter night and ♫
♫ kiss the most beautiful spring together ♫
♫ Stand side-by-side before the daybreak ♫