KoreanDramaX.co
How come there are two people here?
They are even dreaming.
This fatty only knows to eat.
Come with me then.
What's going on?
Where is Yuan Shuai?
Yuan Shuai!
Where am I?
Zhan Xiong Fei! Zhan Xiong Fei!
Zi Su!
Why are you here?
Where are we?
Zhan Xiong Fei, were you thinking about me?
Zhan Xiong Fei, hug me, okay?
Hug me. Hug me, okay?
Zhan Xiong Fei, if you don't come over to hug me, I'll go over to hug you then.
- Zhan Xiong Fei.- Hey, don't come near!
You are not Zi Su.
Tell me, who are you really?
You are quite smart.
I am indeed not Zi Su.
You... What kind of thing are you?!
I am Babe Ya, Baby Ya.
I don't care if you are some Baby Ya or Baby Yan.
Let me tell you. I've seen so many demons and monsters. You can't scare me.
Can't you tell good from bad?
I am here to help you.
If not because I saw that you were upright and brave even though you are an ungrateful one,
I wouldn't be minding your business.
Hurry and save that lady.
She is in big trouble.
Huh? What?
Where is Older Bro Fei?
Where could Older Bro Fei have gone?
Older Bro Fei!
Come.
- Two good brothers! Eight horses!- Here.
Why didn't you inform me beforehand?
Isn't it just one pigeon who flew here?
What is the big deal?
That is how I communicate with the people on the mainland.
A black pigeon means that something bad has happened there.
What bad thing can happen?
A very severe matter.
How severe can it be?
When my supplier got exposed before, he didn't even send over a black pigeon.
This time, it means that our island is in danger.
How sure are you that the problem comes from my cargo?
The cargo before were all just fabrics, leathers, cigarettes, and silk.
Only your cargo led to a problem.
Let me ask you. Why did you steal from a government ship and not tell me?
Why can't I steal from a government ship?
There are rules in your kind of business. You know that very well.
One must not touch the government's ship.
It will bring in disaster.
I am a pirate!
In my territory, there is only being able to rob or not.
There is not a case of allowing to rob or not.
You will eat the fruits of what you sow sooner or later.
I'll wait for that day.
Come. Drink!
Older Bro Fei!
Why is he gone so suddenly?
What has really happened?
Older Bro Fei!
Older Bro Fei, where have you really gone to?
Big Bro! Big Bro!
Just want to ask. Have you seen a quite tall and ruffian looking guy?
I didn't see one.
He is very thin, about... a half of me.
And then when he walks, he is like this,
swinging side to side, very unique, right? You must know about it, right?
I really didn't see him.
Oh, right, I have one final trick.
Look. I have a drawing.
This is our house.
This is me.
This is Thirteenth Older Sis.
This is Zhan Xiong Fei, the Older Bro Fei that I'm looking for.
He really is very important to me. Have you seen him?
I really didn't see him.
- Fine then.- Hey!
Oh, right. There is a small shop up ahead.
Foreigners usually go there.
How about you go there to take a look?
Thank you, Big Bro!
Okay. You're welcome.
I didn't find the corpses of your friends.
I asked around everywhere but I found no news about them.
This probably is a form of good news.
It's just a bit better than some news about their death.
Still not contented?
Do you really have to see their corpses?
Lady Boss, can you not have a devil's tongue?
I want to ask for leave today.
I am not in the mood to work.
Are your friends that important?
Don't you have any sincere friends at all?
If you want me to help you find them, it's not impossible, either.
What do you mean?
In every pirate bay, it is indeed difficult to find people.
But it depends on who is looking.
As long as you can help me find my friends,
I won't refuse to do any dangerous thing for you.
No need.
You just need to accompany me to one place and it's enough.
Don't worry. If there are indeed very dangerous situations,
it won't be your turn to go.
Okay.
This must be the place.
Owner!
Waiter!
How come no one is here?
This wouldn't be some racketeering shop, right?
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Although Older Bro Fei usually looks very quick-witted,
he actually is very stupid.
He wouldn't have been tricked, right?
Older Bro Fei! Older Bro Fei! Older Bro Fei!
You two are indeed running a racketeering shop, aren't you?
Let me tell you. Hurry and hand over my Older Bro Fei
or else I won't be courteous with you.
Don't think that because you know martial arts, we'll be scared of you.
You were sent by Xiao Dao, right?
Threatening and intimidating doesn't work.
Right now, you guys are starting to use despicable means like slandering and framing.
I don't know any Older Bro Fei or Older Bro Gou.
Go back and tell Xiao Dao...
tell him not to cause trouble here again.
He better just give up on this as early as possible.
I really don't know the Xiao Dao you are talking about. Let me tell you.
Earlier, somebody told me that Older Bro Fei followed the road and came here.
On this road, there's only your shop.
If my Older Bro Fei didn't come here, where else can he go?
Hurry and hand him over.
Older sis, did we make a mistake?
He doesn't look like a bad guy.
Younger sister, aren't you being too naive?
Will a bad guy write 'bad guy' on his face?
Moreover, Xiao Dao posted a note on our door yesterday.
He said that he'll come here at noon.
The time right now is exactly that.
If it is not him, who else can it be?
Hey, I say... Can you ask your boss to come out? I'll talk to him.
I am the owner.
You?
Owner?
I don't believe it.
Stop pretending already.
Let's just be straightforward and be frank about things.
I can see that your martial arts skills are quite good,
but you don't look to have a proper job.
Tell me, how much did Xiao Dao give you
to let you serve him?
How come I can't understand anything that you are saying?
I am just here to look for one person.
Aren't you all just bullying us sisters for having no people to rely on?
Let me tell you. Older Bro Ying Jun will be here soon.
By that time, you won't even have the time to cry!
How come there is some Ying Jun now?
After saying so much, we actually get our wires crossed.
Xiao Mei, he really can act.
Not joining the theater group and be there main star is really a waste.
Fine. Fine. I won't ask anymore. Is that okay?
I'll just go look for him on my own.
Stop!
Hurry and just go back.
Stop doing evil things with Older Bro Xiao Dao.
Even if Older Bro Ying Jun won't be able to come back,
Xiao Dao will still get the retribution he deserves sooner or later.
Xiao Mei, who said that Older Bro Ying Jun won't be able to come back?
You are not allowed to say those kinds of words in the future.
No. No. No. I said it wrong.
Older Bro Ying Jun will surely come back.
What really is going on here, Heaven!
Save me!
- Xiao Dao...- Xiao Dao...
Older sis, what do we do now?
Xiao Cai...oh, wrong, my wife.
Wife, so sorry.
I had a drink with some of my friends earlier
so I came late.
You are not unhappy about it, right?
Clean up your language!
Wife, you wouldn't really be angry about it, right?
Or else... Or else let me, your husband, pamper you.
Give your husband a kiss.
Don't get near my older sis!
What does me kissing my wife have to do with you?
Could it be that you also want to...
Fine. Come.
Let brother-in-law kiss you.
- Don't come near!- Don't come near!
- Hey, Buddy, wait for a minute.- Don't come near!
Is he that handsome Xiao Dao that you were talking about?
I don't find him that handsome.
But buddy, good thing you are here.
Or else, I don't know for how long I am going to be the scapegoat for this.
Let's talk privately.
It's fine.
You... From where did you, her lover, come from?
You dare to meddle with other people's business here?!
Leave!
Do you have cancer of the eyes?
Let me tell you. I came here before you.
The person that I hate the most are scum like you who bully women.
I have decided to interfere with this matter.
Hey, don't move!
Do you know what this is?
This is a knife.
But in dealing with you, I don't need a knife.
Hero, have mercy! Hero, have mercy...
Hey, it's good that you know to be afraid. Hurry and leave!
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Sorry. There must be some misunderstanding earlier.
Who told you to come in such a bad time?
Then, are you really here to look for someone?
Right. Right. Right. I'm here to look for my good buddy.
He is called Zhan Xiong Fei, called Older Bro Fei.
Let me find it.
Be careful!
You... Just you wait and see!
- Are you alright?- Are you okay?
Wake up!
- Are you alright?- Wake up!
Quickly wake up!
- Wake up!- Hurry and wake up!
KoreanDramaX.co
Good! Good!
Customer, please come inside.
Boss. why did you take me to such a place?
If you want my help, then follow my work method.
Don't ask so many questions.
But this place is an indecent place, I don't want to stay here.
Stop being so delicate.
Are your feelings more important or my matter?
Moreover, don't you want to look for those friends of yours?
Of course, I want to.
Then just listen to me.
Stop your nonsense. Just do as I say.
Fine.
Take care.
Yo, Boss Ming Zhen.
Aren't you Boss Ming Zhen?
Are you here to look for our lady boss?
No. Bring me upstairs to drink.
Okay. This way please.
Just walk around and look.
Yo, customer! Are you here to have fun?
Come and enjoy.
So sorry.
I'm waiting for someone. I'm waiting for someone.
Waiting for who?
- That's right. - What do you think about me?
What really do you want?!
Younger Sister, you've stared at me this way for several days.
I really can't continue looking at it anymore.
Today, the captain is here.
You must give me an acceptable answer.
What do you mean?
Servant, change her clothes.
Dream on!
- Get over there!- This one's not bad.
This one's not bad...
Very beautiful. She's quite beautiful. This one's not bad.
Move your dirty hand away!
Quite fierce.
You have quite an attitude.
I like!
Immediately get lost!
Okay!
Let go of me!
- A Ji Ya!- Let go!
A Ji Ya! Hurry and go!
Where did this stinky brat come from?!
Attack!
You are really something, little girl.
Your little lover even came here.
- I don't know him.- A Ji Ya, what are you saying?!
I am here to save you!
Your love... is just one-sided, right?
Quite interesting.
This little girl looks like she doesn't want to go nor stay.
Fine. It just so happen that we're quite bored right now.
I'll play a game with you.
I have time to play games with you! Just quickly let her go!
No way.
This is a thousand-year-old rule of us pirates.
If you win, you can take her away with you.
But if you lose,
you can't leave this room, either.
Hey, are you Pirate Bay people men of your words?
Of course, we are.
Okay.
- Let's play then!- No...
The rule is very simple.
We will take turns to turn the wheel.
On which bowl it lands, then you drink that bowl.
Whoever stands until the very end, he'll be the winner.
Okay.
Come.
Stop.
Bring out the pirate king.
This can cause a life.
How is that a wine?
It clearly is poison.
No one dares to drink it.
Mr. Captain, he is just a child.
Stop get serious with a child.
Boss, no matter what pirate king is,
I can drink it.
Don't be so arrogant.
Do you know what kind of wine the pirate king is?
Just drinking a mouthful, you can be unconscious for three days as a light effect,
but worst case scenario, you may die immediately.
Bai Ze, don't drink it!
A Ji Ya, I came here today in order to take you away.
I am not afraid to drink any amount.
Waiter! Bring out your pirate king!
- Okay, coming.- Bring the wine over here!
Okay.
I'll be lenient with you.
I'll go first.
I'll go first!
What good drinking ability!
No! Bai Ze!
Don't drink anymore!
Bai Ze!
Can't take it anymore?
Come!
Brat! There are only two bowls of wine left.
Don't say that I am bullying you.
You choose first.
Okay.
I'll choose that bowl.
♫ If you don’t want to have regrets in your love, ♫
Okay.
But you drink first.
♫ This love didn't come easy. ♫
♫ You should treasure it even more. ♫
♫ Only ask fate and predestination to treat me with leniency ♫
♫ It's because of these things that have happened ♫
♫ and unalterable facts... ♫
- Bai Ze, don't drink...- Captain...
Captain...
♫...to cause sorrow not able to leave and ♫
♫ us not able... ♫
- You are surely going to lose! - Hurry and drink!
Bai Ze, don't drink!
Hurry and drink it!
Bai Ze, you will die!
♫ They're all these little uncertainties ♫
No...
♫ which surpass our... ♫
A Ji Ya, even if I die,
I still must save you.
No... No...
♫ I admit that I'm not perfect ♫
♫ You're the lost pearl in my life ♫
No... No... Don't drink it, Bai Ze!
♫ The love letters I wrote you are like the mistouch of soul ♫
No, Bai Ze!
♫ so lonely as if there is only one Asiatic apple flower left ♫
Don't drink!
♫ I hold it to sleep every night and it doesn't wither ♫
♫ I water it everyday ♫- No!
Bai Ze!
♫ When I miss you, I think of you till I cry ♫
♫ You're the lost pearl in my life. ♫
Bai Ze! Bai Ze!
♫ I so wish to give for you once more. ♫
♫ Many people ask me why so stubborn. ♫
Bai Ze!
♫ I answer that because I know ♫
♫ to love is happier than being loved ♫
This... What's going on now?
Hey! Who are you?!
How did you get in?
This can't be real, right?
I recognize you.
You are the friend of Her Lady Highness Princess.
What is this place?
This is Princess Zi Su's room.
This is Zi Su's room?
Yes.
Hey, where is Zi Su?
Princess Zi Su has gone missing.
I don't know about the specific details, either.
But the Emperor is already panicking crazily.
Zi Su is missing?
Hurry and go save that girl!
She is in big trouble.
Where is His Majesty?
Ah... he is probably in his chambers.
Hey! Where are you going?!
You're saying that you met a little monster called Babe Ya on that island.
It was he who sent you back here.
Yes, Your Majesty.
It was also he who told me that Zi Su was in trouble.
What Babe Ya or Babe Mi, so mysterious...
Could it be you escaped midway?
Hey.
Looks like that island indeed has a lot of strange and mysterious things.
Since you are already back,
don't think about what's happening there now.
Yes.
Right now, I just hope that Bai Ze and Yuan Shuai can be blessed by Heaven
to eventually meet up and investigate the truth clearly.
Then the most important thing now is to save Zi Su.
Eunuch Cao, what did that spy say earlier? Say it again.
That spy really dared to ask for such a high price.
Just for some news, he dared to ask 10 pieces of gold bars.
If not because I am worried about Her Lady Highness Princess...
Get to the main point.
He said that he personally saw
Ma Shun abducting Princess Zi Su.
- Ma Shun.- And Ma Shun even got the information from them
that the Magic Star stolen from the Royal Tomb was done by the white-skin people.
What?! The Magic Star also got stolen?
All troublesome matters have happened all together.
The most important thing now is to save Zi Su.
Others are not important.
Since Ding Song and his men are asking about the whereabouts of that Magic Star,
it then means that they are not allies of the white-skin people.
We can't make such conclusions so quickly, either.
It is also possible that they are doing a dog-eat-dog.
I heard that those white-skin people have been living underground for a long time
that's why their skin and pupil color are not the same as ours.
Even if we know that Zi Su was taken there,
but how are we going to find that underground city?
I indeed was able to get information that
there is a Jianghu warrior with a code name called Yu Qi Lin.
He knows how to contact these underground people.
Yu Qi Lin?
His code name is quite refined.
Who can find him?
A person like him usually is hard to track.
I'm useless. I was only able to learn that such a person existed.
As for if he is a man or a woman, I don't even know.
This person is our only hope of finding Zi Su.
No matter where he is, even if he is in a tomb,
we will dig him out regardless.
How about we send out the imperial army to do the search now?
You can't.
Right now, we already know that Zi Su is in Ding Song's hands.
If we increase the scale of our search for Zi Su,
it will surely alarm the enemies.
By that time, if they are pushed to the wall and
do some extreme actions which will harm Zi Su, that's not good.
Zhan Xiong Fei, do you have the confidence of bringing back Zi Su here safely?
As long as I'm not dead, I surely will bring Zi Su back.
Okay. I'm entrusting this matter now to you.
You must know, Zi Su is very important to me.
Your Majesty, Zi Su is also very important to me.
KoreanDramaX.co
Ding Song! I advise you to just better let me go now.
Go back and admit your mistakes to my older bro.
Maybe I can even put in some good words for you
and let my older bro be merciful and spare your life.
Since time immemorial, the winner becomes the king and the loser becomes the bandit.
Once I get the five Magic Stars, it's still an unknown of who'll sentence who.
You!
You better just be obedient.
I will guarantee your safety.
Don't dare play some tricks.
You won't escape.
Lord!
10 miles more in this direction, it will already be the area that you said.
Lord, the person you have an appointment with is called this Yu...
Yu Qi Lin!
Oh, right, right, Yu Qi Lin.
What kind of person is he?
Making things really mysterious and insisting on meeting in the desert.
I heard that this Yu Qi Lin is very mysterious.
No one ever saw his real face.
But that's all not important.
As long as he can tell us how to go to the Yongzhou Underground City, then that's enough.
I really hate people like him;
one covers himself up and is so mysterious
as if he were doing some illegal activities.
A criminal calling for the arrest of another criminal.
So funny!
Do you believe that I'll stuff your mouth?
Come then! My mouth is in my body. I'll say whatever I want!
Can you do anything about it?!
Of course, I--
Jeez, enough already.
What use is it arguing with her?
I heard that this Yu Qi Lin sees money* like its his life (very greedy for money).
The gold in our carriage will surely be able to satisfy him.
Let's hurry and get in the carriage and continue our journey.
Yes, Lord.
- Let's go.- Hurry and move.
Move!
- Hmp!- Lord.
Move. Get in.
I don't want to sleep.
I am not sleeping. I'm drinking!
A Ji Ya!
Xiong Fei!
- Owner, this guy has a weak scholarly look but is quite loyal.- One more.
I can still go save my friends.
There's no more need for you here. You can go now.
Yes.
You clearly can't drink but you still have to force it.
How come people now have become this arrogant?
Where are you?
Are you okay?
Hurry and lie down.
A Ji Ya... A Ji Ya...
A Ji Ya, sorry.
Let go!
I am Ming Zhen.
Mother!
I am incapable.
I can't even save my own friends!
Stop hitting yourself!
Mother!
Stop hitting now!
You are drunk. This isn't your fault.
Mother, I miss you so much.
I also miss Father.
Where are you?
It's such a pity that I can't even save my own friends.
Mother...
Mother.
Where has time gone to?
Boss! A customer from the capital is looking for you!
Okay. I get it.
[Ming Zhen's Tavern]
May I ask what customer wants to eat?
Is there any duck liver?
What kind?
One side fresh, one side cooked.
I don't want one that's too small.
Customer, let's talk privately.
What really is the situation now?
Right now, they found someone with the goods.
Although I already bribed most of them, it still didn't work.
The government is very angry about an official ship being robbed.
Following the source of the items in the market,
and then tracking it further,
I'm afraid...
You are afraid of what?
I'm afraid that once they trace it to here, this island will be in great danger.
Isn't there any other way?
Right now, the government is already utterly discomfited.
They surely must arrest someone to execute.
What you mean is if I want to protect this small island, I must give out that person?
I already relayed the words.
What to do next will depend on yourself.
Of course.
You worked hard.
I already prepared the room.
You have been exhausted from your travel.
Go rest early.
No more. I still must hurry back.
Auntie!
Auntie! Auntie!
What?!
What did you call me?!
So sorry. I saw it wrong.
I just want to ask how do I reach the Yongzhou Underground City?
You... are a foreigner, right?
Yes.
Why are you going there?
I have a very important matter to do in the underground city.
The underground city isn't a place that one can just enter.
I...
Branded bag?
Fine.
Seeing that you are a foreigner,
I'll take you to a place. Someone there will tell you about it.
- Come with me then.- Hey!
Do you really know? Hey!
Granddaddy Earth, I'm here to visit you again.
This is my offering to you.
This is just a little dilapidated temple.
Don't look at Granddaddy Earth as just being a low level god.
In our place, everyone knows him.
Then... will he know how to get to the underground city?
This young lad, are you the one going to the underground city?
Who is talking?
Don't look anymore.
I am here.
Is Earth... Granddaddy Earth really that magical?
Don't be disrespectful.
You are quite lucky. It's Granddaddy Earth making his presence felt.
Granddaddy Earth, I want to go to the underground city.
But I don't know how to go there.
I hope Granddaddy Earth can guide me.
Granddaddy Earth, this one is my friend.
He doesn't know the proper way of showing respect. Don't blame him.
Look at this rotten temple of mine, so dilapidated.
Only this lady comes here to tidy this place and even gives me offerings.
Other than this lady, I won't help anyone else.
Miss, help me put in some good words.
Okay.
Granddaddy Earth, just help him.
He surely will donate a big amount of money to help renovate this temple.
Ah... that's right. That's correct!
Granddaddy Earth, as long as you help me,
I'll surely help renovate your temple and donate a lot of money.
Just be benevolent and tell me how to get to the underground city.
Regarding the underground city,
it's so far yet so near.
Huh? What do you mean?
One cannot leak Heaven's information.
Then how about sharing some more with me.
Ascend another story to see a thousand miles.
Granddaddy, I never went to school.
Stop making it difficult for me already.
Just tell me what it means.
Jeez, give some money first.
Give money?
Gods still need money?
Of course.
When Monk Tang went to the west, he still had to pay money to see Buddha.
But I really don't have any money with me right now.
Don't you have any money inside your wallet?
- Jeez, just leave.- It's fine.
Granddaddy Earth, just wait for a while.
I'll go get some money now.
Hey! That's not allowed.
Granddaddy Earth still has to go report back at the Heaven's Palace.
- Just come back tomorrow.- Hey!
Granddaddy Earth, I...
Jeez, just leave.
Then fine.
I'll come back tomorrow then.
Granddaddy Earth, wait for me!
So much fun.
Hey! Get up to drink some soup.
Hey! I'm talking to you!
Get up to drink some soup.
I'm talking to you!
Don't leave me...
Hey! Wake up.
I'm talking to you.
- Don't leave me...- Hey!
Don't leave me!
Let go of me! Let go!
- Don't leave me!- What are you doing?!
Don't leave me!
- Don't leave me! - Older sis!
- Don't!- Your hands!
Older sis!
- Don't leave me!- Let go!- You are really something!
No...
- You can't hide your fox tail now, right?! - Older Sister...
You can't hide it anymore! You can't hide it anymore!
You can't hide your fox tail now anymore, right?!
What are you doing?! Why are you hitting me?!
Did you connive with Xiao Dao?!
- Who are you two?!- Older sisr!
Older sis, stop hitting.
Older sis, stop hitting him.
I think he has something to say.
Who are you two?! Why are you hitting me?!
I...
Who am I?
What is this place?
How come I am here?
I... How come I ended up here?
Who really am I?
- How come I can't remember anything?- You are pretending to be confused now, is that it?
- Confused, is that it?- Hey, Older sis, Older sis...
Could his brain have gotten damaged from being hit?
I heard from storytellers that people with amnesia are like him.
Did he really lose his memories?
We can even encounter such things, right?
Hey! Let me ask you. Can you still remember what your name is?
I am called...
- You are called Yuan Shuai.- I am called...
Right. Right. I am called Yuan Shuai.
This name is very familiar.
I am called... I am called Yuan Shuai.
Older sis, he doesn't look like he is pretending.
Then let me ask you again.
What is the last memory in your brain? Can you still remember it?
It seems like...
Seems like what?
Seems like I can't recall it anymore.
Seems like I can't remember anything anymore.
You were having a nightmare earlier.
Do you still remember the events in your dream?
You were saying earlier... Who were you asking not to abandon you?
Why did you hug me earlier?
I seem to be... seem to be looking for a person.
Yet in the end, I can't find him.
Right. You are indeed looking for--
Looks like, you really have lost your memories.
Then let me tell it to you then.
Look at the clothes you are wearing.
What's wrong with my clothes?
You are a waiter in our shop.
I am... a waiter in your shop?
Yes.
The local rascal Xiao Dao around here always comes to harass us.
Earlier, you helped us drive him away.
But... he swung a bamboo stick to your heard earlier and caused you to faint.
I even thought that you haf connived with him to do some torturous trick to win our trust.
Looks like, I wrongly blamed you.
But don't worry.
Since you were hurt because of us,
we will surely take care of you.
Oh...
Then... other than losing your memories, are you okay in other aspects?
I'm all fine.
Just a bit dizzy.
Then that's good. Then that's good.
Then rest well.
It's okay to not remember things from before.
We will slowly help you remember them.
Okay. Thank you.
Xiao Mei, let's leave first.
Okay.
Hey, what are your names?
I am called Xiao Mei.
She is my older sis, called Xiao Cai.
Let's go.
How come I can't remember anything?
KoreanDramaX.co
♫ In a rainy night, ♫
♫ I've not put away that windbreaker umbrella ♫
♫ My hand, that grasps it, is unwilling to throw it away ♫
♫ I want to be together till the end ♫
♫ Upon opening my eyes, ♫
♫ there may be only fallen leaves all over the ground left ♫
♫ There may be only those cold long streets left ♫
♫ I have you next to me ♫
♫ We agree to wait till tomorrow ♫
♫ Wait until snow and frost compromise with sunshine ♫
♫ You must believe ♫
♫ those agreements that we made at young ♫
♫ We agree to wait till tomorrow to ♫
♫ walk through the coldest winter night and ♫
♫ kiss the most beautiful spring together ♫
♫ Stand side-by-side before the daybreak ♫