KoreanDramaX.co
When I was imprisoned by Ding Song, the one who I missed the most was you.
I remember when you first ran into the palace, you were only seven years old.
Yes, I remember.
At that time, Royal Father punished Nanny Tang who had been taking care of me.
At that time, I liked to feed and rear crows,
but Royal Father felt that it was unlucky to rear crows in the palace.
He didn't want me to rear them.
I secretly let Nanny Tang rear them in the Imperial Garden.
In the end, they were still discovered by him.
Hence, he kicked Nanny Tang out.
Subsequently, you were angry with Royal Father
and ran out of the palace alone.
I wonder how Nanny Tang is doing now.
She took care of me since I was young.
In this palace, other than you and Older Brother Bai Ze,
she was my closest family member.
Let's not talk about this anymore.
When Royal Father was alive, he was especially strict with us.
He also did that out of good intentions.
Who told us to be born into a royal family?
Older bro, if you could be an ordinary man now,
but you could live happily forever, would you be willing?
How come you are suddenly asking this?
It's nothing, either.
It's just that I was really happy with Xiong Fei and the others during these times,
but... there are also a lot of things that I can't understand,
so I am in a bit of a dilemma.
Alright, Zi Su has grown up.
You have something in your heart now.
Can you tell your older brother about it?
I still have to think about it more
if I should tell you about it.
Fine then. Looks like someone will be hurting.
- Who?- Of course, it's Bai Ze.
Why?
Since you were little, you had been following behind your Older Brother Bai Ze.
Even saying that you wouldn't marry anyone else but him.
Who would have thought that after going out for quite some time, you already...
Older bro! What nonsense are you spouting?!
Do you think I didn't notice it?
Earlier, while we were in the Grand Hall, your gaze never left that lad.
When did I?
I won't talk to you now.
I'm going back to my room to sleep.
The sunrise at this place is 1 hour earlier
than those islands of the same sea level.
The sunset time is also 1 hour later.
There is actually such a thing?
I am guessing that a special item must be present over there
causing the island to be unusual,
not excluding that there might be...
Magic Star?
Ikeda, can you be sure of it?
This is only my guess.
I still can't be 100% sure.
I'm leaving it to Lord Ding to decide.
Lord,
although we aren't sure if there's a Magic Star on this island or not,
going there to investigate isn't really going to be a bad thing.
After all, the day of gathering all the Magic Stars is getting closer and closer.
Lord Ding, what do you think?
Ikeda, set out tomorrow and go there on my behalf.
Lord Ding, how about our agreement before?
Ikeda, what do you mean?
Unless you think that our Lord will go against his words, right?
Oh, no, no, no. Of course, he won't.
Don't worry.
Once the matter is done, I will surely give an order to abolish sea restrictions in the whole country
and open up trading with your people.
Thank you, Lord.
Then if Lord doesn't have anymore instructions, I will go prepare now.
Why is Zi Su not happy today?
That's because she has something on her mind now.
How about we take Zi Su out for a stroll?
Will she be a bit happier?
She probably will.
Zi Su, Zi Su, let's go out and play.
Okay? Okay?
Have you had enough with the wooden puppet acting?
Come out now, you.
My legs are numb! My legs are numb!
Boring.
How about it?
Zi Su, accompany me for a stroll.
I don't want to go.
What's really wrong with you?
There's nothing wrong with me.
If you want to go out, go and look for Yuan Shuai instead.
I told you already, she doesn't want to go.
The reason she doesn't want to go is
because she is thinking of the person that she likes in her heart.
I am not. You are making up things!
Hey, don't make up things.
If you continue saying things like that, I'll tear your mouth.
I wasn't making up things.
That's what she said.
She already said earlier that the person she is thinking is called...
called 'Don't like to say it.'
Hey, who is 'Don't like to say it?'
A man or a woman?
Who is 'don't like to say it'?
Hey, you're annoying.
Who is 'don't like to say it'? Tell me. Tell me.
Who is he? Who is he?
Clay dolls! Clay dolls!
Come.
Miss, I have been carving clay for so many years. You are the prettiest that I have done.
- Really?- Yes.
Of course, it is. Who else is prettier than you?
- Here.- Thank you.
- Does this look good?- Looks so good.
Fellow villagers!
This is our first time here!
Those with money, please give us some.
Those without, please just be our audience.
Come!
Wow! So great!
Which one do you want?
I want that one over there.
- I'm just a bit off.- Try it out again.
Maybe you'll get in on the next try.
What to do?
Miss, try it again. Yehey! You got it!
It's a hit! Thank you, Owner.
You still have one last ring. Which one do you choose?
Got it.
Since you got it, it's yours now, right?
Come with me then.
Everyone, come to take a look. It's real.
- Let me see.- Hey... What are you doing?
What are you doing?! Destroying our show?!
- Hurry and escape!- Hurry!
Hey! Stop! Don't move!
Move aside! Move aside!
Don't move! Stop!
Don't run! Stay right there!
It's so delicious!
Delicious.
Mr. Ikeda, we'll have to trouble you for the island matter then.
May Lord Ding and Lord Ma just wait for my good news.
- Goodbye.- Goodbye.
Is this information reliable?
I heard it personally.
Okay. You have worked hard.
This information you got is very valuable.
Go down to have a good rest.
Yes. Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, what urgent matter did you call us for?
I just received news
that before Ding Song escaped, he has colluded with the Toyo people.
He sent them to the Money Island.
It should be related to the Magic Stars.
Ding Song's claws really have reached so far out.
Then what does Your Majesty want us to do now?
Counting the days, that Toyo person should have traveled far already.
I ordered you all to immediately chase after that Toyo person.
And also, you all must leave quietly.
Don't let Zi Su know about it.
Or else, she will be crying and insisting to go with you.
Your Majesty, that doesn't seem right.
What's not right about it?
I'm her older brother.
This is her home.
I letting Zi Su stay home, will that be worse than leaving with you?
Xiong Fei, what His Majesty said is right.
We will then leave now.
We surely will find the truth behind this.
Okay. Then I'm counting on you then.
Yes!
Ha! Ha!
Ha!
We have to catch up with him but none of us know how to drive a boat.
Are we going to swim over there?
Jeez, look at your stupid self. Don't worry.
His Majesty most likely has prepared a huge boat waiting for us already.
When you are on a huge ship, it's the same as standing on ground.
With the sea breeze blowing on you while eating seafood,
isn't that such a happy way of living?
Have you been on the seas?
I only heard it from other people.
Right now, we are quite behind Ding Song's men.
If we can't catch up with them before they get on the ship,
it'd be harder to look for them out in the open seas.
Okay!
Ha! Ha!
Ha!
Toyo people.
Hey, is this that Toyo person that Ding Song sent?
Hero, I think this road might have been yours
but you had the wrong people.
Look at us. We look like kids.
That... That we surely don't have any money with us.
You three have been following me all throughout. You must have been exhausted already.
Don't think I don't know.
You are Heaven Strategy Envoys sent out by the Emperor.
I heard that you're also looking for the Magic Stars
relying on a Star Chart which can locate the Magic Stars.
Is it with you? Hurry and hand it over.
Star Chart? We don't have one.
- Search them.- Yes.
Stop touching me now. It's not with me.
It's not with me.
Big Bro, there really isn't one. Just search.
Hey! I already told you!
We don't have any Star Chart with us.
Now, do you believe us?
Since we didn't lie to you, either, then let's just...
A great man doesn't dwell with the shortcomings of little men.
Just let us go.
Then does it mean that the Star Chart is really not with you?
That's right. We little kids never lie.
Since it's like that, I won't make it difficult for you anymore.
I'll send you to your death now.
Who is it?
Hey, hurry and escape!
Let's go.
Chase after them!
Hurry! Hurry!
Hurting others with hidden arrows, what kind of brave hero are you?!
If you have the guts, come out!
How come there is not even one boat here by the seaside?
Hey, Mister. Are there any boats going out into the sea?
"I've been in a gorgeous outfit riding on a mighty horse since young."
Ha? What did you say?
"The weeds grow so high that it covers horse's hoof completely."
My fellow buddies, just come with me.
Hey... What's going on?
You don't understand, right?
That is our Heaven Strategy Envoys' secret password.
- Let's hurry and go.- Oh...
This is the boat prepared for you.
Please depart.
- Thank you, this Big Bro.- Thank you.- You're welcome.
This boat was prepared for us by His Majesty.
What a big boat!
How come I don't find it big?
- Oh?- Let's go.
- Let's go.- Okay.
- Wow!- Bai Ze, let me teach you how to maneuver a boat.
Hey! So rowing a boat is this tiring?!
You were just starting.
Try hard to lose some weight.
I don't know how she is doing now.
Are you are still thinking of A Ji Ya?
She must be hating us so much now.
She never wants to see us again.
Does this matter really have no room for reconciliation?
The hatred of stealing one's wife, the grudge of killing one's father,
if all this hatred and grudges were really so easily resolved,
how come there are still many stories about love, hate, affection, and revenge in all ages?
Bai Ze, think about it.
If you realized that your friends' fathers' hands
were all covered with your family's blood, what would you think?
Bai Ze, did you ever think about this? Our fathers are Heavenly Strategy Envoys.
How could they did such a thing?
What do you mean by that?
A Ji Ya's father, King Salin, is a subject of the empire.
All worked for the empire.
But because of the Magic Stars, he suffered such a tragedy.
Elder Jiong Ye was remorseful of that matter and asked for forgiveness.
What do you really want to say?
From my experience of reading a thousand story books and watching numerous plays,
an expert in official, unofficial, and dynastic histories of heroes,
I feel that the Heaven Strategy Envoys don't seem to be some straightforward and upright heroes.
The hero in your heart is a person who has a clean background and does things with clear regard for right and wrong.
That's why, let's stop suspecting the deeds done by our fathers.
Why not just look at what we should do now?
That is correct.
Yes, you both are right.
Hey! Hey! Hurry and look!
- What's going on?- It's a huge storm!
- Hurry and move the boat forward with full speed.!- Okay.
Royal Brother!
Royal Brother, where did Zhan Xiong Fei, Older Brother Bai Ze, and Yuan Shuai exactly go?
Hey, Eunuch Cao, didn't I ask you to tell Zi Su
about where Bai Ze and the others went?
Oh...
Your Majesty indeed told me to relay that to Princess.
I have forgotten it.
Your Majesty, please forgive me.
Princess, please forgive me.
Look at you. For the matters I told you to do, you just forget them.
Do you still consider me as your superior?
Enough already. Stop acting already.
I am not a 3-year-old kid. Do you think I can't see through that?
Royal Brother, I know that you are thinking about my safety.
You want me to stay here in the Palace,
but I'm no longer that princess in that past, who's always been waited on hand-and-foot.
I am going to look for them. They need me.
Let's clarify that first.
Is it that they need you
or you can't be away from that Zhan Xiong Fei?
Royal Brother, you... I don't care.
Hurry and tell me where they are.
Your Lady Highness Princess, just listen to His Majesty this time.
His Majesty has already too many things to worry about.
Fine. Even if you both won't tell me, I can still find it out.
Hey! Hey! Eunuch Cao, hurry and look for more palace maids and guards to look after Zi Su.
- Don't let her leave the palace.- Yes.
The storm earlier was quite huge.
Good thing, we were lucky. We found this natural harbor to hide.
Or else, there was even a possibility that our boat would have capsized.
I think that this harbor is an abandoned area.
Even if you don't talk, no one will treat you as mute.
What abandoned or not abandoned?
Being able to find a harbor is already good enough.
Talkative.
Hey, Lord, look.
What is that?
Let's go. Let's take a look.
- Yes... - Hurry.
Such huge waves and it didn't drown them.
Really a miracle.
I assume that they dog paddled themselves up.
- Hurry. Take them all away.- Yes.
Hey! You took advantage when we were weak.
What kind of hero is that?!
Little kids... goodbye forever.
I'll be leaving now.
Hey! You... Let us go!
Light the dynamite.
Hey! Don't go!
I still don't want to die.
Yuan Shuai, don't worry.
If there is anyone dying, I'll be the first.
Bai Ze, hurry and think of a way!
No way!
We are Heaven Strategy Envoys. We surely won't die.
There must be a way. We... We...
- Amituofo.- No way!
Heaven! Take good care of A Ji Ya, His Majesty, and Zi Su for me!
A Ji Ya?
How come the dynamite still hasn't exploded?
Telescope.
How come there is a woman over there?
Really?
A Ji Ya, thank you for saving us.
That's right, A Ji Ya. It's really thanks to you this time.
Thank you.
You're really quite stupid. Being caught twice in a day.
So last time, it was also you who saved us, right?
Bai Ze, I think that you being able to survive this time
means you'll be receiving abundant blessings afterwards.
Then... you won't leave anymore after this return, will you?
Hey... Hey...
Where are you going?
What does that have to do with you?
Isn't your matter, my matter?
KoreanDramaX.co
[Ding Residence]
What are you looking at?
You cannot stay long here.
May I ask Mr. Officer, what really happened to the Ding Residence?
That old criminal Ding deceived his superior, deluded his subordinates and had evil plots.
He has become a wanted criminal.
Why are you asking about these? Hurry and leave!
Or else, we will treat you as his accomplice and catch you.
Thanks then.
Qian Yi Shou!
Ma Shun?
Why are you here?
To tell you the truth, Lord Ding has fallen in dire straits.
The Ding Residence has been sealed up.
Okay. Then it's good that you are here.
Return that chest of Lord Ding's deposit money back to him.
What do you mean by that Hero Qian?
Lord Ding has just fallen into difficulty.
Are you severing all your ties with him?
I don't mean it that way.
It's just that it's already been quite long and I still haven't done any of the tasks ordered by Lord Ding.
I indeed feel guilty about it.
It looks like the title of being the no. 1 assassin in the world needs to be removed.
I indeed should just retire from Jianghu.
You just return to Jianghu.
Now you are retiring again,
and also it's not early or late, you just have to choose when Lord Ding is at a difficult state, right?
Lord Ding said that we should first wait for you to become comfortable and steady before looking for you.
But unexpectedly, you and I bump into each other today.
Then I'll just relay to you his words then.
What did he say?
Lord Ding said that he admires you a lot.
He can forego bothering with the tasks that you were not able to complete.
And also, Lord Ding has already guessed that you would return that money.
Hero Qian, I can take that money away.
But it doesn't mean that the matters between you and Lord Ding are all settled.
This is a favor that you owe him.
You must repay it in the future.
Okay.
As long as it isn't against my work principles, I won't refuse it.
Hero Qian, let me give you some advice.
Although Lord Ding right now has fallen into dire straits,
if he wants to turn things around, it's just a matter of a blink of an eye.
Then I wish everything goes Lord Ding's way.
Hero Qian, take care.
Bai Ze, please understand this.
Our past friendship was all fake.
Right now, whoever holds the Star Chart, that's the owner.
You want it? Then come and get it.
A Ji Ya, aren't these words of yours too much?
In our journey, we shared happiness and hardships together.
We also treated you sincerely as a friend.
That's right. Aren't we one group?
Those are just your one-sided thoughts.
Now I don't kill you. It's counted as my payment for this debt of friendship.
A Ji Ya...
Then why must you save us every time?
A Ji Ya!
Let go.
We have been through so many things together.
Don't you really treat us as friends?
i never treated you all as friends.
Your eyes tell me
that you don't think this way.
I don't want to loose you as a friend, either.
Bai Ze, stop being that you are always right.
Do you think that I really won't dare to kill you?
A Ji Ya!
Let go. Let go!
Bai Ze!
A Ji Ya, are you for real?!
A Ji Ya,
you feel that you can really be cruel enough to do it?
Now that you already hit the person.
You should have vented your anger enough, too.
We still have a mission.
- Don't force me.- A Ji Ya!
A Ji Ya, aren't you being too much?
Pointing your sword towards your own friends.
Don't you have any morality?
Didn't Uncle Zhan take you into the Illuminati and raise you?
And then afterwards, just to save us all,
he sacrificed his life and died with Elder Zhao Ran.
Isn't that affection?
You only think of your own pain.
But have you thought about what Older Bro Fei felt?
He just reunited with his own father and didn't have enough time to reminisce with him,
he already had to say goodbye to him forever.
This pain of losing what one has just obtained,
isn't it more painful than yours?!
Yuan Shuai.
Saying so many highfalutin words can't change the fact that he is a thief!
I was not really some upright person to begin with.
A Ji Ya, the Star Chart is in my hand.
If you want it, then just kill me.
And me!
As long as I am still alive,
I won't let any of you slaughter each other.
Xiong Fei, Yuan Shuai,
my father is the leader of the Heaven Strategy Envoys.
Logically speaking,
all the consequences... should be mine to bear.
Bai Ze, stop that!
Just kill me.
I definitely won't avoid it.
Bai Ze, don't say such stupid words.
A Ji Ya has gone crazy. She really will kill you.
If killing me... will make your hatred disappear,
then just kill me.
I am willing to die.
A Ji Ya,
after you kill me, you must continue with Yuan Shuai and Xiong Fei
the mission of gathering the Magic Stars and stabilizing the world.
Okay.
Hey!
Hey! A Ji Ya!
Zhan Xiong Fei, if you don't give me the Star Chart, I'll then kill him.
No. I'll give you the Star Chart then. Here.
Hurry. Go there and arrest them, especially that woman.
- I want her alive.- Yes.
You three indeed have someone helping you.
The little lady looks so pretty.
How come you started to fight?
Could it be there is too little meat for so many wolves?
You...
We...
Only you Toyo people have such dirty thoughts.
I am not with them.
Right. You are mistaken.
She is not with us.
Do you still want to fool me?
In front of me, stop playing good cop and bad cop.
Because all of you are too soft.
Men, arrest them all.
Yes!
So this is the legendary Star Chart that can locate the Magic Star?
Hurry! Throw them all into the sea to feed the sharks! Hurry!
Wait!
I have something to say.
You are already about to die, so what nonsense do you still want to say?
Your aim is to get the Star Chart and to find the Magic Stars.
But what you don't know is that I'm the only person
in this world who knows how to read the Star Chart!
That's right.
In this world, only Older Bro Fei can decode the Star Chart.
Even if you have the Star Chart, you won't be able to locate the Magic Stars.
To put it another way, the Star Chart is just a useless brick to you now.
If that's the case, leave him alive first.
As for the remaining, throw them into the sea to feed the fishes!
Wait!
My condition for working with you is that you must let my comrades go.
And also, you must not hurt them.
Or else, I'd rather die than help you.
Fine.
It's getting more and more interesting.
I just like the kind of people like you with affection and loyalty.
Since you insist on talking conditions with me, then I will also give you my condition.
Immediately tell me the location of the Magic Star.
Or else...
- I'll kill her.- Hey!
You should know... that the sword of us Toyo warriors
can cut through steel like mud.
And also, don't you dare play tricks on me.
That way, you will all die more tragically.
Not saying, is that it?
Okay.
No!
Stop!
Could this place be a territory for swindlers?
A Ji Ya...
Xiong Fei, Yuan Shuai!
This smoke has poison. Hurry and escape to the seas.
A Ji Ya...
Yuan Shuai! Xiong Fei! Escape to the waters quickly.
Hurry and go!
Who are you?!
A Ji Ya!
Yuan Shuai!
Come. Come. Here. Here.
Take him away. This one. Take him away.
Okay. Okay. Come.
This one's not bad. He can surely sell for a good price.
Surely no problem.
Take her away.
- And also this one. Take him away, too.- Okay.
This one's not bad. Take him away.
Okay.
Hey...there is even a Toyo man here.
Don't know if anyone will buy him.
Forget it. Just let him go.
Hey, there is even one who escaped there.
It's just one.
Let's go.
Go. Go.
- Let's go now!- Go. Go.
A Ji Ya!
Yaun Shuai!
Xiong Fei!
Where is this place?
Is there anyone around?
Hey, Yuan Shuai.
Yuan Shuai.
Is it time to eat?
What eat?
Look. Where are we?
Where are we?!
How would I know?
How come we ended up here?
Yuan Shuai, what is this?
You also have one.
- That's right. 100?- What does it mean?
- How about we ask around?- Okay.
Who will we ask?
- How about... that bald head?- Okay. Go.
Hey! Bald head!
Where are we now?
Where?
You'll know later.
Then... Then what does this mean?
Hey. If we know, why would we still ask you?
That's right. Just hurry and say it.
Hey, Big Bro, I feel that we should calm down a little!
Don't be afraid. Don't be afraid. His feet are also tied up.
Don't be afraid. Don't be afraid. He is chained. He is chained.
Come. Come.
- Bring them out.- Yes!
- Open the door!- Yes.
Why did you lock us up?
Stop your nonsense.
The show for today will be starting soon.
Is it a celebratory show?
Is there anyone around?
Time to eat.
What is this place?
- Just eat.- I'm asking you, what is this place?
I am just a servant that delivers food.
I don't know anything else.
I won't eat your food.
Whether you eat or not has nothing to do with me.
I am just a food delivery person.
Take me out.
Drop the chopsticks. You are not going anywhere.
Just behave and stay here.
Buddies, let's go.
Hey, that girl does have some skills.
We should be careful.
How long have you been working with us here?
Just that kind of woman?
Starve and scare her for three days and
I guarantee you that she'll obediently go out and serve the guests.
That is indeed.
In a few days, I will be transferred to the main hall.
The task to watch these people will be left with you guys.
You just do your job well. Boss Sakai won't treat you unfairly.
Yes. Yes. Older Bro Jie's words are right.
Let's go. Let's go out and have a drink.
I just got out of the tiger's den but ended up in the wolf's lair.
Now, no one will come to save me anymore.
KoreanDramaX.co
♫ In a rainy night, ♫
♫ I've not put away that windbreaker umbrella ♫
♫ My hand, that grasps it, is unwilling to throw it away ♫
♫ I want to be together till the end ♫
♫ Upon opening my eyes, ♫
♫ there may be only fallen leaves all over the ground left ♫
♫ There may be only those cold long streets left ♫
♫ I have you next to me ♫
♫ We agree to wait till tomorrow ♫
♫ Wait until snow and frost compromise with sunshine ♫
♫ You must believe ♫
♫ those agreements that we made at young ♫
♫ We agree to wait till tomorrow to ♫
♫ walk through the coldest winter night and ♫
♫ kiss the most beautiful spring together ♫
♫ Stand side-by-side before the daybeak ♫