KoreanDramaX.co
Are you alright? Hey!
Water...
Here.
Today, is a day of welcoming the newbies.
In this arena,
money and strength are supreme!
Wow! Who are all these people?
We wouldn't have landed in some tribe again, right?
Yuan Shuai, have you seen a cockfight?
Never. But I have seen a dogfight.
Today, we are being treated as dogs in a dogfight.
Next, let us welcome our power king!
Wow!
How come he is that tall?! Is he still a person?
He... Is he a person?!
These two are our newbies.
To tell you the truth...
Don't be afraid, Yuan Shuai. No matter whether he's some king of strength or big gorilla,
we-we'll attack together.
...can fight with the power king.
But we still won't have a chance...
There is always a chance.
Staying alive is winning.
Dying is losing.
I want him. Within one incense time, I can pinch you to death 10 times.
- He wants to fight you.- No. Older Bro Fei...
- Save me. I don't want to fight him.- I...I will save you.
Unchain that little fat guy for me. Let him go in.
- Hey! Hey! Let me fight with him!- I don't want to fight him...
- This one is quite weak...- Let me fight with him!
Yuan Shuai! Yuan Shuai! Run!
The competition starts now!
Let me fight with him!
Let go of me!
- Come over. - Don't come near.
Wait! Let me tell you. I know martial arts!
Don't come near! I'll beat you to death!
Fierce tiger goes down the mountain!
Fierce dragon crosses the river! White goose raises its wings!
You brat are playing dirty with me.
Yuan Shuai!
Yuan Shuai! Hold it together. I'll save you!
Older Bro Fei, during critical times, I can really depend on you!
- Are you alright?- Yuan Shuai.
I'll protect you.
- Don't be afraid.- No. No.
Don't be afraid. Don't come near!
The competition ends.
The result is... a tie!
Older Bro Fei, we survived!
Hey! Hey! Don't come near!
Fight! Fight!
Stop trying to act brave. Just go home.
Don't fight anymore. That's right.
Find two more people and fight again.
Don't worry.
It's all thanks to me.
It's all thanks to you, Older Bro Fei.
All of you look! You, too, come here.
Come. Come. Come.
Everyone, look.
These are our newly arrived three dogs.
Look at this dog. Little.
Especially these two little dogs. These two...
Don't look at it being small.
It is very nimble.
His flesh is very buff.
If you boil it, the aroma will reach more than ten miles.
Strong enrichment!
It enriches iron and blood, too.
Even if you eat his bone, it's very nourishing.
Very nourishing. Right.
- Hey!- Are you buying a dog?
No. Hey.
That dog is a man's most loyal friend.
Everyone shouldn't eat dog meat. Am I right?
It's none of your business. How come it can't be eaten?
No.
It's you.
Aren't you that...
- Do you know him? Go back to work!- Hey!
How can you hit other people?!
Do you dare push me? I'll hit you, too!
Hey, don't fight anymore!
Star Chart?
Catch him!
Hurry and catch him!
Stop right there!
Stop!
Hurry and chase him! Stop right there! Stop running already!
- Stop!- Please move aside!
Stop! Stop right there!
Look where you are going!
- Stop! Stop! He's there! Hurry and chase him!- Hey!
Don't run! Hurry! Stop!
Stop! Stop! Don't run!
Stop! Where are you running to?!
- You rascal, come out!- Come out!
Search!
What do you think this place is?
You can just search as you want?
Ming Zhen, let me tell you.
I am here to catch that rascal.
It has nothing to do with you.
Any matter here in this tavern is my matter.
Don't mind her. Search!
Ming Zhen, no need. No need.
Rascal, even if you are able to hide now, you can't hide forever!
Okay. Ming Zhen... just you wait and see. Wait and see.
Let's go. Ming Zhen!
You wait and see. Wait and see!
Let's go.
Thank you, Heroine.
If you don't want to die, then just stay here to work.
- No. No.- Can you not push me?
Get in.
- My bones have already loosened and scattered.- No.
My foot has dislocated.
It's meal time! It's meal time!
- Older Bro Fei, don't push me down!- I am not!
Hurry and steal!
You... a group of beasts...
You group of beasts!
You are beasts!
- Even food, you can't serve as enough to be full. How are we going to play?- Just this much? We fought so hard earlier.
Older Bro Fei, I'm hungry...
Alright, i's okay. It's okay.
Keep it. Keep it.
- Baldy. Oh, wrong. Big Bro. - Big Bro.
- Big Bro, let me massage this for you for a while. Woah!- Big Bro, you are really a good guy.
What a big and strong arm.
- What a stylish bald.- Such a beautiful mustache--
Never thought that you were that lucky.
What do you mean?
When we welcome newbies, only one is able to come back alive every time.
We've never seen one where both came back.
You... Have you been here for a very long already?
Due to the big waves, our boat capsized.
I was washed up to this small island.
I don't know how but I got dragged into here.
Let me out! Let me out!
Let me out!
Let me out! I want to find my daughter!
- I want to find my daughter!- Shut up! Stop your nonsense!
Let me out!
- I want to find my daughter!- Shut up!
Let go of me!
Attack!
KoreanDramaX.co
This place is a hell on earth.
Hey, then did you ever try escaping?
That's right.
Go to sleep.
You still have one round tomorrow.
Don't.
You must tell us.
We need to escape from here.
Our friends are waiting for us.
Friends?
You better take care of yourselves first.
People who still don't know if they will survive tomorrow or not,
why ask so many questions?
Ming Zhen, the price you gave for this batch of products is too low.
The highest, 500 liang*.(* Chinese money)
No. 900 liang.
500 liang is a reasonable price.
You should remove the word reasonable.
This product is something that I exchanged my life to get.
My place is a tavern, not a hospital.
I'm not responsible in treating people.
Ming Zhen, I know.
That rascal is just here in your tavern.
Just hand him over to me, okay?
Hand him over to me!
Boss, your eyebrows are gone.
Your mustache is also gone.
Ming Zhen!
Go. Go.
Quickly go. Quickly go.
I'll say it again.
Either 55 or 500 liang.
Okay. Deal.
- How about it?- Your so hateful.
- Are you happy?- Did you like what I bought for you?
I like it.
- I'll buy you another one next time.- Okay.
- Hey, Mister Feng. You can't enter here.- Mister Feng, you can't enter here.
I just want to enter this room.
What?! Newcomer? Not allowed to be seen?
- I have the money.- Hey, Mister Feng.
- Mister Feng. - Lady Boss has instructed us.
The newcomer has quite a wild personality.
We will just look for another one for you.
Wild?
I just love wild ones.
Hey, Mister Feng!
Mister! Mister!
Hey, her look isn't quite bad.
No wonder you are locked up and not allowed to see customers.
Come. Come. Accompany me to drink.
Mister Feng, are you alright?
Get lost.
I just love fierce ones.
Hey, are you leaving this soon? Not even informing me first.
This lady really is quite a beauty.
Her martial arts are also very good.
She's way stronger than these useless men under me.
Hello, my name is Sayuri Sakai.
I still don't know your name.
I am A Ji Ya. I just passed by this place.
We are strangers meeting by chance.
Hope Older Sister won't make things difficult for me.
Strangers meeting by chance?
Okay. Then let's be friends.
I am also just older than you by a few years so just call me Older Sister.
I also have read several books. A Ji Ya is a good name.
It means destiny.
Indeed.
How come this skin of yours is so smooth and soft?
You are really making me envious.
Can you tell me how you foreigners take care of your skin?
This... I don't know much.
Starting today, you should learn how to take good care of skin.
A woman's skin is the weakest.
You are not like me who only secludes on the second line.
You still have to fight on the front line.
What do you mean?
I saved you so you now belong to me.
This is the rule on this island.
You earning money for me, that is your duty.
A person should learn how to show gratitude. Isn't that so?
I thank Older Sister for saving my life.
But as for Older Sister's request, I can't agree to it.
I still have to go find my friends.
Is this place not good?
I saved you from the traffickers.
I spent so much energy and money for it.
Even if you don't give considerations to the monk, you should give one to Buddha, right?
- Older Sister, so sorry. I really can't do as you want.- Stay right there!
Do you really think I have the interest to talk reasons with you here?
Drag her away.
Watch her well.
A girl who doesn't know what's good for her.
I should also go back and have my beauty sleep.
Don't bother me again for such things.
Yes!
Put it in there.
Those friends I told you about, have you seen them?
Don't worry. These past few days, I have been taking note of it.
- Once there is any news, I'll immediately inform you.- Okay.
- Thank you.- Okay.
Be careful on your way.
Slave combat. Always exciting everyday.
Remember to go.
Here. Have one.
Hey!
- That...- What?
This... Is this a fat guy?
That's right.
By his side, is there still a slightly taller and thinner guy?
Can you take me to see them?
Based on what?
Look.
Here. Take it.
Take me to see your boss. Okay?
Hey, meal time! Meal time!
Woah!
Hurry and eat. Tomorrow, it's up to you guys.
Wow!
Has the sky changed? How come they are being so nice?
- There's even a drumstick.- Earlier I heard them talking about something...
He seems to have said that if this drumstick was cooked for an hour more, it might taste better.
How come you only know how to eat?
Or else what?
They were talking about... about... seeing what our fate will be tomorrow.
What does it mean?
Don't know.
- This drumstick...- No...
No. We don't want it.
What's going on?
i don't know.
While there is a drumstick, just hurry and eat it.
The people in here have not eaten any drumstick yet.
Why?
Aren't there chicken drumsticks in the kitchen?
The chicken drumsticks in the kitchen are for the Power King.
- Ha?- Only people who are fighting with him get to have a drumstick.
It's just that...
It's just that what?
Hurry and say it. How come you stopped midway?
It's just that people who have eaten a chicken drumstick have never returned.
Never returned?
Older Bro Fei, does it mean we can get out?
Never returning means we have to forever stay in the arena.
How can this be called a chicken drumstick?
This is totally arsenic.
It's not even as good as arsenic.
If you die because of eating arsenic, you don't even need to get beaten up before dying.
Let me out! Let me out!
I still don't want to die.
Older Bro Fei, I still want to live longer.
I still want to eat lots of food.
I still don't want to die!
Stop being noisy already.
You won't die.
Older Bro Fei. Older Bro Fei.
You are so smart so you must have an idea already, right?
How come it's so few?
These are 500 liang.
We worked hard for 2 months. Once we divide this among us, it's not even enough to buy a woman.
Didn't we already agree to sell them for 900 liang?
How come there is only 500 liang?
Only 500 liang?
Captain, our buddies are complaining that their share is quite few.
What do you mean?
Some people are saying...
that you personally pocketed the money.
I, Cheng Ming Pan,
am not that kind of person.
I know that with captain's character, you won't do such things.
But our buddies just want an explanation.
How come the money we got this time is so few?
Right.
I know.
I know that you all are discontented.
You found a captain and followed him
just for him to bear the responsibility that you all can't bear and to make appropriate decisions!
So as to preserve your own interest.
In this world, only money and power are most realistic.
Money may be lost
but power will never be lost.
Let me tell you.
What others can't do, I can do.
What others can't defeat, I can defeat.
If I say that I can't do it,
then on this island,
none can do it.
Let's go.
You people let go of me! Let go of me!
- Are you blind?!- Who is this?
Captain, we picked him up on the beach two days ago.
Let's try to get along. Let's try to get along.
This... Who is the one paying for all these?
Ladies, go disperse now.
Disperse. Disperse.
Go. Let's go.
He is a Toyo man.
You all know that I am a Toyo man and do you still treat me like this?
You all will die tragically!
- Come! Throw him into the ocean to feed the fishes!- Yes!
- Get up!- Wait! Wait! Wait!
I can tell you all a chance to get rich.
A chance to get super rich.
It is 100 times more than the money you earn right now.
You all leave.
Yes!
Come. Sit. Sit.
Let me tell you.
On a mysterious small island,
there is a very valuable treasure that's worth several cities.
- Are you talking about the Money Island?- That's right.
The legend of Money Island is known even by a three-year-old child.
Did you think I'd believe it?
It's up to you to believe it or not.
Everyone does know about it,
but who really went to find it? Think about it.
Don't be rash. Listen to me.
We Toyo warriors believe one saying the most.
Chance is given to people who loves to take risks.
Think about it. Did I endured numerous dangers and hardships to come here
just because of a legend?
I am thinking on your behalf.
I am giving you a chance.
Look at those sailors of yours.
They only see money.
Without money, you don't even get the power to rule them.
I'm afraid your captain position might be hard to keep.
You can choose not to believe what I'm saying.
Go to the island and ask about it.
There surely is someone who knows this secret.
It's just that they won't tell you.
Won't share it with you.
What you are talking about is...
Ming Zhen?
Smart.
Just because you say that they are your friends,
you are asking me to let them go.
Little child, you are too naive.
In this world, there are no free things.
Okay. Then you tell me. In what way will you set them free?
Very simple.
Everything in here are merchandise.
As long as you are able to have enough of that,*(* money)
you can take anyone away.
You want money, is that it?
Okay. How much?
Let's not first talk about money.
This little fatty
is currently loved by the audience.
He is my precious.
I really kind of can't bear to let him go.
Didn't you say that if I have the money, you will let them go?
Just say it. How much money do you want?
Can you see this box?
In it is all the betting money.
During the competition, this money will grow more and more.
As long as by that time, you can give me twice the amount,
you can take the people away.
You clearly don't want to set them free!
If you won't accept it, I won't try to force you.
Okay.
I accept it.
But you must first let me see them.
They, you can't.
Just seeing one, you can.
Pull that little fatty up here.
Yes!
KoreanDramaX.co
Miss. Miss.
Miss, wake up.
It's time to eat.
What is your name?
My name is Ah Chang.
Ah Chang?
My foot seemed wounded.
Do you have any medicine?
These exact medicines I have will be useful.
Being a woman and going on fights outside,
why didn't you prepare some medicines?
You really are very considerate.
That who, has my Younger Sis eaten yet?
She still hasn't.
What is this thing?
Her foot is injured.
I brought her some medicine.
You are quite considerate.
- Leave first.- Yes.
What really are you planning to do to me?
You are my precious treasure.
How can I bear to do anything to you?
I am even hoping for you to earn money for me.
By that time, the two of us can be rich.
Once we divide the money,
wandering the ends of the world and travelling around the world,
who would be willing to stay in this god-forsaken and inhumane island?
Let me tell you. I will never do any of those things you are telling me to do.
You better just give up on this idea.
Younger Sister,
a person should learn to be grateful.
If not because I saved you,
you already don't know where you're at now.
I even give you good food and drinks everyday.
Why don't you just let me work in the kitchen?
Will I let a beautiful lady work in the kitchen?
Am I insane?
You are indeed insane.
Younger Sister,
just listen to my advice.
Just do your job well.
You tell me, you are just staying in this place everyday, what can you do?
Listen to me.
I guarantee that your future life will have endless glory and wealth.
These are all high quality cosmetics.
Style yourself well.
You must be beautiful.
A woman... should be beautiful.
As long as you are beautiful,
let's talk about some other things.
I thank Older Sister for saving me.
But for the matter you want me to do, I can't do it.
Too bad, it's not up to you.
Such a pretty lady,
that even my heart flutters just by looking at you.
Not just five years ago,
even 10 years ago, my skin isn't as good as yours.
Really so envious.
I am giving you one chance to get the top beauty position.
Once you have decided, tell it to me.
Let's go.
I don't know where Bai Ze and the others are right now.
How come I still am thinking about them?
They have no relations with me at all.
- Get over there.- Bai Ze!
- Yuan Shuai!- Move away!
Yuan Shuai, how are you and Xiong Fei?
We both are doing good.
I thought that I would never be able to see you anymore.
It's all my fault. I don't have the ability to save you from those human traffickers.
Why must you still say all this now?
We all have no freedom to act independently now.
Have you found A Ji Ya?
Not yet.
I plan to save you and Xiong Fei first
and then let's look for A Ji Ya together.
- Okay.- Enough already.
You already saw the person and talked to him.
Just think of a way to gather the money now.
Take him away.
Go!
Wait for me! Once I'm able to come up with the money, I surely will come back to save you!
If something bad happens to me and Older Bro Fei,
help me tell Thirteenth Older Sis that we are having a good life in a far away place.
We will forever miss her!
- Remember!- Stop saying nonsense!
Hey!
I will surely bring you the money before the competition starts.
But you must not hurt my friends.
I believe you.
Go now.
Your sailors only see money.
Without money, you don't even get the power to rule them.
Your captain position won't be stable.
Captain, our boss is here.
- You can leave now.- Yes.
It's so late already. Captain wants to see me for what reasons?
Actually, we can work together.
How?
I know. You have stayed the longest here on this island.
You surely know where the treasure is.
Even a three-year-old child knows that there is no treasure on this island.
Let me tell you. This island...
I have the greatest strength.
If you won't tell me the location of the treasure,
I am making an oath that I will let you have nothing.
If you really feel that this island has a treasure,
then just go look for it yourself.
If you find it, it's all yours.
I don't want any of it.
Okay.
You're not saying the truth, is that it?
Just you wait then.
Miss, are you better?
I'm better.
- You... are Ah Chang, right?- Right.
Do you have a family?
Ah Chang, those... I'm giving them to you. Give them to your wife.
I am just a food server. I don't have any family.
What's the meaning of that?!
Who says that a food server can't have any family of their own?
Ah Chang, have you thought about living a new kind of life?
You go to work outside while she is at home washing clothes,
cooking, and raising your children.
When you go home, there will be warm dishes waiting for you to eat.
When you are doing nothing, you all go out to stroll the town,
to watch plays,
to do anything that you want to do.
Ah Chang, why must you let yourself suffer by staying here?
Isn't Sakai like you, wanting to escape this place and live a more wonderful life?
How come you won't?
- Come with me.- Ah Chang, you...
Don't say anything anymore. Come with me.
Hurry.
Here.
Stop! Stop!
What time is it?
Will you still let people sleep?
Not even choosing a good time to escape...
- I'm begging you already. Just let me borrow the money.- No.
Before it was because I saw you wander into here
and were being chased, I felt you were quite pitiful
so I helped you.
I already gave you extreme benevolence and did my utmost duty.
Don't dare ask for more.
Believe me.
Just loan me the money first, I will definitely pay it back.
You are just talking and not showing me anything to hold on to.
How can I believe you?
Actually, I am the capital's...
I went out to sea this time because I have to do an important mission.
Who would have thought that we would encounter a sea disaster midway,
my friends and I got separated.
I am borrowing money in order to save them.
How about this?
As long as I can go back,
I'll immediately send men to bring you the money.
If I believe everything that I hear,
I won't be able to live up to now.
You must know.
In this world, no one is duty bound to help you.
Okay. Then tell me.
On what conditions will you be willing to help me?
I won't lend it to you no matter what.
Hey... Hey!
You tell me, you two,
can't even choose a good time.
Didn't I tell you to take good care of your skin?
Look at you. You must have not slept well last night, right?
Your black eye circles have all come out.
Don't say anything anymore.
I will not listen to you.
Just let me die.
Hey... stop mentioning death.
Who doesn't know how to die?
A person should live with a bit of meaning.
If I am like you choosing to die every time I encounter a problem,
I would have died a hundred times.
Stop your nonsense! Just kill me!
You are just young but you have such a bad temper.
Always getting angry will make you age fast.
You should try smiling more.
You're even lecturing me? Don't you also want to escape?
Fallacy.
No one is hindering or stopping you, yet you still stay on this island.
You even have the nerve to scold these people who want to die?
Every person has their predicaments.
Tell me. What method must I use to make you stay?
How about this? I'll make a deal with you.
Aren't you looking for your friend?
Tell me his name and what he looks like.
If you agree to stay,
I'll then help you find your friend.
KoreanDramaX.co
♫ In a rainy night, ♫
♫ I've not put away that windbreaker umbrella ♫
♫ My hand, that grasps it, is unwilling to throw it away ♫
♫ I want to be together till the end ♫
♫ Upon opening my eyes, ♫
♫ there may be only fallen leaves all over the ground left ♫
♫ There may be only those cold long streets left ♫
♫ I have you next to me ♫
♫ We agree to wait till tomorrow ♫
♫ Wait until snow and frost compromise with sunshine ♫
♫ You must believe ♫
♫ those agreements that we made at young ♫
♫ We agree to wait till tomorrow to ♫
♫ walk through the coldest winter night and ♫
♫ kiss the most beautiful spring together ♫
♫ Stand side-by-side before the daybreak ♫