KoreanDramaX.co
Father! You are indeed here!
Are you alright? Father.
Zhao Ran, you dare bully my father?!
See how dangerous I am!
- Xiong Fei!- Child!
- Are you alright?- I'm fine.
Zhao Ran, you tell me why your complexion is so bad.
You tell me, did you get that old from being too angry?
You see how old your face is.
It's so old that we can't tell what your age is anymore.
- Are you around 100 years old already?- Jeez,
Elder. Your face is full of wrinkles. So scary.
Zhan Xiong Fei, you better not look at him.
Maybe it is contagious.
- It is even contagious?- It's so disgusting.
My god...
Your facial skin really looks so bad.
It almost looks like the old tree barks outside.
You really need some good facial maintenance.
How about this, I'll teach you some maintenance techniques.
Or else, this aging of your face might kill you one day.
That's right.
You can't go out of your house if you are like that.
If you go out, you'll scare people.
You guys are still so young but you dared to go against me?
Today, I'll let you father and son die here!
Wow! Your creases can even talk!
Father, let's attack together and kill this wrinkled monster.
You tell me, do you think this labyrinth will collapse soon?
- Impossible.- It's real.
Earlier, this ceiling almost--
Let's go. Let's follow them.
Let's go.
Elder Chang Ming... weren't you already...
No. I just lost all my power.
Right now, time is money. You hurry up to leave this place.
This place will soon disappear.
Respectfully greeting Elder.
Elder Chang Ming, hurry and save the Illuminati.
Hurry...
A Ji Ya, the Illuminati will never die.
Only bad people will perish.
Listen to me for now first.
Immediately leave this labyrinth first.
Elder...
- Older Bro Fei, Zi Su- Bai Ze.
- Are you alright?- We're fine.
That's good that you're fine.
You all came just in time.
Men! Arrest them all!
Elder Zhao Ran, you willfully changed the teachings of the Illuminati.
You are not worthy to lead the Illuminati.
Only I can become the real elder of the Illuminati right now.
Are you rebelling?
You are committing sins.
Whom among you...
really has the Magic Star?
If you don't tell me, I will have to use force.
Little brute!
Shut up!
Don't even think of treating me like a lackey of yours again.
Elder Zhao Ran, there are some things
that one should be paying back already!
Are you... Chang Ming?
Elder Chang Ming?
You all must hurry and leave this place,
including you, Elder Jiong Ye.
After leaving this place, just leave here to me.
You are still alive.
No. I can't be considered as being alive.
I already lost all my power.
But with my remaining energy, I can still open this box.
All of this will end here.
So you are the ultimate secret key for the Thousand Return Doors.
Father!
Little Biao Zi, goodbye.
Let's play a finding the treasure game again one last time.
A Ji Ya, I can only pay what I owe you up to here.
How did we end up here?
Hey, are you all alright?
I'm fine.
Good thing I didn't lose the Magic Star.
Father!
Little Biao Zi, goodbye.
Let's play a finding the treasure game again one last time.
A Ji Ya, I can only pay back what I owe you up to here.
- Zhan Xiong Fei! Where are you going?!- Older Bro Fei!
- Xiong Fei!- Zhan Xiong Fei!
Older Bro Fei!
Xiong Fei, what are you looking for?
My father said that he left me a finding the treasure game.
Older Bro Fei, let me help you find it together.
I found it.
Magic Star?
Father...
KoreanDramaX.co
My father said that the Magic Stars originally don't belong to the human world.
Why must he leave it to me?
Maybe just like what your father said, this is predestined.
Ma Shun respectfully greeting Your Lady Highness.
- A Ji Ya! - A Ji Ya!
You are still not dead, A Ji Ya...
What you said was right.
They care about you very much.
This way, matters will be easier.
What Your Lady Highness said is right, A Ji Ya is indeed not yet dead.
But... she will die very soon.
Hey!
Let's make an exchange.
Use the two Magic Stars in your hands in exchange for the life of your one and only companion A Ji Ya.
This business deal is very fair and reasonable, right?
It's yours!
I never thought that it would be that easy.
But what if I'm going against my word now?
- Hey!- You!
No need to panic that much. I was just joking.
Doing business must depend on trust.
I do still know that principle.
A Ji Ya, I won't kill you.
No need to thank me.
Hope to see you again next time.
Go! Go!
A Ji Ya!
Don't come near me!
Although I can't kill you right now,
I still can't forget this hatred.
Zi Su, these court beads were given by your father to the domain king.
A Ji Ya!
A Ji Ya, listen to me.
What else do you still want to say?
Everything that must be said has already been said.
Don't force me to kill you!
Can't the friendship that we developed in our journey really withstand a single blow?
Can't withstand a single blow?
If you tricked me, I could forgive you.
If you made me angry, I could also forgive you.
But your father killed my father.
Having such a huge grudge! How can I forgive you?!
A Ji Ya, the matter of our fathers,
why must we be the one to bear it?
Enough!
If we are not the ones who will bear it, who will?
Let me tell you. I hate you!
I hate you all!
Okay.
Okay. I won't say anything anymore.
No matter where you'll go, I won't care anymore.
But you must take this.
This is your father King Salin's personal adornment.
Hope it can bless you with blissfulness and happiness.
I don't want these court beads.
In your eyes, this is a royal grant.
But in my eyes, it is hatred and pain.
Whatever it had represented in the past isn't important.
But it now represents the care that we your friends have for you.
I will never forget the first time I saw you.
Your smile is deeply carved in my heart.
What's the use of saying these things now?
I will never remember them.
I have already forgotten them.
You have forgotten.
But I won't forget.
In my heart, it is already deeply and stably rooted.
Unless time could go back and I chose not to meet you.
If time could go back, I wouldn't give you that bread.
If time could really go back,
I would surely stop my father and not let him do those--
Enough!
In this world, there isn't that many "if's."
You are also being too naive.
From now on, you look after your own concern
and leave me to my own affairs.
Hope to see you again in the future.
Hope we won't see each other again.
Forgive me for not being able to see you off
because I don't want the last image in my heart
to be your back while you are leaving me.
Xiong Fei...
Don't be like this...
If you are sad,
just say it.
You keeping it to yourself and not talking like this
is really making us all worried.
Zi Su,
when I was little, this was how my father left me.
How come the same thing must happen to me twice?
Why? Why?
Xiong Fei.
I know.
We all know.
Elder Jiong Ye...
your father, is such an adorable person.
You both lived alone for the past ten plus years.
It wasn't easy for you two to have finally reunited.
But for us...
I know that your heart is sad, Xiong Fei.
How come the one who died, isn't me?
Zhan Xiong Fei! Don't say things like that.
Even if... Even if you kill yourself now,
your father won't be able to come back anymore.
Zi Su...
I wasn't able to protect my father.
I wasn't able to protect the Magic Stars.
If you encounter any disaster in the future,
I won't also be able to protect you.
I can't even protect the things that I want to protect.
What's the use of me still living?
- What's the use of me living?- Your spouting nonsense.
Of course, your life has meaning.
You still have to become a hero who shares his blessings
and takes responsibilities for hardships.
Moreover...
we all are living well.
Who needs your protection?
As long as you understand what I mean, that's good.
I'm going to find the Magic Stars.
Where are you going?
Move aside!
Such an important matter,
you think it's something that will come true just because you say so?!
Bai Ze, stop lecturing me!
Move aside!
Stop being stubborn already!
Let me tell you. We are sad too that Elder Jiong Ye died.
You can be sad, throw tantrums, and be stubborn here!
But if you are just going to have yourself killed for nothing,
I will never allow it!
Bai Ze, stop being opinionated!
Move aside!
Not moving aside!
Right now is not the time for you to try to be a hero! Do you know that?!
Stop fighting! Stop fighting!
Older Brother Bai Ze, you stop fighting!
Don't fight anymore...
Zhan Xiong Fei! Bai Ze! You stop fighting!
- Stop fighting.- Does anyone want to eat some corn?
What are you doing?
Hey... Hey...
What happened?
Yu!
Big Bros, do you guys have water? Can you give me some?
We have. Go give her some water.
Thank you. Thank you.
Miss, why are you traveling alone here in the Gobi desert?
I can see that you didn't bring any luggage or equipment, either.
That shouldn't be.
Where do you plan to go?
I am going home.
The Helan Meadows is my home.
Oh... Then does it mean... that you're also from the Helan tribe?
Heaven bless you.
Miss, how long have you not been in your hometown?
Probably 10 years already.
Then you don't know what our present hometown looks like now.
Since 10 years ago during the death of King Salin,
the tribe got ruled by a subordinate of King Salin called A Lamusi.
He called himself the Helan King.
Helan King?
We people in the grasslands all revere the Helan God.
No one ever had the nerve to call himself Helan King.
Right. This Helan King has very huge ambitions
but he is really very ordinary.
- It's already getting dark. We have to continue with our journey.- Thank you.
Miss, take that.
I wish you good fortune.
Heaven bless you.
Buddies, we have to continue our travel now!
Set out!
Let's go now.
Hurry and come in. It's time to eat.
Why are you so slow?
That... I have something to report.
Today, a friend who doesn't want him to be named,
asked me to relay a message to his other friend.
He had hit quite hard earlier
and said quite hurtful words.
He feels very sorry.
And another one, another friend who doesn't want to be named, either,
asked me to tell his other friend
that what he did earlier was also quite excessive.
And then... Jeez, can you two just say it?
Two grown men, can you resolve your problem by yourselves?
I won't mind you two anymore. I am eating now.
- That...- That...
Earlier, I indeed was very rash.
I was also quite rash.
My language was also quite excessive.
My punches were quite heavy.
It was indeed quite heavy.
It still hurts up to now.
But I didn't punch you lightly, either.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Alrihgt. Alright. We all are still friends.
Me too. Me too.
Okay.
- Okay.- Okay now.
Alright. Alright. Let's go to the next topic of discussion now.
What topic of discussion?
What do we do next?
I don't know what to do next.
I just want to know how A Ji Ya is doing now.
Right now, we weren't able to accomplish anything.
If we go back to the capital just like this, how embarrassing would that be?
But if we don't go back, we won't be able to get any new clues.
When we just arrived at Guangming Town, I sent His Majesty a secret message.
If nothing bad happens, we should receive the reply from the capital soon.
You tell me why must the grudges of the past generations
be passed on to us?
Could it be that we must inherit the hatred and grudges?
All of these were not our mistakes to begin with.
It wasn't us who instigated our fathers
to do those things.
Older Bro Bai Ze, say something.
About the matters of our fathers, we aren't fit to make any comments, either.
Anyway, A Ji Ya will never be returning.
I feel that if it was me,
just taking the Star Chart away is just a light punishment.
Since A Ji Ya took the star chart away now,
she even knows how to read it,
so then the person who will gather the Magic Stars next most likely will be A Ji Ya.
I instead feel that this Star Chart is A Ji Ya's greatest source of danger.
Huh? What should we do now?
Should we just continue to wait like this?
Or else, do you have any good idea?
I... Oh...
Let's go.
Go.
KoreanDramaX.co
Black Magic Star.
We are able to get it without wasting any effort.
Oh, my...
What is going on?
He is too heavy.
Hurry and come over here to help out.
Let's go.
Looks like Ding Song and Ma Shun
and his subordinates
have gathered in the Royal Palace.
He is also quite at ease. Playing some empty city strategy here.
He is quite magnanimous.
Right now, since we are already here,
we can't just leave without making some noise.
This way, it would be too kind to that evil Ding Song.
We should leave him some traces of our might.
No.
Why?
This is a rare opportunity.
If we miss this,
it will be hard for us to have another chance like this.
Doing that now is just for a moment of happiness,
but it'll alarm the enemies. The loss outweighs the gain.
And also, His Majesty is still in their hands right now.
We first better think of a way to save His Majesty.
Right. Right. I agree.
Hey!
You really do have such a sturdy body.
Wake up this fast.
Walk on your own!
So many imperial guards.
Looks like we can only use the strategy of besieging Wei to save Zhao.
Let's act separately.
How about this, Ma Da Dao?
Qian Xun and I will cover for you and you just charge into the prison directly.
Let's go.
Who are you?! Who are you?!
Let's go!
Is something happening outside?!
It is probably nothing.
Be at ease.
We should just focus on guarding this place.
Don't mind other things.
We just mainly need to keep watch of these two old men.
Don't let any mishaps occur.
Who?
Your Majesty, could there be something going on outside?
Could it be Ding Song has already found the Magic Star and he is here to get rid of us?
- Who are you?!- What are you planning to do?!
I am here to save you two.
- Who are you?- I am just some measly thief.
Come with me! Come with me!
Hurry, Your Majesty! Your Majesty.
[Ding Residence]
Lord.
Something bad has happened.
Last night, the Royal Palace suddenly caught fire.
A few assassins rescued both His Majesty and Eunuch Cao from the prison during the chaos.
I can't take you with me anymore.
Every time I see you, I remember him.
I really hate myself.
How come I keep remembering him?
A Ji Ya, he is your enemy for your father's death.
He is the descendant of your father's killer!
Can't you have a bit of backbone?!
You can't be soft hearted anymore.
You must forget him.
Why?
Why?!
Don't be like this!
This will cause your wounds to gape open.
Anyway, you have already rescued the Emperor.
Why are you still wasting time to save me?
Don't say words like that.
As for His Majesty, I will plead to him in your behalf
and let him forgive your crimes.
I know that... you were just used by Ding Song.
Qian Meng,
you still care about me.
Let's go.
The medicine most likely has finished brewing.
Go back with me.
His Majesty!
Isn't she the lady boss of Casual Guests' Inn in Yanjiao Town?
How come you're also here?
- I...- What do you mean by 'how come she's also here'?
Last night, if not because of her, Qian Yi Shou and I wouldn't have helped to save you.
You must thank her very well.
Ma Da Dao, don't talk out of place.
We still haven't formally greeted His Majesty.
No need. No need.
What Ma Da Dao said is right.
Right now, you all are my saviors.
Where is Qian Yi Shou?
He is a weird person.
He doesn't want to see Your Majesty no matter what.
Maybe he is worried about Your Majesty blaming him for trying to assassinate you before.
An ignorant person is innocent.
Moreover, last time, I was in disguise.
Why would I blame him?
Hey, Your Majesty, look. The three of us already saved you.
What do you plan to do next?
Of course, it is to eliminate the Ding Song's group,
return to the capital again, and then attend the court to listen to government matters.
Have you finished?
I'm done.
- Did I ask you?- You...
What Eunuch Cao is right.
The most important matter right now is to return to the capital and eliminate Ding Song.
From what I know, when General Su was still alive, you already said that you wanted to eliminate Ding Song.
But this thing never happened.
Now that you have fallen into this state, you don't even have any army,
why is it you still speak so arrogantly?
Ma Da Dao.
Your Majesty, he is just a boor.
- He doesn't know how to speak properly.- Who is a boor?
You must not bother with him.
You say...
Ma Da Dao, go to the kitchen and take a look
if the food for His Majesty is already done.
- Go.- Sure.
He is so not giving His Majesty any respect!
If we were in the palace-
Eunuch Cao,
this is not the palace.
We are on someone else's territory now.
Miss Qian Xun, this time I really have to thank you properly.
Your Majesty, you still have to properly thank one person.
If not for her rushing to get help, we wouldn't have even known something happened to you.
Oh?
KoreanDramaX.co
♫ How long can my friends around me to accompany me? ♫
♫ I’m tired of hearing those comforting words ♫
♫ I’m pulled between courage and collapse repeatedly ♫
♫ I cry out to myself to hang in there ♫
♫ I’m still awake at 3 in the early morning ♫
♫ I can only expect for a good night sleep but not having it ♫
♫ If I’m not careful, I’ll be disturbed once I think about you ♫
♫ Memory has been overturned into a kind of sin ♫
♫ Having loved one very much is wrong but so what ♫
♫ Loneliness is also just a process ♫
♫ We still have next person waiting for us ♫
♫ I’ll remember those wonderful things ♫
♫ Shedding tears isn’t need ♫
♫ Thank you for your choosing ♫
♫ Don’t force myself to give blessing ♫
♫ Be a mature person ♫
♫ Having loved one very much is worth the pain and so happy ♫
♫ I need to learn to let go those I can’t part with ♫
♫ Having loved one very much is wrong but so what ♫
♫ Loneliness is also just a process ♫
♫ We still have next person waiting for us ♫
♫ With a little regret, I’m more complete ♫