KoreanDramaX.co
From what I know, when General Su was still alive,
you already said that you wanted to eliminate Ding Song.
But this thing never happened.
Now that you have fallen into this state,
you don't even have an army.
Why is it you still speak so arrogantly?
Ma Da Dao!
Your Majesty, he is just a boor.
- He doesn't know how to speak properly.- Who is a boor?
You must not bother with him.
Hey, you say. Hey...
Ma Da Dao, go to the kitchen and take a look
if the food for His Majesty is already done.
- Go.- Sure.
He is really not giving His Majesty any respect!
If we were in the palace--
Eunuch Cao,
this isn't the palace.
We are on someone else's territory now.
Miss Qian Xun, this time I really have to thank you properly.
Your Majesty, you still have to properly thank one person.
If not for her rushing to get help, we wouldn't have even known something happened to you.
Oh?
Qian Meng, why are you still here?
His Majesty is back. Won't you be in a hurry to see him?
But... His Majesty didn't call for me, either.
Hurry and just come with me.
Go and see His Majesty now.
Tell him all the hardships you endured
and your daily yearnings for him.
Hey, come.
Come in.
Qian Meng?!
Your Majesty.
It's really you.
I thought I was dreaming.
KoreanDramaX.co
Instead of recuperating well,
why are you peeking while other people are having sweet talks?
I... just passed by.
Why did you come here?
It's time to eat. I'm here to call them to eat.
Move aside.
It's me.
This is not a dream.
I am Qian Meng.
I thought that I would never see you again in my lifetime.
I previously made an oath to Heaven.
Even if there is just a glimmer of hope,
regardless whether I have to go up a mountain full of blades or through a sea of fire,
I must save you.
- If one day... something bad happens to you--- Hey...
Forger it. Just let them finish their talk.
Hey, I know the pain that you are feeling now.
This thing called love...
A melon that's forcefully picked before it's ripe isn't sweet.
Just accept your fate.
Look. Aren't I doing well now?
Qian Meng, these past days, you suffered a lot.
I really don't know how to make it up to you.
How about this, just tell me what you want.
Even if it's the moon in the sky, I'll think of a way to give it to you.
I don't want anything. I just want Your Majesty to be well.
Being just a lowly imperial doctor is already fine with me.
I understand what you mean.
But if I don't thank you well,
I will feel guilty about it.
If Your Majesty will really want to give me a reward, then I beg you to spare one person.
Hey, get up, get up.
This is easy to do.
As long as that person isn't Ding Song.
No matter what crime he committed,
as long as you say it, I will pardon his crimes.
Come in!
He is...
Your Majesty, when you were put under house arrest by Ding Song,
his is the person that Ding Song used evil techniques on to disguise as you.
- May His Majesty spare his crime of treason and deceiving the emperor.-Oh?
♫ I'm sorry that I'm not a doll. ♫
♫ Smiling for a long time will make me tired. ♫
♫ Whatever way I want to think, I think that way. ♫
♫ I'm too lazy to pretend again. ♫
Royal Father, I finally found you all.
I missed you.
I feel so down right now.
Royal Father, please guide me to what path I should take.
Should I just forget these grudges and never again enter the Central Plains?
Do you also hope that I stay by your side forever?
I have fallen in love with Bai Ze.
♫ Do we really love? ♫
No matter how hard I try to forget him,
he won't disappear from my mind.
♫ If it’s just like role play that ♫
♫ you want to have a home then you’ll have a home ♫
I clearly had so many chances
to point my sword towards his throat.
But I can't bear to...
♫ Open a model of full view ♫
I really hate myself so much.
How come I can't do all of these things?
I previously thought that Bai Ze,
Zhang Xiong Fei, and Yuan Shuai were all my friends.
I know that all of these were wrong,
but I kept moving towards them.
Why?
Why must Heaven make fun of me?
I totally can't do anything about it.
I don't know what to do.
♫...that kind of graciousness you want ♫
♫ If I want to cry, I cry ♫
I...
You tell me, what should I do?
You teach me, okay?!
I really am in so much pain...
For you.
♫ Do we really love? ♫
- Bai Ze! - Go!
Bai Ze!
♫ That’d be very happy. ♫
♫ Are there painted eggs at the end? ♫
♫ Who will fight to speak the truth? ♫
♫ Love isn’t like role play ♫
♫ that we could forget because we agree to ♫
♫ like adults ♫
Keep your distance from that thing.
That is the resting place of the ancestors of the Helan tribe.
I am here to pay respect to my parents.
Are you talking about King Salin?
Are you Princess A Ji Ya or Princess Gu Li?
I am A Ji Ya.
You've grown up.
You... know my father?
I knew him for a long time. He is a deceased old friend.
Then how long have you lived here?
I don't remember anymore. Probably 4 to 5 years.
For these past years, I guarded this place although I don't know what I am waiting for.
Initially, I thought that I'm here to wait for the day of my death
and accept my sentence by Heaven. But right now, I understand it.
It was Heaven who arranged it for me to stay here and wait for you.
What do you mean by that?
Who really are you?
I am A Lamusi.
You are the rebel A Lamusi?!
So all of you call me as such...
There was even a time when I was soaking in
the address of King Helan by other people.
When the tribe encountered difficult times, you were holding much power,
yet you didn't immediately come to save us
and instead signed a contract with the Emperor.
Do you know that the downfall of our tribe
is one-half your responsibility?!
I admit to everything that you said.
Today, if you don't explain things clearly, I will kill you!
A Ji Ya, listen to me.
I've long contracted a severe illness long ago and won't live long.
You don't need to rush in killing me.
I just beg you to give me the chance to finish my words.
Afterwards, you can kill me.
Say it.
At that time, the news about your Royal Father
obtained a magic star under Mount Helan
was spreading fast.
Your father was unwilling to hand it over so
he then rejected the officials sent by the Emperor here to receive the Magic Star.
Unexpectedly, the Emperor secretly sent the top Heaven Strategy Envoys
to come here and fight for the Magic Star.
That time, I did my best to negotiate with the Emperor with hope to reach an agreement
because I wanted them to just take the Magic Star away but not harm your father.
Never thought, in the end, it led to such disaster.
I won't believe these vain excuses of yours.
You clearly are just trying to exonerate yourself.
Afterwards, I succeeded to take over the management for the tribe as I had wished and
because the King Helan that people were talking about.
Yet my heart was full of guilt towards your father.
But when he was still alive, I promised him that if ever something bad happened to him,
I would then continue his will
to lead our tribe into great heights
and live a rich, contented, and blissful life.
But I was too stupid.
I never thought that my...
son who got blinded by power would rebel against me and took away my throne.
Right now, he is continuing to call himself King Helan
while I can only be exiled alone.
I initially planned to commit suicide to apologize to Heaven and our tribe's ancestors.
But with the play of fate, I ended up here.
Hence, I just stayed here and kept guarding your father's tomb.
Praying and repenting everyday.
Right now, I beg you to kill me.
Let me to completely be cleaned of my sins in this lifetime.
I won't kill you anymore.
I'm sure that you also are very guilty because of this matter.
You are indeed King Salin's daughter.
Like him, you have a kind heart that's purer than the moon and
a chest that's broader than this meadow's.
Thank you.
No need to thank me.
If you want to thank anyone, thank my Royal Father.
If it was him, he'd forgive you.
I am not thanking you for sparing me.
I just want to say thank you for listening to my words.
Letting my heart be peaceful before I die.
What are you doing?!
Thank you for saving me.
Only by doing this can I clean all of my crimes.
If I knew that my appearance would make you...
No. No. No.
It doesn't have anything to do with you.
You are the one who untangled my heart's knot.
Get up.
A Ji Ya, my child.
I heard earlier the words you said in front of you father's tomb.
If you are willing to hear my advice, I would be very happy.
You say it.
The thing that can resolve hatred and grudges in this world isn't one's fist
but the great love in one's heart.
When you are willing to put down the entanglement in your heart
and try to forgive can you start seeing the wonderfulness of this world.
The past will become the past.
Your future cannot be one that lives in hatred and grudges.
Go follow the love and kindness in your heart.
Go look for your friend.
Just let bygones be bygones.
Starting today, you're a free person.
You don't need to serve anyone else.
If your father were still alive,
I believe that he would also tell you the same thing.
KoreanDramaX.co
Your Majesty, we finally are able to see you again!
Your Majesty, not dying despite such dangerous situations, you surely will be blessed later!
After seeing you, we finally have the courage.
How were you all able to find this place?
Your Majesty, it was Eunuch Cao who sent us the message.
We were afraid that information might be leaked so we traveled out of the city overnight.
Through that, we were able to see you.
Your Majesty, we all deserved to die.
We are so ashamed to meet our ancestors.
In these past days that Your Majesty went missing, we all have said numerous words against our hearts and
did so many things against our will.
May Your Majesty punish us.
Lord He, don't say those kinds of words anymore.
If there is someone who did anything wrong, it was me.
I wasn't able to be a good emperor.
I was too lenient on Ding Song causing you all to get dragged into this.
If there is anyone who should be ashamed to face our ancestors, I should be the top one.
Get up now.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Ma Da Dao, the words you said that day are right.
Right now, I already don't have an army.
If I want to defeat Ding Song, it's really an impossible task.
But I don't believe that Ding Song would really be able to continue this savagery.
Because the people's heart is with ours.
Heaven's justice is with us.
Ma Da Dao, help us until the very end.
I want to borrow the men in your mountain lair.
Once that mob of his loses their leader,
they will surely be like monkeys scattering when the tree falls.
Ma Da Dao, take it as I'm begging you.
I am begging you in behalf of the world's citizens. Is that still not enough?
You already said it that way. If I still don't agree, won't I look like I'm not upholding justice?
All my buddies are with you.
Okay. Ma Da Dao, listen to your conferment.
I am immediately conferring you as General Mighty.
All your mountain lair buddies will also be conferred a status.
Are you still not kneeling down to thank Your Majesty for his grace?
Right. You got conferred to become a general already.
Ma Da Dao, hurry and thank His Majesty.
Okay. Okay. Rise. Rise.
No need.
A hero doesn't stick with these trivial matters. Doesn't stick with these trivial matters.
Come. Let me go first.
I want to congratulate my buddy, Ma Da Dao, being conferred by the Emperor to become a general.
It's something to be happy about.
Come. Congratulations, Ma Da Dao.
Hey, Ma Da Dao, why aren't you drinking?
This wine is especially to congratulate you for becoming a general.
Come. For this second cup, Qian Xun, let me give you a toast.
During these days that I met you, I was very happy.
For the third cup, I still have to toast it to you two.
Just treat it as a farewell wine.
Because... I will soon... be leaving.
What? You are leaving?
Did you get some news about the Magic Stars?
It has nothing to do with the Magic Stars.
I have to go back to see my teacher.
I actually already planned to leave at the time that you came here.
I already got delayed for several days.
We've been together for so long but how come I didn't know that you still have a teacher?
I already haven't seen him for several years.
But unless it's a very emergent reason, he usually won't come to find me.
And also, in passing, I still have to go to the capital
to finish my matter with Ding Song.
What is there to finish with him?
Each matter must be dealt with separately.
I have my working principles.
Qian Xun? Not talking?
Don't you want to know when he will be coming back? Who his teacher is?
I won't ask anything.
I know... that even if I ask, he won't tell.
I also want to tell you.
But there are some things that have no answers at all.
All the things that I want to say are all in this wine now.
Treat it as me thanking you two.
- Come. Hurry. - Hurry.
- Come.- Sure.
Here.
The ones whose names were crossed out in this list
were those that publicly showed their support for Ding Song.
Even those that are with circles, aren't also 100% dependable.
We still need to carefully consider it.
It was all because of me not doing my job very well.
Your Majesty, how can you say such things about yourself?
Eunuch Cao, look at how many names are in this list.
They all have lost the ideal beliefs.
It's fine whoever will sit on that throne in the Grand Hall.
As long as he can guarantee them a life of wealth and glory,
isn't that my responsibility?
Your Majesty, you were the one who promoted this ministers.
Most of them are just grass that sway with the wind.
Some are people from the wild grass type and it's hard for them to be loyal.
Eunuch Cao, what really do you want to say?
I feel that Ma Da Dao
is still a bandit to begin with.
Giving the huge task of eliminating Ding Song to a person like him now,
isn't it a little bit risky?
And also, his attitude has always been arrogant.
Eunuch Cao, you are just worrying too much.
Ma Da Dao is my life savior. I, of course, believe him.
Eunuch Cao, for this matter, I feel that what Your Majesty said is right.
Although Ma Da Dao is a boor, he's usually careless but quite sharp at times.
He's a person with affection and faith.
I feel that he totally can be trusted.
Oh, right, Eunuch Cao.
I had been locked up for a long time and lost communication with Bai Ze and the others for so long.
Do you have a way to contact them?
We only have one last messenger pigeon.
Good thing that Lord He has brought it to us.
That's great. I'll immediately write a message to them.
[Ding Residence]
- Check the back. - Search!
- Yes. - Yes.
Stop searching now.
I already searched each and every corner of this place.
Right now, there is not a single person here in Ding Song's residence.
Then based on what you just said, other than us, there is no one else here, right?
Buddies, we are rich now.
Do you want treasures?
Then you might get disappointed.
You all came a step late.
Ding Song has already secretly transported all his treasured belongings out of the city.
And also, he and Ma Shun are missing.
- There really is nothing left.- That's right.
Even here is all cleared, too.
Ding Song, this old fox, is really sly enough.
There was originally a Magic Star here. Ding Song took it away.
How many Magic Stars are there exactly?
Ma Da Dao, you are back just in time.
Come over and take a look.
Look at the words I wrote for you.
How was it? "Loyal Hero."
Ma Da Dao, you must not decline it.
These words, Loyal Hero, is so suitable for you.
Oh, right. What do you plan to do in the future?
Do you plan to stay here and guard this place or go back with me to the capital? You decide.
But I still haven't accomplished my task.
Ding Song and Ma Shun currently are missing.
I know. Qian Xun already told me about it.
This is called an evil person having a guilty conscience.
He knew that you saved me.
He understands that his power will soon be gone so he ran away.
I am sure that right now, he really can't cause any trouble.
Don't talk about him anymore.
You better take a look at these words now.
If you don't like it, I'll write you another one.
You tell me and I'll write it.
What you are saying is true, right?
A king never lies. Come on.
I'll say it then.
During the spring of the 31st year of Mingyang,
the second royal son, Zhi Min, suddenly died.
How did you know about this?
What I know isn't just this.
I know there's an eagle shaped birthmark on your right shoulder, too.
Who are you?
I think that you already know who I am, right?
I initially thought that you didn't know the disgusting things that your father did to my father,
so you were able to stably sit on your throne.
Based on your reaction earlier, I think that you know more than I do.
Am I right? Huh?!
Ma Da Dao, I don't know what you are talking about.
When you leave this door, you are still a meritorious officer, a hero.
You will be able to live a rich life for the rest of your life.
If I wanted those things that you are saying,
I wouldn't have been saying so many words with you earlier.
Don't you know that?
Okay. I understand now.
You also said that you want to strive for vindication.
But nothing can be proven just by a birthmark.
Don't rush.
Wait for me to return to the palace and check the files to confirm.
If it is true, I will surely give you justice.
I'll be waiting for the good news then.
His Majesty has sent a message!
Hurry and read it. What did my older bro say?
Bai Ze, Zi Su, no matter where you two are now, immediately return to the palace.
There is an urgent matter that I must tell you two.
- His Majesty is asking us to return to the Palace?- Right.
His Majesty seems to be rushing us so he surely has some important matters to tell us.
I... won't go back.
If I go back, he won't let me go out again.
We haven't found the Magic Stars.
We'll be meeting for the first time.
It isn't good to be empty handed, is it?
Older Bro Fei, are you going to see your brother-in-law?
It's the Emperor.
What does he lack?
Zi Su, don't worry.
If your older bro won't let you come out afterwards, I will then go and steal you out.
Hey. What really are you two thinking about?
It's not like I'm asking you two to go back for a blind date or meet your father-in-law.
Since His Majesty is calling for us, we then must immediately set out.
Hurry and pack up your things.
Let's leave immediately.
Lord, when did you arrange for all of these things?
Even I don't know.
When His Majesty got saved by someone, I already predicted that something bad would happen.
That's why I already made preparations.
Maybe at this moment, someone is searching our house.
Lord, you really are a prophet.
Do you know what this is called?
- Preparing for the rainy days. Courage--- Enough already.
What time is it already and you are still trying to suck up.
You all leave now.
Yes.
Eat. Eat.
Eunuch Cao,
the Emperor will be leaving for the capital this afternoon.
There are so many things needing your attention now.
You tell me, you aren't helping him but instead accompanying a bandit like me to drink some wine.
You're being too courteous.
As the saying goes, 'Everything in life is cyclical.'
Right now, you aren't a bandit anymore.
You are the government's General Mighty.
If I still wait to treat you once you return to the capital,
I might have to wait for three days and three nights.
I just take the initiative to gain the upper hand.
I'm not interested in this General Mighty position.
That's right, too.
Just a measly Commanding General,
for a person with a status like you,
it indeed is nothing.
Did he tell you something?
His Majesty didn't tell me anything.
I was thinking about myself.
From the time I entered the palace... so many years have passed.
I accompanied His Majesty in braving through wind and rain.
I already saw a lot of different kinds of things.
But someone like you who claims to be of royal blood upon the first meeting,
it is really the first time.
I don't intend to make connections. I just want justice.
Let me give you some advice.
There are some things that even if they are true,
it is still better to just keep them a secret.
So many years have passed.
What do you want His Majesty to do?
Recognize a cousin like you who just fell from the sky?
How will people look at the royal family then?
Don't you think that there aren't enough troubles now?
What really do you mean?
I... I don't mean anything.
Is this some sort of Hongmen Banquet*?(* a dinner where treachery was planned)
Why are you still here?
Qian Meng, you go first.
What are you doing?!
Don't hurt other people.
Ma Da Dao, let's go.
Chase after them!
Stop there! Stop running!
Stop running!
Stop there! Go after them!
Your Majesty, it's getting late.
Let's set off.
Go take a look where Ma Da Dao and Qian Qun went.
They clearly know that I'm leaving.
Why aren't they here to bid me farewell?
They don't observe formalities.
Just ignore them.
We'll just take our leave.
This won't do. Go and find them now.
I want to wait for them.
Your Majesty!
Something bad has happened.
Get up now. Tell me about it.
Your Majesty, save Ma Da Dao now.
Eunuch Cao wants to kill him.
Eunuch Cao, what's going on?
I... I...
Qian Xun, I should thank you.
If not, I would have lost my head.
Ma Da Dao, what grudges do you have with Eunuch Cao?
Why is he suddenly trying to kill you?
I don't have any grudges with him.
He is only carrying out a task for his master.
Are you referring to His Majesty?
You just saved His Majesty.
Moreover, you help him to close down Ding Song's residence.
He even trusted you and conferred you as a general.
This only happened recently
and he's going to kill you, right?
You can't totally blame him for this.
Blame me for being too naive instead.
I told him my identity.
I thought he would take our blood relationship into account.
In the end, his desire for power was greater than anything else.
There is a rumor. You may have heard about it.
It's said that the previous King had a twin brother.
He died a violent death when he was young.
He left a child behind.
When the mother of that child went missing,
no one knew where that child went to, either.
Have you heard about this?
Are you talking about...
you...
You don't believe it, right?
I guessed that you wouldn't believe it.
The rest doesn't believe it, either.
They think I'm a greedy person
who would make up any story for money and glory.
Hence, I didn't even tell Qian Yi Shou about this.
I finally understand now,
the reason you hesitated when I asked you to save His Majesty.
And also the meaning behind what you said.
It's pointless for you to understand.
What can we change?
I only hope that he can keep his words,
correct his mistakes
and let the people live a good life.
What do you plan to do from now on?
What else can I plan?
I'm going to find a safe place.
Qian Yun, let me tell you this.
Qian Yi Shou is not a bad person.
Fend for yourself.
No matter where he goes, he will come back and find you.
Keep yourself for him.
You really have guts.
You even dare to hurt General Mighty whom I conferred.
Do you know your mistake?
I think I didn't do anything wrong.
Everything I did was for Your Majesty.
How dare you? Men!
Give him twenty strokes of the paddles.
Eunuch Cao has always been loyal to you.
He was with you during your most difficult moments.
Even if it's for old time's sake, you can't do this to him, either.
Your Majesty, be lenient.
Eunuch Cao is too old to withstand the twenty strokes of beating.
Fine. Everyone is pleading on your behalf
and also that you have always been loyal to me.
I will spare you this time.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Thank you, Your Majesty, for your kindness.
This is bad. Looks like Ma Da Dao made a mistake about His Majesty.
So this is His Majesty, right?
He looks just like an ordinary person with nothing special.
Don't talk nonsense.
Be careful that he keeps you staying here as a eunuch.
Bai Ze, are the two next to you the descendents of the Heaven Strategy envoys?
Your Majesty, you are right.
This is Uncle Zhan Ke's son, Zhan Xiong Fei.
This is Uncle Yan Sang Lan's son, Yuan Shuai.
We risked our lives together to turn our misfortunes into blessings.
We are good friends now.
You are truly young heroes.
Miss Qian Yun has already told me about the both of you.
By the way, my younger sister didn't give you any troubles on the way here, right?
Older bro, how could you be so shortsighted always?
Not only did I not give them any troubles on the way here, I even helped them.
Your Majesty...
Princess Zi Su did help us a lot on the way.
She even saved us a few times.
Looks like she has definitely improved over time.
Fine, I will take back what I just said.
This is more like it.
It's just... that we have gotten the Magic Star from the Illuminati,
but it was taken away by Ma Shun eventually.
We have disappointed Your Majesty.
Lord Ding is a cunning devil.
Don't even talk about you, I also fell into his hands.
Fortunately, friends from Yanjiao Town helped me to escape.
I also just heard that Thirteenth Older Sis joined forces with Ma Da Dao to save Your Majesty.
This is really surprising.
This could be a blessing and protection from God.
Ding Song still hasn't been caught yet.
We must not lose our guard.
You are right.
Thus, I have issued an Imperial order to the palace guards to be extra vigilant and to be on strong defense.
There is something else.
Since you've inherited the burden of the Magic Star search from your fathers,
you should have a title.
Thus, I have decided to reinstate your title of Heaven Strategy envoy.
Of course, this can only be a secret now.
Once all the Magic Stars are collected, I'll announce to everyone.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.- Thank you, Your Majesty.
Rise.
When I was imprisoned by Ding Song, the one who I missed most was you.
I remember when you first ran into the palace, you were only seven years old.
Yes, I remember.
At that time, Royal Father punished Nanny Tang who had been taking care of me.
At that time, I liked to feed and rear crows,
but Royal Father felt that it was unlucky to rear crows in the palace.
He didn't want me to rear them.
I secretly let Nanny Tang rear them in the Imperial Garden.
In the end, they were still discovered by him.
Hence, he kicked Nanny Tang out.
Subsequently, you were angry with Royal Father
and ran out of the palace alone.
I wonder how Nanny Tang is doing now.
She took care of me since I was young.
In this palace, other than you and Older Brother Bai Ze,
she was my closest family member.
Let's not talk about this anymore.
When Royal Father was alive, he was especially strict with us.
He also did that out of good intentions.
Who told us to be born into a royal family.
Older bro,
if you could be an ordinary man now,
but you can live happily forever, would you be willing?
KoreanDramaX.co
♫ How long can my friends around me to accompany me? ♫
♫ I’m tired of hearing those comforting words ♫
♫ I’m pulled between courage and collapse repeatedly ♫
♫ I cry out to myself to hang in there ♫
♫ I’m still awake at 3 in the early morning ♫
♫ I can only expect for a good night sleep but not having it ♫
♫ If I’m not careful, I’ll be disturbed once I think about you ♫
♫ Memory has been overturned into a kind of sin ♫
♫ Having loved one very much is wrong but so what ♫
♫ Loneliness is also just a process ♫
♫ We still have next person waiting for us ♫
♫ I’ll remember those wonderful things ♫
♫ Shedding tears isn’t need ♫
♫ Thank you for your choosing ♫
♫ Don’t force myself to give blessing ♫
♫ Be a mature person ♫
♫ Having loved one very much is worth the pain and so happy ♫
♫ I need to learn to let go those I can’t part with ♫
♫ Having loved one very much is wrong but so what ♫
♫ Loneliness is also just a process ♫
♫ We still have next person waiting for us ♫
♫ With a little regret, I’m more complete ♫