I really couldn't even have imagined that
it would end up like this. Really!
Then, what are we going to do now?
- As it has come to this, let's quickly finish off now.
- Stop the "shofunow" kind Japanese!
Stop the "Shofuno" kind Japanese!
That's just great! Since it's come to this,
let's do the merger fast.
Haven't you heard anything on CEO No?
I haven't.
I'll have to use this status disclosure request
this morning, and find out what is up.
That's it. Let's do a cheer. Come on.
With me.
1, 2, 3... Yeah!
There is plenty of work, but
nothing suits me, I guess.
Where are you going?
I need to look around for some work.
Whereabout...
It's just here and there...
Don't I need to at least make a try?
We can't even handle living expenses.
Yeah... It must be hard, I see.
It's hard, but I have no choice.
It's almost time for the bus.
I just can't miss that bus.
Is that so? Why didn't you say that earlier?
- Oh, it's no problem...
- I kept jabbering on. Hurry up and go... Let's go.
Making fools of people...
- Sister-in-law.
- Yes.
Fighting, it is!
It's because they hear all these
odd rumors about CEO No.
I know it's all nonsense but...
him to have become a vegetable...
to have died...
to have gone coocoo...
and to have supposedly had a...
sex change surgery...
What are you doing, hearing all
this babbling nonsense?
That's just what I would say too!
All these rumor monger fellows should be
pronto arrested and...
we should flat-out slap them
with libel lawsuits, really!
This won't work... I should immediately go to
the legal counsels, and sue the pants off them!
Hey, hey, hey, hey... It's fine. It's fine.
Anyway, about CEO No, really...
There's no particular problem, right?
Only if I know precisely about the CEO's condition
can I decide on something... or do nothing on it...
Didn't I tell you already?
that he's currently convalescing after the surgery.
Then, how about him being seen once
publicly in the company itself?
At the company?
I mean, well, if that disclosure is also seen,
that will help the staff spirit too.
Even all these odd rumors...
One look at CEO's bright face, and
just like that they'll all be rejected.
If it is all right to do, there is
no reason not to do it, right?
Understood.
I will try to discuss it with Min Hyeok.
Say what? Suddenly you will quit working?
Why?
I'm sorry.
I mean, you're perfectly fine cleaning the
anchovy guts, but what's this suddenly?
Is it this anchovy guts
the reason for quitting?
No. That is not it.
As I was thinking about quitting work,
I just happened to be cleaning anchovy guts.
You mean that is not it?
What is the reason?
My divorced husband keeps asking to
remarry and it bothers me.
In this world with 2 moons in the sky,
who knows when I'll die...
Cleaning anchovy guts in other people's house.
Is that all I would do, I wondered.
So I was right! About you quitting
because of anchovy guts.
If that is how you take it, I can't help it.
Anchovy guts is only the symptom
but not the cause.
No Min Hyeok... Clearly something is up with him.
If only I know his location, I will just...
What is it again with that
scary, rolled-up-eye look?
What about his location?
Again into 'eliminating'?
We have no time left, now!
Director. Isn't there this poison blow-needle...
that's blown like this?
Using that, anyone can be handled in a blink.
Ah, enough!
What kind of woman are you, being so
murderous the moment you talk?
You, really!
I was badly worried yesterday.
So I put all the possible situations in order.
Only No Min Hyeok's body is abnormal.
He is only mentally abnormal.
Everything is abnormal.
He's unaware of the USB's existence.
He's unaware only of the USB's contents.
He knows of both its existence and contents.
Ah, stop at that. Stop it!
You writing a thesis? What's the conclusion?
Say the damn conclusion.
As conclusion, there are 24 possibilities.
As only 3 scenarios among those are safe for us,
for the time being, we can monitor what happens.
Ah, enough!
There isn't even a bullshit conclusion.
After going on for so long...
Min Hyeok might somehow have to
make a trip to the company, it seems.
In that state, how can Min Hyeok go anywhere?
Still it's been so long since the accident.
As he has not shown up and
there are strange rumors,
even a disclosure request has come in.
We should just ask Dr. Min about
how long he has to stay and play
in the hospital without returning.
Let's eat, I'm hungry.
Call for a delivery. No ajumma anymore.
Why?
That ajumma, damn... Shouldn't she work
at least till somebody else is found?
How heartless must you have been, for her to
leave like that without even looking back?
I was wondering why you hadn't said it yet!
For you, whatever the issue is,
it's all my doing, right?
Was there nothing to what I said?
It's because you are so mean to others--
Hey, hey, father, just eat this... aigoo...
- Oh, so hot!
- Aigoo... Was it so hot?
Is it so hot? You eat one and see!
If it's scalding, just spit it out.
Spit it out, dad! Why do that?
So hot!
Oh, so hot.
Now do you see?
The tongue is all scalded.
Scalded, right?
Can't say... but it does look a bit red.
Then, till we find an Ajumma,
we'll only be having takeaways?
Yeaaa... Dat's Yight! Dat will do!
What?
This morning, I saw the garage
sister-in-law looking for work.
Anyway, it is quite like we are
already living together.
Having her handle the work in our home
will work out, right?
Then she's happy to find work, and
we're happy to find our person.
Both would be happy, right?
Are you crazy? No way.
Why?
How can we ask people
we know to do the work?
Also, it's housekeeping...
Anybody can do it, you think?
To do housework for a large house like ours
is a normal task, you think?
Is that so?
I feel it will be all right.
That's right. Somebody we know
helping out, is only nice, isn't it?
Isn't that right?
What do you all think?
I've no problem with anything.
As long as there is hot food.
But, is she good at cooking?
She is good. Quite tasty.
See? They all say they like it!
As I see it, without a job, they don't
even have sustenance money.
So just take it as doing a good deed,
and let's try having her take over.
Housemaid?
Yes.
Sister-in-law, you also stop taking
all the trouble to find other jobs.
Working at our home
will be convenient too.
That's of course true, but the wages...
What I know is that it's 2 million Wons a month.
(~US$ 1800)
2 million...
As the work specifications are good,
I can find somebody right away anytime.
But it's you that I recommended for it.
I want to help you however I can.
Oh, what to do? I know I'm quite clean and
efficient at managing my house.
But I have never done
this type of work before.
Then just do as you normally do.
Then I will go, taking it that
you have agreed to do it.
So enjoy your meals.
Are you really going to do it?
Then I must do it. Isn't it 2 million Wons?
(~US$ 1800)
I don't feel too good about it.
Can we afford to be picky about this and that?
We'll be struggling badly in no time.
I have organized here the things you need to do,
so please refer to it.
As the situation has come to this,
I have to ask for your help.
Don't worry. Though I look like this, in my life
I have been quite efficient in house duties--
I think you'll have to start right away.
First do a vacuum cleaning.
Once it's done, grab the bedsheets for a wash,
and clean out the fridge once too.
You can finish before noon, right?
Ah, well, yes...
If you are ready, we should leave.
Sister-in-law.
Yes.
Why did you say 'fighting'? If anyone sees,
it's like something special is going on.
Ah, come on, you...
It's no big deal.
You are happy now?
The homeless ones get a place to sleep.
The jobless with no money gets a job.
To them, you must be like Jesus.
I won't go as far as Jesus...
But then again...
Then, you are saying it's okay to get discharged?
As I had explained, there's nothing
abnormal with the brain.
The problem lies with the missing memories.
Going back to those daily life conditions,
and getting timely treatment here,
would in fact be better than being here, right?
I see. Then, his memories...
When do you think they will return?
As the memory is like a thread ball,
if we just find where it starts,
there can be a quick recovery, as in many cases.
That means, when he's at home,
just as per our instructions,
please keep repeating the
brain stimulation exercises.
If you talk a lot with him, it can only help
us find the thread head, right?
No Min Hyeok is in which hospital, you said?
Sujieub Jeongmo hospital, 902?
I got it.
How is CEO No's condition?
It's a VIP patient room, so it's
impossible to get close to?
Fine, I see.
Good job!
So we know the hospital?
Then right away eliminate him.
That's it... Again it's elimination?
Quit it. That talk.
I mean, isn't it a bit urgent for us?
We do know that...
Piss off, man...
I said stop it!
Quickly check if there are people
we know at the Jeongmo hospital.
The USB can be in the washing machine
or its vicinity, from laundry time, right?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Give it to me.
No need. No need.
Let me know anytime if you need my help.
Sure, thank you.
Miraculous, however one looks at it.
How can one's fate change like that
just as easily as turning one's palm?
My fate remains the same,
all 4 seasons, all year round.
Then come home soon tonight as well.
Wee need to discuss some Min Hyeok matters.
Fine then.
Sister-in-law, how is it?
Quite a lot of things to do?
Well, as the house is quite big,
the chores are not trivial.
Take some rest too.
Cleaning rag! Cleaning rag!
Quick, quick, quick!
Hurry, bring the damn rag, ajumma!
We must quickly wipe!
Hurry up. Hurry!
- Yes, sure...
- Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry!
- Detergent! Detergent!
- What?
Kitchen detergent... Detergent!
I'm going insane! Ah, really...
Make it fast. Make it fast.
What are you doing? Bring it quickly. Quick!
Is it stained?
Will it be fine?
What do you think? Does it look worn out?
It doesn't really look worn out.
Is that so?
Sorry, Sister-in-law.
Carry on with your work then.
Lost 10 years of my life!
Sister-in-law.
Take some rest as you work.
Ajumma?
(ajumma - older lady, maid)
Yes, he called me ajumma!
Must be a slip of the tongue.
Must be a habit from calling
the earlier maid 'ajumma'.
What slip of the tongue?
People's true colors come out under stress.
That's the only way I will take it.
Only impolite speaking came out. And then I had
fallen down, but still he was throwing temper.
Forget it. Stop talking, it's enough.
It was just a sofa that was getting a stain.
Had others seen it, they'd think
the house was on fire!
A little stain, and he says he lost 10 years of life.
A real miser. In my whole life I haven't seen
such a miser, really!
I've reached. I need to get down. Hanging up.
Hongberg!
What's up?
May be you were waiting for me?
No.
No? Then what are you doing here?
Watching buses.
Hey, now that you are a rich kid,
shouldn't you get rid of this "no no" syndrome?
Give it.
Oh ho? May be then you wanted to carry my bag?
No. Suddenly I wanted to
carry a bag like this once.
Is that so? Can't do anything if your
"no no" syndrome is incurable.
Anyway, thank you.
Won't they think that it's strange?
When nobody can tell anything as they see him,
if Min Hyeok doesn't get back to work,
won't they think it's strange?
When they see no problems.
That's nothing... We can just say that
he's still recuperating and all that.
For that, isn't he is looking a bit too perfectly fine?
Then say it's only looking so, but he isn't fine.
Just saying he isn't fine won't do, you know.
Though he looks quite fine,
there's something that stops him from working.
One look, and it should be clear.
That's how we should make it.
Then just put on a cast, won't that do?
Oh... That will work, I think!
Wow, sister-in-law, you have good sense!
Brother-in-law, some reward money please.
A cast isn't bad. It's clear from just looking.
Correct. If he must go, let's do it that way.
That way, we can buy some time.
Where should the cast be?
Neck? Arm? Leg?
Isn't arm better? I feel it is more comfortable.
Do it on the neck, I guess.
Ot the neck, won't it look a bit too serious?
That's why it's better on an arm.
The arm would look not serious-enough.
A wheelchair would be good, no?
He'll look rich.
Let's ask Min Hyeok once too.
Why ask him about such a thing?
The affected person has opinions too!
Min Hyeok, if it's neck, arm or leg for a cast...
where would you want it to be?
What is a cast?
Can't I wear it all over?
Only one?
Then, leg?
Not sleeping?
I need to just wrap this up.
They never pay money and yet
use people to death or what?
My arms, legs, all the limbs....
You were working hard!
What kind of house is it, like a playground?
If people slip and fall, one needs a
cart to take them out.
Especially the living room.
You can play even football there!
Exaggeration!
Then, putting a leg cast is what it is.
Hey, don't play football at night.
Seeing you totally tired, mom,
you'll snore loudly tonight.
What do you mean? I don't snore or anything.
-=The CEO=-
Ms. Na Jin A.
I return home tomorrow.
Really?
Wow, that's so nice.
I will go to the company too. When I come there,
Na Jin A, I can see you too.
Yes.
Right. Also, I'll be on crutches.
Why crutches? Are you hurt?
Yes. Badly.
Really? How did you get hurt?
I'm joking. It will be fake.
Huh? Why?
I don't know. It seems I must do it.
So late at night, but not asleep?
Yes. As I think of going home tomorrow,
sleep just won't come.
I keep watching Superboard.
Ms. Jin A, do you also like NarARa Superboard?
No. I have never seen it.
Oh... I do know the song.
Chiki chiki chaka chaka chuku chuku cho.
Isn't that right?
The tooth-brushing dance.
That's correct.
Chiki chiki chaka chaka chuku chuku cho
If you ever do bad things...
Do what, you said?
Hurts-bad things?
Doing just "bad" things.
Bad things?
Chiki chiki chaka chaka chuku chuku cho.
You will get exposed by us.
Na Jin A, you know no more than chiki chaka?
Yes. When you come to the company,
sing it again for me, for me to learn.
I will then do chiki chiki chaka chaka for you.
Okay.
When we say "exposed by us", what are we?
Oh... That is... What it is...
If you ask who we are...
For that I will have to tell you the
whole story from the beginning.
At the start, the Tripitaka buddhist monks found
the Son O Gong monkey king stuck under a rock.
Initially the evil spirits who defeated Son O Gong
were sealed inside Princess I Sa's bracelet.
Why, ask ask? Because Princess I Sa is
the Jade Emperor's daughter.
To not get sucked into a space-time tunnel...
When Tripitaka monk was kidnapped, Pigsy and
Monk Sha went to Flame Mountain to save him.
With a cracking sound, the 7 hoodlums
of the universe appeared!
Sister-in-law. Sister-in-law.
Did you call me?
Good, you're here.
Yes, what is...?
Nothing much else... but as I was eating peanuts,
one fell under the bed.
I want to get it out, but my arm isn't reaching it.
Just 1 more centimeter would've been enough.
Just leave it, please.
Later when I clean, I can take it out.
If it's not done now itself, it'll keep bugging me.
I would be nice to get it out before you go out.
Then, shall I look for a long rod or something?
No, as the peanut is round and rolls... All we need
to do is to... blow on it with your mouth, it seems.
Huh?
My lung capacity is too poor, which is why.
As long as you blow "phoo" from there,
I think it will roll 1 centimeter this way.
Then I shall... take it out.
It's moving, it's moving, it's moving!
Just a bit more. Just once more.
Blow with some force.
Snatched it!
Ok!
You did great there!
Are you all right?
I exerted too much to blow air. Got a bit dizzy.
Please throw it away for me, sister-in-law.
This fellow. Damn I'll just...
Why do you look at me like that?
It's nothing.
You aren't ready to go to the hospital?
I have to get ready.
Early morning, why are you staring at
each other with such loving-like look?
What loving-like look?
She looked at me like this. So I also...
Why would she look like that?
But then, to those folks you are a Jesus.
Of course she will look up to you.
Look at you, really...
Receiving respect from somebody
is not anything bad, right?
Keep your senses to behave right and
not let it go to a romance or anything.
In her eyes, you have charisma, good looks,
money and a good voice too.
As a target of crush for her, a perfect fit, it is!
What?
If this continues, really...
she might fall for me, no?
The poor woman...
I'll go down first and be waiting.
Fine.
Even if it's uncomfortable, hold on
for a few hours. Understand?
Aigoo, such a perfectly fine fellow
being like a half-wit--
Father-in-law!
What?
It's because I'm sad that I say it...
Hold the crutches and try to walk.
The foot is wrong. You hurt your right foot.
How can the right foot be walking?
Use the other foot to walk.
But I never hurt my right foot.
What I mean is, aren't we playing the game of
pretend-injury? Try it once more.
Give it to me. Give it to me.
Look closely at this grandpa.
Like this. Like this. Like this.
- Left leg.
- What's so hard?
Oh, I get it.
Left leg. Use the left leg.
Left leg. Left leg. Left leg.
At the company, say just 3 things when you
see others, we asked. You remember it?
Long time no see.
I'm glad to see you.
Soon I'll be coming back.
There you go. Say just these 3 sentences, okay?
I got it. But why say only these 3 things?
Because the company folks think
you turned into an idiot--
Father-in-law!
What?
It's because I am sad that I say it...
Fine, then. Let's go.
Correct. Left leg.
What?
No Min Hyeok is heading to the
company now, you mean?
Aigoo, CEO sir, really, long time no see.
Long time no see.
I'm glad to see you.
Aigoo! How worried we were!
Seeing you so safe and sound... It's a real relief.
Soon, I'll be coming back.
Pardon?
Let's go in quickly. We don't have much time.
- Hello.
Long time no see. I'm glad to see you.
Soon I will be coming back.
- Dad. Ms. Na Jin A...
- Left leg. Left leg.
Left leg should be on the ground.
Left leg. Left leg.
Ms. Na Jin A. Take that CF file
to the design office for me.
Yes.
Where did the plan on the character roles go?
Hmm? What for?
The CEO is back. We should
quickly get his signature.
The CEO is here?
Yes.
The stacked up files are all now signed.
That's all for today.
Crutches.
Having come after a long time, there's lots to
report to you. May be a brief meeting might...
Do it the next time. Next time.
That's right.
Looks like he hasn't seen the USB.
You think so too?
If he saw it, he can't be just
leaving like this, right?
Quick, let's get inside.
It's Ms. Na Jin A.
CEO sir, are you leaving so soon?
Please say something before you go.
Yes, please give us a speech.
Well... Today he's a bit busy.
He'll do it formally next time.
If you ever do bad things...
You will be exposed by us.
So, then...
This does it. This does. Don't I tell you
only 3 cases were safe?
Finished. All finished.
We are finished, I tell you!
This is simply declaring a war.
You sure that it was directed at us?
Looking right at you, director, with a smile...
"You will be exposed by us".
He did it and my hairs stood up!
Saw the smile and they stood up more!
Let me just understand the situation.
For now, you just stay put.
There's no way this will do.
If we rely on just the Director,
we are in deep shit.
What do you want to do?
I know how to handle this.
You just help me.
Is somebody living here?
Oh, a company staff called Na Jin A.
Ms. Na Jin A?
Didn't she run an errand to you at the hospital?
Why is Na Jin A living here?
They have a situation.
Let's go in fast. They are all waiting for you.
Come on, let's eat.
I can't believe such a day would come.
A day when Min Hyeok and Jun Hyeok are
in this home for us to have a meal together.
Come on grandfather. Why are you crying
on such a good day?
She's right. Now we'll be together many times.
But, why is Na Jin A living over there,
in the garage?
Didn't I tell you... that they have a situation.
What does a 'situation' mean?
Why do you keep wanting to know this?
She's into cars, you know. Cars.
So, it's to sleep with cars that she lives there.
This fellow has now turned us into freaks.
Oh, that's why she lives there?
Yeah, I knew that would be it.
Na Jin A by herself?
No, she lives with her mother.
Mom? Na Jin A has a mom too?
Yes. She has one. It's me.
I am Na Jin A's mom.
You, ajumma?
But Na Jin A is so cute looking...
Hell, what's this now?
I have to tell you this squarely.
I'm helping you, but it absolutely doesn't mean
that I second your views, okay?
Just so you're sure, I'm making it clear to you.
Get the rope properly fixed.
Hardly a thought, in shooting poison?
Where in the world did you learn this from?
Heck, there's tuition class on this too?
During college days, I stayed a while
in South Africa.
Then I learned it just in case I needed it.
Why had you gone to South Africa?
Charity work.
You went all the way for charity work
and learned to shoot poison needles?
Why you are so bull-headed,
I really have no idea!
1102.
1002.
902.
This is it.
Where did he go?
Went to the bathroom?
Oh, so cold.
Has everyone left?
I guess...
How come the car can't exit?
Isn't the garage entrance narrow?
Min Hyeok and Jun Hyeok have already slept?
Min Hyeok oppa wanted to sleep together.
He took Jun Hyeok up to his room.
Really? Rascals...
What cookies are these?
Oliooli.
Quite tasty.
Is there anything that you need?
No. Finished your work?
Yes.
Then, let me get going now.
Then, take some of this with you.
What is this?
It's American cookies.
Go and please eat it, sharing with Jin A.
American cookies?
I thought Jin A may have never seen
anything like American cookies.
Take it back and eat together.
Damn, I want to just...
But then, to those folks you are a Jesus.
In her eyes, you have charisma, good looks,
money and a good voice too.
As a target of crush for her, a perfect fit, it is!
Shall we see one more episode?
No, we'll watch just that much today.
Has Na Jin A returned?
Why is Na Jin A sleeping in the garage?
Really because she likes cars?
Who knows?
Right. Where had you gone?
Grandpa had said it. That you went somewhere
for a long time and came back.
Where had you gone?
It was just... here and there.
Will you leave again?
You won't, right?
Mmm.
It's cold.
What are you doing? Not there?
Why is he not coming back?
It's-s-s-s-s... cold.
Give them some more?
Truly three-faced!
Dead face, hateful face, irritating face.
Stop it, please!
That face is like a flat-screen TV,
too flat and wide.
The things he does. Oh, what a scrooge!
Saying it's American cookies, he gives 4 pieces!
We are what, beggars?
It's not like it's the 80's.
American cookies... how ridiculous is that?
Supermarts are full of American cookies.
He knows nothing of the world, nor sensitivity.
This morning when I was blowing the peanut
I nearly gave him a slap.
Mrs. Gil Seon Ja. You better stop it. Understand?
Really, it's just the 2 million Wons wages.
Just for that money, I have to take this!
- Who is it?
- Who is it there?
Truly three-faced!
Dead face, hateful face, irritating face.
What is this?
Why me? What wrong have I done?
To those folks... you are what, a Jesus, right?
Right. Though I'm not sure
I'll take it as far as Jesus...
I was always very kind and
gentle towards them.
These looks and this smile.
No matter how hard I think, me being taken
this way... is hard to believe for me.
Where did it start going wrong?
American cookies?
Peanut?
Where did I start going wrong?
Great job guys, great job! You won't listen to me
and are off doing what you want, really?
If he was discharged, why didn't you
tell us quickly?
I also came to know only now.
Anyway what is with this outfit?
How can you go to the bathroom?
Unable to go, to the bathroom.
And this outfit is too conspicuous.
Was this meant to camouflage?
The color, look at this color.
How can the gloss be so extreme?
Gloss is the essence of this costume!
They don't come out in dull texture.
hey, where did you get this costume from?
Stationery store?
A complete set with the poison needles?
-=Next Episode Preview=-
How about going to another hospital
to re-do a DNA test?
Must it be done?
Jun Hyeok will be hurt if he knows.
What are you doing? Card games?
We have our version that's more fun.
Shall I teach you guys?
For now, I'll cut his nails in a casual way.
i will ruffle your hair one more time.
- You got it?
- Of course! I nearly died for this.
How can you teach the children
to play Hwatu?
Why do you think Hwatu is bad, with no doubts?
What are you doing? Really!
I can't do it anymore.
I feel guilty, drop me from this.
This time, break the light.
Put all you have at stake
and wage your fight.
Even if it's not the real Jun Hyeok, wanting to
just accept him is how I feel now.
I hate spoiling it.
-=Inside the boxes that say CEO,=-
-=if you put the seal, that will do.=-