I'll go to see Min Hyeok. I had told Bo Yeong that
I'll take over at 3 o'clock and I am late.
Why do you look like that?
Lately, the pee is a bit...
It seems I'll have to get it checked out.
Again it's a pee problem?
Why are you always so edgy?
No. I have a bit of a bad feeling on this.
- What's wrong?
- It's nothing.
What is it?
No, but lately the pee is always--
Ah, stop that.
I thought it was about Min Hyeok.
Every day it's urine, urine, urine. All my life,
I have never seen anybody who pees so much.
Pull a bit harder from inside.
Pull again a bit.
Don't just hold with the hands.
Push it up.
How can I push anymore?
How can you have it in here?
This is a bus. Not a moving van. Damn.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Ajumma, what are you doing now?
(Ajumma - old lady, aunt)
- Hurry. We will be late for work.
- Still not done?
Mom, hurry, hurry.
This won't work. You just go to work.
Mom, what are you going to do?
I will slowly roll it, what else?
That makes no sense.
How can you roll it all the way there?
Why can't I roll it?
Sir, just go ahead.
I'll call you.
So late. See how long it took.
Hey, you should've asked her to take a taxi.
What do you think?
Is there something unusual?
This should be virtually asymptomatic.
How did you even feel it?
As it is usually not sensitive,
it would be hard to guess.
What... what is it you are saying?
There's a tumor on the kidney.
Roughly 1.4 cm.
Don't you see it here?
Tumor?
Then, a cancer is...
Well, a kind of cancer, you see.
It's a kind of cancer, you see.
Though a cancer, it hasn't spread or anything.
Having found it this early,
it can be easily removed.
It's hardly anything.
Since you're here, let's go eat something.
Anterior to it, there's just a--
Stop deliberately acting to
make it easy on me, you!
Hey, what is this you're doing?
Tell me honestly.
How long do I have left?
How long left, of what? It can be removed with
just a laparoscope. What's your problem, really?
Cancer...
Keep it a secret from the family for me.
If the family folks know,
they will be in deep distress.
It will be a big favor.
You know, right?
Why is he going so overboard like this?
He was always going overboard, but his mother
had suddenly passed away with cancer though.
Because of that shock,
his cancer-phobia is quite big.
Chauffeur Gim,
Really, do my sad premonitions ever go wrong?
Mom!
Are you doing well?
I want to see you, mom.
Your son Su-eet Dong is sure to come to you.
Your cute little Su-eet Dong
will sure be following you.
Mom!
Mom, where are you?
=Oh... a sauna house.=
Got there easily?
They'll let the luggage be there?
That's good to hear.
Eat meals on time.
You see those blue and red icons there?
The blue one is me, and the red one is you.
Where did you go? Son of a bitch.
Have everyone heard of asteroid babies?
From couples' intimacy worldwide the night before
the asteroid came, many babies are to be born.
Because of this, the Obstetrics and Gynecology
departments are in for a bonanza.
What is she saying?
On the asteroid day, many babies got conceived.
They'll be called asteroid babies, she said.
How silly. When they heard of the world ending,
these people only wanted to sleep together?
You're back, dad?
Father!
Damn, it hurt like hell, you brat. You gone crazy?
You don't see that I'm picking earwax?
My ear.
Dad, you crying?
No.
I won't cry.
My daughter...
Long time since I hugged you.
What's with you, dad?
You fellow, why are you always
catching people off-guard?
Father, I should ask why you are like this!
Su Yeong, you too.
This way, you'll all regret it.
Just give it some time.
When the time comes,
it will be too late.
Dad, where are you going again?
What is up with him?
Is he like pregnant or something? That fellow...
Mom, which sauna house did you say it was?
- It's an asteroid commemoration event.
- What is the name of the sauna house?
I've come somewhere nearby.
What for? It's fine.
It's pretty good. You just go back.
What do you mean go back?
Now I have to go to work only tomorrow.
What? Meet in front of the Singyo dong-office?
Why?
(Dong - an administrative area)
That's right.
Meet me in front of the dong-office in 20 minutes.
- Mom!
- Omo! You scared me to death!
What is this you're doing,
sitting in the alley?
So your conclusion is to sleep on the street?
What else to do? Everybody sends me out
saying they can't take in this stuff to keep.
Plus, sleeping is the same anywhere.
Sauna houses cost money too.
Since when are you living so frugally?
That's why I ask
why you bought the hot mats?
Again that talk?
My ears are going numb, seriously!
If you talk so much, why didn't you
take up that assistant manager job?
If you hadn't quit from there,
it would've been better than this.
Now, what right do you have
to talk back at me like--
Ah, keep that down, will you?
Kicking up ruckus in other people's crib...
Quickly get everything.
What? To go where?
Wherever it is.
In any case, how can we sleep here?
If I ever do bad things...
He is showing that there were
things he liked where his memories ended.
He is thoroughly happy,
and active also, right now.
That's right.
Later as well, we'll continue the psychological
treatment like this, till the memory recovers.
You're here?
Hello.
Min Hyeok!
Daddy, what is this?
What are you doing?
The boy is concentrating on something.
- Then, I will see you again tomorrow.
- Sure, yes, yes.
They are giving him things he liked
from where his memories ended.
They say his behavior is good. He's also become
active, and there's a big change in his optimism--
Are you crazy?
The son's around, and you've gone mad?
What is this?
All passionate now?
Isn't this your company?
Sleep at your company office?
It's you who said nobody
will take on this luggage.
For tonight, just stay here.
Then go through the front entrance.
Why enter by the back door?
You think Security will let us in?
If we go to the underground parking lot,
we can directly take the elevator up.
Don't just try pushing hard.
Do it with a strategy.
How do we do it with a strategy?
Don't think of just pushing.
Feel how it would roll.
Like this. Like this.
In 1 day, you became a
rolling engineer ajumma!
From here it goes downhill, right?
For downhill, it's a counter-position.
Yeah, it's here.
It won't work this way.
Let's do it in one shot.
Come back here.
1. 2. 3.
Hello.
Is this Bo Yeong?
My dearest daughter, Bo Yeong.
Oh, dad. Later, later.
Do you know how much I love you?
I remember from when you were little.
When you went with me to Grandmother's place,
you said you wanted to catch lantern fish--
The room seems to be locked.
There is no other vacant room?
What, is this a hotel?
Who said it's a hotel?
I just asked if there's a vacant room,
and you start on something else...
Might as well go to our office itself.
Mom. It's weird, must you wear
night clothes in an office?
What about it?
What is weird about wearing
might clothes when you sleep?
Even if you sleep only an hour,
you should sleep right.
Not just that you're my mom,
but you're unique.
Oh...
What are you wearing tomorrow for work?
Not sure. May be the sky blue colored
piece I had bought some time back?
Oh? that one?
Wait a moment.
It''s fine, it's fine.
How can you find it like that?
Here it is!
What's this? You are a
first class baggage handler too?
The wrinkled insides need pressing.
When do you start work tomorrow?
8 o'clock.
Then we'll have to get up at 5 o'clock,
to have enough time.
It's all done.
Mom, I see that people have
things they have aptitude in.
- What do you mean?
- Mom, how you look now... what shall I say...
looks so natural.
Like an otter that saw water.
I am tired. I will have to sleep.
Toothbrush...
The surgery will surely fail.
My sad premonitions never miss the mark.
Is my life going to end in such emptiness?
My life... My memories...
They end... in a miserable way.
Hey, horse head. Have you by chance
heard any news on Choe Yeong?
Went to the U.S. after a marriage?
Oh... Is that so?
Would you perhaps know her contact details?
You don't know?
Hey, Gim Seun. May be you remember this?
We had promised to go together to
Sahara desert once we were 60.
Shall we go together at least now?
What do you think?
Lying down here like this
is quite comfortable.
What comfort? Just go to sleep.
Before I forget, what happened to
your CEO who had got hurt?
I don't know. He still hasn't
come to the company.
How did our next-door youngster
disappear without even a word?
I don't know. Son of a bitch.
Seonbaenim! seonbaenim!
(Seonbaenim - senior colleague)
I made this with the motivation from
that iron shovel. Isn't it a fun thing?
Sure, Na Soe Dol.
You were a good man.
It's me.
About us sending rice to Na Soe Dol's family...
Haven't we been sending it in recent years also?
I was anyway going to report to you on that.
This time the rice got returned.
Returned? Why?
Mom!
Mom! Mom! Mom! Wake up quickly!
What's wrong?
- What?
- It's 8 o'clock. 8 o'clock!
Get out, first.
Good morning.
Oh Miss Jin A, you're already here?
Yes.
But, what is that?
That one is...
Supplies. It's supplies.
Supplies?
What supplies?
It is for taking to the storage.
I will take it there now.
But Miss Jin A, you have no make-up on?
It's not like that.
I was making it a bit natural.
They say its popular lately.
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
Would you like to see me do
an Lee Jeong Hyeon number?
When I practiced a little while back,
it was coming out very well.
Why are you dancing right from morning?
How is it? Isn't this good enough
for me to enter Superstar K?
(TV talent competition)
Can't say. May be better not to take part?
Then I'll just take the supplies away!
Ms. Gil Seon Ja. Ms. Gil Seon Ja.
Ms. Gil Seon Ja.
What was there now? May be a ghost?
Whatever it was that went in so fast.
May be so.
It was wearing some flowing white dress.
My hairs are standing up.
Flowing dress?
If it's a flowing dress...
Ms. Gil Seon Ja!
Supplies. It's supplies.
Ms. Gil Seon Ja.
Where did she go?
She didn't take her mobile phone either.
Where the heck did she go?
Is there anyone inside?
Isn't anybody there?
Shoot, what do I do?
I am not seeing the feet.
Isn't it because there's nobody inside?
Isn't it locked from inside?
Obviously there's someone.
Oooooh, then what's it?
That fast-moving ghost is there, you mean?
Creeping us out in the morning itself...
It seems she was seen upstairs
moving in a flowing white dress.
Try to take a look from above.
No way. If you are so curious, you try looking.
This won't work. I'll go call the Security ajussi.
There's something I need to get done.
Can an employee--
No. No need to ask an employee.
Send up anyone among the interns.
Which floor was it on?
7th floor.
It seems locked from inside,
but nobody's there. It's strange.
I heard someone upstairs felt that
they saw a ghost in a flowing dress.
It can't be that, can it?
Look, is anybody there?
Open the door.
So, you won't?
I am breaking it open and coming in.
What was that just now?
That is crazy fast!
Ms. Gil Seon Ja.
Answer me, Ms. Gil Seon Ja.
Here, here!
Do you know how much playacting
I was doing since morning?
Why didn't you set the alarm?
Didn't you say you would?
I had set it. Without knowing
I must have shut it off.
Shut it off, you said?
I really go insane because of you!
- But where is our big bag?
- In the parking garage. Hurry, it needs to go out.
The door seems locked.
Try to open the door.
Just a moment.
Climb up over there.
How do I climb up there?
There's no time. Hurry up.
What are you doing?
It's open.
How are you doing?
What are you doing here?
I thought there was a training session here.
I'm sorry.
She scared me.
How come I just don't get a good impression
whenever I see her?
Is it that she is only a high school grad?
I had secretly sent somebody to look for
the USB in that house, but she failed.
But that fox of a woman keeps on
asking me to give her money.
Saying she would let out our plan
if I don't give her money.
What would be best to do here?
See this, see this. Here it comes again.
- Hello
- Hurry up, give me the dough. Dough!
You don't give it, and it is all coming out!
Okay?
I understand.
I'm in a meeting now.
Let's talk later, okay?
What do I do with this?
Just kill her, what else?
For you, they are all there to be just killed?
This way, someday you will kill me too!
You too have to be killed, if needed.
What? See this. Hey, kill me, then.
Kill me, then. Kill me, then!
That's enough!
You guys meet, and it's only to fight.
Like it's all planned...
Your fight is all in the script. Isn't it so?
What script do you mean?
I'm suffocating.
What's that?
How about convincing her to take just half of it?
You think she'll get convinced?
Just kill her.
What if she gets convinced?
What if she is not?
- If she doesn't, we can find a solution then.
- If she doesn't, there will be nothing we can do.
- Wake up and smell the roses, my friend!
- How the heck am I a friend to you?
That's enough. Enough!
It's these guys I take along and...
But why does a poop smell keep coming?
Didn't someone fart here?
It can't be me.
Not sure of him though.
It's not me, okay?
For a while I was feeling the
stench to be coming from above.
See this, he clearly lets one out,
but blames this place, how dare--
Quiet!
But just now some sound did come from above...
I'm busy like hell and he asks to
send up an intern or whatnot...
Oh, Miss Na Jin A.
What are you doing here? Busy?
No, I'm not busy or anything.
Ah, then that's great. Go up to the
Adviser's office now. Hurry up.
Did you call me?
Could you go look for something
in this neighborhood?
There's somebody I need to find.
At this place?
I heard that the people there have moved out.
Please ask around for me
where they have gone.
See the name written there?
Someone called Na Geon A.
I'm about to die. Where is this place?
But may I ask you
why you're looking for these people?
They are the
family of a close junior I had long back.
I wondered how they're doing.
This Na Geon A is...
that friend's son.
It is Na Jin A.
A daughter.
Was it a daughter that Soe Dol had?
But...
It is me...
This place is... the house that we were living in.
I am the late Na Soe Dol's daughter.
Na Jin A.
Really?
You are?
Yes.
Oh, I'll be darned!
You were so near me, you mean?
- You live with your mom now?
- Yes.
Mom is doing fine, right?
It would be so nice to see your Mom once--
What is this?
Oh, it is... Hello.
I mean... from there... how come?
Mom, hurry, get down. What are you doing?
That means, because you had nowhere to go
you stayed the night in the company office?
- Yes. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
How sad...
I should have properly taken care of you.
Seeing my sister-in-law and Geon A--
It's Jin A. Na Jin A.
Jin A...
You are no different than family to me.
It's me who feels sorry.
- Then where--
- No, it's nothing.
For sending rice every year, many thanks.
What thanks?
But Geon A, how did you--
It's Jin A.
Jin A, how come you...
thought of working in our company?
Working at Kong Kong was my dream.
Then temporarily, you sister-in-law and Geon A--
Jin A, Jin A...
Jin A... You both are in a
desperate housing situation, right?
It seems, until you find some housing,
you need at least a temporary shelter...
No, no. We should be able to handle it...
At least temporarily you need to
have some place to stay.
It's nothing. We are all right.
Adviser, with that money,
finding temporary stay is a bit...
Really? It's not more than 100 000 Wons.
(~US$ 88)
They can't find a motel or something?
May be no more than 2 days.
Is that so?
Prices have gone up?
Should I go look for some money?
Then temporarily... why not stay at our house?
- Huh?
Because you have all the house stuff,
it's tough to go anywhere, you said.
Temporarily, just stay at our place then.
We have many vacant rooms in our house.
No, we shouldn't.
Can we really do that?
It's all right. Soe Dol's family is my family too.
It's only temporarily anyway.
Just do it that way.
Thank you. Thank you.
Then just temporarily...
Thank you.
Honey, it's me.
What's wrong?
It's nothing much else...
Didn't you know Soe Dol? Na Soe Dol.
I just met Soe Dol's wife and daughter.
They both seem to be homeless now.
So what are you saying we do?
So I was thinking about it.
I felt it would be nice if they could stay
in our house at least temporarily.
Don't we have guest rooms?
Our house has some guest rooms?
Well, on the 2nd floor...
What room on the 2nd floor?
Even the storage room has so much
clothes and is overflowing.
Seriously, you aren't talking of
Jun Hyeok's room now, are you?
I'm not. Just take some clothes
out from the storage room and--
Stop the nonsense. With Min Hyeok in this
state now, you're bringing outsiders here?
Have you lost your mind now?
Just this time, let's go by what I say.
I told you not to say pointless crap.
What kind of nonsense is this?
Whatever the hell I say,
do you have to oppose it?
I really hadn't planned to tell you this but...
I have cancer!
You have cancer, so what?
What?
I also know it.
I had a phone call with Dr. Yu.
As it is found so early, it can be fixed with a
simple laparoscopic surgery, then what?
What does that have to do with
giving them a room here?
Room? No way!
Just listen to what I say, please.
I am a cancer-stricken fellow!
Geez!
In any case, a room looks a bit iffy...
It's all right. Thank you so much for the concern.
What to do with this?
A place to sleep...
Hey... No, no, no, no, no, no...
That won't make sense.
What won't?
I mean, at my house...
Hey, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No way can it make sense...
Oh, it's all right. Want did you want to say?
Well... It's that...
People are not vehicles. How can I do this?
I don't know what you're getting at,
but for us, wherever it is,
if we could at least leave the big bag,
it wouldn't matter where.
In a garage, your stay will be quite inconvenient.
It's just temporary. It is quite all right.
Temporarily, yes.
Ah, right!
Though I can't do much else,
let me raise you from intern status
to a regular employee.
Oh, no. It is all right.
I would rather have it based on my abilities.
That is it. Well, it's not even so hard.
This can be done with a phone call.
Oh, please don't. It's really fine.
May be so, but she does chant the song
"regular employee, regular employee"...
Director O, it's me.
You know the youngster among
our interns called Na Jin A...
It would good if you could raise her right away
tomorrow to a regular employee status.
Please make that happen for me.
You understand?
Well, that's a bit... heavily problematic.
What kind of problem?
To do that, we will have to change
the company's personnel policies.
Explaining it to the other interns
will become way too nonsensical.
If we flay the policies like this and make
somebody a regular employee one fine day,
from now the personnel policies will be pointless,
it will be a complete mess, discipline-wise.
Oh, will that... be so much like that?
There is no way out?
I'm not sure.
There is no way, I guess.
Is that so?
Well, I... understand.
What to do?
It can be done if it has to be, but... the company's
personnel policies... will need to be broken.
I' also think the same way.
Even if you were to do that, I would have
requested you to reconsider it.
In an upright way, I will come up
the ladder on my own abilities.
Will this really be all right?
As there is no heating there,
it will be completely cold at night.
But still, it is better than the street, no?
Then we will trouble you temporarily.
I'm really thankful.
Fine. Then, take rest.
- Please take care.
-=Next Episode Preview=-
In the garage? How could you think of
bringing some people into the garage?
They have nowhere to go.
They are Soe Dol's family!
Adviser, sir. Is the CEO doing all right?
He is fine. If you are asked at
the company, say he's all right.
Ah, I'm frustrated. If all of you
leave for good, what about me?
Why do you look so distressed?
Is it so obvious?
Mom, I am scared.
- Nuna... Miss Jin A. This is No Min Hyeok.
- CEO sir!
CEO No Min Hyeok's condition...
Is he at home or at a hospital?
In case something goes wrong and
something bad happens to this fellow,
I wonder what I will do!
Don't worry, father. I will stand firm.
TvN Potato Star.
Potato Star.
From Monday every week,
Till Thursday.
Keep the channel right there.
-=Episode 12=-
-=Why aren't you gone?=-
-=Hurry, get out!=-
-=It's hard for me!=-
-=Those stinking...=-
-=Personnel Policies.=-
-=Just change them, goddamnit!=-