Hello. I am called Seo Yu Jin.
Who is she?
She is the new housekeeper girl.
The old one quit.
Go on and start working.
Yes.
Where did you find this young lady?
We can't find that old maid,
ever since the asteroid came.
Besides, with Min Hyeok in that state,
we need a maid. Okay, I'm off to the hospital.
Let's go together.
Let me put Cheol Min down and...
No, No! You want to create hell
at the hospital like last time?
No, why would I?
Then it was that doctor fellow--
But wait. Min Hyeok's condition now must be
absolutely a secret. Even from people like that.
If it's known in the company,
it's not that he'll have to quit as CEO right away,
but as our claim is that he was all healed at
the first hospital, it was only secretly that
we could change hospitals.
Well, who said anything about that?
- I also want to see Min Hyeok and--
- Do it later, please!
I will tell you how it turns out!
Also, there should be somebody at home.
If all of us are at the hospital,
who'll watch the house?
Will the "Eagle-5 Brothers" watch the house?
("Doksori-o-hyeonje" - Korean super-hero
animation series, 1972-74)
What?
("Doksori-o-hyeonje" - Korean super-hero
animation series, 1972-74)
What? The Eagles are out, to watch the house?
("Doksori-o-hyeonje" - Korean super-hero
animation series, 1972-74. Based on Gatchaman)
Where are they?
("Doksori-o-hyeonje" - Korean super-hero
animation series, 1972-74)
Take care.
Here's the payment.
Thank you.
Sure.
You too take care.
Careful!
Are those things you have had for long?
Yeah.
For more than 20 years we used them.
The wooden chairs were made by my dad.
They will get a new home. Don't worry.
You're loaded.
Then it's a pork strips party tonight?
You aren't getting this, are you?
Minus the debt-payment,
the money left over is nothing.
You'd give me pork strips
once you get money, you said.
You're something else, man.
That was if we got our savings.
With someone who's fully broke
and wiping the floor,
you're now asking for
a pork strips meal?
True.
I see that.
Too dirty and disgusting,
I wont even eat it.
Pork strips?
Fine, lets eat that.
Anyway a promise is promise, right?
Today is not so good.
Tomorrow evening.
It's fine.
I too have self-respect.
Pork strips?
Quit it. Not much fun.
This is... me, you mean?
Yes. That is a mirror, right?
How do you find your looks?
You like it?
You grew handsome, you think?
Yes. I've grown handsome. Extremely...
Good. We will go to the inspection room and
do some more of the mental tests.
- Yes.
- Please come this way.
Okay.
What do we do with him?
Please don't worry too much.
It is a kind of dissociative amnesia.
You can say that it's a bit extreme.
As such cases involve more of psychological
issues than any particular brain abnormality,
there are many cases when the memory slowly
returns once the mind gets relaxed from rest.
Oh, okay.
Plus, as the patient himself is
happy with how he appears at present,
we can expect even better results.
Is that so?
Yes. Didn't you see it now?
Seeing the great changes in one's own looks
can be shocking, and can feel quite bad.
But he feels himself to have grown
handsome. Extremely so, he felt!
This doesn't happen that often.
But isn't he handsome, in fact?
Extremely.
Oh, you think so?
Okay.
This feels quite strange.
The hospital is changed suddenly.
Which hospital it is, stays a secret.
Hospital visits aren't allowed either.
They are obviously hiding something.
Isn't it enough to
check with the first hospital,
how his condition was
up here, before he left?
Of course I asked.
But what was bad
had all healed, they said.
If he's all healed
we have to kill him quickly.
Is killing somebody
so easy for you to speak of?
It goes wrong, and we are finished.
Then what else to do, idiot?
If that USB is seen, we are finished.
It could be a lie that
he's all healed, you idiot.
If must be true, you idiot.
Even if he's all healed,
he could've been quietly moved.
Even if the USB is opened, one may
just not see that folder, you idiot.
Fine. Like a pacifist would say,
let's just wait a bit.
Yessir. I win.
It is 1 to 0.
Yeah, fine.
I see. Be careful.
Damn, you jobless fellow.
I already said no. We cannot.
Grandfather, I'll do a bit of room cleaning.
When my grandson is hurt and in hospital,
you want to bring friends and have fun?
How muddle-headed is that?
Ah, you fellow, really...
Then quietly come over for a cup of tea.
- You also get up.
- Get up.
You have no sense of how to have fun!
Let's have a quiet tea, I said.
Who asked you to have a dance party?
It's the heaven's wish! There are 2 bright moons
up there, and we should be having our fun.
Make way, make way.
Punk.
Yes.
Nothing much, really.
It would be good if what goes on today
is kept a secret from my daughter-in-law.
What?
These days, things aren't so
hunky-dory around here.
I only just wanted them to come for a chat today.
Who knew he would create a pandemonium?
Yes, I understand.
I'll keep it a secret.
That's it. A secret.
Why does rain come so suddenly back to back
like this, making us go mad?
But I guess we should be happy to
still have some roof over us.
But what will we do?
The day after tomorrow
we'll have to move.
This is all because of whom?
Still saying such things shamelessly?
Hey, stop this, you wretched girl. You're so damn
young, how come you're so unable to let it go?
A girl who should use her time
to think about her future.
You think this is about the future?
What the heck do we do day after tomorrow?
Fine, fine. I should just die so many times.
Turn off the flame for the broth!
I know!
What soup is it?
Pollack fish.
Check the taste. See if it's too salty.
Not so! Tastes great!
Then ask the next-door guy to eat with us!
I got it!
What?
I am scared.
Because it's dark.
Hey... Hongberg.
No problems, right?
Yes.
I thought you would be sleeping
at the hospital tonight.
I was supposed to, but our youngest daughter
wanted to stay there with her dad.
Why are there so many rice wine bottles?
That is...
What is all this?
I kinda like a bit of rice wine, so...
So you mean you drank
all this rice wine all by yourself?
In your room?
Okay, I see.
You came back?
Aren't you staying tonight at the hospital?
Su Yeong said she would stay there.
Leave that aside, father-in-law,
why in the world would you do that?
What?
I was told you had your friends over
for a dance party during the day.
When Min Hyeok is in that state,
this is what you'd want to do?
No. It is that old fart Gim who--
Oh come on, what's with this old fart Gim always?
Is old fart Gim the house-owner here?
Sorry.
Oh please, act your age for God's sake.
Who is it?
What?
Who said I did it?
Was it her? Yu Jin or whatnot.
If so, what do you want to do?
You want to take revenge?
No, no! Not so.
We'll just wait and see.
Keep the leftover soup in the refrigerator?
The refrigerator also should have been sold
earlier if we could get a few tens of thousands.
(few 10s of US$)
Nobody will want this kind of thing for that.
Thanks for the meal.
I'm going.
But if it keeps raining like this, will you be fine?
Doesn't it leak at your place?
Not so.
I didn't even know it was raining.
You punk. Isn't that itself a disease, really!
That's right, in fact. If it rains like this,
how will you sleep? It's just a shed.
Take a sleeping bag and sleep here.
With no furniture, it's like a playground here!
It's fine.
Yeah right, fine!
You'll be here just as you say it, right?
Not so.
Your disease really needs to be treated.
You know that you really make others annoyed?
- Not so.
- You punk, you really need this to cure it.
When you guys are like this,
it's just like you are siblings.
Say what, the horror!
It's not even 9 o'clock, but we sleep.
The TV also is gone.
Ah, this is crap... There's nothing to do.
Shall we play hwatu?
(Korean card game)
We have no hwatu cards.
Oh, that's right, that's right.
Shall I go buy it?
No, forget it.
Buy what, in this rain?
Like we see on TV or something,
there must be some game we can play.
Why don't we try something?
Like there is some game...
Don't you know some fun game?
No clue.
You just might know, right?
What I know are only Bear-paw Jigsaw-puzzle
Mafia-007 Spacecraft-0 Eye-expression-game
Corpse-drops-from-sky Cola-drinking like that.
What do we do first?
Which will be the best?
=From the Bongcheon-dong accident scene,
this is CJB News' Gim U Hyeon.=
They are still showing this news?
Yeah, like Today's Weather, every day.
=Hello everybody. Asteroid 2013QR3 is presently
maintaining a 33 000 kilometers height.=
=For every revolution around the Earth,
it takes about 16 weeks.=
=As it is much faster than how the moon revolves,
if you look carefully, you can feel them
moving apart gradually.=
=Just that, as the entire mainland has rain today,
it's only in Jeju Island that the asteroid is visible.=
Bear paw paw, my palm palm.
My palm palm, bear paw paw.
Bear paw paw, horse hoof hoof.
Horse hoof hoof, my palm palm.
My palm palm, bear paw paw.
Bear paw paw. Horse pa pa.
That was all slurred!
What? Who said it wasn't right?
Awawawawawawawawoy... Indiaaaan... BAM!
Might as well poke me with a fork!
Yes, I won that!
Hey, you came last.
I'm a girl, you know!
Just this once, can't we forget it?
You sure know we can't!
Bend over!
I won that! Yahooooo....
Where are you going?
Let me off once please.
Fine. Then show something you're good at.
If we like it, we'll let you off.
There's nothing like that.
Pak Yeong Gyu.
Aigooma...
So close, so close.
Better be exact.
Do another.
Im Jae Beom.
Suppose I...
Fine, right? You'll let me off?
What let-off?
Stay still.
I asked not to talk
but the dimwit can't get it.
Hey. Look here.
Where is she?
What are you doing here?
I came to grab the clothes to wash.
If you are getting clothes to wash,
why are you flipping the pockets?
I was checking if it had pockets.
You weren't just turning it over, the way I saw.
Huh?
What are you...
What is going on?
What is the issue?
This is very suspicious.
What is?
She was flipping Min Hyeok's pants pockets.
I caught her red-handed.
Before putting them in for laundry,
I was checking for pockets.
Fine, I know. Take it and go.
You know, you said?
How come you won't believe my words?
You think I'm saying some nonsense?
Would you please stop that?
You make it difficult for your own heart.
Just because it's difficult, it is fine to let
a thief remain at home with no concern?
Because she ratted on you, you are now
finding fault with her, aren't you?
What finding fault?
I saw her flipping pockets.
To wash clothes, can't people flip pockets?
Sure I also know that
pockets are flipped before washing.
But while flipping
she did it very suspiciously.
Like this, like this, like this, you see.
Oh, enough of that.
Please don't be like this.
This woman! Seriously...
There is surely something about that girl...
Not asleep?
Yeah.
The rain keeps coming.
From now on we won't have a house either.
How long have you lived in this house?
Since I was 3 years old.
Dad had bought his first house.
Once Dad passed away, it became
rented yearly and then rented monthly.
Eventually we were chased out.
So losing out was a way of life, I guess.
This still remains here?
What?
From my dad measuring my height.
This is from the last time Dad measured me.
He passed away when you were 6 years old?
Yes.
The pencil marks are
what I did myself.
To show Dad if he were to come back.
But he passed away, you said?
Because I didn't see it with my eyes.
So, may he would come back, I hoped.
Then I used to get the same dream everyday.
Dad coming back,
opening the door with a smile.
Here is where it ended?
That dream?
You said both your dad and mom
are no more, right?
Then in whose house did you live?
Gyeonggi-do, Yangju city, Janghyeong-dae, 5-12.
House number 5.
Look at this.
Wasn't I right that she's a thief?
What's wrong?
That Seo Yu Jin or Seo Yu Beer,
where did she go?
To the shop. What's it now?
My gold ring has disappeared.
It was worth so much money.
You let a total thief be in this house.
Based on what proof
do you think that she took it?
Because it disappeared
after my room was cleaned.
Did you look for it anywhere else?
Of course I looked.
It's not there anywhere.
It's her. No doubt it's her.
Really?
What really?
Since yesterday's thing, he has kept at it.
Is that so?
What was so, you said?
- Come on father, for no reason--
- I will get you. Eat this and stop up.
Ah, father. Ah...
You shouldn't be accusing...
I should go and rummage through her things.
Father-in-law, you needlessly doubt an innocent
one, and if it wasn't her, what will you do?
These days if he take domestic helps lightly,
you could get sued.
On some hunch with no evidence,
you can't suspect people!
Evidence? You see when I check into her things.
It will come out. No mistaking.
Is there some problem?
You happened to return?
Saw everything? Is that enough now?
My pockets also...
It's fine. I know you wouldn't do it.
If an elderly won't get convinced now and wants
to blame you, rather let him rummage. Sorry.
No, it's nothing.
Rather than be suspected, this is better.
Where she put it won't be easy to find.
You. I am watching you!
Could you please stop this? Seriously...
What kind of scallion-pancake
is it for you to eat like this?
Father took such a big piece
and stuffed in my mouth.
Now I have to eat all of it.
Bear paw paw. Horse hoof hoof
Horse hoof hoof. Bear paw paw.
Bear paw paw. Horse hoof hoof.
Bear paw paw. Horse Pa Pa.
You got it wrong, just wait.
Indiaaaan... BAM!
You can go now.
When's the bus coming?
In 3 minutes.
That seems right.
Why did you sit? Go on.
To annoy you.
Wait a moment.
Why?
I'll install a fun thing.
What's it?
Just for when we're bored...
It's still a beta version.
Right now the users are only you and me.
Here.
Near U?
What is this?
Click it.
You see those blue and red icons there?
The blue one is me, and the red one is you.
It will show me where you are currently?
Yeah. If the connected person
is within a 1 kilometer radius,
at that time "Near U" will flicker.
If you press it, it will show the location.
What is this?
There are many others that track
people from even farther distance.
This will show it only from within 1 kilometer?
Isn't this outdated?
That's why it's still a beta version
needing a lot of tweaking.
Still when it's pitch-black on the street,
won't you be happy to see the light flicker?
Say you have come to the lane at night.
If it flickers, it's like "Oh, Hongberg is here".
You'll be happy. Isn't that good?
Bullshit. Plus, once we leave this neighborhood,
aren't we done with you coming to get me?
Ah, damn crap. Isn't that right?
Impossible.
The bus is here.
I'll buy pork strips and come in the evening.
Wait for that.
Okay.
Then just give it to me now.
Huh?
First send me a photo of the bill.
There's no need to see it. Where I live,
dry cleaning is without a doubt just 10 000.
(~US$ 8)
I have no cash now.
Get in touch with me. Understood?
Damn, he never contacted me.
Why?
Grandpa got conjunctivitis?
I understand.
Grandpa.
Grandpa, what's wrong?
The conjunctivitis is this serious?
That's right.
Can't even open my eyes.
I'll do it.
How did this happen?
I don't know about that.
Till the morning he seemed fine.
I wasn't fine even in the morning.
It's just that you didn't know.
Aigoo, now I can't see anything at all.
Su Yeong. Take me to my room.
If it's so bad that you can't see, what do we do?
What do we do?
I'm all just fine.
Then you were lying? Why?
This maid is a thief who I saw flipping the
pockets of Min Hyeok's pants in his room.
Knowing that I am watching her,
she's suddenly all careful.
So this is a trap I am setting!
Grandpa, seriously!
These days if we let anyone in the house,
we can't drop our guard, right?
Then when the time comes,
I can catch her red-handed.
But if you are wearing this,
you can't see anything at all, no?
You think I'm a fool?
I removed the gauze inside. I see everything.
Really?
You don't believe me?
Then you let a punch fly at me.
Like this?
Whoa...
What do you think now?
This is a secret between just us both, okay?
I'm back.
Why are you panting like this?
To get through the lane before sunset,
I was running.
I bought pork strips.
Wow, you bought fresh meat?
Not frozen?
Yeah. Isn't it our last dinner with
Hongberg in this house?
I had scolded him a lot all this while,
so I spent some money.
It's a good thing. Ask him to come.
Don't grill it yet, okay?
I want to show it to Hongberg.
Hey, Hongberg!
I bought pork strips as promised.
Say thanks and come to...
Why are you back alone?
That brat isn't there.
He went somewhere?
Did he go somewhere?
I don't know.
His things aren't there either.
I had told him in the morning that
I would come with pork strips.
Where did he go?
Call and see, where he is.
Call?
But to do that, I don't know his phone number!
After being so close,
you don't even know his number?
I was seeing him here at home every day.
Ah, right.
The app from this morning.
If he was within a 1 kilometer radius,
"Near U" was supposed to show it.
He seems not to be
within a 1 kilometer radius.
Won't that thing
know the phone number?
It would seem so.
But I have no way to find it.
Would he have gone somewhere
as something urgent came up?
What do we do with these pork strips?
Tonight let's just eat some bagged food and...
The pork strips, we'll eat it with him tomorrow.
Even after buying fresh pork,
it seems we are only eating frozen stuff.
Don't be so out of it.
You should take the eye-patch off at least to eat.
No, it's all right.
Su Yeong.
Put some item on this.
It is some egg.
It's so bad that you can't see anything?
No, I can't.
I can't see a thing.
Hey, your mouth is here.
Ah, I told you, I can't see a thing!
Will you be at home today?
No. I have to go out.
I have to meet some friends.
Then what to do?
Till I reach the hospital to send your mom home,
who will take care of your grandpa?
No need to bother about me.
I'm just fine being by myself.
It's Min Hyeok you should take care of.
Over here!
Next-door youngster,
you there?
In the morning itself
you want to have pork strips?
It was in the fridge yesterday.
I felt we should eat it soon.
Next-door youngster!
I'll go and see.
Grandfather.
Please move your feet a bit.
- What? You are cleaning right in front?
- Yes.
I just can't see a thing,
how would I know?
Bingo!
Caught red-handed, you!
What are you flipping around now? What?
What is it, grandfather?
What is it?
You crafty little devil.
You think I can't see, right?
It was to catch you stealing stuff
that I put on a show, do you see?
Then you were
deliberately doing it because of me?
Now that I caught you doing it,
you've nothing to say now, do you?
What did you catch me doing, you mean?
You stole my ring. Now you're caught
stealing from Min Hyeok's drawer!
For the ring, I rummaged through everything.
I'm just arranging his drawer.
So you will deny it all the way through?
Fine, then.
You come here.
Father-in-law, what are you doing?
Ah, you came just on time.
I caught her right at the scene of the crime.
What scene of the crime?
No, it's not so. It wasn't.
We'll see if it wasn't.
Call the police. Police.
First take your hands off, then talk.
What happened here?
I mean, I was just fixing the room.
He kept saying I was stealing something.
Whatever explanation I give, doesn't work.
Wow, take a look at her acting!
Seems like the real thing, you!
Why not be a TV actress or something?
Would you please stop, seriously?
Stop what, you mean?
I caught her in the act.
I have to find my ring, don't I?
You searched through all her things, right?
After you lost it somewhere,
why do you do this to an innocent girl?
Look at you talk!
If I were to lose the ring,
how and where could it be?
Come on, you are always going up and down
for doing something on the balcony.
Did you check there also?
What, you think I have turned senile or what?
I looked everywhere. It's not there.
Without even checking, you say this.
What do you mean I haven't checked?
You go and take a look, then!
Who does she think is stupid here?
If the ring was here, why wouldn't I see it?
Oh damn, crap!
It's not anywhere here?
Where would it be? It's not here.
Hongberg came back?
The final demolition notice has come.
They'll be tearing it down starting tomorrow.
Then it seems we'll have to pack up soon today.
For now, can we go to may be a motel?
To keep some luggage,
a sauna house may be better.
It is not that I'm suspecting you.
But as long as the ring isn't found,
the old man will keep hassling you so much.
If you were to continue here,
it can only get harder.
For not being able to do anymore
than this for you, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Bye.
Grandfather, please stay healthy.
Hi, it's me.
This was a failure.
With that old man who should be dead constantly
picking faults with me, how could I even work?
I wanted to beat him up half-way to death,
but stopped myself, barely.
It would've been nice to eat with him,
but he disappeared without a word, it seems.
This is the last dinner in this house too.
It's quite tasty.
Why do you cry?
I don't know.
A little bit more.
Aigoo, aigoo.
That's it.
Aigoo. That's it.
Yeah, that's it. Aigoo.
Bye.
Mom, wait a moment.
-=Next Episode Preview=-
What's wrong?
Lately, the pee is a bit...
There is a tumor here. On this side.
This won't work. You just go to work.
Mom, what are you trying to do?
I will roll it and go.
Help me keep it a secret.
I am in deep confusion.
Brat, are you crazy?
What is this you're doing,
sitting in the alley?
Then what to do?
This is too big to keep anywhere.
- Is it Bo Yeong? The daughter I love most...
- Hold on, I'll call you later.
Isn't this your company?
Let's spend this night here.
Mom!
I'm following you soon.
-=Episode 11=-
-=Go Chang Dong=-
-=Hongberg. I don't even know=-
-=your name or phone number.=-
-=Call me, you son of a bitch..=-