We can't eat regular food and
have to keep eating instant food...
Our health gets all destroyed.
If so, had you brought even a small pot
we could've cooked something.
Sure I brought one.
As we moved the big bag,
it must have fallen out somewhere.
A car is coming in.
Just when people are eating,
they come sending exhaust fumes out.
- You're back?
- Hello.
- You've been eating, I see.
- Yes.
I heard the surgery ended well.
Congratulations.
That means a lot more now.
Please say hello. These are the folks
that I told you about.
- Hello.
Hello.
Even in a garage like this,
people can survive, I guess?
It is like a cave-dwelling Circean tribe.
Why is this ajumma and nuna
staying in the garage?
(Ajumma - Older lady, Nuna - Elder sister or girl)
They have a bit of problem situation.
Let's go in now. We need to be there for dinner.
Nothing is uncomfortable, right?
Well, it is...
We're alright.
Then, please have your food.
What? For me to eat?
Thank you.
Nuna, you have some too.
Whoa! She caught and ate it!
- How did you do that?
- Just like that.
- Do it once more.
- Stop it.
What are you guys up to, not eating?
Mom, this nuna catches cookies
with her mouth and eats!
What are you up to?
Oh, I am sorry.
It's nothing.
How can you throw food at people?
What are these people, really!
Is this like a zoo or something?
You too, actually. Why do you catch it eat?
Are you an ocean seal? Or a monkey?
You also took it and ate!
It was with my hands that I took it
to eat. Like humans do.
The arms are falling...
Why did you do it like that?
What is this?
What did you do wrong to get to this?
Hyeong was throwing cookies at the
people staying in the garage.
I was only watching.
It was just an accident?
Yes. On the night the asteroid came,
there were many falling accidents.
We think your son also had such an accident.
Have you fully investigated who was
at the company at that time?
Yes. We did that, but hardly anybody was left
at the company at that midnight hour.
What's left are the females. They'd have no
motive to forcefully push your son to his fall.
Physically speaking, there is no chance.
We're closing the case as an accidental fall.
How is it?
Just an accident...
I mean, something looks odd, doesn't it?
What does?
To think that he fell from being
shocked about the asteroid...
Hearing that the police started investigating,
I thought it would come to something.
What's there for it to come to?
That day there were so many people
getting shocked and killing themselves.
That fits CEO No's nature?
I heard that my grandson did a bit of mischief.
If it was unpleasant, I'm really sorry.
- No, it's nothing.
- It's all right.
Is there anything uncomfortable?
- That...
- Nothing at all.
Then, please take rest.
I swear, why is this man always asking if there's
anything uncomfortable? Like he can settle it.
What's uncomfortable are way too many.
Why does he keep asking that?
Mom...
Omo.
- I had something to get from the car.
- I see.
If there's anything inconvenient,
please let me know. It is fine to.
It's all right.
Then, you know...
Can we borrow one small pot?
Small pot?
We have a gas stove, but no pot.
If you could lend one small pot
we can cook something to eat.
I see. You should have told me earlier.
There are so many pots at home.
Please wait. I will get it for you right away.
Who threw this?
Who is it that threw this in the recycle bin?
Is it you?
Is it you? Is it you?
- No.
- No, it's not me.
Then who is it?
Is it you?
What is?
Is it you who threw this in the recycle bin?
Why would I throw that?
Who was it?
Ajumma, did you throw this?
No, I...
It was me who asked her to throw it.
What did you say?
Wait a moment.
I asked to throw that. It's too old and tattered.
Too old and tattered?
Even if it is all tattered,
why would you throw it without
checking with me?
One moment.
You threw it in the multipurpose room, so you
wanted to get rid of it, I thought. What's wrong?
I put it there briefly, as a stain
was smeared on it.
You don't know how precious
an outfit this is, to me?
How would I know about?
If it's old, I would throw it!
Also, a floral design? What's up with that?
Not even suiting your age...
What is not suiting? Is there a law against
old people having floral designs?
Then you think the polka dots suit you?
Bullshit, it suits you!
I can't dare throw even trash, I guess.
- Oh, I'm sorry
- What? Trash?
This is trash, you think?
Then this is trash too.
Isn't it well-matching for you?
Seriously, why are you like this?
Then you too take your clothes off!
I'll take it and throw--
Father, please stop it.
These two fight the minute they meet,
just as they meet...
Still I'm glad that they can't fight,
as Mother-in-law went inside.
The bilateral power-struggle in this house is
due to the strive for hegemony between
Mother-in-law and Grandfather.
- How can people talk so irresponsibly?
- Open the door!
To use a nation-based metaphor,
like America and China, they are 2 superpowers.
Unfortunately due to the antagonistic relations,
their disputes are not ending.
While a majority of their disputes are
ended on a partitional-basis like now,
if affiliated parties join the fray,
it can be major war scenario.
Such major wars have broken out
twice in this house.
The Great War I and the Great War II.
The reason why the Great Wars broke out,
was that the family members joined the 2 sides
in the fight, which led to such wars.
They ended, but only with some of them
sadly perishing in the battlefield.
I personally witnessed one of them,
and I read the annals of the other.
As per my mother-in-law diary,
"The Wang Yu Jeong Journal",
Great War I was 38 years ago, in 1975.
It broke out when Father-in-law and
Mother-in-law were to get married.
The nations going to war were...
Grandfather, Grandmother,
aunt Wang, Mother-in-law's mother,
Father-in-law, and Mother-in-law.
The background for the Great War is as follows.
Marriage? What marriage?
She is even pregnant,
then what do we do?
Pregnant? What kind of talk is that?
How dare some shitty girls' trade school grad
think of coming into our family?
That's right, eonni. See how the world is now.
Do they all marry just because of pregnancy?
(Eonni - elder sister)
Oh, this makes no sense.
That time, Grandfather and aunt Wang
opposed the marriage.
Though only a country girls' trade school grad,
Mother-in-law was very bright.
Sensitive and vulnerable as Father-in-law was,
Mother-in-law was already in firm control.
The reason why I went to trade school
is not business success,
but was family plight, is what
you should say very clearly.
Father, the reason why she went to
trade school was not business success,
but family plight.
Really?
On one phrase from Grandfather,
the war broke out.
Forget it, forget it.
No need to talk. In our family, I won't have any
marriage to a shitty girls' trade school grad.
- Father!
- Husband...
Shitty trade school for girls?
As for the war, once neighboring countries joined,
the scope expanded.
Who said my daughter went to
a shitty trade school for girls?
It was I who said that,
so what? What?
Who said it's a shitty trade school?
If it's a shitty school, it's a shitty school.
What's the great education do you have?
How great was the school you went to?
I am a Seoul school graduate.
How great was that school, I want to know...
What is this commotion about?
What are you up to?
- Don't do it like this.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Ah, really...
Grandfather and aunt Wang formed
the allied front against the wedding.
Father-in-law and mother-in-law.
Between Grandmother and the joint force with
Mother-in-law's mother, intense war erupted,
that continued for 6 months.
Though eventually the wedding was conducted,
a cold war continued for 2 years,
and Grandmother passed away.
While the official cause
was pancreatic cancer,
there is considerable opinion that
it was due to war-induced stress.
It was a tragedy left behind by Great War I.
You bought pork?
Hurry, put it in. Hurry.
In one week since coming here,
for the first time we're eating hot food.
That's right.
If we only had a small pot
we could've eaten things like this.
Wasn't it good that I asked?
Brat, you better know that
I can do good things.
Really, look at you showing off.
Who was it that caused this all--
I guess not. This is a good day,
so let us not fight.
Yes. When it's a good day like this,
let us really focus on eating kimchi soup.
May be because it's a rich house.
Even the pot looks so tasteful.
It seems it's not made domestically.
Where did the Italian cast-mental pot
that was here, go?
I'm sure it was there earlier.
If it was there earlier, how could it
just walk out and disappear?
What are you looking for there?
The Italian cast-metal pot. I want it for pork stew
but however much I search, it isn't there.
Dad had gone out earlier with
something just like a pot.
Did you go out, taking a pot with you?
Wh... what... well...
Why? Where did you go with that?
Oh... To that... garage.
Why the garage?
You know what kind of pot that is?
Nothing... To cook something, they
wanted to borrow it for some time.
You crazy? It's an Italian cast-metal pot
that even I hardly use.
Go get it back right away!
Tomorrow, I'll go--
Tomorrow? What tomorrow?
It has an enamel coating. If it's used
without a clue, the coating will come off!
You won't get it back right away?
In all-time history, Gil Seon Ja's kimchi soup
today seems like the very best.
Really?
With some pork, we can eat just this.
Hurry, get some rice.
I want to eat in such hurry, my hand shakes!
Isn't it crazy?
Excuse me.
Where's the pot that I gave earlier?
It's here.
Thanks to you, we're making stew.
One moment.
I'm sorry. Saying it is an Italian cast-metal pot,
my wife is flying off the handle.
What do I do about this?
Is that so? Then what to do?
We'll eat right now, wash it,
and send it back with you.
I am really sorry, but it can't wait at all.
Right away now itself,
I'll have to take it back.
Right now itself? It's enough if just
the pork is done. It'll be very quick.
I'm really sorry. Let us pour this somewhere else.
Yikes, it's hot.
Here, napkins.
Then please pour here.
Really... Really sorry about this.
It's enough if just the pork is done.
It'll be done quickly.
I'm really sorry too.
Let me lend you another pot later.
Every day he would ask
if there is any discomfort.
But he won't even wait till
the pork gets cooked?
I want to take the Italian cast-metal pot and
hit that fellow on his head, seriously!
I want to take this cast-metal pot and
hit you on your head, seriously.
I got it back, you know!
Try this stunt ever again and see!
What's wrong?
What?
Following the regional war of the afternoon,
the tensions continued through the evening.
If this continues, couldn't a 3rd Great War erupt?
I worried.
That is because wars always break out
due to trivial matters.
It was the same with Great War II.
Great War II broke out 6 years ago.
The nations at war included...
Grandfather,
Father-in-law,
Mother-in-law,
Brother-in-law,
Sister-in-law,
my wife,
Gyu Yeong,
and aunt Wang.
This was war that I also experienced.
Cheol Min scratching Gyu Ho's face
sounded the sirens of Great War II.
Gyu Yeong, take this thing and
get rid of it somewhere.
See what the son of a bitch did
to this perfectly good cup--
It was a dog brought in by Grandfather that
Mother-in-law asked Gyu Yeong to get rid of.
Gyu Yeong brought the dog back to the house,
and that dog promptly scratched
Gyu Ho who was hardly 2 years old.
While that forms the background
of the expansion of the war,
the real reason was the resentment that had
developed among the family members.
Is it a boy that you would ask
to get rid of a dog?
Is he stupid not to do it?
You think a boy would throw away a dog?
Gyu Ho nearly lost an eye!
Yeah... That's kinda true.
Why were you throwing my dog
just as you like?
- That dog broke a cup..
- Mom, I am not done with you!
- Playing with cups is normal?
- You know how much that cup was worth?
You brat, all day long you bother the dog.
Why do you hit me?
In 2 years I will be 60!
Grandfather, what are you doing?
What is this you are trying?
How can you do that with Grandfather?
- Is it Gyu Yeong that you'd ask to throw a dog?
- I never never asked him to bring it back.
It was he who brought it back.
Aren't you tired of seeing
that dog all day long?
The war was truly intense.
The war that extended to 2 weeks,
had the house regimented in trenches.
The public sentiment was divided into the allied
forces and the united front, in a jittery state.
Then it happened.
Oppa.
Look at your plight! Doesn't a daughter-in-law
even give you some hot food to eat?
You are the culprit here! You are.
Aunt, why are you poking your nose
into my family matters?
Say what?
You asked for it!
Aunt Wang would soon leave this world.
While the official cause was high blood pressure,
in the final analysis, it was war-induced anger,
a tragedy left behind by Great War II.
What?
How far did you go?
I'm almost at the restroom. Why?
I am dying to pee!
What can I do about it?
I asked you to come with me.
Even to wash dishes, I have to go away.
Come even now, you want to?
Forget it. I'm hanging up.
Hello.
Is it 010434267?
CEO sir?
Yes.
Have you been well?
Yes. How about you, CEO sir?
Do you want to buy ice cream and come over?
I am by myself now.
I can't. They won't let anybody in there.
Once you return home, I will buy you
a lot of ice cream.
That means... you should recover quickly,
so you can come home.
Yes, I understand.
Shall we try cajoling Na Jin A?
That school grad intern?
Why?
She is staying at CEO No's family's garage.
Then it should work.
That girl?
But she always seemed like trouble, to me.
That too, as she was CEO No's pick,
he was always guarding her, right?
Moving into the garage with nowhere to go, was
because the Adviser offered her shelter, as well.
Well, that's true.
If I say I was once close to her dad,
it is possible to fool her, however.
Isn't that dangerous?
If she joins our side and screws it up,
it's us who'll be finished.
Isn't there a way to cleanly
fool her into doing it?
How about making use of a pretty boy?
Pretty boy? Who?
Hell it's not you, is it?
I am in no mood for jokes now,
so if it's you, you are a dead man!
Seeing him all tongue-tied,
it seems he did mean himself.
You blockhead, seriously!
Tell me then. You meant yourself, really?
No.
Then, who?
Won Bin.
Do you know Won Bin?
You know him well enough to ask?
It is not like that.
How about just requesting him, I felt...
You twerp... seriously!
I'm sorry.
Hey, you better stop right there!
Sorry.
What happened?
The shrimp hit him, it seems.
What's it? What happened with him?
He did get hit... by the shrimp.
This nitwit of no use...
After dinner, do you eat Chaga mushrooms
every day?
They say it has good anti-cancer effects.
From now on it is really important.
For me, this is a fork on the road
leading to life or death, really.
Is it that serious?
Of course. The way I think now,
if it can cure cancer, I could cook and eat
even the paper you blew your nose into.
This twerp even talks weird stuff now.
Isn't it just a metaphor for my feeling of urgency?
What's wrong?
Father, you just carry on taking care of
Cheol Min, who's most precious to you.
=Hello everybody. Asteroid 2013QR3 seems to=
=be maintaining a 31 000 kilometer distance,=
=and rotating around the earth.=
=As estimating planetary calendars=
=is impossible due to the asteroid,=
=lately the weather bureau has been almost=
=unable to predict high and low tides times.=
=Thus incidents with people caught in=
=tidal mudflats, have increased a lot.=
=As the tides come and go as it likes,=
=if you work in mudflats and feel a high tide,=
=it is best to escape to the seaside quickly.=
=While you escape, rather than run like this,=
=if you can run like this, it will help you=
=run at least a little bit faster.=
=This was Today's Asteroid Update.=
They must be crazy. This is all news?
You can say that.
This messed up world feels a bit odd--
What are you trying to do, now?
Just now, weren't you seeing to your business?
We said you can't step into the garden,
how can you do your business here?
It was the lesser business.
Lesser business or bigger business,
we had an agreement!
If you don't keep it,
what about how my situation will be?
For the pot incident, I'm really sorry!
But you did go too far here.
If you say it like that, then
you really go too far too.
Huh?
I really hadn't planned to tell you this but...
Honestly, when Jin A's dad was alive,
think how much he contributed to the company.
Think how much he helped you.
But, though I'm thankful for you
letting us stay in the garage,
is this even letting people live?
In the garage, is there a bathroom,
or is there anything at all?
Everyday we have to walk 1 km
to some big store,
wash our faces, get our business done,
wash our dishes and come back.
To wash clothes, we have to even
take a bus and go to a laundromat.
Is that how it is?
But I had asked you to tell me if there was
anything inconvenient, then why?
Even if I had told you,
it wouldn't work out, right?
Though I thought I would tell you,
I just couldn't tell you.
What is this you are...
Excuse me for saying this, but
it's your wife who decides it all.
Not everything, you know...
On the bathroom issue also,
isn't it pointless to--
Please go pee. Go.
Pardon?
Please pee in our bathroom, I said.
If your wife knows of it, what to do?
It's me who will talk to her.
Come inside and please pee.
Su Yeong, why aren't you back?
How is Min Hyeok today?
You seem to really like injeolmi.
(Traditional Korean rice-cakes)
Oh yes. It's way too tasty.
Honey. I told Soe Dol's wife here, to use
our bathroom as she wishes from now.
What?
Come on. For a bathroom, they have to walk
a kilometer and find one in some big store.
Sister-in-law, come in and take care of it.
It is fine.
What is fine?
When they were let into the garage, they were
not to step in the garden, so what're you saying?
Isn't the bathroom a different matter?
Please go pee. It's all right.
I'm sorry. You can't. Please leave.
She just needs the bathroom for a moment.
Even that we cannot allow?
You really won't show a human side?
That's right. It's not right to be
mean to good people.
Go in and pee. Pee as much as you want.
What pee? Peeing is not the problem.
The problem is other people coming and going
as they please at our house.
That's right. As mom said, this is not
an issue of whether she pees or not.
I feel uneasy.
There is much division.
Finally, are we at the prologue of Great War III?
Why are you stepping up?
Are you the house-owner here?
What kind of talk is that from you?
Hurting my feelings...
You better stop that.
Go in and pee. Just as you like, pee.
You cannot. I'm sorry, but please leave.
That's right.
Who is she?
Damn it!
You are deliberately doing this with me?
All through from daytime?
What did I deliberately do?
Come on, you're really too much.
What's it? Why are they like this?
It's about the people from the garage.
They want to even use our bathroom.
We are on the verge of Great War III.
In every Great War, one person's
life has to be lost.
The people in this place aren't
even trying to fool anybody...
Where did she go?
Mom.
Mom!
How can you do that to me in front of outsiders?
I am the head of the household here!
How can you trample on my self-respect?
I am the head of the household.
Your mom says it can't be done?
This can gradually spiral out of control
into a Great War III.
Grandmother, a text came in.
That is mine. Give it to me.
Just at the right time, there comes
a text for Father-in-law.
That finally was the starting gunshots of
Great War III breaking out.
Hey Fatso, here's the phone number
of the Choe Yeong you miss.
010-3277. She is in Seoul.
Try calling her up. haha.
Wait a moment!
What is this?
Choe Yeong's phone number.
Have you heard any news on Choe Yeong?
Would you perhaps know her contact details?
This is what you've been up to lately?
Asking for Choe Yeong's contact details?
No. That...
- Dad! What is this about?
- You asked for a woman's phone number?
What's wrong? If he recently asked for
somebody's phone number, what's the big deal?
Father, You are now
siding with your son?
That just won't work.
A married man. This is just
my friend doing some joke!
It's the truth. Believe me.
My friend is playing a joke.
Hey, what is this you're doing?
It is Great War III.
Let go! Let go!
It is just my friend doing a joke.
Dad has fainted.
What's wrong?
Dad!
A victim will eventually emerge
in Great War III.
This time, that was me.
Dad, please don't die... Dad!
Are you all right?
- Dad.
- Honey!
I was a war casualty.
For 1 minute 39 seconds.
Great War III, with the moniker "Garage Folks'
Toilet Liberation Struggle", was extraordinary.
I died but was revived.
Father-in-law was kicked out in the dead of night
wearing a sleeveless running shirt.
Go out right now! I hate
even seeing your mug.
Honey...
It's a misunderstanding. It is.
I only casually asked. That bastard Horsehead
made a big deal of nothing, honey!
Sister-in-law.
Jin A.
Asleep? Sorry.
Just for a bit... open the door.
Please come in.
Mom. Mom.
What? Why?
What's wrong, in the middle of the night?
Is it okay for me to stay here briefly?
What?
But why are you in just a running shirt?
I had a bit of a situation.
- Is there anything uncomfortabl--
- None. Nothing.
There is nothing.
You must be cold. Please come over.
Will that be okay?
For spoiling your sleep...
I'm really sorry.
- Nothing we can do about it.
- It's all right.
It seems you have nowhere to go.
Then, excuse my manners...
This mat feels quite warm.
By chance, if anything bothers you,
please let me know... any time.
-=Next Episode Preview=-
This is a split-up?
How dare this lowlife...
But how did you see that he was the thief?
I can hear the sound of what others are thinking.
What bullcrap is that?
He must be somewhere here.
What hellhole is he living at?
Take the meat out and just give the soup.
How did you know that I eat it like that?
Didn't I tell you,
that I can see what all you're thinking
by just looking at the eyes.
As I see it, she has now got another man.
I will ask without beating around the bush.
You found someone you like?
Yeah.
Oh my God!
But when I am with you, grandfather,
it feels like I have got a family.
Punk.
Who are you?
Stop playing hard to get,
and properly reject her.
It feels like I have no such ideas.
Why are you sitting there instead
of finding shelter somewhere?
Because of the rain I cannot tell you no.
Grandpa, are you a fool?
-=Episode 14=-
-=Great War II (2007)=-
-=Then 2 years old=-