You're here?
Yes.
Ever since your younger grandson was found,
you have been beaming.
Leave aside the beam on my face
to keep beaming...
What is it that led you to be at the police station?
For someone who is a lawyer...
I am sorry.
Will Bo Yeong let you back in now?
What kind of absurd misunderstanding was that?
I am sorry.
Looks like you are kicked out from home.
No, well...
Gyu Ho, let's go now.
Let me finish this. Just ten minutes.
When you leave, take some appetizers along.
Yes.
Grandpa. New Zealand...
What kind of country is it?
Why do you ask?
As we have a classmate sent from New Zealand,
our assignment is to learn of New Zealand.
New Zealand... is the country next to Australia.
Beside Australia?
Where is Australia?
Beside New Zealand.
Then New Zealand is?
Beside Australia.
Awesome.
What is it?
I asked where New Zealand is, and
Grandpa says it's beside Australia,
and Australia is beside New Zealand!
It's in the South Pacific. It's Oceania.
What about New Zealand, suddenly?
My assignment is to get to know New Zealand.
It's Grandfather that you asked about that?
It's a country famous for its sheep.
They primarily rely on stock-farming.
And they speak English.
Lord of the Rings was filmed
in New Zealand, right?
It's the southern hemisphere, so the
seasons are opposite to our country's.
If we have winter, it's summer there.
If we have summer, it's winter there.
That's right. That kind of country.
Why are you asking Grandpa on assignments?
Give it a rest!
Huh? Rest what?
Why did you ask him twice asking grandpa?
What is it that you know so much of?
Did I say that I know something?
Asking Grandfather about a distant country...
He could well ask me, right?
Then, should he ask a shitty female
trade school grad like you?
He keeps harping on it... really!
Why is my school a shitty female trade school?
Please leave it that.
Hold on a bit...
You are so ready to say that
my school and I are ignorant!
Father-n-law, what, you are
more cultured than me?
Better than you.
Better than me? Oh really?
The banking friends I meet are
all alumni of famous colleges.
They are all shocked seeing me.
Why shocked?
You jump out from behind to shock them?
You know a little about real estate and stocks,
so you think you know a lot more than me?
It is not just real estate and stocks, that
I happen to know a lot more than you.
In the few things I am about to say now,
if you know of any one thing, pray tell.
Enviro-hormone. Sociopath. LA Dodgers.
You know any of that?
I know all of that--
I know all that. Why?
Then what is Enviro-hormon?
Are you now doing a test on me?
Obviously you don't know.
What don't I know?
I know but I don't care to tell. So what?
Those with true knowledge will not
show off like you everywhere!
Even if they know, they'll only keep quiet.
If you did that, that will be nice!
Then, let me also ask you something.
Do you know what is a yellow bird song?
I'll tell you of intellect. Knowing a few
buzz words is not what intellect is.
Historical classics...
I do know the Yellow bird song.
How would I not know?
What is it?
The yellow bird song by King Yu Ri, right?
Mirthfully fly the orioles, male-female pair to nest.
Lonely as I feel, whom do I go back to nest with?
Isn't that the one?
I finished it. Dad. Now we can go.
Okay.
Please leave it at that. We will leave now.
- Take care
- See you again. See you again.
Good bye.
Hola, Jun Hyeok.
I have to greet you differently.
In future when I see you, I will be affectionate
with you. No objection, right?
We have no memories of us playing
together in childhood, right?
When you were 4 years and me 5 years,
you had disappeared, you know.
As for memories of you, at one time we had all
the family gathered at seaside and had sashimi.
May be it was vinegar sauce? It fell in your eyes
and you cried loudly, as I vaguely remember.
That apart, I don't remember anything.
Let's enjoy it from here on.
If anybody bullies me, guard me well.
Isn't that the younger brother's duty?
Right?
Shouldn't we get Jun Hyeok
to go for his studies?
If he is to work in the company in future,
he needs to have an education isn't it?
About the DNA testing hospital.
Why did we do it at such a small place?
Was it you who asked for it?
No but, rather than do that...
with Min Hyeok in this state,
should we first have him learn managing?
Why weren't you putting some care into
where such an important test is done?
What?
Looking at Min Hyeok's condition, shouldn't we
let him join, and formally have him manage,
for him to quickly learn the business?
Son-in-law Gim says there was a
case of mistakes in test results.
Studying... can be done on the side
as he work at the company, right?
Why aren't you hearing what I say
and just talking by yourself?
Look who's talking, aren't you not hearing me
and talking by yourself?
Fine. Why do I even bother to talk?
Good, then. Try not to talk.
Ignoramus, really!
How dare she disgrace people like that!
Your daughter-in-law is smart
and knows a lot too.
Knows a lot, my foot! Coming out of a
shit-bucket female trade school, what can--
Whether a shit-bucket trade school grad,
or a piss-bucket trade school grad,
she knows quite a bit.
It's because you're ignorant,
that you see it that way.
I should show her what a
real intellectual can do.
What a real intellectuals can do?
What then? Write a Chinese poem
to show her that true ability?
Chinese poem?
But you don't have such ability, you know.
So just stay put.
Old brat. You think I am like you?
Ignorant fellow.
Look at this!... You open your mouth
and it's "ignorant fellow".
How the hell am I ignorant?
Aren't you ignorant, old brat?
You were No. 1 ranked from the back in school.
Shut up. You this...
It's because you're like this, that you
have no friends. You know that?
What? My friends have all died.
That's why I have no friends.
Why wouldn't I have friends?
Yeah, you don't have!
You say you had, you fart?
What?
A brat 3 years younger than me
but I still play with him... Rascal!
You call me older-brother
from now on, you old brat!
You are only older by 3, but if you keep this up,
I won't be friends with you anymore!
This... Forget it. Forget about it.
Forget it, fine... you old brat.
This damn shit...
Crap face.
Can't you wait just a little bit more?
I might be able to get a hold of it soon.
It's still a deposit of 50 million, right?
Still into wishful thinking, really?
What?
Are you going out somewhere?
Yeah.
Where?
It's just...
Taking young sir to the departmental store.
The aunt wanted some clothes
to be bought for him.
Yes.
Please get in. Aunt will be out real soon.
Okay.
So you are off to the departmental
store for clothes?
Now on you'll be like rich kids,
only in brand-name items!
No. I'm not.
There comes the "no" syndrome.
Right. When are you treating
me to the rib-eye steak?
What?
See this noble-fellow...
Like you're hearing it the first time.
Somebody who will soon wear
branded clothes worth millions
won't keep a promise to buy rib-eye steaks?
You will keep it, right?
Yeah.
When?
Soon.
When is soon?
What month? What day? What time? What min?
Fine. Buy it whenever, for me.
You don't buy, you're dead.
You alma mater female trade school, ignorant...
(Supposedly in Chinese?)
You, You alma mater trade school female...
This does not rhyme.
If she even knows the Yellow bird song,
This is too obvious for her.
You brat, now you're even
stealing my credit card.
That's why I ask why you took
my card away?
Why do you stop studying
just as you wish?
Didn't I say I'm now mulling over it?
Give me my bag. Now.
No way. Tomorrow I'm returning it.
Don't be like this. It's a limited edition.
Mom, if you share it, won't that do?
No way.
Hey, really...
- Not giving it back?
- What is this?
- So you want this?
- Ah, yikes, ah, ah...
You brat, seriously!
Must you hit somebody's head?
So what if I hit? If you do
what invites a hit, I will hit.
[Spanish] It's bad. Very bad.
I hate you, and you're stupid.
What?
[Spanish] Why not? You are very bad and stupid.
And you don't go. Okay?
You swore at me, right? You brat.
Su Yeong.
What? What do you want to do,
learning Spanish?
I want to piss off your mom.
To help you take revenge.
But when she can't even understand?
That's why she'll be more pissed off!
Didn't you just do that?
That's right. With those with crappy education,
what's most detestable is a foreign language.
[Spanish] La Escuela...
(The school)
Where is Jun Hyeok?
Washing his face. He will be coming soon.
The bag... In the end you returned it?
You thought I wouldn't?
Shouldn't the newspaper be left in the living room?
Why did you take it into the bedroom?
Yeah. Why did you take it in? Why?
I'll bring it out later. Why are you adding
to the confusion? You don't even read it.
I read it. Why wouldn't I?
[Spanish] La escuela pobre como caca.
(Your school is poor as shit!)
Huh?
What did you say?
Awesome!
You just spoke to me in Spanish?
What did you say?
I won't tell you.
How was that?
Jun Hyeok.
After having breakfast, go with me
to the company.
Pardon?
This is a working day for me.
Isn't it good for you also to have a look
at how the company is?
Wear the suit we bought yesterday.
Why take him there already?
What, why not?
Hello.
Sure.
This is the new office building
since our merger this time.
Hello.
Toy companies are in general small in size.
But our toy company is seen as a large firm.
You have come over!
There are no problems, right?
Ah, yes.
Why did you come to the company? If there's
time, shouldn't you be finding the USB quickly?
It's not in the room.
Did you look through the clothes worn
when No Min Hyeok fell?
Yes. It wasn't there.
Did you check all the clothes
before they were laundered?
Yes.
Why isn't it there if you checked through?
I'm going insane, really!
Isn't it because you keep thinking it isn't there
that it's going like this?
Have a positive mindset that you will find it
and look for it again!
Director O. You're not getting out?
This is a life or death matter for me, damn it!
Director O.
What's wrong?
Not getting out? It's the 7th floor.
Yes.
A bit... strange, don't you think so?
Stop saying that. How often do
test results turn out wrong?
I have to go to a get-together.
Why haven't you brought the newspaper out still?
Isn't it here?
[Spanish] La escuela pobre como caca.
Since earlier, what's this you have been saying?
Whatever it is, even if I explain it,
you just won't get it.
As you have no foreign language basics.
La escuela pobre como caca.
Excuse me please. I am sorry.
Excuse me please. Coming through.
How come you had to be here?
Just like that...
What's with this outfit?
You were always dressed like a bum
and I had never quite noticed,
but now that you look like this...
Huh?
You look more like a bum!
Already learning management?
Whoa...
It's not like that.
I came just for a look.
Hey, what are you doing? The director is waiting.
Yes.
Put that back up. Hurry!
Hey... What are you doing? Hey!
I am sorry.
Could you please stop that?
What?
La escuela pobre como caca.
Caca?
Shit?
I knew as much.
La escuela pobre como caca.
La escuela.
Shit-like school?
Shit-bucket girls' trade school?
I knew that would be it.
Fine. So this is how it will be?
An eye for an eye. A tooth for a tooth.
Seeing you come with me to the company...
I don't know how happy I am...
I had a cancer surgery a little while back.
This stuff... is good for the body, they said.
Now I've got to see you after 20 years, like this...
I should at least see your marriage and die...
Why am I like this suddenly?
They say anal hair grows if you cry while laughing.
It's if you laugh while you cry that it grows, I hear.
Anyway, studying is also the same,
with a lot to do up ahead.
For the moment, just do what you want to do,
and just live free and easy.
Yes.
Really, all these years, you must've had
things you wanted to do but couldn't.
What is it that you want to do the most?
What?
I have a friend whom I had given a lot of trouble.
Is that so?
And so?
So...
I wish to repay that friend.
Repay?
How so?
- Meat.
- Meat?
Yes. Meat.
May be buying some beef would be nice...
Buy it, buy it. Isn't it fine to just buy it?
You have no money, is it?
Shouldn't you have... just told me earlier?
For the moment, if you need to spend on it,
do it with this.
I'll return it to you right after
I buy the meat.
No need. You just keep it.
Shouldn't you be a bit careful?
I am sorry about that.
What a pity!
He gave you a credit card?
Yes.
That old scrooge?
Wow, he really loves his son or what?
A fellow who borrows 1000 Wons from a contract
worker and won't repay even at end-of-contract.
Is it okay to take and spend it?
Spend, spend.
He is such a miser, but you
won't believe how rich he is.
If you take a scoop of water from
the Pacific Ocean, is it noticeable?
Why is the TV always on with no one watching?
Switching it off.
What's your problem?
[Spanish] La escuela pobre como caca.
You love to say "shit-bucket
girls' trade school", I see.
I have no foreign language basics and
can't understand it, you think?
Just surfing the internet for some
self-study is enough to figure it out.
What? What did you say?
You didn't get what the basics-less me said?
[Spanish] Comportarse bien, por favor.
What was she just saying?
Better not to know.
Knowing will only make you angry.
What is it? What? What was she saying?
Yes, CEO sir.
How have you been lately?
Seeing NarARa Superboard, and studying.
(Korean animation, circa 1992)
Right. Starting yesterday, I'm writing a diary.
Wow, really?
Is it fun to do?
It must be a diary to show the doctor?
Yes. Shall I read it for you?
Yes, I'm curious about how interesting it is.
November 11. Clear skies.
Ate a meal. What did I eat?
I had some soup.
After that, I watched NarARa Superboard.
How many episodes did I see?
I saw 3 of them.
Then the nurse nuna came over.
(Nuna - Elder girl or sister)
Which nuna was it?
It was Pak Sueng Hui nuna who came in.
Have you had dinner?
No. Not yet.
Yes. It was very interesting.
Next time read more for me. You must, okay?
Okay.
Let's go out.
I will buy you rib-eye steaks.
Really?
I am finally getting to eat rib-eye steaks?
What? Rib-eye steak?
Why rib-eye steak?
Ajumoni also come with us.
Okay if I come too?
What are you doing?
[Spanish] Compartarse bien, por favor.
Will you stop it, please?
I am also going to do some Spanish.
Though a shit-bucket girl's trade school grad
with no foreign language basics,
learning by myself is quite easy.
[Spannish] Compartarse bien, por favor.
Let's have a go at it, is that it?
You think I can't do it, as I'm 90 years old?
[Spanish] Compartarse bien, por favor.
Fine! You just watch!
I'll show you how far a shit-bucket girls' trade
school grad can hang with me on this.
Su Yeong. Get the Spanish book and come........
You'll get a headache this way. Enough, Grandpa.
What enough? When she's messing with me,
will I say enough?
You, don't try stop me.
-=You have ignorance. I'm educated=-
[Spanish] Tu tienes ignorancia. Soy educado.
Why are you messing with him?
Grandpa is crazily learning Spanish.
I'm sure he is. I'm not stopping, right?
-=I have no ignorance. I'm erudite.=-
[Spanish] No tengo ignorancia. Soy erudito.
Sorry that even Mom came along.
Did I bother you by coming along?
No, you didn't. I know how much
food I have eaten from you.
Naturally I should invite you.
Welcome.
For you.
Just briefly... to the bathroom...
Oh... What?
I'm sorry, but other than the friend I earlier
told you of, one more friend has come.
There is no way... but to get...
one more order of meat, I think.
So what about it?
Even if I get one more order, will it be okay?
Get it, get it.
Ah, yes. Thank you very much.
That kid. Maybe from how he grew up?
He takes it all seriously.
Then, should we order it?
Over here. Rib-eye steak, 3 orders.
Sure.
Not filling enough?
No. It's all right.
It's not quite that filling.
Meat ordered by headcount
is never filling enough.
I need a brief trip to the restroom.
Yeah, what?
It's that...
I'm sorry...
but I wondered if I could order
a little bit more of meat.
Just get more. It's fine to get more, right?
We've had 3 orders. Another 3 more orders
will be needed, it seemed...
Oh, sure! Just order and have it.
Thank you very much!
So the meat is not filling, right?
Over here... please get us 3 more
orders of rib-eye steaks.
Sure, I've got it.
If we're ordering meat, shouldn't we order some
staple too? Cold noodles for me. What about you?
Not sure.
I need to... just briefly...
I'm not having it. We have 3 more orders meat
coming. How do we eat staples too? I won't.
Can't eat anymore?
And you youngster?
I am all right too.
Really?
Then I'll also have to eat just the meat.
- Weren't you going to the washroom?
- No.
Really, you fed us so well!
It's nothing.
Look at the card, it's a gold card!
Whatever you say, rich people are different!
It's nothing.
So great to be out, after so long!
Even better that us 3 are together like this.
I am really feeling like having a drink!
There, again! What drunk act
do you want to do now?
It's not any liquor to drown sorrows.
At that kind of a place, in a happy mood,
and having a glass of wine--
Stop saying such useless stuff. Yeah right, wine...
As I'm sorry to keep calling you,
I'm texting you instead.
I'm really sorry, but my friends
want to have some wine.
Would it perhaps be fine to have the drinks?
PS. If we add appetizers, the estimate
is 100000 Wons, I think. (~US$ 85)
The kid! Come on...
May be from living a hard life?
He thinks small, eh?
Whom does he take after?
Drink, drink!
I can't even talk about that? Damn you...
Should we go and have some wine?
Really?
Yes.
Let's just go to that bar.
Wow. This is what they say is
the might of the rich, really!
Aren't you supposed to be back home quickly?
No.
Grandfather?
He will be coming soon.
Suddenly, with all the Spanish study,
he's a bit out of it.
What's with this sudden fascination with Spanish?
Your mother too...
What else can it be? Those two are
in a battle of pride using that.
Over this while, you both learned a
new way of talking? Awesome!
[Spanish] blah blah... how dare... blah blah.
blah blah... I'm smarter... blah blah.
Isn't that enough? Is it some 3rd-rate
foreign film we're are watching here?
I seem to be a bit drunk.
I should stop drinking now.
Yeah. You had one glass after another from
earlier on. It was no small sipping.
So much trouble. Taking a beggar
mom and daughter to eat good food.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Having let some fluids out,
I'm a little bit sober.
Drink some more, then.
Huh? Yeah.
Come on, let's go.
Wait a moment.
Youngster...
I have a favor to ask from you.
What is it?
Well... aren't you quite well off?
I'll repay you in a jiffy, but lend a 50 million--
(~US$ 45K)
What are you doing?
You...
Stop with that, really!
So scared, I can hardly talk...
My heart is... jumping, o haeyo....
If you... would know it--
Don't sing anymore.
What? Aigoo, aigoo, aigoo...
[Spanish] La escuela como caca.
comportarse bien, por favor.
That whole while, their gestures were great.
Live long enough, and one
gets to see the wonder
of the wife and her 90 years old
father-in-law fighting in Spanish.
[Spanish]
The credit card!
The card isn't there?
This is weird!
Earlier after having wine,
didn't you use it to pay the bill?
Yes.
Just now when you held mom,
you must have dropped it!
I am all clear-headed after the wine buzz.
I'm really sorry.
What's there to be sorry?
Quickly report the loss and it'll be fine.
What did he say?
It is fine. He asked to report the loss now itself.
Where's ajumeoni?
I found it! I found it!
It got dropped at the shop front there.
You need to take this.
No need. He said it's already invalid,
so I will need to re-apply.
Really? Then, I'll keep it as a
memento of finding it.
Thank you for today.
Thanks to the rich family friend,
I had my first rib-eye steak.
Take care, go in.
Hey, Na Jin A.
Just tell me anytime in future.
Tell what?
Rib-eye steak. Just tell me if you want to eat it.
I'll treat you anytime.
Once more.
Just as expected.
Ajumma, you are not alone here.
Please wait a bit. Just one last time.
Just once more.
I beg you, please work. I beg you.
Grandfather is still studying Spanish?
Yeah. Mom too.
What are these two up to, really?
Grandpa and Mom are studying even harder
just to piss off each other.
Just like Columbus who headed for India
but discovered the New World,
both unexpectedly discovered
their own new interests in life.
Grandpa at 92 years old, discovered
his dormant desire for knowledge.
Mom was attracted to
Spanish art and culture
[Spanish] I am a boy. You are a girl.
I would like it if I can learn dancing.
What kind of dancing?
A dance that is suitable for this outfit.
Someone had sent me this from Spain.
As it's really pretty...
Isn't it Lady Boss?
Hello.
How come you are here?
I'm a member here.
You should be telling me, why you would be here?
- The capital is Palma de Mallorca. The languages
are Catalan, although we speak in Mallorquin,
and Castellano, which is Spanish.
- I have a question. Is Don Quijote the best
Spanish novel?
Caramba! You fool!
-=Next Episode Preview=-
The rumors on the CEO No are that
he dies, he's gone crazy, he had a
sex change operation, etc.
I'm looking for a job.
Just work for my family.
Won't that be enough?
How does one looking so
perfectly all right be an idiot--
I have been so worried.
- I'll be sure to come back.
- What?
I wrote down all what you need to do.
You should finish before noon.
Rest and do at the same time.
Support yourself with this and try to walk.
Left leg, left leg.
Perhaps the house is too big.
There are lots to do.
Hurry up bring the rag, ajumma.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry.
-=Behave yourself right... Please=-
[Spanish] Comportarse bien, por favor.