Movie premiere?
One university seonbae has
became a film director.
(Seonbae - Senior in college, school or work)
It's an invitation letter but
there is a VIP reception.
(Seonbae - Senior in college, school or work)
for interacting with the director
prior to premiere.
(Seonbae - Senior in college, school or work)
You have a film director
amongst your seonbaes?
Yes, he always had a camera during school days.
He was bound to become one.
What movie is it?
"Intro to Civil Engineering"?
Intro to Civil Engineering?
I had seen that advertisement.
That movie seems to be rather so so...
- Mother. I want to see the movie too.
- Me too! Me too!
You guys can't. You can't watch an adults' movie.
What's an adults' movie?
A movie where man and woman
kiss a lot, that's an adult's movie.
Kissing too much will cause tooth decay.
You know what?
If you watch the stars with an open mouth for
an hour at night, you won't get tooth decay.
I checked into it.
Shut up! Red Sun.
It's true, you know!
What happens when DNA test
results are out tomorrow?
What the hell have you done these 2 days?
You still haven't gone inside the room?
Last night I went in and searched for a while,
but it isn't there.
Searched a while and it isn't there?
Where's your sense of responsibility?
You need to keep looking till it's brought out!
How can a young guy be
so lacking in a sense of justice?
You don't want the money?
If successful, you get 10 million Wons.
(~US$ 8500)
Not worked up? Only I'm worked up? Only I am?
I understand.
Tonight is the final chance. Don't forget.
Together, we will punish those evil forces.
They are not so bad to be
called evil forces, are they?
Oh yeah? Look what you are saying now!
Since you are finessing it for them,
you are growing close, right?
You don't even know how bad they are.
How bad are they?
What do you mean, how bad?
Listen properly. To say how bad they are...
Forget it.
Fine, I'll say just this much.
They are so bad that it's so tough to be
so bad as to be as bad as them!
Understand?
So tonight, without fail find the USB.
But can I ask you just one thing?
What?
What happened to their real son?
The theater itself has a third-rate feel.
No such talk when we meet him, okay?
No Bo Yeong!
Seonbae.
You are really just the same as in those days!
No, may be you got even younger?
Come on, I'm an ajumma too now.
(Ajumma - old lady, aunt)
Anyway, congrats on becoming a director!
This is my husband.
Hello. I'm Gim Do Sang.
To actually meet a film director like this...
It's an honor.
It's you who is here to watch it.
I'm really happy!
Of course I must come to see.
Whose movie is it after all?
The other guys?
Not yet. Hey if you're here,
that's enough, no?
Director.
One moment.
I have to go. Let's catch-up later.
We'll be enjoying the film.
Why only a nod towards me?
Had I known it, I too would've only nodded.
Director, we hear that this movie
is your autobiography.
Is that true?
Yes, a large part was from my personal
experiences. You can say that.
On the creation of the movie, we can't avoid
mentioning its connection to memories.
May I ask you what that would imply?
Tough to say...
Don't certain songs lead to special
memories with certain people?
Me as well, as I hear something memorable,
I'll automatically think of those times.
Perhaps that is what it means?
Differently from other 'first love' movies,
a lot of kissing scenes are there, it seems?
The first time one falls in love,
is there anything but kissing?
Was I the only one like that?
Right on, really.
Sure sounds logical. Since we are on this topic...
may be we would want to
listen to those stories?
You went out somewhere?
What about you? Going to the loo?
Stop worrying. I haven't used
more than 5 pieces of tissues.
You sure? Seeing that fishy look, you must've
wasted many rounds of tissues.
Already like a house-owner?
Test results will be out tomorrow, right?
It's the night before your fate gets set.
You must be very nervous?
- No.
- Like you aren't!
If you are the real son, you know you have to
buy me rib-eye steaks, right?
Since it will be released tomorrow morning,
why can't you tell us now?
Just because it's Sunday,
it's so hard to take a peek?
Why is this hospital like this?
Other hospitals only take 1 day,
but you take 3 days.
You're here?
Yes.
It's fine.
Sit down.
You're here?
My waist is all healed.
How could it?
He had an injection.
It's all thanks to you that it has healed, I think.
This kid massaged me with lots of care.
When I had my body bath 2 days ago,
he didn't even sleep and kept me company.
Should I trying carrying you now?
You need to get completely healed.
I said I'm completely healed. See this.
Hey, hey, hey. Stop it, or you'll get hurt again.
Hurt? What hurt?
- Are you all right?
- Father!
Just teasing you!
The for-ever grouchy grandfather has
suddenly turned naughty since you came.
You rascal, calling a 90 years old father
a naughty kid makes sense?
Wasn't that a good thing I said?
This is an autobiographical movie?
Really crappy!
Keep quiet.
Those are the times that create memories?
What the hell...
I too like memory creation so much.
I too have songs that contain memories.
All those good songs are now ruined!
Ah, damn it!
You better stop it now...
Is that what a movie is?
Even I can film something better than that.
But, whom are you chatting with
since a while back?
That director seonbae.
When I said I enjoyed the movie,
he asked me back for a drink.
What drink?
Directors should film good movies.
This one was like dog shit.
I asked you to give it a rest!
What movie-criticism is this?
Longer than even the movie...
I mean, a movie should at least
have the basics--
I'm sleepy. Don't talk to me.
=Ever since the asteroid appeared,=
=violent crime rates have risen by 40%.=
=The problem of a Judgment Day cult=
=religion forming is serious as well.=
=This time, due to rumors that the asteroids'=
=infrared rays are beneficial to health,=
=haven't there been more people taking=
=nude asteroid-light baths at night?=
=Yes, it's correct. It we go to=
=the Han River banks at night,=
=people who have stripped naked, and=
=all spread out, is a common sight.=
=Is it that even underwear aren't worn?=
=The majority aren't wearing them.=
=Presumably it's due to the rumor that the faint=
=infrared rays are very good for them.=
The world is getting weirder with these
total crazies everywhere or what?
Can't say you're wrong.
You found it?
Not yet.
I'm off to sleep.
Have a good night.
But, the test result will be out tomorrow?
Yes.
This kid is Jun Hyeok, for sure.
I just know it all.
I'm retiring too.
See you... tomorrow.
For the DNA test results come out, it will take
a few days, over the weekend.
While you enjoy the life of the rich till then,
help me with this one thing on the side.
You earn money, and you do a good deed.
How about it?
You are Jun Hyeok, am I right?
Alone all these years...
How scary and difficult it must've been!
I am sorry for not finding you.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
The real son is already dead.
Even then they keep looking.
Those nasty people are a terror,
sticking with it for that son.
If you come like now as if nothing happened, to
stay by me like nothing happened, it'll be nice.
By chance if you are that real son,
then treat me to some good beef!
Rib-eye steak.
I haven't had it even once.
This sure feels strange.
3rd rate films. Eclectic films. Nonsensical films.
The No Bo Yeong who hates
those 3 types of films,
doesn't have a word to say about
a film that fits all 3 types.
Just because the director is a seonbae?
Is that all it is?
It's you who is here to watch it.
I'm really happy!
Of course I must come to see.
Whose movie is it after all?
If you're here, that's enough, no?
Coffee!
What's it? Ping pong?
Don't change it. Isn't it fun to watch?
I took part in the ping pong team in college.
Strangely, I find engineering grads cool.
Like civil engineers.
They build bridges, and roads!
Don't they seem high-scale?
You mean this is all coincidental?
Wait a moment.
Now that I see it, earlier the
the female lead was called...
Pak Yeong Hui
Pak Yeong Hui...
Ba Yeong Hui.
Ba Yeong-i...
Bo Yeong-i ????
That... Son of a bitch!
The first time I went on a trip with her...
Was it to Cheongju?
Attorney Gim's hometown is Cheongju?
I didn't know that.
Cheongju is beautiful.
Cheongju is beautiful, she said.
No Bo Yeong, who is a 3rd-generation
Seoul city dweller...
For her to have gone to Cheongju...
If that's the case...
With that bastard?...
In that trip, I only remember
kissing the entire day.
We kissed as we walked.
And kept kissing, getting into a van.
Our lips not separating for the entire day
was beautiful, I think.
That damn son of a bitch!
What is the sound?
It's nothing.
Not sleeping?
Yeah, sleeping.
Hey, but... You...
Nevermind.
That damn son of a bitch.
It can't be, right? Could she...
Yes, it just can't be.
It's not so.
Jun Hyeok!
Jun Hyeok.
You boy...
Father!
The test results say it's true.
Our Jun Hyeok.
Isn't it? Correct, right?
Didn't I already say it's correct?
You rascal fellow... You rascal.
Test result came out this early in the morning?
It's your dad who called ahead to confirm.
Su Yeong. Your younger brother Jun Hyeok
has come back. Say hello.
He's been here for a few days.
Regardless, Jun Hyeok.
I really missed you.
Honey... Our Jun Hyeok. The one we
missed day and night for 20 years.
So sorry for these few days.
No...
I am sorry.
That's right.
Mom had got hurt many times in the past
after getting her hopes up. That's why.
What are we doing on such a joyous day?
We must celebrate!
Let's have a celebration party!
Celebration party!
Grandfather, it's 6 am in the morning.
What celebration party?
Does the time matter for a celebration party?
Call over people! Call over everybody!
The more people, the better for a celebration.
Let's just celebrate nicely among
just us, father-in-law.
Ajumma.
This woman!
Aigoo, this rascal.
What happened here?
What do you think happened?
Out of no choice, I had to make some moves.
You hurry up and find the USB.
What 'moves'?
Isn't this a crime?
Is being there instead of a dead son
some crime? It's a good deed.
The way that family thinks,
even if we say you are not,
I reckon they will deceive themselves
into believing you are the son anyway.
Hold on, hold on, just listen to me.
If you are that reluctant, it's enough to
just confess it once you find the USB.
You do fit that family's specifications on
the missing person and that isn't a lie.
You don't know about the test results,
so you have no responsibility in that.
Do you get what I'm talking about?
I'm hanging up.
Find that USB fast.
Jun Hyeok.
No Jun Hyeok.
Yes.
- Jin A!
- What?
Jin A!
What? What?
The youngster is really the son.
What?
The youngter... is that... family's real son, yes.
Is it so?
See that! I had... told you to bite him, right?
No, no. Now that the groundwork is set,
at least from now on... That's it!
You too get mentally prepared
at least from now.
This... for us, is an opportunity.
Understand?
Whatever, please don't be like this!
You are the one who shouldn't be like this.
This is an opportunity, an opportunity.
They say an opportunity is a 'chance'.
You won't know it?
Mom, 'chance' means opportunity in english.
Isn't that what I was saying?
An opportunity is a chance.
Don't miss the chance, Jin A.
Excuse me, I'm here.
- Oh, come on in, come on.
- Your daughter?
She's at work.
This type of celebration, and you
invited even me. Thank you.
Right now, I feel like having a
3-month celebration party.
Yes, of course. Where do you find
such a happy occasion?
Wondering what if the youngster isn't the
real son, I was also so badly worrying.
I couldn't even get sleep last night.
Ajumma, why wouldn't you get sleep?
Well... Oh, do you need any help?
Jun Hyeok.
Uncle.
Exceptional dance, I must say!
Having fun like this, the afternoon time flies!
Oh, it's the seal nuna!
(Nuna - Elder sisier, elder girl)
- Come on in.
- Come on in, come on.
Come and sit down.
What are you doing?
Let go.
Come, sit down. Sit down.
Come, sit down. Sit.
How can the lead actor sit outside like this?
I'm sorry, but can I do a celebration ritual?
When we see baseball, the home run hitters
get a good dose of something!
Can I do it just this once?
I will, okay?
Cowabanga, dude!
Why no reaction, like this?
Ah, right! You better not forget about
buying me rib-eye steaks.
If you don't wish to be a
rich kid, recently deceased.
Come to think of it, the name is kinda nice.
Of what?
Rib-eye steak, I mean.
Is it because there's an eye, like a flower?
Rib-eye steak.
Rib-eye steak...
Rib-eye steak!
Not only is the name pleasant...
but the smell must be great too, right?
Why do you look like that?
Since a while back?
Towards what, and where to
let myself carry on, and how...
isn't very clear.
What are you talking about?
Turned rich, and you're already all smug?
Doesn't suit you, okay?
I've seen you in all kinds of shit before,
and you get picky with words now?
Jun Hyeok, where did you go?
Dad. Quickly bring Jun Hyeok to visit Min Hyeok.
Min Hyeok has been looking
for Jun Hyeok for a while.
Okay, I'm hanging up.
You going out somewhere?
- Yeah, a party.
- Party?
What party?
That "Intro to Civil Engineering" seonbae is
throwing it, as the movie made it to no.1.
What? The movie is a no. 1 hit?
"One Same Vegas" is that place where
we had an earlier get-together, right?
Yeah. There, well...
You really must go?
My schoolmates will all be there.
I'll just go, show my face and return.
What's the point in just going to show the face?
Why all this interrogation?
I just have to go, so I will go.
There's salad and sandwiches in the fridge.
Don't forget to feed the boys.
Why? You changing into this?
Yeah, this feels a bit too dark.
Go out. I want to change.
You going somewhere?
I want to take Jun Hyeok to the
hospital to visit Min Hyeok.
Jun Hyeok.
Yes.
He will be extremely happy to see you.
Even as kids, he liked you a lot
and took you out to play.
Yes.
What's this small small rise of uneasy feeling
that I keep getting?
A suspicious party, out of the blue.
A red one-piece dress.
My suspicion the day before must be correct.
That dog-like...
Dad.
Dad!
Dad!!
Why are you shaking your legs?
Dad, if you keep shaking your legs,
this will shake too, you know.
Sorry.
Correct. Buried deep... Buried deep...
everybody has a past, don't they all?
But a party today?
Dad! Why do you keep shaking?
Dad, don't shake your leg.
This will get shaken!
But yes. It's not like it's a solo meeting with him.
Won't all the schoolmates be there?
Moreover, it is the No Bo Yeong who
beheads those she can see through.
But what if that fellow keeps
making his moves...
No Bo Yeong.
Why are you like this?
The old days came to mind.
After all this while, if we return to that...
Seonbae, what are you doing?
Think about our Cheongju trip.
That's it!
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing, Dad?
I have to go out for awhile.
You guys have your dinner first.
Min Hyeok, after an accident,
has no recent memories.
Till he recovers, you will need to
take good care of your brother.
Of course, we are on the way to the hospital.
Currently crossing the Seongsu bridge.
Child, say goodbye to your mother.
Tell your mother to go in peace.
Mom,
Go in peace.
Who is he?
It's Jun Hyeok.
The brother you have been yearning for.
Jun Hyeok.
You are Jun Hyeok?
Why are you here only now?
I had missed you so much.
Why do you look like that?
I don't know...
Towards what, and where to
let myself carry on, and how...
He is not Jun Hyeok.
What?
Why?
Isn't he the same one, from the test results?
I feel there is some mistake.
Somebody must have done something.
No matter how I look,
it's not Jun Hyeok. That guy.
Sing together.
Louder!
That bastard.
Hey, you punk!
Won't take your hands off?
You crazy psycho bastard!
Are you crazy? What are you doing?
You!
Who would you be?
What?
There are such mad guys around?
I am a lawyer.
Please let me have a discussion with the victim.
The victim has already lodged a report.
You just stay quiet, over there.
You didn't even feed the boys.
Where are you?
Chan U asked me to have a drink.
I'll be back in a jiffy.
Still not letting go? Don't you know
who my husband is?
If I just make a call, all of you are finished.
Do you know?
- Ajumma. Just be quiet, please!
- Let go. Let go.
Hold on.
One moment!
Excuse... Excuse me.
What?
Aren't you... perhaps Gim Do Sang?
You are...?
By any chance...
You remember?
It's me. Su Ji.
In our university days, didn't we join
the folklore department together?
Go Su Ji.
Do Sang oppa.
(oppa - older brother, boyfriend)
Let's do a toast.
- Salut!
- cheers.
This time who will be no. 1?
I was watching Taekwando yesterday.
It's really great.
Keep it up. Keep up the top position.
Boxing and wrestling aren't bad either.
Let's go together.
I will be back after a toilet trip.
Wait for me!
Initially it was... Gim Dong Yul of the exhibition
that I liked a lot.
From today, oppa, is it okay if I like you...
more than Gim Dong Yul?
Su Ji.
Actually, right from the first time I saw you,
I felt that it's not Gang Su Ji, but you Go Su Ji,
that I found more beautiful.
Your... your... your... chin.
No, no, no... You both... Your chins!
What do we do?
Please don't!
-=Next Episode Preview=-
New Zealand is the country next to Australia.
Why are you asking grandpa such a question?
That ignoramus, really. How dare she
disgrace people like that?
This is the new office building
since our merger this time.
Why come to the company? If there's time,
shouldn't you be finding the USB quickly?
Why are you learning Spanish?
I want to get your mother pissed off.
(In Spanish) Your school is shit.
You are talking to me in Spanish now?
I have a friend whom I have troubled a lot.
I want to repay a little.
No matter what, it seems like
we'll need to get more meat.
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.
(In Spanish) Behave yourself, please.
You want to challenge me, is that it?
Credit card!
Don't you have lots of money?
I'll return it in a flash.
Just lend me 50 million dollar.
Thanks.
-="Intro to Civil Engineering"=-
-=With Director Lee Gwang Su=-
-="Intro to Civil Engineering"=
-=Invitation Pass for 2 inside.=
-=Cheongju=-
=Sorry for not buying you rib-eye steaks.=
RIB
EYE
STEAK
-=Seongsu Bridge=-