I need to do whatever I can to convince her.
She is staying at his home. She's the best
candidate to find and get us the USB.
Of course I know it's dangerous, but now is
not the time to pick and choose.
She's here. Hanging up.
Over here. Here!
I didn't know what you would like,
so I got what came to my mind.
Something expensive.
I'm sure I'll enjoy it all.
You will enjoy it all, you say?
Then hear what I say as you eat.
Okay.
Now, where should I begin?
It's nothing that big.
At the moment, you're...
Excuse me.
Yes, it's me.
What?
Really?
Continue talking.
Why this rather inappropriate buttering up?
Why is he suddenly trying to get close?
But I am like, totally "thank you"!
Short-rib stew!
It's really been a long time...
What's that? He left just like that?
Who the hell was it?
Who put a ball on the side at the entrance?
What's wrong? Did you hurt yourself?
He tripped on the ball and hurt his hip.
Who put the ball there?
Is it you?
It was just Cheol Min who was earlier--
How do you know it was Cheol Min?
A dog that can't talk!
It's true.
He was playing with that in his mouth,
and he left the ball there.
You sure it wasn't you who
played with that in your mouth?
You come over here, hurry!
Please stop it. You think it's okay
not to go to the hospital?
For now, it seems using a warm mat and
watching for a while may make it better.
Still not coming? Hurry up!
If you want to kick, kick Cheol Min.
Why do you want to do it on me?
Come here fast!
I don't want to.
If you come, I will kick you once now.
Later if you catch me on anything,
you kick me 10 times. Hurry, come!
Give it a rest, please!
What changes if you kick his ass?
Thanks for your help.
Don't mention it. But really,
it was nearly big trouble.
I saw him standing there and about to fall,
and had to come running to hold.
That's right. But for our friend from the garage,
I would have nearly died.
Oh, thank you.
But how come you are
so fast physically?
I was always really fast.
My old nickname was cheetah.
Ah, cheetah?
From now on, this 'cheetah'... I mean,
let us have these garage folks
use our bathroom.
- Right...
- To do that, they have to go even to street shops.
How can that be?
It's all right, sir.
We were done talking about this.
Outsiders can't come into the house.
Please be understanding.
Yes.
So what if outsiders enter here?
Whatever it is, no way.
Just listen to what I say!
What's it again, with you?
It's alright, sir.
Though it is really inconvenient for us now,
it's fine if we go through it for a while.
Thank you.
I call this fellow to come, and
he won't come, like he'll die.
You can die, but you
still won't listen to me.
Heck, if you both don't care to help me, then
I should just die here with a head concussion.
Director sir.
Why? What's the matter?
What's it?
The invoice from the restaurant earlier.
What is that?
I know I was the one who ate. But it was
only as you asked me to a meal.
I had no money or card, so
I had to leave my ID card there.
So I should pay for this now?
How much is it?
160 thousand Won.
(~US$ 140)
What were you enjoying eating
for 160 thousand Wons?
It was just what you had ordered.
Here. Is that it?
For 160 thousand Wons, adding 10% tax,
it is 176 thousand Wons.
More and more demands...
I only have 150 thousand.
You pay 15 000.
Thank you.
Bugs me. Bugs me.
Why does she bug me so much?
She really doesn't give me a good vibe.
At first, the bad vibe was because
she's only a school grad.
But now nothing she does
leaves a good vibe.
Just eliminate her.
Why won't you stop that talk again?
You know nothing but killing
to eliminate everything?
I'm so with constant hindrances.
All hindrances must die?
Are you like a human eraser?
She's really seen me being
around you many times.
If she tells the CEO,
what do we do?
I too have hindered you,
so eliminate me too!
That talk was over, damn it.
We finished that talk, and are discussing
us being seen together, now!
Sorry. But the talk of us being a team
is really no big deal.
All the other employees only think that we are
together because we're in an alumni club.
Is that so?
Is that right?
But still, we have to be careful.
Good. Let us be careful and
stop with that for today.
Here.
1, 2, 3... There!
How much meat did you eat?
Not even eating dinner?
Going to such a once-in-a-million-year
restaurant, I ate all of 2 people's food.
May be I got over-nourished?
Pigged out too much?
You want to go to the toilet?
Should I come along?
For now I'll try to stand it.
What's the point in standing it?
Hurry, go have a dump.
I'm not at that point yet.
I'm there, I'm there... at that point!
Go together?
You just eat.
The street light is fixed,
so it's bright enough.
Hey! Where are you going?
I told you to take this to the hospital!
An important appointment came up.
What appointment,
if it's that important?
It's THAT important an appointment.
Chauffeur Gim isn't around. I need to go out too,
then what about this?
How sad!... What do we do,
big trouble...
You damn brat, seriously!
Hello.
Back from working out?
Not a work out. I went to a rest room.
You know...
I'm sorry, but could I ask you
to run an errand for me?
Run an errand? What is it?
I was to make a trip to my son's hospital.
But nobody is at home, and
I have an urgent appointment too.
May be if you could--
Yes, I understand.
Is it an okay time for it?
The time is extremely okay!
Is it so?
Then, I will pay you later.
Take this over there.
- Yes, I understand.
- Thank you.
Also, in future if it's very urgent,
just use our house bathroom.
Huh?
- No. It's all right.
- Thank you very much.
When it's urgent, we will sure use it.
In fact, when it's straining
to come out, it's like dying.
So sometimes we may come to dump.
Mom!
Then let me go.
Mom, don't you have any self-respect?
You so easily talk of needing toilet to take dumps
when the bottom strains and you can't wait?
That's right. If we can take dumps,
I will easily talk.
Thanks to that, we don't have to
wait to dump. Isn't it good?
That's all mine. All mine.
In the end, she even found another man?
Guess we'll hear more of how bad the brat is.
If the bitch is so bad, kick her out anyway.
That's right. Just go back to the States.
In my view, it is all over.
But still I can't let her go.
Ah, a grown man cries over even this!
That's right, don't cry, man.
Wait!
It came out, it came out.
Go. Go. Go.
I am godori.
("5 birds" - a 3-card set)
I was just shaken just now.
Twice you, Ajumma. Double.
The godori set is still alive.
Why are you yelling Go?
Oh, it is right.
In the performance just now,
the last song was great.
"That side of the bridge... let's go"
Is it a song you made on the asteroid day?
What is it?
You aren't hurt, are you?
Are you all right?
Yeah.
How come even your reaction
to pain is a half-beat slower?
Better be careful in future. Okay?
He's nowhere to be seen.
Who are you yelling at?
What should we eat for dinner?
Shall we eat some meat?
You want to go eat meat?
I know a good place.
Strictly speaking, it was not
made on the asteroid day.
What's is that about...
Earlier... To what I asked on when it was made,
you are giving the answer now?
I wanted to tell you accurately.
What is this... really!
Oh hurry... Let's go eat some meat.
- How about some Potato soup?
- Forget it.
Let's just eat meat.
Hello.
Ms. Na Jin A.
You're alone?
My sister just left to find the nurse.
Tada! Ice cream.
Woah! Thank you.
You're playing this? Rubik's cube.
I'm really good at it.
Really? I also used to play it as a kid.
Then try it!
How do you do this, again?
I forgot it all.
You can't? It's super easy.
Should I teach you?
Look closely.
Once the top is done like this,
Just like this, to the top, and then to the side.
Like this, to the bottom side.
How is it?
You got it, no?
Go ahead and try.
How did he do this?
It's super hard.
This is hard, you say?
I just showed you how it's done.
Na Jin A is not so smart or what...
How can this be difficult?
To the top and then to the side.
And then do the bottom...
and it's done!
I see.
You will recover really soon, seeing your
old days' appearance coming out.
Old-days appearance?
No, not like that. I was just saying that
you were always... extremely smart.
Even if I lost my memory,
the brain is the same, right?
Sure.
So the family folks take turns everyday
to stay with you?
Yes. Except for Jun Hyeok.
Jun Hyeok hasn't been here.
Who is Jun Hyeok?
It's the younger brother who went
missing as a young boy. Jun Hyeok.
Min Hyeok's memory stops before he
went missing. He still doesn't know it.
As we fear that he'd get upset,
we've kept it a secret for now.
So, Jin A, you also act like you don't know.
Sure.
This is the 57th minute asteroid update.
There is news of a variation
in the asteroid's orbit.
According to the U.S. space agency, NASA,
though asteroid 2013QR3's orbit
is now approximately 60 km closer,
causing some nervousness,
it is observed that it is getting no closer,
and is in a stable and safe orbit.
You see those blue and red icons there?
The blue one is me, and the red one is you.
If the connected person
is within a 1 kilometer radius,
at that time "Near U" will flicker.
If you press it, it will show the location.
Hold on a moment!
I need to get down here.
Ajussi!
(ajussi - older man, uncle)
I'm getting down here.
Terrible guy. He can't even call once?
A fleeting mayfly, more like a dung fly.
Son of a bitch.
What did you say?
I understand.
No. No. I will come over there.
Yes. Yes.
Honey. Get up fast. Hurry.
Why? What was the call about?
The detective agency center
wants us for something there.
What's up there?
It looks like they've found Jun Hyeok.
What?
You get dressed fast.
What has happened?
Wasn't there a report of a woman called
Sang Sun keeping the child?
It seems they found somebody
matching that report.
Ah, what's wrong with these pants?
Calm down. You have the pants on backwards.
Hurry, you too change clothes quickly!
Like those kidnappers had said, Jun Hyeok
does seem to have run away then.
If the reports are true on a Jeolla-dialect-speaking
woman called Sang Sun taking the child away,
then he accurately matches those specifications.
But how come you found that woman only now?
At that time, we had checked through the official
residents' register in that neighborhood,
but there was nobody matching the report.
As we found out, she wasn't living in that area,
but she was in Seongsu.
Moreover, she already died at age 96.
Once Jun Hyeok was sent to an orphanage,
we couldn't find him anymore.
Name and the name showing in the
official registry are unchanged.
But how did you find him now?
We happened to speak by chance
to somebody who knew him.
Though we will know only through a DNA test,
the specifications from that time
are matching accurately.
Then, where is he now?
He's next-door.
- Bring him in.
- Yes.
You are Jun Hyeok, am I right?
I don't really know.
You... don't recognize me?
How about Mom?
I am sorry.
Take a good look.
The two of us... don't bring out any memories?
Not really...
You don't remember even Mom?
Have a good look.
Mom's birthmark here...
You don't remember it?
You used to rub it every day.
This is our old family portrait.
There is nobody that you remember?
I don't know for sure.
I think it is Jun Hyeok.
Isn't it so?
I do think he is Jun Hyeok.
Alone all these years...
How scary and difficult it must've been!
I am sorry for not finding you.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
First of all, we have to do a DNA-test.
We will collect some hair.
Why do you look like that?
The stomach is still not well?
Yeah. How come it goes this long?
I think it's bathroom time.
Hello.
It's our seal nuna.
(Nuna - Elder girl or sister for a male)
I'm not a seal.
Try to catch this and eat.
Don't do that.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey boy, even after we told you
not to throw food at people--
We're sorry.
Go. Hurry.
Let's go.
- Nuna, don't catch this.
- Don't do that!
Has he come?
Not yet.
It's Jun Hyeok, right?
As per what Dad says, that seems right.
They left a while back.
Why haven't they come back?
Try to give them a call again.
Why aren't they back yet?
Come on, give me a ride on your back.
Yes. Yes.
Just stay there. They will come soon.
It's too stuffy, so I should go out
to the courtyard and wait.
It was enough to wait here.
- They have come.
- Oh, have they come?
Hurry. Over there. Go over there.
Quick. There, there, there, over there!
Quick, quick, quick!
You are... You are Jun Hyeok?
I am not.
Father. He is a staff person.
Jun Hyeok. Come on in.
Where?
Hello.
Are you Jun Hyeok?
You kid, where were you, to come only now?
Yes it's my dakpul.
(Dakpul - Sunset hibiscus flower. Also glue from it)
You're Jun Hyeok, right?
It's him, it's him, I guarantee.
This kid is our Jun Hyeok, I know.
Isn't it? Isn't it right?
It's right.
You don't remember this grandpa?
Not... really.
No memory at all about old times, right?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Just for the bathroom...
Like said earlier, it's after your mom died
that you got to the orphanage, right?
Before she died, your mother
never told you anything?
She said nothing particular.
In the TV dramas, if it isn't the real mom,
it's normally said as last words.
Isn't this a drama?
The way I see, there's no doubt.
See the bridge of the nose on this fellow.
Precisely how he was when he was young.
Wasn't the bridge of your nose
just like mine then?
There's no mistaking it.
Don't be talking like you are so sure.
You have done the same in the past too.
That time I was mistaken.
On him, I am right, you know!
His face is like a lion's.
He has a Maori tribe look.
Lion. Lion.
- What's with you both?
- To your uncle?
Hey! Red Sun.
Then, well.. As he doesn't remember anything,
we can only wait till the test results come out.
Yes. It will be out the day after tomorrow.
Then, where will he stay till then?
Well, that...
As they demolished the place he was staying at,
he doesn't seem to have a place to stay for now.
If it's okay, if he can stay here
till the test results come out...
Of course, he can do that.
Where can he go otherwise?
Staying here is a bit strange.
What is strange?
Please take care of him till the results come out.
We will give money for that.
Look at you!
Money is all, in everything?
A kid who lived away for those 20 years.
You will send him out again?
Are you even in your senses now?
For God's sake, don't act so sure.
Matters in life are so fickle.
Must you get so excited so early?
We are sorry, but staying here is a bit weird.
What is so weird in that?
To me, you're the weirdest.
Grandfather. There is something to
what Mom says.
It's not too late if we wait till
it is confirmed, you know.
Forget it, forget it.
He has nowhere to sleep.
What's wrong if he sleeps 2 nights here?
What are you doing?
Say something!
You are going to say nothing at all?
I was thinking of saying it.
Sure. Let him be here.
With no place close by, you also really--
Hey, it's commotion in the house!
Why?
Looks like the lost son has reappeared.
I too heard of him.
That he is the CEO's younger brother.
But they really found him?
It's looking that way.
I don't know who it is, but his fate
is about take a big turn for the best.
A lotto win, isn't? Lotto!
What does he look like?
Similar to the CEO?
I couldn't see well, except for
the back of the head.
Thanks for the dinner.
Why aren't you eating some more?
I ate a lot.
It doesn't seem like it at all, right?
Why? Because he can't remember?
It's usual for nothing to be recalled
from 4 years of age.
What? What? What are you talking about?
It's nothing.
That way, that way.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa...
Over here?
Have some apple.
Eat some fruits.
Whether you're the real Jun Hyeok or not,
I am anyway older, so I'll be casual.
Eat some peach. Tasty.
No, thanks. I'll be eating some apple.
So you'll rebel?
Just teasing.
Grandfather...
This rascal...
You still know that the grandpa gets it first.
When Jun Hyeok was small, I accidentally poked
him with a fingernail. Won't the scar be there?
Yes. But will that be still there?
It wasn't bad enough to still be there.
Check it, check it. By chance
it could still be there, right?
As my eyes are bad...
I suppose it could be so.
I'm sorry, but let me take a look.
You can eat. You can eat. It's fine.
Is the mark there?
Not sure.
What?
- It's there?
- It's not this...
There's something that's
more conclusive than the scar.
What is it?
Jun Hyeok's circumcision
went a bit strange, right?
Circumcision?
When Min Hyeok was in primary school,
they were circumcised together.
As the suture on one side broke a bit early,
things looked a bit strange.
Weren't everybody laughing at that?
Oh, that's true, you're right.
Try checking that.
But that... How can we check it?
Why can't you?
Check it, check it.
Sorry that I'm asking...
Have you... had a circumcision?
Pardon?
Yes.
When was that?
Not really... sure.
Seeing you not remembering,
you must've been really young then.
Seems right. That's right.
Is it fine... for just one time,
if I try to check on something?
Thanks for doing that.
Eat some fruits.
So, how did it turn out?
You, help me.
Oh, yes.
On the back.
Make it quick.
Over there. Over there.
Giddy up. Quick, quick.
Okay, so what happened?
We were right?
Not sure. Usually it is supposed
to be like this, you know...
But... When he was small, the thing was a
bit strange as it had become like this.
But his thing has actually become this way.
My thinking is that it looks different.
But then, how it looks can change
as one grows up, I suppose?
Sure. That can happen too.
That means, it is him, isn't he?
Guess so.
What's that sound?
Didn't you just hear the sound
of some wall cracking open?
It is the sound from my stomach.
What's wrong?
I've got a stomach flu.
It's coming.
What's it?
Just go to their house.
How can you go to the store like this?
It's okay.
Just go to the house.
I don't want to.
Na Jin A, you can do this.
I can... not stand it.
You can't, right?
See that!
Just go. Why not at the house?
Just let him use Jun Hyeok's
old 2nd floor room.
I'm sorry, but sleep here itself.
Yes. Thank you.
Geez.
- Then, if you want to eat anything at night...
- Just the toilet...
toilet is where you can eat.
What's that?
I'm sorry. Just needed the toilet...
Go on.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
- What sound is that?
- What's it, what's it?
I'm sorry.
What? How did this happen?
How come that guy...
Some toilet paper would've been nice.
I didn't bring the mobile phone either.
I will go insane.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Oh, I am sorry.
Good you came.
What's with you?
How come you are here?
Don't tell me... you're this family's lost son?
Who are you?
You know me?
What?
Hongberg... Isn't it you?
Am I not right?
No.
Seeing you say no, I know it's you!
What's this? You are going to act dumb?
Why were you throwing so much stuff
onto the door like that?
Some toilet paper...
Toilet paper?
You used 5 pieces to finish it?
There was none! What 5 pieces?
Get it fast.
You told me that on so many days.
I too wanted to try it once.
Wait a moment.
You sonofa...
What are you doing?
Some toilet paper... She said there's no
toilet paper in the washroom.
I will give it to her.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Hey, can't you get it fast--
I'm throwing this.
Thank you.
Embarrassing.
Really, the lost son in their house
is our next-door youngster?
I told you it's true!
I was also flat-out shocked.
How is this possible?
What to do about this now?
What do you mean what to do?
Hello.
I saw you going into this place.
Ajumma, have you been doing well?
Yeah... But how did this happen to you?
Are you really a son in this family?
No, I'm not.
How? I hear you are.
What a world!
Somehow, right from start, I was totally
getting the feeling that you were
totally of a dignified pedigree.
At first you reported me as a
murder suspect, you know.
It was this girl who reported you!
What is with this girl?
I can care less if you're the son here or not.
Can't you call saying you're leaving, you bastard?
Why now, about that...
Without toilet paper, I wasn't thinking earlier,
so I forgot to kick your ass there.
But I just remembered.
Step out with me.
You damn well tell me clearly
what crap you've been up to.
Only you should hear that?
I want to hear too.
So I was with the people at
the private detective center.
You didn't even have time for a call?
Terrible fellow.
My mobile phone had to be changed.
I was all confused.
At first I thought I'd call to tell you everything.
All just talk, right?
Put in your number.
Like it's dark right below a lamp,
I was dumbstruck, and didn't even know
your phone number!
- Here.
- Name too!
I was dumbstruck that I really
didn't know your name either.
What is your name?
Hong.
Ber-geu.
Hongber...
Damn you, seriously!
I'm asking what your real name is?
Hong Bo Gu.
Hong means jewel. Bo means see.
Gu is 9. So it means "see 9 jewels".
You're lucky that I hate just
beating people up too fast!
Forget it. Fine.
If you are a son of that family,
you'll get a new name.
But, do you know that it's our CEO's family?
I knew just before coming.
Anyway, congratulations.
You're fortunate.
Being a son in such a rich family
simply does not fit you though.
I won't be.
- Won't be what?
- The son.
Why?
Again that "Not not" disease?
No.
But I wouldn't be.
Really.
Oh... The Near-U software you installed here
can be deleted, I think.
The registered users are only you and me.
We have no further use for it, right?
Just leave it there.
Why? For me to search for where I am?
Just...
leave it there.
Why are you coming out from there?
Just the bathroom...
The bathroom is here, no?
Was sleeping on the sofa uncomfortable?
No, it wasn't. Not at all.
Survive the discomfort just a bit more.
The test results will be out real soon.
Sure, yes.
But, is it okay if I go out briefly?
Where to?
To a friend... just for a while.
Sure, fine.
-=Next Episode Preview=-
I've decided to give you up.
Romance can change too, I guess.
You go back right away and make sure to find it!
Report to me right away when it's found.
How come he is sleeping like this?
The men walking by just now
weren't even blinking while ogling.
Am I so inconspicuous in your eyes?
A have a not-recognizing disease.
The next-door youngster.
You grab him and come.
Don't talk nonsense, okay?
I hate him to death!
I'm so inconspicuous in your eyes
but you'll date me?
It affected my heart.
Isn't this a good thing?
That's why I said we'll date.
I just knew that you'd be like this.
Hongberg!
It seems the power is gone
in the whole neighborhood.
I will stay here till the power comes back.