What happened with that thing?
You found it?
No. Not yet.
The lady asked me to sleep in the living room.
Then you should go in when
everyone sleeps.
As the ajussi keeps going to the toilet,
I don't get that much time.
Definitely find it today. Right past the weekend,
the DNA test results will be out.
You hate getting money?
No.
I am dying from anxiety.
Has No Min Hyeok come home?
No.
How is No Min Hyeok's situation?
Have you heard anything?
No.
It's only 'no' all along, huh?
You know no other word but "no'?
No.
There, again!
Wouldn't you hear something
they can't avoid saying?
There's nothing special
that they're saying.
Also, our contract from the beginning was
for me to only find the USB, wasn't it?
I need to even report that man's condition?
The contract may be so, but shouldn't you
be doing such stuff as free service?
Think how worried I must be,
to be doing this.
That terrible guy stole my files and
is after my life, making me crazy.
Are they such bad guys?
Don't you know after seeing them?
So bad that I can't even tell you!
Imagine your worst, and they are
worse than even that!
They don't look so bad to me.
Do bad guys have "bad" written
on their foreheads?
Hurry back there today and
find it without fail!
Report to me right when you find it.
Hurry up. Go, go, go!
Sure.
Go, go, go!
You mean, go out?
Go, go, go... How many times should I say?
Can't you drop me near the house?
I don't have the taxi fare.
Practicing?
It's the weekend tomorrow. Shall we meet?
Anyhow, he's slow. So slow.
A reply will come at least
tomorrow morning, right?
What's the deal? So fast?
Su Yeong, can I see you for a moment?
Oh, come here, come here, come here.
You went somewhere so early in the morning?
Yes. To see a friend.
You had breakfast?
Come close here. Come close.
My waist was hurting, so I couldn't come down.
I wanted to see him so much the whole night.
=Quite suddenly this morning,=
=a 2 million kilowatt generator=
=at the Panbit nuclear plant developed=
=problems and stopped operating,=
=again causing an emergency in power supply.=
=The government has convened=
=an urgent response meeting.=
Yet again? Starting from summer,
power supply has kept failing.
It's all those corrupt guys taking bribes.
What's becoming off our country?
Those corrupt guys taking bribes went
completely unpunished, that's why.
Isn't it our family who bribes?
Mom, at the Olympics time,
you sent cash in apple cases.
That's how we got rich, right?
- You brat!
- Shut up.
Julien.
Su Yeong. Were you doing well?
Yeah.
- Julien, now I...
- I...
I'm going back to New York.
You are dating that guy called Jang Yeol, right?
(It means "stomach fever")
It is not Jang Yeol.
It's Jang Yul.
Anyway, I think I'll let go of you.
I'm really sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
It's possible for love to change too, I guess.
A asked to see you to tell you this
as the last words.
Take care, Su Yeong.
Stay healthy and take care.
You too, Su Yeong.
Bye.
Adios.
(Adios - farewell in Spanish)
Sounds good. See you tomorrow.
What shall we do tomorrow?
That's not it.
If I ask a question, who knows
when a reply will happen?
Let's have fun watching a movie tomorrow.
In front of the Cheong Dam CGV at 3 o'clock.
(CGV - Movie theater chain)
It seemed the business was going well.
It's now for rent?
Yes. We had some issues.
How much is the rental deposit for such a place?
What? 50 million Wons? You squandered all my
money, and still dare to say this?
(~US$ 50K)
Don't jump the gun, you wretched girl.
You think I won't jump the gun, now?
50 million is some child's play?
Who said do it now? Anyway, there's no money.
I just happened to say it.
The location was great. The rent was
extremely cheap too.
All we needed was 50 million--
I said stop it. Please!
What's your problem?
I can't even speak to myself?
Others should hear you talk to yourself?
You make me laugh, seriously.
What am I doing to make you laugh?
Come on, how long can we be living like this?
Stop your crap! Stop creating trouble,
just stay put nicely.
You're just great, I guess.
I need to take a dump.
I'm eating here... seriously!
What?
Look at you talk, not even letting
people talk to themselves, really!
Why do you say that to yourself?
If you need a toilet trip, do it as much as you like.
Why say it out that you'll take a dump?
Ah, really! I can't even talk,
all afraid of a daughter.
Have some mango please.
Father. Dong Gyu's father has
passed away, I hear.
Is that so?
When is his funeral?
In two days.
I'll just use the bathroom.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
What about Hongberg and me?
You both used to stick so close together.
Did anything happened?
There's nothing. What if there is?
You were born so cute.
Why is even your face so useless?
What's with you?
May be like I was a hedgehog,
you were cute only in my eyes?
Now on, you better start
listening to what I say.
I won't. I don't want to listen.
You wretched girl.
I will say just one thing.
It's about the next-door youngster.
Bracing for his debut as the real son,
you quickly bite on to him.
What?
Just now when I was in the house,
I saw him eating mangoes.
He isn't even proven to be the real son
but he's eating such expensive mangoes.
Could he indeed be proven as the real son?
When that thought flashed in,
I wondered what we should do now?
Don't they say that everyone has
3 chances in a lifetime?
To us, this is the first of those, right now.
Geez! Really.
Listen to me. Before he is proven as the real son,
this is our last chance.
If he's proven to be the real one,
it will look like we got close with ulterior motives.
We aren't in his league either.
It is already a bit late.
But we can think that we are late
only because time went by fast.
Once the test results come out,
it's over, okay?
- Oh, for God's sake, such--
- Shut, shut, shut the heck up.
From what I see, he's very innocent. If you
go after him properly, he is hooked, no doubt.
If I were just 10 years younger, even I would've
made a move, really.
Oh, yeah? What's with you, really?
If he is not, what then, after all this fuss?
If he isn't, nothing to lose, right?
Listen to my words. Bite him quickly.
Bite right away. Bite without a doubt!
Satisfied?
Yike Yike Yikes Yikes.
Don't say anymore. He and I are
casual-enough to talk of even poop.
What if you talk poop?
Anyway, once married, it's all fair game.
You talk of poop and marry,
or marry and talk of poop.
Oh, please! Stop talking nonsense.
What was nonsense in that?
I hate to death being like that with him. What?
What?
What's so great about you
to be so high and mighty?
Just a high school grad...
What?
Look at you Mom, seriously.
High school grad, what?
Honestly, in your conditions, if you try finding
a man, you really think it'll be a great guy?
Even on Lottos of 1 in eight million chance,
people try their luck.
Doesn't this have a much higher
chance for success?
Why won't you even attempt it?
Attempt, my foot! It's to grab 50 million Wons by
using me that you've turned ruthless now, right?
Try to dare talk about this again!
Whom does she take after? Such bad temper!
We don't have much time.
You found it?
Not yet.
Find it fast. What are you doing?
Him? I'm seeing him. Why?
How come he is sleeping like this?
No, I wasn't talking to you.
I'm hungry, so I need to
make some night snacks.
My special diet supper snack.
How come he is sleeping like this?
Jun Hyeok!
Did you call me?
You're not sleeping?
I just called, wondering if you were.
What is the matter?
I woke up too early.
I'm sorry but could you please help me?
Because my waist hurts.
Okay.
This rascal...
Aigoo, you precious rascal.
This is nice.
It's great to take half body baths at midnight.
It's my secret to longevity.
I am done. You try it.
No, it's all right.
Listen to me and try it once.
It's really great!
Green hills...
- Feel great?
- Yes.
Like I did, you should sing too.
This has the effects of abdominal breathing.
It stretches out your vocals and body.
It's great!
Okay.
Green hills...
How sad that you're leaving!
This is for you to eat on the plane.
Thank you ajumma.
(ajumma - older lady, aunt)
Anyway, because of that wicked girl, you came all
the way to Korea, only to stay in a sauna room.
Isn't your flight leaving much later?
Before you leave, go and have a tour of Seoul.
Seoul? It's not a city I really wish to remember.
Even then, when will you
ever be back to see it?
Yeah.
I heard there there are those tour buses.
Shouldn't you take the tour and
see what Seoul looks like?
What are you writing so seriously
since a while back?
You don't need to know.
It's to stay alive that I struggle like this.
Struggle with what?
You don't need to know.
Don't have any clothes. Clothes.
What are you doing?
Going out somewhere?
Yeah, an appointment. Why?
If it's not important, postpone it.
Grandpa and Dad are attending a funeral.
I need to go Min Hyeok's hospital.
Then will anyone be here?
Bo Yeong also has a school parents' meeting.
What if no one is at home?
Isn't it weird to leave him alone at home?
So what if he's left here?
When are the test results out?
Monday.
Will it really be Jun Hyeok?
I don't know.
I think there's just no way he can be.
Anyway, you just stay at home.
Understood?
I can't. I have an important appointment.
Am I like a watchdog?
I shall keep a good watch!
I'll be home only at night.
See you later.
Okay.
The maid and Su Yeong will be at home.
If you need anything, let them know.
Okay.
I'm going. If you get bored, take a
half body bath. It's excellent.
Yes.
Everyone has left?
My mother asked me to keep a eye on you.
If I'm not around, will you steal anything?
What?
Are you a thief? Or a bad guy?
No.
Then I am leaving now.
My leaving is a secret from mom.
OK?
Why aren't you answering? OK?
Yes. Ok.
(Speaking Spanish)
Seoul. A city that I really don't
want to ever remember again.
No coming back here again.
Heartbreak city, Seoul.
Setting his sights on what's a bit too high!
This man, why is he still not here?
Where are you going?
I didn't see.
How can you not recognize
even your girlfriend?
I have a bit of 'un-face-recognizitis'.
What?
This would usually be done by a man.
It's because you're busy with performances
that I'm doing it, understand?
Thank you.
I was just joking.
What? What was?
What I said earlier that I have
'un-face-recognizitis'.
It was too crowded, so I couldn't see well.
If your slow replies make me mad,
your explanation is even more so.
Am I so inconspicuous in a crowd?
Those passing men were all
stealing glances at me.
But yet the boyfriend can't see a thing.
This hurts my pride.
I'm sorry.
If I am so inconspicuous in a crowd,
why are you dating me?
Must think again?
Then forget it. Forget it.
Can we just not watch the movie?
Huh?
I suddenly don't wish to watch the movie.
Let's go to the suburbs and enjoy the breeze.
But we have even bought the tickets.
Just returning it will do.
I want to see this movie.
I don't want to see. Let's just go.
I see. Go outside, I guess.
Good. Let's just...
Sorry. Su Yeong, you go to the suburbs now,
and call me later about where you are.
Once the movie ends, I will come over there.
What?
You're here?
You're playing NarARa Superboard again?
(Korean animation, circa 1992)
Because Son O Gong monkey king is
back to normal from being an idiot.
I'm going. Min Hyeok, see you tomorrow.
I've heard this song so much
that I've memorized it too.
Mom. But, why hasn't Jun Hyeok
come even once?
Can't you bring Jun Hyeok here too?
One can drink directly from this, right?
Our boss is extremely sensitive.
It's a triple filter product,
so feel free to use it like that.
I am all done.
So we'll meet in 2 months again.
And Oh... Do you know this
Min Dong building nearby?
That place is a bit complicated.
I'll come out and give you the directions.
Thank you.
Nice. Youngster, you are home?
Yes. Need to use the bathroom?
No. I just came.
Why is the house so quiet?
You're alone?
Yes.
One never knows of this world, right?
When we kept fighting at my house,
who would've thought we'd meet here?
What past life connection is
bringing us back together?
Were we a family?
So amazing.
The test results are still not out,
so you must be all alone and bored.
No, I'm not. Not particularly.
I'm also bored.
Shall we do something?
Huh? Do what?
I have to go to the supermarket to
buy a dishwashing brush.
Do you want to come?
Dishwashing brush?
Heartbreak City, Seoul.
But still, it's beautiful.
I didn't know that.
Is the river so big?
Quite impressive.
For me to eat?
What's this?
- Carp bread.
- Carp bread?
Carp is a fish.
It's seafood!
Bread made using fish?
(Bungeoppang is a pastry. Only shaped as a fish)
What is this? The guts of a fish?
It's red bean. Red bean.
Red bean?
It's crispy on the outside and
sticky-fragrant inside.
Something so amazing and tasty exists?
How much is this bread?
300 Wons.
(US$ 0.25)
4 for 1000 Wons.
(US$ 0.80)
What?
Such a treat and it's just 1000 for 4?
Unbelievable!
May I ask what your name is?
I'm Gim Tae Hui.
Say it once again.
Tae Hui.
- You mean...
- Gim Tae Hui.
Aigoo.
(Aigoo - Oh dear, Oh my god)
The weather is great. Isn't it?
Yes, I guess...
What is that?
Shall we go there to take a look?
Where to?
This is for memories. Put one on.
Earlier we had the bear paw game
and the cola soda game.
Looking back later, we will really
have a ton of memories. Won't we?
Yes.
What is this?
I was walking on the street with the youngster.
I... open-quotes... pat the lad's shoulder
close-quotes... and say.
Shall we bet on who reaches the tree first?
Youngster...
What?
What? You don't think I'm a rival to you?
Not so, my friend!
My old nickname is cheetah.
It's true. Want to try?
Get set...
Go!
At the tree, the youngster and I
lay down panting, on the lawn.
I felt a sense of closeness.
I... open-quotes
ruffle his hairs. close-quotes.
I never had a son, and always
wanted a son like you.
If you weren't a son from a rich family
but my son, I would have no regrets.
Even in that small house, when you were eating
and sleeping like a son, those days were so nice!
If you are truly a son of that family,
you will forget us, right?
It's not possible for it to be true.
Saying that it's not possible is like saying
that you will forget us if it is. Right?
Am I not right?
Wonder why people always change?
How nice would it be if nobody changed?
The youngster... open-quotes
looked softly at me, close-quotes.
Like that Ajumma and Mom there, I will also look
after you well if you are a real son of that family.
Really?
Yes.
Then, shall we see some proof?
If you are truly a son, can you
lend me 50 million Wons?
(~US$ 45,000)
Has this Mom lost all her senses?
Why are you walking so fast
without saying anything?
I need to run, to catch up with you.
Why do you think I am like this?
Huh?
Well, that...
You have something urgent to do?
I'm going to pass away from suffocation!
When you see a woman like this, you don't get
the feeling that may be she is angry?
How can a man turn out to be this dull?
Hold this first.
Look here!
Why is your shoelaces always loose?
It's dangerous.
It was loose sometime back also,
when you came to see me.
Su Yeong, after you left I kept feeling bad.
Might you have fallen down?
Might you be hurt badly?
I kept thinking of only that.
Didn't that mean I liked you?
That's why I said we would date.
All of a sudden... what's this you're...
Didn't you ask me,
why I said we would date?
What I asked earlier before seeing the movie...
It's now that you answer it?
It was an important question, I felt.
So I had to think for quite some time.
Mr. Jang Yul. You know you are
a really weird guy, right?
Fine, I guess. You were such a man
right from the start.
Let's go to eat something.
Was that effective?
What's this about, damn it?
You want the 50 million so badly
as to deceive others?
Hey, wait. You're looking at
somebody else's diary?
Geez.
Reading such things written in a diary
is a first for me!
So annoying, seriously.
Go to Sindangdong and get some fired rice cakes.
Why do you ask for Sindangdong fried rice cakes
all of a sudden?
Suddenly I am craving for Sindangdong fried rice
cakes, that's why. Go and get it. Hurry. Hurry.
What are you doing?
- He's cool.
- He's way too cool.
Not one we see too often.
Hi.
It's just you alone who came?
Huh? Yes.
You're able to speak Korean?
Just a little.
Not too long since I learned it,
so don't I sound too foolish?
My pronunciation is weird too.
No, you do it extremely well.
- You are cute.
- You are cool.
Me?
Being a foreigner,
I may be like a big stupid nailhead.
You find me cool?
Big stupid nailhead?
You are no stupid nailhead.
You are fabulously cool!
- You're so cute.
- So damn cool.
Seoul women would all be like Su Yeong,
and dislike me, I thought.
They say it's not so?
And on top, they are damn pretty too!
Oh my!
If you have time, you want to
have some fun together?
Great, then. I have all kinds of time.
Seoul is a highly bewitching city.
No. Not yet.
Does it make sense that you still haven't even
gone into that room?
What did you do all night?
Pulling crazy crap!
Find it fast, damnit! In 2 days the results
come out and it's over, blockhead!
Blockhead?
Okay, sorry about 'blockhead', find it quickly,
we have no time, my... dear friend!
Is there something that you need?
No.
Hongberg,
It's dark, I'm scaredy-scared.
Can you pretty-please pick me up
from the bus-stop?
Did this girl eat something wrong?
What are you doing here?
What else can I be doing?
You asked me to pick you up.
Damn her... That's why she asked
me to get her fried rice cakes?
This ajumma is seriously...
What about an ajumma?
Nothing at all. Want to eat fried rice cake?
Tasty, no?
I come here every time after practice ends.
Yes, it's sure tasty.
The soup is the best.
Drink and see.
Hold on a bit.
Where are you going?
Going to the washroom?
What's this?
Open and see.
Do you like it?
No need to feel obligated.
Just like you worried seeing my shoelaces,
it affected me too, when I saw your shoes.
The sole would drop off, I felt.
I'm going.
Take care.
What has gotten into this ajumma?
I tried my best to beautify it.
When you both intimately eat fried rice cakes,
find a way to bite him, I beg you!
I have to head this way.
Take care.
Huh?
Fine.
No matter how late you are for practice,
shouldn't you still send me home? Geez!
That's not what I meant.
The receipt, please.
Huh?
Didn't you ask me earlier
if I liked the shoes?
Honestly, I don't quite like it.
Give me the receipt, for me to exchange it...
Let me get up first.
The news said the power station malfunctioned.
It seems the power is gone.
It has to be somewhere here.
Where is it?
Me, it's me.
Hongberg!
I just knew that you'd be like this.
Seems like the power is down for
the whole neighborhood.
Oh, I'm saved!
Can you be here by yourself like this?
I have some matters to do.
Oh, go on.
Why haven't you gone?
I will stay till the power comes back.
The candles look lovely.
50 million Wons was blinding my mom
when she bought them, just recently.
Huh?
My mother wants me to entice you
before you turn into a rich family son.
The text message sent earlier
was also my mom's doing.
But don't worry. I have no plans to entice you.
If I'm a man, a housefly is a bird, you said!
Remembering useless words!
Not that a housefly is indeed a bird...
but I would just... hope we can continue like this.
If you can come over like now
as if nothing had happened...
and stay by my side as if nothing has happened,
that will be nice.
In other words, even if you were to be
a 2nd generation rich family guy...
Nevermind.
If you become a 2nd generation rich family guy,
things will completely change.
No chance it happens.
Still, by chance if it does?
Even then we'll be friends, right?
By chance if you are that real son,
then treat me to some good beef!
Rib-eye steak. I haven't had it even once.
Promise?
And also, in case...
Even if you've really become that family's son,
please don't lend my mom 50 million Wons.
That's why I deliberately
talked about 50 million Wons.
If you are to do that, I will be
too embarrassed to look at you.
Understand?
Just wait a little bit more. For all you know,
it may be possible to get 50 million dollars.
How many pyeongs is the floor space?
(Pyeong = 3.3 sq.meters)
-=Next Episode Preview=-
- No Bo Yeong!
- Seonbae.
(seonbae - senior, mentor)
The first time one falls in love,
is there anything but kissing?
Was I the only one like that?
Isn't this a crime?
DNA result will be out tomorrow.
What to do?
Let's return to our teenage years
after a long time!
In that trip, I only remember
kissing the entire day.
Son of a bitch.
If you are the real son, you know you have to
buy me rib-eye steaks, right?
That bastard.
Hey, you punk!
Why are you here only now?
I wanted so much to see you.
I'm also unsure...
what, how and which direction it should be.