Two kinds of sounds exist in this world.
One kind of sound that other people hear.
One kind of sound that only I hear.
I want to fart.
Hold it in?
Nah, let's discharge!
I was to tell him that we're splitting.
When should I do it?
Whoa! Completely my style.
My world is... noisier than other peoples'.
It's bloody loud!
Senile old fart. You can't hear my horn?
Two kinds of sounds exist in this world.
One kind that other people do not hear.
One kind that only I do not hear.
That grandpa looks like he has some cash.
You were going to steal the
grandfather's wallet?
How about just getting lost?
What the heck are you?
"This tall handsome kid might be good at fighting
and it's scary." Isn't that what you are thinking?
What?
You're right. I can do some Taekwondo.
Shall I show you?
What's this? You stinking gangster thug...
Are you all right?
Thank you.
If you weren't there, it would've been big trouble.
But, how did you see that he was
about to steal my wallet?
You must have good eyes.
It wasn't seeing it. I heard him thinking.
Heard his thoughts?
This was always a secret, but
I will tell just you, grandfather.
I am able to hear what
other people are thinking.
What?
What kind of bullcrap is that?
Isn't he a crazy guy?
I'm not crazy.
Huh? What's this? He really
can read my thoughts?
Yes. I can really read your thoughts.
I'll be damned! Really, live for long
and one would see such things.
I've lived for almost 100 years.
Seeing someone like you is a first for me.
Then please take care.
One moment, one moment.
I should give you something...
It wasn't for getting any rewards.
I just felt like helping guard you, grandpa.
In that case, I am even more grateful.
Oh then... Here.
It's my number, to call.
As I have something to do now,
I will treat you to a meal next time.
What did you do that?
This time you can ask for dry cleaning fee.
Won't I have to compensate you?
=[Kkatalk] with Bullshit Prince=
Got it dry-cleaned well?
What are you doing this weekend?
=[Kkatalk] with Bullshit Prince=
Performing now?
If your fingers aren't broken,
you better give me a call.
What's this? He is not even checking it.
Dead or what?
Su Yeong. By chance, did you die?
Why aren't you even checking the texts?
If you are alive, for God's sake
at least check it, Su Yeong.
Have this to wash it down.
Is that young lady still incommunicado?
Yes. She isn't even checking the texts.
She may be trying not to hurt you.
Actually I wanted to tell you this...
As I see it, that young lady
has got another man.
That is not so. Su Yeong is just fickle
which I can't... say she is not.
It is just not another man, you know.
It can't be, right? Ajumma?
(Ajumma - Older lady, aunt)
What, he can read people's minds?
Of course. I told you it's true.
How does he know others' minds?
Is he psychic?
What psychic? Must be a con-man.
Look at you. I told you my thoughts got pulled
out word for word. He was reading it all.
What is so hard in that?
I can do that too.
Shall I try reading your thoughts?
What?
Try to read, try to read,
what I am thinking of.
"As she wants to scold me now, can she possibly
guess my mind?". Isn't that what you thought?
- What?
- So I guessed it right?
Why are you looking like that?
Ah, this ground meat, damn.
What's with you?
Who am I?
What do you mean who?
What? You are Choe Yeong's ex?
Why again say that?
It was all over, I said.
Yes, you should stop. Dad had to suffer through
as much as he possibly could, because of it.
He was really in bad shape.
It's fine, you leave it alone.
I'm somebody who had cancer surgery.
What kind of food is ground meat,
for one who had cancer surgery?
Ground meat is said to be
most lethal with cancer.
There you go again. When you already eat
all that Chaga mushrooms and blueberries.
If I eat those things, that's enough?
You hardly bother about my diet.
I'm cancer-stricken.
The cancer was in such an
early stage, seriously!
Early stage or zero stage, it is cancer.
Cancer!
You are always like nothing at all
has happened, with me.
Why so? What is your reason?
I do want to know that, really!
Oh, I know, I know. Don't eat it then.
Eat something else, whatever it is.
Okay, I'll eat it.
But... From now on, you better
take care of me a bit!
Rascal, you're bothersome, really!
Don't be saying that, please.
If Cheol Min had cancer surgery and it's
ground meat here, would you say that?
Why are you staring, all round-eyed,
you silly whelp?
You have nothing else to do
but ask for trouble?
His eyes were always round,
so what are you going to do?
Sure, sure. Say no more, please. Just don't.
Jong Seok!
It's for me. That friend.
Here I go, to meet him.
Why are you like this
since a while back?
You have a call you need to wait for?
Nothing like that.
This is all 1, it seems.
Why are you looking at others' texts?
If it's 1, it could be blocked.
What?
Didn't you tell me that?
If the number 1 doesn't go away,
it could be blocked, you said.
Who would block me?
You think I'm like you, grandfather?
What's there to think?
Didn't you say...
that it's like knocking 100 times at a house
and nobody answering.
It is not so, okay?
Geez.
Come on, let's go.
This means I'm blocked?
How dare this lowlife...
How are you?
I was anyway going to call you.
Looks like you contacted first.
I just wanted to see you, grandpa.
That's a good thing!
We could've eaten something expensive.
Why did you pick a sundae shop to meet?
(Sundae - Rice stuffed in intestines)
Sundae is tasty, right?
Would you like to order?
A sundae soup for me.
I...
Sundae soup without any more meat,
and with just sundae in it.
Okay.
How did you know that I liked to eat that?
Didn't I tell you, that I can look at the eyes
and hear what one is thinking?
Sundae soup is what you like most, right?
I had read that also, the last time.
That's why you asked to come here?
Next time, let's plan to go eat some meat.
I will buy you something good.
It's all right.
But grandpa, don't you feel odd about
me reading other people's thoughts?
Most people get scared like I'm some monster.
Monster?
It's strange, yes, but not scary.
It's because they don't know. Isn't there
so much in this world that feels strange
only because we don't understand it?
You can't be coming in here.
It's that... there's someone I need to find.
That guitarist... Where is he?
Who?
- That worn-out... and dark-looking... that..
- Worn-out and dark-looking?
Jang Yul seems to be who she's talking of.
Oh, Jang Yul?
He quit.
He quit?
Why?
Who knows?
Ah, whatever...
He himself said it.
Our shades of music don't match or whatever.
That fellow, what bloody shade is that?
We have the shade of shit and
he has a shade of gold?
What's this, what's this, come on...
What's with you?
You think I am that guy?
Where is that guy's place?
It should be somewhere here...
Which corner rat-hole is he living in?
~ I am in love with you, hey why not,
for real, in love with you. ~
just like this, I can confess. ~
This doesn't work.
This is supposed to be a song?
Look here.
~ I am in love with you, hey why not,
for real, in love with you. ~
~ ..not, extremely, in love with you. ~
~ ..not, like dying, in love with you. ~
Look here, Jang Yul.
Ah, that shocked me.
Even your shock comes slow, it seems.
You know me, right?
Have a chat with me.
This sucks baldy. My feet hurt like I'll die but
even the seats for the elderly are all taken.
What are you doing?
That gentleman is getting off at the next stop.
Is that so?
What did you want to say?
Why do you ignore my texts?
I did not ignore...
What are you saying? I was always checking.
Got dry cleaning done.
There is no weekend performance.
Why must we get in touch?
What kind of response is that,
combined over so many days?
I am not one who beats around the bush.
Honestly you are not even my type.
Your looks are kinda meh...
Your style is all worn-out.
I even know that you have no interest in me.
As an impoverished musician,
you are inconsequential at present.
You'll only be more inconsequential
in the future. I know all that.
Are you even hearing what I am saying?
Yes.
If you are hearing, make at least
a sound in response... Seriously!
Let me continue.
You're so leisurely in your response
that it bugs me.
You won't see the texts properly.
You won't take a call properly.
So, if we start dating, that will be a horror incident
the vision of which already flashes into my eyes.
But I still have a feeling of curiosity.
Not a good feeling, but a curious feeling.
So I would say...
Let us date.
That was too short.
Didn't you hear it?
Let's date, I said.
I saw it a little while back.
What?
The texts.
I saw it a little while back,
and replied right away.
I responded to what I heard too.
But why?
What kind of a 'why'...
When I said we should date, what's this 'why'?
Just like that. Why should we
do that, I wondered.
You hardly interest me.
I said I know that you aren't interested in me.
Anyway, make a decision quickly.
Will you date or will you not?
You take your own sweet time, so
a reply takes a few days, I guess.
Don't forget, and reply.
You must reply, okay?
If I don't get a quick reply, I will be
so curious, I won't even get sleep.
I won't be able to do anything all day long.
Understood?
He is so slow.
I will be waiting. Understand?
I said it was fine not to escort me,
but you still came all the way.
It is a dangerous world, you know.
Grandpa, you are a precious person for me.
Me?
Yes.
I got separated from my family
when I was young.
All this while I was living alone.
But when I am with you, grandpa,
It feels like I have got a family again.
Wouldn't that mean you're precious?
You punk.
This street light is still not fixed?
Now you can go.
Till you've left, I won't be going in.
Yes.
Hey, look at this silly whelp.
I turn around, and you're back up on the sofa?
You are the leaseholder of this sofa?
You whelp. You seem to
ignore it that I'm here.
You are a dog. You think
dogs can ignore people?
You... Father may be a little fond of you,
but stop showing off to me, seriously.
How long do you think you can
just monopolize Father's love?
You feel love is eternal?
You plan to keep bullying Cheol Min?
What bullying? I was just
goofing around with him.
Oh my... Cheol Min.
Were you doing all right?
Why is the street light in front
of the house still not fixed?
Give them a call tomorrow.
Yeah, what's it?
What?
That rascal...
Thank you.
Yes. Take care.
The bad street light seem to be fixed.
Who did this nice thing?
It was me.
What?
No. Nothing.
What's this? This guy looks a bit strange.
Good-looking, though.
Does he live around here?
No. Way over around there.
What's the deal with him?
Ah, that scared me.
I thought a car was coming in.
The street lamp was kaput, but you
didn't even come and pick me up?
Even otherwise, I was about to change
and come to pick you up, silly girl.
But why are you standing here
if you were changing clothes?
As you read it, I will go dry the clothes.
CEO sir?
Ms. Na Jin A.
Yes. Are you doing well?
You must be by yourself, to have called me.
Yes. There is something I'm curious of.
What is it?
By chance...
"Tarzan has 10 Wons worth of underpants on him"
"20-Wons worth is the sword he
wields as he sings songs".
Do you know this song?
What?
Yes, I do know that.
That's good to hear.
Mom is not taking the call, so there was
nobody but you to ask, Ms. Na Jin A.
By chance... if Tarzan is wearing
underpants worth 90 Wons,
do you know how much his
word should be worth?
If it's after 90 Wons,
shouldn't it be 100 Wons?
100... 100 Wons...
Then, "Tarzan..."
How will that work?
"Tarzan has 90 Wons worth of underpants on him"
"Hundred Wons worth is..."
Oh, it's just "hundred".
We can't say "Ten 10 Wons".
It is "1 hundred Wons".
We drop the "1" and just say "hundred".
"100 Wons worth is the sword he
wields as he sings songs. Ah Oh Ah..."
I can see that.
Thank you.
I may call you again.
Sure. Go back to rest.
Oh... Good Lord...
What call was that?
What kind of call is it, with Tarzan songs and all?
Better not to know.
You must reply, okay?
If I don't get a quick reply, I will be
so curious, I won't even get sleep.
I won't be able to do anything all day long.
Understood?
Oh, loca!
I've gone crazy.
Completely a hanging ending, wasn't it?
What? Can't sleep and can't do anything, I said?
This hurts my pride.
What to do, what to do?
Su Yeong, I'm in front of your house.
Let's meet briefly.
I have something to ask.
I will ask you straight-fart-word...
It's not "fart-word".
"Forward".
"Straight-forward."
If so, then I will ask like that.
Su Yeong,
By chance have you found somebody you like?
Yeah.
Sorry.
Oh my God!
Don't tell me I have to eat through this.
It's not "eat through", but "get through".
Heck, "eat" or "get",
is it what's important?
That means, because of that guy,
you are splitting up with me?
It's not like that.
My mind has already changed from before.
Didn't I talk to you about all that?
If I like another person,
it has nothing to do with you.
That person also likes you a lot, Su Yeong?
- No.
- No?
He said he has no interest in me.
Then why?
I have interest in him, so I don't care.
I'm sorry. Really.
Su Yeong.
The ajummas at the sauna house said this.
For women, rather than men they like,
it's men who like seeing them
who make them happier.
I can make you happy, Su Yeong.
I brought some appetizer dishes with me.
- How is Min Hyeok?
- Whoa Whoa...
Why are you again going "whoa whoa"?
Didn't I tell you not to do that?
Mom. Somebody Grandfather knows, is able to
look into people's eyes and read their thoughts.
What do you mean?
He met some strange guy recently and
is all excited. It's about that fellow.
Grandfather is dating again?
Dating a guy wouldn't match him,
but this feels just like dating.
They talk on the phone everyday.
Some days back he was like this
from the 2nd floor window...
"Take care. Dream of me!"
That's how they two were parting.
Really?
"Take care, dream of me" was what he said?
I wonder if "dream of me" was said...
But anyway, the feel of it was just like that.
They both were terribly mushy-mushy.
What's this? What gives?
Cheol Min, you whelp.
You are also finished.
Father now likes somebody
more than you. You get it?
You were all acting high and mighty
from getting Father's love.
Serves you right, you silly whelp.
Don't just take painkillers.
Just go to a dentist.
Careful. You'll get hurt.
Son of a bitch.
Not even calling, in the end.
Hello.
=What are you doing?=
What do you mean what?
=What are you doing in the evening?
We're going clubbing. You want to go?=
What's in it? Forget it.
No no. Let's go, let's go.
Where are you going?
And then?
What?
This is really funny.
Let's stop talking on the phone.
Let's meet and chat.
Coffee would be fine with me too.
Fine.
That cafe?
Now?
What time in the evening?
I got it.
What the hell are you? Get lost!
So I would say...
Let us date.
Just like that. Why should we
do that, I wondered.
You hardly interest me.
You must reply, okay?
If I don't get a quick reply, I will be
so curious, I won't even get sleep.
I won't be able to do anything all day long.
Understood?
Fine, that's it. I too won't date now.
It's finished.
~ I am in love with you, hey why not,
for real, in love with you. ~
~ ..for real, in love with you, hey? ~
Even after sending so much blood into the head,
the lyrics are just not happening...
Hey, son of a bitch! This can flat-out
shock you when I tell you this.
May be this won't be pleasant to hear.
If you ask why,
I live like it's no big deal.
Nothing special that bothers me.
There are no worries to speak of.
Flat out...
Flat out shocking you...
...shocking you... will be what I tell...
Go wake up father-in-law.
Ask him to have dinner soon.
Is he still saying he won't get up?
Then what was the use in taking
2 painkiller tablets?
Well, he says the toothache is really bad.
Father. Please have dinner.
It's already past 9 o'clock.
Have dinner quickly.
9 o'clock?
Jong Seok! I had promised to meet Jong Seok.
Why did you promise to meet him again?
What is that guy, for you to keep going--
He goes to meet that guy and even
kicks you on the way out!
Your good times are all a
thing of the past, you see!
Now you are also like me, like
Nakdong river's ducks that nobody cares for!
Why are you here, getting drenched?
You should have gone inside.
Wasn't it here that we said we'd meet?
You weren't taking the calls, and
because of rain I couldn't come over either.
I don't know what I should do with you.
If you catch a cold or something,
what will we do?
You haven't eaten dinner, right?
Let's go to eat some food.
Though it's late, let's go eat some meat.
It's all right.
We will just eat some Sundae.
We'll eat meat today.
Hadn't I said that I would buy you
some tasty meat?
Let's get up.
Grandpa, are you a fool?
Even with the toothache,
buying me food is the issue for you?
How can you do this?
This rascal...
What is that? What are they doing?
What is that grandpa up to?
With some boy?
Must be a Grandpa Over Flowers.
[Refers to a Korean drama title]
~ Live like it's no big deal,
there are no worries to speak of. ~
Who are you?
Have a brief chat with me.
What you want to tell me, is...?
You know Su Yeong, right?
Suyeom?
(Suyeom - Beard)
Not Su Yeom. Su Yeong.
No Su Yeong.
Yeah.
But why?
I am someone who loves Su Yeong.
But Su Yeong... says it's you she likes.
But I heard you don't even
have an interest in Su Yeong.
You definitely won't be able to date Su Yeong.
Su Yeong's temperament is so impatient.
She's a woman who changes the order
from the menu 5 times at a restaurant.
You both definitely don't match.
Don't play hard to get.
Cut-and-dried... reject her that way.
You have nothing to say?
Whatever it is, just say it out.
Forget it.
In any case, I will leave,
assuming that you will do so.
It feels like you can't leave assuming that.
What?
I'm also getting it.
Getting what?
Interest.
In that woman.
You said you had no interest!
I'm getting it.
Some 3 hours ago onwards.
Dating, it is.
- Grandpa!
- Jong Seok!
You're back from the dentist's?
It's all perfect now.
Shall we go eat some meat today?
He is the Cheol Min you've been raising?
Mmm.. He is. He's always following me,
so I thought I'd bring him along today.
Cheol Min, glad to meet you.
So it's you?
This so-called Jong Seok fellow?
What's it?
May be you read dog-minds too?
I must say I'll bite you.
I'll bite those who have heard of you too.
I'll bite them all, bar none.
It's nothing.
I need a toilet trip.
Watch Cheol Min just for a bit.
Yes. Go ahead.
You dog-shit-smelling punk.
I was waiting for this day.
In all of this... I was not the cause.
You are the one starting it!
Hey, what's with you?
Wait there. You can't. You can't bite.
You can't bite!
How come you aren't eating?
Because of that guy you talked about?
That fellow has completely fooled grandfather.
I can no longer let it go. That punk.
When you see him, just bite his ding dong.
To humans, that is most lethal.
Ding Dong?
Ah, yes!
-=Next Episode Preview=-
Wait a moment!
If I am within a 1 km radius,
Near U will start flashing right then.
I see the family that giving you company
changing shifts once every day.
Jun Hyeok never come.
Who is Jun Hyeok?
Jun Hyeok, am I right?
I don't really know.
Even feeling pain comes slow to you?
She found some other man in the end?
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
It's right, my baby.
It's really the decisive secret aspect.
Foreskin surgery?
I'm sorry, but let me take a look.
Right?
It's grown like this?
You are the lost son of this family?
Who are you?
-=[link] The strongest comics in the Universe=-
-=that you can now enjoy with your games!=-
-=Jong Seok=-
-=Dear customer, it is now possible for you to=-
-=get even a 50 Million Won Loan. Anytime...=-
-=Bullshit Prince=-
-=Delete Contact=-
-=Delete Selected Contacts=-
-=Cancel. Confirm=-