Live for long, and I only end up
sleeping in somebody's garage...
Look what our life is...
You said it... This is like a horse-stable
of a house in the old days.
Mom, thanks to you we really
gain worldly experience.
Ms. Gil Seon Ja, you're the best.
Whatever you say, I am your mom,
so what can you do about it?
Just take it as your fate.
Who said anything here?
How come it is so cold?
You didn't turn on the hot mat?
I did. The water in it isn't warm yet.
See, had I not redeemed at least this hot mat,
you think we could've slept in such a place?
It's the hot mats that made us
sleep in such a place.
Your sense of reality is in the pits, really!
In the pits? You wretched girl...
It's cold.
If you want so much to get away from me,
you leave.
I will stay like this temporarily.
Temporarily until when?
I won't tell you. Just know that living
apart from you is the wish of my life.
Attain your life's wish now itself.
Live apart. Hurry, leave now.
You just wait. I will do just that.
What? You let them stay in the garage?
You out of your mind?
How can you let people stay in the garage?
Even the garage won't work?
What you are doing is too much!
Too much or too small,
get them out quickly.
Min Hyeok is in that shape. Why the heck
bring outsiders into the house?
Even families have secrets to keep.
They have nowhere to go, you know.
They are Soe Dol's family.
Soe Dol's family, so what?
How long back did he die?
Absolutely no way.
Send them out first thing tomorrow morning!
Damn, I'm cancer-stricken!
Cancer-stricken, so what?
Stop this old cancer talk.
He said it's in an early stage.
Why go overboard like this?
It's not overboard. I know this.
My mom was in the same shape too.
I know it...
My ending will be the same as Mom's.
No mistaking it.
My sad premonitions never miss the mark.
Yeah right, sad premonition!
It never fails to go wrong.
What?
What do you mean what?
Bo Yeong wasn't feeling well, but did that
premonition say that she was pregnant?
Father-in-law had blood in his stool, and did
the premonition say it was hemorrhoids?
What had it got correct?
Why bring up old matters?
Anyway from now on,
I'll do things I wish to do.
To those who did favors to me,
I want to do good things, okay?
Only then will I have no regrets
whatever happens to me.
Doing good things or repaying favors
is all up to you.
Those people in the garage
must be sent out pronto tomorrow!
Give a bit of thought to me losing face, please!
What's with you, really?
It's a garage that I gave to
them who deserve a room!
Even that I cannot do? Really?
Just give them money for
them to go find a place.
Whatever... Forget it.
I too don't give a damn.
When I'm already cancer-stricken,
must you make me lose face too?
If I said no way, it means no way!
But how do we eat some food?
What do we do for a bathroom?
They'll have to let us use a bathroom.
Would they ask us to eat with them?
That would be the best.
Not sure of a bathroom, but eating... well...
Rich people would never want to
face people like us.
Is it so?
Well, anyway we get a good look
at a rich family's house.
Where we step out from here
is a proper garden.
Huh?
Don't step into the garden?
I had to agree on that with my wife. I am sorry.
But if we can't step into the garden,
how can we come in?
Through the roll-up shutter
garage entrance.
My wife has become damn sensitive lately
since our oldest son got hurt, that's why.
Please understand it for me.
If it's through the shutters, that means we wait
for a car to return and only then get in?
I will get a garage remote made for you.
On this itself, my wife was asking
how we could open it for outsiders?
I insisted that I would open it.
Thank you so much.
Then, let me know if there is any discomfort.
Then, excuse me...
From now on, what's going to happen?
I'm told the CEO's falling incident
will be investigated by the police.
Really?
Yes.
Seeing them investigate, it appears not to be
a pure accident. Who would have done it?
Not sure.
And also, there is a rumor that
the CEO's condition isn't normal.
Really?
Team leader, you go every day to top staff
meetings, but you seem clueless on this.
An outcast now?
Me?
Adviser, sir.
You weren't supposed to step into the garden.
I'm sorry.
What is it?
Could I ask you if the CEO is doing all right?
I was just worried.
He's fine. If you're asked at the company,
just say he is fine.
I told Chauffeur Gim to keep it a secret that you
are living at my house, so nobody will ask you.
But don't come out and say anything.
Why are you eating alone?
What?
An open outcast or
quietly isolated?
What's this?
Don't do this to me today, okay?
For this graphics, it's enough
if you fill in your survey data.
Try typing it.
Where did you go and why won't
you show up? Hongberg...
Miss Jin A, you aren't coming to the dinner party?
I'll try finishing this proposal
and then come over.
Do it later. Come fast.
But, team leader, I shouldn't
think of having drinks today.
Is it okay if I don't drink?
I thought you said you wouldn't drink...
Miss Jin A, is something wrong?
Or something unpleasant?
Nothing like that.
It's like this, just like that...
They all suddenly disappeared.
Damn, it's messed up!
You'll all be fine when you leave.
But what about me? Me!
Mom.
Coming only now?
You were drinking?
Yeah.. Dinner party.
Why are you here?
Came out to pee, but couldn't get back in.
Damn, this place really sucks. To any restroom
in this residential area, it is 3 miles!
Gosh, they should let us use
at least a potty, seriously!
But street lights are bright, so I wasn't
scared at night. Now, that is great!
Even if it's night, I need not come to get you.
That's all really great, yeah sure!
If he's giving a remote, give it fast!
Why make us wait for a car to come?
It's really petty, really.
Do the surgery on Monday.
Stay for 2 days afterwards.
Get up. The car's here.
You've returned?
Any inconvenience, yet?
Well... When can we get the
shutter remote, I wonder...
That's right. Here!
Thank you.
How come so...
How come you look so distressed?
Is it that obvious... on me?
That is... sort of... like that.
What is it?
That day I happened to overhear.
It seemed you talked of cancer.
Are you seriously ill?
Is it really showing?
I must undergo surgery, in 3 days.
Ah, I see...
That is a secret.
Other than my wife, nobody knows it.
If other family folks know,
it will throw them into chaos.
Your dad is having a tumor surgery on Monday.
What tumor?
Something minuscule on the kidney.
As I'm told, it's in fact a cancer.
As it's early, remove it and it's done.
The surgery is simpler than
even an appendicitis surgery.
No need to cut open anywhere else?
Yes. Early stage.
Saying the family would be in confusion
he had asked not to tell.
But there was nothing here
to keep it a secret.
So I am keeping you posted.
Bo Yeong.
Why keep it a secret?
What big chaos?
The fellow really goes overboard!
Cheol Min. Why do you keep groaning
and squealing these days?
Are you feeling unwell?
You're back, dad?
Dad, I heard you have a surgery on Monday?
Who said that?
Mom did.
Have a great surgery. Fighting!
Brat... Fine, this dad... will do the fighting.
I wanted to keep it a secret
from you till the end...
What's with you?
Father.
Please don't worry too much.
Whatever happens, I won't cry.
So father, you too--
Is he not going to croak it?
Croak it...
- Father.
- Cheol Min,
What's wrong?
I see. Good job.
You're back?
Why did you tell the family about the surgery?
What's the big deal if I did?
What? Somebody said something?
Who cares to say anything?
Who has any concern for me anyway?
What is wrong?
After talking of the surgery, there was
no big commotion, so you are angry?
Su Yeong at least said a "fighting".
But my father... seriously!
It's cold.
So cold.
I'm leaving to see Min Hyeok at the hospital.
You're going somewhere?
I have to take this fellow to the vet.
You want me to take you?
It's fine. I'll walk over there.
Hello--
Her manners!
Where did the wretched girl go?
Mom. I'm scared.
The surgery is day after tomorrow.
I'm worried to death, about the fellow.
All the odd thoughts come up suddenly.
If it goes wrong and something happens
to the fellow, what will I do, I wonder.
I keep tearing up...
Father.
I don't know if he can withstand a surgery.
The fellow has some age too...
Please don't worry, father.
I... shall firmly withstand it.
Please don't say such things.
I can't live without the fellow.
I can't live even for a day.
Every day, he's so happy when I come in,
moving my heart.
In the morning when my eyes are closed,
he comes to lick my face.
Really... I can't live without this fellow.
Bye then.
Father!
Oh so suddenly!
Why do you yell and get on my nerves?
So the fellow was Cheol Min?
Without whom you won't live.
Thinking of whom brings out tears.
The one who won't withstand
a surgery... is not me then!
I am your son.
I am cancer-stricken..
What's with you? Your surgery is simple.
It's the early stages.
But I have cancer you know!
Cancer, cancer. Cancer!
What surgery does this whelp have?
Does this whelp have cancer?
He has kidney trouble. Why?
The whelp has some kidney stone.
I have cancer!
I'm your cancer-stricken son, okay!
This whelp is not a person, but a dog!
All he has is kidney stones.
I can't even get as much of your
concern as this whelp does? Huh?
- You stupid fellow!
- Father, you never liked me even
getting into your sight, no? Right?
The moment you gave a son of a bitch
a human name, I knew it!
This whelp is more of a son to you than me?
Right?
Dad, why are you like this?
Let go!
Father!
You really shouldn't be treating me like this!
Once I'm dead and gone, you can be
with this whelp for a million years...
Dad.
Why is he like that?
That twerp... seriously.
If that twerp is like this, what's he good for?
I am back.
You're here?
Did my son sleep well?
But why are you sitting like that today
without seeing NarARa Superboard?
(Korean animation circa 1992)
In NarARa Superboard, when he sees the
Son O Gong monkey fool scenes,
(Korean animation circa 1992)
he gets stressed out.
Why would Son O Gong monkey fool
stress him out?
Then we used to ask him to
recall this Gong or that Gong,
so he may've got some
psychological damage.
I think he feels he has the
same plight as Son O Gong.
Suddenly he can't get even a bit of sleep.
Really? You did a good job. Go back.
Min Hyeok. See you tomorrow.
My son is a bit down on
NarARa Superboard, huh?
What do we do to play?
You remember the Tarzan song?
The one you sang every day
in kindergarten days.
Don't you remember?
I can remember it.
Tarzan has 10 Wons worth of
underpants on him.
20-Wons is the sword that he will
wield as he sings songs.
Remember it?
Join me.
Tarzan has 20-Wons worth of
underpants on him.
- 30-Wons is the sword that he will--
- Mom, I get nausea...
I want to go out.
We'll do that?
Okay.
Hey, my friend.
How many times should I say?
Really, it is not a serious surgery.
My mom's was also the same.
She was operated on saying
it was nothing serious.
That was in old days.
For you, we've done all the cell biopsies.
It's just fine. Pefectly clean.
Don't worry, and come over thinking
you are getting a stomach inspection.
It's hot.
Really hot.
Oh... friggin hot.
Happy to have come outside?
In a little while, you can play the
memory game with the doctor.
Shall we do a bit of practice?
No.
You don't like anything today?
Ah, right! Shall we do some Tamagotchi?
(Japanese electronic pet game, mid 1990s)
What I had brought for you earlier
as you wanted to play pet-raising?
(Japanese electronic pet game, mid 1990s)
Then wait a little bit.
I'll go to the car and get it.
Tarzan has 10 Wons worth of
underpants on him.
- 20-Wons is the sword that he will--
- CEO sir?
Is this where you were? In this hospital?
Who are you?
Huh?
It's me, Na Jin A.
Na Jin A?
Don't you remember me?
Intern... Na Jin A.
Intern... What's that?
Then, you don't remember anything
about the company either?
How come?
Then nuna... Are you a nuna in our company?
(Nuna - sister or elder girl to a male)
Yes. But I'm not a nuna to you.
Na Ji Na, is what you've been calling me.
I see.
Ms. Na Jin A.
Yes.
What work do you do at our company?
What work?
It was just... whatever you asked, CEO sir.
Really?
Then, if I need something bought from there,
will you buy it for me?
What?
What would be...
Ice cream!
Ice cream?
Sure.
But... I don't have my wallet with me.
Instead, I'll surely buy it later for you.
Really?
Yes.
Promise...
This is a telephone, right?
Let me know your phone number.
My phone number?
You knew it earlier...
010-?34267.
Shall I write it for you?
I don't have a pencil.
010.. ?3403...
434267.
010-?434267.
Who are you?
That means you are...
that Soe Dol's daughter?
Yes. I'm sorry.
How can you think of getting
in the car after getting drunk?
This is why I told him not to let people
into the garage. In the end...
I'm sorry.
I heard you were an intern in our company.
What will you be saying in the company?
What?
What will you say about Min Hyeok, I mean.
What did you feel, seeing Min Hyeok?
Tell me honestly.
After seeing Min Hyeok, what did you
feel his condition is?
- I did...
- Idiot? Like an idiot?
Idiot is what you'll say?
No, no. "I didn't know for sure when I met him
just now" was what I was going to say.
But he seems to have lost some memory.
That's what you'll go to
the company and say?
You're a cheap-mouth, right?
No. I am not.
Seeing that mouth on the face, if you open it
it's big enough to fill it, so it must be cheap!
It's nooot soooo....
Sure? Then, take it like
you never saw Min Hyeok today.
- Do you keep your word?
- Yes.
Why do I see your eyes go here and there,
like you won't be keeping it?
I will be keeping my word.
Dad's now on the way to get admitted.
Okay.
Oh... It is Grandfather.
Cheol Min is also getting admitted today.
Admitted?
That whelp too?
Let's take Grandfather to
Cheol Min's vet.
- Chauffeur Gim...
- Leave it.
Just go on, Chauffeur Gim.
You have been at the Adviser's house?
Not at the house. In the garage.
I had a bit of a situation, so
the Adviser sir helped out.
But how did you know of that?
If it has to do with the company, won't I
know it all like the back of my palm?
I heard you are Na Soe Dol's daughter.
Yes. Did you know my dad?
Not just knowing...
He was close to me too.
Really? My dad--
CEO No Min Hyeok...
What is his current status?
Pardon?
Then, take it like you never saw
Min Hyeok today.
I don't know... all that well...
Is the CEO right now at the house...
or at the hospital?
I'm not sure. As I stay in the garage,
I don't know of anything.
How come Father-in-law's health is not-so-good?
I'm not sure.
He is jealous of Cheol Min, and unsatisfied with
Grandfather, which is really his condition.
In any case, he would like it if we worry a lot,
so show some good concern. Do you see?
- Yeah.
- Our dad, geez...
- You guys too?
- Yes.
Gim Gyu Yeong.
Why didn't you answer?
What?
What is it you asked?
Dad, eonni and family are here.
(Eonni - elder sister)
- Hello.
Oh my, father-in-law! Such a troublesome
surgery... what do we do?
Well... No other option...
Life is all like this, no? One only looks
for a narrow escape from death...
You shouldn't say stuff like escaping death!
Dad, you have to live a long time.
Thank you.
Mom has to be in charge at oppa's room,
so she can't come today. You know it, right?
Of course she should watch Min Hyeok.
But... in the end your grandfather...
isn't coming, is he?
Grandfather... well, it's that
there is nobody at home.
Don't say it's to watch the house!
He is surely hugging and pampering
that whelp Cheol Min.
To my father, that son of a bitch is a million times
more precious than this cancer-stricken me.
Why do you say it like that?
Cheol Min's is also a major surgery.
Then me? I have cancer!
Father will come to his senses only once I die.
No. Even if I die, he'll only be
pampering that whelp Cheol Min.
This really sucks.
I'll go to dad and come, okay?
As the patient in room 2 could not sleep all night,
he's to be given a sleep inducer dose after dinner.
You know it?
Yes, we know that.
Hello.
It is 010-?434267, right?
What?
Ms. Nuna Jin A...
Nuna Jin A?
Who are you?
I am No Min Hyeok.
CEO sir. But why are you...
You said you'd buy me ice cream but
why haven't you bought it for me?
That... I was supposed to buy
when we meet next time.
Why not ask Mom to buy it today,
and next time I can--
Not what I want... Buy it for me now.
I am all alone now.
Where are you?
9th floor. 9.
What room?
Number 2.
Hello? CEO sir?
Mr. No Su Dong, please be ready to
go into the surgery room in 5 minutes.
Dad, "fighting!". You got it?
I guess it is that whelp Cheol Min
who has my father with him for surgery.
Fine. You just watch.
I won't forget this till I die.
You all watch closely how I will
treat your grandfather till I die!
What kind of pointless crap
are you saying to the kids?
He did say he would come.
Must be stuck in traffic on the way.
What is the point if he comes only after
that whelp Cheol Min's surgery is done?
That's even more disgusting!
A surgery is supposed to go well only if
one goes in with a happy mood.
Going in with this kind of a mood,
is it possible for the surgery to go well?
I guess it probably won't.
I don't have the will to even live.
- Looks like Grandfather has come.
- You are here?
You still haven't gone into surgery?
What did you come here for, now?
What?
You rascal, I had a hard time getting here,
and you ask what for?
Father, I'll ask you just one thing.
You came because that son of a bitch
Cheol Min's surgery got done,
or was it despite it going on?
So what about it?
Useless fellow.
Please do tell. Going into surgery with this kind
of a mood, makes me feel discomfort.
Did you came once Cheol Min's surgery
was done, or while it was going on?
- Oh, stop it.
- Father.
We will be moving you in for surgery.
Wait a moment. Tell me please. You came after
Cheol Min's surgery was done. Isn't it so?
Please tell me. I asked you to please tell me!
Hold on a moment.
One moment, stop!
Stop right here.
There, there, there, there, useless fellow!
Damn, when will he get some sense?
I'm administering anesthesia.
Father. Cheol Min is what...
Why is he so unanesthetized?
Why is this patient whispering?
Cheol Min is a son of a bitch.
I will have you dead and...
What are you here for?
I came to visit Mr. No Min Hyeok in room 2.
Visitors are prohibited for the room 2 patient.
Is that so? Would it be all right
for you to pass this on to him?
As it is ice cream, I fear it will melt.
Outside food is also prohibited.
I had said I'd get it for him...
You got it, right?
It will all melt. What to do?
You can't sleep well lately, right?
Once you get this shot, sleep will come.
Nuna!
Keep it quiet. The nurse said
that visits are prohibited.
You bought ice cream and came?
Yes.
It has melted a bit. We will keep it in
the freezer for a bit before having it.
Also, I'm not a nuna, CEO sir.
Please call me Ms. Na Jin A.
Okay...
When I got your call earlier, I was a little lost.
But now I feel right about this.
As I met you so suddenly last time,
there was a lot that I couldn't say.
What is it that you couldn't say?
First of all, so happy to see you.
Really!
And then, have you been doing well?
It is like I had a lot to say.
But I don't remember anything.
So I get scared.
As I don't know what I might have lost.
Thoughts will slowly come out.
Please don't get too worried.
Everybody at the company is looking forward
to you getting healthy and returning, CEO sir.
Because in our company, you are...
like this!
I... What kind of person was I?
What kind of person you were, you mean?
Can I tell you as we eat the ice cream?
I think it should be frozen by now.
Fine.
Last time when you asked me to get it, a child had
bought ice cream and was eating something else.
It is that ice cream that
you want to eat first, right?
Are you sleepy?
No, I'm not.
If you are sleepy, you want to
sleep and eat it later?
If you eat it now, you will
have to brush your teeth.
It's all right. Please tell me the things.
Sure. First, you are a smart person
who is even a Harvard graduate.
What is this harvard?
It is the best university in the world.
Even with that, you were quite humble.
There are two ways to be successful in life.
Either you're great,
or you stick alongside someone great.
If I am of the first type,
you are all of the second type.
Because you met me.
You were always warm and friendly with people.
Hating those gasbags who tout their worthless
degrees, I had picked you instead, Na Jin A.
But it's equally useless after all.
More than anything, you're the one who let me
join the company... which I'm thankful for.
Ice Cream...
It is right here.
Sleep and eat it later.
Put it in the fridge.
Yes. I'll put in the fridge.
Ms. Na Jin A.
Yes?
- Later on... Is it okay to call you again?
- Yes.
-=Next Episode Preview=-
I am told my grandson was doing
a bit of mischief. I'm really sorry.
Are you an ocean seal? A monkey?
Who threw this out?
I guess we can't throw trash out now...
This is trash?
Whatever it is that is uncomfortable,
feel free to tell.
If you could lend us a pot, so we could
cook something to eat...
Better know that this is all because
your mom is a good one.
CEO sir?
Yes, are you doing fine?
And you, CEO sir?
Shall we cajole Na Jin A into it?
Even if we make her come to our side,
if she fails, we're finished.
Sister-in-law, come in and
take care of business.
Whatever.
No!
Please go back.
She just wants to use a bathroom.
Even that isn't allowed?
Is this family into playing with people or what?
-=Episode 13=-
-=This story is purely fictional. Any resemblance
to real people or incidents is only coincidental.=-
-=The day of Su Dong's surgery=-