[One week before the live show]
[What's with this room?]
What's this?
I can't see anything.
Is this on purpose?
What do you think you'll do here?
I don't know.
Oh it's an envelope.
[What is inside of the envelope?]
Gosh, what is this?
Do you remember?
Yes.
Wow.
This is making me realize that I've come really far.
-Do you remember when you were writing it? -Yes.
I doubted that I would make it and just turned it in.
[First step towards the dream]
Don't do this.
No.
What?
[Footage from last summer's district try-outs]
What is that?
I don't want to see it.
[Not confident but with passion alone,]
[they threw themselves into the world]
I kept thinking,
even if I didn't do music, wouldn't it be okay to live a normal life?
But now I feel like I found something again.
I learned so many things here.
I feel like I grew here a lot.
It's a very valuable experience for me.
I'm somehow doing the things people cannot do even if they wanted to.
I didn't know I was special.
But I came here and they really loved me.
So I was really happy.
I want to make music that would be helpful to those people.
[Incheon Nam-dong center live show]
Survival audition K-pop star season 5.
Introducing the TOP 6 contestants that made it into the live shows and the 3 judges!
The soul-genius Yoo Jay!
The sentiments of ballad, Lee Si-eun!
And the judge Park Jin-young!
[Yoo Jay, Lee Si-eun]
The endlessly charming Woo Ye-rin!
The center of popularity Ahn Ye-eun!
And the judge Yoo Hee-yeol!
[Woo Ye-rin, Ahn Ye-eun]
The best of sentimental R&B Lee Soo-jung!
Charismatic Mazinger S!
And the judge Yang Hyun-suk!
[Lee Soo-jung, Mazinger S]
Please give a round of applause to the TOP 6 who made it through so many stages
and the 3 judges.
Survival audition K-pop star season 5 emcee Jun Hyun-moo. Hello!
The judges and the TOP 6 has been invited on stage.
This is your first time for you. Right Mr. Yoo?
Yes, it's my first time making an appearance like this.
Yes you look a little nervous.
I didn't know when I was up there.
But this is what the contestants must be feeling.
I'm so nervous.
-You are? -Yes.
But Mr. Yang you've done this for a long time honestly.
You don't get nervous or anything like that right? How are you today?
I was nervous every year
but I'm not nervous this year for some reason.
That's new.
-You're not nervous? -No.
So
I get a good feeling that the contestants will reveal their potentials today.
I'm looking forward to it.
He said that he's not nervous but is just looking forward to the performances.
The winners will once again get to choose which company they would like to go to.
Mr. Park?
Do you feel confident this year for JYP?
I don't know.
Some years were good for JYP and others weren't good.
I'll try my best and make my comments as soft and warmly as possible.
I think I need to change the way I judge.
I think maybe it's a little too late.
Yeah we'll see how effective it'll be.
After 2 weeks, one of the TOP 6 will become the winner.
Before that, we got a chance to see which company the contestants would like to go.
We'll be able to watch the clip right away.
Before we watch the clip,
please give a warm applause to the TOP 6 and the judges!
[We asked the TOP 6!]
Please write the name of the company you'd like to sign with right now.
Do I write now?
Don't look.
Yes. After you've written it place it in the box to the right.
But what if I'm half and half?
It's just what you think today, it can change later.
Okay.
I hate this sound.
[What are TOP 6 really thinking?]
I feel like I could do more than the music I'd like to do if I go there.
I like that kind of style.
I think he'll help me do better in the things that I'm good at.
I want to be like the artists in that company.
I don't think I'll change my mind.
[TOP 6's first selection of which company they'd like to go to is over!]
[To which company will TOP 6's dreams be headed to?]
We cannot reveal the voting results until the winner is announced.
But I think I can give you a little hint. The staff let me know that-
there is one place where the majority of the TOP 6's chose.
Out of the 6, 3 votes went towards to this company.
Judges please raise your hand if this company is yours.
3 out of the 6 votes. That's 50%.
1, 2, 3.
YG and Antenna.
Are you trying to be humble JYP?
I've been really mean in my feedback.
I don't think it'll be me.
You don't think you'll have 3 votes.
You don't know that yet.
Yeah we'll keep this as a secret.
K-pop star season 5. Who will be the winner at the end?
And which company will be chosen by the winner?
Please stay with us until the end.
Alright before we let the contestants take the stage,
I'll explain the competition rules.
TOP 6 competition will consist of 60% from the scores from the judges
and 40% from text votes from the viewers.
They'll be added to make the score.
The 4 teams that receive the highest score will forward to next week's live shows.
And the last 2 teams will leave K-pop star with this stage as their last.
Who will be the TOP 4 that will continue onto next week out of the TOP 6?
Who will be the eliminated last 2 teams? Stay with us until the end.
I will tell you the order of performances and each contestants' numbers.
First
the contestant that's always surprising us with a new side, number 1 Woo Ye-rin.
The sentiments of ballad number 2 Lee Si-eun.
The soul gem from New Jersey Yoo Jay! Number 3.
The dominating harmony and performance. Number 4 Mazinger S.
The best of sentimental R&B Lee Soo-jung. Number 5.
The beloved musician with her unique music Ahn Ye-eun. Number 6.
The viewers' text votes that make up 40% of the score.
It is more important now than ever.
We will tell you how to vote by text now.
This person will let you guys now. It's been a while. Hello.
Hello. I'm back on K-pop star after 3 years.
I'm Boom! Good to see everyone.
I was with K-pop star for its first 2 seasons.
I saw Lee Hi, Park Ji-min, Ahk-dong musician, Baek Ah-yeon and many more on the stage.
It feels different to be back.
Yes I will pour out my passions on my to work from now on.
Alright.
There is one very important thing for K-pop star live shows today.
It's your text message votes.
You can text the name of the contestant you'd like to vote and
their number to #0606.
You can become JYP, YG, and Antenna
and make the decisions yourselves.
But everyone you need to remember,
one person is only able to vote once.
Please remember that.
We'll go ahead and begin the K-pop star season 5 lives shows now.
And the text votes begin now as well.
Everyone are you guys ready?
Are you ready?
We'll shout this together.
K-pop star!
[Text message voting begins!]
[Live shows D-20 TOP 6 moves in together]
[TOP 6's dorm is on the 2nd floor]
[Very excited]
[Being on the 2nd floor is bad only for a moment]
[A cozy room with bunk beds]
Yes! Bunk beds!
[The roommates just get happy about beds]
I really wanted to live with other people.
It's fun.
We can each take a bed.
I think it's good that I get to live with my friends.
Isn't this everyone's first time using bunk beds?
Everyone is musicians are here.
I think we were able to tell each other and ask questions
about how we could improve anything musically.
Ye-rin. I don't know how many rooms she has in her heart.
She began as a singer-songwriter.
And as we went on she is now almost like a performance singer.
Her spectrum is so wide.
What will be added this time?
She is the contestant with the most of everything. She has many charms.
[The charming Woo Ye-rin, her song selection is revealed]
If she makes this a fast one it'll be a hit.
I think it'll be another surprise if she can maintain the fast tempo of the song.
[Woo Ye-rin's selection Kim Gun-mo's "A sleepless night and it rains"]
[The million seller Kim Gun-mo's 1st album title song]
I organized the stage so that
it'll be rhythmical and fun for everyone. Almost like a musical.
I heard that you had a special reason to come all the way to TOP 6.
I had a dream and-
you know the 12 Chinese zodiac animals.
My house's veranda was filled with them bouncing in a very cute way.
But I opened the door and hugged the pig like this.
People would usually buy a lottery with that kind of a dream.
If I buy the lottery,
the luck might not come to me being here.
Yeah.
There may have been luck and other things too
but people acknowledged my talent.
I think I'm more confident now.
[1 Woo Ye-rin]
[A sleepless night and it rains - Kim Gun-mo]
When I look out the window it rains.
It makes me sad for no reason.
I can't comfort my sadness
on a night I can't fall asleep either.
In my faint memory you become distant more and more
and only your sad smile remains in my heart and flows.
On a rainy night you make me even sadder.
The song I used to listen to lingers around my ears.
On a night when it would rain like this at night,
I meet you with my weariness of missing you.
When this rain stops,
I'm going to leave to find you.
I don't want to listen to sad songs.
You who have been asleep in my heart finds me again.
On a night when it would rain like this at night,
I meet you with my weariness of missing you.
When this rain stops,
I'm going to leave to find you.
Thank you.
Number 1 Woo Ye-rin, everyone.
It was a great performance much like a musical.
Please come to the center.
We'll hear from the judges the score and the feedback.
First
yes Mr. Yoo.
We're always able to see various things in Ye-rin's stage.
You incorporated "Singing in the rain" in the intro, and it suited this song.
And you showed us a various rearrangements of the rhythms towards the end.
I think we were able to see a little bit of Ye-rin's rearrangement abilities.
But one thing I'm a little worried about is that
I think you were missing a little bit of that "taste" of the song.
Because you were trying to show a wide array of music styles
it may have been great as a performance but its completion may be lacking
because it had too many components to it.
I think it had both its positives and negatives.
Okay. Antenna's score is
out of 100,
91!
It's a high score. This is good.
Next judge please.
Yes Mr. Yang.
Because this is the first live show,
in the last 6 months we had many opportunities to see Ye-rin's vocals
but watching her today with the band and the viewers,
I think she was trying to show her other sides more than her vocals.
Honestly I wasn't trying to see whether she was good at singing or not.
I was trying to see how comfortable and natural she will be.
It makes me wonder if the other contestants will be as natural as her.
You looked really comfortable.
You didn't look awkward at all.
I want to praise you on that.
Good job. Thank you.
Thank you.
She seemed natural and comfortable.
YG's score is-
He had more good things to say-
90!
Alright.
Mr. Park?
If you're on a stage like this,
and stand in front of this many crowd
for a person without experience, I mean, she's still an amateur.
I think people need to consider how nervous she would be.
2 things come up when one is nervous. The first is
you tighten up.
And secondly air begins to disappear from your voice.
It's been a while since we heard that.
She actually had an excellent vocalization skills before but today
because you were nervous your voice was too thin and sharp.
And you were certainly tightened up because of your nervousness.
And so
unlike Hyun-suk,
I saw you be more nervous.
So honestly I didn't get to see you take control of the song
or enjoy the song both vocally and performance wise.
So I thought it could've been better.
But I think it's such a big stage, you can't help but to do that.
JYP's score is
Okay. JYP's score-
It was the first of season 5's live shows and the first performance.
85!
Thank you.
She received a total of 266 points.
If there are viewers who supports Woo Ye-rin, please text 1 or her name to #0606.
Everyone. Ms. Woo Ye-rin!
[During the TOP 10 competition]
Lee Si-eun!
[After many dangers of being eliminated]
[she made it to the live shows after being chosen by the viewer judges!]
Lee Si-eun!
I was surprised that this many people were supporting me.
I was really thankful that so many people voted to save me.
I was thankful to realize that this many people were supporting me.
[Lee Si-eun's song selection this time?]
Lee Si-eun.
She's taking a risk.
The song I will be singing for the first lives show is
called "Sigh" by Lee Hi.
[A healing song by the K-pop star season 1 2nd place Lee Hi]
I've been singing songs that were popular back in the day.
This is my first time singing a newer song.
[1st on the 8 music charts as soon as it was released!]
The lyrics are so good.
I felt like I'm being comforted after hearing it once.
I think I chose it because I wanted to be the one to comfort people
on a big stage like that.
Si-eun, out of all the contestants,
her biggest weapon is her perfect high note.
If she uses that well, she becomes the contestant to be feared.
How do you feel to be finally at the live shows?
It honestly didn't feel real.
But I saw last week's preview and
they showed the audiences and it was huge!
After just seeing that I got so nervous and scared.
[The rising pressure as the live show approaches]
But I can do well.
Isn't this your first time saying you can do well?
I can do well.
[2 Lee Si-eun]
[Sigh - Lee Hi]
Try to take a big breath
until the sides of your chest
even hurt a little bit
Try to breathe out
until you feel like nothing is left in you.
It's okay
even if you run out of breath.
No one is blaming you.
You can make mistakes at times
everyone has.
"It's okay," I can only comfort you by words but-
Someone's sigh,
that heavy sigh,
how could I ever understand that?
Your sigh,
I probably won't be able to understand its depth
but it's okay.
I'll give you a hug.
Others may see your sigh as discouraging
but I know
that your day was so difficult that you couldn't even let out a little sigh.
Don't think about anything else now.
Try to take a deep breath
and breathe out.
Someone's sigh,
that heavy sigh.
How could I ever understand that?
Your sigh.
I probably won't be able to understand its depth but
it's okay.
I'll give you a hug.
You worked so hard.
Number 2 Lee Si-eun everyone.
I think she showed all the high notes that she's got.
What did the judges think of her performance?
Many of her fans are here today too.
Mr. Yoo would you like to go first?
My hearts beating really fast right now.
I think it's been a while since I felt so full in my heart seeing a contestant.
She suffered the most difficulties last season.
But as she moves up more and more I think Si-eun, so-
I think it's really scary how you don't falter if you're just good at the basics.
This time too, this is actually a very difficult song to sing. Especially here.
You really have to compete just with your voice.
You have no performance or other things to rely on.
That power you have to fill this place with just your voice and to break through
I really felt that you're incredible through this song.
Antenna's score is-
He said that she were incredible. The score?
96!
It's a very high score.
Next judge?
Mr. Park is getting ready to speak.
I think you need to consider 2 things when hearing someone sing. How good are they,
and secondly
how original are they? How do they sing differently?
You have to consider them both.
If you ask how good you are at singing you're amazing.
You're, you're really good.
But last time when you sang "beautiful farewell," for the first time I
I was able to see how you look inside for the first time in your song.
So not your looks but
your mind and your heart.
I think I was able to see for the first time what kind of a person you were but
you weren't tense then and I felt like it originated from the inside.
When you sing without the pressure to sing well.
But when you were singing the beginning part today
it was better than when you were singing "Beautiful farewell."
You were even more relaxed.
So now
now I finally see what you look like
what your soul looks like but
to me I felt like you returned to your usual self when you sang the high notes.
You tightened up again.
You sang well but you were tensed up,
I didn't feel like you were singing from your soul.
So I actually liked the verse, before you hit the high notes, better.
So today it's about half and half of the feedback I've given you.
The beginning was really good
it was the best part.
The latter high notes, although you sang really well,
I felt like I didn't feel any soul.
That's what I felt.
JYP's score is
We're very curious of the score, half praise and half criticisms.
JYP's score is 87!
Mr. Yang?
Lee Si-eun and Park Jin-young's love-hate relationship quite something to watch.
They almost remind me of two people having a thing.
As Park Jin-young said, it's about how well you sing and how original you sing.
Park Jin-young's feedback and mine are pretty split today.
First, you sang well.
For the first part.
And to me, it felt original.
Because Lee Hi's voice is the opposite from Lee Si-eun's
so you couldn't sing the same way even if she wanted to.
When I first heard Lee Si-eun's "sigh"
I did end up sighing.
A sigh of relief.
When contestants sing Jin-young's song I usually compliment them a lot.
But you don't compliment them when they sing YG songs.
I think there might be a personal reason with his feedback.
I erased the score and gave you a little more.
YG's score is
It probably has nothing to do with it. It was a joke.
95!
Score of 278.
[Lee Si-eun total 278]
It's a high score.
Those of you viewers who support Lee Si-eun,
text number 2 or Lee Si-eun to #0606.
Number 2 Lee Si-eun everyone!
I should be feeling good about going to TOP 6
but because I made it to TOP 6 after not doing so well,
[Yoo Jay sang "I want to fall in love" during the TOP 8 round]
You lacked focus.
You have to focus.
After I heard the feedback
I thought a lot about which song to sing.
I have to choose a song that I can really focus on.
So I chose a song that I can really sing and have fun.
[Which song did she choose for the first live show?]
[Ray Charles' best hit "Hit the road jack"]
I already want to hear it.
This is a song that Jay can extract all of her soulful potentials.
I'm looking very forward to it personally.
[First day of practice!]
Faster faster.
[She's more into rearrangements than she was before]
I'll put in the scat here.
I want to show myself having fun singing and dancing this time.
[On the other hand, 4 days before the live show in the dorms]
Jay!
[What's making Jay smiles so much?]
[Video calling with her family in America]
Are you practicing today?
No. I'm in the dorms.
You're in the dorms right now?
Yeah.
Jay.
Yeah?
I miss you.
I miss you and
I'm proud of you.
You said before that you were scared.
You said you were scared of the live shows. Are you not scared anymore?
I thought I would be less nervous if there were more people.
But I made too many mistakes.
Are you worried that you'll get nervous?
I don't know.
[She's worried to think she'll be singing in front of thousands of people]
What I'm looking forward to from your stage this time
is that you'd naturally show the real you while you're on stage.
Jay you can do it!
[She was very encouraged by her family's genuine support]
There will be a lot of people
but I'm going to just brainwash myself.
"It'll be fun it'll be fun."
I'm going to sing trusting myself.
[3 Yoo Jay]
[Hit the road jack - Ray Charles]
Yoo Jay's very soulful stage.
There were some performances in the middle too.
It looks like the judges might have different opinions from one another.
Mr. Park Jin-young first please.
As I've said before
in many other jobs you have to be in your right mind,
but it's not right for a singer to be in their right mind while they work.
But during the entire performance you looked like you were in your right mind.
You have to really lose yourself.
You
you really have to lose your mind to the music and your body, especially for this song
these are the kind of songs that you play piano with your feet and things like that.
I'm very disappointed that you sang a song like this
so calmly with the right mind.
It could've been the song that you just let go of yourself and go crazy.
I think I was looking forward to that.
But since you are still young and this is a big stage
you can't help but to get nervous.
You're the youngest right now out of all TOP 6.
You couldn't help it I think.
JYP's score is-
She probably did get nervous since this was her first live show.
JYP's score is?
86!
It's not easy to get above 90 from Park Jin-young.
Who's next?
For the first time today Park Jin-young and I agree.
I'm disappointed too.
Because I know Yoo Jay has this massive power in her voice
but she chose the genre that she's not able to do well instead to have fun on stage.
You didn't have fun though, first of all.
Park Jin-young is honestly not someone with the best vocals,
to be honest.
You're pointing that out.
What I do acknowledge is that he can have fun on stage.
When he's on stage he does his best to have the most fun, I acknowledge that
but you didn't play and have fun as much as I had expected you to so I regret that.
YG's score is-
They had similar things to say.
She didn't have fun.
85!
Great.
Mr. Yoo Hee-yeol?
I still remember the first time I saw you Jay.
When I first saw you I thought, this is a little extreme, but you were a monster.
You played around with the song all you wanted.
I saw for the first time what we call a gem, a diamond out of them all too.
But as you go forward, you had to be on stage with a lot of pressure,
you definitely can't ignore experience either.
You were nervous and even were off on some of the notes today
and you were especially very tight in your body.
I think you were the only one nervous on this awesome stage,
even the dancers were having fun putting together the stage.
But the main role was nervous.
We were not able to enjoy the stage to the full extent.
Antenna's score is-
He talked about the pressures of a live show.
Yoo Hee-yeol's score!
90!
Total of 261.
If any of you viewers are supporting Yoo Jay,
text number 3 or Yoo Jay to #0606.
Number 3 Yoo Jay everyone!
[Kim Ye-rim, Denise Kim, Joyce Lee, Yuyu Liu]
I think it's really amazing because
a couple of months ago we didn't know each other at all
Ye-rim from Incheon
Joyce is from Houston and Yuyu Liu came from China.
No one would've imagined that we would be together.
It's really amazing how we didn't have a single fight in the months we were together.
But it's really weird.
It's because you're good to us.
Wait.
That's a surprise.
She says she already beat us a hundred times in her heart.
Wait.
She means this.
Really?
When?
"Let's practice."
[They don't have a problem joking around]
[They've gotten closer as they were together all the time now]
I'm thankful that I met friends that I feel like I could be friends with forever.
I'm thankful.
What song did they choose? "She was pretty" last time was a game-changer.
It's good.
This is good.
I think this is going to be great.
It's the best song selection.
[Mazinger S' song Chae-yeon's "Two of us"]
Mazinger S has been strong in pop and soul in the past performances
this song has a strong Korean pop feel.
Despite that,
there are many parts in this song they can show their talents in.
The strength of being in a team is that the song can be rearranged entirely.
We'll have to see how they oriented this song to be rearranged.
Here here here stay still.
[Taking a picture before the live show!]
You should come here.
Okay that's my spot?
We want to show our best and
I want them to be able to say to themselves
"So that's Mazinger, that's who Mazinger S are."
[Two of us - Chae-yeon]
Don't approach me hastily, come in a more cool manner.
I want to feel tonight with you, the blazing love.
I sing a song love love
you and I become one.
That dance I cannot stop dancing,
I want to dance with you tonight.
I'll give the love I can give you to you.
Our love without hesitation, just the two of us.
I'm looking at you, I have a smile on my face until you approach me.
I'm gesturing to you, you're approaching me, attracted to the look I've given you.
I chose you today.
Embrace me.
I'll trust all my lonely heart to you.
Don't approach me hastily, come in a more cool manner.
I want to feel the blazing love with you tonight.
I sing the song of love, you and I become one.
I want to dance the dance I cannot stop with you tonight.
Don't look around and
You'll come in a cool manner.
There will be regrets.
I'll give the love I can give you to you.
Our love without hesitation, you and I, just the two of us.
I want to dance with you tonight.
Number 4 Mazinger S everyone!
Ah yes.
They brought it today.
Please come to the center of the stage.
Park Jin-young is in a hurry.
Please go ahead.
You have to be loose in your body.
None of you girls are tense in your body.
Your shoulders, arms, and your neck.
You have to first be relaxed to be able to
let your soul, what's inside of you dance but if your body's tense
the song gets very difficult but all 4 of you
how are you guys having so much fun? Of course the 4 of you-
Denise Kim is only 15 actually.
Who did the choreography?
Who choreographed?
We all did.
Who-who came up with this?
You guys came up with it? Not a choreographer?
They helped us.
Choreography was excellent.
And like I said before, how you guys can be so loose and have fun
that was great and your vocals on top of that.
JYP's score is
He mostly had praises.
JYP's score is!
97!
It's a good start. Yes alright.
Let us hear from other judges.
Usually
it takes years for girl groups to practice and prepare.
To come up with something.
This team came from all over the place and it's only been months since they practiced.
But they're better than girls groups that's been practicing for years.
Even vocals aside, they play so well on stage.
And some of these girls have never danced before.
To me the most surprising aspect about Mazinger S is
their effort.
Antenna's score is-
Antenna's score-
He said that they were better than most other girl groups.
94!
They have a running high score.
Mr. Yang?
If I were told to praise Mazinger S
I think I can go on for about 2 hours.
But since this is live
we have a short time.
They keep telling me to end it quick.
It'd be beneficial for you to save that time too.
Right?
First
Yuyu Liu had a mistake in the middle.
She made a mistake because it was a Korean lyric.
You can make mistakes like that a hundred times and you're fine.
If you can put on this kind of performance.
I really think this was the best.
YG's score is-
Alright.
Mr. Yang was praising the team as well.
95!
Total score of 286!
The best score so far.
If any of you support Mazinger S
please text number 4 or Mazinger S to #0606.
Number 4 Mazinger S everyone!
[Incheon airport]
[Lee Soo-Jung is waiting for someone with a sign]
Who are you waiting for right now?
My mom and my grandma.
They're going to see me perform for the first time
on a live stage.
[Her mom and grandmother are coming a long way to see her]
Other contestants has had family here to see them but
because my family is in Chicago-
[After the TOP 8 competition]
[Everyone runs into their family's arms to share the joy]
[Soo-Jung had to swallow her joy alone]
[Today is the day that Soo-jung's family will come to warmly embrace her]
Mom!
My granddaughter!
[She's running towards her much missed mom and grandma]
You look so pretty.
It was like a drama.
When I was running to my mom.
That's what it felt like. It was great.
[Shall we go on a drive with mom and grandma?]
Good car.
Yay!
[Listening to Soo-jung's past performances together]
Did you memorize it?
[Thanks to mom and grandma her laugh is brightened]
[Came to eat much craved Korean food]
I felt bad for her because no one was there.
I was proud to see her go through it all alone.
Mom. Yaho!
[Soo-jung's family's special way of encouragement "Yaho!"]
[Which song will Soo-Jung sing in front of her mom and grandma?]
[Lee Moon-seh's "Girl" remade by Oh Hyuk recently]
Will she do well?
This is.. make it or break it.
I want to praise her for challenging herself to choose Korean pop constantly.
It would be a lot easier for her to sing pop.
She's persistent, she's singing Korean pop.
I feel like I'll be able to hear a whole different song "Girl."
I'm really looking forward to it.
My family came a long way to see me.
[The live shows that she's dreamed of since the beginning]
I'm thankful and
I'll do my best.
[Girl - Lee Moon-seh]
Stay
just by my side.
You can't
leave me.
I can't leave the longing and go on the long journey
and find your rainbow.
I sit by the window in the sunset
and look to the clouds floating far away
I draw the old memories
that I want to find.
In the cold wind that blows
you cry out of loneliness.
But I will always remain by your side.
I will not leave you.
In the cold wind that blows
you cry out of loneliness
But I will always remain by your side.
I will not leave you.
Stay
just by my side.
You can't
leave me.
Number 5 Lee Soo-Jung everyone!
Crowd is going insane.
Mr. Yoo please go first.
Before I start the feedback I have a request for the staff.
Can I get a divider here please?
Park Jin-young was doing this the whole time.
I thought he was taken by the spirit.
I thought he was crying too.
I think it's just minutes before he'll start speaking in tongue.
I was really worried when she chose this song.
How is she going to sing this?
I'll make it short.
Soo-Jung is really-
the power that she has is incredible.
I don't know if I could say this to a contestant but
she's a really cool girl. Really.
Antenna's score is-
He made it short and sweet. A cool girl.
Yoo Hee-yeol's score is?
95!
It's a high score.
Mr. Yang?
If a contestant who can sing Korean pop well sings Korean pop well,
"they're pretty good" is all I'll say.
And if a contestant who can sing R&B well sings R&B,
of course they're good.
That's what we'll think but
Soo-Jung your song choice today was very successful.
Because Park Jin-young and I love R&B singers being able to sing Korean pop well
because the Korean and the R&B sentiments coexist together.
People say that it's hard to catch two birds.
If you chase one the other will run away but
I think Soo-Jung you caught two birds today certainly.
YG's score is-
She caught two birds with one stone.
YG's score is?
Score is?
97!
I think Park Jin-young might have said it all with his body but
please go ahead.
I knew something was coming when you started singing.
I was just thinking that and-
the part "long journey-" and raised that note.
Starting from then
things that I did not expect were beginning to take place.
That's when you began to move.
Where do I start- first!
There were 2 changes for Soo-Jung from the start of K-pop star to now.
The first is
she's a lot brighter.
Secondly, her high notes began to come out.
Today for the first time
I heard for the first time a very open sound.
But this happened during the K-pop star season.
And I- what I was talking about before about not being original was that
is if I ask you to sing again will you sing the same way or different?
I think Soo-Jung will sing in 10 different ways if I make her sing 10 times.
These changes are not calculated.
They're very spontaneous.
I think I'm beginning to see more and more how I said that
she's going to become Korea's Mary J. Blige.
I really see that you're singing from your heart and your soul
and on top of that she has the talent.
The two of them took away 5 and 3 points.
I don't understand where they could take away the points from.
JYP's score is-
What does he mean? JYP's score is-
No. Really? Really?
100!
A score of 292!
She has the highest score!
Awesome. Any of you who are supporting Lee Soo-Jung
please text number 5 of Lee Soo-Jung to #0606.
Number 5 Lee Soo-Jung everyone!
[First live shows TOP 6 interview]
How do you feel to have made it to the live shows?
I think it'll be fun.
The sound is blasting and there will be a big audience.
The very fact that I'll be singing at a place where everything will be big
I'm excited.
[What song will Ahn Ye-eun sing for us on her first live stage?]
Ahn Ye-eun's song selection.
It's her own song again.
"If spring comes"
[What kind of song will it be?]
I think it'll be good because
she would've expressed spring in her own way
with her own scent and her sound
I think she would've expressed it originally.
This last and the last last round the judges
they complimented me saying that my lyrics were clever and unique
that they were sad and funny at the same time.
This song is very different from that so I'm a little worried but
I have a story I want to tell through this song so-
that's why I chose this song.
What story?
[The story she wants to tell us through this song]
When I was little,
my heart was weak so I had a couple of surgeries
I'm very healthy right now.
When I was a senior in high school I went to a meeting that
people with my same heart conditions were in.
After seeing me, the-
the mothers who were raising their infants with the condition
they walked away hopeful that their kids might grow up to be healthy like me.
I really felt that a person like me could be a hope to others too.
I wrote this song because I wanted to give hope to a lot of people.
When spring comes, you're encouraged and new life sprouts
all of this is an expression that's used often and may sound cliche but
[If Spring comes to us, I'm going to give you a pretty light]
it might be something that someone really needs to hear right now.
To tell someone "Spring will come in your life"-
I would like people to listen to this song and be encouraged.
[6 Ahn Ye-eun]
[If Spring comes - Written by self]
If Spring comes to us,
if the dark clouds go away and sun comes up,
if that day comes,
I'm going to present you with a pretty light.
If Spring comes to us,
if the warm sky surrounds us
if that day comes,
I'm going to lay on your knees and dream.
If the people who are indulged in the darkness (lose their mind one by one)
If the tears you've shed all night (combine to become the ocean)
Everyone say hooray! when the butterflies come.
When the buds of flowers sheepishly open the door for you,
say hooray! when your tears melt away.
Hold each other's hands.
If Spring comes.
Everyone say hooray! When the forest awakens,
When the cold gray world wears the colorful clothes.
Say hooray! when the ice begins to crack.
Hold each other's hands
Hold each other's hands.
Say Hooray!
Tickles your nose.
Say hooray! if the winter's all passed.
If Spring comes.
Number 6 Ahn Ye-eun everyone!
Ye-eun has brought another song that's entirely different.
Alright.
We'll hear from the judges.
Mr. Yoo Hee-yeol?
This song is different again.
It's different from the songs you've been singing.
The lyric is a lot heavier than the ones you've been writing.
It's heavy but it carried a significant message.
What was interesting was I think you used a vocoder for a solo part.
You have a very good rearrangement skill.
And it was a song with a simple theme
if we're talking about the organization of the song.
But you took that and made it in many variations
it was almost like you were shouting into our hearts.
So if this was a festival full of your fans,
they may have jumped to your song.
I think I was able to feel that spring has come, like the message of your song.
Antenna's score is-
Antenna's score is.
Ye-eun brought a self-written song with a very different feel.
93!
Good.
Who's next?
Park Jin-young.
I-
always say
that I want to meet a musician with a soul
but I'm not talking about the African American music soul.
Everyone has a part that cannot be seen to the eye, the inner part.
It's the matter of how much that aspect is laid out in the song.
If you define soul that way I think Ye-eun is over-flowing with soul.
In the lyrics,
In the lyrics, melody, rearrangements, the vocals,
I feel like your mind is all in there.
I can feel that.
And
you wrote the song with the idea of light and darkness.
I think you were able to write songs like this because you're beginning to be loved
because you said if spring comes you'll give the light,
it sounds like there is no light in the person, you have to receive it.
If you look at the moon at light it looks like it's shining but it has no light.
It's receiving the light from the sun.
In the same way, you're receiving all the love
now you're able to have a heart to give the love too.
I enjoyed it. JYP's score is-
He compared Ye-eun to the stars.
The score is?
98!
Alright. We'll hear from Mr. Yang Hyun-Suk.
Every time I see Ye-eun I think
"Could Ye-eun be here right now?"
I think maybe she's a contestant that's too good to be here.
And do I have the qualifications to judge this person?
I also think that.
She's not a contestant that's here to become a singer.
You already look like a complete artist.
I'm sorry to even give you a score from me.
YG's score is-
He says that she's a complete artist.
YG's score is?
95!
A total score of 286. It's a high score.
If you're supporting Ahn Ye-eun,
please text number 6 or Ahn Ye-eun to #0606.
Number 6 Ahn Ye-eun everyone!
Amazing amazing. Everyone's festival K-pop star!
That's the end of all the TOP 6 performances.
After 1 minute, the text votes will end.
We'll watch the highlights as you finalize your final decisions.
Who will move up and who will be eliminated?
We'll announce the results very soon!
Let us watch the highlights.
K-pop!
Star!
[1 Woo Ye-rin]
[2 Lee Si-eun]
[3 Yoo Jay]
[Mazinger S]
[5 Lee Soo-Jung]
[6 Ahn Ye-eun]
[End of text votes!]
To the winner of K-pop star season 5, a total of $300,000 will be awarded.
They will also be awarded with the global midsized car
that has been with K-pop star all its seasons.
[Incheon Nam-dong center live]
Survival audition K-pop star season 5.
All TOP 6 performances have ended.
The text message votes have closed
and in the hands of the 3 judges and mine are envelopes.
Whose name is written in these envelopes?
We'll open the judges' envelopes first.
Alright. This is the combination of the text message votes and the judges' scores.
Mr. Park Jin-young?
Yes.
TOP 4.
It's the semi-final round of K-pop star.
The first contestant to move onto TOP 4.
1 of the 4 contestants who will forward to the live shows next week.
Mr. Park?
Who is it?
Who do you guys think it is?
This is the contestant I
gave the highest score today. Lee Soo-Jung!
Lee Soo-Jung! Congratulations.
I'll invite you come up to the platform. Congratulations.
Please come to the platform.
Next
Mr. Yang Hyun-Suk?
I wasn't nervous in the beginning but now I am.
Yes.
Don't look.
The next contestant to move onto TOP 4 is
The second contestant.
The 2nd contestant to go forward!
-Ahn Ye-eun. -Ahn Ye-eun congratulations!
Please come up to the platform.
Ye-eun.
Out of the 4 who will be continuing to next week's live shows,
2 have been selected.
Mr. Yoo Hee-yeol. Please.
Alright.
The 3rd contestant to forward to TOP 4 is-
Mr. Yoo. This is the third contestant to pass.
It's tense.
Congratulations.
Who is it?
Ms. Lee Si-eun!
Lee Si-eun!
The master of high-notes Lee Si-eun.
I'll invite you to the platform.
Lee Soo-Jung, Ahn Ye-eun, Lee Si-eun.
The 3 of them
will be moving onto TOP 4.
Now
out of
the 3 teams left
only 1 team is able to move onto the next week's live shows.
That name is inside of the envelope in my hand.
I don't know either. I will reveal it now.
[Who will be the last contestant to move onto TOP 4?]
I'll announce it now.
Will there be a turnover?
Or will it be just follow the judges' scores?
Out of the 3 teams, the team to continue onto next week's live shows is!
Congratulations!
Mazinger S!
Mazinger S has become the last contestant to become TOP 4.
3 teams please come down.
Alright so
Ms. Yoo Jay and Woo Ye-Rin
will be eliminated.
First. Ms. Woo Ye-rin.
Today was your last stage on K-pop star. How do you feel?
I think
I was able to experience some valuable things that I will never get to experience here
I'm really glad.
And I met-
Thank you.
I met really good friends so I'm happy.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you.
Yoo Jay has become a hot topic throughout her time here but this was her last stage.
Can you tell us how you feel?
Thank you so much for this opportunity.
I thank the writers
I thank the judges and thank you for letting me meet good friends.
Thank you.
Please say a few words to them. They've worked so hard.
Mr. Park can you represent the judges?
Both of the contestants
have surprised all of the judges very much.
I look forward to their future.
I think for Ye-rin she was able to learn more about herself during her time here.
And I think Jay is only eliminated because she's still young and without experience.
After gaining some experience you'll become a great singer.
You two worked so hard to get here and
I'm really proud.
This is how difficult K-pop star is.
This is very surprising. Yoo Jay and Woo Ye-rin has been eliminated.
With that news, we'll come back next week with K-pop star TOP 4 stages.
Survival audition K-pop star season 5! Thank you!