[Incheon Nam-dong center live]
Survival audition K-pop star season 5.
Introducing our TOP 4 who overcame many challenges with their talent and passion.
Lee Si-eun!
Lee Soo-jung!
Ahn Ye-eun!
Mazinger S!
Give it up for the TOP 4 who came a long way!
To tell you the truth, every season,
it never went as we expected it to go.
Everyone has such distinct styles.
A contestant who sings ballad well, a contestant who writes her songs,
a contestant with a sense of pop,
and a contestant with potentials.
Everyone is so different.
There's not a team that's dominant over others right now.
So personally this season is the most interesting for me to see.
[Now headed towards the finals!]
Could it be? No way.
100!
[Lee Soo-jung received a score of a 100 from Park Jin-young]
[She presented the thousands of audience with the best performance!]
She has the perfect sense.
And she has the perfect techniques.
You know the saying "form is temporary but class is permanent."
Soo-jung is different, she's on a different level.
[Ahn Ye-eun performed astonishingly with her song "If Spring comes"]
You look like an already complete artist.
I want to say that she's a high-quality artist.
Each and every single one of her lyrics and melodies seem real.
They're all a work of art.
[Lee Si-eun re-interpreted "Sigh" with her unique powerful voice]
It's been a while since my heart felt so full by seeing a contestant sing.
The moment Si-eun is able to explode her feelings on stage,
K-pop star season 5's results become unpredictable.
[Mazinger S sang "The two of us" with overflowing energy and perfect harmony]
I loved seeing you girls play around while not being tightening up
and on top of that your vocals-
I think your performance was simply the best today.
The four of them are getting better and better as each of them grow.
If they continue this on,
they can easily win.
[And]
[Voting once again for the second time following last week]
[The company each of them want to sign with.. Could they have change their minds?]
[Polls finished!]
Alright.
We took a poll following last week asking the contestants of their choice of company.
If I were to give you a tip,
some of their choices have changed.
Some team's changed their choice from last week.
What do you think Mr. Yoo?
Who do you think changed from where to where?
Because it pertains to their life I think they certainly do have to be thoughtful.
I'm not sure where they would have changed from and to.
Do you think this change would've been beneficial to you or
maybe not?
I'm going to believe that it's going to be beneficial to me.
I see.
Mr. Yang you raised both of your hands last week
and were confident that everyone will go to your company.
What do you think?
I was kidding.
You're saying that now?
I'm certain of one thing.
It's not Park Jin-young.
Okay. Mr. Park.
What do you think?
They changed their minds.
By the time contestants are to choose their company,
I regret all the mean things I've said to them.
Yes yes.
I shouldn't have done that in the beginning if I think of this moment,
I don't know why I keep giving feedback like that. It's unfortunate.
I see.
He began to give kind feedback starting from last week.
We'll see what effect it'll have.
Today's K-pop star season 5 is
the semi-finalists.
I will tell you again that the performances prepared will make everyone go crazy.
I'll explain the rules for today.
TOP 4 competitions will be a combination of 60% judges' scores and 40% viewer votes.
and 40% viewer's text message votes.
The top 2 teams with the highest scores will continue onto the final rounds next week.
The rest of the 2 teams will leave K-pop star after this round.
I will now announce the order of performance and contestants' numbers.
First, the contestant with the perfect high-quality pop vocal, number 1 Lee Si-eun!
She received the highest judge score last week.
Dazzling power R&B singer, number 2 Lee Soo-jung!
A developed musician whose popularity is growing sharply. Number 3 Ahn Ye-eun!
The best harmony that produces 3 minutes like a movie.
Number 4 Mazinger S!
And we also have prepared a special stage today.
The winner of K-pop star season 3,
Bernard Park will reveal his newest song for the first time to you guys.
Look forward to the lovely stage he and Wonder Girl's Hye-rim will be performing.
TOP 4 competition will begin soon.
As I said before viewers' text votes are 40% of the decision.
This person will explain how to vote by text.
Take it away.
Hello good to see everyone.
I'm Boom! Hello.
K-pop star season 5!
Who are you guys rooting for?
The atmosphere in here is bombastic fantastic!
Viewers. Who are you all rooting for?
Are you just rooting for them in your heart?
Please don't do that.
Please root for them hardcore through your texts.
Right this moment text the name or the number of the contestant you're rooting for
and please send it to #0606.
Your one text can change the fate of the contestant.
It's texting time.
Then now, K-pop star season 5 TOP 4's performances will begin!
The text votes begin at the same time as well.
The first stage will be contestant number 1
we have prepared for you Lee Si-eun's stage.
Is everyone ready?
K-pop star!
[Text message votes begin!]
[1 Lee Si-eun, 2 Lee So-jung, 3 Ahn Ye-eun, 4 Mazinger S]
[After the first live performances...]
[Park Jin-young is coming to say hello to the contestants]
He's up on the stage.
[He goes straight to Si-eun]
He told me that all I needed to do was to relax my shoulders.
Don't be so nervous and relax
and sing.
He told me that directly, not through a microphone.
I was both really surprised and grateful.
[Si-eun is encouraged by Park Jin-young, what song did she choose?]
[What does this mean?]
Has Si-eun ever drunk alcohol before?
[The best song of shy confessions! Jun Ram-hwoi's "Drunk confession"]
I'm worried about one thing.
This song is a bit masculine.
I don't know how a female's- or Si-eun's interpretation is going to turn out.
[On the other hand]
[A guest came to Si-eun in her practice room?!]
[They came with both their hands full]
[Who are these guest?]
What?
[Who do we have here?]
[Suh Kyung-duk who was on the same team with her during Battle Audtion]
What? Who do we have here?
Who do we have here?
Good to see you.
[Park Ga-kyung  is here too!]
Ga-kyung you're in middle school now?
Yeah.
I would've never imagined.
I didn't think they would come all the way to cheer me on.
I didn't know they would come.
They came with food and everything to encourage me. I was very thankful.
Are their signs that have your name on them too?
Yeah.
I was surprised.
I didn't think people would make signs for me.
But people did.
I was very amazed. The stage is gigantic too.
I had a lot of experiences of me liking someone but I quickly gave up
thinking it wouldn't work.
So I'm thinking a lot about how I should sing this song.
You can maybe imagine that I'm the person you're talking to.
Me? You?
Confessing to you?
You two look good together.
What?
Nothing.
I'll pretend like I didn't hear that.
It's been hard to think through things alone.
I think they came today to gave me tips.
I think I can do a little better.
Please look forward to me becoming a shy girl.
[1 Lee Si-eun]
[Drunk Confession - Jun Ram-hwoi]
Yeah.
Maybe I'm drunk.
This might be a mistake.
When morning comes
I might get nervous,
because I don't remember anything.
Why
do I always
say the opposite things when I'm with you
and regret it later?
I'll tell you the truth now I have loved you from the beginning.
This is how much I love you.
My not-so-smooth words may be
a bit old-fashioned
and fall short of your expectations,
but I don't just say these things to anyone.
I'm just as awkward as you are.
I can't look at you directly.
I'm sorry to say the same things over again
but I'm going to tell you everything today.
THis is how much I love you.
My not-so-smooth words may be
a bit old-fashioned
and fall short of your expectations,
but I'm not just saying this.
This will
never happen again.
When the morning comes,
I'm going to once again
embrace you and
tell you I love you.
I love you.
Drunk confession.
We heard Lee Si-eun's version. I wonder what the judges thought.
It wasn't easy for me to tell from the judges' faces.
Which one of you will give a feedback and a score first?
They aren't able to get to the microphones just yet.
Mr. Yoo?
This was Jun Ram-hwoi's song called drunk confession.
This is Kim Dong-ryul's song.
Before I give my feedback,
even Kim Dong-ryul finds it difficult to sing this song at his own concert.
Because the range of the song is very low and ends up very high.
But he finds something more difficult than the range of the song.
He says after singing this song he runs out of energy.
Because
he said that he almost has to risk his life to sing this song.
What's meant by that is
if you don't throw in your everything this song is not brought to life.
For me, for the first time,
I like the
strength of your high notes
and the stability of your lower notes but
for the first time it sounded bland.
To my ears.
So
in this song's latter part you're really confessing your feelings, while being drunk.
I didn't feel like you were confessing but you were just singing.
I felt like I didn't receive any feelings from the song.
You sing well but-
Drunk confession. The story you tell sincerely as you're drunk
I didn't necessarily receive that.
Okay.
Antenna's score is
Antenna's score. We'll see.
She sang well but she didn't carry the emotions well.
90!
Mr. Park Jin-young?
I think you held back too much.
I don't know what it is but
today you've lived 21, 20 years. Right?
I feel like you're someone who held back on something a lot.
You've stuffed it too much that your heart has a callous I feel like.
So no matter how much you try to make it tender and move about freely,
I feel like you stuffed everything too much, you have a callous and you can't.
Si-eun have you ever yelled and gotten angry with someone when you felt anger?
Have you ever full-on cried when you were sad?
Have you ever confessed to anyone drunk because you like someone so much?
So you've never done any of these things before.
How would you be able to carry that in a song?
From now on, regardless of the results, I'd like you to encourage your emotions.
When you're happy, encourage your happiness.
When you're sad, encourage your sadness.
If you don't make these callouses more tender,
not matter how good you are at singing there's a limit to you moving someone's heart.
I think it starts now but
it's not about the vocals.
I really feel it now, it's not your singing.
Encourage your emotions on a daily basis.
JYP's score is-
He said some similar things.
She could've delivered her emotions more.
JYP. 87!
Now we have Mr. Yang left to give her feedback.
Last week,
after the live performances ended,
I heard Park Jin-young called his mother.
Your mom called you?
His mother said,
Try to say good things to Lee Si-eun as much as you can.
You can't do that man. I mean, never mind the man.
That happened but I think Jin-young is a very consistent person.
Seeing him criticize Si-eun again after what his mother told him
I thought "he's a very consistent person."
She'll call him again too then.
Okay. What the two of them are saying are similar.
There's nothing more we expect from you in terms of your vocals.
It's very difficult to increase your vocal skills but
I think it's more difficult to know how to express your feelings.
Especially for a singer on top of your vocals, emotion expression should come before.
I thought you could've been better in that aspect as well but
it's also true that you're still very good at singing.
And here and there I heard for the first time some R&B styles of singing.
I gave you a higher score than you'd expect.
YG's score is-
Alright. YG's score.
There is nothing to question about her vocals, it's true.
92!
Score of 269!
If you're rooting for Lee Si-eun,
text Lee Si-eun or number 1 to #0606.
Number 1 Lee Si-eun's stage everyone!
[Last week. First live performances]
I was really surprised at first.
I feel like it's a dream right now.
I feel like I'm in a dream.
Good job.
[On a sunny spring day]
[She left the practice room for the first time in a while and heads somewhere..]
Where are you going right now?
I'm heading to my great aunt's house right now to see my Chicago grandma.
[North Choong-chung Young-dong great aunt's house!]
Grandma!
Grandma.
Hi grandma.
Thanks for coming all the way here.
I was so happy because you did so well last Sunday.
Thank you.
Hello.
You met her when she came to America.
How is your health?
So so.
Don't cry.
[Soo-jung spent a lot of time with her grandma growing up because her mom was busy]
Thank you.
We looked at hats
and we saw how they made Korean popcorn.
I liked it.
I did everything for the first time with grandma. I love it.
Yaho!
[She even received cheers filled with love]
[What song did Soo-jung choose this time?]
[Park Jin-young's "The house you live in"]
I always sing sad songs
so this time
I wanted to do a song that was a little crazy.
I thought of JYP first as soon as I thought that.
JYP is
always
like his feet
playing the piano with his feet.
He always says those things so
because I can sing this song
a little bit more crazily
so I chose this song.
[Looking at Soo-jung's song choice..]
She's scary, really.
I'm scared of this contestant now.
Despite the fact that she's not perfectly fluent in Korean,
despite the fact that she has a little bit of the accent,
it's scary how the lyrics hit you before you can realize that.
You continue to sing Korean pop.
To tell you the truth, compared to other contestants,
I need more time to prepare for Korean songs.
It's hard but
if I don't do the hard things
you don't grow.
If you just do the same things you stay the same person.
[2 Lee Soo-jung]
[That house you live in - Park Jin-young]
In front of my car stopped at the red light on a crosswalk,
holding the hand of a pretty child who looks like you,
you were crossing and after seeing you
I was so surprised I followed you.
In a cozy little house,
everything I see through the window
I can tell they're cared for by you.
On a white table,
you are setting the food that you made
with your pretty hands.
Is this a dream?
That house that you live in,
that house should've been mine.
That car that you drive,
that car should've been mine.
The food that you prepared,
even the child you have in your arms,
they should've all been mine.
They should've been all my kids.
I still
feel like you're my man.
I still really feel like you're my man.
You've become someone else's man
and the kid's dad,
and making me just stand here not being able to do anything.
That house that you live in,
that house should've been mine.
That car that you drive,
that car should've been mine.
The food that you prepared,
and even the kid that you're holding,
they should've all been mine.
They should've all been my kids.
That house that you live in.
That house should've been mine.
The food that you prepared
and even the kid that you're holding,
they should've all been mine.
They should've all been mine.
That house that you
live in.
We just heard "That house that you live in" with a whole different feel.
Park Jin-young began to move his head again.
What will he say?
Soo-jung while you were singing "Lies"
you ended up crying.
Right?
Never in K-pop star did a contestant cried consumed by their emotions. Right?
It was the first time.
A person's.. mind?
What we usually call a soul.
Honestly this is-
I think you have to divide the two.
It's
both the mind and the spirit.
What the mind does
can be all done by a computer.
They can do it even better.
But what the spirit does
is completely different, because the root of the spirit is love. It's love.
But a computer does not know love
so
it can never do what a spirit does.
So if you're competing a computer for singing
and you begin to cry, what does the computer do?
It probably won't know why you're crying.
You're getting what he's saying right?
Yes.
Okay.
I just thought I should check.
What I wanted to say is-
There's this weird thing that love does.
It makes you cry during a song, destroying your notes and your beat.
And because of that we cry too, as the audience.
So if you sing just like that
you'll become a singer a machine cannot mimic.
Today
it
feels like you sang with your mind and not your spirit.
It seemed like you were less crazy.
You lacked in that.
Because that stage, those stages left with me such a big impression.
I hope I can see you on stage singing with an inspiration again.
-Thank you. -JYP's score is-
He's expecting a lot from her so he's telling her these things.
95!
A high score as expected.
We'll hear from the next judge.
Mr. Yang?
Jin-young and I love R&B so much to begin with.
You arranged the song that you sang today really well.
I tell you that you arranged it well because
you could've sang it with the multiplied emotions but
as Jin-young just said
it is true that you fell a little short in delivering your emotions as we expected.
For me, every time I hear "That house that you live in," I think of
Jin-young's dance move.
My least favorite dance move.
He says everyday to the contestants
to not sing obviously.
How obvious is this dance move? That house that you live in.
I was hoping that you'd please not do that dance move
and I'm glad you didn't.
So I gave you the appropriate score.
YG's score is-
That could've been close.
YG's score!
94!
Thank you.
A high score again.
Okay now Mr. Yoo?
We'll hear his feedback and his score.
Soo-jung came from Chicago.
And in Chicago,
I once heard a song that you worked on
with a couple of friends that do music there.
But they didn't do songs that were too wide in the range, it was rather typical
and sang songs with the mood usually.
The part you most changed in after Soo-jung came to K-pop star is that
you began to sing songs with a drama, ones with a climax.
In doing so, you began to challenge yourself to songs that requires you to sing high.
The part I was surprised the most by you during training-
I see it today too in this song.
The part when you say "like you're my man, like you're my man,"
you change the key and vary the music a little bit.
If the arranger says "sing it like this," other singers sing it that way.
But she knows how to bring it back to her.
She gives many ideas as to how to sing the song.
And in today's song,
I saw you lead the song with your own arrangements and style.
When you become a professional, you'll be a musician and a vocalist many will love.
I can't help but to think that.
Antenna's score is-
Okay. A musician and a vocalist.
It was a praise.
Antenna! 94!
Thank you.
A total score of 283. She ended up with a high score.
If you're rooting for Lee Soo-jung,
please text number 2 or Lee Soo-jung to #0606.
Number 2 Lee Soo-jung everyone!
[The staff asked to see Ahn Ye-eun in the parking lot]
[They get her in the car first]
Hi.
W-What is this?
[She doesn't know where she's going but they're taking off!]
Where are we going?
We're going to have
a surprise meet with your fans.
I'm not that big of a deal.
This is so weird. What do I do?
[Same time, a cafe in Gangnam]
[They're preparing for a fan meet with Ahn Ye-eun]
[Fan club 'Purple Witch' enters]
[30 fans have been specially invited]
[They excitedly wait for Ye-eun]
[Ye-eun is taking something out of her bag]
[I've gotta look pretty for my first fan meet!]
I think we'll get there after we turn on this street.
Oh no.
[Worried but still focused on makeup!]
[All dolled up]
The pikachu bag!
[Anticipant]
[The main person of the night is very nervous]
[Hesitant]
[Surprised!]
[Loud cheer!]
[It feels good but also embarrassing]
[Ye-eun we really wanted to see you]
Little giant!
Go Ahn Ye-eun!
[The little giant is confused]
What do I do?
I am about a hundred times more thankful than I may look.
I never have imagined that anything like this would happen.
I was thinking just on the way what song I should sing for all of you.
I thought probably no one has heard the full version of this song.
I'll sing "Hong-yeon" for you first.
[The fans go crazy to hear the song they wanted to hear]
[Singing her first song at K-pop star "Hong-yeon"
to her fans at a very close distance]
They say when you come into the world
if the two are meant to be
a string connects them from one's finger to another's.
[Her favorite purple flower]
I think this is really really much more than I deserve.
Honestly I didn't care too much about the results of the competition before
but to see all these people I'm thankful for
I'm thinking now that I should do well, even if it's for them at least.
[What song did Ye-eun write this time for her encouraging fans?]
My goodness.
Goodness.
It's a lot.
Pushover?
She means that kind of pushover I am thinking of, right?
People call someone who foolishly give their everything to others pushover.
When you're dating a lot of the times there's a power dynamic between two people,
So
I tried to write about a story of someone who is overly compensating,
someone who's pitiful to the point their mental health is in danger.
[3 Ahn Ye-eun]
[Pushover - Written by self]
Love is so difficult.
You can neither drift away nor get accustomed.
I still don't know
how I'm supposed to do this.
To fit your taste, I
have even been a locksmith.
To be face-to-face with you once more, I-
have even been a blank check.
I can't help but to love you.
Even when you're smiling brightly with someone else.
I don't have a choice but to love you.
My air, my sun
you're like a poison I cannot quit.
Because I don't want to fight with you, I
have even been a framed convict.
To spend even a minute more with you, I
have even been a taxi driver.
I can't help but to love you.
Even if my time with you disappears more and more.
Even if I won't be able to see your heart because I'm blinded by you.
I don't have a choice but to love you.
My saving grace, my heaven,
an early dawn making me want to get drunk,
like a trap
I cannot escape.
Again she filled her semi-finalist stage with a unique self-written song.
Ye-eun. This way please.
We just listened to a song called "Pushover."
Which one of you will talk first?
Mr. Park.
Every time I saw Ye-eun perform I have said that they seem like a work of art.
As I've said before the-
just-
she didn't make it with just her mind, it's spirit-like, very unique.
Something that's inside of her, the strangeness
that cannot be seen is incorporated into her song.
I told you if I were to choose a color it was like purple.
Today it just feels like green? Or blue?
The lyrics were
not as different
and unique as I thought.
The music too, the chords, melody, in any aspect-
That unique aspect of you that we cannot see. Your mind?
What is she thinking inside?
What does her mind look like? How does she come up with music like that?
I wasn't curious today.
I think it's because my expectations have risen.
I'm already expecting this much from you to begin with.
The lyrics fell short of what I expected and the music was more simple than expected.
I felt like the purple lost a little bit of its color today.
But it doesn't make sense for you to write a song every week either.
It's amazing what you're doing.
JYP's score is-
We'll see JYP's score-
What is it?
88!
Thank you.
Let's hear from the next judge.
Is it Mr. Yang Hyun-Suk?
Last week, I said that I felt like I was looking at
more of a developed musician than a contestant.
Despite that something that I was curious about was
because you have the characteristics of a very unique musician,
after the K-pop star ends will Ahn Ye-eun
be able to approach the mainstream audience?
I did sit and think about whether she'll be able to become a mainstream artist or not.
I think it's true your song today wasn't as unique as your songs before.
Because since these shows are live you only had a week.
Park Jin-young
said that it was like the purple color changed
but I don't think
it's great if all of the flowers
are purple.
Today I realized that Ye-eun can right songs for the mainstream audience.
Today's song was like the baby's breath flowers that surround the purple flower.
So actually
because you've been so unique in all rounds,
I was actually able to see something other than those songs
I'm hopeful today in regards to the question I had
about whether you'll be able to connect with the mainstream audience.
I think I was glad to hear today's song.
Okay. YG's score is-
YG's score.
He said that he was able to see that she has potential for mainstream music.
YG. 95!
It's a high score.
Yoo Hee-yeol?
It's the semi-finals. Now.
It's the TOP 4 and
if you do well here you'll go to the finals.
Something that I'm very surprised by Ye-eun.
I think it's amazing how she dares to compete every round with her own song.
Normally you'd try to be mainstream. If it's a competition, an audition,
I thought to some degree
you'd compromise but
you never do so
I thought that your guts were something to be recognized for.
When you sang "If Spring comes" last week I was personally very worried.
Because your last song
it didn't feel like the song was reaching out to me first.
The message came to me first. But today I hear the music first.
So I thought that was a relief in a way.
I read into your lyrics more closely today Ye-eun.
Your title is Pushover.
You wrote about love but
if you just look at the lyrics
it sounds like it could happen to someone
but the perspective you have to daringly title this song Pushover.
I was astonished by that honestly.
There's this part in the lyrics
to spend even a minute more with you, I have even been a taxi driver.
You can't help but to run to the person. As you've said it's an illness.
I think it's a song only a person who's been the weaker person in love can write.
I really like this song personally.
It felt like a really sad song.
It's a song that only Ahn Ye-eun can sing.
But the arrangement of the song could have been better.
Because you're not a professional yet.
Okay. Antenna's score is-
Antenna's score.
What will it be?
Out of 100, 95!
A total of 278.
If you're rooting for Ahn Ye-eun,
please text the number 3 or Ahn Ye-eun to #0606.
Alright. Number 3 Ahn Ye-eun everyone!
You're watching K-pop star season 5's semi-final stages.
As of now you've seen 3 of the 4 TOP 4 stages.
Just looking at the judges' scores right now
Lee Soo-Jung with the score of 283 is in the lead.
We only have left Mazinger S' stage at this point.
But because the final scores reflect 40% of the audiences' text votes,
please participate now if you haven't.
Okay then this is the last stage of today's semi-final stages.
Number 4 Mazinger S!
[Park Jin-young receives Mazinger S' song selection]
Song selections are really important for Mazinger S.
What?
Finally came an opportunity to see each of the member's voices.
[Hero - Mariah Carey. Very powerful and emotional ballad song]
Our group's name is Mazinger.
It stands for "Real singers who want to move people's hearts"
but we felt like we haven't sung any songs to move people's hearts.
[Can we express the deep emotions incorporated into this song?]
I think some people could tell us that.
Why are you guys abandoning what you've been doing so well
at a critical point like this and choose to take a risk?
People might say that.
So I want us to do this even better.
Yeah.
Nervous shake.
We said let's think of this as our last stage and not regret in our song choice
so we chose a song that would force us to compete only with our vocals with no dance.
We're going to do our best.
[11PM. TOP 4 dormitory]
[4 of them return to the dorms after a late night practice]
What are these?
Hi.
[A table full of warm food]
Wait.
[Surprised]
[Joyce Lee's parents came all the way from LA]
["I really missed you"]
Were you hungry?
Ye-rim sweetie.
[They missed the warm embrace of parents]
Because you haven't eaten home-cooked meals, your mom made your favorite egg rolls
[She prepared a delicious dinner for the girls who are weary with practices]
[Eating mom's food for the first time in months]
When I was your age
there was something called the College music festival.
College Music Festival?
You know it?
-MBC? -Hey!
Why didn't you tell me?
My mom made 2nd place there back then.
You girls are going through hard times right now.
Going out early in the morning and coming back late at night. Right?
What you girls are doing
is really good practice I think.
Right?
I hope you girls do well on the TOP 4 stage so you won't regret anything.
I'd like you all to have confidence while doing it.
I'm really really proud.
Thank you so much.
I felt really proud.
I thought it was a really proud moment for my parents.
I want to do even better now that my parents are here.
[4 Mazinger S]
[Hero - Mariah Carey]
They showed us a perfect harmony as usual.
Number 4 Mazinger S.
We'll hear from the judges the scores and feedback.
Mr. Yoo?
For the first time, Mazinger S didn't do what they were the strongest in.
They chose to face the challenge directly with this world-renowned ballad
the 4 of them harmonized to the song.
You girls had behind you a string orchestra and even a large choir.
You put together a stage with a full band on this live stage.
Okay.
Over 50-60 people appeared behind you girls on the stage.
The main characters should've been just four
but I don't know if you girls beat them in that.
I can see that you girls worked hard on harmonizing and individually but-
With this large of a stage you have to sing really well.
In that aspect I'm a little disappointed.
And
you girls did just what I expected dividing them perfectly as I expected.
And in that aspect too
it kept falling short of my expectations so I think it could've been better.
But you guys worked really hard.
Antenna's score is-
Okay. Antenna's score.
Out of 100, what would it be?
89!
Thank you.
Next. Mr. Park Jin-young.
Individual vocals were better than I expected.
Actually I heard Yuyu Liu sing properly for the first time.
Except for the short-breathing and faltering notes it was better than expected.
The rest of you sang well too.
But as I'm saying it seemed like you were singing in your right minds.
How can we have you sing not with your mind but with your spirits dancing-
How?
If you add the "in" in front of spirit it becomes inspiration.
Inspiration?
While singing this song called Hero, be crazy about the lyrics.
I think I want to see you sing with your minds lost.
I was disappointed in that aspect.
JYP's score is
Okay. JYP's score-
He's talking a lot about spirits today.
90!
Next is Mr. Yang Hyun-Suk.
We'll hear our last feedback and score.
Because I'm a producer
Jin-young is one as well but
I do consider that you only have a week to prepare for a live performance.
Viewers only see results but
because I see how hard it must've been to prepare all of this,
honestly for 4 people to practice together for a week and not just individually
if you compare it to running it's like having all your legs tied.
So teamwork is really important.
I think that the time given and the conditions could not have everything be perfect.
Because the 2 of them already said the criticisms,
to say something positive,
the girl groups with 4 members right now
I don't know how many there are but
will they be able to sing as well as Mazinger S?
With all 4 of them?
Even more so those girl groups practice for months to prepare one song.
I think it's amazing you girls can come up with this much in only a week.
And I
want to praise Joyce Lee's vocals
especially.
I think she's leading the other 3 well.
I thought it was good today. YG's score is-
He had more good things to say. YG's score-
What will it be?
Out of 100
YG.
94!
Thank you.
A total score of 273
If you're rooting for Mazinger S
please text the number 4 or Mazinger S to #0606.
Number 4 Mazinger S everyone!
Korea's #1 audition program K-pop star!
All of the TOP 4 performances have taken place.
At this point,
Lee Soo-Jung with a score of 283 is in the lead.
But we cannot be sure of the results yet.
The text votes are coming in close with each team.
Who would you like to see on the final stage?
Don't tell me.
Please express it in your text messages.
As we're waiting for the viewers text votes,
we have prepared for you a special stage.
Everyone you are in luck today.
He is coming, the winner of season 3.
Bernard Park has returned with a fuzzy song to go along with Spring.
And today he's prepared a special stage with Wonder Girls' Hye-rim.
Are you guys curious?
We'll meet them now.
K-pop star!
Bernard Park & Hye-rim (Wonder Girls)
[I see you - Bernard park & Hye-rim]
I see you
you're far away but
I can recognize you.
You look very small but
I know that you're smiling.
You're getting closer.
You who are so lovely gesturing to me.
I get more and more nervous so I only smile awkwardly.
You look me in the eyes
and hold my hands naturally
and even if I don't tell you where we're going
you walk with me
and we're happy about the obvious things.
I hope time would just stop now at this moment.
I discover new things about myself as I get to know you.
You're my one and only, a lucky 4-leaf clover.
Thank you. I love that you're beside me.
We're perfect the more I look at us, I love it.
I dream of these butterflies last forever.
I'm not curious as to see how much time has passed.
A sweet kiss after embracing me warmly.
You look me in the eye
and hold my hands naturally
even if I don't tell you where we're going
you walk with me.
We're happy about the obvious things
This moment, you and I, just like this
Hold each other's hands.
Even if I don't tell you where we're going
you walk with me.
We're happy about the obvious things.
I hope time would stop right this moment
I see you.
You're getting closer.
Bernard Park's perfect Spring song.
Thank you so much for that.
YG's Yang Hyun-Suk. What did you think about the stage?
I have many complaints.
Why?
Bernard Park came to sing today on stage
and in next week's finals stage Park Jin-young makes his comeback.
Right yes.
And Antenna Music's Sam Kim is coming out next week too right?
I don't understand why you're not letting any YG singers on stage.
I saw Lee Hi's face very briefly. Where are you Hi?
Lee Hi is in the audience yes.
Yeah I didn't know she was here either. I'm kidding.
Bernard Park and Sam Kim were both guys we had many expectations for.
I think viewers who love K-pop star would've very much looked forward to it.
I think people can look forward to Park Jin-young's stage next week too.
We'll look forward to YG's comeback as well.
Soon the time of fate will arrive.
We'll announce who passes and who will be eliminated.
Take a look at TOP 4's highlight clips and
we'll wait for your texts for 1 more minute.
Who will pass and who will be eliminated? Stay with us until the end.
Let's look at the highlights.
K-pop star!
[1 Lee Si-eun]
[2 Lee Soo-Jung]
[3 Ahn Ye-eun]
[4 Mazinger S]
[End of text votes]
The winner of K-pop star season 5 will receive a total of $3,000,000.
And they will also be awarded with a global midsized car.
[Incheon Nam-dong center live]
This is an important moment. Survival audition K-pop star season 5.
We only have left the announcement of who will continue onto the final round.
As a result of 60% of the judges' scores and 40% of the text votes,
only 2 of the 4 teams standing here will be on the next week's final stages.
I think Yang Hyun-Suk in the judges seats is holding an envelope.
And I just received an envelope as well.
The 2 envelopes have inside them names of people who will continue onto the finals.
Because we haven't opened it yet we do not know.
We'll have to hear how the TOP 4 are feeling right now.
Si-eun. How are you feeling?
Everyone did so well today
but I can't really tell who's going to be eliminated.
I see.
Your feedback weren't all that great today regarding your stage. What do you think?
Are you disappointed? Or-
I feel like I didn't show everything I had so I am a little bit but it's okay.
Okay.
Soo-Jung?
How do you feel right now?
Everyone did so well so I'm curious as to how it's going to turn out.
I see.
Do you think your name will be called? Or not?
What are you predicting?
I don't know.
You don't?
I see.
Ye-eun?
Yes.
What do you think? Do you think you'll make it to the next round? Or
do you think you'll get eliminated?
I'm wondering that myself.
I asked you because I was wondering.
I don't really know.
You don't?
I see. How do you feel right now?
Do you feel good? Or-
I think I did everything without regrets so-
You don't have regrets about your stages.
Okay.
Mazinger S?
How do you feel?
It's sad to think this might be our last but we have no regrets.
I see.
How about Joyce Lee?
Yes. How do you feel?
I want to know the results but I'm proud that we worked hard.
I see.
I think everyone's calmly waiting for the results now.
Who,
out of these 4 teams,
everyone has the ability to win,
will be the 2 teams to go onto next week's live stages.
Mr. Yang will you announce it?
Please announce the first team to continue on.
[Who will be the first to go on to the final round?]
Unfortunately the feedback were overall not very positive today
and just by looking at the judges' scores
the scores do not differ by much.
Everyone differs by 4-5 points.
It means that it was a close competition.
The text votes came in very close as well.
Okay. Mr. Yang Hyun-Suk!
Who is the 1st team to continue onto the next week's live final round?
A contestant I really love is going onto the final round first.
The first team to continue onto the final round is
I'm getting nervous.
I'm getting anxious.
The judges' scores were not far apart.
For everyone.
I'll announce it.
Lee Soo-Jung.
Congratulations!
Soo-Jung please come up to the platform.
She interpreted Park Jin-young's "That house you live in" really well in her own way.
Soo-Jung is on the final platform first.
Now the remaining 3 teams.
Only 1 out of these 3 teams will be on the final rounds next week.
I will now open this envelope that I am holding.
Who had the second largest number of votes in combination of both scores?
[Who will be the last team to join the final round? And who will be eliminated?]
I will announce it now.
Lee Si-eun, Ahn Ye-eun, and Mazinger S.
Whoever I announce
no one will object.
Everyone did well today.
But from the results
this person, this team will be continuing onto next week's live stage.
Lee Si-eun with the perfect high notes,
Ahn Ye-eun who surprises us every week with her self-written songs each week,
and Mazinger S with the best harmony and performance.
Out of these 3 teams,
this team is going to continue onto next week's live stage.
I'll announce it!
The team
who will be on the TOP 2 of K-pop star
the last team to continue on is!
Ahn Ye-eun!
Congratulations.
Soo-Jung you can come out.
Yes so..
She overcame the pressure to have to come up with a new song every week
and ended up in the TOP 2.
Okay the-
Ye-eun. How do you feel right now?
I don't know if I deserve this.
But because I'm presented with it, I'll prepare my best. Thank you.
Will your next week's final stage be your own song as well?
I think so.
She says she thinks so.
Regrettably Lee Si-eun and Mazinger S will leave K-pop star today.
First, Si-eun.
How do you feel right now?
I think I learned a lot having gone through this.
I thank the 3 judges for giving me such good advice
I thank the staff who worked so hard, my fans, family and friends who encouraged me.
I'll work hard and grow more from now. Thank you.
Thank you.
There's no question that Si-eun has talent.
Mr. Park why don't you tell her something.
Yes.
You two had a mentor-mentee relationship.
I can't
ever forget Si-eun's first song "I will sing."
Those, those lyrics back then
felt like you were just pouring what's in your heart right into the song.
If you can just find that again I think you'll become an excellent singer.
That performance will linger with me for a long time.
Thank you. You worked hard.
Okay.
Please thank Park Jin-young with another awesome stage in the future.
Mazinger S. A word?
I was thankful that each of us from different countries were able to come together.
I thank our parents for giving birth to us beautifully.
Thank you judges for working so hard.
I thought it was impossible for us to come all the way to TOP 4 so
I really thank God.
Thank you.
Coming to K-pop star, this was really a miracle, making it to TOP 4.
I was able to meet all my friends and I'm thankful. Thank you K-pop star!
Thank you.
So K-pop star season 5 ended up with two finalists
Lee Soo-Jung and Ahn Ye-eun.
Next week's final stages will also be live.
Please look forward to Lee Soo-Jung and Ahn Ye-eun's stages.
We'll see you next week. K-pop star! Thank you.