[Your song, it awakens the world's sensibility]
[A 10-month journey to find the new Kpop star]
Kpop star season 5's
much anticipated final round.
[Made it all the way here through all the competitions!]
[Both are uniquely talented in their own ways]
I think it's the first time that 2 such different contestants ended up in the finals.
It's simply the matter of whether it being a vocalist? Or an artist?
Soo-jung has her distinct color.
From the start
she was anticipated to be the finalist.
She even received a 100 last time.
She's good.
Ye-eun continues to write her songs and
I'm scared because she's really good.
She has many fans so I feel overwhelmed.
No one can predict this at all.
[And! The unique trajectory only with the Kpop star]
[Last poll! Which company do you want to sign with at the moment?]
I'm really nervous right now.
I can't be too obvious about who I want.
If I have the opportunity I would love to share the joy with this contestant.
Today, another Kpop star is born.
[A fifth Kpop star is born today!]
[Incheon Nam-dong center]
Survival audition Kpop star season 5 has finally
arrived at its finals round.
Introducing the final 2!
The first favorite to win
the height of a twist ending,
increasing in popularity
Ahn Ye-eun!
2nd contestant.
A deliberate deliverer of emotions,
quality R&B Soul, Lee Soo-jung!
And the stars of Kpop star, introducing the 3 judges!
JYP Park Jin-young!
YG Yang Hyun-suk!
Antenna Yoo Hee-yeol!
Please give it up one more time to
the final 2 contestants and the 3 judges!
Today is our final day.
The live show that will decide Kpop star season 5's winner.
I'm emcee Jeon Hyun-moo. Hello.
This season particularly had several unique contestants.
Today we have left Lee Soo-jung and Ahn Ye-eun.
No one is able to predict who will be the winner of these 2.
Mr. Yang, representing the judges, how do you think today will go like?
Because today is a special day, Yang Hyun-suk came without a hat today!
This is personally my first time seeing his hair.
It's your own hair right?
Honestly before you mentioned that, when I first saw him,
I thought he had plastic surgery.
Doesn't his hair kind of look like GD's?
It does.
It feels like you got it done at where GD gets his hair done.
It wasn't from GD's place, it was around his neighborhood.
Oh just around the neighborhood?
Alright no pun intended.
Mr. Yang. What do you predict?
Out of the 2 of them, whoever wins,
I don't think anyone will object but-
it's another topic of interest for us judges
to see which company the winner will choose.
Last year JYP took Bernard Park
and last year YG took Katie Kim.
It is my hope that this year's contestant
will consider going to Antenna.
That is my hope.
Mr. Yoo what do you think?
Unfortunately there has not been a winner that chose Antenna yet.
What do you predict?
I
can't really tell what the contestants are thinking.
And because this is a decision with their life dependent on it
rather than thinking about where you go,focus on today's performance.
I ask that you'll show us everything you have, like it's your concert.
You'll focus on the performances too right?
Yes.
Because as soon as the winner is announce, they are to choose a company.
The 3 judges can't help but to be nervous as well.
Mr. Park today's final round is a little different from the past rounds correct?
Yes the 2 contestants will be competing twice against one another.
The first competition will consist of songs that they each want to sing.
The second competition you can only see at Kpop star.
The contestant chooses a song that the opponent contestant sang in the past
and interprets in their own to way to sing. It's a round with a mission.
Yes.
Through these 2 competitions,
the winner will be decided.
Today's round will also be 60% of the judges' scores and 40% of viewers votes
and the total score will decide the winner today.
Then I will announce the order of performances today and their numbers!
First TOP 2,
increasing popularity with no limits,
now a developed artist number 1 Ahn Ye-eun! Number 1.
Next.
The careful sensitivities that captures our ears,
the quality R&B Soul, number 2 Lee Soo-jung. Number 2!
Kpop star season 5's final last stage.
Stay with us until the end.
We have prepared many stages along our TOP 2 stages.
Boom! What do we have prepared?
Hello I'm Boom!
Make some noise!
The grand Kpop star.
It is finally our last stage.
So we have many special stages prepared for you today.
First, Kpop star season 3's 2nd place winner,
Sam Kim, he prepared his debut album for the past two years
and it will be first revealed here!
And
he is awesome as Kpop star's judge
but when he goes on stage the crowd goes crazy.
The musician that makes us happy,
JYP's new song will be revealed here for the first time!
Amazing.
This is not the end.
The popular contestants from Kpop season 5
has prepared a special stage for us as well.
Everyone. By the end of this hour, the winner of Kpop star season 5 will be announced.
Please make the winner win yourselves.
All you have to do is to text the name of the contestant you support
or their contestant number to #0606.
Who will be the winner? Stick around until the end.
First, we'll begin with the viewers' votes
and we'll begin the final competitions as well.
Contestant number 1
Ahn Ye-eun's stage is ready.
Are you guys ready?
Kpop star!
[Text votes begin]
[After last week's semi-final round...]
Ye-eun you're amazing.
You have to bring something more impactful at the final rounds.
Don't think about what will be good just pick one that'll make you go crazy.
Whether you write a song or you pick one that's out there-
They told me to go crazy.
I was thankful that they told me that but
I also had to think what song would I be able to sing with excitement?
[Comtemplative Ye-eun, she is heading somewhere with her mom]
Hello.
Ye-eun.
How are you?
[Where did they go?]
There's a place I used to perform and work at.
I was able to build up my experiences there so I wanted to go before the final round.
But it's really pretty.
The stage is really pretty.
Are you reminded of the old times?
Yeah.
You enjoyed it back then.
I'm reminded of the old times now that I'm back here.
I enjoyed performing back then.
I used to be really excited.
I want to perform like I used to, while having fun.
[What is Ahn Ye-eun's new song that she's written for the final round?]
The title is not as unusual as the song titles before but
for some reason I think the song will be very unusual because the title isn't.
I wrote this song in 2012 so
I remember being really excited when I was writing this song.
I'll be excited and have a lot of fun since this is my last stage.
Please look forward to it.
Go Ahn Ye-eun!
[1 Ahn Ye-eun]
[Tell me - Ahn Ye-eun]
I pick up and put down the empty cup, biting my nails for no reason.
The time is running but you don't seem to be hurrying up.
My eyes lose sight with your mouth shut.
With your eyes looking afar my heart loses its way and dances.
Your heart is kicked out to the side and I look for the password.
I am a baby bird having lost its mother as I'm trapped in a maze.
Please. Tell me something, anything.
Please untangle your thoughts that are unknown to me.
Just look at me just once, please.
My heart that's shriveled at your cold stare.
No matter how much I think about it and think back,
I don't know why you're mad.
I rewind, untangle, and piece them back together again,
Do you know what I did wrong?
Tell me.
Please. Just let me at least feel you breathe for just once.
Please untangle the knots that you have tightly roped around your heart.
Please look at the once-beautiful memories.
What to do with my love that's been cut by the ends of your sharp stares?
What to do with my future?
What to do with the rest of my life?
No matter how much I think about it,
No matter how much I think about it and think back,
I don't know why you're mad.
I untangle, rewind, and piece it back together.
Do you know what I did wrong?
Tell me.
She presents us with another unique and a dynamic stage today.
We'll hear from the judges.
I thought Park Jin-young's face lit up.
Can we hear from you?
I think the most common thing I've said about your stages is that it's a work of art.
Products? Or a work of art.
A product and a work of art can be similar in its idea but
they have a astronomical difference.
It's a work of art if it has within it the mind and the thoughts of the maker,
if it's just for the purpose and its looks it's a product. Like this pen.
When I look at all the songs you've written I can tell what kind of a person you are.
The song carries much of your past life, personality, and your daily life.
So I keep referring to them as works of art.
Today's song as well. It seems like you have always loved this way.
You give everything like a fool
and in front of the person you love you don't know how to manipulate them or lie.
You just love them.
And men took advantage of that in your past.
Because I feel like I can know the kind of person that you are,
I can't help but to say that it's a work of art.
I think your music, and the person that you are is a work of art.
I wasn't too surprised by your music this time, just a little bit.
That's a minute detail I wish I could've seen.
I didn't know a day would come when you'd be able to go crazy like this on stage
this is all thanks to the love the people pour out to you.
JYP's score is-
He said that Ahn Ye-eun is a work of art herself.
Out of a 100, what is JYP's score?
92!
Mr. Yoo?
Not many people would've predicted that Ye-eun would have made it to the final round.
Especially because you didn't make the cut for episodes 1 through 10,
the viewers were not able to see you and you made you appearance at episode 11.
You are persistent in coming up with a variety of your songs that you write yourself.
I was surprised once again to see you bring your own song to the final round as well.
I was surprised by 2 aspects.
The first was
your vocal skills are getting better from the first time I heard you.
It feels like your vocal is becoming more developed.
Second.
Up to this point, starting from Hong-yeon, probability of numbers, Mr. Mystery, etc.
There were a variety of songs but the song that you sang today, "Tell me,"
I feel like what's musically unique about you is all inside of this one song.
So
apart from the fact that this song is special,
it's complete.
It feels a lot more lyrically organized.
this might be your signature song.
I have been waiting for a musician that could be rendered special.
I think that's you Ye-eun.
Okay. Antenna's score.
He praised that this was Ahn Ye-eun's signature song.
Antenna.. 97 points!
It's high!
It's high.
Mr. Yang.
This might be something that Park Jin-young said the most this season.
I think he compared products and work of art the most this season.
Usually artists, the drawing artists,
only draw one kind of work.
For example Korea's artist Paik Nam Jun made one work of art,
and a famous artist like Andy Warhol draws only one work of art.
That's why we call their creation a work of art.
I 100% agree that Ahn Ye-eun is a work of art because
I honestly believe that it'll be difficult to find another artist like Ahn Ye-eun.
Since is this the final round I'll talk more about your strengths.
Your vocal style
is kind of like trot, something that even the older 50s and 60s audiences will enjoy.
But then her music has many characteristics of indie music.
And your lyrics are very hip, something that young generation will like.
You're a contestant that no one has ever seen or heard before.
So it's really difficult for me to give you a score.
YG's score is-
What score will she receive?
It was unclear whether it was a praise or a criticism-
95!
A total score of 284!
For the first round, she received the total score of 284 from the judges.
If you're rooting for Ahn Ye-eun, text the number 1
or Ahn Ye-eun to #0606.
Number 1 Ahn Ye-eun everyone!
[It's already been 6 months since the beginning of Kpop star]
It's already been 6 months.
Hello. My name is Lee Soo-jung.
When I first came here from Chicago,
I never thought I would make it this far.
I thought I would be eliminated on the first round.
But-
[Mazinger S and Lee Si-eun all left the dormitory]
Soo-jung are you crying?
Don't cry.
[Her friends that she's become close to continued to leave her]
Bye.
Friends left one by one and I
continued to say "Huh? Where's Joyce?"
or "Huh? Mazinger should be here soon" I kept doing that.
Now it's only 2 of us left
it feels really empty.
[Admist the pressures of being a TOP2, what song did Lee Soo-jung choose?]
[What is the meaning of this sigh?]
I can't imagine it.
How is she going to sing it? Does she know this song?
It's Korean pop, first of all.
Soo-jung is stubborn 'til the end.
I honestly thought she'd choose pop.
It's the Koreanest Korean pop.
Kim Kwang-jin's "Letter."
[Traditional Korean pop with the sentimental, Kim Kwang-jin's "Letter"]
To be honest I wanted to sing pop, which would be more comfortable for me.
[Why do you continue to choose Korean pop?]
But
I sang more Korean pop as I went on with Kpop star,
I will sing Korean pop on my last stage as well.
I think Soo-jung's R&B stands out more
when she sings slower songs rather than faster ones.
I came this far, I want to see how much more I can go.
I sing for myself.
I'm just going to try my best because this is my last stage.
[2 Lee Soo-jung]
[Letter - Kim Kwang-suk]
I guess this is the end.
I will turn my back now.
I won't try to go against fate by force
and bother you.
Things I want to say
things I meant to say-
I will leave them all here.
I intend on giving up on any small hope and expectations as well.
dear please be happy.
Your long silence,
I will take it as goodbye.
Don't worry
about hurting me.
Dear I have loved you,
I won't be able to see you anymore but
I am honestly thankful
that I was able to overcome the difficult day because you were by my side.
Meet someone nice.
Forget me while you go on with the rest of your life.
I wish that you'd be happy.
Just take my heart with you.
I guess this is the end.
I will turn my back now.
I intend on giving up on any small hopes and expectations as well.
Just take my heart with you.
Number 2 Lee Soo-jung's stage.
She interpreted in her own way a sad ballad.
We'll hear from the judges if she has moved their hearts.
Which one of you will grab the microphone first?
Yes. Mr. Yoo.
It's the final round.
2 contestants are fighting over the remaining winning spot.
1 contestant continues to come out with her own songs
and you
are stubbornly holding onto Korean pop.
I know because I trained with you that you're not completely fluent in Korean.
So I thought you'd sing pop.
Because this is your most critical stage.
But after seeing you choose Korean pop even on this stage,
I was surprised.
This song is too particular to show your pop-like characteristic.
There were things like that at the end but
seeing you face your challenges directly
I am continuously surprised by that.
So later when you debut,
I think it's really important to push through with your style.
Okay today-
I wish I could've seen more of your strengths.
But I combined every side of you that I've seen until now.
And I also took into consideration that it's the final round.
So the score. Antenna's score is-
What score would he have given? Antenna's score-
Out of a 100,
a score of 93.
Next.
Mr. Yang?
I thought the same things as Yoo Hee-yeol.
Before Soo-jung sang
this song called "Letter,"
Park Jin-young told me "do you think she can sing this well?"
He was telling me that he was worried.
Because this is a song with such a different style.
So I was hoping she would change the song entirely to her style
I was expecting that when I was listening.
I was a little surprised that you didn't change it at all.
So on the positive note
you're trying something new
you kept to the originals.
But I wish you could've taken advantage of this opportunity
had she changed it to your style entirely and sang it that way,
I think it might have been much better to listen to.
YG's stage, YG's score is-
We'll see YG's stage later.
The score is
92!
Nice.
He pointed out some points of improvement. Mr. Park?
I, too,
agree with what Hyun-suk said.
But actually,
you can't
really change this song very much.
So
until now you've showed a couple of times that you were able to
embody other genres that we didn't think you could pull off.
Perhaps your challenge to yourself this time may have been a little too audacious.
I think this song might have been a little difficult to do that. But-
I want to praise you for continuing to step out of your comfort zone.
But I do want to point out,
your vocals have developed a lot.
You can't even compare where you are now and where you began.
I am very proud of you in that aspect.
JYP's score is-
He complimented her in vocal improvement. JYP's score?
92!
A total score of 277.
If you're rooting for Lee Soo-jung,
please text the number 2 or Lee Soo-jung to #0606.
Number 2 Lee Soo-jung everyone!
Thank you for the 2 contestants' stages.
We'll look forward to the 2nd round of mission competition soon as well.
As of right now
Ahn Ye-eun is on the lead by not very much.
Now it is our time to invite the special stages.
Kpop star season 3's semi-finalist.
Sam Kim, who was named the guitar genius and was very loved by many is coming.
After preparing for the last 2 years at Antenna,
he will be debuting right here and now.
Mr. Yoo. You were with him every step of the way.
Tell us what kind of a stage and a song this is. Right now.
Yes.
The following stage is of a song that Sam Kim wrote himself.
He wrote and rearranged all of the songs on his album.
One particular person is helping him out with this song.
Crush, who is very popular these days, is featuring the song.
It's called "Let's leave it."
We'll see after seeing the performance whether the song is good or not.
The most beloved Sam Kim has now returned as a singer.
Let us invite him on stage.
Kpop star!
Hello.
I'm 15, 15. My name is Sam Kim and I am from Seattle, Washington.
Thank you.
I think this was meant to be.
Let's go to the ends with me.
[Sam Kim is now a family of Antenna, his first stage begins now]
[Let's leave it - Sam Kim]
You told me to tell you first.
You told me to tell you right away when I'm mad.
I don't understand.
What are you thinking.
I have lots to think about right now here and there.
I'm clueless.
I don't know if I'm being unbelievable
I'm a fool for liking you, you're a fool for already knowing. It's all complicated.
How many more times should I say that you're pretty?
I'm getting weary because of you.
Why are you getting mad?
Don't lie.
Enough is enough.
What are you thinking?
I have lots to think about right now here and there.
Don't you get tired?
I'm clueless.
I don't know if I'm being unbelievable
I'm a fool for liking you, you're a fool for already knowing. It's all complicated.
Everything is complicated, the same, you're right.
At times even talking all night on the phone won't even do.
The aversive strategy is becoming banal for a reason perhaps.
You're not the only one at fault.
I'll be better to you definitely.
I don't ever intend to leave you and go.
How great would it be if you were honest with me?
Then don't show that you're mad at least.
You're more important than anyone else.
You hurt me more than anyone else.
You know why.
I'm clueless.
I don't know if I'm being unbelievable
I'm a fool for liking you, you're a fool for already knowing. It's all complicated.
I'm clueless.
I don't know if I'm being unbelievable
I'm a fool for liking you, you're a fool for already knowing. It's all complicated.
Kpop star stage stayed the some but Sam Kim returned a changed man.
He became a man and a celebrity.
Thank you for the great performance.
Now, as Mr. Park said, it is the mission round.
The two contestants are in trouble. The contestants find this round most difficult.
We'll continue the second round with "Sing the other contestant's song".
Because the 2 contestants are very unique in their styles
I can't imagine them having to sing each other's songs.
We'll see what they have for us.
We'll invite number 1 Ahn Ye-eun first.
Number 1 Ahn Ye-eun everyone!
[The staff asked to meet the two somewhere]
[What's going on?]
[An envelop enclosed with a mission is handed to them!]
Please open the envelop at the same time and read what's written inside of it.
[What mission surprised the two so much?]
The final round mission is
to sing each other's song.
I had no idea what to do.
I was shocked.
I think I would've cried.
I would've asked why I had to do this when we're at the end.
I would've broke down.
Anyone can tell the two of them have such a different music style,
they also have different singing styles.
I'm worried about that but at the same time
I'm looking forward to it.
How many songs are on there that you think you might be able to do?
There is none.
None?
Either they're ballads I have never heard before
or a R&B.
All of them.
I didn't even know where to begin.
[Ye-eun is listening to the songs that Soo-jung's sung]
[Getting more difficult as she listens]
I don't have as stable and an excellent of a vocal.
One song I thought maybe I could rearrange
was this song.
[What song did she end up choosing?]
[Looking hard]
This is literally a mission for Ye-eun.
Stevie Wonder's Part time lover.
[The song Soo-jung sang with Yoo Jay during the casting audition "Part time lover"]
She was really praised for that performance.
I was worried I would continue to be reminded of that performance as I was singing.
I sing the first verse in English.
I tried to change the lyrics to Korean that goes along with the lyrics.
I rearranged the song the best I could to change the song to my style.
This is a challenge, a very big challenge.
But who knows?
If she overcame that and owned this song as entirely hers,
I think I'll be completely surprised.
[1 Ahn ye-eun]
Part-Time Lover - Stevie Wonder
The cafe at the end of the cross street,
the second table near the window.
I'll be waiting for you wearing a white dress.
You look to her
your hands onto my waist.
Under the moon,
As if dancing a graceful dance, without any sound,
I walk the night, carefully.
Beyond the eyes where the sun rises,
we prepare tomorrow's secrets.
If I wink my eye, you have to pass me like you don't know me.
If I cough twice you can see me again tomorrow.
You and me.
Without anyone knowing.
She played the keyboard so passionately her hair is messy.
Thank you Ye-eun for singing for us.
What did you guys think about "Part-Time Lover"? Mr. Park?
Because Ye-eun is an agent in her music rearrangements,
we took particular attention to how you rearranged the song.
People typically say, like this song I just came out with, "you're still alive."
I thought about what it would mean to be alive.
You're alive if something goes within you
and is changed by the time it comes out.
Whatever the song may be, to Ye-eun
it goes inside of her
and when it comes out,
it comes out changed, dipped in your particular color.
I think she showed us all the technical of music she could.
Even in reharmonization, she went from high chord progression to low.
She went from minor to major.
Beats from double time to single time.
You were really into this music and had fun while doing it.
Really-
I think you showed all of your strengths on this stage.
JYP's score is-
Nice.
JYP's score.
98!
Very close to a 100.
It's a high score.
Okay. Mr. Yoo?
There are usually typical attributes to an audition program like this.
I have never seen a musician like Ye-eun make it all the way to the finals.
And I have never seen someone not get nervous and continue to keep their style.
Ye-eun,
to be honest,
really.
You have this unique characteristic that some people might not like.
But your one important charm is
that you know how to provoke a person.
And you're not using any shallow strategy,
I'm glad that you're using music to do that.
You're a very interesting contestant.
Should I say a problematic contestant?
Antenna's score is-
The problematic contestant Ahn Ye-eun.
What would Antenna's score be?
98!
She's scoring very high.
What will Mr. Yang Hyun-Suk say?
I don't think I'm giving good feedback today.
I don't like the way I'm doing it.
I think it's because-
Is this your first time feeling that way?
I think it's because I
took off my hat one during season 1
and I'm without my hat for the first time in 5 years.
I'm very embarrassed I feel very unfamiliar.
It's great it reminds me of your Suh Tae-ji and kids days.
It's like going back to your old days.
But this is how powerful music can be.
I was looking at the previous stage with Sam Kim,
I was asking myself why I hadn't recruited him.
His stage was that much excited to even make me regret
and then Ye-eun came out
and put together such a perfect show,
I think I can do better with my feedback now.
The score that I just gave you
is a score that I give to Sam Kim and Ahn Ye-eun.
Okay. YG's score is-
What could he mean?
A score given to Sam Kim and Ahn Ye-eun.
100!
A total score of 296!
Yang Hyun-Suk gave her a score of 100.
If you're supporting Ahn Ye-eun,
text number 1 or Ahn Ye-eun to #0606
Number 1 Ahn Ye-eun everyone!
Now we only have left our last performance of Kpop star season 5.
How will Lee Soo-Jung interpret Ahn Ye-eun's particularly unique songs?
Number 2 Lee Soo-jung's stage everyone!
[The most difficult mission faced during the final round!]
[Soo-jung's face darkens as soon as she opens the envelop]
[She just looks at the song lists without saying anything]
Can you read the songs that's written?
Almost all of them are written by her.
[Except one song, all of them are Ye-eun's songs]
To be honest I was a little mad.
Because all Ye-eun's songs are written by her.
The songs are great the way they are,
I didn't want to touch them.
[Which song did Soo-Jung choose out of Ye-eun's songs?]
I feel like it's going to be this one song.
I thought she was going to sing Mr. Mystery.
[What did Soo-Jung choose instead of the popular Mr. Mystery?]
This was unexpected.
The song I'm going to sing is
Stick-er by Ye-eun.
[stick-er portrays the obsession of a stalker]
This song is the symbol of Ye-eun's dark purple color.
How will Soo-Jung change this to her classy gold, black, silver?
Soo-Jung can act a little bit when she sings.
Maybe a different stalker?
She might be able to portray a sexier vibe I think.
I can't play the piano or play any other instruments so
honestly I only have my voice.
I will use my voice well to sing.
[2 Lee Soo-Jung]
[Stick-er - Ahn Ye-eun]
That day
that night.
I came out of that room.
I walked a far way barefoot.
That day
that night.
Everything ended.
I sang a very sad song.
I'm going to find you.
I will.
I followed your voice, your scent
and your footsteps.
I slowly recalled the traces yet to be burned.
Are you happy?
I'm not.
I put my hands
on a cold wall.
Your eyes, your gestures,
your everything, everything about you.
The way you look from the back, your shadow,
even your single breath-
I'm not going anywhere.
You can't go anywhere.
That day
that night.
I came out of that room.
I walked a far way barefooted.
That day
that night.
I was broken.
I sang a very painful song.
I'm going to
find you.
Number 2 Lee Soo-Jung. Park Jin-young has both his hands up.
Yoo Hee-yeol had a face that I could not read.
Yang Hyun-Suk had a wide smile on his face.
She was behind by 7 points in judges' scores from the first round.
Will she be able to make up the points?
Mr. Park.
Before
when you were singing "letter."
I felt like I was going crazy because I felt like I couldn't breathe.
Is this how this is going to end?
Here?
You showed it all on your second song.
You perfectly show what kind of a person you are, what kind of a singer you are.
I mean, this contestant
was the same one who couldn't hit the high notes during the first round.
She didn't know how to sing the high notes so she used her high notes.
How could this happen?
She challenged herself with K-pop songs but
she also discovered how to sing the high notes during this program.
She's an amazing contestant. And as I always say,
she always does things that I cannot predict.
Earlier-
when she sang there was a part when she dropped to major 7.
Those things. People usually don't go to that note.
There are definite reasons to cut down on points when giving a score
JYP's score is-
She is unpredictable.
JYP!
A 100!
It is his second 100!
Personally for Lee Soo-Jung it's her 2nd 100 as well.
It is the 2nd 100 of the day as well.
Okay.
Mr. Yang?
It looks like right now
I feel like I'm watching a movie with a twist or something.
This is the last song.
To be honest, before she sang this song
I thought Ahn Ye-eun might win.
But Soo-Jung
when she encounters a song that suits her,
she hits a home run.
On the other hand, Ahn Ye-eun showed us a very unique stage with her own songs.
The score that I'm giving you may seem like it's low.
YG's score is-
It may be low.
YG's score?
A movie with a twist.
A 100!
2nd 100!
Today's 3rd 100.
Lee Soo-jung's 3rd 100.
She currently has a score of 200.
Mr. Yoo?
Unbelievable.
You sang Kim Kwang-jin's "Letter" earlier.
The first lyric of that song
says "I guess this is the end."
That's how the song starts.
I was wondering why you chose a song with those lyrics.
Is she saying goodbye?
Why did she choose that song?
But the last lyric of this song
it's like, almost like a femme fatale in a movie,
she portrayed a twist saying "I'm going to find you."
I have goosebumps all over my body right now.
Ye-eun may have written the song
but I think Lee Soo-Jung owns the song.
Antenna's score is-
Would this not be the end?
No way. Antenna.
A 100!
300. A perfect score!
Thank you.
There has never been a judges' score of 300, a perfect score.
This is unprecedented in the history of Kpop star.
Viewers. If you are rooting for Lee Soo-Jung,
please text number 2 or Lee Soo-Jung to #0606.
Number 2 Lee Soo-Jung everyone!
Final round of Kpop star's season 5!
Is it Ahn Ye-eun? Or Lee Soo-Jung?
Is it Lee Soo-Jung? Or Ahn Ye-eun?
Who are you rooting for?
Ahn Ye-eun!
Who?
They are really close.
They have a difference of 3 points.
We are waiting for your votes everyone.
Please vote for the contestant you are rooting for.
In just a moment
the winner will be announced.
Viewers and every fan around the globe.
This one stage is coming to you.
Park Jin-young's comeback stage is being prepared.
The title is "Still alive."
Mr. Yoo. What do you think this stage is going to look like?
To be honest, I
To be honest, I watched the music video of this song beforehand.
I was very surprised by the lyrics.
It sounds like he wrote his own autobiography.
I thought at first "Could he do that? How can he be so shameless?"
but of course he's forever a music-lover.
After I heard it I thought that JYP has returned.
I was really glad and I
want to cheer him on as a friend.
JYP's first comeback stage in the world.
The best singer who's been giving us happiness for years.
Everyone let's invite him up on stage.
Park Jin-young!
["Still alive" - Park Jin-young]
Everyone stand up!
Singer who dances is how old?
40 and 4 more. He's still at his peak.
He's different from the stars that are newly popular.
Those of you who come and go. Watch.
I don't act like I'm cute, I'm not pretentious.
I don't say that my lover is all of you.
I play like the party-animal I am.
Even after that I'm still alive.
Records became cassettes.
Cassettes turned into CDs.
Even after CDs became streaming downloads.
Even in the 90s, 2000, and in 2010,
I'm still alive.
Even in the 90s, 2000, and in 2010.
Everyone gather around. You know who I am right?
I'm different from the boy groups that you like.
I debuted before those boy groups were born,
but I get awards in front of those boys.
I'm sorry. I hope your boys survive as long as I did.
But that's not as easy as it sounds so I'm a little worried.
If you study me the probability goes up.
Records turned into cassettes.
Cassettes changed to CDs.
Even when CDs' become streaming, and downloads
even in the 90s, 2000, and in 2010,
I'm still alive.
Even in the 90s, 2000, and in 2010.
It's not the survival of the fittest.
The ones who survive are the fittest.
You call someone a singer after 10 years.
You call someone a star after 20 years.
You call someone a legend after 30 years.
So just like that I am still hungry.
Records turned into cassettes.
Cassettes changed to CDs.
Even when CDs become download, and streaming,
even in the 90s, 2000, and in 2010,
I'm still alive.
Even in the 90s, 2000, and in 2010.
You call someone a singer after 10 years.
You call someone a star after 20 years.
You call someone a legend after 30 years.
So just like that I am still hungry.
Still alive.
JYP does not disappoint.
You find yourself going with the rhythm.
I think this place turned into JYP's concert for a moment instead of Kpop star.
What did the 2 judges think?
They're really big deals.
Mr. Yang?
What did you think?
Park Jin-young is 3 years younger than me.
The fact that he can sing and dance on stage
I think is incredible especially seeing it in person today.
Park Jin-young performed a comeback stage last year too
and that song became number 1 in the charts.
It did.
I think he might be drawing attention to himself once again today.
On the final round.
Presenting his new song.
I think Park Jin-young's stage is great, needless to say.
We have with us today last year's winner Katie Kim.
Our iKon is here as well.
And Kwon Jin-ah, Jung Seung-hwan, and Lee Jin-ah are here as well.
I wanted to introduce that they were here to the viewers.
So I thought I'd mention them.
More important than giving feedback on JYP's stage,
is to introduce his company's artists.
What did you think Yoo Hee-yeol?
I was glad to see that for the first time JYP's choreography was something I could do.
I'm very glad.
From what I understand you can't even dance that.
Alright.
It was a great performance.
I think he might take over the music charts once again.
Now the time has come for us to finalize our Kpop star season 5 journey.
Before we announce the winner and her choice of company,
we have prepared a special stage to celebrate our last stage of Kpop star.
Kpop star's participants and this person will come to stage.
You will be very surprised.
What could it be?
Let us see the special stage.
We'll invite them up now!
This season's contestants'
process of overcoming their fears and their pain
it gave us courage just by observing them.
I read once online that someone wrote
I don't know if Si-eun will read this or not but I was very encouraged by her song.
When I read that I
was very touched and almost cried.
Our family told us that thanks to you guys our last 6 months have been so fun.
All our hard-work was worth it.
There are people out there who were happy and had fun because of us.
That made me really happy.
My name is Joo Mi-yeon, 25 years old, from Kwang-Joo.
I was very scared of stages.
I was scared and shook with fear.
I realized that I could be loved when people encouraged me.
So I was very encouraged.
One of them overcame stage fright,
another overcame language, the language-barrier.
Still another had no idea how to express emotions but they began to here.
Seeing all of that
as I personally feel stuck as I'm faced with reality
I am comforted and encouraged.
[Everyone - Yoo Bok-hee]
[Singer Lee Jin-ah]
If you are
in affliction,
I will comfort you.
If you are
feeling sad
I will
be your tears.
On a dark night
when you're walking through a dangerous road
I will be your light.
When you're feeling empty
and lonely
I will be your friend.
I am forever your brother.
I am your friend.
I am forever your friend.
I am your joy.
[Jazz Saxophonist Lee Jung-sik]
[Singer Yoon Bok-hee]
I am, I am, I am, I am your friend.
I am your
If
we are feeling lonely
who will comfort us?
All of you.
No one would've imagined.
The stage was put together by Yoo Bok-hee and the participants of Kpop star.
It was a very touching and a beautiful performance.
Lee Jin-ah's piano performance also touched my heart as well.
Yes.
We didn't even tell the judges.
They were so surprised they got out of their seats.
Thank you.
Now we must focus. In just a moment, the text votes will terminate.
The much anticipated final winner will be decided.
Ahn Ye-eun as of now is leading by 3 points.
For those of you who have not yet voted, we will show their highlight clips of today.
In one minute the text votes will close. If you have not voted yet please do so.
Who will be the winner of Kpop star season 5?
Let us watch the highlight clips together.
Kpop star!
[1 Ahn Ye-eun]
[2 Lee Soo-Jung]
[Text votes closed]
The winner of Kpop star season 5 will be awarded with $3 million.
Also they will be awarded with a global mid-sized car.
[Incheon Nam-dong center Live]
After the amazing special stages,
now what is left to announce the results.
All we have left is to announce the winner of Kpop star season 5.
Will it be Ahn Ye-eun or Lee Soo-Jung?
As of right now with the judges' scores, there is only a difference of 3 points.
Okay.
How do you feel right now? Ye-eun?
Who do you think will win?
I think it'll obviously be Soo-Jung.
Why is that obvious?
You're leading by the judges' scores.
Really?
But she received a perfect score earlier.
And she did really well.
I loved that she did so well.
And you were even more proud because it was your song right?
Yes.
You could be proud as the song-writer.
To be honest after the 1st round, we were
worried that it might be an easy competition.
But then you received a perfect score.
Won't you win at this rate?
No.
I would want Ye-eun to win.
You think you'd win but you want Ye-eun to win?
Because she worked so hard and it was a song that she wrote herself.
And I just-
I see.
She's nervous and stuff so she's not able to finish her sentences.
As you can see, I have a pink envelope in my hand.
Inside of this envelope will be written either Ahn Ye-eun or Lee Soo-Jung.
I will represent all the participants who worked so hard and announce the winner.
Okay.
You two are so close and you're holding hands right now.
But I don't know what they're thinking inside.
The results are out and the die is cast.
I will announce today's final winner now.
[Who is the winner of Kpop star season 5?]
Okay. This is live.
I will open this envelope in front of you guys.
The final winner of the Kpop star season 5.
Everyone. Who do you think it is?
I hear Lee Soo-Jung and Ahn Ye-eun.
Alright.
Who's name will be written inside of this envelope?
Ahn Ye-eun first received a very high score from the first round
and everyone thought that today's winner will be Ahn Ye-eun.
But-
Lee Soo-Jung, during the song change round,
received a perfect score of 300.
Everyone was surprised.
I imagine that viewers votes would have flooded in as well.
We cannot predict the results at all.
I will announce it right now.
I will open this envelope right now in front of you guys.
Okay. Everyone.
I saw the name.
In the nation of Korea, I'm the only one who knows.
I am the only one who knows who the winner of Kpop star season 5 is.
You two must be nervous.
I'll announce it!
Everyone! The winner of Kpop star season 5!
Who is it?
I'll announce it.
The first letter
of this person's name
has an O sound.
Okay!
I'll announce it!
The final winner of Kpop star season 5 is!
Everyone!
It's incredible!
Lee Soo-Jung!
[Lee Soo-Jung wins!]
Lee Soo-Jung is the final winner.
Season 5's participants are all out congratulating her.
Ye-eun is giving her a hug as if she's won and is happy for her.
Soo-Jung please tell us how you feel.
Did you think you'd win?
Yes.
You predicted it?
How do you feel right now?
I feel great.
And
I'm really thankful.
Writers, producers,
and the judges.
Thank you guys.
I'm happy that I met many good friends from Kpop.
I will work hard.
Alright.
Ahn Ye-eun won 2nd place.
Ye-eun please tell us how you feel.
You were very close.
You won second place but that's still amazing.
Thank you.
I'm honored to just be standing here.
I'm really thankful to the judges.
It was great that I was able to let you guys hear my songs.
Thank you those of you who cheered me on. Thank you.
I'm thankful that I got to meet good friends.
I'm really really thankful that Soo-Jung sang my song so amazingly.
This was such a valuable experience.
Thank you.
Everyone this is not the end.
The winner has been decided between the two.
It is now time to decide who will win from those 3.
The winner Lee Soo-Jung.
Which company out of JYP, YG, and Antenna did she choose?
We'll reveal Lee Soo-jung's choice right this moment.
I said some harsh things relatively.
[Being flooded with regrets]
I intend to make it up to them.
I think it'll be better for me to point out the negatives of the other companies.
It's obvious that Antenna is a very good company.
They just don't have much experience in producing.
And for JYP,
he has a new song coming out again, so he's very busy himself.
YG has many employees
one might be able to debut a little faster.
I have one expectation.
The 3 weeks of training we had.
Would she have forgotten that?
We don't know how to make a star.
But we're a company who knows how to do music for a long time.
If you'd like to have the musician career for your life,
please choose Antenna.
[Which company will the final winner choose?]
[Winner's final choice]
Now it is time for Soo-Jung to choose the company she'd like to go to.
Starting from Park Jin-young please give a short shpiel.
I-
won't say anything else.
I will write you a really good song that you can lose your mind and sing.
If you come to my company, -You'll write her a song!
I think that's the best thing I could tell you.
You said you'd make it short.
Mr. Yang?
Make it short and sweet please.
I did not predict this
so I am nervous.
Are you saying that you didn't know she'd win?
No. That's not what I mean.
Before we came up here we talked about who Soo-Jung will choose
all of us said that we had no idea.
I'm already nervous that I might be the one chosen.
Alright.
Mr. Yoo?
Short and sweet please.
I'll make it short.
I'm going to find you.
Will that work against him? Or will it work?
Soo-Jung. I heard that you kept changing your mind in terms of the company you want.
Have you made up your mind?
Yes.
What was your criteria for choosing this company?
The company I chose is
Yes.
Okay.
She's not perfectly fluent in Korean. That's okay.
We'll hear from the final winner which company she has chosen!
Yang Hyun-suk's YG?
Or Park Jin-young's JYP?
Yoo Hee-yeol's Antenna?
Who does the final winner Lee Soo-Jung choose?
Which one is it?
She changed her mind a couple of times.
The three of them are hopeful.
Your choice is?
It's Antenna.
Antenna Music!
It's Yoo Hee-yeol!
Please come out! Yoo Hee-yeol!
Congratulations.
Lee Soo-Jung chose Antenna music.
Come out please.
Alright.
The judges are sharing the joy.
Two of you come out too please.
Antenna music's Yoo Hee-yeol.
Great.
Soo-Jung. Can you tell us why you chose Antenna music?
I worked with him.
It was really nice.
I would like to work next to a genius.
Because he's a genius.
Please tell us how you feel Mr. Yoo.
It's my first time.
In my participation with Kpop star.
From now on, with a heart of a father, like a parent,
I'll be responsible for her for the rest of my life.
Please sing us the song you were singing earlier.
Can you be quiet?
I see.
I think it'll be a good home for her.
Soo-Jung will now find a new home at Antenna music now and develop into a singer.
Please cheer her on.
We'll end Kpop star season 5 here.
Thank you for everyone who followed us along to the birth of a new Kpop star.
Thank you everyone who's watched us thus far.
We'll come back soon.
Goodbye everyone! Thank you!