- Have you fallen asleep?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I think you must be in love or something.
Why does the old bitch pick on me?
That's the second time this week. I nearly
told her what she could do with the job.
Hey, you asleep?
That's what I asked her.
She wants me to stay till 7:00 again.
What polish are you putting on?
- The usual one, madame.
- Oh, I'm fed up with it.
I feel like a change.
- Uh, give me Revlon's Fire and Ice.
- Oh, I'll go and get it.
Madame Denise?
Madame Denise,
Mrs. Rendlesham wants Revlon Fire and Ice.
I don't think there's any left.
Put this on.
She'll never know the difference.
Hello, darling.
How about a bit of the other, then?
You can't eat stuff like this.
Come on.
I'll take you to Wheeler's. Okay?
I have to get back.
Oh, we can have a...
we can have a quick meal.
Come on.
I can't. I'll be late.
Well, just... just one thing.
No?
I can't.
Well, good-bye.
Well, just a -just a minute.
What about tonight?
I'm sorry, but I'm busy tonight.
You really make me feel wanted.
Who's the lucky boy?
I'm having dinner with my sister.
Is she a good cook?
I don't know. I never thought about it.
Well, at least it can't be
any worse than fish and chips.
I think we are having rabbit.
Rabbit? Oh.
I thought they'd all been killed off.
- No. She has a friend...
- A rabbit?
No, I think the friend has rabbits.
Poor bunny.
Well, what about tomorrow?
- Tomorrow?
- Yeah. Let's have dinner tomorrow.
I'll meet you at the Hoop and Toy.
You know, the pub along there.
About, uh, 7:00?
- Hello.
Come along, boy. Walkies. Walkies.
Walkies.
Have a good day?
- Darling?
- Yes.
- How was work?
- All right.
It's close today.
- Are you still going away?
- Oh, darling, please don't start that again.
- How long are you going for?
- I've told you.
- Fortnight?
- Mind.
How long?
Ten or 12 days.
No more than that?
I heard such a funny story
on the news this evening.
Does he have to leave his things
in the bathroom?
The minister of health...
What's his name?
He found eels coming out of his sink.
It was on the television.
Even the announcer was laughing.
Why does he put his toothbrush in my glass?
Carol, please.
We must get this crack mended.
What?
- Hello.
You're early.
I didn't expect you for hours.
I couldn't live without you
for another minute.
Idiot. Anyway, you said 8:30.
I haven't even started yet.
There's a marvelous story
in this evening's paper.
- It takes at least one hour.
- Huh?
Your rabbit. I'm cooking it.
Look. "Bring to the boil. Skim and allow to
simmer slowly for one and a half hours."
Yes. Well, we'll eat out tonight.
I'll take you out.
Here. Look. Read that.
Oh, I know that.
I saw it on television.
That bloody bell.
Eels.
Pity it wasn't lobster though.
You never give me a chance
to show you what a good cook I am.
Well, you can tell me over dinner.
You'd think they'd have something better to
do than clang away like that all the time.
Hmm. It's worse when they start
doing it at midnight.
I wonder what they ring it for anyway.
Perhaps they have wild parties.
Maybe they'll invite me sometime.
Go and put your best bib and tucker on.
I feel like a spree.
Ah.
The beautiful younger sister.
Comment ça va?
I thought you were eating in.
Aren't you going to have dinner?
Yes. I'm going to have dinner.
- But not here.
- No.
Not here.
Pass me that brush, will you?
There's a love.
Just because I go out once,
there's no need to start sulking.
- I'm not sulking.
- Hmm. Well, you're not exactly smiling.
Come on. You're not going in
for the Miss World competition.
Will we go and see
the Leaning Tower of Pisa?
I don't think Cinderella likes me.
- Cinderella?
- The little sister.
Ah, don't be silly.
Well, are we going to see
the Leaning Tower of Pisa?
She's a bit strung-up, isn't she?
She's just sensitive. That's all.
You can say that again.
She should see a doctor.
- What do you mean?
- Nothing, nothing, nothing.
- No. You tell me what you meant by that.
- Nothing. Let's forget it.
You want to see the Leaning Tower of Pisa,
we'll see the bloody thing. Now let's relax.
- We're going to dinner, aren't we?
- Don't always change the subject when you start talking like that. You hear?
Come along, boy. Din-din.
Time for din-din.
Come along, boy. Lovely din-din.
Oh, come -.
Oh!
Mmm.
I'm sorry.
Oh, look. I've got to run.
I've left something at the flat.
Well, aren't you going to drop me off?
I've got no time.
Mmm. That's bloody hot.
No, you -you'll have to take a cab.
Uh, here.
Oh, here. Are you...
Am I gonna see you tonight?
Um...
I-I'll ring you, hmm?
I'll ring you.
Hello, darling.
How did you sleep?
All right.
Is he going to stay here every night?
I really don't think it's
any concern of yours.
He's married though.
Darling, it's my affair.
We all have to lead
our own lives in the end, you know.
Well, just don't stand around like that.
Go and answer the phone.
Can't you see I'm busy?
- Hello?
- Miss Ledoux?
Yes.
How much longer are you going to
keep me waiting for the rent?
Oh. You want my sister.
- Ah. I suppose she's out.
- No, no. She's here.
Just a moment.
- Who is it?
- The landlord.
Oh, damn. He would ring up today.
- Hello, yes?
- Miss Ledoux?
- Look. I'm terribly sorry...
- I bet you are.
- Now look. How much longer are you going to keep me waiting?
- I promise -.
- I've had your promises before.
- I promise you'll have the money tomorrow.
That's what you said a fortnight ago.
You'll have the money
tomorrow without fail.
- Look. If you're not going to play fair by...
- My sister will bring it round to you.
- Not you?
- N-No.
I'm going away on holiday.
Now look, Miss Ledoux.
This time I've had just about...
She'll bring it round to you tomorrow.
I promise.
She better, Miss Ledoux.
That's all I can say.
Just the sound
of his voice makes my flesh creep.
Money, money, money.
That's all he ever thinks about.
Good heavens.
I shall be late again.
- Is Bridget about?
- Oh, she's downstairs.
Oh.
Bridget.
What's the matter?
- Nothing.
- Tell me.
Nothing.
Just bloody men.
Promise you the earth, and then...
- Oh, I could cut my throat.
- Don't talk like that.
I thought this one was different.
- Did he...
- Oh, he was a pig. Forget him.
Oh. Look at my eyes.
Will Miss Bridget please come to the salon.
Mrs. Prendergast has arrived.
I'll tell you the sordid details later.
Oh, why are they so filthy?
Don't be upset.
Will Miss Bridget
please come to the salon right away.
- Cheerio then.
- See you later.
- You're joking.
- No. You should have seen them.
They went for each other like those
women wrestlers in Hamburg.
One, a big lady with bloody great charlies,
tried to claw the other girl's face.
Got her fist right down her throat.
Two pints of bitter, please.
- Two pints, sir?
- Lesbians?
No, no. They both fancied the same bloke.
I should have his luck.
And then they started in with their teeth,
rolling about on the floor.
It was like a madhouse. And I was
the only mug who tried to prevent them.
I ought to have my head examined.
I wouldn't have minded seeing it.
Feel free, anytime.
- I ended up -
- Thank you.
My coat torn,
my shirt covered with blood.
If you like that sort of thing,
I'll introduce you to my cousin.
- She's a black belt.
- Black belt?
How did you get on?
- What?
- What's your cousin like?
- Well, how did you get on with Little Miss Muffet?
- She sounds fun.
- When?
- Well, I thought you were taking her out to dinner.
Your cousin - what's she like?
Is that the right time?
- No, sir.
- Oh, come on. Fill us in with the gripping details.
The gripping details are
that she had dinner with her sister.
Well, maybe you should try the sister.
Are you playing hard to get?
I've been waiting over an hour.
Wh... What for?
Well, not for Christmas.
We made a date. Remember?
We're having supper tonight.
Oh, I forgot.
Oh.
Well, next time you forget,
maybe you'll let me know.
It's not that, but...
Are you all right?
You look...
I don't know.
You look sort of-sort of funny.
I don't feel...
I mean, I don't know.
Oh, well, anyway, come on. Now I've found
you, let's - let's go and eat something.
- I'm starving.
- But it's too late.
Look. Have... Have you been
fired or something?
All right. Come on.
I'll take you home. Come on.
Listen, Carol. I - I...
- I don't -
- Clumsy bitch!
For heaven's sake.
Carol!
Dean doing a little
illegal bit outside the ring...
but a neat head butt there by Larsen...
and over to the corner
with Ray Hunter coming in.
Finally Rebel Ray Hunter comes in
after Stedman the giant.
And Hunter turning Stedman
all over the place now, but he...
still exchanged places with Larsen.
And Larsen again for Hunter. And now
it's Hunter in again against Stedman.
Hunter really throwing Stedman around.
I don't know why he goes out.
And it's Larsen in again. Larsen comes in
with a twopenny drop. He's gonna need one.
Stedman almost into the ropes there.
Darling.
What is it?
Don't you feel well?
Oh, I know you don't
want me to go away, but...
Hello?
But the first point to Hunter and Larsen.
Fourteen and a half minutes gone.
Mmm.
Why'd you throw Michael's things away?
- Why'd you do it?
- I don't like them there.
It's got absolutely nothing to do with you.
You silly little fool.
I've put the money for the rent
on the table.
Oh, please. Don't go.
Now, please,
don't forget to give the money...
otherwise we shall both
be out onto the street.
- Look. Are you coming, or aren't you?
- Yes, yes. I'm coming.
Don't look so sad.
The time will pass very quickly.
Don't do anything I wouldn't do.
Go on.
Oh!
- You're killing me!
- Sorry, Miss Balch.
- There's only -
- Good morning.
Good morning.
There's only one way to deal with men.
That's treat them as though
you don't give a damn about them.
I've told you all this before.
Still, I'm glad to see
you have listened to me just this once.
There's only one thing they want,
and I'll never know...
why they make such a fuss about it,
but they do.
And the more you make them beg for it,
the happier they are.
- He rang me up this morning.
- I said he would.
- He was practically on his knees.
- Well, make sure he stays that way.
I wonder, I don't suppose it would
do me any harm if I had a little snack.
Well, what do you fancy?
They're all the same, just like children.
They want to be spanked, then given sweets.
Perhaps a...
little Danish pastry.
- Tsk, tsk.
- And a cup of chocolate.
Carol will order it for you.
Carol.
Stop dreaming.
Are you feeling all right, love?
Carol, what's the matter?
There's nothing you'd like to tell me?
I mean, uh...
How do you feel now?
Still biting your nails, eh?
I think you'd better go home. Would you
like one of the girls to go with you?
No, please. I'll be all right.
Take a taxi anyway.
Uh, ask Millie to give you the money.
Thank you.
Hello?
Hello, Carol?
It's-It's Colin. H-Hello?
Carol. Carol, it's me.
Carol. Please answer...
I'm running a business here, Carol,
not a rest home.
You can't just disappear for three days.
Are you sure - Well, I mean,
you're not in any trouble?
No, I'm not. I'm really...
But surely you could have phoned.
- Well, what is it?
- Mrs. Shaw-Taylor wants to see you.
All right.
I'll be with you in a minute.
Carol, I can't help you
if you won't tell me what's the matter.
Oh... Well...
Well, one of my aunts
came to stay very suddenly.
Oh. I was back at work two days
after I had my first baby.
If you're going to vanish
every time a relative appears...
we might just as well
put up the shutters.
I'd better go and see
what that old bitch wants.
Now, you go back to your work.
I'll talk to you later.
And, Carol?
Do something about your hair.
Yes, madame.
- Oh, my God. Look, look.
- It's nothing.
Out.
I should have your luck,
getting off early.
Come on. Cheer up.
Don't look so mis.
You know, you really don't look well.
- Is it a man?
- A man?
Well, I thought that maybe that smooth boy.
What's his name? Was making you unhappy.
You know, the one I've seen you with.
Are you in love with him?
I'm not in love with anyone.
Well, what were you up to
for the last three days?
Nothing. I stayed at home.
Oh, well. That's enough
to drive anyone up the wall.
You ought to go out,
go to a movie or something.
- Oh, I'd love to.
- That's it then. Do it.
We saw such a funny Chaplin film
at the Classic the other night.
What was it called?
I thought I'd die laughing.
He was so hungry,
he wanted to eat his shoe.
- No.
- Yes.
He pretended the laces were spaghetti.
There was this huge, great big fat man
who wanted to eat him.
- What? Him?
- Yes.
He wanted to eat Charlie Chaplin.
He thought Charlie was a chicken.
- Chicken?
- Yes.
And the chicken walked like Chaplin too.
You know.
Roger laughed so much,
I was quite ashamed of him.
You ought to see it though
to cheer you up.
Still keeping her legs crossed?
She's getting you down, you know.
The old, old story -
"Not before we're married, darling."
I wouldn't waste your money.
She seems a dead loss to me.
I mean, don't let her
being foreign fool you.
They're all the same, these bloody virgins.
They're just teasers, that's all.
She seems to have old Colin
nicely steamed up though.
She gets a big thrill out of it.
You tell her. She'll soon strip off.
- When I want your advice, I'll ask for it.
- Ah.
I do believe the old lad's in love.
- What about that then?
- Another good man gone.
I think your friends
are going to have to help you.
Why don't you, um, take her over
to Reggie's pad one evening?
Here. Steady on, John.
Oh, Reggie will lay something on.
Won't you, Reggie?
Or on something.
I can see the scene now.
Sweet music, soft lights, a big jug of iced
gin with, um, orange or lemon on top of it.
- Oranges.
- Why, tell her it's a fruit cup...
and three of the most eligible
bachelors in London.
Here. I'm getting excited already.
By the end of the evening,
she'll be begging for it.
- You'll soon be able to stop twitching.
- She'll weep with gratitude.
Yeah. Maybe we will too.
- Maybe you want your face pushed in.
- Here. Take your hands off me.
Colin, for heaven's sake.
Relax. Take a joke.
Hit me or something.
Now, look, boy. You've got it bad. Look.
You see?
He's been in the sun too long.
Look, it was only a joke.
There's no need to bloody bust out going on
like Cassius Clay all over the place.
- A joke, boy. Joke.
- Fellas, fellas, please.
If you go on like this,
you will be old before your time.
Look, relax, take it easy, enjoy life.
There's somebody there.
I can see your shadow.
What's the matter?
I just want to talk to you, that's all.
Carol!
If you don't open the door,
I'll bloody well break it down!
- No!
- What?
I'm sorry.
It's all so sordid.
What's - What's the matter?
I'm sorry. I just...
Well, I had to see you, that's all.
Honestly, it's been so -
so miserable without you.
I phoned and phoned.
The ringing tone nearly drove me mad.
Is it, uh - Is it something I've done?
Carol.
Please.
Tell me.
I'm not really like this, you know.
Oh.
I wish I could find the
proper words to say.
They just keep going round and round
in my head.
I - I just...
I want to be - to be with you.
All the time.
Hello.
You filthy bitch.
I'm sorry. Who is this?
Who is this? Who is this?
Who do you think, you filthy little tart?
You think I don't know he's with you?
You think you're clever,
but you're not that clever, you filthy...
Come on! Open up this door.
Come on. Open up.
I know you're in there.
It's no use hiding.
Else I'll call the police.
Well!
Where's Miss Ledoux?
I am Miss Ledoux.
You don't look like her.
- I expect you want my sister.
- Expect?
I certainly do.
Where is she?
She's not - But I can explain.
Explain?
Well, I doubt that, my dear.
I can see it with my own eyes.
Now then, what's the idea
of barricading the door against me?
You're not only late with the rent...
but you're damaging the property.
I've got the rent here.
Let's have a little light on the subject.
No!
I'm not a bloody owl, you know.
Ah, I thought I'd seen everything.
This is a flaming nuthouse.
I don't know.
Uh, do you always, uh...
run around like, uh, this?
I mean to say, it's a bit, uh...
What's the matter?
You ill?
Ah.
The, uh, heat's getting you down, hmm?
Uh, I don't like it myself.
I'll, uh - I'll get you
a... a glass of water.
You're white as a sheet.
Hmm.
What the hell is this?
Oh. No wonder you look ill, if you
have things like this hanging around.
It's the dustbin for you, my lad.
Good Lord.
Beats me
how you young people live in such a mess.
It's like a pigsty. Huh.
Ah.
I know. Ah.
A nice, hot cup of tea
might be better, perhaps, hmm?
Of course, um,
your sister's gone away, hasn't she?
Yes, uh...
A nice, hot cup of tea and, uh...
and an aspirin...
and you'll be as right as rain.
You must be a bit lonely, I expect...
now she's gone.
Yes, I - I should have guessed it.
All alone, by the telephone.
There's, uh, no need to be alone, you know.
Huh?
Poor little girl.
All by herself.
All shaking
like a little frightened animal.
Oh. Ah.
Ah.
They're your family, hmm?
Very nice. Hmm.
Yeah. There's no need
to be frightened of me, you know.
Is that you?
Huh?
Where was it taken? In, uh - In London?
- Brussels.
- Ah.
Ah. Brussels. Hmm.
I could be a very good friend to you,
you know.
You... look after me...
and you can forget about the rent.
Come on. Come on. Just...
Just a little kiss between friends, huh?
Come on.
You go on up. I'll park the car.
Carol?
Carol! Are you in?
I say, what's the matter?
What a terrible smell.
What the hell's going on?
Well, get a grip of yourself, will you?
Now, what's the matter?
Ba - Bathroom.
No! Oh!
Go in there.
Just sit... sit there.
- Have you got a phone?
- Who are you?
I need to phone. I need to phone!
- Want a telephone?
- Yes, a telephone.
Oh.
Everything will be all right.
He's gone to the porter's room
to make a telephone call.
She doesn't speak English, does she?
Yes, I think she does.
What's the matter? What's happened?
I don't know. We just came in.
Let's see. Oh.
Oh.
Now, you better not touch her.
They've sent -.
- I won't forget tonight in a hurry.
- Now, come - Now, don't touch her.
I'll get her some brandy.
- Has anyone called for an ambulance?
- Yes. He's gone to telephone now.
- Who?
- Man we saw on the stairs.
- Ah.
- Can anyone do artificial respiration?
You shouldn't touch her.
You shouldn't move her.
- Oh, dear.
- I'll get her some brandy.
Somebody must help her.
Please, someone help her.
I wouldn't touch her. Don't touch her.
What's he doing?
- Oh.
- Good Lord.
- Oh, he's gotten her up.
- Please!
He shouldn't touch her.
© anoXmous
@ http://thepiratebay.sx/user/Zen_Bud