If I had a gun, I'd shoot a hole into the sun
And love would burn this city down for you
If I had the time, I'd stop the world and make you mine
And every day would stay the same with you
Ah...aha...ahaaa....
I'll give you back the dream, and show you now what might have been
If all the tears you cry would fade away
I'll be by your side when they come to say goodbye
And we will live to fight another day
Excuse me if I spoke too soon
My eyes have always followed you around the room
'Cause you're the only God that I'll ever need
I'm holding on, I'm waiting for the moment to find me
Ah...aha...ahaaa....
Hope I didn't speak too soon
My eyes have always followed you around the room
'Cause you're the only God that I'll ever need
I'm holding on, I'm waiting for the moment
for my heart to be unbroken by the seams
Ha...hahaha...ha..haaa.....
Let me fly you to the moon
My eyes have always followed you around the room
'Cause you're the only God that I'll ever need
I'm holding on, I'm waiting for the moment to find me
Ha...hahaha...ha..haaa.....
If I had a gun, I'd shoot a hole into the sun
And love would burn this city down for you