===@erysus===
You can't find the feeling
And all is the same
In the pouring rain, y'know, y'know
Coming out of the ceiling
Falling from above
Growing in and out of love
A broken heart is still beating
In and out of time
Hold your body next to mine, y'know, y'know
But you can't stop the bleeding
Sing to yourself and hold on
'Cos everybody's on the run
Everybody's on the run
Hang in there love, you gotta hold on
'Cos everybody's on the run
Everybody's on the run
You've been drifting and stealing
Trying to walk in my shoes
But they don't belong to you, no they don't
But you can't find the meaning
Sing to yourself and hold on
'Cos everybody's on the run
Everybody's on the run
Hang in there love, you gotta hold on
'Cos everybody's on the run
Everybody's on the run
===@erysus===
Hang in there love, you gotta hold on
You gotta be strong enough for love, y'know, y'know
'Cos everybody's on the run
Everybody's on the run
===@erysus===