Merry Christmas.
Rose?
Debbie Carmichael?
Rose Harrison?
Oh, my gosh.
I haven't seen you since-
High school, I'm sure.
How are ya?
Well, you know I married
Bobby Gidecki.
No.
Oh, my.
Four amazing kids.
Can you believe it?
But enough about me.
What about you?
Tell me everything.
I'm married.
Hal, he's a lawyer
down on Wall Street.
Two girls, twins.
Aw.
Yeah.
Britney and Ashley.
And in less than-
oh, my gosh-
seven hours,
I've got to have
Christmas Eve dinner
for 35 friends and family,
so I got to go.
Oh, 35.
Oh.
Yeah, well,
it was nice to see you.
We should... get together.
Absolutely.
We're listed.
We're the only Gidecki
in Hartford.
I bet.
Oh, incredible to see you.
Yeah.
All right, well, I got to go.
Would you like to share a cab?
No, no, no,
I'm just going down here.
Well, merry Christmas.
Same to you.
Unbelievable.
Hi, I was just wondering
what time your party started.
I beg your pardon.
You know, your Christmas party.
What time does that start?
This is an emergency room,
not Radio City Music Hall.
But you usually have
a Christmas party, don't you?
Usually.
Patients only, though.
You planning on being a patient?
You never know.
You look beautiful.
You really do.
Morning.
How ya doing?
Guess what I brought you.
All your favourites:
smoked salmon with capers
and Arugula salad
and a mousse cake for desert.
And what's the occasion,
you might ask yourself.
Well, I'll tell you.
Tomorrow's Christmas.
And that means
that we get to spend
the whole day together,
just the two of us.
How about that, huh, Mom?
Hm?
And you'll never guess
who I ran into.
Debbie Carmichael.
Yep, oh, Debbie Gidecki now.
She married Bobby.
Surprise, surprise.
They have four kids,
a house in Connecticut
just filled with oodles
of joy and happiness.
I could have smacked her.
Here, let's try some salmon.
Hm?
You love salmon, remember?
You know, you got to
keep your strength up, Mom.
That means eating.
You haven't eaten
anything since yesterday.
Let's give a little salmon
a little try.
You don't get any dessert
if you don't try your salmon.
Come on.
Okay.
All right, all right, all right.
Well, you know what?
We'll try again later, okay?
Look at this.
Look what I found:
an angel for your wreath.
How beautiful, huh?
Yep.
Oh.
Hello.
Oh, hi.
I didn't realize
anybody else was here.
Just me.
I'm sorry.
I just thought maybe
I'd cheer things up a little bit.
I felt bad 'cause he never
gets any visitors.
It seems so sad.
Except you, of course,
but I've never seen you before.
Not that you've never
been here before.
I'm sure you have;
it's just that I've...
never seen you before.
It's an angel.
Yes, and very beautiful,
a renaissance angel.
Thank you.
It's very kind.
Oh, well,
it's Christmas, you know.
Merry Christmas.
Well, got to get going.
Excuse me.
Morning, Rose.
Oh, Dr. Barrow.
Good to see you.
You too.
Have you been in
to see your mother?
Oh, yes, we had a nice,
long visit, and you?
I was just on my way in.
Feeling okay
this morning, I hope.
Oh, sure.
I mean, I know it looks bad,
single woman over 40
at Christmastime,
but I'll be fine.
Just keep me away
from the kitchen knives
and open windows
for the next few days.
You meant my mother, didn't you?
Yes.
Oops.
Okay, bye.
Hey.
Hey, listen.
Hey, what do you say
I give you a ride?
Come on, I'm a cop.
You can trust me.
This is where I'm having lunch.
Then let me
take you round the block.
I'll bring you right back
where I found you; I promise.
Oh, I've been around the block.
Ain't nothing
I haven't seen before.
Well, then marry me.
I'll take you anywhere
you want to go.
Don't tell me a man like you
isn't already married.
I've been holding out.
Oh, yeah?
For what?
For you.
Oh.
Okay. But let's make it fast.
I get bored easily,
and I only have
an hour for lunch.
Do you know how much I love you,
Ms. Nina Vasquez,
about to be Mrs. Riley?
No.
How much?
More than you ever know.
Enough to learn
how to dance with me?
Not right now.
Please.
You're gonna have to
dance with me at the wedding.
Morning.
Or should I say afternoon.
Did you type up
the Sulley/Seth revisions?
Yes, I put them on your desk.
Great.
And merry Christmas.
Ooh.
If you hate it,
you can return it.
I'm sure I'll love it.
I'm sure you'll return it.
Your sister called, and she can't
spend Christmas Eve
with you after all.
Seems it's too painful
since your father died,
so she's spending the next week
meditating with Buddhist monks
in the Catskills.
Good for her.
Also, your ex-husband called.
Wanted to know if you would like
to spend tonight with him
and his beautiful wife
and their two perfect kids
in Connecticut.
And... oh, finally,
your shrink called.
She's got to cancel
your session today
because her husband surprised her
with a fabulous trip
to Paris for Christmas.
That's... all?
It rang a couple more times,
but I was scared for you,
so I stopped answering it.
What's so funny?
Oh, it just struck me
as being funny
that a, you know, a woman
who's never had a child
is editing a children's book
when maybe
it would be more appropriate
for me to work on Cooking For One
or, you know,
How to Survive
the Holidays Alone.
Don't look at me that way.
I'm fine.
Do you want my advice?
No.
You've been looking
after your mother for...
nearly ten years now, right?
Yeah.
Before that,
you were looking after
your father
and also your husband,
who walked out on you
the day your mother
came to live with you,
and let's not forget-
What is the point?
It's time that you stop
taking care of everybody else
and start thinking
about yourself.
As my nana used to say,
what you need is-
I know; I know. Someone to
take care of me for a change.
Wrong, what you need is sex.
Good sex.
Your nana said that?
Yes, she did.
And by the way,
Marco has been
looking for you again.
Hm?
He is so tenacious.
That guy is sexy.
He's too young for me.
Every woman
in the building wants him.
Not me.
I just want some coffee.
Coffee it is.
Please, Rose,
sleep with him for me.
No.
You can tell me all the details.
I'll love it.
No.
Coffee.
Just get coffee.
Geez.
Okay, okay.
Nina, no.
No, I got to go.
I can't be late.
Listen, Dennis is waiting
for me, all right?
I got to go.
I can't be late.
I was beginning to worry.
Absent from work yesterday
and apparent
no-show today,
thought maybe
you'd run off to Tahiti
and gotten married on me.
I'd never do a thing like that
without checking with you first.
Of course.
So when are we going to dinner?
Don't you have deadlines
or something?
Hey, I got to eat.
Okay.
When?
Uh, well...
Tonight?
It's Christmas Eve,
so I figure you must have-
No, no, no, no.
Nothing.
Okay, let's do it.
Okay.
Tonight.
Yeah.
After work.
Yeah, it's a date.
Okay.
Those earrings new?
Yeah.
Cute, huh?
They were a gift.
From who?
Mr. Brenner.
Mr. Brenner?
Is that normal, lawyers giving gifts
to paralegals?
Uh-huh.
Mm-hm.
Don't start, Mike.
What?
You know,
some women would be flattered.
Of what, that the man
they were about to marry
was a jealous psycho?
Yeah.
See you at home tonight, okay?
Okay.
Hey, I love you.
Excuse me,
can I ask you for a Coke?
Sure thing.
So anyway, so my plan
is to spend Christmas
in the hospital.
I know that sounds strange.
I mean, the hospital's
probably the last place
anybody would want to be,
especially this time of year.
Thanks.
But see, the thing is,
see, out of all the Christmases
I've ever had,
the only one
that was halfway decent
was the Christmas where I was 14.
I busted my nose open
in this sledding accident.
They made me spend
the whole day at the hospital.
That's a shame.
No, but it wasn't.
That's what I'm trying
to tell you,
because they threw
this killer Christmas party
where the nurses
were dressed as elves,
and they were singing songs,
and they were handing out eggnog
with a little bit of booze in it,
and they even made
little presents,
which was really cool.
That was awesome.
That was the best time
I ever had.
I know.
What-
I...
I know.
I'm sorry.
You know what cup
of coffee this is?
Number four.
Where the hell you been?
Wedding plans, you know.
Just one cup, I promise,
and we're out of here.
What can I get you?
Just coffee.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
Just coffee,
and we're in a bit of a hurry.
Okay.
What was that all about?
I don't know.
Beats me.
You know the guy?
No, I never laid eyes
on him before.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Because he's looking at you
with that, you know, like...
it's, like, weird,
you know what I'm saying?
No, what are you saying?
Okay, here you go.
Here's your coffee.
I had a feeling
you'd want it black.
Right, black.
And I got you
almond butter cookies.
Almond butter cookies,
those are my favourite.
I know.
Ah, he's got a thing for ya.
Come on.
Cut it out.
Come on; his eyes
are all over you.
And that silly smile.
I know that smile. I've used it.
Ah, you're crazy. He's just one
of those real nice guys. You know.
He's like Greek or something.
They're always hugging and kissing.
- Or maybe, he seems kinda slow.
- No no, he's not slow Mikey.
I think the guy's got a
thing for two guys in uniform.
You know what I'm saying.
Two guys?
Nah, he was looking at me, not you.
Nah, he was looking at me too.
Nah, he wasn't looking
anywhere near you.
What are you saying
Mikey? Tha-that guys...
...don't notice me? Is
that what you're saying?
Tha-that I walk down the street and...
...guys don't turn their
head to take look at me?
No, I'm not saying that at all.
I just think the guy's interested
in me and not you.
Oh.
What am I saying?
Just... forget about it all right.
Fine he's all yours.
Come on. Stop it.
You two gonna go
furniture shopping together?
I said forget about it!
I'm gonna straighten this out
right now.
All right, Mikey.
All right. All right.
Calm down now.
Come on;
come on.
Now, you're a cop, for Christ sake.
Now cut it out.
Easy with that famous temper.
Come on now.
You're a cop, okay?
Your turkey club's up,
Artie.
You got my money?
Not yet.
Aw, come on, Jules, look,
if you want to meet Arizona,
I have to get paid first.
Look, you know
I'm good for it, right?
I just got to go do
this one thing,
so why don't you
tell me where to meet you,
and I'll bring you the money.
All right, look.
Meet me at the old theatre
on Avenue A
at about 10:00, all right?
But don't go in without me.
You wait for me.
Why?
Oh, you don't want
to surprise a guy
like Arizona;
that's why.
All right.
Well, Glen, you know
I really appreciate this, right?
It's Christmastime, man.
- Can we meet later?
- What?
I get off at 9. Can we get together?
I mean it's been so long.
- So long since what?
- Since you and I...
- What?
- Since you...
Now wait a minute, I don't know you.
Now you'd better cut this out...
- Mikey, Mikey, Mikey. Wait outside.
- Well you'd better straighten this out.
All right, all right, I'll handle it.
Wait outside, ok?
- Hey don't...
- Hey buddy, do you want to get locked up?
- No.
- Stop hassling my friend will you please?
You don't understand,
it's been such a long time...
Hey, hey, hey... enough! Ok?
You've got the wrong guy. Stop it!
Ok?!
He never has any visitors,
not even family.
Oh, except for this one guy
that was there this morning,
but I've never seen him before,
and I just-
I don't know.
I wish there was something
I could do, you know.
To be sick and alone
and during the holidays,
it's awful.
You know, that's what
I like about you, Rose.
- What?
- You care about other people.
You know, I have to say
that I-
I'm...
Well, I just don't feel
like I'm really your type.
I think you should
let me decide that.
I'm a little uncomfortable
with you, Marco, sometimes.
Let's just relax
and have fun, Rose.
Okay.
Good, because that's all
I really want to do...
...is just have some fun.
- Hey, me too.
Didn't I tell you?
Best pizza in the city.
Mm, mm.
It's very good.
This place has been here forever.
On the weekends,
there's a line around the block.
Why don't you have a girlfriend?
Or do you have a girlfriend?
Well, I did,
but we broke up a few months ago.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Don't be.
It was good that it happened.
Why was it good that it happened?
Ooh, hold it.
What?
Cheese.
Cheese?
Yeah, on the side of your mouth.
Oh, God.
No, let me do it.
So now that I've saved you
from Tony's pizza-
what shall we do now?
Um...
You want to see a movie?
No, not really.
Want to walk somewhere?
Yeah, but it's getting cold.
Don't you live around here?
Yes.
Well, we could, uh,
go back to your place,
maybe have a nightcap.
Um...
Marco, I-I...
Rose, we work together
in the same building.
What's the big deal?
You know me,
and it's Christmas Eve.
I don't have any...
real liquor.
I just have eggnog.
No, I love eggnog.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Do you have family in the city?
No.
My family's all down in Florida,
so it's just me here.
Great place.
You live here all by yourself?
It's my mother's house.
Well, here we are.
I'll get the eggnog.
You know, Rose.
I find you very sexy.
Thank you.
I'm gonna get the nog.
You're not attracted to me?
No, um...
I'm attracted to you.
But this, you know,
it's going a little fast for me.
Okay.
Let's just start with a kiss.
All you have to do is say stop,
and I promise I will.
Okay.
You promise?
Yes.
Okay, stop.
All right,
that was a little quick.
Yeah, I know it was,
but I'm-I...
How long has it been, Rose?
What?
How long it's been
since you've been on a date.
Um...
You're a very beautiful woman.
You should be with someone.
Someone like me.
You know, you work all the time.
I never see you go out, you know.
You got to live a little.
Life ain't that bad, Rose.
You just got to lighten up.
Relax.
Oh, gosh, I just, uh...
It's just not working for me.
What did I say?
Someone tells me
to lighten up and relax,
I just tighten up and get tense.
Hey, I just thought
we could have a good time.
Yeah, me too, but...
I was just trying
to make you feel better.
I know;
I know.
It didn't, though.
I see.
I guess I better go.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, I'm sorry.
I was too forward.
I was wrong.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not you.
It's me.
You're right, Rose.
It is you.
Merry Christmas, Rose.
Merry Christmas.
Yeah.
Hey, you okay?
My stomach is a little nauseous.
I think I'm just stressed out.
Nina, can you please just relax?
Look, it's the glam rock look.
Hey.
What are you doing home so early?
You must be Mike.
Surprise.
What are you doing?
This was for you, you idiot.
He hit my lip.
What's going on
with this guy, Nina?
You can clean up here.
What the hell is he doing
in the apartment?
You have a serious problem.
Oh, I got a problem?
What's he doing in the apartment?
Are you insane?
Who is that guy, Nina?
This guy's my friend!
He was helping me
to prepare a surprise for you.
What kind of surprise?
He's a tree decorator!
All right, look,
I'm sorry, all right?
I made a mistake.
You know what?
You always make a mistake.
Last week, you started
a fight on the street
because you thought a guy
was looking at me.
He was looking-
So what!
Men look at me.
Get over it.
All right, look,
I'm sorry, all right?
It was just a misunderstanding.
It's just driving me crazy.
I saw the two of you
talking today-
Talking when?
When I dropped you off
at work today.
I dropped you off at the office,
and I saw you guys.
Do you spy on me?
No, I don't spy on you.
Listen to me.
I just-I saw
the two of you talking, okay?
And then the next thing I know,
you're hugging and kissing
on each other...
It was innocent, all right,
believe me, completely.
She was thanking me.
Thanking you for what?
This is insane.
Look, I can clear everything up.
Oh, that's not the point.
I'm gay.
All right?
Nina, look, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Mr. Calvert.
Mr. Calvert!
Mr. Calvert,
your rent is due.
I evict you if I have to.
I evict you!
Yeah, but she told me
she was gonna stay with you.
I don't know.
Yeah, I don't know.
Look, uh...
Look, just tell her
I called, okay?
And tell her I love her.
And, uh...
Tell her I'm sorry.
Bye.
What the hell are you doing here?
I need to see you.
I have to talk to you.
Look, pal, you picked
a bad day to mess with me.
Now, you obviously
got me mixed up
with somebody else.
I just need
ten minutes of your time.
I'm not gonna give you
ten seconds.
You beat it.
- Ten minutes, that's all I ask.
I'll explain everything to you,
and then I won't
bother you anymore.
Look, it's Christmas Eve,
all right?
Don't you have someplace to be,
family waiting
for you or something?
What do you want from me?
Ten minutes.
Please.
All right, come on.
Ten minutes.
Let's go quick.
This is for you.
It's not much.
Just something I wanted to...
It's a little, uh...
Thanks.
Take a seat.
Could I have
something warm to drink?
Yeah, you want some coffee?
Yeah, that would be
very kind of you.
Thanks.
Listen,
I didn't mean
to frighten you before.
I hope I didn't.
It's just I was afraid
I was never gonna see you again.
Look, you know, it's obvious
you got me mixed up
with somebody else.
I'm just trying to figure out
what's going on here.
Nothing person, uh, Mister...
Artie.
Mm.
Almond butter cookies.
Your favourite, right?
Right.
May I have one?
Yeah, sure.
Emilio, ven.
Ayuda, ayuda.
Oh.
So heavy.
Thank you.
Hello, familia.
Tengo hambre.
Are you all right?
Mm-hm.
I might be pregnant.
Oh.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
But actually,
I just left my fiancé
who I am supposed to marry
in one week
and who I love very, very much
but who is a jealous psychopath
who thinks that every guy
wants to sleep with me
and who drives me crazy.
You must think
I'm some crazy person,
blurting all this out.
Oh, no, no.
Not at all.
You know, because I'm
a blurter myself.
Sometimes, you know,
you just have to
get it out
so that you can figure out
what to do.
Thank you.
I'm Nina, by the way.
Nice to meet you.
Rose.
Uncle Pedro's friend
from Pittsburgh, right?
Dinner's ready.
Let's go inside.
Do I look like I've been crying?
No, no, no, you look beautiful.
I really-
I can't-
Let's go have some fun.
I have to go.
I really-
Nina, por favor.
I could use a hand inside.
Come on.
Oh, please...
Thank you.
Cariño,
pasamé ese plato.
Maria, come on.
Everyone's at the table.
Um, maybe there's somewhere
I could use the bathroom?
Oh, yeah, right behind you.
Thanks.
Thank you.
A ver, venga.
A comer.
Why not?
Yeah, okay.
¿No es ella?
Wait, Rose.
Rose, wait.
Oh, I'm so sorry, really.
That was so stupid.
Stay with us please.
Please stay with us.
- Tell your-
- Please come back inside.
- Tell your family I am so sorry.
- Sorry for what?
For crashing
your Christmas dinner.
For trespassing.
For breaking and entering.
For being just...
crazy.
Please come back inside.
We'll make room.
- That is so sweet, but I am...
- Please.
I don't... I don't fit in.
Me neither.
Not tonight.
I know a place around the corner.
Maybe we can go there and talk.
They're gonna miss you.
Yeah.
I'll come back.
Okay?
You're crazier than I am.
Come on, it's freezing.
It's so cold.
I know he loves me,
and he's a great guy
with a huge heart.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't be with him,
but he's just so-
Controlling?
Yes, controlling.
He doesn't have faith
in what we have,
how we feel.
He won't trust it.
I mean, I find myself praying
that he will change,
but I don't know anymore.
I mean, we're supposed
to get married in one week.
This is it.
This is forever.
And I can't live like this.
But I can't picture my life
without him either.
You love him very much.
Yeah, so much.
We even decided
that we were gonna try
to have a baby
since we just got the apartment.
We both want a baby very badly.
Even though it's a long shot.
I thought you were pregnant.
Yeah.
To tell you the truth,
I'm not sure.
Well, then you have
to take a test and find out.
Doctors have always told me
that I have a very low chance
of getting pregnant,
and I thought I was
a few times before,
and then I wasn't,
so I don't want to take
another test
and be disappointed again.
Besides, I know I'm just nauseous
from all the stress
of everything going on.
Excuse me,
ladies and gentlemen.
We're having
a little impromptu contest.
Winner takes home
the stunning Christmas tree
on my piano.
Just step up to the mic
and tell us
why you hate Christmas.
Best reason wins.
All those interested, follow me.
Look, all I know is that, um...
nobody's perfect,
and if you find love,
I mean real love,
you just don't throw it away
without a hell of a fight.
Yeah.
Yes.
My wife used to do that
with her coffee.
It was her one vice,
if you can call it that.
It was more like
a simple pleasure, really,
just to put a little brandy
in her evening coffee,
and B&B, just the way you do it.
Who are you?
Look, you've been
very, very kind to me,
and I owe you an explanation.
It's just very hard for me
to get the words out.
What I would like...
Anybody home?
Oh, he's home.
Ho ho ho.
Merry Christmas, Mikey.
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
I come to cheer you up, man.
Look, this is Holly and Mary.
Mikey, get it?
Holly and Mary.
Come on, Christmas.
Dennis, I'm not sure
this is such
a good time right now.
Yeah, the girl's room
is right around the corner here.
Okay, okay, we're going.
Look what I brought you.
Yeah, but, Dennis-
Mike, I get the redhead, okay?
What's going on here, Mikey?
That's the guy from the diner.
What's he doing here?
I'm trying to get
to the bottom of this thing.
You invited him to your apartment.
Mikey, what are you thinking?
He could be some sort of psycho.
He's not a psycho.
Little strange maybe,
but he's sweet.
Sweet?
Mike, is there something
you want to tell me?
What are you talking about?
I'm just trying to figure out
what's going on with this guy.
I'm your partner.
You could tell me anything.
Dennis, you got to get them
out of here.
Girls, Dennis,
I really appreciate
you coming by
and your concern and everything.
Mike, I don't trust
this guy, okay?
I'm on my cell if you need me.
Nah, I'll be all right.
Mike, I'm on my cell, okay?
I'll be fine.
What?
I find that I'm very
attracted to you.
Oh, wait a minute.
- I'm not gay.
- I'm not gay either.
- I like women.
- I love women.
- No, I mean I really like women.
- I love women too.
And I'm getting married.
I'm getting married really soon
to a really great woman
that I love very much.
I was married once
to a woman that I really loved,
and that woman was you.
Excuse me?
Do you believe in reincarnation?
How could you not?
When I looked at you
and you looked at me,
I knew it was she.
I knew it was my Angeline,
my wife.
All right, that's it.
You're out of here.
No, you're out of here!
You're my wife.
Stay away from me!
Please, don't do this to me.
Come on in, baby.
- The car's warm.
- It's freezing.
What's the matter, Dennis?
You're no fun tonight.
Give me one second, all right?
I don't trust this guy
with my partner.
Something's wrong.
Oh, nothing's wrong.
Give me a minute.
Come on, Dennis.
Son of a bitch.
I knew it.
No, no, Dennis.
My goodness, look at...
All right, listen,
I got to straighten this guy out.
I got to.
What I do for my friends, my God.
All right, just-
I got to.
All right, listen,
I got to straighten this guy out.
Just stay here.
Stay in the car.
Oh, come on.
Dennis, wait in the car?
Nina.
What's the matter?
I really love you.
But your jealousy is killing me.
You hold on so tight.
I can't breathe.
That's because
I love you so much, though.
Too much.
Come on, that's crazy.
No, it's not.
You have to let go, Mike.
If we're gonna make it,
then you have to let go a little.
I do have another life,
a career,
a job where I have to
talk to men.
There's nothing
the matter with that.
Yeah, but all these guys want
is to take you to bed.
So some of them try.
So what?
You have to trust me.
Who?
Who what?
What guys try?
No.
No, are they friends of mine?
Do I know these guys? I didn't say that.
No, are they guys from your work?
Did I ever meet them?
Mike, did you hear
a word that I said?
What guys?
Who are they?
Why the hell did I come here?
Come on.
Listen to me.
I don't want to talk to you.
Now you're starting to scare me.
You're gonna have to talk to me.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't listening.
Mikey, your friend here's
waiting in the doorway hiding.
I wasn't hiding.
I wanted to be near you.
I thought you might
come down again.
Not now, Artie.
Nina, please.
Come on.
Don't leave.
Get in the car.
This is all your fault.
Why do you keep doing this to me?
You're my life.
You stay away from me.
I'm warning you.
Stay away from me!
You understand me?
Shit.
Mikey, what'd you do?
I didn't do anything.
Get an ambulance.
And our last contestant,
Ms. Rose Harrison.
All right, let's see.
I hate Christmas because, uh...
Well, you know, actually,
I don't completely
hate Christmas.
I, um...
There's... quite frankly,
a lot of things
I love about Christmas:
those little
dome things that you shake-
Right, okay, sorry.
Um...
Okay, I got pregnant
the summer that I turned 25,
and it wasn't something
that my husband and I
really planned, but, you know,
we always wanted kids,
so we were thrilled.
And we found out we were
gonna have a little girl
and we painted the room pink
with little bunnies and all that.
And we named her
after our maternal grandparents,
Olivia May.
And the pregnancy was great,
and the delivery was great,
and when she came out of me,
she looked perfect.
She had just these little tiny,
tiny little fingers, all of them
and little toes,
and she was blonde.
And you know, I don't know
what colour eyes she had
because, um, well, I never...
um, I never saw her eyes...
because she, um... well, she...
her heart stopped.
It just stopped, and they told us
that it was defective.
And I tried to get pregnant
again after that,
and it didn't happen.
And so I guess that's why
I hate Christmas sometimes
when I think of Olivia May.
That's a sad story, lady,
but what's that got to do
with Christmas?
Oh, right.
She, um...
Olivia May was born...
... died on Christmas Day.
Don't you die
on me, Artie.
A woman in the Bronx
killed her husband
and then turned the gun
on herself.
The woman left a note
by the scene
saying just one line:
"This is something
I just wanted to do for myself. "
On the house, lady.
We'll have details
on this controversial new diet
coming up when we return.
So where the hell
does this guy live?
Arizona?
He lives wherever he can.
He's a squatter.
Moves around a lot.
Don't worry;
you'll see what I mean.
I don't know
if I like this, Glen.
Just got to trust me
on this one, all right?
This guy will take care of you.
Well, what if I change my mind?
Well I don't give a shit what you do,
I got my money.
Who's that?
It's Glen.
Glen, welcome.
- I got somebody here to see you.
- Well, come on down and bring him over.
- All right, you go and I'll wait here.
- You're not gonna go with me?
It's cool.
Don't worry about it.
Hi.
So what can I do for you, son?
Well, Glen said that, um...
Glen said what?
Glen said that you break hands.
Yes.
That's absolutely right.
And whose hands
are we talking about?
Mine.
Oh, sheez.
I'm s-oh, oh.
I'm sorry.
I'm so-
my fault.
Everything okay?
I'm fine.
Just maybe a few too many
Christmas parties, but...
You meant me, didn't you?
Right.
I was just checking.
Um...
So how's Helen?
Well, her blood pressure's
still a little high,
but it's much improved
since this morning.
- Good.
- But she's still not eating.
And I'm very concerned
about that.
If she doesn't eat
something tonight,
we're gonna have to
insert a feeding tube.
Oh, don't worry about that.
She's gonna eat tonight
because mother and
I have big plans,
don't we?
Mother and I, we're
going to sing some carols
and eat some cake
and sip some nog
and light the
Christmas tree.
Sounds fun.
It does sound like
fun, doesn't it?
What do you
think mom?
Do ya think it's
going to be fun?
I think so.
Aww, look at her.
How beautiful she was, hm?
- She still is.
- Hm.
And me, I was such
a timid little kid.
My first day
at kindergarten,
I got one look
at the Nuns
and I just wouldn't
go in.
And mum here
she took my
hand and
brought me inside and
said she would stay.
Sure enough when I sat
a my little desk
and looked out
the window
I could see her
waiting there
for hours
leaning against
her car,
and I was ok 'coz
I knew, she was
there for me.
And now I'm going
to be there for her.
I just don-
I-
I don't know
that she knows
that I am though,
you know.
She knows you're
here though Rose.
I know that's hard
to see, but she knows.
Your mother's lost
her memory
and her ability to
recognise people.
But one thing
she'll never lose
is her emotion.
She can sense and
she can feel.
I know that.
That's why we
tell the families
to touch them,
talk to them.
I know I'm telling you
things you already know
but, you know,
sometimes you forget.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
I'm gonna come back
a little later and...
check on her.
All right.
Let's start the celebration
with some carrot cake, huh?
Let's see.
Here we go.
Just a little nibble.
Here you go, Mom.
Come on.
Please.
Did you hear the doctor?
It's really important
that you eat, okay?
Let's just try,
just a little nibble.
Please.
Come on.
Why won't you eat anything?
Oh, God.
Okay, let's do the tree.
Look what I won, Mom.
Huh, nice tree?
It'll cheer up the room.
Okay.
Let's see.
You like that, Mom, hm?
Merry Christmas.
Oh.
Hold on.
I'll get it.
I can fix it.
Let's see.
Just a little bit of...
What the hell's
wrong with this thing?
Ah, just get this.
I'm gonna fix it.
Don't worry.
Damn it!
I love you.
Get him in room two.
What's going on here?
It's a pileup
on the West Side Highway.
You save him!
He needs help!
Sir, I'll be
right with you.
Looking for my mother.
She was involved
in an accident on the highway.
Her name is Evelyn Jents.
I guess there isn't
gonna be a party now.
Not tonight, sweetie.
Sorry.
I'll try to scrounge up
some leftover eggnog for you.
All right.
Sure wasn't like this
when I was 14.
That was the best Christmas
I ever had.
That's great.
Excuse me.
Excuse me,
but I've been waiting for hours.
Is there any news
on Artie Venezelos yet?
You're gonna have
to talk to Nurse Stein.
Excuse me.
I was hoping
you could give me some news
on Artie Venezelos.
Are you family?
No, not really.
I just-
Either you are, or you're not.
I'm a friend.
I'm sorry;
I can't give out
any medical information.
He's his friend.
You know,
like his friend-friend.
I don't care if he's his priest.
Okay, thank you, Nurse Ratched.
Listen.
I will find out what I can, okay?
Oh, man,
I really appreciate that.
You know, but the truth of it is,
we're not even really friends.
Really?
It's okay.
I figured that.
Can't swim.
Love to learn.
You're the guy from the hospital.
Yeah, Charlie Boyd.
You're the angel lady.
What are you doing here?
Did you follow me?
No, not at all.
Well, then,
well, why are you here?
I could ask you
the same question.
I just want you
to leave me alone.
Can't do that.
I see a woman standing alone
on a pier looking over a ledge,
I gotta help.
I don't want any help.
If you jump in, I'm gonna have to
jump in right after you.
Who said anything
about jumping in?
But if I did jump,
you'd jump in after me
after you told me
that you can't swim?
Yeah, because it's
the right thing to do.
And you always do
the right thing?
Yeah, I do.
It's a bad habit.
You want to tell me
your sad story?
I'm a really good listener.
I'm all ears.
Good, I'll tell you mine.
It's Christmas Eve,
and I'm all alone.
That's it?
You're all alone?
That's the best you can do?
There's more.
I'm a priest.
Really?
Yeah, for 20 years.
Then last year,
I left the priesthood.
Kicked the habit.
Started my life over.
Now here I am.
No more Catholic family,
no personal family here,
no one.
Wow.
Now you want me to guess yours?
Take your best shot.
You're an attractive lady
who forgot her hat,
and your ears are very cold.
Bingo.
Hah.
Take anything off the top shelf.
Want to get a cab
and get a cup of coffee,
and I'll guess more
of your story?
After you.
Still my turn to guess, Rose?
You're this amazing person,
but you're too busy
helping others
to see it.
You take good care
of your friend, right?
Thanks.
Is he a close friend?
What's the matter?
Kind of a bad stomach.
Hurts.
Hope we get someplace soon.
I don't feel so good.
All right, well...
My place is actually
not far from here.
Do you want to go there?
You sure?
Yeah.
Driver, three lights,
take a left.
Hey, you know, I really
appreciate you doing this.
Aw, man, I'm glad I could help.
I know hospital policy
isn't always on our side.
They can be a little stuffy.
I remember when
my lover got sick-
Hey, wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
You made a mistake, uh, Randy.
Yeah, you're making
the wrong assumption
about Artie and I.
I appreciate you
bringing me up here and all,
but the truth of it is,
we ain't a couple.
As a matter of fact,
I just met the guy.
He's a waiter,
and I ordered some coffee-
Oh, my God,
that's how my parents met.
My mother waited on my father,
only he ordered
a tuna fish sandwich
and a ginger ale.
No, now, now look.
I just, I want
to make it clear that-
Don't worry.
Your secret's safe with me.
He's stable now.
Just thank God
for small blessings, right?
Let him know you're here.
I don't care
what the doctors say.
Talk to him.
Tell him how you feel.
He'll hear you.
Mike, we got to talk.
Oh, hi.
Oh, my.
Who's that?
Nah, forget about it.
What do you got? I went to the station.
I got some info on this guy.
Did you know your friend here
served four years
on a ten-year sentence
for manslaughter back in '79?
This guy?
Yeah, that's him.
It was a domestic dispute.
This Venezelos comes home,
finds his wife
with another guy, right,
but it's no boyfriend or nothing,
just an old friend.
He goes into a rage,
accuses her
of being unfaithful, right?
Him and this guy
get into some words.
They start going at each other.
He throws the guy
down a flight of stairs.
The guy's neck breaks.
He died in the hospital
a few hours later.
Wait, it gets worse.
The wife takes off
before the cops show up, right?
She jumps in her car
and speeds away.
She's doing, like, about 80
when she skids out
on this icy curve
and hits an oncoming car head on.
She was killed instantly.
Mike.
Whoa, Mikey, you all right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm okay.
Well, at least we know
who the nut is now, right?
Naw, he's not nuts.
Yeah, all right.
Whatever.
Let's get out of here.
I'll take you home.
Nah, I'm gonna stay
around here for a while.
For what?
They can take care of him.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Dennis, listen to me.
Something's going on here.
I don't know what it is,
but I'm gonna find out.
I appreciate you coming by
and everything,
but I got to figure this one out.
You gonna be all right?
Yeah, I'm gonna be all right.
All right.
All right,
merry Christmas, partner, huh?
Merry Christmas.
Whoa.
I didn't see nothing.
What is it with this guy?
You don't even want to know.
All right, later.
Take care.
This is really hot.
Be careful.
It's tea with bitters.
It's good for your stomach.
Thanks for letting me come here.
Oh, sure.
It's not right, you know.
I should be the one helping you.
Oh, no, I'm the one that always
takes care of everybody,
remember?
My thing.
Must be something
you need, though.
What do you mean?
Well,
what do you want most
in the whole world, Rose?
I guess just to make it
through the night would be nice.
Now we're talking.
I can definitely help with that.
Did I just invite myself
to spend the night?
Sort of.
Maybe I should go.
No.
Stay.
You sure?
Yeah.
On condition that you tell me
what it is that you want.
That's fair.
I don't want to be alone
when I die.
Is that too much?
No. No.
No.
You sure that's him?
Doctor, believe me.
He was just here this morning.
So you think
that it was self-inflicted.
Absolutely.
Well, if that's the case,
we can hold him
for up to 24 hours
for observation if we think
he's a danger to himself.
Have the resident psychiatrist
have a talk to him
before we decide to let him go.
Okay.
Look, if there's not
gonna be a party,
I want to go now.
Can't leave right now.
Why?
You have to speak
to another doctor.
For what?
Those are the rules.
Look, you can't
just keep me here.
I can't, but he can.
Now sit down.
Charlie, I hope
you don't mind my asking, but...
Why did you leave the priesthood
after 20 years?
I lost my faith.
And I began to question
the existence of God.
If you're a priest,
that's not good.
So here I am.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
What about you?
What about me?
How's your faith?
Oh, it's pretty shaky.
Really?
Why?
Well, my mom's been sick
for a long time with Alzheimer's,
and she was always the glue
that kind of
kept the family together.
Now she can't even bathe herself.
And I keep trying
to reconnect with her.
How do you do that
with someone who's not there?
Well, I put...
I put pictures of the family
all around the room,
and I bring her
her favourite foods.
I play her favourite music.
You know,
I'm just trying to find her
just even for, like, a second,
just to have some kind
of moment of clarity, you know,
so that I know she's still there.
Does it work?
No.
Do you pray?
No, not anymore.
Yeah, I know how that is.
Only five more hours to go.
Till what?
Till you make it
through the night.
This is mesmerizing.
Not for five hours.
No.
We should put another tape on.
How you doing?
Look, I want to go home now!
All right?
This is all wrong.
This is not the way
it's supposed to be!
Calm down, Mr. Calvert.
Oh, you want me to calm down.
Calm down.
I can calm down.
That calm enough for you?
What about that?
Get him on the other side.
What are you doing?
I got a broken hand.
Put me-
I didn't do anything wrong.
Orderly!
Let me go.
Come on.
You know, Artie,
I got to tell you,
I feel really bad
about what happened
at the apartment today,
and I want you to know that,
you know, I wasn't mad at you.
See, I was...
I was mad...
Man, Artie,
I really screwed things up
between Nina and me.
You have no idea.
Actually, you probably do,
don't you?
Hey, Artie.
I got to know.
That stuff you were saying today,
about you and me, you know,
about your wife,
that was just crazy, right?
Just some
big misunderstanding, right?
Who are you?
I'm a friend.
I've never met you before.
Paul Venezelos.
Hi.
Michael Reilly.
I'm the guy that took him here.
I'm a cop.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah.
So how's he doing?
He's stable.
All right.
Well, thanks for sitting
with him.
It was good to meet you.
Yeah, of course.
Mike.
Yeah?
He didn't give you
some cockamamy story
about you being
my reincarnated mother, did he?
He did, didn't he?
He's been doing that
to some poor unsuspecting chump
every Christmas since she died.
Well, look,
I promise I'll let him know
that you were here
when he wakes up, all right?
Yeah.
I appreciate it.
Can't believe you're still here.
So he likes to tell people
they're your
reincarnated mother, huh?
Yeah.
Always around Christmas.
Look, I'm sorry about your mother
and all that happened.
He told you what happened?
Yeah, a little.
You know, he mentioned it once.
Wow.
My father
never talked about that.
Anyhow, I'm sorry.
Pop, you know,
he just can't seem to forget it.
It's the past
that holds onto him.
We don't count.
No matter what we do,
no matter how much
we try to be there for him,
we just can't reach him.
I can't reach him.
Do you know he still keeps
that glass angel by his bed?
I swear he sees her face in it.
Glass angel?
Yeah, my mother
had it blown out of glass
to put on top of the tree.
It was a surprise for Pop.
Sounds like
they loved each other very much.
They did.
All my father's looking for
is a little forgiveness.
Where's the harm in that?
Forgiveness from who?
From her.
He screwed up, and he's sorry.
He just never got a chance
to tell her.
I got to take a walk.
I'll be right back.
Keep an eye on him.
Yeah, you got it.
Morning.
How you feeling?
Rose.
Charlie, if you have to leave,
I understand, really.
It's fine.
Look, I made it
through the night, didn't I?
Yes, you have.
But is that
what you really wanted?
Just to make it through the night
and that's all?
Well, I suppose I'd like to think
that my life matters.
Oh, your life matters.
You've touched
other people's lives
in ways you don't even realize.
How do you know that?
Because you touched my life.
You're just being nice, Charlie.
No, Rose, I'm not.
It's more than that.
You saved me, Rose.
I was wondering where God was,
and the next thing you know,
there you are
at the bedside
of a complete stranger
telling him you love him
with such meaning.
And then I knew God was there
in that room with you.
You were there?
Yeah.
Why did you do that, Rose?
I...
Because he was just so alone,
and...
I guess I know
what it feels like.
I know.
That's why your mother
wants you to let go
and live a life.
What?
Your mother wants you
to live your life, Rose.
You don't know my mother.
She knows you love her
and you're there for her.
Why are you doing this?
Because she told me to tell you.
That's not funny.
And you're scaring me.
No, Rose, listen.
I don't have much time.
Charlie, please.
I don't want to listen.
Please listen
to what I have to say.
Get out of the house.
I don't want you here anymore.
I'm not gonna leave
till you hear what I have to say.
She spoke to me last night.
All right,
I'm calling the police.
I know it's hard to believe.
I mean it, Charlie.
Get out!
That's what she wants.
I know that would make her happy.
Happy?
Happy.
My mother doesn't even know
she's my mother.
She doesn't hear me.
She doesn't see me.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
When you look in her eyes,
you see absolutely nothing.
She's not there,
do you understand?
I'm watching
my mother die bit by bit.
So don't you tell me
about my mother.
Get out of here!
Just go!
I love you, Rose.
Did you do that
to yourself, Jules?
No.
Well, there are some people
here at the hospital
that think you might have.
Hey, look, this is bull
have to go through with this?
If you want to leave, yes.
All right.
Fine.
I'll play this game.
My dad died
when I was real young.
My mother married some guy
with quick hands
who didn't have time for me.
So he hit you?
Yes.
A lot?
When he felt like it.
They still married?
I heard he died years ago,
which made me very happy.
When was the last time
you spoke to your mother?
I told you,
I don't have a mother.
I want to help you, Jules,
but unless you tell me the truth,
I can't.
So tell me,
did you do that to your hand?
Yes.
Why?
By the time I was 14,
I was taking a beating every day.
And once, it got so bad,
he even threw my mother
halfway across the room.
And that's when
I told him to stop.
That's all I said.
"Stop it. "
And you know what he did?
He broke my nose in three places
and then threw me
out of the house.
And after they fixed me up,
the hospital called my mother,
and she never showed.
Never even picked me up.
If she'd just given me a little hint.
That she wanted me to stay.
That she cared... something.
Then I would've stayed.
But you know what,
I felt she choose him over me.
I wasn't going to
stick around for that.
Maybe she was scared, Jules.
Maybe she was just as scared
as you
when she allowed those things
to happen to you.
She might have been happy
when you ran away
because she knew
he couldn't hurt you anymore.
Maybe she loved you that much.
Why don't you call her?
I'm sure she'd love
to hear from you.
I can't.
It's just a phone call, Jules.
No one should be stuck
in an emergency room on Christmas
if they don't want to be.
Be back in a few minutes.
I thought I was never
gonna see you again.
Hey.
Long time no see.
Should I get the nurse?
No.
What are you still doing here?
I was waiting for you to wake up.
Thanks so much
for helping me out.
I'm very-
very grateful.
You're welcome.
Artie, listen to me.
I want you to know something.
I forgive you.
You understand?
It's over.
I forgive you for everything.
Looks like there's somebody
ok to see you.
Hello, son.
Hey, Pop.
You okay?
Nina, dear.
I'll be right there.
Ay, Nina.
Come and see what I see.
What are you doing here?
Listen, I've been thinking
about what you said last night,
about being scared.
I shouldn't have
said it like that.
No, I know what you meant.
But you're wrong.
I'm the one that's scared,
not you.
Look, it's not
that I don't trust you, Nina.
I don't trust who I am,
you know?
What you see in me.
You know,
I'm just a cop, you know?
I...
I don't have a fancy suit
or a fancy degree on the wall.
I don't have the words
to make all the things I did
go away.
I wish I did, but I don't.
I just know I want to spend
the rest of my life with you.
Michael...
Look, if you don't want
to get married,
it's fine.
You don't want to see me anymore,
all right.
You don't even know
if you love me anymore...
well, I'll just have to
accept that,
because you're more important
to me than us.
But if you give me
one more chance-
I know I've said this before,
but this time,
this is for life-
I won't let you down.
I won't-
You have to believe me.
I've changed.
I'm not the same anymore.
Mike.
You don't have to say
anything right now.
I want you to think
about what I just told you.
You know,
it's like you used to tell me.
I mean, this is it.
This is forever,
and I want you to be sure.
Okay?
All right.
Hey, you know, one more thing.
Whatever you decide, be happy,
because that's more important
to me than anything.
Excuse me, nurse.
Have you seen the gentleman
that visits this patient?
No one comes to visit him.
I've never seen anyone.
His friend's name
is Charlie Boyd,
and I saw him here myself
yesterday morning.
You're mistaken, ma'am.
This is Charles Boyd,
and no one has ever
come to see him.
Excuse me.
I have rounds to make.
Charlie.
Oh, my God.
It is you.
Hey, Charlie.
Charlie.
Hi.
It's okay.
I'm here now, Charlie.
You can leave now.
It's okay to let go.
Look what you forgot.
Thank you, Charlie.
Hi.
Can I come in?
Yeah, come on in.
I thought I'd come by and...
give you your gift.
Where is it?
It's right here.
Merry Christmas, Mike.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, I love you.
I love you.
So will you marry me now?
Yeah.
Let's get married.
Oh, my God.
I missed you.
I love you so much.
So, Helen,
do you think your daughter
would go out to dinner with me?
You know, I was hoping
you might put in
a good word for me.
What do you think?
I'm a nice-
She's eating.
Mom, you're eating.
That's so great.
Congratulations.
I was just-
You're talking, I know that.
She's a great listener.
Yes, she is.
I suppose I should
continue my rounds.
Oh, Doctor.
What's your first name?
Matthew.
That's Matthew, Mom.
I'm sorry about what you heard
when I was talking
to your mother.
You know, as a doctor, you say
things to your patients that-
You don't really mean.
No, no,
it's just that sometimes-
You don't... you don't want
to take me to dinner.
No.
I mean yes.
I would like
to take you to dinner.
Oh.
Well, good, because, uh...
Well, I think,
I think that's a good idea.
Really?
Yes.
That's great.
I would really like that.
Me too.
Merry Christmas, Rose.
Merry Christmas, Matthew.
You too, Helen.
He seems like a good guy.
What do you think, Mother?
Do you like him?
Merry Christmas, Mom.