This is the sea?
Country of Suruga
I can't see the other side at all!
There is no other side.
The sea goes on forever.
Wow, that's amazing!
And that mountain is so pretty!
That's Mt. Fuji!
It's said to be the tallest
mountain in Japan.
It's so pretty!
We should make this a heritage
for the whole world.
So we're meeting the rest of the
Celestial Maiden Squad here?
Huh?
Yup. We got a letter.
Come here
Mountain
Field
Sea
Then there's another Michimi
Peach Fragment around here?
Hey, Momoko!
Ringo!
Hello, Momoko-san.
C-Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama?
What are you doing here?
It's the Celestial Maiden
Squad's company trip today!
Company trip?
It's part of our benefits package.
The Celestial Maiden Squad's motto
is "a fun, cheerful workplace."
Benefits package?
That seems kind of out of place.
Then you called us here because...
You're always working so hard,
so I wanted to give you a chance to
forget about the fragments
and enjoy yourselves.
So the fragments aren't here?
Don't get so glum...
That's right.
The Miho pine forest is
has of Japan's best views.
And it's the perfect place for swimming!
But for some reason there
isn't anyone else here today!
This place is beautiful!
But I'm going to get a sunburn.
What are you doing here?
What are you planning, coming here?
How rude.
We haven't done anything yet today.
Then what are you doing here?
Sightseeing!
We haven't located any fragments lately,
so we've had nothing to do.
Then why don't we call a truce for today?
Momo Kyun Sword
Episode 4:
Mad Dance of the Giant Boobs!?   The Pine Forest of Miho!
What is going on here?
Now, now, it will be more
fun with more people.
Please understand, this is just how
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama is.
Wait, do the two of you even
need to change into swimsuits?
Of course.
You wouldn't swim in your
formal wear, would you?
Those outfits are your formal wear?
Is this okay?
Why are you hiding?
Nobody would want to see
your disappointing body.
Th-That's why I'm embarrassed.
I'm not big like everyone else.
Oh, jeez.
You're so clumsy.
Y-You can do that?!
Huh? I never told you?
This is the first I've heard of it...
The Celestial Maiden Squad, and her...
Honestly, you're surrounded by weirdos.
What does that mean?
I'm offended.
You know, you're pretty weird yourself.
What?
Wait!
Take this!
What is this?
It's salty!
That's how seawater is!
Take that!
I got you back!
Now you've done it!
Splendid...
Here I go!
Wonderful...
Hey, do you think Momoko got bigger again?
Her boobs and her butt, I mean.
She's grown up so well...
The Celestial Maiden Squad
are normally so formal,
so I can't believe I get
to see them like this!
I'm glad I'm alive!
I know! I know how you feel!
Toutetsu-chan, this way!
I'm so embarrassed.
You look great!
I can't tell if it's a boy or a girl.
It doesn't matter,
so long as they're beautiful.
No fair.
Curse you, Toutetsu.
You wormed your way in with them!
Inugami! Sarugami!
Come play!
Okay!
Hey, Genki!
Put some lotion on me!
Coming!
Make sure you cover every square inch.
Okay!
I'm so alone!
Seimei-sama, don't look so sad.
Come over here and eat.
Here you are.
C-Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama.
I am so honored!
This smell...
Could it be?
W-Wait!
Don't eat that!
This is...
Seimei-sama!
He threw it up.
He died.
Seimei-sama, are you alive?
The squid's ready.
Want some?
Of course!
Genki, cook another squid.
O-Okay.
We're having a truce today.
It's just for today, though.
Okay, thanks!
The human world is such fun.
It's full of things I've never seen!
You live on a place called Onigashima, right?
What's it like?
It's dark and hot and there's no sun,
just volcanoes everywhere.
And it's full of Oni,
so it's just sweaty guys everywhere.
I think Enki and I are the only women.
That sounds rough.
But it's not too bad, I don't think.
My dad seems to disagree, though.
Your dad? You mentioned him before...
Yup!
Jakiou, the king of the Oni!
His overwhelming power and leadership
allowed him to bring together
all the other Oni under his banner.
I look up to him, and I'm very proud of him!
I respect him from the bottom of my heart.
I want to be a great Oni like my dad.
I see.
That's nice.
What's your dad like?
What does he do?
I don't know.
I've never met him.
I was born from a peach,
so I don't know who my mom and dad are.
Wh-What?
If that's a joke, it's not funny.
It's not a joke. It's true.
My granny was washing clothes in the river,
when a huge peach came floating downstream.
She took it home and split it,
and I came out, she said!
They call me Momoko because
I was born from a peach!
I'm sorry.
I asked you something painful.
Forgive me.
Don't worry about it.
I don't.
But...
It's true.
I have my grandma and grandpa who raised me,
as well as Inugami, Sarugami, and Kijigami.
They're all my real family.
I see.
You're actually pretty nice.
I've changed my mind about you.
D-D-Don't be stupid.
My father always told me to apologize
whenever I'd made a mistake.
I'm just doing what he says.
S-Stop saying silly things.
You're all red!
How cute!
Shut up! Shut up!
No Swimming Ahead
Momo Kyun Sword!
It's nice to get a chance to
take a break once in a while.
Yup.
Both of us are court servitors,
so we have it rough.
That's right.
Looks like you found something.
It's a big one!
I-It's a fighter!
Don't panic! Stay calm!
R-Run for it, Onihime-sama!
You guys, too!
What?
What's going on?
What is that?
It's a squid, clearly.
Of course it is!
But why is it so big?
Wh-What do we do?
We left our weapons with our clothes!
I-I've got a really bad feeling.
Oh, my, what a problem.
Everybody, I'll stop it!
You guys run away.
Now, Mr. Squid!
Eat me! I'll sacrifice
myself to save everyone!
Please!
Kushinada...
You're such a great person.
I give up.
What compassion, what friendship...
The squid has opened his heart!
Oh, no!
Looks like I was just imagining it.
We have to do it, then!
Inugami!
Right!
It grew back!
It's just going to keep regenerating!
This is a pain.
Then we'll aim for its body!
Let's go, Enki!
Right!
Thanks.
One more time.
Let's go together this time!
Got it.
What is that skin made out of?
We can't penetrate it!
We can't hurt its body,
and its tentacles grow back.
What do we do?
Celestial Maiden of Earth, Maron!
Celestial Maiden of Water, Suika!
Celestial Maiden of Fire, Ringo!
Celestial Maiden of Wind, Karin!
We'll stop you, evil squid!
The Celestial Maiden Squad is here!
Wh-What are you doing?!
He can't attack during our speech!
That's not fair!
I'm not sure why you'd
expect a squid to be fair.
Enki!
What is this?
It's so slippery.
Let me go!
Let me go, damn it!
Onihime-sama!
Enki!
Oh, my.
You guys!
Are you taking hostages?
That's not fair!
I told you, squid don't
even know what "fair" is.
Wh-What is this?
Wh-What's going on?
I-It tickles...
This is humiliating.
H-Hey!
Where are you touching me?
Stop it! Stop!
You're pretty good.
You're a naughty squid.
Everybody, we've got to go save them.
Sure.
O-Okay, let's do it!
I'll show you my wizardly power!
Are you actually going to do this?
Hey, are you...
I knew it.
That's a Michimi Peach Fragment.
That means our truce is over.
Enki, stop having fun.
We're stealing the fragment.
Aw, too bad.
G-Give that back!
Wh-What is this?
I'm so embarrassed!
This is even more humiliating.
Oh, dear. It looks like
this squid loves swimsuits.
Wh-What a horrible attack.
I'll never forgive you.
In the name of Heaven, I'll punish you.
Stop messing around!
We'll do possession fusion
to defeat the squid!
You really are a naughty squid!
Give that back!
I can't calm myself enough to do
Possession Fusion when I'm naked!
Stop it.
It's not time for that yet.
Hey, the other girls' swimsuits
are over there, right?
Make do with them for now!
Okay! Got it!
Pathetic.
Of course mine is too big for you.
Shut up!
Okay, this one!
No! It's too small!
Sorry my breasts are so small.
I-I'm not blaming you!
Sorry!
That's mine!
You'll never be able to wear it!
It's a bit tight, but I guess it fits!
What?
Momoko, you brat!
Inugami, let's go!
Right, Momoko-sama!
Momokyun Possession!
Inugami is here!
Inugami is here
Okay, Enki! Let's go!
Princess, I don't think we can
broadcast with you dressed like that.
Momoko, aim for the spot
I burned with my attack!
It should be burned and more solid!
Oh, yeah!
My granny once told me to
eat squid while it's hot!
Houkou Reppa!
I've got the fragment!
Good work!
We lost another one!
Huh? The squid...
The power of the fragment
inside it made it bigger.
Does the Michimi Peach Fragment
have power like that?
Yes.
Even a small fragment like this contains
an incredible amount of energy!
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama!
What is it?
Calm down, Inugami.
Deep breaths!
I-I'm sorry, Momoko-sama!
Jeez! Inugami, you jerk!
It really stings...
You need to use sunscreen.
I'm never going to the beach again.
I'm sick of squid.
Am I going to be able to get back?
Next time we go to Sagami!
Kinmedai
Miura's Kinmedai,
and Shounan's Whitebait.
Whitebait
and Tuna from Misaki!
It's got the best seafood in the country!
Tuna
After you eat, you can take a
bath in a Hakone Hot Spring.
Next time:
Suspicion!?
The Trap in the Fog!
Paradise!