Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama, this is...
The fragments are responding
to some great power.
Y-You can't mean...
At last!
This must be...
I've been waiting for this.
Youki, we're ready, right?
Everything's ready as planned.
It's been many years since that nightmare.
At last the time has come.
Gather all your power and find it.
Yes, sir!
The time of our obscurity will end soon.
I won't let you stop us,
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi.
Momo Kyun Sword
Episode 9:
Big Developments!? The Secret of Momo!
The Country of Echizen
This place is pretty.
It'd be great to eat lunch here.
Don't try to hide it.
Just say you're hungry and want to eat.
No! That's not it.
See?
Your stomach is honest.
Let's find a spot to eat, then.
Let's eat!
Again, Momoko?
That's impolite.
No!
It wasn't me!
Then who was it?
Wh-What a coincidence!
Fancy seeing you here.
Onihime?!
A coincidence? Hah!
You're ambushing us here?
What do you want?
W-Wait, wait.
I'm just here to have fun today.
Enki and Genki are busy with something,
and nobody has time to talk to me.
But why would you come to us, then?
We're enemies!
Aww, don't be like that.
We all took a bath together, right?
Don't laugh!
You're the one person I
don't want laughing at me!
You're both bad.
Two girls of your age...
It's pathetic.
I-I can't help it.
I haven't had anything all day.
I see.
Then let's eat together!
Let's eat!
The food's good, the weather's great...
The human world is great.
Grannie told me that if you
go to sleep right after
eating you'll turn into a pig.
You mean a cow, right?
Be quiet.
You're talking like Enki.
I've been wondering... what's inside that?
This?
I told you, I've had it since the
time I was born from a peach.
I don't know who gave it to me, but...
That's...
What? What's wrong?
Wh-Why?
Why do you have this?
What do you mean?
This ring is my...
What's wrong with her?
I don't know.
What is this?
Why do you have the same ring as me?
That's what I want to know!
Why do you have the same
thing that my mom left me?
This is...
Yeah.
It's the only possibility.
Is that...
What?
Do you know something?
Tell me!
What's going on?
All right.
We'll tell you everything.
Momoko, and Onihime...
I want you to listen carefully, too.
This is important to both you.
To both Onihime and me?
Seventeen years ago there was a beautiful
princess in the Celestial World.
She was kind and loved by everyone.
And we three gods served her.
But...
One night she ran from the Celestial Realm.
She had broken the laws of the
realm and had children with an Oni.
Children with Oni blood weren't
allowed in the Celestial Realm.
So she took the newborn babies and ran.
But she was weak, and collapsed midway.
She used the last of her power to let
the children escape to the human realm,
and this is what she said to us.
Please, protect those children.
There were two peaches.
The children were twins.
One of the children was
Momo, and the other was...
That ring is what she left you.
She gave it to her two children
and sent them to the human realm.
We followed them right away but one of
the peaches was caught in the current...
Th-Then...
Momoko and I...
...are twins?
I can't believe the child we
lost that day is still alive.
I've never been so happy.
I'm so glad. I'm so glad!
Wait!
If we're twins does that
mean my dad is Jakiou?
No, that's not true.
It's not Jakiou.
He died before you were born.
Th-Then my dad...
I'm not Jakiou's child.
I guess not.
Why?
Why would my dad lie to me about that?
Probably, after we lost sight of you,
your peach was found by the Oni and
you were raised as Jakiou's child.
If you have that ring, that's proof.
No... that's...
I can't believe that!
I'm Jakiou's daughter, Onihime!
Looks like that was a big shock.
I'm sure.
Are you okay, Momoko?
I'm surprised, but I was always
told I was born from a peach.
I knew I wasn't normal.
Momo...
But I finally know who my parents
are... and they're dead.
I see.
Father! Father!
Where are you?
Father!
What?
Are you thinking about yesterday?
Yeah.
How should I face Onihime the
next time I see her, I wonder?
You know, she's your sister,
but she's still an Oni.
She's our enemy.
It won't be easy to get over that.
There you are!
Momoko!
Hey, guys! What's the matter?
Big trouble!
The Michimi peach...
The Michimi peach core?
Yeah. It's the center of the shattered peach.
It has several times the power of a fragment.
And we know it's in Shinano.
The Oni will certainly come for it.
We can't let them have it.
We can't screw this up.
Be careful.
Momo Kyun Sword.
Country of Shinano
Wow.
I can feel the power, even from here.
Who knows what'll happen if
the Oni get their hands on it?
L-Look!
That light.
The fragment is there.
They already found it!
It makes it easier for us to find it.
Fortunately it looks like
they haven't dug it up yet.
First let's take out the Oni.
You can't have the Michimi Peach Core.
You sound so brave.
But this time we can't afford to lose.
We'll throw everything we've got at you.
There are just too many of them.
It's just one of his illusions again.
Too bad. They're all real this time.
See for yourself!
Get them!
We'll have to fight.
Let's go everyone!
Yeah!
There's no end to them!
If you've got time to whine, take them out!
This is bad!
But we have to fight!
Th-That's...
Tekki!
I'll never forget the humiliation
I experienced that day.
Today I'll defeat you!
Now do your possession fusion!
Wh-What do we do?
He's gotten a lot stronger.
Then we need to do possession
fusion or we can't win!
Momoko-sama!
Yeah, let's go, Inugami!
Momokyun Fusion!
Fast
As
as
The
the
Wind
Wind!
Inugami is here
Inugami is here!
Here I go!
Momoko!
He's way stronger than last time!
That defeat made me stronger.
I'll never lose again!
What do you want, Oni general, Youki.
Oh, hello.
You're the famous onmyouji,
Abeno Seimei, right?
But I'm here for Kaguya-sama.
It's about the Michimi Peach Core, right?
I'm impressed, Kaguya-sama.
Then that makes this fast.
The core will soon be ours.
We need your knowledge and scientific
power to make best use of it.
So you want us to come with you?
Yes.
Jakiou-sama is waiting for you, too.
Please.
You heard him.
What do you want to do?
Unfortunately that's not possible.
She's a guest of the imperial court.
That doesn't concern me in the least.
Don't underestimate Abeno Seimei.
Stupid tricks.
Whose tricks are stupid?
Toutetsu.
Right.
You can't have Kaguya.
Not you or the Celestial Realm!
Momoko-sama!
Let's do it, Inugami!
Houkou Reppa!
Houkou Reppa
N-No!
I win.
Momo!
Momoko!
No...
This can't be!
Splendid.
Genki-sama!
Splendid!
This beautiful light is filled with power.
This is the Michimi Peach Core!
You can't have it!
We won't let you!
Jakiou-sama will be very pleased.
Youki, you fool.
Toutetsu, suck it all up!
Right!
Toutetsu!
Now cry for me!
I love it.
It makes me so hot.
It seems you're the fool.
Now then, Kaguya-sama, will you come with us?
I guess so.
Don't go, Kaguya.
The court will provide
you everything you want.
So...
I only want one thing.
To return to my home on the moon.
I don't care if it's the court or the Oni,
so long as they help me get back to the moon.
Onigashima has excellent facilities.
I'm sure you'll be satisfied.
I see.
You're going to betray us?
Betray you?
We were simply using each other.
Right?
Don't hate me for this.
Goodbye.
Let's go.
...to Onigashima.
Kaguya...
The Michimi Peach Core...
Jakiou has it now, it seems.
We have all the pieces we need.
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi, just you wait!
Next time we'll be going to Kyoto.
It's got Kyoto vegetables,
Kyoto Vegetables
and conger eel and dried tofu skin.
Conger Eel
It's a treasure house of delicious food.
Dried Tofu Skin
I'd like her to enjoy the beautiful capital,
Next time:
Shocking!
Onigashima's Counterattack!!
but will Momoko-san be okay?