Once upon a time, there lived an old couple.
One day, while the wife was
at the river washing clothes,
a huge peach came bouncing down the river.
They cut it open, and inside
was a healthy baby girl!
They named the girl Momoko,
and she grew up big and strong.
And...
...she grew a pair of giant peaches herself.
Episode 1
Possession Fusion! Momokyun Sword!!
At last, the Oni are on the move.
They're after the Michimi Peach Fragment.
They must not be allowed to have it.
Understood, Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama
I'm counting on you, Celestial Maiden Squad.
Yes, ma'am.
The Land of Bizen - Tourikyou
Tourikyou, a small village
in the land of Bizen.
Momoko lived there with the old couple.
Well?
Well done, Momoko-sama.
I'd say an 82.
You're starting to get a lot better.
Aren't I?
Let's try that one thing next!
No, it's still too soon for that.
Did you forget how horribly
you failed last time?
It's still too early for you.
You guys are all so harsh.
I'm growing up by the day, you know?
Let's do it! Come on!
Let's do—
Momoko-sama!
What is she doing?
Who's growing up, now?
67 points.
You're so mean, Sarugami.
Hey, Momo!
Don't look at me, you animals!
D-Don't call us animals, it's rude!
I mean it's true, but...
We're just worried about you!
Whatever! Just don't look at me!
Momoko always had three friends with
her, a dog, a monkey, and a pheasant.
I finally dried off.
What's wrong, Momoko-sama?
Raise it up higher.
The festival starts tomorrow, right?
It's that time already.
Momoko, don't trip in your yukata this year.
I wanted to forget that.
Let's all come back tomorrow,
and bring your grandpa and grandma.
Okay.
All right, time to do my daily
routine before I head back.
Okay, let's go!
The weather's nice, and it's so peaceful!
That's a good thing.
Yup.
It's for the best that I
don't have to use this.
And granny tells me to not just
practice sword fighting all the time,
but to do something feminine for once.
What's wrong?
Momoko-sama?
There are pretty flowers!
Let's go see!
Um...
Momo?
Why do you all look so weird?
Wait!
Momoko-sama!
Even if I was born from a peach,
I have grandma and grandpa.
And Inugami, Sarugami, Kijigami,
you're all my family, too.
M-Momoko-sama!
Why are you saying this now?
I'm embarrassed.
Grandpa, Granny! I'm back!
You're safe, Momoko!
What's wrong?
A traveler told me that Oni have
appeared in a village nearby.
Oni?
I can't see any Oni yet...
Kushinada said they're around here...
Um...
What's wrong, Karin?
I can't find any Oni...
But I see something really bad.
Oh, that again?
Your magic only sees evil things.
Why do you even use it, I wonder?
Really, you're so useless.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Well, if we're going to fight Oni,
it's only natural you'd see bad things.
More importantly...
That's Tourikyou, in the land of Bizen.
There should be an old shrine there.
Then is that where the
Michimi Peach Fragment is?
It's possible.
Let's go.
Wait, Maron!
Oni all over Japan?
Villages and towns are being
attacked, one after the other.
Who knows when they'll attack Tourikyou...
Could this be...
Hey, guys...
This is why you taught me
how to use a sword, right?
Well, that's true, but...
I'll do it!
If an Oni comes I'll fight it!
I'll protect grandpa, and granny,
and everybody in the village!
B-But Momoko-sama...
You've never been in a real fight, right?
Do you know what a real Oni is like?
I've never seen one,
but I've heard about them, so I know!
They look like this, right?
Um...
What is this?
We should've taught her how to draw!
Is this wrong?
They look like nothing you've ever seen,
and they hang out in packs,
and they use weird weapons.
See? It looks just like them!
It looks nothing like them at all!
Trouble!
What's wrong?
People in weird outfits are
heading to the village!
Could it be...
M-Momoko-sama!
Hey, wait!
Jeez. She's not the brightest at times...
Karin, did you find the shrine?
I-I can't see it yet.
But...
I see something really, really bad.
Is that all you know how to say?
So, nothing new.
That's fine. Let's split up and look.
Stare.
You're...
You can't be...
I'm sure of it!
You're the Oni!
Huh?
Momokyun Sword!
Don't try to hide it!
You're in a pack,
and you look like nothing I've ever seen,
and you're using weird weapons!
So that means you're the Oni!
What's with this girl?
Maybe she's stupid?
Yeah. She's stupid.
She looks like she's stupid.
Wha—
If you call someone stupid,
that means you're the stupid one!
My granny told me that!
Stupid! Stupid!
Right, right.
That's enough!
Argh!
Calm down, Momoko.
Are you from the heavenly world?
Yes.
I knew it.
So the Oni really have appeared, then...
Wh-What?
Grandpa! Grandma!
Are you okay?
Momoko!
Inugami, give me the Kongoumaru!
Right!
Let's go, guys!
Take this! And this!
Celestial Maiden of Earth, Maron!
Celestial Maiden of Water, Suika!
Celestial Maiden of Fire, Ringo!
Celestial Maiden of Wind, Karin!
We'll stop the evil Oni!
The Celestial Maiden Squad is here!
You're Celestial Maidens?
Yes.
I'm Ringo of the Celestial Maiden Squad.
I'm Momoko!
I was born from a peach!
Sorry to interrupt.
Where is the shrine?
Shrine?
We're here to protect and recover
the Michimi Peach Fragment,
which is being held there.
Michimi Peach?
A holy peach of incredible power!
Its fragments are scattered all over Japan,
but the Oni are trying to gather the
fragments and use its power for evil.
Something terrible will happen if
we let them have the fragments!
We need to hurry!
So this is it?
That's the Michimi Peach Fragment!
Hold it right there!
That's the village's treasure.
Give it back.
The only ones who can give me orders
are those who are stronger than me!
Momoko-sama!
Too easy.
Tekki-sama, what shall we do now?
Whatever you want.
M-Momoko-sama...
If I don't stop them, everyone will...
She's trying hard.
Fool.
Even if I'm a fool, I...
I'll never give up!
Inugami!
Momoko-sama, I'll lend you all my power.
You can't...
Don't! It's never worked even once!
It's the only way to beat them!
Let's do it, Momoko-sama!
Yeah!
Momokyun Possession!
Fast
as
the
wind!
wind
Inugami is here
Inugami is here!
No way!
She did it!
That's...
Possession Fusion!
Celestial Maiden
Sumeragi-sama, what is this?
Let's go, Inugami!
Right!
Impossible...
This little girl is stronger than me?
Wow...
This power is born of the bond between
we three gods and you, Momoko.
This is possession fusion!
Let's go, Momoko-sama!
Yeah!
Hou
Houkou Reppa!
Houkou
Houkou Re
Houkou Reppa
T-Tekki-sama!
I'll never forget this humiliation!
Let's get out of here!
Right!
Wh-What is this?
No, Momoko-sama!
You need to concentrate or
it will cancel the fusion!
But I don't know how—
Why am I naked?
She needs to train more. I knew it.
We've told you many times you need a
strong mind to do Possession Fusion!
Forget that!
Give me something to wear!
Um... Momoko-san...
Momoko's fine.
What is it?
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama, in the
heavenly world, wants to talk to you...
I saw your last battle.
I'm impressed by your power,
and I have a request.
The Oni are trying to gather the Michimi
Peach fragments from around Japan.
I would like for you to help stop them.
Why me?
Well...
I don't think the Celestial Maiden Squad
are really up to the task themselves.
And you were super strong!
Therefore...
Help me out, Momoko-san.
That was really mean.
Sorry we're not up to it.
She's always so silly.
So that's how it is.
Will you help us?
First...
How long do I have to stay dressed like this?!
If it gets too hard,
you can always come back.
We'll always be waiting for you.
Grandpa... Granny...
Are you really going to do it?
If you want to back out, now's your chance.
That Tekki guy was really strong.
If there are a lot of Oni like that
it would cause problems for everybody, right?
So that's why I'm going.
Grandpa told me if people are
in trouble I should help them!
Momoko-sama...
Now, let's go, guys!
And fight the Oni!
Momokyun Sword
Okay, next time we're going to Harima!
Harima's famous for its Kobe Beef!
Kobe Beef
And Tajima Beef!
Tajima Beef
And Sanda Beef, too!
Sanda Beef
For some reason I'm sounding
like a really hungry character!
Next time:
Demon Combination!?
Onihime is Here!
Is this going to be okay?