Let's go, everyone!
Yeah!
The core of the energy powering
Onigashima is the Michimi Peach!
There must be
a machine inside the castle that's
using its energy to power the castle!
So the Michimi Peach must be there!
There's no time!
Everyone, let's group up and advance!
Yeah!
Momo Kyun Sword
Episode 11:
The Last Battle! Momoko vs. Jakiou!!
Father, they told me that I was born from a
union between an Oni and a Celestial Maiden.
That I'm not your child.
Is that true?
Answer me, Father?
What of it?
Is that all you want to know?
Then... then why did you
raise me as your daughter?
The Celestial Realm has always
hated and despised power,
as well as us Oni,
and the children born from a union
between Oni and Celestial Maidens.
To them, a child like you is to be all the more hated than Oni alone.
That's why I took you in and raised you.
To mock those who abandoned you.
That's the only reason? That's why?
They abandoned you because of their ideals,
and now you will be that which destroys them.
Ironic, isn't it?
Father!
I am not your father.
Hate me if you like.
Do as you please.
Princess...
I'm not a princess.
I'm the child of an Oni and a Celestial
Maiden whose names I don't even know!
I'm not even one of you.
But you're still our princess.
And my dear friend.
Oh, looks like they broke the gate.
I have to go.
What should I do?
What Jakiou said.
Do what you want.
There's nothing tying you down now.
What I want...
I...
Kushinada, you must evacuate, too.
N-No, I'll stay with you to the end,
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama!
Or perhaps I can be sacrificed first...
I'm counting on you,
Celestial Maiden Squad, and Momoko-san!
The Celestial Maidens
have entered the castle.
You must be careful, Kaguya-sama.
You'll protect me, right?
You're the ones who'll be in trouble
if something happens to me.
That's right.
But that was only true until a minute ago.
What are you thinking?
The Michimi Peach is complete and
Onigashima is functioning properly.
We've no more use for you.
That was your plan from the start?
The power of the Peach is finally ours,
we don't want it used to
send you back to the moon.
Goodbye, then.
I won't let anybody have this.
Not even you, Jakiou!
Watch out!
Maron!
Again?
You never learn.
Splendid!
Genki!
We don't have time to waste here.
The rest of you go on ahead.
We'll handle this.
Maron!
Suika!
Now, go!
I'll be waiting!
I won't let you!
You've got to fight us!
Let's go!
Brats!
Seimei-sama!
Yeah.
Show yourself, Youki!
You look upset, Abeno Seimei.
Upset?
Not at all.
I'm happy that I've got a chance to
pay you back earlier than I thought.
Leave this to us!
Seimei-san! Toutetsu!
It's all up to you.
Okay!
Let's go, Toutetsu!
Right!
Momoko!
Ringo!
I won't just let you ignore me.
I'll play with you.
We'll handle this!
Hurry, Momoko!
But!
It's okay.
We'll be there soon!
Indeed.
Ringo... Karin!
Momo!
You're here.
Fool.
You know how much stronger I am.
And you would challenge me anyway?
Are you just sacrificing yourself?
Or...
I won't lose this time.
I'll beat you and go to the Michimi Peach!
Inugami!
Right, Momoko-sama!
Momokyun Fusion!
Fast
as
As
the
The
wind!
Wind
Inugami is here!
Inugami is here
It'll end up the same way as last time!
Wh-What?
Impossible!
It's different than last time!
What is this power?
Last time she'd learned about the
secret of her birth and was uncertain.
But she's different now.
She has something to protect,
something she wants to protect,
and she's scared of nothing!
Go, Momo!
Wh-What the—
Houkou Reppa
Houkou Reppa!
You did it, Momoko-sama!
Yeah!
So you're Momoko?
You're Jakiou, right?
You were banished from the Celestial Realm
because of your accursed birth,
and now you fight with the Celestial Maidens?
What a stupid girl.
It doesn't matter if they're
human or Celestial Maidens!
I'm fighting for the people I love!
Momoko...
Cursed girl...
Then I will fight you with all my power!
Come!
Momo Kyun Sword!
Take this!
Momoko-sama!
Momo!
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah!
Show me your Possession Fusion!
Let's go, Sarugami!
Yeah, Momoko!
Sarugami is here
Sarugami is here!
Take this!
It won't go like last time!
Toutetsu!
Right!
Curse you!
Without your fog, you're no match for me!
It's useless.
There's nothing I can't suck up.
I told you it was useless.
What?!
I saw you do that last time.
You are a fool, Youki!
Too slow!
I'm not done yet!
Why? Why can't I hit him?
Calm down, Momoko!
Six Claw Strike!
Did it get him?
Weak!
Momo, fuse with me!
Kijigami is here
Kijigami is here!
Light Arrow Barrage!
No way...
Momoko-sama!
Try it with me!
Y-Yeah!
Inugami is here
Inugami is here!
Houkou Reppa!
So the Possession Fusion that
defeated my men is this weak?
Did you truly believe you could
stop my ambitions with this?
Momoko!
If you wish to stop us, defeat us with power!
There is no way to stop us except
with a greater power than our own!
You would still stand?
But what can you do?
Momoko!
Momoko-sama!
Momo!
Your power is not enough to stop me.
Begone.
I can't beat him?
Momoko!
You guys...
Yeah.
I'm not done yet!
You're wasting your time!
You understand how much stronger I am!
My grandpa always said that
if you give up, it's over.
So I won't give up!
Momoko!
Everyone!
We can't let you do it alone!
The three of us will follow you anywhere!
That's right!
Thanks!
Let's go, guys!
How stupid.
No matter how many of you there
are, it won't change anything.
Too bad!
We won't give up!
If your power is used to crush the weak,
we'll never forgive you!
Wh-What is this?
The last of the seals on the power
hidden within Kongoumaru has broken.
Heart, skill, and body,
have all gathered, and it has
recognized you as its true master!
Now's the time to come together and fight!
Let's go, Momo!
Yeah!
Momokyun Fusion!
Peach,
Peach
Dog,
Dog
Monkey
Monkey,
Pheasant
Pheasant!
Ultimate Three Gods Fusion!
Ultimate Three Gods Fusion
I can feel it!
A greater power than I've
ever seen is within you.
Is that your true form?
What is this?
Your power is growing!
Impossible!
One girl alone can't...
I'm not alone!
Inugami and Sarugami and
Kijigami are all with me!
And they're all helping me!
This blade holds everybody's hopes!
Wh-What?!
I won't give in to power.
I will risk everything I
have to crush your soul!
Let's go, guys!
Yeah!
What?
Onigashima's power has...
...shut down!
Let's hurry to the Michimi Peach!
Yeah!
So it's finally the last episode next time?
There's still a lot of
things we haven't eaten!
Hida Beef
Like Hida Beef, and Yonezawa Beef!
Matsusaka Beef
Yonezawa Beef
That's just beef!
I can't leave this to you, Momoko.
Next time:
Peach Fantasy!
Momo Kyun Sword
The title of season 2 is Oni Kyun Sword!
Oni Kyun Sword
No!