The Country of Echigo
Looks like I win this time!
Not yet!
Without your possession fusion,
you can't beat me!
Momoko!
Momoko-sama!
What's wrong?
You done already?
Come on, the fragment's right over here!
Wh-What?
Don't ignore me!
Don't you want the fragment?!
Momo!
Momoko!
Onihime-sama, is something wrong?
It's nothing!
Momo Kyun Sword
Episode 7:
Lost!? Momoko's Important Thing
So you got this fragment, Onihime?
Y-Yes!
She was a credit to the Oni
with the way she fought.
I see.
Understood.
You may leave.
Yes, sir.
This sucks!
My dad won't tell me I did good,
and Momoko is ignoring me!
Calm down, please!
Jakiou-sama may not have said anything,
but I think he acknowledges your power.
Genki, you took the princess to the
human world without telling me again,
didn't you?
W-Well...
Onihime-sama forced me!
Silence!
Now, it's going to be a long night.
Oh, dear. What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Enki, I'm going to the human world.
Come with me.
It was around here.
Do we have to be out here at this hour?
What's that?
M-Momoko, what are you doing?
I'm looking for my dagger.
It fell around here.
It's useless.
It didn't get stuck in this tree.
I don't smell it.
It's not around here?
It's too dark to find it.
Dagger?
Wh-What, what, what?!
Why is it so important to you?
Are you trying to get even with me?
It's just a dagger!
It's not just a dagger!
It's a keepsake from my grandpa!
S-So what?
A dagger's a dagger!
If you want another one I'll buy it for you.
It doesn't matter how many
you buy, there's no point.
Not to Momoko.
The dagger is important, of course,
but the charm that was tied
to it is far more important.
Charm?
Momoko has had that charm since she was born.
Since she was born from a peach
it's the only clue she has
to know where she came from.
I think she's telling the truth
when she says she feels like
the old couple are her real parents,
but I think she still wants to know.
Know who her real parents are,
and who she is.
Well, it was in the middle of a fight,
so Momoko doesn't blame
you and neither do we.
Okay, let's search a little further in.
Even if they say they don't blame us...
We're leaving.
Princess?
This doesn't bother me at all.
Not even the slightest bit!
An important charm?
If it's that important,
then take better care of it!
It's your fault for just
letting it hang off your dagger!
I-I don't know what I did, but I'm sorry!
It's bothering you bushels.
If I'd known this was going to happen
I would've stolen the dagger
and charm a long time ago.
Then Momoko would've been
too gloomy to fight!
It really pisses me off!
Momoko!
More!
Go to the human world and
find the dagger and charm.
Yes, sir.
Onihime-sama is right.
If we can get our hands on that...
What's going on?
Is Onihime trying to find the
dagger first to make you sad?
What a nasty girl.
Momo!
Let's call in reinforcements.
Reinforcements?
Why do we have to do
something like this this?
Now, now...
She always helps us find
the fragments, after all.
Well? Do you see it?
Yes. It's inside the forest!
We know that!
You're so useless.
I'm sorry.
I don't have time for this.
What's wrong?
There's something hard.
Th-That's a f-frag—
Find something, Seimei-san?
No.
Nothing!
Where is it, I wonder?
I don't know!
I can't believe there was a fragment there.
Nobody seemed to notice, so let's take it!
Yeah, you're right.
That voice!
Youki!
Is this what you're looking for?
Give that back!
It's mine!
Damn it!
An illusion?
Sorry, but I can't give you this!
I'm told this dagger and charm
are very, very important to you.
So I'd need to trade something for it.
Trade?
You want to trade it for a fragment?
That's right!
Gather all the Michimi Peach
Fragments from across Japan,
and give them to us,
and you can have the dagger and charm back.
N-No...
That's no fair!
What a jerk!
I'll be waiting for the fragments!
Good luck finding them!
Momo!
What should I do?
Momokyun Sword!
Don't cry.
We'll ask Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama
if we can borrow the fragments
we've gathered so far.
Ringo...
You're always helping us out.
Just wait.
I'll see if there are
any other fragments, too.
Seimei-san.
Thank you.
No, anybody else would do the same thing.
Bye!
Cheer up, Momoko-sama.
If you let it get you down you're
just giving them what they want.
We can try and steal it
during the trade, too.
Don't give up!
Yeah, you're right.
Thanks, you guys!
I'm afraid I can't let
you take the fragments.
Wh-Why not?
Momoko's gathered so many of them for us!
We can lend her some!
Calm down, Ringo.
But...
I believe that most of the fragments
in the heavenly world were
gathered with Momoko's help.
Will you still not let us
take the fragments out?
No...
I feel bad for Momoko-san.
Even a single fragment has great power.
Fortunately, the Oni are
simply gathering them
and show no sign of using them.
But who knows what will happen
if they start using that power?
But...
Please understand.
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi doesn't
like this any more than you do.
Jeez.
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama is so cold.
She's thirty times as cold as these noodles!
I'm sorry we couldn't help.
It's fine.
We'll just find another
fragment somewhere else.
Do you have any clues?
Well...
Karin, why don't you use your
fortune telling to find one?
There aren't any nearby.
There's no word from Seimei-san, either.
What do you want to do?
We'll go somewhere else and look.
Do you have any leads?
No, but I'll look anyway.
I'd like to help her somehow.
This sure is a problem.
And it's all Onihime's fault!
Yeah.
That's right.
No objection.
We haven't found a single one.
I guess you can't just
search for them at random.
Let's go a little further on ahead tomorrow.
Yeah.
It's nice weather today.
Momoko-sama?
Morning, everyone.
What?
You've gotten a lot more
cheerful all of a sudden.
Did something happen?
I decided to give up on the dagger and charm.
Wh-What?!
Seriously?
Wh-Why?
It was so important to you!
It's important, but...
There are a lot of things
that are more important.
Momoko-sama...
That charm was your...
Are you sure you can give it up?
I don't know.
But it's okay.
I've got you guys.
So I'll be fine.
Yeah!
And doesn't the idea of being
Youki's slave make you angry?
It makes me so mad!
Let's get him!
Yeah!
Okay, let's go, guys!
Momoko has had that charm since she was born.
Since she was born from a peach
it's the only clue she has
to know where she came from.
Mother...
So long as I have this dagger and charm,
the enemy will get the fragments for
me and all I have to do is wait!
I can't stop laughing.
You look happy, Youki.
Oh, Onihime-sama. Hello there.
My plan worked splendidly,
and now we can get the
fragments without any work.
Way to go, Youki.
That's why they call you
the smartest of the Oni.
Thank you.
I see.
So that's Momoko's charm and dagger, huh?
May I see it?
Here you go.
So this is what she's so desperate to find.
Onihime-sama!
That's—
Wait, Onihime-sama!
Youki is waiting up ahead.
We'll pretend to be interested in the dagger,
and once he lets down his guard we attack!
Yeah!
Granny said if they get you, get them back!
How brave.
Onihime!
What?
What are you doing here?
I heard you were down because
you lost your dagger and charm.
I wanted to see your face.
That's nasty!
Sorry, I'm all better now!
What?
I refuse to be Youki's slave.
I'm going to go attack him!
You'd better stay away.
We can't hold back today.
Wh-What?
You're leaving me out of this?
That's boring. That's really boring!
This is...
I-I picked it up.
That's all.
Onihime! Thank you!
D-Don't get the wrong idea.
I picked it up and now I just threw it away!
We're enemies!
Jeez, who does she think she's fooling?
Really. Weird girl.
Momoko-sama, now we can
fight without worrying.
Yeah.
Momo-kyun Possession!
Jumping
like
Like
a
A
monkey!
Monkey
Sarugami is here!
Sarugami is here
Six-claw strike
Six-claw strike!
I'm glad you got the dagger and charm back.
Never lose it again.
Okay!
This is unforgivable, even for Onihime-sama!
This is clear example of betrayal.
I will make no excuses.
I am prepared for any punishment.
Onihime.
You don't regret it, do you?
No.
Very well, then.
If you acted in accordance with
your beliefs I won't punish you.
P-Please wait. What do you—
A man's beliefs are his honor.
And I will show no mercy to
those who have lost their honor.
No matter what foolish or
dangerous action you may take,
never forget your honor as an Oni.
Yes, sir!
You guys are pretty nasty.
Who's worse, you or the Oni?
We're just doing this for
the sake of the human world.
Peace, huh?
I think it's plenty peaceful right now.
This is...
The fragments have gathered and
started to resonate with on another.
When this is complete an
immense power will be born.
And when that happens, the world
will belong to us humans.
Next time we're going to Dewa,
famous for its free range chickens,
Free Range Chicken
Kiritanpo
and Kiritanpo,
and scary Namahage monsters!
There's a bad girl right here!
Now humiliate me as much as you can, quickly!
Next time:
Peach Plan
The Underwear that
Disappeared into the Steam!?