Tekki, I heard a mere human
girl severed one of your horns.
I'm amazed you had the guts to
show yourself to Jakiou-sama.
I am prepared to endure
any punishment for the
crime of failing you, Jakiou-sama.
One can only recover from
dishonor if they aren't dead.
Redeem yourself!
Yes, sir.
We don't have enough fragments yet.
We will complete the Michimi Peach,
and bring our great wish to fruition!
Yes, sir!
Where are you going, Genki?
O-Onihime-sama?
You're going to the human world
on my father's orders, right?
I'm not taking you.
If they find out, Enki will punish me again.
Why not?
I've always wanted to see the human world.
B-But...
If you don't, I'll tell
Enki all kinds of stories.
And some of them will be true.
Th-That would be bad!
Then it's settled!
Momo Kyun Sword
Episode 2
Demon Combination!? Onihime is Here!
Momoko and her three friends
continue their journey
to defeat the the Oni that are searching
for the Michimi Peach Fragments.
Ow...
M-Momoko-sama!
Are you okay?
I told you you weren't ready yet!
Zero points! Zero points!
I'm sorry, Sarugami.
You need power and heart
for a Possession Fusion.
If your heart doesn't become
one with ours, it won't work.
Basically, you need more training.
Power and heart, huh?
Momoko!
Ringo!
And... who were the others?
You have a bad memory.
I'm Maron of the Celestial Maiden Squad.
Your face is too close.
Is there anything inside your head?
Hello? I'm Suika.
Owie! Owie!
Do you remember that?
U-Um, I'm Karin.
Anyway, we found the next
Michimi Peach Fragment.
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama says that
there's probably one in Harima.
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama is amazing!
We don't know how many fragments
of the Michimi Peach there are,
or where they fell.
But sometimes the fragments
emit a great power.
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama can detect them,
and she's ordered us to find them.
I see.
But couldn't you do it, then?
Why do you need Momo's help?
W-Well...
'Cause you're not up to it, right?
Don't say that to our face!
It's really bothering us!
What a bratty monkey!
Shut up.
I can tell by looking at you.
You need more training, too!
A monkey's making fun of us!
Stop calling me a monkey!
My name is Sarugami!
Momoko-sama and the Celestial Maiden Squad...
They both need a lot of training.
The Land of Harima
Wow!
What a big town!
I've never seen any of this stuff before!
Oh, jeez, you can tell she's from the country.
What are these?
They're so pretty! Wow!
Good grief...
Let's split up and search for the fragments.
Wow! There's so many people.
It feels like a festival!
There's so much strange stuff,
my head is spinning!
You said you'd never seen
this stuff before, right?
Yup.
I've never been anywhere but
Tourikyou and the villages near it.
If I hadn't gone to fight the
Oni I may never have seen this.
I need to thank
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama!
But are you really sure about this?
The Oni are strong,
and it's really dangerous.
It's dangerous for you guys, too, right?
Th-That's true, but..
We're the Celestial Maiden Squad.
That doesn't matter.
We all fought together.
And...
If I have the power to do it,
I want to protect the towns
and villages and people!
Momoko!
And my grandma said once you
decided to do something you
need to see it through.
And my grandpa said to always
do what my grandma said!
What?
Where the heck did she go?
I don't want to be punished anymore!
He's finally gone!
So...
This is the human world, huh?
It's so lively!
Dumplings!
Let's have one!
Okay, we'll take a break!
Yay!
I'll take a dumpling!
Bring me a dumpling!
I'm sorry, this is the last one.
I was here first.
No, I was!
How dare you speak to me that way?!
You insolent fool!
Don't you know who I am?
I don't know who you are,
but I ordered first.
It was me!
Me!
H-Hey!
Calm down, you two.
Don't get in my way!
This is between me and her!
I'm sorry, if you want peach
dumplings I have some.
So whoever eats more of these,
gets the dumpling! How about it?
An eating competition, huh?
I'm in!
This is an unlimited one round
peach dumpling eating contest.
Ready...
Go!
I won't lose!
Neither will I!
Onihime-sama, where are you?
I'm sorry, that was my last peach dumpling.
The match is over!
At 200 to 200, it's a draw.
V-Very well.
Next we'll see who can
have more red-bean soup...
Princess.
I found you!
I found information on the fragment.
We're going to find it and go back.
W-Wait, Genki!
I'm not done yet!
Listen!
We're not finished here!
Got it?!
She's gone.
Um... I think you should pay now.
She never paid for all those dumplings.
That girl!
Momo Kyun Sword!
Could that be...
What are you doing?
You should be looking for the fragments!
I couldn't help it!
It was supposed to just be a little break.
I never thought it would
get so out of control!
I can't believe you were
slacking off, as well, Ringo.
Don't you understand that you're
part of the Celestial Maiden Squad?
Sorry.
But you were at the clothing store...
Anyway, we know where the fragment is.
Let's go get it.
Yes, I do have a small, shining fragment.
But that is our family's treasure.
I can't give it to you.
The Oni are after it!
They'll do whatever it takes to get it.
It's dangerous.
Don't worry.
Our security is impeccable.
But...
What?
What's going on?
Everybody, get out of here!
Hurry!
Okay!
Shouldn't we run away, too!
That's right.
No objection.
W-Wait!
What's wrong?
Something's strange.
I can't see this flame in my crystal.
It can't be...
Suika, try putting out the flames.
Okay.
Huh?
It's not disappearing.
I knew it.
Wh-What is this?
What's going on?
It's an illusion.
B-But it was really hot!
The illusion was just that strong.
Whoever's doing this is powerful.
Is it an Oni?
Let's hurry.
They're only after one thing.
I knew it!
So you broke my illusion?
I suppose I should compliment you.
You're awfully arrogant for someone
who can only use illusions like that.
Then how about this?
What is this?
Our clothes!
They're melting.
I-Is this an illusion?
Huh?
Even if you know it's an illusion,
you can't break it.
That's my power.
Genki.
Aren't you done yet?
I have everyone looking for the fragment.
Please wait a while longer.
Human mansions are filled with strange stuff!
The big eater girl!
The dine-and-dash girl!
I did not dine-and-dash!
We both ate a lot!
And wait, you're an Oni?
Not just any Oni.
I'm the only daughter of the
king of the Oni, Jakiou!
Onihime!
And I guess you're with the
Celestial Maiden Squad?
If I had known I'd have beaten
you to a pulp right there!
What?
U-Um, do you know her?
No!
I don't know any Oni!
O-Onihime-sama?
Stay out of this.
Here I go, big eater girl!
Sarugami, get me Kongoumaru!
You're paying for those peach dumplings!
Momoko...
Onihime-sama?
Another illusion!
Argh!
I know it's fake, but...
Maron, do something!
Sorry.
I can't.
Too easy.
You're pretty good.
But I'm not done yet!
She's fast!
How do you like that?
I'm faster than you!
Momoko!
Inugami!
Kijigami!
Sorry!
Hey!
I'll remember this!
Sorry!
Momoko!
Well?
It'll be a billion years
before you can beat me.
This is bad, Momoko.
We'll have to do Possession Fusion!
B-But if I fail again...
What idiot thinks about failing
before they've even started?
Come on!
But...
This is bad.
Their hearts aren't aligned at all.
Wait!
If you're going to defeat Momoko-san,
defeat me first!
Actually, feel free to hurt
me as much as you like!
Now, make me your sacrifice!
It's started again.
Wh-What is that?
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama's
servant, Kushinada.
When she was a human she was
sacrificed, and I guess she liked it.
Now she has a sacrifice fetish.
What... is that?
So what does this sacrifice
fetishist want with us?
Oh, that's right.
This is for Momoko-san.
What is this?
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama's
special millet dumplings!
If the two of you eat this
your power will increase
and your hearts will calm themselves.
Power and heart...
Isn't that what you need
for a possession fusion?
Yes.
That's why she made them!
Now, eat them!
Okay!
Wh-What?
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama always
makes the most... unique... dishes.
Her skills and sense of taste are
best described as "murderous."
You should've said something beforehand!
I-I thought I was going to die.
But...
Yup.
It tasted horrible, but I guess it worked!
I feel powerful!
Momoko, are you ready?
Yeah!
Momokyun Possession!
Jumping
Like
like
A
a
monkey!
Monkey
Sarugami is here
Sarugami is here!
Wh-What is that?
I won't lose now!
Wh-What the—
She's as fast as me?
N-No...
She's faster than me?
Now, pay half the bill
for the peach dumplings!
No, that's not what we're here for!
We're here for the Michimi Peach Fragment!
That's right.
This is Michimi Peach Fragment!
Wait!
You can't have the fragment!
Shut up!
You, too, shall be stemmed by my illusions.
Six Claw Fists
Six claw fists!
Oh, no!
The illusion is broken!
You did it, Momoko!
I guess it all worked out.
Yeah.
Now if you get the fragment,
you'll get the full 100 points!
Yeah!
Wait, where's the fragment?!
Here!
The fragment!
What's your name?
M-Momoko!
Okay, then, Momoko!
I didn't lose to you!
I lost to your whatsits fusion!
What?
I'll get you next time!
Just you wait!
We're leaving, guys!
Hey, wait!
Calm down, Momoko!
Minus 50 points...
This isn't fair!
I can't believe it.
You're still eating.
'Cause I'm upset!
Onihime!
Onihime-sama, we got the fragment,
so you don't have to eat so much...
Shut up!
How can I not eat?
Curse you, Momoko!
I'm so livid!
Next we're on our way to Yamato!
There's more than just temples
and burial mounds there.
It's also known for its delicious vegetables.
Yamato beef
Its famous for its Yamato Beef,
Persimmon leaf sushi
And its persimmon leaf sushi.
Momoko-sama, don't eat too much!
Next time:
One for All and All for One:
The Celestial Maiden Squad!?