It sure is coming down.
So what have the demons
been up to since then?
It's been more than 10 days
but we haven't seen anything.
They've got the core of the Michimi Peach.
I thought they would do
something immediately.
It's actually creepy.
I can only predict evil things coming.
And not just the Michimi Peach Fragments.
We did possession fusion and we still lost.
To that demon named Tekki...
His defeat at the hands of
Momoko-sama made him stronger.
We can't just let him win and walk away!
We need to do something, right?
Th-Then...
Momoko and I...
...are twins?
Onihime...
There you guys are.
Toutetsu-chan?
It's rare to see you alone.
Seimei-sama has something
important to talk to you about.
Will you come with me?
Momo Kyun Sword
Episode 10
Shocking! Onigashima's Counterattack!!
Land of Yamashiro - Kyoto
It's well known that the Michimi Peach
is a source of incredible energy,
But do you know how that power can be used?
A Michimi Peach Fragment!
You had one, too?
Just holding it gives you
a good amount of energy,
but you need special technology
and science to utilize it fully.
Which means that without that technology,
no amount of peach fragments are a threat.
What is this?
In order to draw out the Peach's power
one must have technology from
a civilization far more advanced than our own.
We humans don't possess such technology,
nor does the Celestial World or the Oni.
Except one person...
Who is that?
Her name is Kaguya.
A scientist from the moon.
The moon?
You mean the one in the sky?
Kaguya came to Japan to research
the human world in a special ship.
But the ship's reactor broke
and stranded her here.
And so the court made a deal with Kaguya.
We'd help her return, and she'd give us the
technology to employ the power of the Peach.
Then she created these plans?
It's a reactor to utilize
the power of the Peach.
We would gather the Michimi Peach Fragments,
she would provide us with
the reactor technology,
and we would use the Peach
to send her to the moon.
That was the deal.
But...
Don't hate me for this.
Goodbye.
Seimei-san, you're hiding
something important, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
Why is it the court wanted technology
to use the Michimi Peach Fragments?
What were they trying to do with it?
We wanted to um...
research new forms of energy!
Yeah...
You should just say it.
We wanted to use the power of the Peach to
rule the Celestial World and Onigashima.
Hey, Toutetsu!
That's what you were planning?
That's horrible!
You're a dick!
I'm disappointed in you!
We didn't have a choice.
We humans aren't as powerful, so we've
always been looked down upon by the
Celestial Maidens and Oni, and oppressed.
So we need to combat your
power with our own, don't we?
Fight power with power...
Will you forgive him?
He's told you everything
and asked for your help
because the situation is that serious.
Wh-What?
What is this?
What's this?
Are those all...
Michimi Peach Fragments?
The Core has activated.
What do you mean?
Kaguya once told me that the fragments
of the Michimi Peach resonate with each
other because they're trying to reform.
If the core is activating all the
other fragments will gather at it.
The Michimi Peach will become one.
Th-Then...
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama!
The time has come at last...
If the Michimi Peach is trying to reform,
the core must be where
the fragments are going.
Yes.
And that is the Oni's castle.
Onigashima!
Kaguya-sama, the fragments are
all gathering at the core!
Of course they are.
I tuned it so that would happen.
Country of Bizen
Fortunately the Michimi
peach isn't complete yet.
We'll attack Onigashima
before its powers activate,
and steal back the fragments.
What's wrong?
Ringo, I'm sorry.
Give me just a little time.
Momoko-sama!
That's...
Tourikyou...
Do we have time for this?
Momoko looked okay,
but I think she was actually
worried the whole time.
She learned who she was and so she
didn't know what to do from now on...
If that wasn't the case there
was no way she'd lose to an Oni.
Will she come back?
Let's wait.
That's all we can do.
Grandpa!
Grandma!
Momoko!
Are you doing well?
I heard the truth.
That I'm the child of a
Celestial Maiden and an Oni.
Momo Kyun Sword.
We didn't have any children.
So when you came out of the
peach that grandma found,
we were surprised, but we were so happy.
Yes, it was like we had a real child.
We were so happy.
Even when they came and told us
everything our feelings didn't change.
Whether you were born from a peach or the
child of a Celestial Maiden and an Oni,
you were still our child.
Grandpa...
Grandma...
Once again, we thank you.
Even after you learned the truth,
you've raised Momoko-sama this far...
Momoko, if you know the truth now,
you can do whatever you want.
Where you go and what you do is up to you.
But remember this.
This is your home.
It's everyone's home.
You can come home whenever you want.
Grandpa, Grandma!
Thank you.
Grandpa, Grandma, I love you!
Be careful.
We'll always be waiting for you.
When it's all over I'm coming back.
To this home...
Momoko!
Okay, I'm off!
She's late.
Is this going to be okay?
I'm back, everybody!
Momoko, are you ready to go?
Yeah, I'm fine now.
I'm glad.
You kept us waiting too long.
You're going to pay us back for that.
So let's go to Onigashima.
There are fewer fragments in the sky.
There's no time left.
Yeah.
The fragments are going under the sea?
Ringo!
It's over there...
Onigashima!
So this is the Michimi Peach...
The complete form is extremely powerful.
Its energy is incredible.
Is it done?
O-Oh, Jakiou-sama!
You have my thanks, Kaguya.
Energy transmission to the engine is at 100%.
120%...
It's ready to go!
Activate Onigashima!
Wh-What?
Th-That's...
Onigashima...
This power...
The Michimi Peach is complete?
It's been many years since
that horrible battle.
And at last we have returned to Earth!
With the power of the Michimi Peach,
we have nothing to fear!
The world belongs to the Oni!
How horrible!
They're just attacking at random!
That's so mean!
There you are, Celestial Maiden Sumeragi!
It's been a long time,
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi.
Has it been since that day?
Jakiou, why—
Why?
You would ask me that?
That day, you sent us Oni to the bottom of
the Earth with your overwhelming power.
And you would ask me why?
The Celestial World refused
to allow rule by force,
and so we sent Onigashima to the
sky with an incomplete reactor.
But you used even greater power to fight us!
Isn't it ironic?
You denied the use of power,
and in the end you relied on it.
No!
Rule by force invites greater force.
There's no future there.
That is the world we Oni desire.
The Michimi Peach that destroyed
Onigashima that day is now in our hands.
Resist all you like, just as we did then!
And then bow before this power!
The Celestial World...
Those jerks!
The only way to stop those attacks
is to enter Onigashima
and retrieve the Michimi Peach,
or destroy it.
Let's go.
At this rate the Celestial World
and the Human World
will end up belonging to the Oni.
Yeah.
That's...
Intercept them.
Yes, sir.
Princess?
Father.
I need to talk to you.
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Ringo, are you okay?
I'm fine.
I can't lose this fight!
Let's go, everyone!
Yeah!
Next time we'll be fighting at Onigashima!
I have a bad feeling.
Oni Manju?
What are they famous for?
Manju?
Oni Manju?
Big trouble!
Oh, right, Onigashima's famous big trouble!
Oni Manju
Pay attention!
Next time:
The Last Battle!
Momoko vs. Jakiou!!
I'm in big trouble, too!