Country of Dewa
Hot Springs
Hot springs, huh?
Dewa's always been famous for
having lots of hot springs.
It's good for nerve pain, muscle pain,
scrapes, cuts,
and makes your skin soft
and makes you look younger.
Soft skin?
Look younger?
Wow! Wow!
They say if you take a bath in these hot
springs your breasts will get bigger!
And it'll slim your waistline, too!
This place is wonderful!
They're really excited to take a bath.
W-Well, we don't have any
clue where the fragment is.
It wouldn't hurt to take a little bath.
Dewa Hot Springs Inn
This is it!
Onihime?!
Momoko?!
What are you doing here?
Is there a fragment around here?
N-No!
We're just here because this
hot spring is really popular.
Yup.
Oh, is that right?
So you're here for the same reason we are.
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama?
We're all girls,
so we all have the same thought.
Then let's forget about out
our struggles for today,
and all enjoy the hot springs!
Momo Kyun Sword
Episode 8:
Peach Plan the Underwear that
Disappeared into the Steam!?
Welcome!
Thank you for coming.
We've got room for your whole group!
Women's Baths
What?
Just you wait.
Once I take a bath here, I too...
Me, too!
This feels so good!
Your peaches are as ripe as ever.
Take that!
What?
Oh, sorry.
They just look so delicious.
What are you talking about?
I'll get you back!
Stop it!
Get bigger.
What are you doing?
It's too late for anything you
do to make a difference.
You're wasting your time.
Nobody asked you!
So you came all the way to the human
world to reclaim your youth?
It must be hard being a middle-aged Oni.
And I think you should make sure
you get you good, long soak.
Your wrinkles are showing.
Oh, I thought that was makeup.
It's a dark spot.
Sorry.
This is paradise, isn't it,
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama?
Yes.
Hey, Kushinada, do I look a little younger?
You look plenty young already.
Oh, that makes me happy.
So about how old do I look?
How many years old?
U-Um...
So how many years old?
They sound like they're having fun.
Well, there's nothing wrong with a
bit of relaxation once in a while.
That's right.
Seimei, when did you get here?
It doesn't matter.
More importantly, are you
willing to let this pass?
What do you mean?
What lies beyond that hated fence?
Yes, the women's bath.
Seimei-sama...
Women's bath. What a wonderful sound.
There are girls on the other side of
that fence who aren't wearing a thing,
and you're just going to let them be?
Well?
But...
If they see us they'll kill us.
I don't care!
I'd rather die peeking than die not peeking!
Is he really the imperial court wizard?
He's just some pervert.
He gets that a lot.
Behold!
He was screaming so loud,
there was no way we wouldn't hear him.
Seimei-san's actually kind of stupid.
Huh?
What's wrong?
They're gone... the panties
I was just wearing.
Mine are gone, too!
So are mine?
They're gone!
They're gone! I can't find them!
Oh, you're right.
Mine are gone, too.
Could it be an underwear thief?
Probably.
They were all stolen?
So he doesn't care whose it is?
The jerk!
This is a problem.
What should we do?
Shall we start with the
most likely of suspects?
Wh-Why is this happening to me?
You can't fool us!
You're the only person who would do this!
That's a mean thing to say.
But he can't really deny it.
Wait.
It's true that I wanted to
see inside the women's baths.
But that's unshakable
proof that my interest in
women's bodies themselves,
not their underwear.
I see!
No you don't!
Aren't you embarrassed to say that?
Then somebody else did it?
Unforgivable.
Let's find them and make them
suffer the torments of hell for
three days and three nights.
Aww, you're exaggerating.
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama,
what should we do?
Let me see...
I say punish them for a full
month instead of a week.
Okay, let's go find the guy, Inugami!
Yup.
Allow me to check the scent, Momoko-sama.
Excuse me.
What are you smelling, pervert?!
If I follow the smell of
the stolen underwear...
W-We'd be able to find the guy, right?
That's right.
B-But...
This way.
I can smell Momoko-sama's scent!
Hey, don't say that so loud.
By the way, you're all wearing kimonos,
but what are you doing for underwear?
Well...
They stole our spare underwear, too.
Which means none of you are wearing any now—
It's not just our underwear.
They stole all our clothes!
That's right, your usual outfit
is basically underwear, isn't it?
It's not underwear!
It's my best outfit!
I can smell Momoko-sama's scent!
It's close!
We found you...
...underwear thief!
This is, well...
I'm sorry.
What do we do with him, everyone?
First, we tie him upside down and splash
him with water for three days and nights.
That's too nice.
We can jam all kinds of things
into every hole in his body...
We should find out what happened first.
There's no point in asking.
He wanted girls' underwear,
so bad he couldn't bear it.
That's all.
You shut up!
Actually, an Oni has begun living nearby.
An Oni?
Yes, it's taken to attacking our villages,
and we didn't know what to do.
And then the Oni said...
...it wanted an offering
of young girls' underwear.
Panties!
Who can give me young girls' panties?!
By making regular offerings
of young girls' panties,
it stopped attacking our villages.
But all the young girls left,
so we decided to invite female guests to
our hot springs and steal their underwear.
No, but then...
The effects of this hot spring
were made up to lure customers.
Yes, I'm sorry.
What? My breasts aren't going to get bigger?
Aww...
It's probably a rogue
Oni who left Onigashima.
I'll get him.
We'll make him pay ourselves.
She looks really mad.
It's one of her own's fault
so she's all fired up.
So were you the one who decided whether the
underwear belonged to a young girl or not?
Yes, you can tell immediately when
it belongs to an older woman.
I see.
Oh, my! Whatever is the matter?
Momo Kyun Sword!
Its effects were a lie, but hot springs
sure feel good, don't they?
They said they'd let us stay here
for free if we got rid of the Oni.
We have to enjoy it!
I didn't know that some
Oni had run away, though.
Any organization has people who
only think about themselves, right?
They didn't have the guts
to fight Jakiou-sama,
so they ran away from Onigashima
and are harassing weak humans.
The scum.
It's the Oni's motto to do our
harassing fair and square.
I don't know if that's much better.
I see.
I guess there are a lot of different
types of Oni. That's neat.
It's not neat.
It's not neat at all for me.
Heave ho! Heave ho!
Ho!
Think the rogue Oni will show up?
He has to come.
But do we need the sacrifice?
She said it was much more likely to
attract him than just underwear...
She just wants to be sacrificed, doesn't she?
Will she be okay?
I feel a breeze...
I feel really uneasy without any underwear.
Shouldn't we have put something
on before we came here?
But the enemy might not come
out unless it's our underwear.
But we can't fight like this.
Is that him?
He's kind of... tiny.
Y-Yeah.
He's here!
My sacrifice will bring peace to the world!
What beautiful self-sacrifice!
Now eat up, quickly!
U-Um...
Hello?
There's a naked girl right here.
You can do what you want to me!
Why?
No!
D-Don't smell them!
L-Look at what he's doing.
No... those are mine!
It looks like he's only
interested in underwear.
How gallant. How manly...
He's just a pervert!
He threw them away.
What were those?
Maybe it was the underwear
from a girl who isn't young?
Okay, let's go, Momoko!
Yeah!
You...
...pervert Oni!
If you're an Oni you should know me, right?
You can't escape my whip!
Enki!
Celestial Maiden of Earth, Maron!
Celestial Maiden of Water, Suika!
Celestial Maiden of Fire, Ringo!
Celestial Maiden of Wind, Karin!
We'll stop you, nasty Oni!
The Celestial Maiden Squad is here!
Stop that!
You'll see it!
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Looks like he's only interested in underwear.
H-He's insulting us!
Let's go, Onihime!
Right!
Got you!
We did it!
Yup!
Now we'll take him back to
Onigashima and punish him!
Get ready!
H-He ate...
...the panties!
Raging
Like
A
Demon
Underwear Demon is here
Wh-What?
Wh-What is this power?
He got stronger after eating the panties?
What's that about?
Rogue Oni,
I understand the pain of not being
understood due to your special tastes!
But you mustn't be angry.
You must take your time to explain things,
and share your understanding.
Now calm down, and look into my eyes!
Why?
Seimei-sama!
We'll have to use Possession
Fusion, Kijigami!
Yeah!
Momokyun Fusion!
Flying
like
Like
a
A
bird!
Bird
Kijigami is here
Kijigami is here!
Even after I do my possession Fusion
I still don't have any panties,
so it feels breezy.
Deal with it, Momo!
He's coming!
What power!
H-He got even bigger?
Onihime, don't let him eat any more!
Right!
Okay, I got them all back!
No!
There's one left!
Wh-What the— What happened?
He just ate the panties he'd thrown away.
They weren't the panties of a
young girl, so he lost his power!
I don't know which old lady he
got them from, but they saved us.
Okay, let's finish this!
Okay!
Light Arrow Barrage!
Light Arrow Barrage
This is the rogue Oni who wanted the panties.
It's safe now.
Now peace will return to the village.
So it's all over!
Yup!
No!
Hey, Kushinada.
Is underwear like this weird?
No, it looks good on you.
Doesn't it?
So from now I'll go with stuff like this.
Do you think the rogue Oni will like it?
Next time we're going to Shinano!
Oyaki
Shinano's famous for its Oyaki,
Nozawana, and Shinshuu Soba!
Nozawana
Shinshuu Soba
Not to mention, Inugami's VA,
Hatano Wataru-dono.
Next time:
A Huge Plot Twist!?
Momo's Secret!
Give me some recommendations
for places to go later!
I'm counting on you!