The Land of Kazusa
So this is Kazusa?
It looks like there're samurai everywhere.
The influence of the eastern
samurai is very strong here.
Their ferocity is known
in the distant capital.
Yeah, everybody looks really sharp and tough.
They all look like they're
spoiling for a fight.
It's like a war's about to break out.
Yeah.
Hey!
Momoko!
What's up, you guys?
Wh-What?
Are they being controlled by the Oni?
Be careful, Momoko!
They're coming!
Celestial Maiden Squad!
What?
What's... going on?
Momo Kyun Sword
Episode 6:
A Star is Born!
We're the Celestial Maiden Squad!
So there's a Celestial Maiden Squad
boom right now.
That's right!
One of the samurai saw the
Celestial Maiden Squad, and told the others...
Right now they're really popular.
Pictures of them are really popular!
Is this a boom?
Celestial Maiden Squad
You never know what's going to be a hit.
They don't have a lot of
experience with women,
so they fall in love.
Celestial Maiden Squad
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama!
Yes, I know.
This is...
I'm so tired.
I can't believe we're so popular!
You're right. I don't understand humans.
But you looked like you
were enjoying it, Suika.
All that attention.
You were being awfully nice, too, Ringo.
'Cause I'm happy!
It was great hearing "You're so cute!"
and "Shake my hand!" from so many people.
I was embarrassed, though,
but I was kind of happy.
Whether we're popular or
not, we only have one job:
to find the Michimi Peach
Fragments. That's all.
Y-You're right.
Popularity is fleeting...
There's no point in getting
all excited about it.
Okay, let's head out.
It would be unfair to
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama
to get all excited about this
and forget our true duty.
That's right.
Why are you dressed like that, Maron?
You're the same, Ringo.
Wh-What's with this outfit?
When did they—
Where are our clothes?
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama?
You all look wonderful.
What is this?
Ringo Suika Karin Maron
Celestial Maiden Squad Debut Announcement
Look at all those people!
What are you going to do now?
I don't know,
but Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama
started talking about making us idols.
Idols?
What's that?
Where did this come from?
I don't know.
We were surprised, too.
But Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama says that...
Bringing joy to the people is part
of our job as Celestial Maidens.
That's what she said!
We have to do our best!
They're being tricked.
Everybody, get ready!
Okay!
See you later!
O-Okay.
Thank you.
Maron-chan's hands were so soft...
I'm never washing my hand again!
Idols, huh?
Celestial Maiden Squad
Debut Song Announcement
Here's our debut song:
"Ready, go! The Invincible
Celestial Maiden Squad!"
Ready, go! The sky is endless
Ready, go! Let's stretch
out our hands to grab it
The bond between us is alive,
let's hold on to it tight
and keep going forever!
Let's go! Let's go! Celestial Maiden Squad!
A burning, passionate fire girl
A quiet, calm water girl
A cold and uncaring ground girl
A silly and ditsy windy girl
A world split into three
The darkness comes flooding in
Believing in a miracle and breaking out
Keep on going now
I keep what's important
to me close to my chest
Towards an unknown world
Each of us working together
with our own special power
Ready, go!  Four colors of pride
Ready, go!  I've got my friends,
so everywhere and always
It's all right
Ready, go! The sky is endless
Ready, go! Let's stretch
out our hands to grab it
The bond between us is alive,
let's hold on to it tight
and keep going forever
Encore!
Encore! Encore!
Kazusa's famous Celestial Maiden Squad bun!
It's hot and fresh!
The Celestial Maiden Squad is really popular!
Everywhere you look,
it's the Celestial Maiden Squad.
Supposedly Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama
is behind this production.
Really?
She's doing everything from
clothing design to stage effects.
She even got Flying Dog to write the song.
She's pretty amazing.
The pictures with a handshake
tickets were her idea, too.
People are buying dozens
of them to get the bonuses.
Momo, are you jealous?
No, I'm nothing of the sort.
Oh, it's Momoko-dono.
Celestial Maiden Squad Bodyguards
You guys!
Why are you dressed like that?
We'll be supporting the
Celestial Maiden Squad
in their idol activities as bodyguards.
Bodyguards?
Why do they need bodyguards?
The eastern samurai are
known for being rough,
and the court is concerned about them.
However, since the Celestial
Maiden Squad appeared,
they've calmed down and stopped making war.
The court decided we should
support this in any way we can.
We're in charge of security at the
events, developing new products,
and explaining things to the locals.
Actually he saw a picture of them
in their swimsuits and became a fan—
Anyway, the Celestial
Maiden Squad being idols
is a good thing for humanity!
So they're idols, huh?
That doesn't matter.
But if the Celestial Maiden
Squad focuses on being idols
and stops looking for the fragments,
it'll make things easier for us.
You're right.
It's better to have fewer enemies.
Okay, I'll leave it to you.
Understood.
Goodbye.
By the way, Onihime...
...sama?
Knock first!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Everyone, you have a new mission.
I'm aware your schedule as top idols is full.
But this is an important task.
Leave it to us.
If you order us to,
we'll do whatever you want.
That is our task as the
Celestial Maiden Squad.
Thank you, everyone.
So...
Celestial Maiden Squad
~Super Concert~
I'm counting on you for this super concert!
Yes, ma'am!
Momo Kyun Sword!
A super concert?
Yes.
I want your technology to help set it up.
Does that have anything to do
with finding the fragments?
It does!
The success of the super concert is
the fastest way for us to find the fragments!
I see.
Understood. I'll make it happen.
Thank you.
Stay in line!
Look at that line.
I guess they're all in
line to get tickets to the
Celestial Maiden Squad's super concert.
I think Momoko-sama is way better
than the Celestial Maiden Squad.
Thank you, Inugami!
All it took was a few skimpy bathing
suits and now all the men love them.
It's pathetic.
There you are.
What is it?
Celestial Maiden Squad
Super Concert S-Seats
These are the two S-seat tickets and
sexy picture that you asked for.
Don't bring those out now!
We said we'd go get them!
That really is pathetic.
No, this is...
The devil made me do it.
Why don't you two join the line?
Wait, Momoko-sama!
Momoko, you're way cuter!
Sexy! Pretty! Cutie Momoko!
Shouldn't we all be looking
for the fragments?
We haven't found one since
they started being idols.
Isn't that a problem?
Yeah, it is.
I'll go talk to them.
Come back sometime.
I will!
Thank you!
I finally made it.
Momoko!
What's wrong?
Stop doing this and let's
look for the fragments!
But we're in the middle of a handshake event!
We've got to practice our concert after this.
It's almost time for the concert.
I'm sorry.
So we'll leave the fragments to you.
We're counting on you!
Dummies!
Forget you!
The villagers say there's
something that looks like
a fragment in that forest.
And this is the super concert stadium, huh?
Celestial Maiden Squad Super Concert
I guess being an idol
was more important to them
than finding the fragments.
The jerks.
That's right.
That light!
Looks like that's it.
Let's go, then!
Yeah.
Okay, from now on it's the four of us!
Yeah!
It's almost time for the Celestial
Maiden Squad super concert!
You two look way too down.
So do you, Suika.
Is this really okay?
I'm pretty sure it was around here.
Hold on!
When did they...
There are so many.
Kijigami!
Right.
They're...
Illusions?!
Looks like there are some real ones mixed in!
We're just going to have to...
...take them all on!
Yeah, but we have to do this!
I wonder how long they'll last.
Are all of you ready?!
Celestial Maiden Squad!
Are you ready?
Hm?
What's wrong with you all?
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama, I...
Everyone, please hear us out.
What's going on?
I'm really glad you all came
here for our super concert,
but I'm sorry, we can't sing any longer.
I really like dancing and singing,
but that's not who we're supposed to be.
We've realized that the Celestial Maiden Squad
has a much more important mission.
That's why today is the
last day for us as idols.
We're going back to the old
Celestial Maiden Squad!
What?!
That's how the Celestial
Maiden Squad should be!
Celestial Maiden Squad!
The real Celestial Maiden Squad is back!
This was the right thing, wasn't it?
Are you sure this is for the best?
It seems like they all
finally realized what they
should be doing and what's important.
You can't mean
you wanted them to understand
that, so you made them be idols?
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama knows all.
What amazing foresight.
To be honest, she was really
just after the money.
What?
She might be the Celestial Maiden, but she
has her own life to attend to, as well.
I have my title, so I need
to play the part, you know?
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi...
She's terrifying.
Hey, you!
Hm?
Give us our money back if
you're canceling the concert!
What?
Give us back our money!
W-Wait!
Seimei-sama!
Another fake!
They don't stop coming.
There isn't even enough time
for us to do a Possession Fusion.
What should we do?!
Genki!
I took the fragment.
And next...
I'll take your lives!
Not happening!
Who are you?!
Celestial Maiden of Earth, Maron!
Celestial Maiden of Water, Suika!
Celestial Maiden of Fire, Ringo!
Celestial Maiden of Wind, Karin!
We're going to stop the Oni!
The Celestial Maiden Squad...
has arrived!
You guys!
Momoko, we're getting back the fragment.
Right!
I-I'm not letting you have it!
Let's go, guys!
Hey, don't run away!
Momo, let's do a Possession Fusion!
Right!
Momokyun Possession!
Flying
like
Like
a
A
bird!
Bird
Kijigami is here!
Kijigami is here
Light Arrow Barrage!
We're far enough away now.
Good work, you guys.
Yeah.
Hm? What's that?
We weren't far enough away at all!
Momoko...
We...
It's fine.
You came for me.
Thanks.
The explosion should have been around here.
There's someone here.
Isn't that the...
I bought one hundred of those pictures.
Oh, this isn't good.
I think we should retreat for now.
Wait for me!
Celestial Maiden Squad!
Calm down, Momo!
If you start getting that flustered, I'll...
Now that I think about it,
I should have just flown away, too.
Pictures
Momoko
Oh, my.
The naked picture of you is pretty popular.
Why did this have to happen?
Don't get so down.
It's a new record, supposedly.
The amount of these pictures they've sold.
So you're an idol now, too, Momoko.
Isn't that great, Momoko?
No...
No, it's not!!
Sold Out
We'll be going to the Land of Echigo next.
Hegisoba
Hegisoba and tarekatsu are well known there,
Tarekatsu
but my recommendation is definitely the rice.
Rice
Get yourself some good Koshihikari and sake.
Next time:
Lost!?
Momoko's Important Thing
Nothing better.