Father...
You would still call me father?
I don't know what to do!
I don't even know who I am.
Am I an Oni? A celestial maiden?
Or...
You are a fool, girl.
No matter who you are, there is
one thing that will never change.
You are you.
I am me?
There is nothing left to tie you down.
Live as you like.
Wait, I...
I...
Power is a mirror that reveals
the heart of he who wields it.
Jakiou, your heart is warped and twisted;
it could never defeat
Momoko-san and the others.
Why didn't you realize that?
So long as I possess this,
my power will be amplified!
These wounds will heal quickly!
Stop it, Youki!
You're too late!
The power of the Michimi Peach
now belongs to me!
Wh-What?
What is this?
What's going on?
Foolish man.
Kaguya!
The Michimi Peach has fused once
again and activated its power.
Its power is too great,
and it has become unstable.
Did I forget to tell you?
You little—
I won't give up!
If I can master this power
I will surpass even Jakiou!
Wh-What... incredible power!
What wonderful power!
My wounds are healing!
What? What's going on?
This is...
My body is disappearing!
Th-Th-Th-That's...
That's impossible!
What a fool.
Onigashima!
No! If nobody stops it...
Wh-What's going on?
What's happening?
This is...
It can't be!
We need to go, too!
Yeah!
That power is great enough
to float all of Onigashima.
A single Oni couldn't contain it.
I've got to start all over again.
Wh-What?
The Michimi Peach that was keeping
Onigashima afloat is gone.
Now it's going to fall.
I-Is now the time for calm explanations?
We need to get out of here!
Onihime...
Momo Kyun Sword
Episode 12:
Peach Fantasy! Momo Kyun Sword
Hey, what happened?
Princess!
I haven't settled things with you.
Fight me, Momoko!
Now's not the time for this!
Onigashima is falling!
We need to escape—
Shut up!
Here I come, Momoko!
As a princess of the Oni, I'll defeat you!
Stop it!
We're sisters!
There's no reason for us to fight!
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
I'm the daughter of Jakiou, Onihime!
With my father gone,
I'm the leader of the Oni now!
Prepare yourself!
No...
But... but I...
Shut up! Shut up!
Stop running, and fight me!
What's wrong, Momoko?
Come and get me!
Onihime...
Momoko-sama?
What's wrong?
I'll fight on my own now.
Wh-What are you saying?
Onihime is throwing all of
her feelings into this fight.
So I need to do the same.
Come on, Onihime!
Sounds good to me.
Why do they have to fight?
They're sisters!
That's why.
Onihime is suffering now that she
knows the secret of her birth.
And Momo understands how she
feels better than anybody!
So she's trying to tackle
her feelings head-on?
That's like Momoko!
What's wrong?
You can't defeat me like this!
I'm just getting started!
Their swords are crying!
But Momoko is accepting everything.
Her rage...
Her sadness...
It's pure and honest.
That's who Momoko is.
My... what a bothersome sisters' quarrel.
What are they doing at a time like this?
I can't understand it at all.
That's right.
What Onihime-sama said back there...
Jakiou-sama must already be...
So it seems.
But we don't need to worry, right?
Because look.
We've got a wonderful heir.
No matter what happens,
the princess is the princess, right?
Okay!
Hang in there, Princess!
I know!
Momoko-sama! Fight!
If you lose there's no dinner for you!
Right!
Go!
You can do it!
The collapse stopped?
Could this be...
We'll stop Onigashima from falling!
Everyone, hurry and escape!
It won't last that long!
That's Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama for you.
Her kindness resonates throughout
the entire universe.
Now's not the time for this.
Calm down.
We can fly.
Let's take Seimei-san and
the others and escape.
Wait a second.
Th-This is bad.
We can't fly.
How do we get out?
Jeez, you're annoying.
We just need to grab some rope from the
storehouse and climb down or something.
Oh, I see.
I'll get started.
You take command and ensure everyone escapes.
Got it?
Yeah.
What about you, Enki?
I...
I'm going to watch this to the end.
It'd be sad if it were only
the princess left here.
B-But...
Don't worry.
I'll escape with the princess.
Now get going.
O-Okay.
I'm staying here.
You guys escape.
Wh-What are you saying?
Don't you understand the situation?
I do.
That's why I'm staying!
When Momoko wins, she'll need
someone to take her home, right?
Ringo, you...
We don't know for sure that Momoko will win.
She will.
I know it.
I believe in her.
Very well.
Take care of things, then.
Yeah!
Make sure you come back!
We'll be waiting!
Now then, let's see the
results of your training!
No! You need to escape!
What are you talking about?
We three will stay with you forever.
Let us stay with you.
Okay, Momo?
Inugami!
Sarugami!
Kijigami!
Thanks!
Calm down and go down one by one!
Don't panic!
I can't hold it anymore!
Wh-Why you...
You're too slow, Onihime!
Did you think you could beat me like that?
Shut up!
I'm still coming!
There's too big an opening after you attack.
Thirty points.
What?
You're telegraphing your attacks.
Zero points!
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
You think you can lead the Oni like that?
Aren't you embarrassed?
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
Here I come, Momoko!
I'll put all my power into this attack!
Here I come!
I accept your challenge, Onihime!
Momo!
I win.
Come at me as many times as you like.
I'll fight you as much as you want!
You did it, Momoko!
Is there anybody left?
Everyone, hurry!
Everybody, we're getting out of here!
Hurry, Princess!
Onihime!
M-Momoko?
Momo!
Momoko-sama!
Princess!
Momo Kyun Sword!
It's been months since the
incident at Onigashima.
The recovery in the human world
is still lagging behind schedule.
You must help the people.
Understood, Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama!
I'm counting on you, members of
the new Celestial Maiden Squad!
Right!
Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama!
Oh, my! It's the members of the
old Celestial Maiden Squad!
Stop calling us the old squad.
We're still working.
That's right.
You girls, help the human world recover, too.
Right!
Um, Celestial Maiden Sumeragi-sama,
you should sacrifice me to ensure
the prosperity of the human world...
By the way, I wanted to ask you something.
Would you like to be idols again?
Look, I've already made new outfits,
and I've ordered a new song from Flying Dog!
It's time for the second stage of the
idols of the Celestial Maiden Squad!
She didn't learn a thing.
But I love her anyway!
I have a horrible feeling about this...
Then you don't intend to complete
the Michimi Peach again?
That's right.
That power was too much for me, too.
I can't control it either like that.
I see.
But I can control it when it's fragmented.
As long as I don't mess up the energy
ratio and the amount of fragments,
I should be able to return to the moon.
There's more to research.
Glad to hear it, Kaguya.
The court will continue to help you.
Jeez...
Second Onigashima Building Grounds
Don't slack off, or the harvest will be late!
You may be better off doing this.
There's nobody else to do it.
Will you do it?
No.
It looks annoying.
Enki's like this, and Tekki's
off training by himself...
It's going to take a long time to
get Onigashima off the ground again.
Isn't that fine?
There's no reason to hurry.
Though one of us certainly is.
That's right.
Welcome back, Inugami, Sarugami, Kijigami.
Excuse me.
Oh, hello.
You're back?
You never learn.
Shut up, animals.
Where is she?
Today's the day I finish this!
Jeez, you're here every single day!
Give up already!
"Come at me as many times as you like."
"I'll fight you as much as you want!"
That's what you said, right?
Now, fight me as much as I want!
You brat...
You've lost 99 of our last 99 fights!
No!
There were 99 fights and 99 ties!
Our 100th fight will be
when I finally defeat you!
You mean it'll be the 100th
time I beat you, right?
Here I go, Onihime!
Good luck, both of you!
Your millet dumplings are so good, grannie.
Thanks.
Momoko!
Onihime-chan!
I've got some for both of you!
Thanks for always making those for me!
You're such a brat!
You should know better!
I don't want to hear that from you.
Okay!
Whoever wins gets all the dumplings, then.
Fine!
I won't lose!
You saw, didn't you?
What a stupid man.
Here I go, Momoko!
I won't lose!
And so Momoko and her friends
lived happily ever after.
The end!
The End