The fog again?
Everyone, be careful!
This way, Momoko!
Sarugami!
Wh-What do you mean this way?
I meant this way!
Where did you go?
Don't mess with me!
Ow...
W-Watch where you're going!
You, too!
This fog is just like the last one.
We won't fall for the same trick forever!
There you are!
This way, everyone!
Momo!
Wait! Wait!
It's me!
I got the fragment again!
Both the master and her servants are stupid.
To fall for the same trick twice!
Well, it makes things easy for me!
Bite me!
It won't happen a third time!
I'm Youki.
I'll fight you as many times as you want.
Goodbye.
He makes me so mad!
Momo Kyun Sword
Episode 5
Suspicious!? The Trap in the Fog!
You're as fast as ever, Youki.
As your servant, Jakiou-sama,
this is nothing for me.
That fog is poisonous.
Inhale it and you lose your
sense of direction and smell,
and you can't think straight.
But it's in such small
amounts they don't notice.
They act weird and they don't know why.
And eventually they become
suspicious of one another.
And at last...
Do what you have to.
But don't let your guard down, Youki.
Yes, sir.
We don't have enough fragments.
We cannot let our guard
down for even a moment
until our great wish comes true.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
My plan is perfect.
It hasn't any flaws.
Just you wait and see, Jakiou.
Country of Sagami
He took another fragment from us!
You guys got to get it together!
Weren't you lost and staggering
around in the fog yourself?
So were you!
Sarugami always goes the wrong way,
and Inugami's nose stops working.
I'm better than Kijigami,
who can't even fly in the fog!
I don't want to hear that from
idiots who run off in deep fog,
even when I tell them it's dangerous.
I-Idiots?
That's right! Idiots!
You're no better, Momo!
What did you say?
I just don't like Youki.
He never plays fair.
As a fellow Oni I'm embarrassed.
But Jakiou-sama said he didn't
care what we had to do, right?
B-But...
I don't like it either,
but results are all that matter.
Using poisonous fog to make
Momoko and her friends
distrust one another so they
can't do possession fusion...
It's given him two victories in a row.
Those guys are simple,
so they're easy prey for Youki.
They may just keep losing.
This sucks!
I don't know why, but this sucks!
What's with the people in this town?
They just don't want to see
your stupid monkey face.
What did you say?
Maybe they're just scared of a
certain somebody's ugly frown!
Who are you calling ugly?
Don't get close to them!
Hold it, you guys!
What?
What, you want to tell our fortunes?
Sorry, I'm not in the mood
for my fortune right now.
Bye.
Hold on a second.
At this rate something awful will happen.
What do you mean?
You are all fighting right now.
He's right!
He's amazing!
Anybody could tell that.
And right now you're journeying
to find something important.
How did you know?
But lately it hasn't been going well.
He's right!
The four of you have done
just fine so far, but...
What's this?
What? What?
What's going on?
You should stop your journey here.
One of you will bring disaster to the others!
If you stay with them you'll
all meet with disaster!
How scary!
Wh-Who is it?
Who are you talking about?
I don't know.
But my predictions always come true!
Please be careful.
One of us...
Will bring misery to all the others?
Who is it?
Could it be them?
Perfect.
Now their suspicions will
change to certainty.
And the bonds between them will shatter.
If their hearts can't become one
they can't do possession fusion!
So where are we?
Weren't we supposed to make it
to the next town before sunset?
Where's the town?
Let me guess, we're lost.
That's pathetic.
There's three of you animals
and none of you noticed.
You were walking in front!
Who kept going forward when
they didn't know the way?
Wh-What?
Then you should've said something!
You just followed me without saying anything!
You're both idiots.
So are you!
You're all idiots.
You're an idiot.
You're the biggest idiot.
So are you!
I'm sick of this!
I'm done!
We're getting lost,
we can't find the fragments...
Nothing good comes from
being around you guys.
That's my line.
Do you know how much trouble
you're always causing for us?
Well, it's true that we've got a
lot of useless morons around here.
I'm not sure why you're not
including yourself in that.
What about you?
What?
This isn't working.
I can't travel with you guys anymore.
That's right.
All right, in that case...
Yeah, bye.
Hmph!
What?
You left all of them!
Yup.
But don't worry, I can find
the fragments on my own.
Actually it'll be easier without them around.
Th-That's not the issue.
It's so great being alone.
I should've done this a long time ago.
Are you serious, Momoko?
Of course!
Now, where's the next fragment?
It was Momoko-sama's decision.
I won't go back without her saying so.
B-But...
I'm finally done being a babysitter.
Let me be free.
Are you sure that's for the best?
Of course it is.
It's best for me, and for her!
You guys can take care of Momo.
I'm sick of it.
We don't want to, either.
It sounds like a pain in the butt.
Anyway, I'm not doing it.
You guys have fun.
Momoko...
My plan's working perfectly.
If they're not working together
they can't do a thing.
Now it's time to have some fun with them.
Jeez, where'd the path go?
Kijigami, is there another way?
This is fine.
I was just thinking I
wanted to visit a cliff.
Momokyun Sword!
Over there!
Hey, Momoko!
Momoko-sama!
We've been looking for you.
So you've been over here, crying?
I'm not crying.
So granny yelled at you?
That's what you get for eating your
whole dinner before dinnertime.
She didn't have to get so mad.
Of course she got mad, you did something bad.
And we told you what to do when
you did something bad, right?
You say sorry.
Yup. You do know.
So let's go home and apologize to her.
I'm sure she's worried about
you being out in this rain.
But...
Don't cry.
We'll apologize with you.
I suppose we have to;
we're your teachers after all.
We'll all say sorry, okay?
Okay!
Jeez... Fine!
Oh... I fell.
Sorry, huh?
Oni!
Inugami, give me Kongoumaru!
Wh-What are you doing, guys?
Where are you going?
What about you?
I was just making a little side trip...
This is the way we came.
Why are you going back?
What about you? What's the hurry?
I, well...
So we all had the same idea, right?
We can't just leave her, can we?
Let's go!
There are so many of them!
How long can you last with just that dagger?
I can kind of smell Momoko-sama!
We finally caught up?
Momo!
I put extra-strong poison in the fog today.
You shouldn't breathe too much of it.
Poison?
That was making everybody act weird, right?
If it weren't for this fog...
Momo!
Are you okay, everybody?
This is poison fog that Youki made.
Poison?
It was all part of their plot?
I'll blow away the fog.
Everyone, hurry and go to Momoko-san!
Got it!
I'll put you out of your misery.
Goodbye, girl.
Momoko-sama!
Are you all right, Momoko?
You guys...
Karin got rid of the fog.
Wh-What?!
We'll handle the little ones!
Momo, Sarugami!
You take Youki!
You guys...
I...
We can talk later!
Let's go, Momoko!
Yeah!
Momokyun Possession!
Jumping
like
Like
a
A
monkey!
Monkey
Sarugami is here!
Sarugami is here
Take this!
Paralysis Binding!
She disappeared?
I'm over here!
Six Claw Fists
Six Claw Fists!
Curse you...
I'll get you next time!
We did it!
Yeah!
100 points, Momoko!
Looks like you got your butt kicked, Youki.
I'm ashamed.
Don't underestimate Momoko.
We don't know the extent of her powers.
I'm sorry.
Let's go, Momoko-sama.
We're almost to the next town!
Yeah!
Next time we're going to Kazusa.
It's famous for its peanuts.
Peanut
But the warm climate makes
it the best place in
Peanut
Eastern Japan to grow things.
Next time:
A Star is Born!
We're the Celestial Maiden Squad!
But that aside, what's going to happen to us?