Country of Yamato
And so this time, the Michimi Peach
Fragment is somewhere on that mountain.
Where is it?
You're Celestial Maidens, so wouldn't
it be faster to fly and find it?
We thought that, so we went to look for it,
but we couldn't find it.
It should be up here.
Let's hurry.
Okay.
I don't know where it is,
but please work together
to find the fragment.
Okay.
Um, if there's anything you need, call me!
I'm totally prepared to be your sacrifice!
Let's go look for the fragment, then.
Okay!
Oh, there you are.
I've been looking for you.
Celestial Maiden Squad,
and Momoko, who was born from a peach.
Who are you?
I apologize.
I am Abeno Seimei.
A wizard.
Nice to meet you.
Momo Kyun Sword
Episode 3
One for All and All for One:
The Celestial Maiden Squad!?
Abeno Seimei-san?
I believe he's a wizard who
serves the imperial court.
The rumor is that he's very good.
I'm surprised my name is known in Heaven, too.
I'm honored.
The imperial court has
ordered me to help you.
Help us?
Why?
Protecting the Michimi Peach fragments,
scattered across Japan,
and stopping the Oni from
threatening humanity...
Our goals are one in the same.
Let's work together!
Hey, isn't he kind of cute?
Sorry, not my type.
Actually, look at that.
Oh, I see.
So that's your type.
No, everyone!
This is my familiar and servant, Toutetsu.
I'm not into that!
That's what everybody says.
How naughty.
So are you the cool bottom, Seimei-san?
Or is Toutetsu-san the little devil bottom?
What does that mean?
A human who uses something
called Possession Fusion, huh?
I've never been so humiliated in my life!
Please, Enki!
Take me to the human world!
Sure...
I'm interested in the fragments,
but I'm interested in that Momoko girl, too.
N-No!
She's my quarry!
I know!
Well, there are four Celestial Maidens.
I can entertain myself with them.
Well... as long as we can
broadcast it on the air.
No Entry Beyond This Point
There's a legend that a shooting
star once fell on this mountain.
Ever since then, anybody who
visited this mountain is said
to have their wounds and illnesses healed.
Could the shooting star be
a Michimi Peach Fragment?
Probably.
It's believed their great power
affects their surroundings.
If a power like that exists,
we can't let the Oni have it.
Let's hurry.
Karin, can you see the crystal?
I just see something that's kind of bad.
That's all you ever see.
I'm sorry.
Well, there's no point in listening to her.
Let's ignore her and keep going.
Suika!
What?
Ow...
Are you okay?
Um...
There's a pitfall there, so be careful.
It's too late for that!
Jeez...
That was horrible.
I'm sorry.
But why was there a pitfall there?
The locals probably put it there to
keep someone from taking the fragment.
Then does that mean there
might be other traps?
Be careful, Momoko.
Hey, what's this string?
Don't!
Karin, which way do we go?
U-Um...
Th-That way.
Yes.
That way is dangerous.
You need to tell us sooner!
Um, this way is dangerous.
So's that way.
So this way...
Jeez, just tell us the safe route first...
So this way is the most dangerous!
You're doing that deliberately, aren't you!?
I hate snakes!
If there's a trap that means
this is the right way.
So Karin's prediction was correct.
I see.
That's not the issue.
At the rate we're going,
we won't live to make it to the fragment.
We know there are traps.
We just need to be careful.
She loves to backtalk.
What a brat.
Jeez...
Are they always like this?
Well, um...
To be honest, they practically
hate each other.
You shouldn't expect too much.
I see.
This might not work.
Maybe not.
So that's Momoko and her
Celestial Maiden Squad.
Time for round 2!
Let's go, Enki.
Don't be in such a hurry.
Finding a single fragment on this
huge mountain is going to be a pain.
Let's fight them after they find it for us.
I see!
Smart thinking, Enki!
But promise me one thing, Princess.
Don't do anything dangerous.
If you do I'm sending you straight back home.
I know!
You always worry so much.
Then let's go.
Yeah!
What? What is this?
A human trap!
Jeez!
Stupid tricks.
You can't stop us Oni with this stuff.
What?
Seems like somebody triggered
one of the traps.
Maybe it's an Oni.
Then we need to hurry.
Yeah!
Momoko?
What's wrong?
Nothing!
This way! Come this way!
Hey, wait!
Everybody else, come this way!
Momoko-dono!
Jeez... what a nasty trap.
Wow...
Somebody triggered another trap.
Poor guys...
I don't know who you are, but I'm sorry.
Momo Kyun Sword!
Ugh. I can't go on anymore.
Where is the fragment?
I-I'm sorry.
I still don't know the details yet.
You really are useless.
I'm not listening to your
useless prophecies anymore.
Suika...
You don't have to go that far.
I do kind of understand how you feel, though.
We walked around all day
and still didn't find it.
Yeah.
I'm not even sure why I'm here now.
Very well.
We'll leave Suika here since
she doesn't want to go,
and we'll find it ourselves.
Wh-Why are you saying it like that?
It's like I'm the bad guy here!
Our task is to recover the fragments.
You abandoned it,
of course you're the bad guy.
What?
Is there a problem?
Calm down, both of you.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault!
Karin!
We meet again, Momoko!
Onihime!
That was awful!
Those nasty traps!
We're changing the plan.
I'm Enki.
If you want this girl back,
find the Michimi Peach Fragment.
You'd better hurry, or...
Karin!
We'll wait until morning.
Good luck finding the fragment!
Onihime!
She just keeps getting in our way!
We don't have a choice, then.
Yeah.
Let's split up and search for the fragment.
Guys?
I wonder if they'll bring the fragment.
If they don't, we'll just
take her back to Onigashima.
Her skin looks so healthy.
I love it.
It's welling up within me.
Now, give me a wonderful scream.
I'll show you heaven.
No! Stop!
Enki, you need to cut it out or a lot
of people will get really mad at us.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Well, just hope your friends do a good job.
Just like we promised, if we get
the fragment we'll let you go.
I don't think anybody will come.
Why?
I'm useless.
They're probably glad I'm gone.
What?
You Celestial Maidens are cold.
It's not their fault.
I really am useless.
Looks like it's here.
It's huge!
Is this caused by the fragment, too?
What great power!
Okay!
Let's go to Onihime and save Karin!
Mission complete.
Maron?
I'm returning to Heaven.
What about Karin?
As I said, the Celestial
Maiden Squad's mission is
to recover the fragments.
Nothing more.
B-But...
You're wasting your time.
That's how Maron is.
She's only interested in her mission.
She's the ideal Celestial Maiden.
But...
Goodbye, then.
Wait, Maron!
How cold!
I'm disappointed in you,
Celestial Maiden Squad.
I can't believe they really didn't come.
I'm not worth saving.
Don't get so down.
I'll make you forget all the bad things.
We've brought the fragment.
Now let Karin go.
What? They did come.
Wh-Why?
Why else?
We're the Celestial Maiden Squad.
We're comrades.
You really are a pain to take care of.
You guys...
Now the trade is complete.
Bye!
Hold it!
Maron and Suika are such brats sometimes.
I-I haven't forgiven her for what happened,
or changed my mind, okay?
Karin is part of the
Celestial Maiden Squad, so...
You deliberately acted cold to avoid
involving Momoko and her friends?
That's great, Celestial Maiden Squad.
I believed in you!
Now that we've saved Karin,
all that's left is the fragment.
I'm taking it back!
You fight me.
Princess, we have the fragment.
It would be wise to run.
But my fight with Momoko...
Onihime-sama!
We're leaving, Enki.
Have a nice day!
Hey, give back the fragment!
Momoko, we'll handle them.
Get the fragment!
Come forth, my familiars!
Now go, Momoko-dono!
Give it up already!
Go, Momoko-sama!
Yeah!
No!
I can't catch up!
Don't give up!
Momo, I'll help you!
Possession Fusion!
Kijigami!
H-Here we go...
Yeah...
Momokyun Possession!
Flying
like
Like
a
A
bird!
Bird!
Kijigami is here
Kijigami is here!
Light Arrow Barrage!
Light Arrow Barrage
Princess!
Enki!
I'm taking back the fragment.
Princess, no...
I know.
Don't worry.
Momoko, I lose this time.
But...
Next time I'll get revenge for Enki, too!
Just you wait!
Onihime...
Calm down, Momo!
Don't get upset just because
your boobs popped out!
No!
Thank you.
We'll keep this safe in Heaven.
Okay!
Thanks!
I'm glad the fragment is safe.
The court will continue to help you.
So I look forward to working with you.
As do we.
Let's head home, then.
Thanks to a certain idiot,
I missed my beauty sleep.
I-I'm sorry.
But... thank you.
Let's go.
Bye!
They actually make a good team, those four.
My granny told me that the more
you fight, the better you taste!
No, she didn't.
The better friends you are!
Was that it?
It was!
You're always thinking about food.
I'm sorry... You did that for me.
Don't worry about it.
You're more important
to me than the fragment.
There'd be trouble if my dad heard that.
But forgetting the fragments,
the human world is really interesting.
Will you take me back there?
Sometime, if you promise not
to do anything dangerous, okay?
Okay!
It's a promise!
Yes. It's a promise.
I see.
So the fragment was taken to Heaven.
Well, we'll let them do
what they want for now.
Celestial Maidens... Humans...
And Oni.
Who will complete the Michimi Peach?
We already have our trump card.
We won't let anyone have it.
The Michimi Peach belongs to us humans.
All right, next time we're going to Suruga.
We'll be visiting the Pine Forest of
Miho, which is a world heritage site.
It's famous for Mt. Fuji,
the Feather Robe legend,
Mandarin
Oranges
Tea
mandarin oranges, tea, and wasabi!
Wasabi
Next time:
Mad Dance of the Giant Boobs!? The Pine Forest of Miho!
B-But what is this strange episode title?