Then... You've made up your mind?
You are going through with it?
Why not?
For one thing, he's an excellent champ.
At least try to get some sleep.
If I were you, no more Congnac.
We'll come for you at five.
It'd give you three hours.
You will be here.
I don't mind so much to being killed.
But you know how it is for
me to get up in the morning.
Good night.
I'm afraid this time, Stephan has picked
a fight with the wrong man
I wonder if he'll be here
when we come back?
Who is it?
Brown.
Good morning, Mr. Brown.
Cheer up, John.
This is one engagement
that I have no intention of keeping.
Honor is a luxury.
Only gentleman can afford.
Pack my things...
Whatever you think
that I'll need for a indefinite stay.
I have a cab downstairs...
In about an hour,
I'll go out the back way.
I'm sorry.
I won't be here to see their faces.
Has this come during the night?
Would you bring me
some coffee... with Congnac?
"By the time you read this letter,
I may be dead."
"I have so much to tell you,
perhaps very little time."
"Will I ever send it?"
"I don't know."
"I must find strength to write
before it's too late."
"And as I write, it became clear
that what happened to us"
"...had its own reason beyond
our poor understanding."
"If this reaches you..."
"You'll know how I became yours..."
"When you didn't know who I was,
or even that I existed."
"I think everyone has two birthdays.
Day of his physical bir
"And the beginning
of his conscious life."
"Nothing is vivid...
or really my name."
"Before that day in Spring..."
"When I came home from school,"
"And found a moving
van in front of our building."
"I wander about in our new neighbor..."
"Who owned such beautiful things."
Lisa! Come in, Lisa!
Come in this minute, did you hear?
Lisa!
Yes, mother.
Who is going to play that dock?
Me. I suppose.
I have nothing to do.
You better get another rope.
Uh?
Alright!
Get another rope!
This is the last time I move a musician.
Why does he have to play the paino?
Where do these go?
What?
In the study.
Thank you.
Lisa, what are you doing out there?
Come inside.
"I didn't see you that day,
or from many days that day after
"But I could listen to your playing."
I wish he stop that noise.
What noise?
Don't bite my head off.
Mr. Brown is playing.
You called that playing?
Shh...
How old is he?
Who?
Him!
Quite old, I guess.
Oh.
You know the boy
I was talking to outside the school?
The bony one with the yellow
hair and a long nose.
One who lives next to the grocery.
I'm gonna do something about it...
If he dosen't keep his hands to himself.
The things he does,
Right out in the street
Thank you, John.
I'll be home later.
Thank you.
Good morning.
Why, Lisa! You're all red in the face.
You're bulshing!
I'll get you for that!
"Yes, I was blushing."
"And hard as it
may be for you to realize..."
"From that moment on,
I was in love with you."
"Quite consciously,
I was preparing myself for you."
"I kept my clothes neater,
so you wouldn't be ashamed of me."
Bow, two three four...
"I went to dancing school."
"I wanted to become more graceful,
and learn good manners for
Bow... two three, and one two three...
And one two three...
"So I would know more about you,
and your world..."
"I went to the library...
"And study the lives
of great musicians of the past."
"Though I was not able to
go to your concerts,"
"I found ways of sharing in
your success."
"As months went by,
I began to know your friends."
"Many of them are women. Most of them."
Lisa!
Where are you, Lisa?
Aren't you going to finish your dinner?
Sorry, mother.
"But I really lived for
those evenings when you're alone."
"And I pretended
that you're playing just for me."
"I know you didn't know it..."
"You're giving me some
of the happiest hours of my life."
"Then came a great day for me."
"In the building where we lived."
"Thursday was rug-beating day."
Come on, let's help him!
Oh! I've got to do my own.
I'll do it for you afterwards.
Come on!
Remember what you've promised!
I will.
Beautiful rug.
It's a beautiful rug, isn't it?
Oh, it's just a rug.
Oh, you wouldn't know.
Say, what are we doing this for?
Shh! He will hear you.
Oh, he can't talk.
Well, he can hear, can't he?
You're welcome.
Come on, Lisa.
I'll be right down.
What are you going to do?
Go away, I'll be right down.
Go away, or I'll throw you downstairs.
Are you crazy?
Lisa!
What are you doing up there?
Come dear, I've something to tell you.
It's really good news.
If you think about it sensibly,
you'll be very happy.
Sit down.
I can understand
that you must've been startled...
When you saw
her customer and me in the hall.
Perhaps it's my fault for not telling
you something about it
You see, dear,
your mother is not really old.
She can have admirers, too.
She can even be in love with a man.
Someday you'll understand
better what I means.
Besides...
You know how hard it is for us to
get along on that small pe
That guy has a comfortable business.
It links... a military tailor.
And he's down here
to ask me to marry him.
Besides, he is a kind man,
and he likes you very much.
I'm sure with his help,
it'll be much easier for you to...
Mother!
What is it?
But we have to go to Lance?
We have to live there?
But why not?
What is there to keep us here?
I won't go!
Lisa!
What's the matter?
But... what is it?
Lisa!
I won't go.
Now Lisa!
Do be reasonable and tell your mother.
I won't! I won't!
Lisa!
That will do with our ocean part liner.
Let see...
We've eleven altogether.
One. Two. Three. Four. Five. Six.
Seven. Eight. Nine. Ten. Eleven.
It comes, Dear.
Don't worry, dear.
I'll take care of everything.
The adjustment promised the trunk
said that...
Oh, either I'd lost half a minute...
or the station parted ear
How much would that be, please?
It's up to you, sir.
Up to me?
One dollar should be enough.
The guy promised the trunk
would be here on time.
With all the boxes...
One. Two. Three. Four. Five. Six.
Uh... how long will it take
if we send them through the third
Two weeks, maybe.
Two weeks... very good.
Now each of these... second class.
Third class...
Each of these... third class.
Yes...
Ah... what did I tell you.
When you're going to a thing,
do it one time
That is always nice.
Hello. Thank you.
You can unloaded it here.
Our train doesn't leave until 12:00.
Yes,12:00,darling.
The twelve!
Please don't get excited, dear
I'd be calm.
"Suddenly I knew
I couldn't live without you."
"I didn't know what I had in mind, or..."
"...what my parents would do
when they found me missing."
"All I wanted was to see you once more."
"To be near you again."
"To throw myself at your feet,
cling to you, and never leave you."
"Nothing else. Nothing else matters."
Alright, alright.
Oh, it's you, Lisa.
I thought now
that you're half way to Linze?
Didn't your train leave in about...
I forgot something.
"These rooms where I've lived,
have been filled with your music."
"Now they were empty."
"Would they ever come to life again?"
"Would I?"
"Only you could answer."
"So, I waited."
"Waited..."
"For what seemed endless hours
I set outside your door..."
"Try to keep myself awake."
"...afraid that
I might fall asleep and miss you."
"Then..."
Who is it?
Brown!
Good morning, Mr. Brown.
"And so, there was nothing left for me."
"I went to Linze."
"You who have always lived so freely..."
"Have you any idea
what life's like as a little garrison in
"I was eighteen now..."
"And was expected to take
my place in society."
Come now, Lisa.
Don't look down at your feet.
Please be tactful and
let him do the talking.
But not all the talking.
Do you hear me, Lisa?
Good morning, Colonel.
Good morning.
Mrs. Castler, Miss Castler.
Mr. Castler.
May I have the honor to
present you my nephew...
Leitenent Leonard Oncathelic...
I have the honor to kiss your hand.
Very pleased to make your acquaintance.
Thank you, Lieutenant.
Mr. Castler, I have the honor, sir.
I'm very pleased to make
your acquaintance.
Thank you, Lieutenant.
Thank you.
Allow me to present our daughter, Lisa.
Lieutenant Leonard.
Good morning...
Excuse me.
Do you like it here in Lance?
Quiet well.
It must seemed
very restfull living in Vienna?
I like Vienna.
Indeed.
What did you like about it?
Perhaps you were found of the music?
Yes.
We also have good music here.
Every other Saturday afternoon
they gave a concert on the co
Oh, really?
Perhaps someday you'll allow
me the honor to escorting you?
Very nice of you.
When there was a good chance,
I'd take part of it myself.
I played second trumpet.
Oh, how nice.
I must say I'm glad that you like music.
You see...
There's nothing wrong
with her if she meets the right people
Up! Up! Up! Up!
Up! Up! Up!
"The Lieutenant was right."
"Linze was a musical town."
"So twice a month
that's what I listened..."
"The Lieutenant and I."
Before the afternoon is over,
I'm sure we'll hear an announc
Nothing could please us more, Colonel.
Is that right, my dear?
Miss Lisa, this is a subject
which I wish to bring up for so
I trust you'd forgive me to
presume the action that I allow
It maybe unnecessary to mention that...
Eversince you first came
to my attention,
I've been most favorably impressed.
Thank you.
And I believe
that your parents are not opposed...
...my keeping company
that is dedicate with you.
But, Lieutenant, I...
Oh, please allow me to finish.
As far as my prospects are concerned,
You must be aware that...
It's generally pleased
by my uncle and others,
That I have a qualifications
for an ourstanding military car
It's no doubt of that.
Naturally, it's too soon to
discuss a definite step.
We should know each other
for a reasonable time...
But, Lieutenant...
I'm sorry, it's impossible.
It's impossible?
Please allow me to explain.
I must insist.
Is there someone else?
Yes.
I'm engaged to be married.
Engaged to be married?
I should've told you before,
But I didn't realize that how...
But all the time you've been in Linze,
I haven't seen anyone's company.
He doesn't live in Linza.
He lives in Vienna.
In Vienna?
He... he likes music, he's a musician.
But how can that be?
Your mother and father,
they gave my uncle the encouragement...
They don't know yet!
You're engaged to a man,
and your parents don't even know it?
Um...
I'm sorry, I...
Then, please.
Waiter, the wine. The wine.
Up! Up!
But I don't understand.
Lisa, sit down. What happened?
Nothing.
But after all...
But you must've said something.
What did you say to him?
I only told him the truth.
The truth! What do you mean the truth?
What did you say to him?
I told him, I wasn't free.
What...?
"My poor parents,
for them this was the end."
"For me, it was a new beginning."
"Vienna, when I saw her again,"
"Seemed to have taken
on a new splendor."
"All the time I've been away,"
"I thought longingly, it's your city."
"Now, it's our city."
"Madam Spitt's where I found work."
"It's the kind of establishment
where one learns many things
Miss Lisa, please.
Coming.
Hold your breath.
Miss Lisa, we're waithing.
Very pretty.
Yes.
Very.
Very charming. Very charming, indeed.
Do you think...
She is not like the others,
I don't understand that girl...
But every evening,
As soon as this shop are closes,
off she goes straight home.
Really?
"Madam Spitt spoke the truth."
"I was not like the others."
"Nobody waited for me."
"Off I went, not home..."
"But to the only place
that it ever seemed home to me."
"Night after night,
I returned to the same spot."
"You never noticed me...
until one evening."
I've seen you before, few nights ago.
Right here. Or... your live near here?
No.
You like to listen to the street singers?
Um... yes.
Neither do I.
I should introduce myself.
No. I know who you are.
I suppose sooner or later,
we have to decide where we're walk
I have something I should call off.
I'd never get to the place
where I start out for, anyway.
Pardon.
Excuse me.
Very charming.
Thank you.
Anything else I can do for you,
Mr. Brwon?
Will you please tell Mr. Bowlish,
I won't be at the rehearsal this evening.
Congratulations.
Bruce, is that gentleman free now?
Just moment, sir.
Don't you see I'm busy with Mr. Brown?
Now... how about Lady Lilian?
If she comes,
how am I going to tell her?
Well, tell her...
I'll tell her... It was most important
and you had to work.
Yes, that's it. That's fine.
I'm sure she will understand.
I'm sure.
Thank you.
Bye.
Stephen, I missed you yesterday.
I have to talk to you.
Later.
I saw the manager group at the conchter.
It's a young man I met...
His father owns half the colege to
I thought it was something
for one of your concerts.
If you just go outside...
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Tomorrow...
Now, don't be frighten.
If it's not to becoming,
the lobster would have no intention.
I was wrong. It is becoming.
Let see,
when do they have lobster again?
Friday. How about Friday?
A week is a long time.
How about Wednesday.
That's pheasant.
They have pheasant on Monday.
Could you possibly make it on Monday?
I've no engagement at all.
I've none, either.
We'll have dinner tomorrow night.
Dinner, that's all
Excuse me, Mr. Brown.
The lady in the next room,
If I'm not mistaken,
is The Countess Newesky.
Would you sign her the program
of this afternoon's concert?
Certainly.
She said, Mozart
himself could not have done better.
How nice of her.
There you are.
Thank the Countess for the compliment.
Thank you. Haybra.
The note is not the least she deserves.
Four years ago
when you played the D Minor.
You remember that?
The morning review, also.
Compare too young Mozart.
I was very young.
You like it?
Mar Poly Charli, it's called.
First thing you see
when you come down the other side of the
The Italians say,
it is such a good wine,
Because the grapes have
their roots in the vine,
And the eyes on the mountains.
Please...
Please what?
Please talk about yourself.
I believe you really want to hear about it.
Why?
Uh, never mind why.
The truth is,
I had rather an easy time of it.
People accepted my music very quickly.
Perhaps too quickly.
Sometimes it seemed easier
to please others than oneself.
What're you going to say?
You know you don't talk very much.
Well... I can't say very well. But...
Yes.
Sometimes,
I felt when you're playing that...
Go on.
That... your haven't quite found
what you're looking for.
How long have you
been hiding in my paino?
Uh, never mind explaining.
I just assume you're a sorcerous,
And that
you can make yourself very tiny.
It might be a good thing
to have a sorcerous friend.
Who knows?
You maybe able to help me someday.
How could I help you?
So, that's what you've been thinking?
You're a very stange girl.
Who ever you are,
where ever you came from...
Don't you have any problem?
Not... important ones.
It's been a long
while since anyone did that for me?
Stop here, please.
Woo... Ah.
Good evening, Mr. Brown.
Good evening.
Roses?
Yes. Please.
Nice red ones?
No. Red is the wrong color.
I think the white one would be perfect
This is a special occassion.
Here you are. Good night.
Good night, Mr. Brown.
Enjoy yourself.
Did I guess wright?
Is it your flower?
From now on it will be.
Would you like me to close it?
No.
Hah... and now to the park.
Do you think it would all be close?
I hope not.
I never come here in the season.
It's more pleasant in the winter.
I don't know why.
It's perhaps...
Because you prefer to imagine
how it will be in the spring.
Because if it's spring,
then it's nothing to imagine and to w
Is there anything about
me you don't know?
A few things.
For instance, one thing I don't know,
If one day they would
make a wax figure of you and put it th
Because you'll be so famous.
Well, if they do, will you pay your
penny to come in and see me?
If you come alive.
Now I see you as a little girl.
You do?
When my father was alive,
we traveled a lot.
He went nearly everywhere.
We've had a wonderful time.
I didn't know you traveled so much.
Oh, yes.
Perhaps we've been in some
of the same places.
No, I don't think so.
Where did you go?
Well, it was a long time. But...
For instance, there was Rio de Janeiro.
Beautiful, exotic,
real with its botanical garden.
Its Avenue palms, Sugarloaf fountain,
And the harbor where you can
look down and see the flying fi
We're in Venice.
Yes, we've arrived.
Where would you like to go next?
France? England? Russia?
Switzerland.
Excuse me a moment
while I talked to the engineer.
You and the lady,
are you enjoying the trip?
Very much.?
We're off to Switzerland.
There you go. Thank you.
Oh... thank you.
Switzerland.
So, you're looking
down at the flying fish. Then what?
Aren't you going to finish the trip?
Well, there weren't any trip,
do you mind?
You see, my father
had a friend in the Travel Bureau.
My father worked across the street.
He was an assistant super
attendant of the Municipal water?
And he used to bring photos home
with pictures in them.
And in the evening,
he'd put on his traveling coat.
That's what he called it,
'Cause I was very young.
And he'd say:
where should we go this evening?
And I would say: Verra Cruse.
Because it's a beautiful name.
And then he would say: um...
it's summer there,
You don't want to be roasted
like a coffee bean, do you?
So, you never did get there?
No. It's just like I tripped the land
with the midnight sun.
What stop are you in time?
The weather.
I thought of India.
But then father remembered
it was the raining season.
Your father was an expert on climates.
My mother used to say that...
He knew what the weather
was everywhere except home.
What mountain was that?
That's the Mt. MataHorn.
You've climbed it?
Um hum.
Tell me when you've climbed up
the mountain,
what then?
Well, you come down again.
Tell me more about your father.
Well, then he finally did go away.
He had the nicest eyes.
Yes, I can see them.
Why do you like to climb mountains?
Well, I suppose because,
No matter how high you climb,
there's always a higher one.
And you like to imagine
that the other one is even more wond
Like the spring in the park.
You know far too much about me already,
And I know almost nothing about you
Except you traveled a great deal.
0End of the line.
All change.
What now?
Where haven't we been?
We have no countries left.
Then we'll begin all over again.
There you are.
Thank you.
We'll revisit the scenes of your youth.
I don't know about them
but I'm going home.
Right after this number.
? Me too, if he is not paying
me 50 quarters.
I'd like to playing for married people.
They've got homes.
You're sorcerous.
Now I'm sure,
How else could we dance this way
Unless we've danced together before.
And if we had,
we should ever remember it.
Please.
Promise me something.
Anything.
But I don't even know where you live.
Promise me you won't vanish.
I won't be the one who vanishes.
We're here.
Thank you.
Who is it?
Brown.
Good morning, Mr. Brown.
(End of Side A)
Please be seated.
Lisa, leave it on.
Someone wants to see it.
Oh.
Real customer. Looks like a good one.
One moment.
You'll like this one, I'm sure.
I'm sure.
I like it very much.
Very much.
How did you find me?
I'm a good detective, what you think?
You are.
I'm afraid we have to put off
our play for tonight.
I couldn't go away without seeing you.
Where are you going?
Milano.
The whole orchestra are going.
We go to play at Chigano.
It's wonderful.
I've forgotten all about it.
It won't be long.
Just two weeks.
The train leaves at 5:30.
Do you suppose you could see me off?
I'll try.
I'll look for you then.
Good bye. Thank you.
Good-bye. You will be there.
How did it go?
He wasn't interested in the suit.
But... Madam,
could I leave a bit earlier today?
How early?
About 5:00.
Yes.
Sure.
Thank you, Madam.
Congratulations, my dear.
Stephan, the train is leaving.
Just a minute
How long have you been standing here?
I don't want to go. Do you believe that?
I'll be here when you get back.
Come on.
Yes.
Stephan, hurry, please.
I still know so little about you.
You like mistery.
That a woman like you exist,
and I found you.
That's mistery to me.
Say"Stephan",
the way you said it last night.
Stephan.
As if you've said it all your life.
Better hurry, sir.
Yes.
Good-bye.
Stephan.
Won't be long.
I'll be back in two weeks.
Good-bye. Two weeks.
"Two weeks... Stehpan,
how little you knew of yourself."
"That train was taking
you out of my life."
"He was a married man."
"Does he live here in Vienna?"
"If we knew who he was,"
"He might be willing
to accept his responsibility."
You won't tell us his name?
But you haven't the means
to take care of the child.
We'll get along.
It's your duty to tell us.
When a man does...
I'm feeling tired.
Would you go?
"You may wonder
why I never came to you for help."
"I wanted to be one woman
you've had known,"
"Who had asked you for nothing."
"My deep regret is
that you never saw your son."
"There were times during those years,
I prefer not to remember."
"But this I can assure you,"
"Whatever the cost,
he'd repayed me a thousand times."
"You'd have been proud of him, too."
"When he was almost nine."
"As much for his sake as mine,
I married."
"You know who my husband is."
"Yohan Stafe asked to marry me."
"Knowing the truth about us,
and about our child."
Oh. How lovely.
Thank you, Yohan.
What a nice birthday!
This..., and Stephan home.
You know,
I'm not good at saying such things.
But... Lisa, I want you to be
as happy as you may be.
If I were really deserving why,
I'll be ready on time.
You are happy?
You are?
"Why shouldn't I be?"
Let's say Good-night.
Is that your another talent?
He has a lot of talents,
but not until he finishes his milk.
Or for brushing his teeth.
Made in Switzerland.
Switzerland must be a very nice place,
don't you think?
Who gave it to you, darling?
Her Frank.
Who's Her Frank?
His music teacher.
He said that he thinks
that I'm nature talented.
For harmonica?
No. For music.
Oh.
Good night, Stephan.
Good night, sir.
Good night, darling.
Good night, mother.
Mother!
Yes!
I'll be right back.
You remember the last time,
first night I was home from school.
Um-hum, what about it?
When you went out,
you let me sleep in your room.
Alright.
It's a special concession
because it's your first night home
But hurry. I'm late.
In just a minute.
There's no hurry.
Good night, sir.
Good night.
You know, Stephan, it might be nicer...
If you could say "Good night,
father!"instead of"Good nigh
But I've always said it that way.
I think he'd like it
if you could manage to change it.
Suppose you said to me
"Good night, Madam."
It would sound very silly, wouldn't it?
Now, promise me you'd go to sleep,
and not wait up for me.
I promise.
Would you bring me
the program of the opera?
I promise.
Good night, Madam.
Good night, Sir.
After all when a person treats
you so much like his son,
He is make sense of your father.
Alright, mother, if you say so.
Good night.
"The course of our lives can
be changed by such little thing
"So many passing by,
each intent on his own problems."
"So many faces,
that one might be easily lost."
"I know now. Nothing happens by chance."
"Every moment is measured.
Every step is counted."
Curtain. Curtain going up.
Second act.
Curtain going up. Second act.
Look! Isn't that Stephan Brown?
He played last week.
Is that a concert tour?
Pleasure trip, most likely.
The way he's burning himself up,
it's a wonder he's still alive.
Ten years ago, he showed great promise.
Too bad.
With that talent,
he could've been a great pianist.
Perhaps talent is not enough.
Perhaps he's have too many talents.
Second act!
Curtain going up!
Sorry.
We're late.
You know the colonel is going...
Everyone is asking for you.
You've made a conquest.
My dear, you should have joined this.
"Suddenly, in that one moment."
"Every thing was in danger."
"Every thing I thought was safe."
"Somewhere out there were your eyes.
couldn't escape them.""Somewhere out there were yo
"It's like the first time I saw you."
"The years between were melting away."
I have a headache.
I'll take you home.
No. Please don't worry.
I'll be alright.
Please stay here.
Would you be kind enough
to give my husband a message.
He's in 17. Not now.
But after the show.
Tell him, I've decided to go home.
Tell him not to worry.
Thank you.
Call my carriage, please.
Yes, Madam.
Sergeant!
Excuse me.
You must realized
that where there's a pursuit.
And there'd also be a pursuer.
I've seen you somewhere, I know.
I followed you upstairs.
And watched you in your box.
But I couldn't place you.
And I had to speak with you.
I know how it sounds.
I assure you in this case that it's true.
Believe that, don't you?
Yes.
Thank you.
Now please, just a moment.
Is that any place we could have met,
that I might have seen
At one of my concerts?
There must have been sometime ago.
I haven't given any concerts
in Vienna lately.
Or anywhere else in that matter.
You don't play anymore?
Oh, it's not quite as final as that.
I always tell myself that,
"Beginning next week."
And when next week comes,
it's this week.
So, I wait for next week again.
What are you waiting for?
It's a very disturbing question.
My carriage...
You can't ask such a question,
and just walk away.
I have a feeling...
please don't think I'm mad.
I know it sounds strange.
I can't explain it.
But I feel that you understand
what I can't even say.
And that you can help me.
Have you ever shopped
for places like cards,
Hoping to find the one...
Lies somewhere at the edge
of your memory.
The one you've been waiting for.
But tonight, when I first saw you.
And later
when I watched you in the darkness.
It looked like one face amongst others.
Who are you?
Promise me, I'll see you again.
I must see you.
I don't know.
Yohan,
you don't think I want this to happen?
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
Lisa. We have a marriage.
Perhaps it's not all you once
hoped for. But...
You've a home, and your son.
People who care for you.
I know that, Yohan.
I'll do anything to avoid hurting you.
But I can't help it.
And your son?
Can you avoid hurting him?
I have to calm down and see that.
There're such things as honor,
and decency.
I told myself that hundred times
this one evening.
You talk like it is out of your hands.
It's not, Lisa.
You have a will.
You can do what's right,
what's best for you.
Or you can throw away your life.
I have no hopes whatsoever.
That's romantic nonsense.
Is it?
Yohan, I can't help it.
I can't dispute that.
What about him?
Can him help himself, either?
I know now that he needs me
as much as I always needed him.
Isn't it a bit late for him
to find that out?
We're home, sir.
Good night.
Good night, sir.
Lisa. If you do this,
you can never turn back.
You know that, don't you?
Yes.
I warn you. I shall do everything in
my power to prevent it.
Hello, darling. Wake up.
It's time to go to your own room.
Did you have a nice time?
Yes, darling.
Good night, father.
Good night.
Did you hear? I just said it.
Yes, darling.
Tell me about the opera...
was it exciting?
How's that?
You're wonderful.
You've always been a wonderful boy.
You know how much that it's meant to me?
Be so proud of you, always.
I know it.
Don't worry, mother.
Two weeks will go like an express train.
You sure you're coming?
Of course. I promise.
You can even get
my room in the village for me.
I'll get you the same
one you're there last time.
The one with the balcony.
Didn't I tell you
that compartment was quaranteened?
I'm sorry, Madam.
This compartment had to be closed up.
I'll take you to the next cart forwards.
That's good.
I'll be near the local motive.
I'll take the box.
Do we have two local motives
on our train?
We usually get along with one.
But I talked to the engineer.
How about that one over there?
You can have two seats in there.
He's traveling alone.
Don't worry about it, Madam.
I'll take good care of him.
We leave in about a minute.
Better hurry and get your seat.
You'll see better if you sit over here.
And if you get chilly,
you can put up the window.
Yes, mother.
Stephan. You know how I've
longed for you to being home.
And now I can't even explain.
I hope some day, very soon...
I'll be able to give you a reason.
But now, you just have to believe
that it's for your own goo
I don't mind going back so much.
Especially when you're coming so soon.
It'd be like two vocations.
Alright, darling.
I'll show you the new walk
we found since you're there last
Better get out, lady.
You'll write me often, won't you?
Yes mother But I can't write very often.
We've only two weeks.
Good-bye, mother. Two weeks.
Make way, please.
What happened?
Someone hurt?
No reason to get alarmed.
They said that it's typhus.
Typhus?
Yes. Typhus on the train.
Yes. Madam.
Yes. Mr. Brown. Stephan Brown.
Brown? One moment, please.
Fritz!
Um?
Could you tell me has Mr. Brown
been here this evening?
Oh, Mr. Brown is no longer
a customer of ours.
Not for sometime.
Mr. Brown these days
is more likely to be found in the Ritz.
Thank you.
Good evening, Madam.
I still have nice flowers left.
I'm closing up.
And I've saved you
a nice bouquet. Very cheap.
I'll take those, the white ones.
Don't bother wrapping them up.
Doesn't matter.
Now, drive.
Drive on!
Stephan Brown. Is he in?
Thank you.
This is a surprise.
But I assure you're a very happy one.
John didn't prepare me
for such pleasant occassion.
I thought last night...
The darkness might've
been tricks with my eyes.
You're even more
beautiful than I imagined.
Very kind of you.
This is just the hour
for a bit late supper.
Or is it too late?
Oh, it makes no different.
You're here.
As far as I'm concerned,
all the clocks in the world will st
Exuse me a moment.
John!
John, I'm sorry to send you out so late.
Would you go out to the coners,
and get a few things.
We're going to have supper.
The usual things.
John makes life possible for
a hopelessly single man.
She fascinates you, too!
Do you remember...
The Greek built the
Statue of God they didn't know.
But hope someday would come to them.
But mine happened to be a Goddess.
And you've never found her?
For years, I never woke in the morning,
But I said to myself,
"Perhaps today she will come.
My life will be really to begin."
Sometimes it seemed very near.
But now I'm older, I know better.
Even for yourself,
you don't play anymore?
Oh, I remember last night,
you're kind of being interested...
I forgot John locked
it when I went away.
Nowadays, I'm away quite a lot of time.
I'll ask him for the key
when he comes back.
You wear very lovely.
It's a beautiful dress.
Thank you.
How could you do that?
Give it up altogether.
Well, if you're so curious,
I'll tell you.
One night I came back to this room.
I had given a concert like
all the others.
Not bad, and not worse.
Afterwards,
they said all the usual things.
The things you say
when you are not really convinced.
So, I happened to look into the mirror.
This one here.
The young protege was no longer young.
Certainly wasn't perpetual.
Since then, I found out a thing to do.
More amuzing things.
I knew last night. Didn't you?
I haven't even
offered to fix you a drink.
Stephan.
Yes.
I came here...
I have something to tell you.
If it's something to do with you,
l"m very interested.
It has to do with us.
We can't possibily
be serious this early in the morning.
At least not without
a glass of champagne.
Won't be a minute.
Champagne tastes much better
after midnight, don't you think
Much better.
I've just came back from America.
It's a fascinating country.
The men are fond of money.
And their wives... are fond of Europeans.
Must have been a wonderful trip?
Have you travelled a great deal?
I couldn't get
you out of my mind all day.
No, I don't believe you.
If I only knew you're coming...
To tell you the truth,
I never dared to hope
that you could've managed so soon.
But you're so cleaver,
you've arranged it so beautifully.
You know, you're a very strange woman.
Am I?
Something you've said last night,
it keeps running through my
What was that?
I'll tell you in just a moment
as soon as I get the ice.
Are you getting lonely out there.
Very lonely.
"I come to tell you about us."
"To offer you my whole life."
"But you didn't even remember me."
Can I take you somewhere, young lady?
Anywhere at all?
It makes no difference.
"I don't remember where I went."
"Time will pass me."
"Not in days, or in hours."
"But in the distance
that put between us."
"Now I think again.
I went to my son."
"But is was too late."
"He died last night from typhus."
"Without even knowing I was there."
"Now I'm alone."
"My head throbs,
and my temple are burning."
"Perhaps God had been kind.
I, too, have caught the fever."
"If this letter reaches you,
believe this..."
"That I love you now as
I've always loved you."
"My life can be measured...
"By the moments
that I've with you and our child."
"If only you could've shared
those moments."
"If only you could've recognized
what was always yours."
"Could've found whar was never lost."
"If only..."
You remembered her?
Lisa...
Bring my things.
Ready, gentleman?
"If only you could've recognized
what was always yours."
"Could've found what was never lost..."
The End.