Mathematicians won the war.
Mathematicians broke
the Japanese codes...
and built the A-bomb.
Mathematicians... like you.
The stated goal of the
Soviets is global communism.
In medicine or economics,
in technology or space,
battle lines are being drawn.
To triumph, we need results.
Publishable, applicable results.
Now who among you will be the next Morse?
The next Einstein?
Who among you will
be the vanguard
of democracy, freedom,
and discovery?
Today, we bequeath
America's future
into your able hands.
Welcome to Princeton, gentlemen.
MAN: It's not enough Hansen
won the Carnegie Scholarship.
MAN #2: No, he has to
have it all for himself.
It's the first time
the Carnegie prize
has been split.
Hansen's all bent.
MAN #2: Rumor is he's got his
sights set on Wheeler Lab,
the new military
think tank at M.I.T.
They're only taking
one this year.
Hansen's used to
being picked first.
Oh, yeah, he's wasted on math.
He should be running
for president.
There could be a
mathematical explanation
for how bad your tie is.
[Laughs]
Thank you.
Neilson, symbol cryptography.
Neils here broke a Jap code.
Helped rid the world of fascism.
At least that's what he
tells the girls, eh, Neils?
The name's Bender.
Atomic physics.
-And you are?
-Am I late?
-Yes.
-Yes, Mr. Sol.
Oh, good. Uh, hi.
-SOL: Richard Sol.
-NEILSON: The burden of genius.
-BENDER: There he is.
-So many supplicants, and so little time.
-Mr. Sol.
-How are you, sir?
-Ah, Bender.
-Nice to see you.
-Congratulations, Mr. Hansen.
-Ah, thank you.
I'll take another.
Excuse me?
A thousand pardons. I simply
assumed you were the waiter.
-Play nice, Hansen.
-Nice is not Hansen's strong suit.
HANSEN: Honest mistake.
Well, Martin Hansen.
It is Martin, isn't it?
Why, yes, John, it is.
I imagine you're getting quite
used to miscalculation.
I've read your pre-prints...
Both of them.
The one on Nazi ciphers,
and the other one on
non-linear equations,
and I am supremely confident
that there is not
a single seminal
or innovative idea in
either one of them.
Enjoy your punch.
[Chuckles]
Gentlemen, meet John Nash,
the mysterious West
Virginia genius.
The other winner of the
distinguished Carnegie Scholarship.
-BENDER: Oh, okay.
-SOL: Oh, yeah?
BENDER: Of course.
[Choral Record Playing]
[Coughs] Oh, Christ.
The prodigal roommate arrives.
Roommate?
Oh, God, no.
-Ugh.
-[Music Slows, Stops]
Did you know that
having a hangover is...
Is not having enough
water in your body
to run your Krebs cycles?
Which is exactly
what happens to you
when you're dying of thirst.
So, dying of thirst...
would probably feel
pretty much like the hangover
that finally bloody kills you.
[Chuckles]
John Nash?
Hello.
Charles Herman.
Pleased to meet you.
PLAYER: All right, well done.
CHARLES: Well, it's official.
I'm almost human again.
Officer, I saw the
driver who hit me.
His name was Johnny Walker.
[Mimics Rim shot]
Whew.
Well, I got in last night
in time for...
English department cocktails.
Cock was mine,
the tail belonged to a
particularly lovely young thing
with a passion for...
D.H. Lawrence. You're not
easily distracted, are you?
-I'm here to work.
-Hmmm, are you? Right.
I see. Crikey!
Is my roommate a dick?
Hmm?
Listen.
If we can't break the ice...
How about we drown it?
So what's your story?
You the poor kid that never got
to go to Exeter or Andover?
Despite my privileged
upbringing,
I'm actually quite
well-balanced.
I have a chip on both shoulders.
[Chuckles]
Maybe you're just better
with the old integers
than you are with people.
My first grade
teacher, she told me
that I was born with
two helpings of brain,
but only half a
helping of heart.
[Chuckles]
Wow! She sounds lovely!
The truth is that I...
I don't like people much.
And they don't much like me.
But why,
with all your obvious
wit and charm?
[Laughs]
Seriously, John.
Mathematics...
Mathematics is never going to
lead you to a higher truth.
And you know why?
'Cause it's boring.
It's really boring. [Chuckles]
You know half these schoolboys
are already published?
I cannot waste time with
these classes and...
these books.
[Coughs]
Memorizing the weaker
assumptions of lesser mortals!
[Chuckles]
I need to look through...
to the governing dynamics.
Find a truly original idea.
That's the only way I'll
ever distinguish myself.
It's the only way
that I'll ever...
Matter.
Yes.
HANSEN: All right, who's next?
No, I've played enough "go"
for one day, thank you.
-Come on.
-I... I hate this game.
Cowards, all of you!
None of you rise to
meet my challenge?
Come on, Bender. Whoever wins,
Sol does his laundry
all semester.
-Does that seem unfair to anyone else?
-Not at all.
-BENDER: Look at him.
-Nash!
Taking a reverse constitutional?
I'm hoping to extract
an algorithm
to define their movement.
-Oh.
-Psycho.
SOL: Hey, Nash, I thought
you dropped out.
You ever going to
go to class or...
Classes will dull your mind.
Destroy the potential for
authentic creativity.
Oh, oh, I didn't know that.
Nash is going to stun
us all with his genius.
Which is another way of saying
he doesn't have the
nerve to compete.
You scared?
Terrified.
Mortified. Petrified.
Stupefied... by you.
No starch.
Pressed and folded.
Let me ask you something, John.
Be my guest, Martin.
Bender and Sol here
correctly completed
Allen's proof of
Peyrot's Conjecture.
Adequate work...
without innovation.
Oh. I'm flattered.
You flattered?
Flattered.
And I've got two weapons briefs
under security
review by the D.O.D.
Derivative drivel.
But Nash achievements.
zero.
I'm a patient man, Martin. Is
there an actual question coming?
What if you never come up
with your original idea?
Huh?
How will it feel when I'm
chosen for Wheeler...
and you're not?
What if you lose?
BENDER: Ah, there it is.
[Chuckles]
You should not have won.
Hmmm.
I had the first move, my...
my play was perfect.
The hubris of the defeated.
The game is flawed.
Gentlemen, the great John Nash.
CHARLES: You've been
in here for two days.
You know Hansen's just
published another paper?
I can't even find a
topic for my doctorate.
Well, on the bright side,
you've invented window art.
This is a group playing
touch football.
This is a cluster of pigeons
fighting over bread crumbs.
And this here is a woman who is
chasing a man who stole her purse.
John, you watched a mugging.
That's weird.
In competitive behavior
someone always loses.
Well, my niece knows that, John,
and she's about this high.
See, if I could
derive an equilibrium
where prevalence is a
non-singular event,
where nobody loses,
can you imagine the effect that
would have on conflict scenarios
-and arms negotiations...
-When did you last eat?
... Currency exchange?
You know, food.
You have no respect for cognitive
reverie, you know that?
Yes. But pizza...
Now, pizza I have
enormous respect for.
And of course beer.
I have respect for beer.
I have respect for beer!
-BENDER: Good evening, Neils. Ladies...
-HANSEN: Hey, Nash.
Who's winning? You or you?
-BENDER: Evening, Nash.
-SOL: Hey, guys.
Hey, Nash.
WOMAN: He's looking
at you for sure.
Hey, Nash.
Neils is trying to
get your attention.
-BENDER: You're joking.
-SOL: Oh, no.
-Go with God.
-Come back a man.
-Fortune favors the brave.
-Bombs away.
Gentlemen, might I remind
you that my odds of success
dramatically improve
with each attempt?
This is going to be classic.
Maybe you wanna buy me a drink.
I don't exactly know
what I'm required to say
in order for you to have
intercourse with me,
but could we assume
that I said all that?
Essentially we're talking
about fluid exchange, right?
So, could we just go
straight to the sex?
Oh, that was sweet.
Have a nice night, asshole!
-[Man Laughs]
-NEILSON: Ladies, wait!
CHARLES: I...
I especially liked the bit about
fluid exchange. It was...
... really charming.
PROFESSOR: Walk with me, John.
I've been meaning
to talk with you.
The faculty is completing
mid-Year reviews.
We're deciding which placement
applications to support.
-Wheeler, sir. That would be
-And....
-my first choice. And actually, I don't
-John...
-really have a second choice, sir.
-I know, John...
-I don't really have a second choice.
-John, your fellows have attended classes.
They've written papers.
They've published.
I'm still searching,
sir, for my...
-Your original idea, yes, I know.
-Governing dynamics, sir.
It's very clever,
John, but I'm afraid
it's just not
nearly good enough.
-May I?
-Thank you.
I've been working on
manifold embedding.
My bargaining stratagems are
starting to show some promise.
If you could just arrange
another meeting,
if you'd be kind enough,
with Professor Einstein...
-I've repeatedly asked you for that, sir.
-Now, John.
-I'd be able to show him
-John...
-my revisions on his...
John.
Do you see what they're
doing in there?
-PROFESSOR: Congratulations.
-MAX: Thank you so much.
Congratulations, Professor Max.
-MAX: Thank you, sir.
-Thank you.
It's the pens.
Reserved for a member
of the department
that makes the achievement
of a lifetime.
Now, what do you see, John?
Recognition.
Well done, Professor, well done.
Well, try seeing accomplishment.
Is there a difference?
John,
you haven't focused.
I'm sorry, but up to this point,
your record doesn't warrant
any placement at all.
Good day.
And my compliments to you, sir.
Thank you so much.
I can't see it.
[Whimpers]
-Aah!
-Jesus Christ, John.
I can't fail.
-This is all I am.
-Come on, let's go out. Come on.
-I got to get something done.
-John!
-I-I can't keep staring into space...
-John, it's enough!
Got to face the wall,
follow their rules...,
You wanna do some damage?
-That's fine...
-read their books...
-But don't mess around...
-Do their classes.
Come on! Go on, bust your head!
Kill yourself.
John, do it. Don't mess around.
Bust your head! Go on,
bust that worthless
head wide open.
Goddamn it, Charles! What
the hell is your problem?!
It's not my problem.
And it's not your problem.
It's their problem.
Your answer isn't face the wall.
It's out there...
where you've been working.
-[Panting]
-[Gasps]
That was heavy.
That Isaac Newton
fellow was right.
-He was onto something.
-Clever boy.
[Giggles]
JOHN: Don't worry, that's mine.
I'll come and get
it in a minute.
-[Both laughing]
-Oh, God.
-NEILSON: Incoming, gentlemen.
-SOL: Ay-Yi-Yi.
[Sighs] Deep breaths.
SOL: Nash, you
might want to stop
shuffling your papers
for five seconds.
I will not buy you
gentlemen beer.
BENDER: Oh, we're not
here for beer, my friend.
-JOHN: Oh.
-[Sol Chuckles]
Does anyone else feel she should
be moving in slow motion?
Will she want a large
wedding, ya think?
Shall we say swords, gentlemen?
-Pistols at dawn?
-Have you remembered nothing?
Recall the lessons
of Adam Smith,
the father of modern economics.
"In competition..."
SOL AND NEILSON: "individual
ambition serves the common good".
-Exactly.
-Every man for himself, gentlemen.
BENDER: And those who strike out
are stuck with her friends.
HANSEN: I'm not
gonna strike out.
SOL: You can lead a blonde to water,
but you can't make her drink.
-I don't think he said that.
-SOL: Nobody move...
She's looking over here.
She's looking at Nash.
HANSEN: Oh, God. He may
have the upper hand now,
but wait until he
opens his mouth.
-[Laughing]
-Remember the last time?
BENDER: Oh, yes, that was
one for the history books.
Adam Smith needs revision.
What are you talking about?
If we all go for the blonde...
we block each other.
Not a single one of
us is gonna get her.
So then we go for her friends,
but they will all give
us the cold shoulder
because nobody likes
to be second choice.
Well, what if no one
goes for the blonde?
We don't get in
each other's way,
and we don't insult
the other girls.
That's the only way we win.
That's the only way
we all get laid.
[Laughs]
Adam Smith said
the best result comes
from everyone in the group doing
what's best for himself, right?
That's what he said, right?
-Right.
-Incomplete.
Incomplete, okay?
Because the best
result will come...
from everyone in the group
doing what's best for himself...
and the group.
Nash, if this is some way for you
to get the blonde on your own,
-You can go to hell.
-Governing dynamics, gentlemen.
Governing dynamics.
Adam Smith...
was wrong.
-SOL: Oh, here we go.
-NEILSON: Careful, careful.
Thank you.
"C" of "S" equals "C" of "T".
[Muttering]
You do realize this
flies in the face
-of a 150 years of economic theory?
-Yes, I do, sir.
That's rather presumptuous,
don't you think?
It is, sir. [Stifled Laugh]
Well, Mr. Nash,
with a breakthrough
of this magnitude,
I'm confident you will get
any placement you like.
Wheeler Labs,
they'll ask you to recommend
two team members.
[Whispering] Yes!
Stills and Frank are
excellent choices.
Sol and Bender, sir.
Sol and Bender are
extraordinary mathematicians.
Has it occurred to you, Mr.
Nash, that Sol and Bender
might have plans of their own?
[Laughing]
-Baby!
-Wheeler, we made it!
-Cheers, cheers, cheers!
-To... oh! Oh!
Okay, awkward moment, gentlemen.
Umm...
hmm.
Governing dynamics.
-Congratulations, John.
-Thanks.
-Toast!
-To Wheeler Labs!
NEILSON: To Wheeler!
MAN: General, the analyst
from Wheeler Lab is here.
Dr. Nash, your coat?
Thank you, sir.
Doctor. General, this is Wheeler
team leader Dr. John Nash.
Glad you could come, Doctor.
Hello.
Right this way.
We've been intercepting radio
transmissions from Moscow.
The computer can't
detect a pattern,
but I'm sure it's code.
JOHN: Why is that, General?
Ever just know something, Dr.
Nash?
Constantly.
GENERAL: We've developed
several ciphers.
If you'd like to review
our preliminary data...
Doctor?
NASH'S VOICE: 6-7-3-7,
0-3-6...
[Mental Voice]
8-4-9-4.
[Continues Listing Numbers]
9-1-4-0-3-4.
I need a map.
46-13-08,
67-46-90.
Starkey Corners, Maine.
48-03-01,
91-26-35
Prairie Portage, Minnesota.
These are latitudes
and longitudes.
There are a least ten others.
They appear to be routing orders
across the border into the U.S.
Extraordinary.
Gentlemen, we need
to move on this.
Who's big brother?
You've done your country
a great service, son.
-Captain!
-Yes, sir.
Accompany Dr. Nash.
What are the Russians
moving, general?
Captain Rogers will escort you
to the unrestricted
area, Doctor.
Thank you.
CAPTAIN: Dr. Nash,
follow me, please.
MAN ON RADIO: None
of those who have
said they don't like the method
have told us any other
method they could use
that would be effective.
-And when you hear...
-DRIVER: It's Dr. Nash.
All right.
-Thank you, sir.
-Home run at the Pentagon?
Have they actually taken
the word "classified"
out of the dictionary?
Oh, hi. The air
conditioning broke again.
How am I supposed to be
in here saving the world
-if I'm melting?
-Our hearts go out to you, John.
You know, two trips to the
Pentagon in four years.
That's two more than we've had.
It gets better, John.
Just got our latest
scintillating assignment.
You know, the Russians
have the H-bomb,
the Nazis are repatriating
South America,
the Chinese have a standing
army of 2.8 million,
and I am doing stress
tests on a dam.
Hey, look, you made the
cover of Fortune... again.
Please note the use of the
word "you", not "we".
That was supposed to be just me.
Oh. [Laughs]
So not only do they rob
me of the Fields medal,
now they put me on the
cover of Fortune magazine
with these hacks, these
scholars of trivia.
John, exactly what's
the difference
between genius and most genius?
Quite a lot.
He's your son.
Anyway, you've got 10 minutes.
I've always got 10 minutes.
SOL: Before your new class?
Can I not get a note from
a doctor or something?
You are a doctor, John, and no.
Now, come on, you
know the drill,
we get these beautiful
facilities,
M.I.T. gets America's
great minds of today
teaching America's great
minds of tomorrow.
Poor bastards.
Now, have a nice day at school.
The bell's ringing.
[Door Opens]
The eager young
minds of tomorrow.
[Loud Jackhammering]
Can we leave one
open, Professor?
It's really hot, sir.
Your comfort comes second
to my ability to
hear my own voice.
Personally,
I think this class
will be a waste...
of your...
And what is infinitely worse...
my time.
However, here we are. So...
... you may attend or not.
You may complete your
assignments at your whim.
We have begun.
Miss.
Excuse me!
-Excuse me!
-Hey, hey!
Hi!
Um, we have a little problem.
It's extremely hot in here
with the windows closed and
extremely noisy with them open.
So, I was wondering if there
was any way you could,
I don't know, maybe work someplace
else for about 45 minutes?
-WORKER: Not a problem.
-Thank you so much!
-At a break!
-Got it!
WORKER: Let's go. Let's
clean it a little bit!
As you will find in multivariable
calculus, there is often a...
a number of solutions
for any given problem.
As I was saying,
this problem here
will take some of you
many months to solve.
For others among you,
it will take you the term
of your natural lives.
MAN: Professor Nash.
William Parcher.
Big brother,
at your service.
What can I do for the
Department of Defense?
Are you going to
give me a raise?
Let's take a walk.
-Impressive work at the Pentagon.
-Yes, it was.
Oppenheimer used to say,
"Genius sees the answer
before the question."
You knew Oppenheimer?
His project was under
my supervision.
Which project?
That project.
It's not that simple, you know?
Well, you ended the war.
We incinerated 150,000
people in a heartbeat.
Great deeds come at great cost, Mr.
Parcher.
Well, conviction, it turns out,
is a luxury of those on
the sidelines, Mr. Nash.
I'll try and keep that in mind.
So, John, no family,
no close friends...
Why is that?
JOHN: I like to think it's
because I'm a lone wolf.
But mainly it's because
people don't like me.
[Chuckles]
Well, there are
certain endeavors
where your lack of
personal connection
would be considered
an advantage.
-This is a secure area.
-They know me.
Have you ever been here?
We were told during
our initial briefing
that these warehouses
were abandoned.
That's not precisely accurate.
[Low Radio Chatter]
[Tapes Screeching]
[Sirens, Man Speaking Russian]
By telling you what I'm
about to tell you,
I am increasing your
security clearance
to top secret.
Disclosure of secure information
can result in imprisonment.
Get it?
What operation?
Those are a good idea.
This factory is in Berlin.
We seized it at the
end of the war.
Nazi engineers were attempting
to build a portable atomic bomb.
The Soviets reached this facility before
we did, and we lost the damn thing.
The routing orders
at the Pentagon,
they were about
this, weren't they?
The Soviets aren't as
unified as people believe.
A faction of the Red Army
calling itself Novaya Svobga,
"the New Freedom", has
control of the bomb
and intends to detonate it on U.S.
soil.
Their plan is to incur
maximum civilian casualties.
Parcher. Man is capable
of as much atrocity
as he has imagination.
New Freedom has sleeper
agents here in the U.S.
McCarthy is an idiot,
but unfortunately that
doesn't make him wrong.
New Freedom communicates
to its agents
through codes imbedded in
newspapers and magazines,
and that's where you come in.
You see, John,
what distinguishes you
is that you are,
quite simply,
the best natural code-breaker
I have ever seen.
What exactly is it that
you would like me to do?
Commit this list of
periodicals to memory.
Scan each new issue,
find any hidden codes,
decipher them.
DOCTOR: Place your
chin on the chin rest.
-Stare into the light.
-MAN: Pulse 88, regular.
Okay, this may be a
little uncomfortable.
[Groans]
That's got a little zap
to it, doesn't it?
He just implanted
a radium diode.
Don't worry, it's safe.
The isotope decays predictably.
As a result, these numbers
change over time.
They're the access codes
to your drop spot.
So what am I now, a spy?
-[Knocking]
-Come.
Boy, you must be
really important.
It's all right, Mike.
What are you working on?
Classified.
Everyone waited half an hour.
For?
Class.
You missed class today.
Oh. I suspect that...
nobody missed me.
[Chuckles]
The problem that you
left on the board...
I solved it.
Oh, no you didn't.
You didn't even look.
I never said that the Vector
Fields were rational functions.
Your solution is elegant.
Though on this
particular occasion,
ultimately incorrect.
You're still here.
I'm still here.
Why?
I'm wondering, Professor Nash,
if I can ask you to dinner.
You do eat, don't you?
Oh, on occasion, yeah.
[Chuckles]
Table for one. Prometheus
alone chained to the rock
with the bird circling
overhead, you know how it is.
[Laughs]
No, I expect that
you wouldn't...
You wouldn't know.
If you leave your
address with my office,
I'll pick you up Friday at 8:00
and we'll eat.
One-One more thing.
Do you have a name,
or should I just keep
calling you "miss"?
Governor, may I present...
-Miss Alicia Larde.
-How do you do?
-Professor, please. You and the governor.
Wait, one second. I'm sorry.
I want a copy of this.
First big date and
all, you know.
So, you boys need to look good.
Which is not a state you find
yourselves in altogether naturally.
There. Better.
-I'm surprising him.
-You just keep on surprising him.
Professor.
God must be a painter.
Why else would we
have so many colors?
So you're a painter?
That's not actually what I said,
but, yes...
I am.
Here.
Me.
Your date?
Practice human interaction
and social comportment.
That's a plan.
Champagne would be lovely.
I'll be outside.
I will get the champagne.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you for that.
No, keep it.
I believe in deciding
things will be good luck.
Do you?
No.
I don't believe in luck.
But I do believe in
assigning value to things.
Oh.
I once tried to count them all.
I actually made it to 4,348.
You are exceptionally odd.
I bet you're very
popular with the girls.
A pair of odd ducks, then.
Mmm.
Pick a shape.
What?
Pick a shape. An animal...
anything.
Okay.
An umbrella.
Do it again.
[Chuckles]
-Do it again.
-All right.
-What would you like?
-Do, uh...
an octopus.
[Dog Barking]
[Alicia Chuckles]
ALICIA: You don't
talk much, do you?
I can't talk to you
about my work, Alicia.
I don't mean work.
I find that polishing
my interactions
in order to make them sociable
requires a tremendous effort.
I have a tendency to
expedite information flow...
by being direct.
I often don't get a
pleasant result.
Try me.
All right.
I find you attractive.
Your aggressive moves towards me
indicate that you
feel the same way.
But still, ritual
requires that we
continue with a number
of platonic activities
before we have sex.
I am proceeding with
those activities,
but in point of actual fact,
all I really want to do is have
intercourse with you as soon as possible.
Are you gonna slap me now?
How was that result?
GIRL: What are you doing?
I'm attempting to isolate
patterned re-occurrences
within periodicals over time...
and you?
You talk funny, Mr. Nash.
Do I know you?
My uncle says you're very
smart but not very nice,
so I shouldn't pay no mind
if you're mean to me.
And who might your uncle be?
The prodigal roommate...
returns.
[Chuckles]
-Come here.
-Charles, Charles, Charles.
My sister...
got herself killed
in a car crash.
Not too far now, Marcee!
Her cowboy husband was too drunk
to know that he was
too drunk to drive.
So, I took her in.
-She's so small.
-She's young, John. That's how they come.
I'm at Harvard...
doing the great
author's workshop.
D.H. Bloody Lawrence.
I really do think you should
buy yourself a new book.
[Chuckles]
Well, I've been reading
a lot about you.
How are you, John?
At first all my work
here was trivial,
but a new assignment
came up and...
I can't really tell
you any details.
Top secret? Black bag?
Black ops?
Something like that.
-And, uh...
-Yes?
Well, I... I met a girl.
-No! A human girl?
-Homo sapiens.
-A biped?
-Yup. And contrary to all probabilities,
she finds me attractive on a
number of different levels.
[Laughs] Really?
God, that's wonderful.
There's no accounting
for taste, is there?
Should I marry her?
Oh, God. Right.
I mean, everything's going well.
The job is fine. I
have enough money.
It all seems to add up.
But how do you know for sure?
Nothing's ever for sure, John.
That's the only sure
thing I do know.
WAITER: Good evening.
Alicia, please don't be angry.
I just lost track
of time at work...
-again.
-Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry.
I didn't have time to wrap it.
Happy birthday.
The refractive faces
of the glass, you see,
they create a full
wavelength dispersal,
so if you look inside
it, you can see...
-Every possible color.
Yeah.
Remember you said that time
God must be a painter,
because of all the colors?
At the governor's house...
you said that.
I didn't think you
were listening.
I'm always listening.
It's beautiful.
[Chuckles]
Alicia, does our relationship
warrant long-term commitment?
'Cause I need some
kind of proof,
some kind of verifiable,
empirical data.
[Laughs]
I'm sorry, just give
me a moment to...
redefine my girlish
notions of romance.
A proof?
Verifiable data.
Um... okay.
Well, how big is the universe?
Infinite.
How do you know?
I know because all the
data indicate it.
-But it hasn't been proven yet?
-No.
-You haven't seen it.
How do you know for sure?
I don't, I just believe it.
Mmm.
It's the same with
love, I guess.
Now,
the part that you don't know...
is if I want to marry you.
[Applause]
Smile for the camera!
Well done!
Oh, sweet pea.
-I love you.
-Congratulations.
Hey, Sol.
WOMAN: You look beautiful.
SOL: Hi, how are you?
ALICIA: Hey, Sol.
-WOMAN: Bye-bye.
-MAN: Bye, now.
-Bye!
Be safe!
[Gate Opens]
Get In. Hurry.
They're following us.
Who's... Who's following us?
The drop's been compromised.
-[Gunfire]
-Parcher. Get down!
-And stay down.
-[Horn Honks]
-[Pants]
-[Horn Honking]
[Gun Firing]
-Here, take this.
-I ain't shooting anybody.
-Take the goddamn gun!
-No!
Son of a...
[Screams]
You stay back. Don't move.
[Tires Screeching]
ALICIA: John?
Hi.
Where were you?
-S-Sol...
-Yeah, I talked to Sol.
He said you left the
office hours ago.
Why didn't you call me?
Are you all right?
Honey?
[Bolt Locking]
John...
Please, talk to me.
Tell me what happened.
John, open the door.
Come on, open the door!
Let me in!
Talk to me!
John!
Open the door!
[Panting]
WOMAN: Watch for cars, kids.
[Door Opens, Closes]
John.
William.
This is not what
I signed on for.
Every time a car backfires
or a door slams...
I understand... better than
you could possibly imagine.
You need to calm down, John.
Now listen to me. We're
closing in on the bomb,
in large part due to your work.
Now don't you think your fear
is a small price to pay?
William, my circumstance
has changed.
Alicia's pregnant.
I told you attachments
were dangerous.
You chose to marry the girl.
I did nothing to prevent it.
The best way to ensure
everybody's safety
is for you to
continue your work.
Well, I'll just quit.
You won't.
Why would I not?
Because I keep the Russians
from knowing you work for us.
You quit working for me,
I quit working for you.
Parcher!
John, you all right?
John?
Turn it off! Turn off the light!
Why would you do that?
Why would you turn the light on?
What is wrong with you?
You have to go to your sister's.
I left the car out the back.
You take Commonwealth.
-No side streets,
-John.
you stay where it's crowded.
John, I'm not going anywhere!
When you get to your sister's,
you wait for me to call you.
-No, I'm not going.
-Just get your things.
-I'm not leaving...
-stop! Stop it!
Please, Alicia.
I'll explain when I can.
MARCEE: Uncle John!
Uncle John!
[Growls]
-Hey, baby girl!
-[Marcee Laughing]
Wow, someone needed a hug!
I saw you on the slate
and I thought to myself,
"How can I miss seeing
a guest lecture"
"by the inimitable John Nash?"
What's wrong?
I got myself into something. I
think I might need some help.
Well, now you tell
me, what is it?
WOMAN: Professor Nash!
Welcome!
After?
JOHN: So, we see that the...
the zeroes,
of the Reimann zeta function,
correspond to singularities
in space-time,
singularities in space-time...
And conventional
number theory...
it breaks down in the face
of relativistic exploration.
Sometimes our expectations
are betrayed by the numbers.
Variables are impossible
to assign any...
rational value.
Professor Nash!
-Hold it!
-Professor Nash?
Professor Nash,
let's avoid a scene, shall we?
What do you want?
My name is Rosen,
Dr. Rosen. I'm a psychiatrist.
Forgive me if I don't
seem persuaded.
I'd like you to
come with me, John.
Just for a chat.
It appears I have no choice.
Oh-hh!
Help me! Somebody!
[Screams] Somebody!
Help me! Get off me!
I know who you are!
No, no, no, no, don't.
Charles, they're Russians!
Call somebody! Call
somebody, Charles!
-They're Russians!
-Steady the leg.
Get away from me.
Stay away from me!
DR. ROSEN: There, now.
All better.
-Everything's all right here.
-[Gasps]
Watch your head.
[Dr. Rosen, Faintly] John?
Can you hear me?
[Faint Whispering]
Go easy now.
Thorazine takes a little
while to wear off.
Sorry about the restraints.
You've got one hell
of a right hook.
[Weakly] Where am I?
Macarthur Psychiatric Hospital.
I find that highly unlikely.
You made a mistake.
My work is non-military
in application.
Which work is that, John?
I don't know anything.
[Laughs] There's no good in
keeping secrets, you know.
[Groans]
[Buzzer]
Charles?
I didn't mean to get
you involved in this.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Charles...?
The prodigal roommate revealed.
"Saw my name on the
lecture slate"?
You lying son of a bitch!
Who are you talking to?
Tell me who you see.
How do you say, "Charles
Herman" in Russian?
How do you say it in Russian?
There's no one there, John.
There's no one there.
He's right there.
Stop! I don't know anything!
Stop! I... I don't
know anything!
My name is John Nash.
I'm being held against my will.
Somebody call the
Department of Defense.
My name is John Nash.
I'm being held against my will!
ALICIA: What's wrong with him?
John has schizophrenia.
People with this disorder
are often paranoid.
But... But his work.
He deals with conspiracies...
Yes, yes, I know.
In John's world, these behaviors are...
accepted,
encouraged.
As such, his illness may
have gone untreated
far longer than is typical.
What do you mean? How long?
Possibly since graduate school?
At least that's when his
hallucinations seem to have begun.
What are you talking about?
What hallucinations?
One, so far, that I am aware of.
An imaginary roommate
named Charles Herman.
Charles isn't imaginary.
He and John have been best
friends since Princeton.
Have you ever met Charles?
Has he ever come to dinner?
He's always in town for so
little time, lecturing.
-Was he at your wedding?
-He had to teach.
Have you ever seen
a picture of him,
-talked to him on the telephone?
-This is ridiculous.
I phoned Princeton.
According to their
housing records,
John lived alone.
Now, which is more likely...
that your husband,
a mathematician with
no military training,
is a government spy
fleeing the Russians...
You're making him sound crazy.
... Or, that he has lost
his grip on reality?
Now the only way I can help him
is to show him the difference
between what's real
and what is in his mind.
Come on.
What's he been working on?
His work is classified.
He mentioned a supervisor
by the name of William Parcher.
Maybe Mr. Parcher can
clarify things for us.
But I can't get to him
without clearances.
You want me to help you get
the details of my
husband's work?
John thinks I'm a Russian spy.
Is that what you think?
-What did the doctor say?
-Is he sick?
I don't know.
I want to see what
Johns been working on.
But Alicia, you know you
can't go in his office.
You know, it's classified, Alicia.
Stop.
Oh, my God.
Why didn't you say something?
Alicia, I mean,
John's always been
a little weird.
He said he was doing
code-breaking,
that it was eyes-only.
-Top secret, part of the military effort.
-Was he?
Well, it was possible, you know? I mean,
directives come down all the time
that some of us
aren't cleared for.
-It was possible.
-Possible, but...
not likely.
Lately, he'd become
so much more agitated
and then when you called...
So, is this all he's
been doing every day?
Cutting out magazines?
Well, not all.
[Door Opens]
-ALICIA: I'm so sorry.
-JOHN: It's okay.
-I missed you.
I have to talk to you.
Okay.
Alicia, I've been
thinking about it,
and I do realize
that my behavior
and my inability to discuss
the situation with you
must have appeared insane.
I left you with no other choice.
I do understand...
-and I'm truly sorry.
-That's okay.
Everything's gonna be all right.
We just have to talk quietly.
They may be listening.
There may be microphones.
I'm gonna tell you
everything now.
It's breaking with protocol
but you need to know,
because you have to help
me get out of here.
Alicia, I've been doing top-secret
work for the government.
There's a threat that exists
of catastrophic proportions.
I think the Russians feel
my profile is too high.
That's why they simply just
don't do away with me.
They're keeping me
here to try to stop me
from doing my work. You
have to get to Wheeler.
-You have to find William Parcher.
-Stop.
-He can help us.
-Stop. Stop. Stop!
I went to Wheeler.
Good, good.
There is no William Parcher.
Of course there is.
-I've been working for him.
-Doing what?
Breaking codes?
Dropping packages
in a secret mailbox
for the government to pick up?
How could you know that?
Sol followed you.
-He thought it was harmless.
-Sol followed me?
They've never been opened.
It isn't real.
There is no conspiracy, John.
There is no William Parcher.
It's in your mind.
Do you understand, baby?
You're sick.
You're sick, John.
John?!
John!
Code red.
[Over P.A.] Dr. Rosen, code red.
Observation room two.
Dr. Rosen, code red.
[Keys Jingling]
John?
The implant's gone.
I can't find it.
It's gone.
DR. ROSEN: You see, the
nightmare of schizophrenia
is not knowing what's true.
Imagine...
if you had suddenly learned
that the people and the places
and the moments most
important to you
were not gone, not dead,
but worse...
Had never been.
What kind of hell would that be?
Administering insulin.
MAN: 8:42 a.m.
How often?
Five times a week for 10 weeks.
ALICIA: John always spoke so
fondly of being here at Princeton.
And Hansen is running
the department now.
So he keeps reminding
us, and reminding us.
[Laughs]
Yeah.
John won't come near
the campus, though.
-I think he's ashamed.
-[Baby Cries]
Hey. Hey.
Want this?
So, Alicia, how... how
are you holding up?
Well, the delusions have passed.
They're saying with
the medication
and low stress environment...
No, I... I mean, how are you?
I think often what I feel
is obligation.
Or guilt over wanting to leave.
Rage against John,
against God and...
But...
then I look at him
and I force myself to see
the man that I married.
And he becomes that man.
He's transformed into
someone that I love.
And I'm transformed into
someone who loves him.
It's not all the time,
but...
it's enough.
I think John is a
very lucky man...
Alicia.
So unlucky.
-ALICIA: This is us.
-SOL: This is it?
-It's nice.
-It's near where I work.
ALICIA: John? You've a visitor.
Hi.
I hope it's okay.
Hey ya, chief.
-Cigarette?
-Ah, no, thanks.
I quit, actually.
-Hello.
-Hey, John.
Have you met Harvey?
Umm, I...
[Laughs]
-John, there's no...
-Relax, it's okay.
There's no point in being nuts
if you can't have a little fun.
Jesus Christ, John. [Laughs]
I should have known.
Here you go.
I can take those later.
You're supposed
to take them now.
-Can I bring you something?
-I'm okay.
Okay.
So, um... yeah. I...
I was in town
giving a workshop.
I go back tonight.
You know, Bender,
he really wanted
to stop by and you know, see you.
You know, say hi.
Squeamish?
Yeah.
I suppose I would be, too.
But alas, I'm stuck with me.
I'm trying to solve the
Reimann Hypothesis.
Oh, yeah?
I figured if...
if I dazzle them,
they will have to reinstate me.
But it's difficult
with the medication,
because it's hard to...
see the solution.
You know, John, you
should go easy.
There are other
things besides...
Besides work.
What are they?
[Baby Crying]
Shh-hh.
Shh.
[Door Closes]
What are you thinking about?
What do people do?
It's life, John.
Activities available,
just add meaning.
You could try leaving the house.
You know, maybe...
talk to people.
You could try taking
out the garbage.
[Muffled Voice]
JOHN: And there's some more...
there's some more in...
[Muffled]
Who... Who were you talking to?
Garbage man.
Garbage men don't come at night.
I guess around here they do.
[Man Whistles]
[Truck Approaching]
[Giggles]
Sorry.
ALICIA: Is it the medication?
[Door Closes]
[Screams]
[Sobs] I don't know what to do.
[Sobbing Continues]
[Car Door Opens]
My mother's going to keep the
baby a little longer tonight.
I can get three
hours of overtime.
[Faint Music Playing]
I'm going to bed.
-Good night.
[Clattering]
[Gun Cocks]
PARCHER: It's good
to see you, John.
It's been a while.
Parcher?
Yes, sir.
You're not real!
Of course I am. Don't
be ridiculous.
[Rifles Cocking]
I-I don't think that I
would go that way, John.
It's time for you to
get back to work.
PARCHER: The bomb is in its
final position here in the U.S.
Knowing your situation
requires you keep a low
profile, "Mohammed",
we've brought the
mountain to you.
[Generator Whirrs]
[Radio Signals]
We've narrowed the bomb's location to
somewhere on the eastern seaboard.
But we haven't been able to
pinpoint its exact position.
Their codes have grown
increasingly complex.
Here, look at this, John.
What?
-Dr. Rosen said...
-Rosen! That quack!
"Schizophrenic break
from reality", right?
Psychological bullshit!
Look at me, John.
John, look at me.
Do I look like I'm imagined?
Wheeler has no record of you.
Do you think we
list our personnel?
John, I'm sorry you had
to go through all this.
I've gone to a great deal
of trouble to get you back.
I can restore your
status at Wheeler.
I can let the world
know what you did.
But I need you now, soldier.
I was so scared
you weren't real.
There's a storm coming.
I'm just going to grab
the laundry, okay?
I'll draw his bath.
It's okay.
Okay.
[Faint Radio Sounds]
[Muffled Radio Voice]
[Radio Static, Broken Voices]
[Whimpering]
[Crying]
[Thunder Rumbles]
John!
I've almost got it! Charles,
you just watch the baby.
-[Baby Crying]
-I've got one more to close!
-No!
-JOHN: I'll be right there.
-Oh, God.
-[Crying]
I need a towel.
Shhh.
Charles was watching him.
He was okay.
There is no one here.
-Charles was watching him.
-There is no one here!
He's been injected
with a cloaking serum.
I can see him because
of a chemical
that was released
into my bloodstream
when my implant dissolved.
I couldn't tell you, it was
for your own protection!
Alicia!
-No!
-Hello, I need Dr. Rosen's office, please.
You've got to stop her, John.
You leave her out of this.
-Who are you talking to?
-It's not her fault.
-John.
-She'll compromise us again.
-No, she won't.
-You'll go back to the hospital.
-John, answer me!
-Countless people will die.
Alicia, please, put
the phone down.
-I can't let that happen.
-Yes, hello?
Hi, I need Dr. Rosen. Is he in?
I'm sorry, John.
JOHN: No-oo!
Alicia?
PARCHER: You know what
you have to do, Nash.
-Get away from me.
-She's too great a risk.
-Get away!
-[Baby Crying]
I didn't mean to hurt you!
Finish her. She
knows too much now.
Uncle John?
PARCHER: Take care of her,
you pathetic piece of shit,
or I'll take care of you.
John,
Oh Christ, John, please
do what he says.
Move, soldier.
Now.
MARCEE: Uncle John?
CHARLES: John, please!
Now!
[Mental Voices] Alicia and Charles
never co-exist in the same
interactive field.
Alicia and Parcher...
[Voices Continue]
-MARCEE: Let's play!
-[Voices Increase]
...Charles, and Marcee
cannot co-exist with Alicia.
I understand.
[Engine Starts]
[Screams]
She never gets old.
Marcee can't be real.
You see them now?
Yes.
Why did you stop your meds?
Because I couldn't do my work.
I couldn't help with the baby.
I couldn't...
I couldn't respond to my wife.
You think that's better
than being crazy?
We'll need to start
you on a higher run
of insulin shocks and
a new medication.
No.
There has to be another way.
Dr. Rosen. Schizophrenia
is degenerative.
Some days may be symptom-free,
but over time, you
are getting worse.
It's a problem.
That's all it is.
It's a problem with no solution.
And that's what I do,
I solve problems.
-That's what I do best.
-This isn't math.
DR. ROSEN: You can't
come up with a formula
to change the way you
experience the world.
-All I have to do is apply my mind.
-There's no theorem, no proof.
-You can't reason your way out of this.
-Why not? Why can't I?
Because your mind is where the
problem is in the first place.
I can do this.
I can work it out.
All I need is time.
Is that the baby?
The baby's at my mother's, John.
[Marcee Humming]
DR. ROSEN: Without
treatment, John,
the fantasies may take over...
entirely.
ALICIA: You almost ready?
Rosen's waiting outside.
I can't go back
to that hospital.
I won't come home.
He said that if you said that,
he has commitment
papers for me to sign.
Well, maybe you won't sign them.
Maybe you'll just
give me some time.
I will try to figure this out.
Whatever you do,
Rosen is right about one thing.
You shouldn't be here.
I'm not safe anymore.
Would you have hurt me, John?
I don't know.
Maybe you should let Dr. Rosen
drive you to your mother's.
[Muffled Voices]
[Car Doors Close]
[Engine Starts]
[Car Departs]
[Footsteps On Stairs]
Rosen said to call if you try
and kill me or anything.
You want to know what's real?
This.
This is real.
Maybe the part...
that knows the waking
from the dream,
maybe it isn't here.
Maybe it's here.
I need to believe
that something
extraordinary is possible.
[Sighs]
HANSEN: Come.
Hello, Martin.
Jesus Christ.
No. I...
I don't have that one.
My savior complex
takes on a completely
different form.
[Nash Chuckles]
I heard what happened and well,
I... I wanted to write and
I tried you at Macarthur's
but you'd left, and I just...
this is Helinger's old office.
Yeah.
Yeah, I stole it from him.
Seems that you won
after all, Martin.
They were wrong, John.
No one wins.
Please, please have a seat.
God, it's so good to see you.
What brings you
back to Princeton?
CHARLES: John?
John, I'm sorry, but
you have to tell him.
Tell him you're a genius.
You're a genius, John!
Tell him your work is critical.
John, please!
Is there any chance that you
could ignore what I just did?
Of course, what are
old friends for?
Is that what we are, Martin?
Friends?
John, of course.
Of course. We always have been.
Alicia and I think that...
That fitting in,
being part of a community,
might do me some good.
That a certain level
of attachment,
familiar places,
familiar people,
might help me...
elbow out these...
These certain delusions
that I have.
It's a lot to ask, and
now that I'm here,
I'm quite certain that
you will just say no.
But I was wondering if
I could hang around.
[Sighs]
Huh.
Will you be needing an office?
No.
No, I could just work
out of the library.
Well, this guy tries to
wander into the library,
-but he doesn't have I.D.
-Why can't people read their memos, huh?
Then he goes totally nuts.
JOHN: Not real! You're not real.
There's no mission.
Oh, shit. Shit.
Not real! You are not real!
Is this what you are, soldier?
Some useless ghoul?
The local madman?
-I'm not a soldier.
-You're gonna end up in a cell!
Old, worthless, discarded.
There's no mission.
And while you rock and drool,
the world will burn to ashes!
You are not real!
You're still talking
to me, soldier.
There's no mission!
I'm not a soldier!
John? John?
John, John, John, John.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey, hey.
John, John! It's okay.
I just heard what happened, I'm sorry.
John...
-I'm not a soldier.
-John. Hey, Nash.
Nash, hey.
Hey, you're all right.
Nash, Nash, hey, hey, hey.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the great John Nash!
HANSEN: John?
JOHN: You should've
seen their faces.
Everybody was just
staring at me.
John...
you know that stress
triggers the delusions.
I know.
But then, on the way home,
Charles was there.
Sometimes, I really
miss talking to him.
Maybe Rosen's right.
Maybe I have to think about going
back into the hospital again.
No.
Come here.
Maybe try again tomorrow.
John, now, you can't
ignore me forever.
Charles, you've been a
very good friend to me.
The best.
But I won't talk to you again.
I just can't.
Same goes for you, baby girl.
[Sniffs]
Good-bye.
I was wondering if I
might audit your course.
It's... It's an honor,
Professor Nash.
Is something wrong?
This will be my first class.
[Laughs]
Good morning,
eager young minds.
[Muttering Numbers]
It's never gonna work, John.
You're just
humiliating yourself.
It's pathetic!
You are being pathetic.
I'm ashamed of you.
[Laughing]
[Laughing Continues]
Oh, man!
Are you coming?
You're gonna be late.
-Dad, you've got my book.
-What?
You've got my book.
Oh, right.
Thanks.
-Good-bye.
-Bye.
ALICIA: See you tonight.
Bye, honey.
Did you just solve Reimann?
Well, what do you think?
Huh.
That's an analog to Frobenius
for non-commutative extensions.
[Chuckles]
Yes, it is.
But it only appears to
work sporadically, so, no.
But...
I believe I'm making progress.
You're...
Youre John Nash, right?
-Toby Kelly.
-Hello.
I've been studying
your equilibrium.
The one you wrote
here, at Princeton.
To come up with something totally
original, the way you did...
You know, I was young.
[Chuckles]
umm...
I've been developing a theory.
I believe I can prove
that Galois extensions
are covering spaces.
That everything,
everything is connected.
That it's all part
of the same subject.
When was the last time you ate?
-Excuse me?
-You know, food.
Oh, uh...
My wife,
she loves mayonnaise.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Go on.
The function...
-is in the two categories.
-Um-hmm.
HANSEN: Alicia!
Alicia!
JOHN: ... coming together
at maximum speed of...
let us say 10 miles per hour.
So you have a fly on
the tire of bicycle B,
and the fly, who can travel
at 20 miles an hour,
leaves the tire of
bicycle B and it flies
to the tire of bicycle a
and backwards and forwards
and so on and so forth until
the two bikes collide
and the poor little
fly is squashed.
-[Chuckling]
-This is the important thing
about actually focusing
in and comprehending
the area that you're
dealing with.
Mathematics is very specific,
and it is an art form,
no matter what these people
around here will tell you,
especially the
people from biology.
Don't listen to any
of those people.
Let me go back to what
you were doing before.
I might want to steal this,
write a book and get famous.
I was thinking that
I might teach.
A classroom with 50 students
can be daunting for anyone.
John, besides, you're
a terrible teacher.
I'm an acquired taste, Martin.
I was hoping there still might
be something I could contribute.
What about the...
Well, you know.
Are they gone?
No, they're not gone.
And maybe they never will be.
But I've gotten used
to ignoring them
and I think as a result they've
kind of given up on me.
You think that's what
it's like with...
... all our dreams and
our nightmares, Martin?
You've got to keep feeding
them for them to stay alive?
John, they... haunt you, though.
Well, they're my past, Martin.
Everybody's haunted by their past.
Well, good-bye.
John, I'll talk to
the department.
Maybe in the spring.
Hey, Nash?
You...
you scared?
Terrified.
Mortified. Petrified.
Stupefied by you.
Now you ought best ring Alicia,
-or you're gonna get me...
-I'll ring her.
...in an awful lot of trouble.
-Thanks, Professor.
-Good-bye.
-Have a nice day.
See you.
-Papers in hand, Mr. Beyer.
-Oh, yes, sir.
Professor Nash?
-Can you see him?
-Yeah.
-You sure?
-Uh-huh.
Positive? He's
within your vision?
-[Laughing]
-Okay. Good.
Forgive me, I'm just always
suspicious of new people.
-See you next week, Professor.
-See you next week.
So now that I know
that you're real,
who are you, and what
can I do for you?
Professor, my name
is Thomas King...
Thomas King?
... and I'm here to tell you
that you're being considered
for the Nobel prize.
JOHN: Forgive me, but I'm
just a little stunned.
KING: Over the past few
years your equilibrium
has become a cornerstone
of modern economics.
Suddenly everybody
likes that one.
What-what about my work on other some
such projects... manifold embedding?
The application of your
bargaining problem
to F.C.C. bandwidth auctions
or to antitrust cases...
-Antitrust cases?
-Yes.
I never-I never would
have considered that.
-Well...
-Have I just reached some
level of honesty that
borders on stupidity?
[Laughs] No, no, you haven't.
'Cause, I wouldn't
have thought of that.
Shall we have tea?
Oh, I don't go in there.
I usually just
take my sandwich in the library.
Come on, John. Let's have some tea.
It's a big day.
M-Most...
Most commercially
available brands of tea
are not suitable to
my palate, you see...
I'm not...
There are some northern Indian
teas which are dense enough...
I enjoy the flavor
that they have...
I have not been in this room
for quite some many years. I
wonder what tea they serve.
JOHN: Why, thank
you, young lady.
Things have certainly
changed around here.
I have a son that age.
-Harvard.
-[King Chuckles]
Hmm.
I would have thought
the nominations
for the Nobel prize
would have been secret.
I would have thought you'd only
find out if you won or lost.
That is generally the case, yes.
But these are special
circumstances.
The awards are substantial.
They require private funding.
As such,
the image of the Nobel is...
I see. You came here to
find out if I was crazy?
Find out if I would
screw everything up
if I actually won?
Dance around the podium, strip
naked and squawk like a chicken,
things of this nature?
Something like that, yes.
Would I embarrass you?
Yes, it is possible.
You see, I...
I am crazy.
I take the newer medications,
but I still see things
that are not here.
I just choose not to
acknowledge them.
Like a diet of the mind,
I choose not to indulge
certain appetites.
Like my appetite for patterns.
Perhaps my appetite to
imagine and to dream.
MAN: Professor Nash.
It's good to have
you here, John.
Thank you.
-It's an honor, sir.
-Thank you very much.
A privilege, Professor.
Professor.
-Nicely done, John.
-Thank you, Tom.
Thank you.
Thank you, Ed.
That was certainly
most unexpected.
[Applause]
JOHN: Thank you.
[Applause Fades]
I've always believed in numbers.
In the equations and logics
that lead to reason.
But after a lifetime
of such pursuits,
I ask,
what truly is logic?
Who decides reason?
My quest has taken me
through the physical,
the metaphysical,
the delusional,
and back.
And I have made the most important
discovery of my career.
The most important
discovery of my life.
It is only in the mysterious
equations of love
that any logical
reasons can be found.
I'm only here tonight
because of you.
You are the reason I am.
You are all my reasons.
Thank you.
JOHN: So nice to have met you.
I'll call for the car, Dad.
Bye-bye.
WOMAN: Bye-bye.
-Are you ready to go now?
-Oh, yes, I am.
Yes, indeed, and yes, please.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
What is it? What's wrong?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
-Come with me, young lady.
-Oh-hh...
I have a car outside.
Are you interested in a ride?
Where's it going to?
I will
Watch you
In the darkness
Show you
Love will
See you through
When the bad dreams
Wake you crying
I show you
All love can do
What love can do
I will watch through the night
Hold you in my arms
Give you dreams
Where none will be
I will watch through the dark
Till the morning comes
All the light
I'll take you through the night
To see
The light
Showing us all love
Can be
I will
Guide you
With my bright wings
Stay till your heart
Learns to see
All love
Can...
Be.
[Female Vocal]