1
00:02:21,387 --> 00:02:23,676
How about I drive, huh?

2
00:02:25,600 --> 00:02:27,012
Oh.

3
00:02:29,063 --> 00:02:31,434
There we go.

4
00:02:34,110 --> 00:02:35,769
About time you showed up.

5
00:02:35,820 --> 00:02:37,813
Some couples like to talk.

6
00:02:37,906 --> 00:02:39,983
Did they see anything?

7
00:02:40,075 --> 00:02:43,326
They don't know the girls,
didn't see the car. Nothing.

8
00:02:48,920 --> 00:02:51,208
How many more miles
do we have left to cover?

9
00:02:51,296 --> 00:02:54,500
We're on Stone Hollow, and
we need to check these two roads

10
00:02:54,592 --> 00:02:55,873
and circle back around.

11
00:02:55,969 --> 00:02:59,173
Harris wants us back to base
by midnight, so...

12
00:03:02,393 --> 00:03:05,181
Maybe the perimeter's
not wide enough. Maybe...

13
00:03:05,272 --> 00:03:07,229
This guy's a traveler.

14
00:03:07,316 --> 00:03:10,565
Maybe the first body
is throwing us off.

15
00:03:47,614 --> 00:03:49,487
Your turn.

16
00:04:54,107 --> 00:04:56,100
New paint, new plates.
It's our guy.

17
00:04:56,194 --> 00:04:59,112
- He's here.
- Shit. Back in the car.

18
00:04:59,157 --> 00:05:01,778
Let him think we're leaving.
We'll get tactical.

19
00:05:02,327 --> 00:05:04,616
All units, this is Predator 5
requesting backup.

20
00:05:04,663 --> 00:05:06,242
We're on Stone Hollow Road.

21
00:05:06,332 --> 00:05:09,368
We have the UNSUB's vehicle...

22
00:05:10,336 --> 00:05:12,294
They're still alive.

23
00:05:12,922 --> 00:05:14,417
Come on.

24
00:05:15,092 --> 00:05:16,124
FBI!

25
00:06:42,195 --> 00:06:44,687
- Oh, God.
- Check the girls.

26
00:06:48,326 --> 00:06:49,738
Sara!

27
00:07:10,269 --> 00:07:12,013
Talk to me, Sara.

28
00:07:21,991 --> 00:07:24,198
Predator 5 to base.
Over.

29
00:07:24,286 --> 00:07:28,747
We have the situation secure.
Repeat... situation is secure.

30
00:07:28,832 --> 00:07:30,790
Suspect is dead.

31
00:07:30,835 --> 00:07:32,495
So are the girls.

32
00:07:34,506 --> 00:07:36,583
There were three shots fired.

33
00:07:40,555 --> 00:07:42,513
Hey!
Sara!

34
00:07:42,599 --> 00:07:44,224
Sara, drop!
Get rid of the line!

35
00:07:44,309 --> 00:07:45,638
Get down! Down!

36
00:07:46,646 --> 00:07:47,725
Drop! Drop!

37
00:08:24,189 --> 00:08:26,182
Ohh.

38
00:08:34,868 --> 00:08:38,488
Man. Thought you guys
were never gonna get here.

39
00:08:40,292 --> 00:08:42,997
Hey, Harris,
I'm fucking starving!

40
00:09:07,865 --> 00:09:09,858
So, tomorrow...

41
00:09:09,909 --> 00:09:12,745
I have a senior staff meeting
with the director,

42
00:09:12,829 --> 00:09:17,244
A Q4 performance review,
and an academy course to prep.

43
00:09:17,335 --> 00:09:21,464
But now, instead, I get to waste
my whole day at your funerals.

44
00:09:22,800 --> 00:09:26,799
Special Agent Moore,
when is the situation secure?

45
00:09:27,888 --> 00:09:30,013
- On the drive home.
- On the drive home.

46
00:09:30,100 --> 00:09:32,972
That's right.
On the drive home.

47
00:09:33,062 --> 00:09:34,770
- Sir, we didn't...
- Shut up.

48
00:09:36,066 --> 00:09:38,189
Cigarettes on the table.
More at the door.

49
00:09:38,277 --> 00:09:39,522
Different brands.

50
00:09:39,611 --> 00:09:42,566
Two cars out front.
4 place settings, not 3.

51
00:09:42,657 --> 00:09:44,614
All should have alerted you
to the possibility

52
00:09:44,659 --> 00:09:47,364
that there might be
another suspect.

53
00:09:47,453 --> 00:09:50,372
- I think...
- I'm sorry? What?

54
00:09:52,126 --> 00:09:53,585
What did you say?

55
00:09:53,669 --> 00:09:57,620
I think you enjoy
watching us fail, sir.

56
00:09:57,674 --> 00:09:59,917
Better in here than out there.

57
00:09:59,969 --> 00:10:01,463
You know this really happened?

58
00:10:01,512 --> 00:10:03,719
The UNSUB was apprehended
in under 2 minutes

59
00:10:03,807 --> 00:10:05,598
without a shot fired.

60
00:10:05,642 --> 00:10:08,643
It took you guys 7 minutes,
and you killed your partner.

61
00:10:08,687 --> 00:10:10,347
Have some cake.

62
00:10:13,609 --> 00:10:15,318
The majority of murders
are committed

63
00:10:15,362 --> 00:10:17,154
by someone known to the victim.

64
00:10:17,197 --> 00:10:20,982
Those that are not solved within
the first 48 hours seldom are.

65
00:10:21,036 --> 00:10:22,578
Not so with serial killers.

66
00:10:22,663 --> 00:10:24,157
One advantage
in this line of work

67
00:10:24,248 --> 00:10:27,367
is knowing that as long as
the UNSUB is out there,

68
00:10:27,459 --> 00:10:29,167
you'll always have
another chance.

69
00:10:29,253 --> 00:10:31,709
With each new killing comes
a resetting of the clock.

70
00:10:31,798 --> 00:10:33,506
Time is on your side.

71
00:10:33,549 --> 00:10:34,831
The model for this exercise

72
00:10:34,927 --> 00:10:38,462
was a missing-persons search
in Buffalo, 1982.

73
00:10:38,556 --> 00:10:41,890
The dead man was an accomplice
who was killed the day before.

74
00:10:41,977 --> 00:10:43,851
The killer staged a suicide

75
00:10:43,938 --> 00:10:46,690
in order to try, in effect,
an escape.

76
00:10:46,733 --> 00:10:51,478
As you can see, some of you
responded better than others.

77
00:10:51,529 --> 00:10:53,772
Well, exactly how many times
has a profiler

78
00:10:53,866 --> 00:10:57,033
been in a kill-or-capture
situation since 1982?

79
00:10:57,119 --> 00:10:59,029
Are you suggesting I'm
preparing you for something

80
00:10:59,080 --> 00:11:01,239
you may never experience?

81
00:11:01,333 --> 00:11:03,207
Success comes
when you understand

82
00:11:03,293 --> 00:11:05,702
that your most lethal weapon
isn't your firearm,

83
00:11:05,755 --> 00:11:08,080
but your brain.

84
00:11:08,173 --> 00:11:10,380
A lot of the old guard
don't believe in my methods.

85
00:11:10,469 --> 00:11:12,176
A lot of them think I'm crazy.

86
00:11:13,346 --> 00:11:14,972
You're a privileged group.

87
00:11:15,057 --> 00:11:17,264
You're all smart
or you wouldn't be here.

88
00:11:17,351 --> 00:11:19,808
I just want you to be smarter.

89
00:11:19,896 --> 00:11:23,847
Our final exercise will be
on the island of Oneiga.

90
00:11:24,736 --> 00:11:29,065
This simulation will be a test
primarily of your teamwork.

91
00:11:29,115 --> 00:11:31,191
I hope you're ready.

92
00:11:31,284 --> 00:11:34,489
Then how could we have saved
the girls at the old hotel?

93
00:11:34,580 --> 00:11:38,163
You couldn't. They were dead
no matter what you did.

94
00:11:38,251 --> 00:11:40,921
What's the point
if we couldn't have saved them?

95
00:11:40,963 --> 00:11:44,415
The point is to get used to it.

96
00:11:46,177 --> 00:11:48,964
<i># There, you've seen it,
my behavior's unacceptable #</i>

97
00:11:49,055 --> 00:11:51,512
Good evening, my fine,
young FBI friends.

98
00:11:51,600 --> 00:11:56,061
I am a pretty little thing
just out of lit class at GMU.

99
00:11:56,147 --> 00:11:59,932
Please note the Jimmy Joyce
in my Kate Spade.

100
00:12:00,027 --> 00:12:03,563
My parents are loaded
as per my expensive ensemble.

101
00:12:03,615 --> 00:12:06,486
And that "J"... Where is it?
On my key ring...

102
00:12:06,577 --> 00:12:10,277
means I'm either a Jill
or a Jennifer.

103
00:12:10,372 --> 00:12:12,531
Those being the favorite "J"
names of Beltway parents

104
00:12:12,625 --> 00:12:15,247
circa 1981.

105
00:12:15,337 --> 00:12:17,958
I like to hang with my friends
and have a good time,

106
00:12:18,048 --> 00:12:22,462
but I'm really just a mature
woman looking for a mature man.

107
00:12:22,554 --> 00:12:25,306
And I recently quit smoking.

108
00:12:26,016 --> 00:12:27,924
Why do you say that?

109
00:12:27,976 --> 00:12:30,432
You see the way she keeps eyeing
the guy next to her?

110
00:12:30,479 --> 00:12:32,638
It's not him.
It's his cigarette.

111
00:12:32,732 --> 00:12:34,476
Spoken like a woman who knows.

112
00:12:34,567 --> 00:12:36,311
How long has it been, Nicole?
3 days?

113
00:12:36,361 --> 00:12:38,401
The lovely Nicole
and her personal demons.

114
00:12:38,489 --> 00:12:42,357
I'm surprised there's enough
room at the table for all of us.

115
00:12:43,703 --> 00:12:45,163
Take me 5 minutes
to get her number.

116
00:12:45,247 --> 00:12:47,156
Take me 2.

117
00:12:48,250 --> 00:12:49,874
- You're on.
- Money's coming out.

118
00:12:49,960 --> 00:12:51,076
$20.

119
00:12:51,170 --> 00:12:52,998
- $20 works.
- Whoo!

120
00:12:53,089 --> 00:12:54,500
Whoa, big money.

121
00:12:56,468 --> 00:12:59,423
Hi. I think I know you,
don't I?

122
00:12:59,514 --> 00:13:01,009
You're, um, uh...

123
00:13:01,099 --> 00:13:02,510
Jill, right?

124
00:13:02,559 --> 00:13:03,590
Jen.

125
00:13:03,685 --> 00:13:06,639
Jen, Jen. Yes.
Yes, Jen, of course.

126
00:13:06,688 --> 00:13:08,764
Okay, obviously
you don't remember me.

127
00:13:08,857 --> 00:13:11,266
My name's Bobby.
Bobby Whitman.

128
00:13:11,361 --> 00:13:13,105
Rafe, you're up.
Profile.

129
00:13:13,196 --> 00:13:14,821
Okay.

130
00:13:14,907 --> 00:13:17,861
Black suit, blond hair,
Martini.

131
00:13:17,952 --> 00:13:19,197
I'm the sophisticated type

132
00:13:19,245 --> 00:13:21,404
on the prowl for pretty,
young things.

133
00:13:21,498 --> 00:13:23,871
Preferably blond.

134
00:13:23,918 --> 00:13:27,749
Preferably a cheerleader
with great big...

135
00:13:27,839 --> 00:13:30,246
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
Enough.

136
00:13:31,176 --> 00:13:33,169
Right about the blond.
You're on fire.

137
00:13:33,261 --> 00:13:35,053
You're projecting.

138
00:13:37,058 --> 00:13:39,929
I don't know. It was 2 seconds
at a lecture last semester.

139
00:13:40,020 --> 00:13:41,218
GMU Lit Department, right?

140
00:13:41,271 --> 00:13:43,430
The Moody lecture?

141
00:13:43,524 --> 00:13:45,149
Yeah, yeah, Moody.
Heck of a writer.

142
00:13:45,234 --> 00:13:46,348
Um...

143
00:13:46,443 --> 00:13:48,733
I'm actually not even
a student myself.

144
00:13:48,780 --> 00:13:50,238
Um...

145
00:13:50,281 --> 00:13:53,117
I work in finance.

146
00:13:53,202 --> 00:13:55,408
Oh. Finance?

147
00:13:55,496 --> 00:13:58,581
- Oh! Right. Bobby.
- Yeah.

148
00:13:58,666 --> 00:14:00,909
- Hi. How are you?
- Hi. I'm good.

149
00:14:00,961 --> 00:14:03,535
He's got 15 seconds.

150
00:14:06,591 --> 00:14:07,457
Thank you.

151
00:14:07,551 --> 00:14:10,090
Lucas, looks like tonight
wasn't your night.

152
00:14:10,180 --> 00:14:12,754
I know her. Her name's Jen.
I told her to play along.

153
00:14:12,850 --> 00:14:14,095
You're full of shit.

154
00:14:14,185 --> 00:14:15,513
You never know.

155
00:14:15,604 --> 00:14:18,855
Ooh.

156
00:14:22,319 --> 00:14:26,187
So, what is going on
in that head?

157
00:14:26,282 --> 00:14:27,480
We're professionals.

158
00:14:27,575 --> 00:14:29,652
We shouldn't have to put up
with Harris' shit.

159
00:14:29,745 --> 00:14:32,200
All right, what's up?

160
00:14:34,291 --> 00:14:36,830
I'm not making profiler.

161
00:14:36,920 --> 00:14:38,295
I was alone in his office.

162
00:14:38,380 --> 00:14:42,295
His recommends were on the desk,
and I read them.

163
00:14:42,384 --> 00:14:44,424
We still have the weekend
at Oneiga.

164
00:14:44,513 --> 00:14:46,006
He says I'm unfocused.

165
00:14:46,097 --> 00:14:47,259
He says I'm not capable

166
00:14:47,306 --> 00:14:51,222
of the psychological commitment
necessary for profiling work.

167
00:14:51,311 --> 00:14:52,936
How do you like that?

168
00:14:53,022 --> 00:14:56,309
Commitment. Like,
"Fucking look at me, man. "

169
00:14:56,402 --> 00:14:58,359
Vince, I think...

170
00:14:58,447 --> 00:15:01,364
You're not making profiler
either, Sara.

171
00:15:03,745 --> 00:15:06,033
Sorry.
I read it.

172
00:15:07,707 --> 00:15:10,032
Don't work too hard
out there, okay?

173
00:15:20,889 --> 00:15:22,929
We've got a late addition.

174
00:15:23,017 --> 00:15:25,343
This is Detective Gabe Jenson.

175
00:15:25,437 --> 00:15:27,394
He's from the Philadelphia P.D.

176
00:15:27,480 --> 00:15:29,022
Good morning.
How you doin'?

177
00:15:29,107 --> 00:15:30,732
He's their resident profiler,

178
00:15:30,817 --> 00:15:32,561
and somehow he got
on D. 0. J.'s good side

179
00:15:32,653 --> 00:15:35,061
and convinced the attorney
general he could sit in

180
00:15:35,156 --> 00:15:37,861
on some exercises
and see how I work.

181
00:15:37,951 --> 00:15:40,074
Do I have the politics
about right?

182
00:15:40,162 --> 00:15:41,408
Something like that.

183
00:15:41,497 --> 00:15:42,695
He's joining the team?

184
00:15:42,749 --> 00:15:45,667
He's just here to observe,
not to participate.

185
00:15:45,751 --> 00:15:47,744
Now, be nice to him
or it's my ass.

186
00:15:47,837 --> 00:15:49,035
No offense, Detective.

187
00:15:49,088 --> 00:15:51,794
None taken. It's an honor
to meet all of you.

188
00:16:08,403 --> 00:16:10,941
You want to do hostage rescue,
a smallpox outbreak,

189
00:16:11,031 --> 00:16:12,407
this is the place.

190
00:16:15,579 --> 00:16:17,737
Navy Seas built it
for wargame practice.

191
00:16:17,831 --> 00:16:20,868
Once a year, they turn it over
to me for the weekend.

192
00:16:23,922 --> 00:16:27,373
Okay, get your rappelling lines
and prepare to drop.

193
00:16:28,552 --> 00:16:30,675
That's a joke.

194
00:16:44,405 --> 00:16:47,156
Here we are.
Crimetown, USA.

195
00:16:47,241 --> 00:16:49,364
Where all the residents
are dead.

196
00:16:49,451 --> 00:16:51,279
Or about to be.

197
00:16:51,371 --> 00:16:54,870
Now, the idea here, people,
is to only kill the bad guys.

198
00:16:56,710 --> 00:16:57,741
But nobody's perfect.

199
00:16:57,836 --> 00:17:00,708
It's nice
to hear you say that, sir.

200
00:17:00,798 --> 00:17:03,006
It's like Beirut
meets Belfast.

201
00:17:03,093 --> 00:17:06,378
Sir, I thought they didn't let
foreign nationals in the FBI.

202
00:17:06,471 --> 00:17:09,046
Don't worry. On the inside
he's 100% American, right?

203
00:17:09,141 --> 00:17:11,715
As American
as the death penalty.

204
00:17:11,812 --> 00:17:12,891
That's my boy.

205
00:17:12,980 --> 00:17:15,056
I think I'm in love.

206
00:17:17,068 --> 00:17:20,651
Oh, there is one other person.
They'll be coming along shortly.

207
00:17:20,738 --> 00:17:21,819
Who's that?

208
00:17:21,907 --> 00:17:24,363
He's called a puppeteer.

209
00:17:24,452 --> 00:17:26,657
He's killed two people
on these streets,

210
00:17:26,746 --> 00:17:28,572
and he's about to kill a third.

211
00:17:28,664 --> 00:17:30,372
Tomorrow you'll find
the crime scene

212
00:17:30,458 --> 00:17:32,036
and receive
your background dossiers.

213
00:17:32,127 --> 00:17:36,505
By O800 on Monday, I want
a full profile of this suspect.

214
00:17:36,549 --> 00:17:38,625
I want to know who he is,
what he does,

215
00:17:38,677 --> 00:17:40,634
and where he's gonna do it next.

216
00:17:40,679 --> 00:17:43,633
I'm asking Special Agent Reston
to be team leader

217
00:17:43,683 --> 00:17:45,425
unless you'd like to defer.

218
00:17:45,517 --> 00:17:46,299
No, Harris.

219
00:17:46,351 --> 00:17:49,638
I will solve whatever sick,
twisted crime scenario

220
00:17:49,689 --> 00:17:50,852
you come up with.

221
00:17:50,941 --> 00:17:52,103
I hope so.

222
00:17:54,486 --> 00:17:55,981
What's the tank for?

223
00:17:56,030 --> 00:17:58,948
The Navy uses it
to simulate Arctic regions.

224
00:17:59,034 --> 00:18:01,704
That's what the nitrogen's for.

225
00:18:01,746 --> 00:18:05,328
In general, if it says
"military," don't touch it.

226
00:18:06,208 --> 00:18:08,534
Oh.
Great.

227
00:18:09,212 --> 00:18:11,371
Navy humor.

228
00:18:15,845 --> 00:18:18,336
The computers are loaded
with ViCAP,

229
00:18:18,390 --> 00:18:19,766
but they're fully firewalled.

230
00:18:19,850 --> 00:18:22,768
Don't do any research offsite.

231
00:18:22,854 --> 00:18:27,017
If you want to do any
blood samples on the autorad,

232
00:18:27,066 --> 00:18:30,186
analyze fibers...
scout samples...

233
00:18:30,237 --> 00:18:32,729
It's all here.

234
00:18:35,076 --> 00:18:37,116
You'll rest up here
till the morning.

235
00:18:37,203 --> 00:18:39,577
Downstairs, there's
a fully stocked freezer,

236
00:18:39,665 --> 00:18:41,493
bunks, and your showers.

237
00:18:41,584 --> 00:18:43,708
Don't forget.
You're 50 miles offshore.

238
00:18:43,795 --> 00:18:47,579
If you run out of toilet paper,
you are shit out of luck.

239
00:18:47,674 --> 00:18:49,216
So, what's the point?

240
00:18:49,300 --> 00:18:50,332
Sorry, Detective?

241
00:18:50,428 --> 00:18:52,717
The island, the middle of
nowhere, they're professionals.

242
00:18:52,764 --> 00:18:53,843
What's the point?

243
00:18:53,931 --> 00:18:58,891
The point is that they're
isolated, alone, and forgotten.

244
00:18:58,979 --> 00:19:02,812
That's what it's like to be
inside the mind of a sociopath.

245
00:19:04,027 --> 00:19:07,111
Have you noticed it's
a really bad feeling here?

246
00:19:13,079 --> 00:19:14,871
Good luck on your profile.

247
00:19:40,445 --> 00:19:41,560
Go!

248
00:20:03,806 --> 00:20:05,513
What?

249
00:20:07,768 --> 00:20:10,177
He said dress for an island.

250
00:20:12,899 --> 00:20:14,608
So, Detective,

251
00:20:14,693 --> 00:20:18,277
what exactly did you do to earn
this island paradise?

252
00:20:18,365 --> 00:20:20,441
Recommended for it.
Same as you.

253
00:20:20,534 --> 00:20:21,483
Why, though?

254
00:20:21,577 --> 00:20:23,950
Did you catch some killer
in Philly or something?

255
00:20:24,038 --> 00:20:25,413
What's the deal?

256
00:20:25,497 --> 00:20:28,036
You don't want to know
my war stories.

257
00:20:28,126 --> 00:20:30,000
Well, actually, I do.

258
00:20:30,045 --> 00:20:31,955
I mean, right now,

259
00:20:32,047 --> 00:20:34,538
what do we know
about you for real?

260
00:20:34,633 --> 00:20:36,876
We know he's got resentments
toward his parents,

261
00:20:36,970 --> 00:20:40,386
as per the overload on tattoos
he's got there.

262
00:20:40,432 --> 00:20:42,804
We know he's just out
of a bad relationship.

263
00:20:42,894 --> 00:20:45,016
He's barely looked twice
at me and Sara.

264
00:20:45,104 --> 00:20:47,725
Maybe you're not my type,
Nicole.

265
00:20:47,816 --> 00:20:49,559
We're alone on an island.

266
00:20:49,609 --> 00:20:52,066
Trust me, I'm your type.

267
00:20:53,739 --> 00:20:56,148
We also know
he watches his words.

268
00:20:56,242 --> 00:20:59,862
So that crossword's either
a sign of honing a talent

269
00:20:59,955 --> 00:21:01,414
or correcting a deficiency.

270
00:21:01,457 --> 00:21:03,497
What you say about me
doesn't tell you about me.

271
00:21:03,584 --> 00:21:05,910
It tells me about you.

272
00:21:06,004 --> 00:21:08,958
Now, I could say
your little gambling

273
00:21:09,049 --> 00:21:11,338
means you have
an addictive personality.

274
00:21:11,426 --> 00:21:12,541
I could say I know

275
00:21:12,636 --> 00:21:15,424
you're sleeping with one
of the guys in this room.

276
00:21:15,473 --> 00:21:17,681
I could say you take charge
of your team

277
00:21:17,768 --> 00:21:20,686
because you never had a leader
in your own life.

278
00:21:20,772 --> 00:21:22,100
And you.

279
00:21:22,148 --> 00:21:25,314
When push comes to shove,
you crack under pressure.

280
00:21:25,401 --> 00:21:27,975
Your partners can't depend
on you.

281
00:21:28,071 --> 00:21:30,360
You don't belong here.

282
00:21:30,449 --> 00:21:32,323
But that's all surface.

283
00:21:32,409 --> 00:21:34,533
Psych 101 bullshit.

284
00:21:34,621 --> 00:21:36,828
That's not who you are.

285
00:21:41,045 --> 00:21:43,620
All for killing him
in his sleep?

286
00:21:49,722 --> 00:21:52,343
Bad for you... 1:45.

287
00:21:52,433 --> 00:21:54,307
Damn!

288
00:22:06,366 --> 00:22:09,653
You push me in,
I'll have your badge.

289
00:22:09,704 --> 00:22:14,497
I, uh, came out here
to feed the ducks.

290
00:22:14,585 --> 00:22:16,827
I see you're feeding the ducks.

291
00:22:16,921 --> 00:22:19,163
Maybe we could feed the ducks
together.

292
00:22:20,174 --> 00:22:21,669
Leave you alone?

293
00:22:21,760 --> 00:22:23,385
No, no.
It's all right.

294
00:22:30,520 --> 00:22:32,513
I don't smoke.

295
00:22:32,606 --> 00:22:34,682
I know.
It's a gesture.

296
00:22:34,775 --> 00:22:37,693
Goodwill, sympathy.
You know, the usual.

297
00:22:37,779 --> 00:22:40,946
In lieu of knowing
what's going on.

298
00:22:41,032 --> 00:22:44,033
He's not gonna let me
make profiler.

299
00:22:45,537 --> 00:22:48,242
He thinks I can't get past it.

300
00:22:48,333 --> 00:22:49,613
Is he right?

301
00:22:59,012 --> 00:23:02,962
When I was a kid,
I lost both my parents.

302
00:23:03,058 --> 00:23:05,134
Freak thing.

303
00:23:05,227 --> 00:23:09,011
10 years old.
Bang. Mortality.

304
00:23:09,065 --> 00:23:11,557
So I grew up living real hard.

305
00:23:11,651 --> 00:23:14,439
Racing cars, smoking, drinking,

306
00:23:14,530 --> 00:23:16,737
sleeping with any girl
I could find.

307
00:23:16,824 --> 00:23:20,609
Real stupid,
dangerous lifestyle.

308
00:23:20,704 --> 00:23:22,662
Then I turned 11, and...

309
00:23:28,088 --> 00:23:30,413
All I know is this.

310
00:23:30,507 --> 00:23:33,462
You don't confront your demons
and defeat them.

311
00:23:33,552 --> 00:23:35,676
You confront them.

312
00:23:35,763 --> 00:23:37,223
Then you confront them.

313
00:23:37,266 --> 00:23:40,220
Then you confront them
some more.

314
00:23:40,269 --> 00:23:42,392
Every single day.

315
00:24:21,943 --> 00:24:24,813
You are seriously fucked up,
you know that?

316
00:24:24,904 --> 00:24:27,312
You know what I hate
about you, J. D?

317
00:24:27,365 --> 00:24:28,563
What?

318
00:24:28,658 --> 00:24:31,115
You only want me for my mind.

319
00:26:11,781 --> 00:26:13,192
What happened?

320
00:26:22,295 --> 00:26:25,081
I'd like to know
how Harris got it here.

321
00:26:25,130 --> 00:26:27,835
I'd say the issue is "why?"

322
00:26:31,513 --> 00:26:33,423
Here, kitty kitty.

323
00:26:35,434 --> 00:26:37,890
What kind of simulation is this?

324
00:26:43,485 --> 00:26:46,106
Ah. Oh!

325
00:26:46,154 --> 00:26:47,898
Ugh.

326
00:26:47,990 --> 00:26:49,319
10:00.

327
00:26:51,328 --> 00:26:53,653
That supposed to mean something?

328
00:26:53,747 --> 00:26:57,331
So, what, is this supposed to be
some kind of warning sign?

329
00:26:57,419 --> 00:27:01,832
Well, if I know Harris,
it's a sign of something.

330
00:27:05,678 --> 00:27:08,845
It's 9:30 A.M.,
Saturday morning.

331
00:27:08,931 --> 00:27:11,470
We're in search
of an unknown crime scene.

332
00:27:12,936 --> 00:27:14,266
We'll split into pairs.

333
00:27:14,355 --> 00:27:17,974
The first one who finds it wins
my eternal love and devotion.

334
00:27:18,068 --> 00:27:19,527
And a dead cat.

335
00:27:20,863 --> 00:27:22,736
And a dead cat.

336
00:27:27,453 --> 00:27:30,124
Now, this place
must remind you of home.

337
00:27:30,207 --> 00:27:33,244
Ha.
Happytown, USA.

338
00:27:33,336 --> 00:27:34,534
Sst!

339
00:27:35,380 --> 00:27:36,708
Look.

340
00:27:40,053 --> 00:27:41,879
It's little Bobby.

341
00:27:43,014 --> 00:27:45,587
Little Bobby's gonna grow up
to be big and strong

342
00:27:45,683 --> 00:27:47,842
and pursue a career
in buried children

343
00:27:47,894 --> 00:27:49,768
and dismembered mummies.

344
00:27:49,854 --> 00:27:53,355
Now, that will make
Happytown proud.

345
00:27:53,401 --> 00:27:56,023
I think you're
in the wrong line of work.

346
00:27:59,617 --> 00:28:01,242
No, mate.

347
00:28:02,744 --> 00:28:04,405
Not me.

348
00:28:06,917 --> 00:28:07,996
Hey!

349
00:28:09,711 --> 00:28:12,499
Dinner at Harris' house.

350
00:28:12,590 --> 00:28:14,133
Pass the nuts.

351
00:28:18,139 --> 00:28:19,883
Charming.

352
00:28:24,270 --> 00:28:26,263
Great.
A cigarette machine.

353
00:28:26,314 --> 00:28:28,640
Temptation is everywhere.

354
00:28:30,152 --> 00:28:32,775
Hey, Agent, we searching
together or what?

355
00:28:32,864 --> 00:28:35,700
Suit yourself.
I'm on vacation.

356
00:28:37,829 --> 00:28:38,860
Hey, Vince!

357
00:28:38,955 --> 00:28:40,913
Check out
the other side of town.

358
00:28:40,957 --> 00:28:43,494
Yeah, yeah, yeah.

359
00:28:43,584 --> 00:28:45,458
Huh.

360
00:28:51,219 --> 00:28:52,678
Hey, everybody!

361
00:28:56,809 --> 00:28:59,728
Harris, you are one sick
son of a bitch.

362
00:28:59,813 --> 00:29:02,481
Stay on my 6.

363
00:29:02,566 --> 00:29:05,900
Okay, everybody, it's about
that time to look alive.

364
00:29:05,986 --> 00:29:09,819
We have victim.

365
00:29:09,866 --> 00:29:11,942
Or victims?

366
00:29:12,953 --> 00:29:16,537
We got a single victim.
Caucasian female.

367
00:29:16,624 --> 00:29:18,582
25, 26.

368
00:29:18,668 --> 00:29:22,333
The puppeteer.
That's a hell of a signature.

369
00:29:24,800 --> 00:29:27,920
Why don't you check
the employee logs, receipts?

370
00:29:28,012 --> 00:29:31,346
See who shopped here, who
worked here. That sort of thing.

371
00:29:31,433 --> 00:29:33,841
Let me run forensic,
work the timeline.

372
00:29:33,894 --> 00:29:36,053
Sara, why don't you check
the carcass?

373
00:29:37,190 --> 00:29:38,352
Sara!

374
00:29:38,442 --> 00:29:39,473
Sure.

375
00:29:42,738 --> 00:29:43,936
Oh.

376
00:29:45,616 --> 00:29:47,360
There's splatter
behind the counter.

377
00:29:47,452 --> 00:29:49,860
The girl was definitely moved.

378
00:29:49,954 --> 00:29:51,948
Any venture as to weapon?

379
00:29:52,040 --> 00:29:54,414
- You want to take point on M.O?
- Absolutely.

380
00:29:54,502 --> 00:29:56,625
Nic, not to step on your toes,

381
00:29:56,713 --> 00:30:00,129
but I'm gonna bet
the guy's a trophy taker.

382
00:30:14,734 --> 00:30:16,229
What are you smiling about?

383
00:30:16,320 --> 00:30:18,727
If the taxpayers only knew...

384
00:30:18,781 --> 00:30:21,486
I think I'll go see if the
UNSUB's still in the building.

385
00:30:21,576 --> 00:30:24,148
Sweetheart, it's just
a simulation, yeah?

386
00:30:24,245 --> 00:30:28,196
Where we're from, a site search
is called procedure.

387
00:30:28,250 --> 00:30:29,744
Yeah?

388
00:30:33,548 --> 00:30:36,086
We should have been allowed
to bring our guns.

389
00:30:36,176 --> 00:30:38,003
It doesn't feel real
without my gun.

390
00:30:38,094 --> 00:30:40,669
Hell, Vince,
how real do you want it?

391
00:30:43,267 --> 00:30:45,095
Don't move.
Don't move! Sara.

392
00:30:48,607 --> 00:30:50,730
Let's see what freak show
Harris has in mind.

393
00:30:54,072 --> 00:30:55,946
It's no fun unless
it's a challenge, right?

394
00:31:39,500 --> 00:31:40,532
Move!

395
00:31:41,627 --> 00:31:42,658
Aah.

396
00:31:43,671 --> 00:31:44,418
Aah!

397
00:31:44,506 --> 00:31:45,704
My legs!

398
00:31:46,842 --> 00:31:48,669
No!
Don't touch it!

399
00:31:48,761 --> 00:31:49,757
Help!

400
00:31:49,846 --> 00:31:51,221
It'll burn you!

401
00:31:51,306 --> 00:31:52,966
- They're frozen!
- Help him!

402
00:31:53,058 --> 00:31:55,016
Aah!
Aah!

403
00:31:55,978 --> 00:31:57,936
Aah!
Stop!

404
00:32:18,756 --> 00:32:20,713
This is a joke, right?

405
00:32:20,758 --> 00:32:23,462
That was just a simulation.

406
00:33:09,189 --> 00:33:11,098
I'm sorry, Nic.

407
00:33:18,283 --> 00:33:21,237
- Were they working before?
- No signal, nothing.

408
00:33:21,286 --> 00:33:23,446
What if it was
some kind of accident?

409
00:33:23,539 --> 00:33:25,865
Someone killed J.D.
Don't you get it?

410
00:33:27,293 --> 00:33:29,453
Someone is here on this island.

411
00:33:30,798 --> 00:33:33,087
That wasn't there
last night either.

412
00:33:39,559 --> 00:33:41,350
12:00.

413
00:33:41,435 --> 00:33:42,811
It's an hour and a half.

414
00:33:42,895 --> 00:33:44,935
It's a message.

415
00:33:47,150 --> 00:33:49,358
What about the boat?

416
00:33:49,445 --> 00:33:52,980
We saw that pier with the boat
when we flew in.

417
00:33:53,074 --> 00:33:55,150
Watch your backs
and everyone else's.

418
00:33:55,244 --> 00:33:56,786
Hit the boat and find the radio.

419
00:33:56,829 --> 00:33:59,368
The simulation's over.

420
00:34:11,679 --> 00:34:14,515
Now is not the time for fear,
people.

421
00:34:15,434 --> 00:34:17,676
Now is the ti...

422
00:34:18,771 --> 00:34:20,052
Shit.

423
00:34:37,418 --> 00:34:38,877
- Sara!
- Ohh!

424
00:34:41,047 --> 00:34:42,292
Sara!

425
00:34:42,382 --> 00:34:44,209
Get her out of the water!

426
00:35:05,535 --> 00:35:08,109
Help me get her
out of the water!

427
00:35:10,041 --> 00:35:12,200
Get her out of the water!

428
00:35:12,294 --> 00:35:14,203
Ugh!

429
00:35:14,254 --> 00:35:16,413
It's okay.
You're okay.

430
00:35:16,507 --> 00:35:18,132
Aah!

431
00:35:18,217 --> 00:35:19,926
I'll handle it.
I'll handle it.

432
00:35:20,012 --> 00:35:21,090
I've got her.

433
00:35:21,178 --> 00:35:23,634
Back the fuck off!
I'll handle it!

434
00:35:29,522 --> 00:35:31,100
It's okay.

435
00:35:31,191 --> 00:35:33,943
You're out of the water,
all right? You're out.

436
00:35:34,028 --> 00:35:35,308
Aah!

437
00:35:36,155 --> 00:35:39,027
All right.
You're out of the water.

438
00:35:40,367 --> 00:35:42,990
- You're okay.
- What's her thing with water?

439
00:35:45,582 --> 00:35:47,456
I think I lost my smokes.

440
00:35:49,003 --> 00:35:52,040
Harris brought us
to this island.

441
00:35:52,132 --> 00:35:55,169
Now we're not allowed to leave.

442
00:35:55,261 --> 00:35:58,013
Let's talk about this Harris.

443
00:35:58,098 --> 00:36:00,091
Harris wouldn't do this.

444
00:36:00,142 --> 00:36:02,632
You can say what you want,
but Harris is a company man.

445
00:36:02,686 --> 00:36:06,186
Did anyone actually see him
get back in that chopper?

446
00:36:06,273 --> 00:36:08,065
Oh, tell me
somebody witnessed that.

447
00:36:08,151 --> 00:36:10,690
Maybe he got tired
of the simulations.

448
00:36:10,779 --> 00:36:13,353
Missed the taste
of the real thing.

449
00:36:15,326 --> 00:36:17,699
I'll give him a taste
of the real thing.

450
00:36:17,788 --> 00:36:20,242
Did he just pull
that gun out of his arse?

451
00:36:21,541 --> 00:36:23,997
We weren't supposed to
bring weapons.

452
00:36:24,044 --> 00:36:25,836
My gun goes where I go.

453
00:36:25,922 --> 00:36:28,876
If you get shot sometime,
maybe you'll understand.

454
00:36:28,967 --> 00:36:31,637
You shouldn't have brought
your weapon, Vince.

455
00:36:32,096 --> 00:36:34,504
You're gonna be glad I did.

456
00:36:45,277 --> 00:36:46,986
Two square miles at most.

457
00:36:47,030 --> 00:36:49,948
Hey.
Check this out.

458
00:36:51,494 --> 00:36:53,902
Who wants to play
some hide-and-seek?

459
00:36:55,457 --> 00:36:57,165
Anyone else is on this island,

460
00:36:57,209 --> 00:37:00,375
Harris or worse,
we're gonna find them.

461
00:37:00,462 --> 00:37:03,547
How's about your Navy?

462
00:37:03,633 --> 00:37:05,875
They don't muck around, do they?

463
00:37:16,565 --> 00:37:18,558
Damn cats.

464
00:37:44,639 --> 00:37:47,213
Aah! Aah!

465
00:37:47,309 --> 00:37:50,394
Oh, for the love of God,
just take the arm.

466
00:37:52,732 --> 00:37:56,731
There. There.
That's the Lucas I know.

467
00:37:56,820 --> 00:37:59,904
You want to get up
and do it all over again.

468
00:37:59,990 --> 00:38:02,150
Are you all right?

469
00:38:02,243 --> 00:38:03,524
Yeah.
I told you I'm fine.

470
00:38:03,620 --> 00:38:05,115
Yeah, you told me, but...

471
00:38:05,205 --> 00:38:07,245
As long as people aren't
asking me if I'm all right,

472
00:38:07,333 --> 00:38:09,160
I'm all right.

473
00:38:10,712 --> 00:38:12,954
So can I ask you
something else, then?

474
00:38:13,047 --> 00:38:15,966
Anything else.

475
00:38:16,009 --> 00:38:18,548
Well, since the end
may be near here,

476
00:38:18,638 --> 00:38:21,971
have you kind of always
sort of had a thing for me?

477
00:38:26,272 --> 00:38:28,146
Aah!

478
00:38:30,652 --> 00:38:32,396
Is that a no?

479
00:38:35,241 --> 00:38:37,483
20 minutes of 12:00.

480
00:38:48,006 --> 00:38:50,544
So at 12:00
someone else is killed?

481
00:38:51,676 --> 00:38:53,337
Somebody left those watches.

482
00:38:53,429 --> 00:38:55,173
And left them
after Harris had gone.

483
00:38:55,264 --> 00:38:57,802
Where is this killer?
We searched the island.

484
00:38:57,893 --> 00:39:00,051
Somebody set that trap.

485
00:39:00,145 --> 00:39:01,555
Somebody rigged that boat.

486
00:39:01,646 --> 00:39:04,138
So what are we saying?

487
00:39:04,191 --> 00:39:05,935
This is some kind of game?

488
00:39:06,027 --> 00:39:09,479
Eeny, meeny, miney, mo.

489
00:39:09,531 --> 00:39:11,773
Who's the next motherfucker
to go?

490
00:39:14,162 --> 00:39:16,119
It's 12:00.

491
00:39:16,206 --> 00:39:18,033
It's 12:00,
and we're still here!

492
00:39:18,125 --> 00:39:20,283
We're still here,
and it's 12:00, and...

493
00:39:20,376 --> 00:39:22,416
Shut up, Vince.

494
00:39:22,504 --> 00:39:24,082
All right. Look.

495
00:39:24,173 --> 00:39:26,545
We know that there
is a killer on the island.

496
00:39:26,634 --> 00:39:28,758
Someone who knows
what we're here for,

497
00:39:28,846 --> 00:39:30,505
someone who knows where we'd be.

498
00:39:30,597 --> 00:39:32,555
There's just one problem.

499
00:39:32,599 --> 00:39:36,100
There's no one
on the island but us.

500
00:39:41,193 --> 00:39:42,937
Now, hold on.

501
00:39:43,738 --> 00:39:45,564
Real slow.

502
00:39:45,614 --> 00:39:47,692
Real easy like.

503
00:39:47,743 --> 00:39:51,575
Let's all move our hands
away from our weapons.

504
00:39:52,039 --> 00:39:54,033
- You get on the ground.
- Lucas.

505
00:39:54,125 --> 00:39:57,626
I'm checking the rooms.
I find this... by his bed.

506
00:39:57,713 --> 00:40:01,082
It's maps of the island,
the building, everything here.

507
00:40:01,174 --> 00:40:02,919
Been doing some research
on the place?

508
00:40:03,010 --> 00:40:05,928
- I can goddamn explain.
- You can get on the ground!

509
00:40:05,972 --> 00:40:09,424
This is a military facility!
No one has access to this stuff!

510
00:40:09,476 --> 00:40:11,434
Whoa.

511
00:40:15,275 --> 00:40:18,941
You got me all wrong.

512
00:40:19,029 --> 00:40:21,152
Oh, yeah, Detective?
They your maps?

513
00:40:21,240 --> 00:40:24,692
I want to see
your hands up. Up!

514
00:40:25,454 --> 00:40:26,912
You believe me.

515
00:40:27,956 --> 00:40:30,449
- No one leaves this room.
- Since when is this room safe?

516
00:40:30,543 --> 00:40:31,954
Since we're all in it.

517
00:40:32,003 --> 00:40:33,961
On your knees now.

518
00:40:34,047 --> 00:40:36,336
Now! Down!

519
00:40:46,186 --> 00:40:49,639
Sara, can you feel your face?

520
00:40:49,732 --> 00:40:52,687
Because I can't feel
your face...

521
00:40:57,116 --> 00:40:59,073
Coffee.

522
00:40:59,159 --> 00:41:00,820
Huh?

523
00:41:00,911 --> 00:41:02,905
There's something in the coffee.

524
00:41:02,997 --> 00:41:05,536
Ohh!

525
00:41:06,335 --> 00:41:07,415
Ohh.

526
00:41:09,506 --> 00:41:10,751
Ohh!

527
00:41:11,883 --> 00:41:12,963
Hey, Nic...

528
00:41:13,051 --> 00:41:16,920
Stay... away from...

529
00:42:38,610 --> 00:42:41,445
You going somewhere?

530
00:42:42,281 --> 00:42:43,692
Come here.

531
00:42:43,782 --> 00:42:45,692
Sit down.

532
00:42:45,785 --> 00:42:48,028
- Hey, man, I can explain.
- Shut up.

533
00:42:48,122 --> 00:42:50,198
- Listen, I can explain.
- I said shut up!

534
00:42:50,291 --> 00:42:51,749
You don't know
what you're doing.

535
00:42:51,793 --> 00:42:52,956
You don't know who I am.

536
00:42:53,044 --> 00:42:55,714
I know you killed J.D.
That's what I know.

537
00:42:55,798 --> 00:42:57,375
Is everybody all right?

538
00:42:57,466 --> 00:43:00,164
Sara.

539
00:43:02,638 --> 00:43:04,714
Hey. Hey.
Sara.

540
00:43:04,808 --> 00:43:07,015
Sara? Hey.

541
00:43:12,608 --> 00:43:16,144
I just had the worst dream ever.

542
00:43:16,238 --> 00:43:17,863
Come on.

543
00:43:17,949 --> 00:43:19,740
Look.

544
00:43:19,825 --> 00:43:22,946
If I'm the killer,
why didn't I run?

545
00:43:24,665 --> 00:43:27,369
You were all lying here.
How come so am I?

546
00:43:27,459 --> 00:43:30,579
Maybe it's a trick so you
can finish what you started!

547
00:43:30,672 --> 00:43:32,831
Look, I'll tell you why
the maps were in the bedroom.

548
00:43:32,925 --> 00:43:35,083
No! You tell us
what you put in the coffee!

549
00:43:35,177 --> 00:43:38,462
- That's what you tell us.
- Hey! Who made it?

550
00:43:39,223 --> 00:43:41,180
Did I make the coffee?

551
00:43:41,935 --> 00:43:43,477
Sherlock Holmes
over there made it.

552
00:43:43,562 --> 00:43:45,353
The man is calling you a killer.

553
00:43:45,397 --> 00:43:48,268
Personally, I think you might
want to defend yourself.

554
00:43:49,193 --> 00:43:51,233
Aah! Aah! Aah!

555
00:43:51,321 --> 00:43:54,322
Oh, fuck!
Ohh!

556
00:43:55,451 --> 00:43:58,571
Oh, fuck!

557
00:43:59,664 --> 00:44:01,039
There's...

558
00:44:01,124 --> 00:44:02,535
There's no blood.

559
00:44:02,626 --> 00:44:04,369
Somebody...

560
00:44:04,462 --> 00:44:06,668
drained his blood.

561
00:44:30,241 --> 00:44:31,653
6:00.

562
00:44:31,744 --> 00:44:33,784
Two watches.

563
00:44:33,871 --> 00:44:37,491
Two watches means two victims?

564
00:44:38,250 --> 00:44:40,577
We got 20 minutes.

565
00:44:40,629 --> 00:44:42,586
All right.

566
00:44:45,885 --> 00:44:47,843
Right. I want to know what
the next trap is.

567
00:44:47,930 --> 00:44:49,888
And I want to know now.

568
00:44:49,932 --> 00:44:52,471
I can't tell you
because I don't know!

569
00:44:52,561 --> 00:44:54,519
You've been lying to us
since we got here.

570
00:44:54,605 --> 00:44:56,314
That doesn't make me
the killer.

571
00:44:56,399 --> 00:44:58,936
The dead people does.

572
00:44:59,026 --> 00:45:01,482
How about the loner mentality?

573
00:45:01,571 --> 00:45:03,445
How about the issues
with the FBI?

574
00:45:03,490 --> 00:45:04,569
I'm not a cop.

575
00:45:04,658 --> 00:45:06,983
I'm an investigator
with the Department of Justice.

576
00:45:07,077 --> 00:45:09,569
I was sent to
investigate Harris.

577
00:45:09,664 --> 00:45:12,239
The attorney general was hearing
rumors about his methods.

578
00:45:12,334 --> 00:45:15,004
There was talk he was
pushing trainees too far.

579
00:45:15,087 --> 00:45:17,496
The FBI investigates the FBI.

580
00:45:17,591 --> 00:45:19,382
Not if you want it done right.

581
00:45:19,467 --> 00:45:21,709
Look, they took him out
of the field for a reason.

582
00:45:21,803 --> 00:45:23,677
Justice was talking
maybe that wasn't enough.

583
00:45:23,764 --> 00:45:25,472
They sent me to see
how he works you.

584
00:45:25,558 --> 00:45:27,965
The maps were prep.
It's a job!

585
00:45:28,019 --> 00:45:29,514
Oh, this is not happening.

586
00:45:29,604 --> 00:45:33,020
You want to hook me up to
a polygraph, hook me up!

587
00:45:33,109 --> 00:45:35,102
Yeah, we know how to beat
a polygraph, too.

588
00:45:35,195 --> 00:45:38,065
He's lying.
Watch his eyes.

589
00:45:39,199 --> 00:45:42,284
I'm not lying.
I just don't like you.

590
00:45:43,954 --> 00:45:45,947
Okay.
You got 15 minutes.

591
00:45:45,999 --> 00:45:47,493
So tell us where the trap is,

592
00:45:47,542 --> 00:45:50,248
or you never leave this room,
and I mean never.

593
00:45:50,337 --> 00:45:51,831
Don't take your eyes off of him.

594
00:45:51,922 --> 00:45:53,666
Okay.

595
00:45:57,179 --> 00:45:59,301
Now, start talking.

596
00:46:03,394 --> 00:46:05,683
It's a nine-number sequence
repeating itself.

597
00:46:05,730 --> 00:46:07,308
Nine permutations.

598
00:46:07,399 --> 00:46:08,977
What? A code?
A combination?

599
00:46:09,068 --> 00:46:11,357
It has something to do
with time!

600
00:46:11,404 --> 00:46:13,148
He has an obsession with time!

601
00:46:13,198 --> 00:46:15,107
Forget the numbers.
We need to find the trap.

602
00:46:15,200 --> 00:46:16,611
The numbers are the message.

603
00:46:16,701 --> 00:46:18,824
What if it tells us
where the trap might be?

604
00:46:18,912 --> 00:46:20,703
Fine. Bobby,
help her work the numbers.

605
00:46:20,789 --> 00:46:22,533
I'm searching the building.

606
00:46:22,624 --> 00:46:24,416
I'm searching with you.

607
00:46:27,214 --> 00:46:28,376
10 minutes.

608
00:46:47,696 --> 00:46:50,104
Phone number, Social Security
number, coordinates.

609
00:46:50,199 --> 00:46:52,358
- Talk to me!
- Seven minutes.

610
00:46:53,912 --> 00:46:55,620
Between you and me...

611
00:46:57,041 --> 00:46:59,080
I'm not a violent person.

612
00:46:59,167 --> 00:47:01,575
The thing I've learned
in my life is this.

613
00:47:01,628 --> 00:47:04,631
Sometimes if you find yourself
feeling deep anger

614
00:47:04,716 --> 00:47:06,092
and frustration

615
00:47:06,176 --> 00:47:10,009
about where you find yourself,
what has happened to you...

616
00:47:10,849 --> 00:47:14,016
The healthy thing to do
is to find an outlet

617
00:47:14,102 --> 00:47:16,510
and let it all fucking go.

618
00:47:17,272 --> 00:47:18,815
6:00.

619
00:47:18,899 --> 00:47:22,020
One of us dies,
my outlet is you.

620
00:47:34,877 --> 00:47:37,414
I am not your guy.

621
00:47:42,678 --> 00:47:44,754
You don't want to do this, man.

622
00:47:45,514 --> 00:47:48,469
You'll have to live
with what you don't know.

623
00:47:49,811 --> 00:47:51,769
I think we're clear
on this level.

624
00:47:51,855 --> 00:47:53,979
The obsession is time.
It has to do with time.

625
00:47:54,066 --> 00:47:55,346
I know it.

626
00:47:55,443 --> 00:47:58,479
5, 8, 2, 9, 9, 7, 9, 2, 4.
Whatisit?

627
00:47:58,571 --> 00:47:59,602
Sara, it's no use.

628
00:47:59,656 --> 00:48:02,194
8, 2, 9, 9, 7, 9, 2, 4, 5.

629
00:48:02,283 --> 00:48:03,279
- What is that?
- Sara...

630
00:48:03,369 --> 00:48:04,863
2, 9, 9, 7, 9...

631
00:48:04,953 --> 00:48:08,323
It's a number!
It's a fucking number!

632
00:48:08,417 --> 00:48:11,121
They're all just
fucking numbers!

633
00:48:23,444 --> 00:48:27,525
7, 9, 2... 4, 5, 8... 2, 7, 9.

634
00:48:27,616 --> 00:48:30,985
Anybody? Anyone?
What are we thinking here?

635
00:48:31,078 --> 00:48:32,703
What about a rate?

636
00:48:32,789 --> 00:48:35,161
When you factor in time,
an amount becomes a rate.

637
00:48:35,208 --> 00:48:36,240
Or a speed!

638
00:48:36,335 --> 00:48:38,458
Yes. What kind of speed
do you measure in the millions?

639
00:48:38,545 --> 00:48:41,118
Atoms? Electrons?
How the hell should I know?

640
00:48:42,090 --> 00:48:43,502
Light.

641
00:48:47,931 --> 00:48:50,933
299 million...

642
00:48:51,018 --> 00:48:53,688
792,458
meters per second.

643
00:48:53,772 --> 00:48:55,516
This is the original
measurement for light!

644
00:48:55,607 --> 00:48:56,852
And you know that?

645
00:48:56,941 --> 00:48:59,064
It's the basic principle
of physics.

646
00:48:59,153 --> 00:49:00,861
Along with "Shit happens. "

647
00:49:00,946 --> 00:49:02,773
Turn them off.

648
00:49:02,865 --> 00:49:04,194
The lights.
Turn them off.

649
00:49:04,284 --> 00:49:07,736
- What if that's the trap?
- It's about the light.

650
00:49:18,717 --> 00:49:20,461
What is that?

651
00:49:20,553 --> 00:49:21,502
What?

652
00:49:21,596 --> 00:49:23,672
The back of your coat.

653
00:49:30,148 --> 00:49:31,976
It's on yours, too.

654
00:49:35,029 --> 00:49:37,401
He's marked us.

655
00:49:37,447 --> 00:49:39,487
Letters.

656
00:49:41,369 --> 00:49:43,113
It's like a powder.

657
00:49:43,205 --> 00:49:44,864
Put on us while we slept.

658
00:49:44,957 --> 00:49:47,080
"A"...

659
00:49:47,168 --> 00:49:48,543
"O"...

660
00:49:48,586 --> 00:49:51,078
"R"...

661
00:49:51,173 --> 00:49:53,711
"T."

662
00:49:53,800 --> 00:49:57,004
Tora? Rota? Roat?

663
00:49:58,764 --> 00:50:00,888
Otra?

664
00:50:00,976 --> 00:50:04,061
First it's numbers,
now it's letters.

665
00:50:06,399 --> 00:50:07,894
It's 6:00.

666
00:50:10,070 --> 00:50:11,612
It just turned 6:90.

667
00:50:16,577 --> 00:50:19,365
Hey, who's out there?

668
00:50:19,455 --> 00:50:21,365
Anybody hear me?

669
00:50:31,769 --> 00:50:33,642
You're a dead man.

670
00:50:33,730 --> 00:50:36,302
You guys!
Down here!

671
00:50:44,867 --> 00:50:46,148
Aah!

672
00:50:47,328 --> 00:50:48,989
Aah!

673
00:50:50,248 --> 00:50:51,874
Aah!

674
00:51:21,117 --> 00:51:22,577
Vince!

675
00:51:24,163 --> 00:51:25,706
Vince, listen to me.

676
00:51:25,790 --> 00:51:27,332
We've got to shut off
the power.

677
00:51:27,417 --> 00:51:29,576
Fuck you!
It's your trap!

678
00:51:29,670 --> 00:51:32,874
Oh, yeah, I'm so clever,
I'm about to kill myself.

679
00:51:32,965 --> 00:51:35,254
Man, there are circuit breakers
in that storeroom.

680
00:51:35,343 --> 00:51:37,916
Can you get there?
Can you reach it?

681
00:51:38,012 --> 00:51:39,424
Can you reach it?

682
00:51:42,059 --> 00:51:45,226
Look, I can, but you got to
give me your gun.

683
00:51:45,313 --> 00:51:46,559
I ain't giving you shit!

684
00:51:46,648 --> 00:51:49,769
Are you gonna hang on forever,
or throw me your gun?

685
00:51:49,860 --> 00:51:51,485
I'm gonna watch you die.

686
00:51:51,571 --> 00:51:54,192
Watch me die, and then what?
And then what?

687
00:52:00,748 --> 00:52:03,370
Come on! Please!

688
00:52:06,838 --> 00:52:08,333
Throw it!

689
00:53:18,381 --> 00:53:22,082
I'm losing my grip, Gabe.

690
00:53:23,845 --> 00:53:24,794
Ohh!

691
00:53:33,107 --> 00:53:34,482
Stairs.

692
00:53:45,579 --> 00:53:48,285
Oh, fuck.
I'm losing my grip!

693
00:53:49,794 --> 00:53:51,834
Come on, Gabe.

694
00:54:02,892 --> 00:54:05,465
Come on, Gabe!

695
00:54:05,561 --> 00:54:06,592
Come on!

696
00:54:13,697 --> 00:54:16,234
Vince, what's happening
in there?!

697
00:54:16,323 --> 00:54:19,527
Stay out of the water!
Stay out of the water!

698
00:54:26,544 --> 00:54:27,873
Where's that cop?!

699
00:54:32,260 --> 00:54:33,458
Vince!

700
00:54:33,553 --> 00:54:34,716
Aah!

701
00:54:37,431 --> 00:54:38,927
Lights out.

702
00:54:48,739 --> 00:54:49,937
I'm alive!

703
00:54:50,032 --> 00:54:51,692
Vince, what's going on?
Talk to me.

704
00:54:51,784 --> 00:54:53,361
I'm alive!

705
00:54:53,452 --> 00:54:54,616
Oh!

706
00:54:59,918 --> 00:55:00,997
Yes!

707
00:55:03,714 --> 00:55:04,710
You okay?

708
00:55:04,757 --> 00:55:08,091
I'm alive! I'm alive!

709
00:55:10,055 --> 00:55:12,808
He saved my life, Lucas.

710
00:55:14,935 --> 00:55:17,343
Still think you know me, Agent?

711
00:55:17,439 --> 00:55:19,146
Still think you know who I am?

712
00:55:23,946 --> 00:55:26,652
All right.
How do we turn off the water?

713
00:55:28,369 --> 00:55:31,286
Look, whoever did this
really knows his engineering.

714
00:55:31,331 --> 00:55:32,873
Remotes, timers.

715
00:55:32,957 --> 00:55:35,448
They teach this in first- year
with siege tactics.

716
00:55:35,543 --> 00:55:39,126
But to set this up fast, you
got to know what you're doing.

717
00:55:39,214 --> 00:55:42,132
Pressure plates,
radio detonators.

718
00:55:42,217 --> 00:55:45,837
It's all private- sector sold.
The wiring's the tricky part.

719
00:55:48,684 --> 00:55:52,932
People take specialty courses
in this sort of thing for years.

720
00:55:56,818 --> 00:55:58,361
Right.

721
00:56:02,325 --> 00:56:03,653
Thank you.

722
00:56:04,828 --> 00:56:06,453
You can all go to hell.

723
00:56:11,419 --> 00:56:13,079
Bobby!

724
00:56:15,840 --> 00:56:18,462
Look at me, look at me,
look at me!

725
00:56:37,908 --> 00:56:39,700
Two watches, two traps.

726
00:56:41,246 --> 00:56:42,953
Son of a bitch.

727
00:56:48,296 --> 00:56:50,419
So how about me, huh?

728
00:56:52,426 --> 00:56:54,714
How about me?!
Is it my fucking time?!

729
00:56:54,802 --> 00:56:57,045
Right here, right now!

730
00:56:57,139 --> 00:57:00,057
Who fucking wants it?!

731
00:57:00,101 --> 00:57:03,056
It was you who said
to turn off the water.

732
00:57:15,660 --> 00:57:18,579
Yeah, whatever
makes you feel better.

733
00:57:30,095 --> 00:57:31,471
Sara?

734
00:57:31,555 --> 00:57:35,849
I don't think any of us
should be alone right now.

735
00:57:35,935 --> 00:57:37,133
Okay?

736
00:57:39,856 --> 00:57:42,145
Nic found another watch.

737
00:57:47,783 --> 00:57:49,906
We've got an hour and a half.

738
00:57:51,704 --> 00:57:53,412
So what's with the jackets?

739
00:57:53,497 --> 00:57:56,284
If it's a message,
what's the order?

740
00:57:56,375 --> 00:57:58,119
The order we're dying in?

741
00:57:58,211 --> 00:58:01,129
J.D., Rafe, Bobby.
Which letters were theirs?

742
00:58:01,215 --> 00:58:03,124
That wouldn't work.
These were traps.

743
00:58:03,217 --> 00:58:04,795
They could've killed
any one of us.

744
00:58:04,886 --> 00:58:08,172
How about the order
we signed up with the bureau?

745
00:58:08,265 --> 00:58:09,593
Who here had seniority?

746
00:58:09,642 --> 00:58:11,433
J.D., then Bobby.

747
00:58:11,477 --> 00:58:12,806
- Then me.
- Then me.

748
00:58:12,896 --> 00:58:15,600
Cro...

749
00:58:16,983 --> 00:58:20,103
Atone?

750
00:58:20,153 --> 00:58:24,448
Crotone?

751
00:58:24,492 --> 00:58:27,578
Crotone, Croato, Croa...

752
00:58:27,663 --> 00:58:29,240
Might as well pick them
at random.

753
00:58:29,331 --> 00:58:31,075
Croatoan.

754
00:58:31,167 --> 00:58:34,999
Like the island, the colony.

755
00:58:36,380 --> 00:58:37,662
Do you know where we are?

756
00:58:37,758 --> 00:58:40,795
Near the Outer Banks
of North Carolina?

757
00:58:40,886 --> 00:58:42,131
It's one of the first sites

758
00:58:42,221 --> 00:58:45,757
settled by the Europeans
in the New World.

759
00:58:45,851 --> 00:58:48,971
In the 16th century,
there was a ship of settlers

760
00:58:49,021 --> 00:58:50,979
who landed right around here,

761
00:58:51,065 --> 00:58:54,350
sent to colonize
the place for England.

762
00:58:54,360 --> 00:58:58,490
They built their town
on Roanoke Island.

763
00:58:58,532 --> 00:59:01,487
Over 100 people.

764
00:59:01,536 --> 00:59:04,491
Two years later,
a supply ship sailed in...

765
00:59:04,540 --> 00:59:07,909
only to find
that the colony had vanished

766
00:59:08,002 --> 00:59:10,410
without a trace.

767
00:59:10,505 --> 00:59:14,882
No bodies, no papers,
no evidence of anything.

768
00:59:16,678 --> 00:59:19,763
Over 100 people.

769
00:59:19,849 --> 00:59:21,676
Gone.

770
00:59:23,019 --> 00:59:26,603
And the only thing left
was a single word

771
00:59:26,691 --> 00:59:29,229
found carved in a tree.

772
00:59:30,362 --> 00:59:32,022
Croatoan.

773
00:59:34,574 --> 00:59:36,116
What was Croatoan?

774
00:59:36,202 --> 00:59:37,744
Some said a body of water.

775
00:59:37,828 --> 00:59:39,951
Others said an Indian tribe.

776
00:59:40,039 --> 00:59:43,456
Point is, is 500 years later,

777
00:59:43,544 --> 00:59:46,332
we still don't know
where those people have gone.

778
00:59:46,422 --> 00:59:48,462
That's the message.

779
00:59:50,385 --> 00:59:52,592
An island full
of people vanish forever.

780
00:59:52,680 --> 00:59:54,471
And it happened here.

781
00:59:54,556 --> 00:59:57,474
The killer isn't after the FBI.

782
00:59:57,560 --> 01:00:00,015
He's after infamy.

783
01:00:02,065 --> 01:00:04,189
It troubles me
that you know this story.

784
01:00:04,277 --> 01:00:07,195
It'd trouble you more
if I didn't.

785
01:00:08,865 --> 01:00:11,535
All right, we know method,
we know motive.

786
01:00:11,619 --> 01:00:16,364
All that's missing now
is where he made his mistake.

787
01:01:01,135 --> 01:01:02,510
Got something.

788
01:01:16,694 --> 01:01:18,189
We've got blood.

789
01:01:18,280 --> 01:01:20,189
Under Rafe's nails.

790
01:01:20,282 --> 01:01:23,698
He struggled with the killer.
We got to run it past autorad.

791
01:01:25,038 --> 01:01:27,280
What are you staring at?

792
01:01:27,374 --> 01:01:28,834
Time.

793
01:01:35,591 --> 01:01:37,335
Somebody know how this works?

794
01:01:37,427 --> 01:01:39,919
I do. We can have
a DNA match in under an hour.

795
01:01:40,014 --> 01:01:42,386
We've only got
less than an hour.

796
01:01:42,433 --> 01:01:45,720
We'll need blood comparisons
from each of us...

797
01:01:45,771 --> 01:01:48,523
unless anyone
has a problem with that.

798
01:02:44,256 --> 01:02:46,499
God, I want a cigarette.

799
01:02:46,593 --> 01:02:48,087
You and me both.

800
01:02:50,598 --> 01:02:53,052
You're a gambling man,
aren't you, Lucas?

801
01:02:53,141 --> 01:02:54,517
Who would you put
your money on now?

802
01:02:54,601 --> 01:02:56,429
Not sure my money
would go anywhere different.

803
01:02:56,479 --> 01:02:58,187
We just about died down there.

804
01:02:58,272 --> 01:03:00,562
You didn't know
you'd be down there.

805
01:03:00,650 --> 01:03:02,395
What do you do?
Not help Vince?

806
01:03:02,486 --> 01:03:04,064
We're gonna trust you then?

807
01:03:04,154 --> 01:03:06,064
I'll trust you when you're dead.

808
01:03:06,157 --> 01:03:08,779
Well, let me enlighten you. You
know there's a bomb on a boat.

809
01:03:08,869 --> 01:03:11,361
You don't run toward it
first in line.

810
01:03:11,456 --> 01:03:12,701
I don't.
Maybe you do.

811
01:03:12,789 --> 01:03:15,161
Enough!

812
01:03:31,396 --> 01:03:33,102
Guns on the table.

813
01:03:33,189 --> 01:03:34,517
Everybody.

814
01:03:48,039 --> 01:03:50,578
I'm not giving up my gun.

815
01:03:50,668 --> 01:03:53,787
I think I speak for the group
when I say, "That would be bad. "

816
01:03:53,879 --> 01:03:57,332
I don't go anywhere
without my gun.

817
01:03:57,425 --> 01:04:01,376
I'll give up my wheels first.
I'll give up my chair.

818
01:04:01,430 --> 01:04:04,800
I'm not giving up my gun.

819
01:04:04,892 --> 01:04:06,222
You got it!

820
01:04:12,069 --> 01:04:13,727
Hit the damn thing.

821
01:04:13,819 --> 01:04:15,101
Hit it!

822
01:04:23,039 --> 01:04:24,202
On the ground.

823
01:04:24,249 --> 01:04:25,281
Nic, wait.

824
01:04:26,335 --> 01:04:28,375
Nic, it's not me.
It's a mistake.

825
01:04:28,421 --> 01:04:30,627
On the ground, damn it!

826
01:04:30,715 --> 01:04:32,588
I will waste you, Sara.

827
01:04:32,633 --> 01:04:34,923
You want to kill me, huh?
You want to kill me?

828
01:04:35,011 --> 01:04:37,847
- Situation secure, Nic.
- That's what Harris says, right?

829
01:04:37,932 --> 01:04:40,387
The situation is secure
on the drive home.

830
01:04:40,476 --> 01:04:41,639
Ugh!

831
01:04:44,607 --> 01:04:46,730
Lower your weapon, Agent.

832
01:04:53,409 --> 01:04:57,075
Lucas, Lucas.
It's not me, Lucas.

833
01:04:57,163 --> 01:04:58,907
Tell them.

834
01:04:58,957 --> 01:05:00,202
It's not me.

835
01:05:01,252 --> 01:05:03,209
It don't make sense.
Why her?

836
01:05:04,214 --> 01:05:06,456
Because she
wasn't gonna make it.

837
01:05:07,676 --> 01:05:10,168
She wasn't gonna make profiler.

838
01:05:10,263 --> 01:05:12,338
Saw the recommends myself.

839
01:05:14,225 --> 01:05:15,850
Neither were you, Vince.

840
01:05:15,936 --> 01:05:20,017
But I never had someone
in my family get murdered.

841
01:05:20,107 --> 01:05:24,520
No kid sister of mine
ever got drowned and raped,

842
01:05:24,613 --> 01:05:29,691
drowned and raped
over and over and over.

843
01:05:29,786 --> 01:05:32,905
Who knows what
that would do to my head?

844
01:05:32,997 --> 01:05:35,405
You don't know.

845
01:05:35,500 --> 01:05:38,704
The FBI didn't save
your sister, Sara.

846
01:05:38,796 --> 01:05:41,751
And they didn't catch
her killer.

847
01:05:41,841 --> 01:05:44,962
So why should they be able
to catch you...

848
01:05:45,012 --> 01:05:48,132
when you're so much smarter
than everyone?

849
01:05:48,224 --> 01:05:49,968
I swear.

850
01:05:51,477 --> 01:05:55,432
It's not me.

851
01:05:55,524 --> 01:05:58,193
She wouldn't.
Not Sara.

852
01:05:58,277 --> 01:06:00,186
That's why she planned it
for the island.

853
01:06:00,279 --> 01:06:02,237
She wanted us dead
and underwater,

854
01:06:02,323 --> 01:06:04,067
so we'd suffer.

855
01:06:04,159 --> 01:06:06,235
You ever see the pictures?

856
01:06:06,328 --> 01:06:08,737
Fucking brutal.

857
01:06:11,334 --> 01:06:14,704
I swear on my life it's not me.

858
01:06:15,756 --> 01:06:18,164
Well, we can stay
in here and debate.

859
01:06:19,761 --> 01:06:22,431
But there's 10 minutes
till the trap.

860
01:06:26,436 --> 01:06:29,188
What is the trap?
Where is the trap?

861
01:06:29,230 --> 01:06:30,476
I don't know.

862
01:06:30,566 --> 01:06:32,357
What is the trap?
Where is the trap?

863
01:06:32,442 --> 01:06:33,723
I don't know.

864
01:06:33,819 --> 01:06:36,524
What is the trap?
Where is the trap?

865
01:06:36,572 --> 01:06:37,568
I don't know.

866
01:06:37,615 --> 01:06:39,407
What is the trap, Sara?!

867
01:06:43,456 --> 01:06:46,160
- You tell me.
- No, you tell me!

868
01:06:46,251 --> 01:06:49,288
What if she's telling the truth,
Nic? Think about it.

869
01:06:50,423 --> 01:06:53,258
This is what the killer wants.

870
01:06:53,300 --> 01:06:56,385
Suspecting each other,
fighting each other.

871
01:06:57,930 --> 01:06:59,591
This is what makes it fun.

872
01:06:59,683 --> 01:07:02,435
You in the killer's mind again?

873
01:07:02,520 --> 01:07:04,429
We were all knocked out.

874
01:07:04,480 --> 01:07:06,722
He could've taken blood
from any of us.

875
01:07:06,816 --> 01:07:09,688
- You could've taken blood...
- I'll take blood from you!

876
01:07:09,778 --> 01:07:11,238
Come off that!

877
01:07:16,452 --> 01:07:17,911
Nicole...

878
01:07:19,664 --> 01:07:21,159
Nicole...

879
01:07:25,213 --> 01:07:27,206
Nobody else is gonna get killed.

880
01:07:27,299 --> 01:07:29,873
You want to protect her?

881
01:07:29,968 --> 01:07:32,720
She's been playing you
from the start, Lucas.

882
01:07:32,804 --> 01:07:37,053
You come after me,
I will shoot you on sight.

883
01:07:38,937 --> 01:07:40,183
Nicole...

884
01:07:40,272 --> 01:07:43,060
we need to stay together.

885
01:07:43,151 --> 01:07:46,485
If I am by myself,
I know who to trust.

886
01:07:46,530 --> 01:07:47,989
- You go out there running...
- Back!

887
01:07:48,032 --> 01:07:49,491
Okay.

888
01:07:50,826 --> 01:07:54,445
You go out that door,
you don't come back in.

889
01:07:54,539 --> 01:07:55,867
Why would I?

890
01:07:58,168 --> 01:08:00,161
Do your job.

891
01:08:01,839 --> 01:08:03,916
Put a bullet in her.

892
01:08:15,188 --> 01:08:16,682
Sara, put yourself
in our position.

893
01:08:16,773 --> 01:08:18,019
You're a professional.

894
01:08:18,108 --> 01:08:20,896
You have a prime suspect.
There are still lives at risk.

895
01:08:20,987 --> 01:08:22,446
What do you do?

896
01:08:23,824 --> 01:08:25,567
I don't fit the profile.

897
01:08:25,659 --> 01:08:27,866
Wouldn't you know
what not to fit?

898
01:08:30,791 --> 01:08:33,363
You say I kill for revenge.

899
01:08:33,459 --> 01:08:36,876
For my personal pain.

900
01:08:36,964 --> 01:08:40,215
That's not this killer.
This killer is impersonal.

901
01:08:40,301 --> 01:08:42,875
Deadlines, rules.

902
01:08:42,971 --> 01:08:45,509
They're ways
of proving superiority.

903
01:08:45,599 --> 01:08:47,639
She's right, Gabe.

904
01:08:47,727 --> 01:08:49,387
You know what else is right?

905
01:08:49,479 --> 01:08:52,230
They don't let killers
in the FBI.

906
01:08:52,315 --> 01:08:55,934
Playing hurt, playing wounded.

907
01:08:57,071 --> 01:08:58,898
Maybe that's her skill.

908
01:08:59,699 --> 01:09:01,906
We all have skills.

909
01:09:01,994 --> 01:09:05,078
Well, I say where there's
a skill, there's a weakness.

910
01:09:08,627 --> 01:09:10,453
We all have skills.

911
01:09:12,756 --> 01:09:13,954
Wait.
Let's think here.

912
01:09:14,049 --> 01:09:16,338
All along we've been assuming
the deaths have been random,

913
01:09:16,426 --> 01:09:18,135
that anybody
could walk into any trap.

914
01:09:18,221 --> 01:09:19,763
But look at the traps.

915
01:09:19,848 --> 01:09:22,386
J.D. dies because
he was out front, leading us.

916
01:09:22,434 --> 01:09:24,226
He was always out front.

917
01:09:24,311 --> 01:09:26,638
And Rafe.
Rafe's a coffee junkie.

918
01:09:26,731 --> 01:09:29,104
And Bobby. Who do we go to
to get something to work?

919
01:09:29,192 --> 01:09:30,307
Who's our Mr. Fix- it?

920
01:09:30,402 --> 01:09:33,023
You're saying he knew
who died, when?

921
01:09:33,113 --> 01:09:36,068
Knew it, planned it
through our characteristics,

922
01:09:36,116 --> 01:09:38,952
our skills, our weaknesses.

923
01:09:39,037 --> 01:09:42,703
All this time the killer's
been profiling us.

924
01:10:09,824 --> 01:10:10,902
Vince, who are you?

925
01:10:10,991 --> 01:10:12,616
What makes you different
from the rest?

926
01:10:12,701 --> 01:10:15,537
I don't know.
I mean, I know history.

927
01:10:15,622 --> 01:10:17,032
I do mazes.

928
01:10:17,123 --> 01:10:20,243
I'm in a goddamn chair.

929
01:10:20,336 --> 01:10:22,209
Lucas, how does he kill you?
Think.

930
01:10:22,297 --> 01:10:25,214
I'm our best shooter, best
driver. Those are my skills.

931
01:10:25,300 --> 01:10:27,459
And your weaknesses?

932
01:10:28,512 --> 01:10:31,430
I say I'm fearless, and I'm not.

933
01:10:31,515 --> 01:10:33,473
That leaves you, Sara.

934
01:10:35,144 --> 01:10:37,387
My sister was murdered.

935
01:10:37,481 --> 01:10:40,317
I haven't been
in the water since.

936
01:10:40,359 --> 01:10:42,103
I see her there.

937
01:10:43,112 --> 01:10:45,569
That's his signature.

938
01:10:45,657 --> 01:10:49,109
Oh, my God.
Nicole.

939
01:11:27,290 --> 01:11:28,914
Nicole!

940
01:11:51,276 --> 01:11:52,438
Jesus!

941
01:11:55,614 --> 01:11:56,943
No!

942
01:12:14,136 --> 01:12:16,212
She found herself
some cigarettes.

943
01:12:16,305 --> 01:12:18,713
They were laced
with some type of acid.

944
01:12:21,311 --> 01:12:23,684
- It's not her, Vince.
- Why?

945
01:12:23,773 --> 01:12:25,232
She figured out the pattern!

946
01:12:25,316 --> 01:12:28,769
So she saves herself.
Wouldn't you?

947
01:12:31,406 --> 01:12:32,901
I don't trust her.

948
01:12:34,284 --> 01:12:36,361
I don't trust any of you.

949
01:12:36,454 --> 01:12:39,325
Island fever. You got it.
He's got it. She's got it.

950
01:12:39,374 --> 01:12:41,581
And we're gonna ride it out
nice and friendly

951
01:12:41,669 --> 01:12:44,421
until somebody finds
another motherfucking watch.

952
01:12:46,967 --> 01:12:49,090
Are you having fun yet?

953
01:12:50,054 --> 01:12:51,547
I'm having fun.

954
01:12:51,639 --> 01:12:56,017
Harris. He's been watching us
all along.

955
01:12:56,895 --> 01:12:58,805
Did he know
you were from Justice?

956
01:12:58,856 --> 01:13:01,228
What if he figured out
he was being watched?

957
01:13:01,316 --> 01:13:01,898
No way!

958
01:13:01,984 --> 01:13:04,559
What if he knew they were gonna
take away his program?

959
01:13:04,655 --> 01:13:06,149
Is this what you wanted?

960
01:13:06,198 --> 01:13:07,277
I'm letting her go.

961
01:13:07,365 --> 01:13:09,822
Too bad you won't get
a chance to graduate.

962
01:13:09,911 --> 01:13:11,950
You're all so weak.

963
01:13:12,037 --> 01:13:13,497
Pathetic, powerless.

964
01:13:13,581 --> 01:13:15,040
You said
you searched the island!

965
01:13:15,124 --> 01:13:17,877
- Every corner of it!
- Every corner you could see?!

966
01:13:17,961 --> 01:13:20,453
You'll never be in control
no matter how hard you try.

967
01:13:20,548 --> 01:13:23,039
All right, he's out there.
Who's with me?

968
01:13:23,134 --> 01:13:25,804
Out there?
What do you think this is?

969
01:13:25,888 --> 01:13:29,339
This is a fucking trap. What
do you mean who's with you?

970
01:13:31,226 --> 01:13:33,100
I'll tell you who's with you.

971
01:13:34,564 --> 01:13:37,102
- I'm with you.
- Are you having fun yet?

972
01:13:37,192 --> 01:13:39,232
I'm having fun.
Are you having fun?

973
01:13:39,319 --> 01:13:41,527
You're all going out there?

974
01:13:41,614 --> 01:13:44,782
Look, I'm not going anywhere.

975
01:13:44,868 --> 01:13:46,826
You're right.
You stay put.

976
01:13:46,912 --> 01:13:49,036
What the fuck?

977
01:13:49,123 --> 01:13:50,582
What are you doing?

978
01:13:53,753 --> 01:13:56,375
Still think
that you're better than me?

979
01:14:01,053 --> 01:14:02,513
Hide.

980
01:14:02,597 --> 01:14:05,005
Don't tell me where.
Don't tell them where.

981
01:14:05,100 --> 01:14:07,010
Just do it till Monday.

982
01:14:07,102 --> 01:14:09,060
It's for the best.

983
01:14:14,986 --> 01:14:17,443
My fucking gun's empty!

984
01:14:22,454 --> 01:14:25,658
Is this real enough for you?

985
01:14:25,750 --> 01:14:28,289
You can't escape it.

986
01:14:28,378 --> 01:14:30,120
You can't stop it.

987
01:14:31,881 --> 01:14:35,298
You can't turn it off.

988
01:15:51,392 --> 01:15:54,394
We can do this
all night long.

989
01:15:55,647 --> 01:15:59,516
I have all the time
in the world.

990
01:15:59,569 --> 01:16:05,277
Still think
you are better than me?

991
01:16:05,368 --> 01:16:08,453
Still think that the pupil
bests the teacher?

992
01:16:08,538 --> 01:16:11,290
Is this what you wanted?

993
01:16:11,374 --> 01:16:13,533
Is this what you expected?

994
01:16:13,627 --> 01:16:16,249
Is this real enough for you?

995
01:16:16,339 --> 01:16:18,497
You're all so weak.

996
01:16:18,591 --> 01:16:20,252
Pathetic.

997
01:16:20,343 --> 01:16:22,966
Too bad you won't get
a chance to graduate.

998
01:16:23,055 --> 01:16:26,590
You'll never be in control
no matter how hard you try.

999
01:16:26,685 --> 01:16:28,927
You always lose.

1000
01:16:29,021 --> 01:16:31,060
If you could only see yourselves
the way I see you.

1001
01:16:31,148 --> 01:16:33,604
Afraid, powerless.

1002
01:16:33,693 --> 01:16:36,647
Let me tell you what I think.

1003
01:16:36,738 --> 01:16:38,815
You look like you're having fun.

1004
01:16:38,907 --> 01:16:41,149
I'm having fun.

1005
01:16:41,243 --> 01:16:43,153
I don't want the fun to end.

1006
01:16:43,246 --> 01:16:46,533
I think they'll find you.

1007
01:16:46,625 --> 01:16:49,246
I don't want the fun to end.

1008
01:16:49,335 --> 01:16:50,961
Because I trained them.

1009
01:16:51,046 --> 01:16:54,048
You think you're smarter
than the rest of them?

1010
01:16:54,133 --> 01:16:55,628
Let me tell you what I think.

1011
01:16:55,719 --> 01:17:00,049
I think you
don't stand a chance.

1012
01:17:00,140 --> 01:17:03,012
You don't know who
you're dealing with, do you?

1013
01:17:03,102 --> 01:17:04,728
You don't know...

1014
01:17:04,813 --> 01:17:07,185
who you're dealing with, do you?

1015
01:17:07,274 --> 01:17:10,643
Come on, finish it.

1016
01:17:10,694 --> 01:17:13,268
Finish it, you selfish child.

1017
01:17:13,364 --> 01:17:14,775
Come on.

1018
01:17:19,497 --> 01:17:21,490
He never left.
He stayed to watch.

1019
01:17:21,583 --> 01:17:23,242
And the killer knew.

1020
01:17:27,798 --> 01:17:30,253
He's wearing watches.

1021
01:17:30,343 --> 01:17:32,419
Three watches.

1022
01:17:35,474 --> 01:17:37,217
What time are they set for?

1023
01:17:39,854 --> 01:17:41,764
They're set for now.

1024
01:17:41,856 --> 01:17:42,603
Aaah!

1025
01:17:59,794 --> 01:18:01,621
Shut it off!

1026
01:18:11,558 --> 01:18:12,886
If it wasn't him...

1027
01:18:16,730 --> 01:18:18,474
No, wait!

1028
01:18:18,566 --> 01:18:20,144
That's a clever story.

1029
01:18:20,235 --> 01:18:22,607
Sent to spy on the program,
spy on Harris.

1030
01:18:22,696 --> 01:18:24,488
You're the one
who's telling stories.

1031
01:18:24,573 --> 01:18:25,772
I know it's not me.

1032
01:18:25,866 --> 01:18:27,741
And I know it's not me.

1033
01:18:27,827 --> 01:18:29,618
So it's not you.
It's not me. It's not her.

1034
01:18:29,704 --> 01:18:31,080
Who's that leave, mister?

1035
01:18:31,123 --> 01:18:33,495
That leaves
the last man standing.

1036
01:18:53,732 --> 01:18:55,940
Jesus Christ, Sara!
Watch out!

1037
01:18:56,027 --> 01:18:58,067
Watch out for fucking who?!

1038
01:19:17,510 --> 01:19:20,133
Stop shooting!
Stop shooting!

1039
01:19:20,222 --> 01:19:23,842
Sara! Sara, stay right
where you are!

1040
01:19:59,601 --> 01:20:02,389
That's the price you pay
for being fearless.

1041
01:20:25,465 --> 01:20:26,960
Sara?

1042
01:20:34,350 --> 01:20:36,390
Sara?

1043
01:23:18,002 --> 01:23:19,829
Close, God damn it.

1044
01:23:26,304 --> 01:23:29,139
Who wants off this island?!

1045
01:23:32,310 --> 01:23:33,389
You.

1046
01:24:28,042 --> 01:24:30,249
Never anywhere without a gun.

1047
01:24:32,255 --> 01:24:34,130
Back on schedule.

1048
01:24:38,055 --> 01:24:40,808
Guess we have answers now,
don't we, Sara?

1049
01:24:49,485 --> 01:24:54,152
Who are you?

1050
01:24:55,200 --> 01:24:57,324
You gonna panic now, Sara?

1051
01:24:58,496 --> 01:25:01,368
You gonna panic
when you've been so cool?

1052
01:25:03,378 --> 01:25:04,623
Oh.

1053
01:25:05,713 --> 01:25:07,622
What are you trying to prove?

1054
01:25:07,715 --> 01:25:09,708
What am I trying to prove?

1055
01:25:10,468 --> 01:25:13,387
How's a fucked- up girl like you
get into the FBI...

1056
01:25:13,430 --> 01:25:15,388
anyway?

1057
01:25:17,143 --> 01:25:19,017
How did I get in?

1058
01:25:19,980 --> 01:25:22,768
How did I get in?
Did you not get in, Gabe?

1059
01:25:22,858 --> 01:25:25,350
Did you try,
and they turned you away?

1060
01:25:25,445 --> 01:25:26,689
What did they tell you?

1061
01:25:26,737 --> 01:25:29,229
You're not sharp enough,
smart enough,

1062
01:25:29,282 --> 01:25:31,025
sane enough?

1063
01:25:32,494 --> 01:25:33,953
Panic.

1064
01:25:38,085 --> 01:25:39,413
Watch her panic.

1065
01:25:39,503 --> 01:25:43,253
Get your hands up.
I want to see your hands!

1066
01:25:44,217 --> 01:25:45,213
Boo.

1067
01:25:45,302 --> 01:25:48,421
You call yourself a profiler?

1068
01:25:48,513 --> 01:25:51,301
Show me your hands.

1069
01:25:51,392 --> 01:25:53,017
I'm the profiler.

1070
01:25:53,102 --> 01:25:55,807
I want to see your hands.

1071
01:25:59,610 --> 01:26:00,890
You're the victim.

1072
01:26:09,829 --> 01:26:10,909
Unh!

1073
01:26:50,669 --> 01:26:51,665
Aah!

1074
01:26:52,088 --> 01:26:53,499
Aah!

1075
01:27:02,392 --> 01:27:04,385
Aaah!

1076
01:27:21,707 --> 01:27:22,453
Aah!

1077
01:28:16,813 --> 01:28:18,474
Watch your head.

1078
01:28:29,994 --> 01:28:32,071
Oh, thank God.

1079
01:28:33,499 --> 01:28:35,374
I thought...

1080
01:28:37,170 --> 01:28:38,878
Bulletproof vest.

1081
01:28:42,719 --> 01:28:47,262
I just need
a little "R" and "R," huh?

1082
01:28:47,349 --> 01:28:49,638
Surf and sand.

1083
01:28:52,020 --> 01:28:54,347
Just stay still.

1084
01:28:56,025 --> 01:28:58,268
- Just stay still.
- Uh- huh.

1085
01:29:00,865 --> 01:29:02,490
Hey, you, uh...

1086
01:29:03,910 --> 01:29:06,318
You think they're
ever gonna believe us?

1087
01:29:08,207 --> 01:29:10,614
They won't have to.

1088
01:29:10,668 --> 01:29:12,744
We can prove it.

1089
01:29:14,547 --> 01:29:16,754
After Bobby died...

1090
01:29:16,842 --> 01:29:19,678
I changed the clock back
15 minutes.

1091
01:29:21,931 --> 01:29:23,426
What are you talking about?

1092
01:29:23,517 --> 01:29:25,592
What did Harris always tell us?

1093
01:29:25,685 --> 01:29:29,269
Know the mind, then anticipate.

1094
01:29:29,356 --> 01:29:33,770
The killer was into deadlines,
precision, timing,

1095
01:29:33,861 --> 01:29:36,780
so I set that clock
15 minutes back.

1096
01:29:36,865 --> 01:29:38,277
The clock?

1097
01:29:38,367 --> 01:29:39,482
Oh, yeah.

1098
01:29:39,577 --> 01:29:42,448
He wanted us to know exactly
when he was going to strike,

1099
01:29:42,539 --> 01:29:43,784
wanted to watch us squirm

1100
01:29:43,874 --> 01:29:46,959
as precious seconds
were ticking away.

1101
01:29:47,044 --> 01:29:48,917
It was all part of his fun.

1102
01:29:49,922 --> 01:29:51,465
His weakness.

1103
01:29:52,884 --> 01:29:55,127
I was betting
he'd change it back.

1104
01:29:55,220 --> 01:29:56,762
I was right.

1105
01:29:57,681 --> 01:30:01,134
But how are you gonna prove it
was Gabe who changed it back?

1106
01:30:02,312 --> 01:30:05,314
Remember the phosphorescent
powder from the jackets?

1107
01:30:05,398 --> 01:30:07,356
That's what I put on the clock.

1108
01:30:15,286 --> 01:30:17,113
It was my turn to set a trap.

1109
01:30:17,205 --> 01:30:18,949
So when he touched it...

1110
01:30:19,040 --> 01:30:22,492
Mm- hmm.
His hands are going to glow.

1111
01:30:22,586 --> 01:30:23,785
Watch.

1112
01:30:55,583 --> 01:30:57,327
This is awkward.

1113
01:31:00,798 --> 01:31:02,589
You know, uh...

1114
01:31:04,469 --> 01:31:07,968
All these things, they worked
pretty good, you know.

1115
01:31:08,056 --> 01:31:10,844
Timers, triggers.

1116
01:31:10,934 --> 01:31:12,643
Remotes.

1117
01:31:14,647 --> 01:31:15,810
But at the end of the day,

1118
01:31:15,899 --> 01:31:20,277
building a better mousetrap
is just pure mechanics.

1119
01:31:20,320 --> 01:31:23,904
It's knowing how to bait
a particular mouse.

1120
01:31:23,992 --> 01:31:26,114
That's the fun part.

1121
01:31:27,537 --> 01:31:29,115
Ah, ah, ah- ah.

1122
01:31:39,093 --> 01:31:41,169
So there I was.

1123
01:31:41,262 --> 01:31:44,382
Sitting next to the bodies
of my parents.

1124
01:31:44,475 --> 01:31:45,589
Just waiting for someone

1125
01:31:45,683 --> 01:31:48,091
to ask me
why I killed them, you know?

1126
01:31:48,186 --> 01:31:50,096
And this detective
comes up to me, right?

1127
01:31:50,188 --> 01:31:51,932
And he says...

1128
01:31:53,401 --> 01:31:54,895
"Want some gum?"

1129
01:31:56,112 --> 01:31:57,358
Gum.

1130
01:31:58,533 --> 01:32:00,192
No one asks.

1131
01:32:00,326 --> 01:32:02,900
It never even occurs to them.

1132
01:32:04,247 --> 01:32:06,573
And like after
every first high...

1133
01:32:06,666 --> 01:32:10,285
it's harder and harder
to get to that place.

1134
01:32:10,380 --> 01:32:14,045
And finally you get so good,
there's no feeling at all.

1135
01:32:14,133 --> 01:32:15,628
It's easy.

1136
01:32:17,054 --> 01:32:19,628
Finding a worthy prey.

1137
01:32:19,724 --> 01:32:22,013
A challenge.

1138
01:32:22,060 --> 01:32:23,638
That's hard.

1139
01:32:24,854 --> 01:32:28,021
You joined the FBI for this?

1140
01:32:28,108 --> 01:32:29,437
Yeah.

1141
01:32:30,736 --> 01:32:32,860
Yeah.

1142
01:32:32,906 --> 01:32:35,528
So while you were studying
tired old hacks

1143
01:32:35,576 --> 01:32:38,364
like Bundy, Gacy, and Dahmer,

1144
01:32:38,413 --> 01:32:40,406
I was studying you.

1145
01:32:40,499 --> 01:32:43,251
Your habits, your hang- ups,
your weaknesses.

1146
01:32:43,336 --> 01:32:46,086
It was so simple
to set you all on edge.

1147
01:32:48,632 --> 01:32:49,712
You know?

1148
01:32:49,800 --> 01:32:51,840
I had to push here...

1149
01:32:51,928 --> 01:32:54,502
pull there...
but once I did...

1150
01:32:54,598 --> 01:32:57,137
Hey, Vince, check out
the other side of town.

1151
01:32:57,227 --> 01:32:59,552
I knew each of you
would play your part.

1152
01:33:02,483 --> 01:33:05,056
The key to effective illusion
is misdirection.

1153
01:33:05,110 --> 01:33:06,521
You know there's a bomb
on the boat.

1154
01:33:06,612 --> 01:33:08,735
You don't run toward it
first in line.

1155
01:33:08,823 --> 01:33:10,152
You know?

1156
01:33:10,242 --> 01:33:11,985
All I needed was opportunity.

1157
01:33:13,329 --> 01:33:15,571
The coffee break gave me
the chance I needed

1158
01:33:15,623 --> 01:33:17,532
to rig a few little surprises.

1159
01:33:20,004 --> 01:33:21,830
The answer was
in front of your eyes.

1160
01:33:21,922 --> 01:33:23,203
You still couldn't see it.

1161
01:33:23,299 --> 01:33:25,919
It was you who said
to turn off the water.

1162
01:33:26,010 --> 01:33:27,173
The rest was easy.

1163
01:33:27,261 --> 01:33:30,429
You're all
so fucking predictable.

1164
01:33:30,473 --> 01:33:32,016
Nicole with her cigarettes.

1165
01:33:32,101 --> 01:33:35,387
Can't she even read
the warning label on the box?

1166
01:33:36,147 --> 01:33:39,848
Vince...
"I'm never without my gun. "

1167
01:33:39,944 --> 01:33:43,313
Bobby the Magnificent
couldn't resist.

1168
01:33:43,364 --> 01:33:46,947
And Harris
just had to stay and watch.

1169
01:33:48,453 --> 01:33:51,027
Party crasher here was more
of a problem than I thought,

1170
01:33:51,123 --> 01:33:54,706
but why am I gonna work
so hard to kill him

1171
01:33:54,793 --> 01:33:56,787
when I knew you'd do it for me?

1172
01:33:59,258 --> 01:34:03,256
You see, the water
ain't your only weakness, Sara.

1173
01:34:07,725 --> 01:34:09,968
Your other weakness...

1174
01:34:10,062 --> 01:34:11,604
is me.

1175
01:34:40,599 --> 01:34:43,055
In truth, I couldn't have
done it without you.

1176
01:34:43,102 --> 01:34:45,094
As a sign of my appreciation,
I'm gonna grant you

1177
01:34:45,187 --> 01:34:46,515
your deepest desire.

1178
01:34:46,606 --> 01:34:51,233
I'm gonna get you closer to your
sister than you ever imagined.

1179
01:34:55,575 --> 01:34:58,362
One Mississippi,
two Mississippi.

1180
01:35:04,376 --> 01:35:07,046
Are we having fun yet?

1181
01:35:10,926 --> 01:35:12,089
Whoa.

1182
01:37:31,133 --> 01:37:32,413
Drop it!

1183
01:37:36,556 --> 01:37:38,965
Go ahead, Sara.
Arrest me.

1184
01:37:40,978 --> 01:37:44,228
We have your blood
under Rafe's fingernails.

1185
01:37:44,273 --> 01:37:47,892
Your fingerprints
on the fire extinguisher.

1186
01:37:47,944 --> 01:37:50,482
And your bullet in my neck.

1187
01:37:51,991 --> 01:37:53,818
That don't look good.

1188
01:37:55,578 --> 01:37:57,405
You're fucked.

1189
01:38:03,129 --> 01:38:05,619
Time's up, asshole.

1190
01:38:30,327 --> 01:38:32,784
Good thing you hit like a girl.

1191
01:38:41,592 --> 01:38:44,260
I guess we found out
his weakness.

1192
01:38:45,386 --> 01:38:47,178
Bullets.

1193
01:39:17,049 --> 01:39:19,256
Do you think they'll let me
make profiler?

1194
01:39:19,344 --> 01:39:22,796
That depends.
One last question.

1195
01:39:24,098 --> 01:39:27,931
When's the situation secure,
Agent?

1196
01:39:28,688 --> 01:39:30,348
On the drive home.

1197
01:39:30,440 --> 01:39:31,769
Yeah.

1198
01:39:32,776 --> 01:39:34,401
On the drive home.

