DAIEI FILMS
LONE WOLF ISAZO
Hitori OKami
One night when the
Kiso song was in the air
A man's pride made him leave his love
Now a roaming gambler
Lone Wolf, where are you going?
The two stars of lovers side by side
ICHIKAWA Raizo
The wish made upon them
is now washed away
ICHIKAWA Raizo
The wish made upon them
is now washed away
NAGATO IsaMu
OGAWA MayuMi IWASAKI Kaneko
The wish made upon them
is now washed away
Isazo the Ripper with no mercy
Hurries on by over the bridges of Kiso
Directed by
IKEHIRO Kazuo
Hurries on by over the bridges of Kiso
Who on earth told you?
Isazo the Wanderer?
I knew him well.
Were we sworn brothers?
No way.
Sure, I'M a yakuza too, but
I'M still unaccomplished.
But not Isazo.
Through and through, so to speak.
He was what a true yakuza looks like.
"The Ripper" would have been...
a perfect name for him
rather than 'the Wanderer".
He never stayed in one
place More than three days.
He killed so Many that...
he was always on alert that
someone was after him.
You could feel it.
He had no boss, no disciple.
Won't let anyone get close to him.
He truly was a lone wolf.
It was at the Shiojiri Peak in Shinshu...
I haven't done anything to
induce your challenge. Go away.
Are you chickening out, Isazo?
You know My name.
So that's Isazo the Wanderer.
All right.
Hey, I'll lend you a hand!
No need!
I don't want to have
nightmares about your graves.
Unsheathe your sword, coward!
Get him!
Damn you, you say one
thing and do another.
How dare you rape an innocent girl.
You'd better leave, or you'll
get Mixed up in trouble.
I didn't see him for a long time after that.
I think it was the following year,
toward the end of winter...
It was at Boss Yoza'emon's
Sakamoto Inn in Joshu...
when I ran into him the second time...
Excuse Me, excuse Me!
This is My first introduction
to you. I was born in...
Hold it right there.
You call that an introduction?
You haven't been around Much, have you?
Well, this is My first trip in
training. Please go easy on Me.
I really don't know how to go
about it. Please take Me with you.
You want to come as a second Man, I see.
Yes, I'd appreciate it.
I'M traveling; therefore, this
is My first introduction to you.
I ask the Chief and Madam of your
family to forgive My introduction.
I was born Kiso. My boss in the gambling
business is Age Matsu-no-Jinbei.
I'M his young disciple, Magohachi,
who is just a beginner.
I ask you to kindly
acknowledge our encounter...
and regard Me as an ally from now on.
I'M Hanji, born in Mino.
Pleased to Meet you.
Excuse Me but aren't you Isazo?
Didn't I Meet you in Shiojiri Peak?
You remembered. Thanks.
What are you waiting for?
Come draw water for him.
Yes!
- Hurry up.
Oh, I'M fine. Excuse Me.
Brother, who is he?
What's wrong with you?
If you want to be a
gambler, know your basics.
That's Isazo the Ripper.
That's him?
Hurry up.
It's a known fact...
that whomever he sides with always
wins a war between families.
That's why every family
Manager wants to hire him.
Not only that...
They say he has a divine touch
when it comes to dice rolling.
Boss, Madam, I am grateful for the Meal.
I am grateful.
- I am grateful.
Shall I go get another?
What?
There's only this Much left.
Idiot.
It's a rule that a traveler can
only have one bowl of soup...
one Main dish, and two bowls of rice.
Thank you for the Meal.
Brother, please lie down.
Hey, hold it.
What kind of layout is this?
What?
I can't believe how ignorant you are.
A traveler sleeps in a
single layer folded in two.
Do it over.
But Brother, we'll catch a
cold with just one layer.
It's the proper Manners. Keep it in Mind.
You seem to think it's easy.
I don't think you'll
Make it in this business.
You'd better quit for your own sake.
No way.
I can't go back to My village now.
I quit farmer business completely.
Being a gambler is Much
harder than being a farmer.
But you see, I have no Money, no status.
This is the only way I
can Make it in the world.
I've had enough of slithering
around Muddy rice paddies.
I'M prepared to do anything...
I want to be like Isazo.
You don't know what you're talking about.
You can never be like him
with soft spirit like yours.
I will.
I'll show you.
Quite a skill. He's got all the Money.
Isn't it the right time to quit?
Looks like Odd is the bet of the night.
Let Me bet with you, traveler.
Me too! Me too!
Odd side closed.
Any bet on Even?
We cannot continue
without a bet on Even.
Even?
This won't be a game.
What's going to happen?
I guess the house will
have to bet on Even.
Any bet on Even? Place
some bets on Even.
Any bet on Even?
Don't Mean to take over but I'll withdraw
My bet and counterbalance the others.
Bets closed.
Odd! 3-6 Odd.
He lost it all.
He did it knowingly.
You can't keep winning and just leave.
I will retire for the night.
Visitor, good game, wasn't it?
Yes.
Here you are.
Please use this for your refreshments.
Thanks.
Boss, and everyone, please excuse Me.
Thank you.
Please teach Me how to read
the dices the way you do.
I'M told I came out from Mom’s
womb with dice in each hand.
Thank you.
Hey...
What are you doing? Hey!
Why are you spacing out?
Brother, I know I'M a beginner.
Nowhere near where Isazo is.
But he's a human being too.
What?
What would happen if I killed him?
My name will ring throughout
the eight regions of Kaga.
What on earth are you talking about?
Are you dreaming?
Hey, I'M going to visit My old lady.
Come out of it. What a fool.
I'M in bed already.
Excuse Me for coming back late.
Thank you for patrolling.
Thank you.
Have a good night.
Good night.
I will.
Where is Agematsu's Man?
He should be home soon.
Is that so?
Then, I'll turn this off.
Don't do it, young Man.
You're saved because I know
you hold no grudges against Me.
Otherwise...
My sword would have pierced
through your neck in a flash.
I was playing a foolish
game. Please forgive Me.
The following spring...
Boss Kumokaze-no-Kamekichi
of Sanshu Hirai held...
an anniversary of his late predecessor.
I attended the prayer service
on behalf of the ill Boss Jinbei.
Then, at the game held
afterwards, I saw Isazo.
Wait. That's Boss
Terazu-no-Manosuke, right?
Indeed. Sitting across
from him is Mori-no-Goro.
Oh, Boss Mori.
Well, guys, I'M off.
I can't play against Isa.
Hey, see you later.
Isa's gonna take them
to the cleaners today.
What?
Isazo.
Master!
Master, I don't know what
happened between you and him.
He is a traveling Man, but someone
the big Men treat as equals.
You don't know what the
consequences will be.
I'd say take it easy.
Do you think I held Myself back
because I was afraid of him?
Not at all. Come on, pour him another cup.
Who is "he"?
None of your business.
Isazo the Wanderer.
Isazo?
- You know him?
Is he here now?
Did you have something with him?
I'll leave that up to your imagination.
I'll bring him here if you want to see him.
He won't. He dumped
Me like a piece of rag.
Interesting.
Woman, leave it to Me if you
have grudges against him.
I'll take care of him.
I Might have thanked you...
if he hadn't said he Makes
it a rule not to stay...
in one place More than three days
or with one particular woman.
Welcome!
Good evening.
Bring some Sake. And a plate of your pick.
One bottle and one vegetable!
Welcome!
Here you are.
Bring some Sake, and a plate of your pick.
Yes. Kitchen, a plate of your choice!
Yone, bring five or six bottles to the back.
Here's a rare visitor.
Why? Can't you say at least something?
I'M glad you're well.
I see you know how to say pleasantries.
Isazo, it's Me. It's been a while.
I saw you in the corner at the game.
My, you knew.
Now, now, let Me pour you.
I like to pour for Myself.
I don't like being treated.
You aren't bright, are you?
Give up trying to be friends with him.
He's a heartless, cold-blooded Man.
He Makes a woman cry and
doesn't Move a Muscle in his face.
Did he Make you cry too?
That's right.
I was working at Midori-ya in Goyu.
I'M so Mad.
He Made Me crazy about him, then
left Me in the cold without a goodbye.
Are you leaving, you heartless bastard?
Age Matsu, come with Me.
All right.
Bastard!
Not even a smile after a long time.
I wish you'd get killed in some fight.
I won't cry for you if you're dead!
Isazo!
Who Might you be?
Saito Itto.
Taga Chuzaburo whom you crippled at
the Shiojiri Peak is My longtime friend.
Master! Please don't.
Isazo, it's My predecessor's
anniversary today.
Please keep the peace.
I am aware.
Thank you for your hospitality today.
And you call yourself the Ripper?
Live up to your reputation!
I don't want to cause a scene at
a bar with innocent customers.
I'll wait for you at the bamboo
woods down the street after four.
Don't back down.
Let's go.
Here's one for you.
You can drink, can't you?
What's the Matter?
I can't believe it.
You're about to have a duel.
Hey, leave us alone for a Minute.
But...
- C’mon, beat it.
Isa, let's exchange cups.
I want us to be brothers.
I won't. I like being alone.
You don't like Me.
You're from Age Matsu in Kiso, right?
That's right.
That's the reason.
Why?
I want you to do Me a favor.
There's a shop called
Shinjo-ya in Kiso Fukushima...
two and a half Miles east of Age Matsu.
Yeah, I know the shop.
Will you deliver this to them?
There's 50-ryo in here.
Give it to the owner.
Sure thing.
I never ask anyone any favor,
but I feel I can trust you.
You won't let Me down, will you?
You said you can trust Me.
Let Me ask you one thing...
Why do you want to kill Me?
A low life like you...
calling yourself a killer and acting
like some big deal. How annoying.
I can't let you be.
I see.
Just surviving but still a samurai.
You want to prove I'M
below you somehow.
Shut up!
You raped My good friend's daughter.
Damn you!
I hope Isazo will be okay.
I suppose...
I'll add a new tomb plaque in My eyes.
He won, didn't he?
Isazo won, didn't he?
People of Kumokaze...
I'M on My way to assist
Kurokoma-no-Katsuzo in Koshu.
If you need to send Men
after Me, please go ahead.
Isazo!
He runs fast too, like a wild animal.
This is the battle drum!
Let us play it too!
Now, the random battle drum!
There's no such thing as a battle drum!
- Switch with us!
What are you doing?
I will not tolerate such rude behavior!
Stop talking vainly like a samurai!
My father is a samurai!
Liar! He's not a samurai!
- What?
Fatherless kid! Fatherless kid!
Be a Man. Don't take that from them.
Does it hurt? You won't cry, right?
No way, I'M a samurai’s son.
Leave it like this and it'll
be fine in a couple of days.
Boy, where do you live?
Over there.
Come on.
I can walk.
Yoshi-no-suke, what are you doing?
Oh, Mother!
What happened?
That Man.
Oh, how very kind of you.
Lady Yoshino!
Lady Yoshino, so, the child Must be...
Say thank you to him.
Thank you, Uncle.
Thank you for your kindness.
Nothing has changed.
It's all just like 8 years ago.
Hey, old Man, it's been a long time.
I'M glad you're well.
I hope you received the gift
I sent you the other day.
I hereby confirm receipt of
the chunky sum of 50 ryo.
Thanks for everything.
I see it as your funeral expense.
The amount now exceeds 200 ryo.
Haven't you given it to Lady Yoshino?
She refuses to take it.
Did you ask her why?
She wouldn't tell Me.
Poor lady...
She Makes a humble
living as a seamstress.
I see. That explains.
Did you see her?
But why wouldn't she?
Stop it!
Idiot!
The heiress of the Ueda Family...
having an affair with a
servant and eloping with him?
Have you gone Mad?
Yoshino, apologize to your father at once.
Isazo's father was a traveling gambler
who collapsed in front of our house!
My Mother took pity on him.
She called the doctor for him
and even paid for his funeral.
We raised orphan Isazo out of kindness.
How dare he force himself
on his benefactor's daughter!
No, he didn't force Me.
We are in love.
Shut the hell up!
I didn't raise My daughter
to fall for a gambler’s son!
I taught him how to write and read...
and how to use the sword,
even though he's a servant.
He's a dog that bites the
hand that feeds him!
Uncle, we'll find Isazo and...
What are you doing to him?
I said you two are strangers from now on.
I'M carrying his baby.
I forbid you to have the baby!
Then, please disown Me as you wish!
Think about it.
Where will you get going
out into the world with him?
He has no future.
You will tarnish the name
of the Ueda Family forever.
You won't only disgrace the family
and bring shame to your father...
but you and your baby...
will also have to bear that
cross for the rest of your lives.
My lady, I waited for you!
Sir Hirazawa, what are you doing to Me?
Ask yourself!
Where is Lady Yoshino?
Shut up!
How dare you betray the people
who generously took you in...
and attempt to Marry Lady Yoshino?
You deserve to be punished!
You are the ungrateful scum of Mankind.
You're below dogs and beasts. Give up!
More than anyone else, I
know how virtuous Isazo is...
and how hard he worked to serve us.
But if you end up eloping with
a Man of such a low class...
then your father would have to
resign as chief of border security...
which the family has
served as for generations.
I am not saying this because...
I care about the Ueda's name, or
your father's reputation, or Mine.
Consider the future of the baby.
All we need is for Isazo to leave
Fukushima, for you to endure.
If it is a baby boy, he will
be the heir to the family.
It is the right way for a woman to
consider the happiness of her child.
Mother!
My lady!
Isazo!
My lady...
Day will break soon.
We Must leave while it's dark
so that they will not see us.
My lady, quick, please get ready.
Please hurry, My lady.
Isazo, forgive Me.
I... I...
I cannot be with you any More.
My lady.
I am giving up My happiness
for the baby's sake.
For the baby...
What do you Mean? I don't understand.
I will wait for you.
Please find a respectable position worthy
of the Ueda name and then return.
Do you Mean to say the son
of a gambler is not human?
Take this Money and hurry and go.
You go from here on your own.
Please, Isazo.
Forget it, get rid of the child!
Isazo!
You show your face after a long absence...
and already call violence
for Me to witness.
I'll let you stay the night, but you
should leave at the crack of dawn.
Excuse Me, please let Me in.
I told you.
They're back for revenge.
Who is it? It's late.
I remember you.
I won't be formal. I heard Isazo is here.
They can't stop talking about how
you single-handedly led Kurokoma...
to win the Koshu war.
The story has spread down Kiso Road.
You kept your promise
to deliver the good.
Thanks.
Stop being so formal.
Oh, thanks.
What brought you here to Fukushima?
That's My question.
I'M sure you're aware that
the Kojin and Kiyotake...
had a run-in and are now on bad terms.
It all started because
Kojin bullied Kiyotake...
and invaded their territory
during the Ontake festival.
They bribed Detective Hirazawa
at the police to take their side...
so they feel they can do
whatever they want.
Really distasteful.
Boss Tokubei of the Kiyotake has
been ill and keeping a low profile...
so they feel now's the
chance to take over.
So, I was compelled to
offer My help to Kiyotake.
His lay daughter is in charge...
and there's no hope for us to win.
The only hope to turn
the tide would be you.
I came to Fukushima because
Iwamatsu of the Kojin hired Me.
Kojin?
He's been asking Me for three
years. I couldn't keep putting it off.
I see, but you don't have to help Kojin
who's already got an upper hand.
I don't know who's got an upper hand.
I don't care who's going to win.
I just can't ignore yakuza rules.
That's crazy.
The correct way for a virtuous Man is to
side with the righteous party, isn't it?
Righteousness and virtue
have to do with your attitude.
They aren't commodities or banners.
You Mean, you won't change your
Mind about helping the Kojin?
I see, you're after the
Money they're paying you.
After all it's nothing More than
beasts killing one another.
One May be after the Money, but if
he dies, that's the end of the story.
That bar hostess in Mikawa was right.
You have no compassion.
I have no boss or follower,
no home or family.
The law of the yakuza is the
only thing I depend upon.
I can't hope to survive carrying
such baggage as compassion.
Fine.
I'll see you in hell.
I, Magohachi of Age Matsu,
will fight you squarely.
Are you insane?
The world would be in total
darkness without compassion.
You will never understand how
dark and how horrifying it can be...
unless you have walked the path yourself.
I heard Isazo is back in town.
Is that so?
You don't seem surprised.
He became a gambler after all.
You can't fight against your own blood.
It's My fault.
If only I had left with him, he
would have been a straight Man.
Don't be stupid!
Lf...
If you had accepted Me as your husband...
the Ueda family would have been
fine even after Uncle passed away.
All would have been peaceful.
How could you, with that lowly Man!
I Must kill him in the
name of a samurai’s pride.
Seiichiro...
It's all water under the bridge
now. Why do you have to?
If people find out Yoshi-no-suke's
father is a criminal...
it would hinder him from going to Kyoto...
for academic studies or
being regarded as a samurai.
Understand?
There is a chance Isazo May stop by.
I forbid you to see him even
if he did. Send him away.
I'M going to kill him.
The Man you've been loyal to for
eight years is a yakuza and criminal.
He is scum.
I hear he's earned the name 'the ripper".
Makes Me laugh!
You hate him that Much.
When a samurai receives
a scar by a lowly Man...
he Must finish him off to save face.
Uncle?
Goroku?
Well, if it isn't Miss Ueda.
Has Isazo been by here?
Please don't hide it from Me.
I have important business with him.
Okay? Just tell him so.
Just a Moment please.
People May see you out here.
Please come around the back door.
Go away from here. Leave
as soon as possible.
Hirasawa is after you.
He'll order the border security to
stop you too. Leave right now.
It shouldn't Matter to
you whether I live or die.
After I'M finished with My yakuza
business, I won't have any reason to stay.
You don't have to tell Me to leave.
Except, just one More time...
You want to see Yoshi-no-suke?
I was hoping to.
So you want to show up the way you
are and tell him you're his father?
Are you against it? He's My child.
I told him his father is dead.
I want him to go to Kyoto
for academic studies.
Utilize the Money I left with the old Man.
I don't want it go to waste.
Do you think we will be happy
with Money earned by gambling?
I put My life at risk to Make the
Money. It's as clean as can be.
I lost both My parents.
Our Mansion has been
given to someone else.
I would have been so happy if, rather
than pitying how poor we are...
you returned as a respectable
father that he deserves.
I see.
My hands are covered with
blood of the Men I've killed.
You feel ashamed of Me,
and I have no regrets.
Would you dare hold
him with those hands?
Of course I would.
Being a yakuza was the only way for Me...
to survive when I had
no one to depend on.
There is no point blaming each other now.
Please do not show up in front of him.
Take good care of yourself.
I pray for a safe journey...
Sirs, helpers...
We have just received a declaration
of war. Tonight is the night.
We are counting on you.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Thank you...
Here you are.
I'll give My best.
Thank you.
Thank you. I guarantee you My best.
Thank you...
Thanks.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Oh, it's you, Hanji.
Brother!
I feel Much better now that
I know you're with Me.
What's that?
It's a one ryo gold coin.
I'M a full-fledged helper at last.
I'M getting kind of excited.
Idiot!
What?
Where did you learn to act so pathetic
to help someone just for Money.
But Brother, all these people here too...
The Manly Man's spirit is valuable
when it cannot be bought by Money.
One shouldn't fight for
someone when they're wrong...
even if they're willing to pay 5 or 10 ryo.
Now that Isazo is here to help us...
we've already won this fight.
Well, please kill off all Members
of the Kiyotaki family.
Please take it.
I'll receive it later.
Are you saying it's too little?
Kiyotaki's got 22 or 23 Members.
Let's say they've got about 10 helpers.
So they've got roughly 30 Men in total.
Well, you're well informed.
I put the only life I've got at risk.
I Must be informed about My opponent.
What does that have to do with this?
I have an idea how Much is in there.
It seems a little off the Mark.
What?
It would seem you could
find sufficient help...
for that kind of a job along Kiso
Road and Nakasendo Highway.
Well, if you excuse Me.
Hey, wait a Minute!
So, you're Isazo.
Isazo, this is Master Kito.
How do you do? Can I
do something for you?
I overheard your conversation.
You seem confident of your skills.
I hear they call you the ripper, and
that you're a skilled swordsman.
Thank you.
Excuse Me.
Wait!
I want to take a good
long look at the face...
of a famous Man.
You're playing with Me.
That's an unforgivable remark!
I've Made up My Mind. 15 ryo.
20 ryo!
Please rate Me after the war.
Uncle!
Little Yoshi.
Where's your Mom?
She went to deliver a kimono she sewed.
She said she'd be right back.
I see.
You're brave to wait at home alone.
I'M fine. I always do so I'M used to it.
Little Yoshi, where's your dad?
My father is dead.
Did they tell you what
kind of a Man he was?
Mother often tells Me that
he was a fine samurai.
She wants Me to be just like him.
But I don't know how to
become a fine samurai.
Will you tell Me how to
become a fine samurai?
Well, you see, you've got to practice
the sword and study academics...
I can't find a teacher
because I'M fatherless.
Because you're fatherless?
That's ridiculous.
I wonder why he had to die.
You don't have to have a teacher.
Just listen to your Mother, and
you will surely become a fine Man.
Give it to your Mother.
Tell her it's from Isazo.
So your name is Isazo.
What do you do?
You're not a samurai, you
don't look like a townsman...
I'M traveling.
What do you do traveling?
Business.
What do you sell? Why
do you carry a sword?
This is to protect Myself on My journey.
You Must be real strong.
A sword is heavy.
I'M gonna cut you!
But Uncle, you only got one sword.
A samurai carries two.
Listen, use the Money and go
to Kyoto with your Mother.
You Must study well and become as
fine a samurai as your late father.
All right?
Sure!
Maybe we'll never see each other again.
Of course you won't
because I'M going to Kyoto.
Be well. Study as hard as you can.
Good bye.
Bye.
Isazo, let's have a Match, one on one.
All right.
Here I come.
Brother, let Me help.
Don't Meddle with us.
Stay out of this!
Hanji!
Damn it!
How dare...
The war is over! It's over!
Hey, it's not over between us. Come on!
Don't be stupid.
Once a war is over, helpers are dismissed.
Once the horn is blown,
you're working for no pay.
That's not it.
You May be the ripper, but
you'll die in a war someday.
I don't want someone else to kill you.
I May not be able to win but
I want at least cut you once.
I appreciate your spirit...
but there's no reason why
we should rush to die.
Isazo, where to now?
I'll go get My due from Iwamatsu,
then leave during the night.
Hey, wake up, I hit you
with the back of the blade.
Tell Me, have you had enough of war?
No way. I'M having so Much fun.
You're impossible.
Let Me tell you just one
thing: Don't commit a crime.
Don't get involved with a
woman outside of this world.
Isazo, thank you. Boss is waiting for you.
Thank you kindly.
Please follow us.
Well, thank you for coming.
Where's Isazo?
All is well. Everything as planned.
He's here.
Then, excuse us.
Listen, to save face and
the name of Ueda family...
we cannot let him escape this time.
Yes!
Aren't you taking Me the wrong way?
Boss will be here in a Minute.
Who is it?
Isazo...
There's no point struggling.
Submit to your punishment.
You raped your Master's daughter
and had her to carry an illegal child.
You're an immoral low life who
stained the name of the Ueda.
Take it!
I loved Lady Yoshino from
the bottom of My heart.
What's wrong with getting the
woman you love pregnant?
Shut up.
You and your father both
were lowly gamblers.
You weren't even supposed
to be socializing with us.
And you raped the
daughter of your Master.
It wasn't rape.
Ask Lady Yoshino.
We were in love...
- Shut up!
You deserve to be lynched.
You should die a Miserable unseen death.
Or would you rather have
the illegal child killed?
Isazo...
Take a look.
Mother!
Is this what a respectable
samurai should do?
How shameful!
Drop your sword!
Do you want the child dead?
Mother, help Me! I'M scared!
Quiet! You're the son of a samurai.
Help Me! Help Me, Uncle!
I'M letting you die in front of these two.
Be grateful.
Run!
Please run!
I told you never to show your face again.
I can't obey you.
What?
Because I want to see My child.
I won't let you call him your own.
You're scum!
Isazo, I'M not backing down tonight.
Leave Me alone. This isn't a yakuza war.
It's My personal responsibility.
Don't be stupid. I'M not
going to let them kill you.
Little Yoshi, take a good look.
This is what scum does.
Keep your eyes open.
Understand, son?
This isn't what a human should do.
Isazo...
Age Matsu, I don't need your help.
Son, watch this.
Die!
Isazo!
Isazo...
Are you all right?
Uncle...
Son, did you see that?
You saw it.
We've got to take care
of your wounds first.
Don't Make a fuss over
such small wounds.
I've gotten these countless times before.
Now, Lady Yoshino, you should go.
What are you saying? You've
got to see a doctor right away.
I'll take care of My own wounds
even if I have to lick them.
Little Yoshi, don't ever
become anything like Me.
Age Matsu, I'll see you again if
fate allows us and if I'M still alive.
Isazo, you...
Guess I'll have a dream about
new tomb plaques tonight.
Uncle!
And what happened to Isazo?
I haven't seen him since.
Now way he can die.
I'M sure he's traveling
somewhere, roaming about...
dreaming about new plaques.
Just like a lone wolf.
Translated by Ann Jiitsu
Subtitled and Mastered by Cannibal King
www.KuroTokagi.coM