Honey,
all I'm asking you to do.
Is change his name.
No.
No, no, no, no,
you don't understand.
We'll be in so much trouble
if you don't.
I swear to God,
we'll be hit by lawsuits.
From every angle possible.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Okay.
Well, I'll give it
to the legals,
But if they say it's a no,
then it's a no.
Okay, yeah, well,
I've got to go.
See you soon.
Sorry about that.
No, that's okay.
Ah, Paula, how have you been?
Fine.
Yeah.
Getting there.
And how's the work coming on?
Um, you know.
It'll come.
Yeah, well, I know it will.
You're too good a writer.
For that talent
just to disappear.
It just doesn't happen.
Now, I don't want to put
any more pressure on you,
But we do have responsibilities,
And ours is our deadline.
I've got the printers
and the whole shebang.
Primed and ready to roll.
Yeah, I know you have.
You know what's funny?
Most... most writers
come to see me.
Chomping at the bit
for attention,
Almost willing to get themselves
into a lawsuit.
To get a piece of the action...
A piece of success, but...
But you...
I do want success.
Oh, it's just...
Come with me.
Look at that.
All those people.
All that noise.
How can you think,
let alone write in this?
Get away for a while.
Go back home and get some rest,
And try and get back in touch
with your writing.
I can't just leave.
Trust me!
Just go.
It'll do you the wealth of good.
Sync and corrections by R3V0LV3R.
Thank you.
"House is old, as you know,
"and needs lots of care.
"Please take your shoes off
so you don't ruin the carpets.
"If you have a problem
with the lights,
"the fuse box is in the cellar,
"and I've left a bottle
of wine in the fridge!
Hope you drink white."
"have a nice stay."
Ooh.
Deal with you later.
Oi.
Gonna give me a heart attack?
Precious.
Mm?
Yeah.
Oh, you're gorgeous,
aren't you?
Excuse me.
Sara.
Sara Phillips.
Hmm?
Robert Gainer.
Book review.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know who you are.
Ahh.
Of course you do.
I just wondered if I could ask
you a couple of questions.
About Paula Martin.
Look, I'm...
I'm sorry.
I'm kind of busy at the moment.
Um...
Could you call the office
in the morning?
And we'll deal with it then.
I'm sure it can wait.
Ah, yes, well,
I've been trying
to contact you via the office.
For over a month now.
I'm just getting
the runaround, you know?
"She's not in today.
"She's at lunch.
She's away from her desk.
She'll call you tomorrow."
Not avoiding my calls,
are you, Sara?
'Cause that's what
it's starting to feel like.
This conversation should not
be happening here, Robert.
All I want is an interview
with your client Paula Martin.
That's all.
Paula is busy, I'm afraid.
Ah, yes.
Writing her second novel.
Yeah, exactly.
That's not what I heard, Sara.
Oh?
And what did you hear?
Well, a little bird told me.
That Paula Martin
had a breakdown.
Just after her last book
went number one.
Now, that's not unusual.
There's a lot of it about.
Just let her talk to me.
Get it out in the open.
Might free her up.
It's a win-win situation, Sara.
Listen, Mr. Gainer.
There's nothing wrong
with my client.
She's in the country
as we speak,
Working quite happily
on her next book,
Away from...
from people like you.
She doesn't do interviews.
You should know that,
And if I read in your
magazine gossip column.
That Paula Martin
had a breakdown,
I'll use every penny we have
taking you to court.
Do you understand me?
Now, before you
say anything else,
Go back to where you came from
and sit down.
You're embarrassing me
and yourself.
Okay.
But I will get that interview,
Sara, believe me.
And gossip isn't really gossip.
If the story's correct, right?
Just tell her
I'd like to talk to her,
If you don't mind.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
You are kidding me!
Oh, God.
Hello?
Hello, Leo.
It's Paula.
Are you all right?
Everything's confusing me.
I mean, this fucking house.
I haven't been here for years.
Just calm down.
I'm sure Sara will help you.
Mm, yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
I'll call Sara.
She could rent me a place
in London or something,
Couldn't she?
Exactly.
I just knew
it was a stupid idea.
Coming back here.
Uh, look, Leo,
I've really got to go.
No.
No, no, no.
I'll call you
when I get out of this place.
Yeah.
Bye.
Just wanted to check
if there's anything special.
You need doing.
Uh, no, that's okay.
I was just on the phone.
The room
should be clean enough.
I just wanted
to introduce myself.
I'm Mrs. Brown,
the housekeeper.
Two days a week,
mondays and thursdays,
9:00 till 5:00.
Mondays is my wash day.
Two days a week.
Ooh, that looks nasty, dear.
What happened to you?
Oh, it's nothing.
I just caught it on a nail.
Stupid.
Oh, well, I'll be down
in the kitchen.
Why don't I have
a look at it for you?
I can clean it up.
You know, you really should
get to a hospital with that.
Why don't I
clean it up for you,
And you get yourself
down there in a taxi?
It's not far.
In fact, I could come with you.
I need a couple
of things in town.
Ah, I can't, really.
I'm meant to be writing.
Really, dear?
Writing what?
A book.
Really?
With a hand like this?
Do you ever hear from my uncle?
No.
I haven't heard
from him in years.
Well, he was traveling
the far east,
Last thing we knew.
Still, pays the wages,
Pays the bills,
Keeps this place going,
So we carry on as normal,
And when he gets back,
It'll all be just as he left it.
When was the last time
you were here?
Oh, must be...
Oh, I don't know.
Um, I can't remember.
Well, I've been here nine.
Really?
Is it that long?
Gosh.
Last few years have been
a bit of a blur.
Look, I do know
how this is gonna sound,
But do you ever think
this place is haunted?
Haunted?
What makes you say that, dear?
Well, it's just...
Just what?
It's just me.
Well, this is a very old house,
And old houses
have lots of secrets.
Yeah.
I know I'm just being
a bit silly.
You know where I am
if you need me.
Oh, and there's Joshua,
the young gardener.
Ah, yes, I heard him.
- Two days a week,
- 9:00 till 5:00.
Got his work cut out
keeping this place together.
So have I.
Now, look, I'm gonna give you
a couple of painkillers.
They might make you
a bit drowsy,
But from the looks of you,
I don't think a few hours' sleep
would go amiss.
I have Robert Gainer
on the line.
Said he wants to make an apology
for last night.
And to see if you've
changed your mind.
He's on line one.
Tell him I'm out at lunch.
All day.
Paula.
I have something for you.
Sara sent me.
She said you were
having trouble concentrating,
And I was to help
take the pressure off.
Help speed up
the writing process.
And get you out of this place
as quickly as we can.
She said that's
what you wanted...
And by the looks of things,
you could use the help.
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's nothing.
Yeah, she's right.
It's...
It's been a struggle,
what with one thing and another.
It's like this house
doesn't want me to work.
It doesn't want me
to write this book.
Sorry, I know
how stupid that must sound.
No.
No, you're an artist.
You're sensitive
to your surroundings.
And what beautiful surroundings.
Oh, yes.
It, um...
it belongs to my uncle.
He could be dead
for all they know.
They just
keep it running for him.
I spent quite a lot of time here
when I was a kid...
Summer holidays,
a few christmases.
How wonderful.
Yeah.
Distractions?
How am I supposed to work
with constant noise like that?
Well, I wasn't really
thinking about the noise.
Just going into town
to get those few bits.
I'll see you later.
Don't hurry back.
Do you fancy a glass of wine?
I'd love one.
Come on.
I'll get it.
So tell me about the book.
To be honest with you,
There's not much to tell
at the moment.
Inspiration hasn't been
exactly forthcoming.
The last book that I wrote.
Has been like a millstone.
I mean, maybe...
who knows?
Maybe that was it.
No, no.
Come on, I read your last book.
I know it well.
It was controversial.
It made people think.
That's why it was
such a success.
Definitely not the work
of a one-hit wonder.
Can I be honest with you?
Hmm?
You need to have
more faith in yourself.
You just have
a touch of anxiety.
Little bit of writer's block?
They say
write about what you know.
That's always
a good place to start.
You must have the beginnings
of an idea to come out here.
Kind of.
Well, I thought I did.
It's just...
It's my head.
It's not been in the right place.
For a couple of years.
I was sick, and I had to
go into recovery for a while.
That's great.
No, I...
I didn't mean that.
I meant...
Well, that would
make a great book.
Well,
there isn't really that much.
That I can remember
about the whole thing,
But who knows?
Tomorrow is another day.
Yeah.
And this has been a long one.
Now, where do I sleep?
Come on.
I'll show you to your room.
I hope you're warm enough.
It does get cold here at night.
I put an extra blanket
on the end of your bed.
Oh, I used to stay in a house
the same as this.
Creaking floors,
Plumbing, always cold at night,
Even in the naves.
Oh, I'm just in here.
You know, you're prettier
than your picture.
Oh, thank you.
Should we
make a start first thing?
Mm, bright and early.
Morning's
my favorite time of day.
I never miss it.
Oh, we'll get on
just fine then.
Um, you're in here.
Hope that's okay.
It's perfect.
Night, then.
Night.
Sleep tight.
Paula?
Paula.
It's okay.
It's just a dream.
It's just a nightmare.
It's okay.
It's just a dream.
How are you this morning?
Oh, fine.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry if I frightened you
last night.
Oh, don't be silly.
I'm all right.
It was you I was worried about.
I'm just a bit stretched
at the moment,
What with one thing
and another.
Can I give you some advice?
Everyone else does.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that.
Go on.
Well, sometimes you're
better off dealing with things.
Than leaving it till tomorrow
to sort out.
Should we have a go
at doing some work today?
I thought we could
make a start on something.
If you're up for that.
I suppose
we got to start sometime.
Well, I'll tell you what.
If you could
harness those dreams.
You were having last night,
You've got yourself
your second best seller.
Straight to number one.
Selling books.
It's all that anyone's
interested in.
It's as if it's the most
important thing on the planet.
My agent, Sara...
She talks about
a number one book.
As though it's the holy grail.
She's obsessed.
Hmm.
Sounds like someone's mistaken
their agent for their friend.
Of course she wants
a best seller.
Anyway, she's probably
a frustrated writer.
They're all the same.
Always ready
to tell you how to do it.
But can't do it themselves.
Yeah.
Look, should we finish in here
and make a start?
I did have some stuff.
I was just getting it down.
When it got swallowed up
in the computer.
Okay, well, let's see
if any of that comes back.
I'll set up in the study
if that's all right with you.
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
Love.
What is love?
Is love an emotion,
A feeling,
or just a state of mind?
Is it a way of life
for some people?
Just a dream for others?
An unreachable dream.
It was unclear to me,
But I knew
that I felt something...
Something that
made me feel uneasy;
Something I couldn't
quite relate to.
Up until now,
Everything that made me laugh,
Cry, even lose my temper,
Had been my personal secret.
This was first time
that I'd ever allowed...
This was the first time
I'd ever considered.
Allowing to really
get to know me properly.
I'd never allowed anyone
to get this close before...
To explore my mind,
Body, and soul...
But the more secure I became,
The more my insecurities.
Found a way through.
"The more secure I became,
The more my insecurities
found a way through."
Yeah, I know what I wrote!
And it is rubbish!
Ah, it's like those crap novels.
You find in the Oxfam shop!
The dog-eared, yellow ones.
That stink of old women.
You might as well
just pack up and go.
I can't do this!
Oh, for Christ's sake,
what's wrong with me?
Hello?
Wait!
Who's there?
Like I said,
Thanks again
for seeing me so quickly.
Not at all.
Please.
So how can I help you,
Mr. Gainer?
Please call me Robert.
Robert.
It's about one of your clients.
Paula Martin.
- Paula?
- Yes, the author.
Yeah, I know who she is.
She's not just a client.
She's a very good
friend of mine.
What is it, exactly,
that you do?
Well,
I'll be straight with you.
I'm a journalist,
And I work for a magazine,
The Book Review,
And, well,
I'd like a little bit
of information.
She's doing her second book,
And we would like
to help her publicize.
Get behind her on this.
You know that it's
really tough out there.
For writers these days,
And they can do
with all the help they can get.
I can't discuss
clients or friends.
With anyone from a magazine.
I'm sure you already know that.
I'm sorry, Mr. Gainer.
You've wasted your time.
Personally speaking,
I think it was a bit harsh,
What they did to you.
I mean, after all,
You were just looking out
for your client, weren't you?
Woman had a bad reaction
to a simple antidepressant.
Clashed with another medication
which I knew nothing about.
I didn't see it
'cause she didn't
put it on the form.
You know,
in situations like this,
I usually find
that a small fee helps.
I've got 1,000 pounds here.
I know you could do with it.
Just tell me
where she's staying.
It's yours.
Simple as that.
What on earth
do you think you're doing?
Nothing.
I just thought I'd help
tidy it up a bit for you.
Tidy it up?
You saying there was
something wrong with it?
No, I didn't say it.
You said it.
You said it yesterday.
You said it was rubbish.
You said it was like
one of those books.
You find in Oxfam
that nobody wants,
Not me.
I just thought I'd help you out.
Yeah, well, don't.
If I'd wanted to hire somebody
to write my own book for me,
Then I would have done it!
Oh, my God!
This has been a bloody joke!
How dare you!
You're my P.A.,
Not a bloody ghostwriter!
Do you understand?
I mean, look at it!
There's bloody pages of it.
You never, ever do this again!
Never!
Is that clear?
Perfectly.
Perfectly clear.
I'll leave it to you.
Hi.
You okay?
Yeah, I think so.
What is it?
Bad dreams?
No.
It's just me being stupid.
Must have fallen asleep
in the bath.
And freaked myself out.
Come in.
Sit down.
It was just really weird.
I thought that...
Look,
Do you want to stay
in here tonight?
Oh, could I?
Would you mind?
Come on.
You just need to get some sleep.
You're getting yourself
all stressed out.
It won't do you any favors.
Positive mental energy.
That's what you need.
Brings good things to you:
Good health, good thoughts,
And more importantly,
good ideas.
If you can do that,
The book will
take care of itself.
Trust me.
You know I'm right?
Yeah, I do.
Thank you.
Don't worry about it.
You just need
a good night's sleep.
I mean for the words.
Just read it.
It's fantastic.
It's...
It's so much darker,
But it's everything
that I wanted to write.
It's everything
that was in my head.
But I couldn't get it out.
Why don't you
stay in bed tomorrow?
Take it easy for the day.
Let me do the worrying for you.
That's why I'm here.
Take the pressure off.
Yeah, that would be nice.
Try and get some sleep.
What the hell
is going on down there?
I can't hear myself think,
Let alone work!
I didn't know
Mrs. Brown was coming in today.
It's not just that woman.
It's the fucking gardener
as well!
What on earth do they think
they're up to?
I was on a roll down there,
And if you could still remember
what that feels like,
Then you'd be kind enough
to sort it out.
Sort it out?
What can I say?
I don't care
what you fucking say.
Just get rid of them.
Get them the fuck
out of this house!
It's either me or them...
And without me,
we're both fucked.
Did they go?
Oh, uh, yes,
But I told them
they could come back tomorrow.
Said what?
That they could
come back tomorrow.
Well, don't expect any work
to happen tomorrow.
And I'll have some coffee
when you're ready.
Sara.
Hello.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm feeling fine.
Yeah, things are really
starting to happen.
I've hit a good vein.
Yep.
Yeah, yeah.
I'd like to get on, though.
All right...
Thanks for calling.
Bye.
Paula!
Oh.
Paula Martin?
Yes.
The author?
Can I help you?
I'm rather busy.
I I'm sorry.
I didn't recognize you
straight off.
You look kind of...
What?
Well, different
to your picture...
But in a better sort of way,
If you don't mind me saying so.
Well, a little bit of makeup
does wonders to you.
Hey, uh, nice house.
Is it yours?
Mm.
Yes.
Um, what is it you want?
I'm Robert Gainer.
You might have heard of me.
I'm a writer.
I'm not in your category,
But I work for a magazine.
The Book?
I thought you could
fill me in on a few blanks.
We could have a talk.
Talk...
Of course.
Why don't you come in?
Join me for a glass of wine.
I think it's that time of day.
Oh, and I think there's
some cheese and biscuits.
In the kitchen.
All right. Thanks.
That sounds great.
Thank you very much.
You know,
If I'd known.
That getting to talk to you.
Was gonna be this pleasant,
Would have caused me
a lot less stress.
Well, stress is the one thing
I don't believe in.
Anything to relieve stress
is good in my book.
What do you think, Robert?
Hmm, yeah.
So Paula,
How's the book coming along?
Fine.
Why wouldn't it be?
Well, I don't have to tell you.
That there were some rumors
floating around out there.
About how you, uh...
Running into difficulties.
Had a little bit of a breakdown.
So much so that you, um,
Employed the services
of a ghostwriter.
Now, I don't
believe a word of that.
I know you're too much of a pro.
But you wouldn't mind too much.
If we talked a little bit.
About the "breakdown,"
would you?
Look, I know
it's a sensitive subject,
But sometimes
it's good to talk...
Get it out there in the open,
And, well,
Show the public
the real Paula Martin.
And you know something?
I've got a sneaking suspicion.
That it won't harm the sales
of your new book either.
I see.
Let me get you some more wine.
Thank you.
So when did it all start?
I mean, was it the, uh...
Pressures of writing?
Everyday life?
I mean, look, there's
no embarrassment in it either.
You know that.
It's all too common out there.
Oh, no, you've got me wrong.
I've no embarrassment.
I'm happy to tell you
what happened.
- Oh, you are?
- Mm.
Where do I start?
Would you mind very much.
If I recorded this?
You see, I don't want
to misquote you, Paula,
And I really would like
to get it all down.
Entirely in your own words.
There you go.
Let's go.
We're ready.
So...
You want everything?
Yeah, everything.
My brother
was fucking my brains out.
From the age of 13,
So I killed him!
I ripped his fucking spleen out.
While he was on top of me.
Now you know everything.
Thought you might like
some cheese and biscuits.
Oh, thank you.
And how are you feeling?
Any better?
Yeah, a lot better.
Thank you.
Yeah, I think I'll get up
tomorrow and do some work.
- Do you, now?
- Yeah, you were right.
A day in bed has done me
a barrel of good.
I'll be the judge of that.
There's nothing
for you to worry about.
That reporter
that came this afternoon...
It was Robert Gainer,
wasn't it?
What did he want?
Oh, he just wanted
a quick chat...
A few words for the magazine.
Don't worry.
I was very polite.
I gave him a drink,
something to eat,
And told him
you couldn't see him.
Because you didn't want
to be disturbed.
You were too busy
hitting that deadline.
Oh, thank you.
Do you think
he'll be coming back?
Like I said,
There's nothing
for you to worry about.
Are you comfortable?
Yeah, thank you.
Good.
Just for the record,
This is the 4th
of February, 1997.
Now, after "three,"
I want you to take
a deep breath in.
And breathe out slowly, okay?
One...
Two...
Three.
Paula,
Tell me about your childhood.
Tell me about
your summer holidays.
They were hot.
So hot...
Sometimes I could
hardly breathe,
As if there wasn't enough air.
I know how stupid that sounds.
Were you alone there?
Hate.
What is hate?
An emotion that eats away
at your soul.
Until there's nothing left.
Burns a hole in your heart.
That seeps poison
into your veins.
Self-loathing
is the most painful addiction...
Disrespect for all that we are.
Who am I?
A soul waiting to escape
the confines of her cell.
Waiting to be set free
from this world of torment...
Until this world drips...
Of blood.
Paula, what on earth
has happened?
Oh, my poor thing.
Come on.
Sit down.
Let me sort this out for you.
I was just making
some breakfast.
I thought you'd be hungry.
You hardly ate yesterday at all.
Now, then,
let's have a look at this.
You see, you have to be
very careful with open wounds.
They get very messy
if you don't look after them.
Now, you need
to take better care of this.
And if it starts
to give you any trouble,
You just let me know, okay?
What is it?
Well?
The book.
Don't you worry yourself
about the book.
I told you,
I'm taking care of everything.
Look at you.
Just leave the mess to me.
It's Mrs. Brown.
I'll talk to her this time.
Where's that bloody mop?
Mrs. Brown.
Hello?
Leo.
How you doing?
Well, yeah,
It has been a while,
to say the least.
What can I do for you?
Listen, Leo,
Why don't I come and see you?
Get me out of the office
for a while.
Make this conversation
a bit more private.
It'll be nice to see you anyway.
Mrs. Brown?
Did you say
you wanted Mrs. Brown?
That's what I said.
Look, I don't know
if you heard me or not,
But I've got to go, and she's
supposed to come with me.
Oh, Mrs. Brown...
she's just down in the basement.
Well, can you tell her
I'm waiting for her?
I've just
got to get off sharpish.
Why don't you
tell her yourself?
What, down the basement?
Yeah, yeah,
She's down there somewhere.
Mrs. Brown?
Mrs. Brown, are you down there?
Well, when you see her,
Can you tell her I'm leaving.
And she'll have to get
a taxi home tonight?
Stupid fucking bitch.
Ahh!
You stupid fucking bitch!
What do you want this time, huh?
Never know how well off you are,
Even when someone's
trying to help you!
Go away.
Oh, please leave me alone,
for God's sake!
Leave me alone!
Where's Mrs. Brown?
She's in the cellar,
You fucking whore!
Can't take your call right now,
So please leave a message.
Leo.
Leo!
It's me.
Oh, help me.
She's trying to kill me!
The girl that Sara hired.
She's...
You really didn't
need to do that.
Thanks very much.
It's been a long time.
Since a woman's
bought me dinner,
Especially one
as beautiful as you.
Listen, don't ruin it.
But it was lovely.
- Do you mind if I...
- No.
Well, cheers.
You miss Paula, don't you?
Yeah, of course I do.
She was...
she is...
Still a major part of my life.
But our relationship
was never physical.
We...
We didn't want that.
Of course,
after the breakdown, well...
So what was it
you wanted to show me?
Fucking bastard, you've been
treating me like a fool.
I should tear
your fucking heart out.
And ride the fucker out.
You're the fucking
devil himself,
You fucking bastard!
Who was that?
Mrs. Brown?
Mrs. Brown.
Help me.
Paula, please.
Leo.
It's the P.A.
- She's after me.
- Calm down.
Paula.
Who is she?
A woman called Linda.
I don't know her second name.
She's already killed two people.
Calm down.
Voice on the tape.
It's a woman called Linda.
She's been stalking Paula
since she was a little girl.
She's back.
Thought I heard you down there.
Come on!
Fuck you!
Go on!
My brother was
fucking my brains out.
From the age of 13,
so I killed him!
I ripped out his fucking spleen.
While he was on top of me!
Fucking my brains out
from the age of 13,
So I killed him!
I ripped out his fucking spleen.
While he was on top of...
Fucking my brains out
from the age of 13,
So I killed him!
I ripped out his fucking spleen.
While he was on top of me.
Fucking my brains out...
You're telling me
that this Linda.
And Paula are the same person.
How?
Dissociative identity disorder.
She's been coming to see me
for nearly ten years.
Some days were good,
And that's when Paula
would come through the door.
Other days were bad.
That's when Linda would show up.
That's the voice
you heard on the tape.
What are you talking about?
Paula and her brother.
Spent all of their
holidays here.
He began to rape her
at a young age.
The older she got,
the more she blocked it out,
Till in the end,
She created a separate person:
Linda.
She has absolutely
no recollection.
Of her brother at all.
With a split personality.
That could cope with the trauma.
Whenever Paula's under stress,
Linda shows up.
That's right.
Paula stabbed her brother
when he was raping her.
Tipped her over the edge.
She was put under
my supervision.
Oh, my God,
I sent Robert Gainer down there.
You sent the reporter
to the house?
We thought it would help
with publicity.
Aw, Christ.
What are you doing?
You wanted to come.
Linda?
Where are you?
I know you're here.
Christ, what's that smell?
Linda!
Paula?
Linda, it's Leo.
All right, you stay here.
Really?
Linda, don't worry.
Just want to talk to you.
Linda?
Paula, is that you?
It's all right.
I told you I'd come.
Hey.
I told you I'd come for you.
You're safe now.
This is brilliant.
Absolutely bloody brilliant.
It's okay.
You're all right.
It's over.
You're right.
It is over.
Leo?
Paula?
Linda.
Where do you think
you're going with my work?
Your biography.
It's incredible.
I've never read
anything like it...
Do you really think
I am gonna let you
walk out of here.
With all my work?
Where's Leo?
Where is he?
Oh, he's up in the bedroom.
Do you want to see him?
Sara.
Get out of here.
Get out of here while you can!
Paula, please!
This isn't you!
Sara, please get out of here.
I can't!
Where's Leo?
He's dead.
I killed him.
Where the fuck...
Shit.
Yeah.
Hey.
Yeah, police.
I'm at Crow's...
Crow's Hall!
I don't know what
the fuck is happening,
But you have to get here quick!
What?
Oh, fuck!
Shit.
No!
Ahh!
So what was your relationship.
To the party?
What were your reasons.
For coming out here
in the first place?
Miss.
Miss, are you okay?
Yeah.
Everything is just.
Perfect.