[Carl] In nature, predators
cut off their prey from the pack,
Ieaving them vulnerable,
easy to attack.
[growls, barks]
[chatter, laughter]
Modern society values independence.
The strength to stand on our own.
To make our own way.
- [whimpering]
- [clock ticks]
Forfeiting not only the comfort of home,
but the bonds of family and community.
[barking]
[children cheer]
[clock ticks]
Gus, Come on! Bring it back.
[barking]
But in our isolation, we become weak.
Perfect victims.
Gus!
[ticking]
- [sobbing]
- [hissing]
[barking]
Gus, where are you?
[sobs]
[screaming]
[barks, whines]
- Thanks for seeing us, Dr. Shields.
- I was surprised to get your call.
The press doesn't usually
take an interest in an accidental death.
That's our question. If the death of the
woman, Jennifer Owens, was an accident.
The decedent's body
was severely decomposed
and suffered significant
post-mortem predation,
but that was my conclusion, yes.
[Perri] Based on the bruise on her head?
A contusion on her left temple,
suggesting she fell, struck a rock
- which knocked her unconscious.
- So in actuality she died from...
Exposure. She never regained
consciousness as far as I can tell.
Any idea why she'd be
in that part of the park?
It's relatively isolated.
No, I generally leave questions
like that for the detectives,
but her car was found close by,
her purse inside.
- Maybe she went for a walk.
- In high heels?
As I say, that's a...
that's a police matter.
- This postmortem predation.
- Yes.
What about the predation on her face?
- What about it?
- Something ate through her nose,
deep into her brain cavity.
Pretty extreme, wouldn't you say?
I suppose so, yeah.
As I understand it, the bite signature
doesn't match any species
native to this area.
Where did you get that?
I didn't put that in my report.
Could this particular predation
have occurred before she died?
Uh, possible, but I don't see
any of the defensive wounds
that would suggest
she was attacked that way.
- Thank you for your time.
- Of course.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
[hushed] Hey! Come here.
Come here. Come on.
Now, do you see what I mean?
I hate to tell you, your boss's answers
seemed convincing.
That's why I called you. I can't
go around his back and call the cops.
- What do you think killed this woman?
- I don't know, exactly.
Whatever it is, it's some mean-ass thing
that chomped through her face
and into her brain.
And you've been able
to determine that,
but the coroner in charge of the case
hasn't because...?
Because... he lacks imagination.
Or maybe you have too much of it.
Look, all I'm saying is, do your thing,
ask questions
and you'll see that I'm right.
[woman]
For a parent to outlive a child...
it's not supposed to be.
Every time I pack something in a box,
it hits me again that she's...
never coming home.
We're very sorry for your loss,
Mrs. Owens.
[Carl] Your daughter disappeared
two weeks ago, ma'am.
Have you any idea why she would
have been in that park that day?
We spoke often,
but she lived her own life.
I couldn't tell you
where she was on any given day.
Did she have a boyfriend
or someone who can give us
an insight into why she was there?
Oh, she didn't date much.
T oo busy with her work, I guess.
- She was a real-estate agent?
- Yes. Worked long hours.
Every weekend. Married to her job.
[hushed] I understand.
You don't think
this was an accident, do you?
Well, that's what we're
trying to determine.
Well, I don't care what anybody says.
I know it wasn't.
Why would you say that, Mrs. Owens?
This was taken the day
she got her real-estate license.
See that? That necklace
belonged to my grandmother.
It was an antique.
Jenny never took it off.
It wasn't found on her body.
Have you told the police
you think she was robbed?
Nothing else was taken.
I keep thinking, if only
I'd never given her the necklace,
maybe she'd still be alive today.
How do I look?
You look beautiful.
What's the matter?
Nothing. It's... Long day.
Aaron.
Aaron, worrying ages you.
Yes, you're right.
You're such a good son.
You always listen to your mother.
- Where are you going?
- Out.
[doorbell]
- Hello.
- [woman laughs]
Marlene, how do you stay so beautiful?
Flattery will get you everywhere.
- Oh.
- [woman laughs]
Oh, Aaron. How are you?
- I didn't know you had a date tonight.
- A mother can still have secrets.
- Where'd you get this?
- It's lovely, isn't it?
Don't wait up.
- You wanted to see us?
- Yes.
- I have to say, I'm a bit embarrassed.
- About what?
If it weren't for your questions, we may
have not ever thought to look for it.
It's very time consuming, because
it has to be done the old-fashioned way,
by examining the entire body with
a magnifying glass, believe it or not.
These are close-ups
of the victim's neck.
We found a needle mark, injected
right into the center of a freckle.
- Oh, my God. It's incredible.
- Then this was a homicide?
With a very careful killer.
I notified the detectives.
I'm embarrassed I missed this.
[Perri] Know what she was injected with?
Nothing came up
in her tox screen first time.
How is that possible?
A drug could have moved quickly
through her system, an anesthetic.
I ordered full blood work. I'd say
this rules out the bite to the face
- as the cause of death.
- Why is that?
There are a lot of animals
in Los Angeles,
but as far as I know, none of them
carry around a hypodermic needle.
- Right.
- I'm curious.
How did you two know to ask about
this case in the first place?
A, um...
- A necklace was taken.
- A necklace?
The dead woman's mother thought
maybe that was why she was killed.
Hm.
- What did he say?
- You were right. It was a homicide.
- He found a needle mark in her freckle.
- He found a needle mark?
No, I think you mean, I found it.
That's why I was trying to reach you.
- You found it?
- It took me all night.
He called you because
I told him about it this morning.
- It still doesn't make sense.
- What's that?
The killer's careful. He injects her
in a freckle to hide his crimes.
[both] Yeah.
Why be so careful if he's gonna smash
her head against a rock to kill her?
- Exactly.
- I don't know.
But Dr. Shields is right.
That wound to her face
makes even less sense.
I'm telling you, that's exactly what
killed her, not this bump on her head
that Dr. Credit-grabber
is telling you about.
[knocks]
Marlene?
[man] Hello? Anybody home?
[Marlene] Door's open.
[Marlene] I'm just...
I'm just getting ready.
- Mind if I mix myself a drink?
- [Marlene] Help yourself.
- Marlene!
- Yes?
I don't think your son likes me much.
[Marlene] What makes you say that?
Oh, he never seems
too happy to see me.
[Marlene] Aaron's protective,
that's all. He likes to take care of me.
[Marlene] I'm sure
the more time you spend together
the more he'll like you.
You just wait and see.
Are you all right?
Fine.
How do I look?
Amazing. Like you always do.
[Marlene] Beautiful.
We've got to be quick.
I've got work this afternoon.
Oh, I forgot my necklace.
Be right back.
She's a pretty woman.
She had a birthday coming up.
The same as mine.
It's not fair to die so young.
No, it isn't. [sighs]
You got anything?
I've called every zoologist
and biologist in southern California.
You agreed that needle mark
ruled out animal attack.
Yes, but, you know, I'm wondering why
an animal would eat into her flesh.
Why? Well, how about
because it was hungry?
It chewed through her cartilage
and bone, eating into her brain.
So if it was that hungry,
why go to all the trouble?
And if it wanted to kill,
why kill that way?
You ask the most interesting questions.
You know that?
What have you got?
I've spoken with her friends.
No one had talked to her in days.
- What about at her office?
- She would have been
showing houses on Saturday.
I've yet to locate her supervisor.
Hey, guys. I got something.
- [Carl] Where are you taking us?
- [Jain] The Beacon's research morgue.
[Perri] I forgot this existed.
It's old newspaper files, pre-1 980.
I like to come down and look around.
Which is how I found it.
- Or rather, Titus did.
- Who's Titus?
Speaking.
[Jain] Titus Berry,
this is Carl Kolchak...
- Hi.
-...and Perri Reed.
Jain said you found something.
[Jain] Yeah, I was, uh,
telling Titus about your story
about the woman
whose face was bitten through.
Well, you know something about that?
[Titus] Let the others scurry about
gathering their contemporary bits
of gossip.
Research.
That is where the joy lies,
and the fascination.
What did you find, Mr. Berry?
[Titus] Oh, the impatience of youth.
I have found something
which you would never find
on the ln-ter-net
or the World Wide Web,
where historical events
are erased from memory
if no one is there
to record them digitally.
- Your point being?
- This crime, it's happened before.
I remembered it the moment
Jain described it to me.
- When, before?
- November 1 7th, 1 970.
1 970?
Lois Arleta. Her body was dumped
in T opanga Canyon Park
after her disappearance
three weeks earlier.
A little like the death
we're investigating...
It's exactly like it, Ms. Reed.
Jain said something ate through
a woman's nose and face, into her brain.
You're telling me the same thing
happened 35 years ago, as well?
"Coroner's office stated
the damage to the face
was most likely the result of..."
- Animal predation.
- Did the police investigate?
[Titus] Yes, they did.
The investigating officer
is listed as Detective Collins.
H never determined
who or what killed this woman?
No, not her. Not any of them.
- Any of "them"?
- This woman was only the first.
There were two other victims,
besides Ms. Arleta,
their bodies
were found a few days later.
All three of these women
were killed the same way.
Los Angeles history.
Remember it,
or be doomed to repeat it.
- Where have you been?
- Aaron.
- Why aren't you at work?
- I left early.
What on earth for?
The police are investigating
the death of Jennifer Owens.
How did that happen?
One of the assistants
found a needle mark on her body.
I've had to order blood work.
Que será, será.
Two reporters know about it.
They... I...
I tried to throw them off,
but they know things.
- Like what?
- Like her necklace is missing.
- You think this is her necklace?
- Don't lie to me!
Watch your tone, young man.
I'm older than you, and much wiser.
I know... I know that. I...
You just need to trust me.
I'm going to take care of everything.
We're so close now.
Is it worth it, Mother?
You're asking me if it's worth
having more time together?
Of course it is.
Of course it is, darling.
Hello?
- Can I help you?
- [gasps]
Sorry, I didn't mean to startle you.
- No, I'm fine. Marlene Harmon?
- Yeah. I was just outside.
- Lovely home, isn't it?
- Oh, I'm not a client,
I'm a reporter. I'm Perri Reed,
I'm with the Los Angeles Beacon.
Oh, a reporter.
Yeah, I'm writing
a story about Jennifer Owens.
Weren't you her supervisor,
Mrs Harmon?
It's "Ms". Yes, I was.
We think someone
may have killed her.
Oh, my God.
Were you aware of anyone
who disturbed her or threatened her?
No, no.
Well, it might have been
an older man.
Oh, so there is a suspect?
Not exactly.
We're following... kind of a hunch.
Bit of a long shot, actually.
I see.
I've always thought it's so dangerous,
being a pretty young woman
like she was,
showing these houses to strangers,
all alone.
You think it might have been a client?
Anything could happen
in one of these empty houses.
And no one would be around to help.
I don't suppose you'd allow me to review
her calendar or her client list?
No, I can't do that,
not to a reporter. I'm sorry.
Oh, of course. No, I understand.
Here's my card.
My home number's written on the back.
If you can think of anything,
anything at all, please call.
OK.
I, uh...
I hope you won't find it inappropriate,
but I just have to say,
you're such a beautiful girl.
Thank you.
Such amazing skin.
What I wouldn't give
to be your age again.
It's all so fleeting, you know?
Yes, l... I suppose it is.
[man] Hello?
- Are you the realtor?
- [Marlene] I'm coming.
Excuse me... please.
- [Carl] Detective Collins?
- Detective, retired.
- You the reporter that called?
- Carl Kolchak.
You want to know about
this case from 35 years ago?
If you remember any details
that wouldn't have been in the paper?
Kinda hard to forget it.
Three women, faces disfigured,
their bodies dumped in the public parks.
Newspaper accounts
say the case was never closed.
Body dumps are the hardest.
Not knowing where somebody died
makes it much tougher.
Did you ever determine
the manner of death?
Mr. Kolchak...
I probably investigated
over 200 homicides in my career.
None of them gave me nightmares
like this one.
Why, because of the violence?
Because of the suffering.
Those girls had needle marks
on their bodies.
- They were injected with anesthetic?
- Paralyzed, but awake.
Helpless.
They died a slow, terrible death.
Never even had a chance
to cry out for help.
You never identified any suspects?
I said the case was never closed, but
I'm pretty damn sure I know who did it.
- Well, who was it?
- A doctor by the name of Luke Russell.
He'd stolen anesthetics
from the hospital where he worked.
- Why didn't you arrest him?
- We never got the chance.
Shot himself in the face
with a 9mm handgun.
- He's dead? Are you sure?
- Couldn't be much more sure.
Wait, and you're certain
he was the killer?
Well, the killings stopped
after we found his body.
Mr. Kolchak,
why are you so interested in this case?
Because another woman died
the same way recently.
And I thought maybe...
the same killer was back.
[chuckles] After 35 years?
Well, I'll tell you this,
if the same guy's going around
killing young girls at his age,
he's got a hell of a lot more energy
than I do.
Thanks.
[Perri] Get anything?
The detective from the 1 970s case thinks
the killer killed himself 35 years ago.
- How about you?
- Another dead end.
- [sighs]
- [Jain] I got something.
[Carl] What is it?
A burning desire compelled me
to look further back into our files
to see if there were any deaths
that were similar to those in 1 970.
- 1 935? You've gotta be kidding me.
- See for yourself.
[Carl] "Three women,
victims of wild animal attacks,
the flesh on their faces consumed."
- All unmarried. All young.
- Fascinating, isn't it?
- That's weird.
- Wait. 2005 to 1 970, is 35 years.
- 1 970 to 1 935, that's...
- 35 years.
That is very observant, Mr. Kolchak.
I had not noticed that myself.
- I know what you're thinking, Carl.
- Let's take a look.
[Carl] March 1 st, 1 900.
"Three ladies
in the West Adams District..."
"Attacked onto their faces."
Wow.
That can't be a coincidence, can it?
Want to go for 1 865?
The Beacon didn't start publishing
until 1 898.
[Perri] Let's give this
the benefit of the doubt.
- First murder occurs in 1 900.
- Right.
When this man would be,
let's be conservative here, uh, ten.
Right.
So he'd be... 1 1 5 years old now.
Going around killing women
in his walker.
Thanks for obtaining
the exhumation order, Detective.
Consider it a favor to Detective
Collins. He's an old friend of mine.
I'm not understanding your interest
in this man Luke Russell.
We think he may have
been involved in murders
similar to Jennifer Owens' in 1 970.
- That was 35 years ago.
- That's right.
How could he be connected to the
most recent death, if he's dead?
If he's dead.
[ratcheting]
[creaking]
I can confirm unequivocally
this man is indeed dead.
Yeah. I'm sorry
for wasting your time, Detective.
- No apology necessary.
- No, wait a minute. Excuse me.
- Look at that.
- [Shields] What?
- The entrance wound.
- What about it?
Well, there should be contact burns,
shouldn't there?
Well, there should be, yes.
Maybe there were,
they just... faded with age.
Yeah, but that wound. I would say
it's circular... not star-shaped.
It's hard to say,
given the condition of the body.
- What does it mean?
- The autopsy might have been wrong.
This man may not have been shot
at contact or even near contact range.
So, he didn't kill himself?
No, he may have been murdered.
Excuse me.
[heavy breathing]
- Gin.
- You win again.
- I don't like losing.
- Hm!
Marlene...
I know your secret.
Yesterday, I saw you
getting dressed. I...
I saw how you...
cover up.
That's makeup
on the back of your hand, isn't it?
Look, what I'm saying is you don't
need high collars or... or long sleeves.
Not for me.
You're a beautiful woman, Marlene.
Hugh, I don't want you to leave here.
Ever.
Jain said the suspect from 35 years ago
didn't kill himself. He was murdered?
- Possibly by the real killer.
- How does that work?
The detective said
Dr. Russell stole anesthetics
- the killer used to immobilize victims.
- He immobilized them?
Remember what Shields said about
Jennifer not having defensive wounds?
- Right.
- She couldn't fight back
because the killer paralyzed her
with an anesthetic.
So the killer got the drugs he needed
from this doctor
and then when the police closed in...
He killed the doctor.
Made it look like a suicide
so they thought they found their man.
- [sighs]
- You going home?
My parents are bringing over dinner.
Well, that's nice. They live in town?
I don't see them as much as I should,
but...
there's something about this story,
you know?
Yeah. I understand.
- See you tomorrow.
- See you.
[phone rings]
- Kolchak.
- It's Nyby.
You gotta get back down here. Now.
A Jane Doe,
her body found by a horse trail rider
in Griffith Park a month ago.
[Carl coughs]
[Carl] Is that a woman?
- What's left of her.
- Yeah, her face is missing.
I'm never going to find a needle mark
to prove it, but you gotta believe me...
No, I believe you.
If she's been here a month,
how come you're only finding out now?
A clerical error.
Somebody misfiled her case.
But if I'm right, it means
Jennifer Owens wasn't the first victim,
she was the second.
It's two down, one to go.
- Aaron, where have you been?
- Driving.
You're late for dinner.
You didn't even call.
I, uh... [clears throat]
...performed an autopsy today.
- You perform autopsies every day.
- On Luke.
Luke?
How did that happen?
These reporters. They...
They know he's involved,
they just don't know how.
Well, then...
that's fine.
You told me he killed himself.
- Aaron.
- You killed him.
He did everything you said
his whole life and then you killed him.
Just like you're going to kill me.
No.
No, no.
Aaron.
I did lie to you.
To protect you.
Your brother was not like you.
He was not as strong, as devoted.
The police kept asking questions,
just like these reporters are doing now.
He would have told them everything.
He would've ruined everything.
So you shot him and made it
look like he killed himself?
And the police stopped asking questions!
They closed the case!
If I hadn't done what I did,
I would not be here now.
You would not be here now.
These reporters are not going
to stop asking questions.
They think an old man is responsible.
And an old man was.
I made sure of it.
What have you done?
I told you before.
I'm older... and wiser.
Everything's going to be just fine.
You'll see...
my love.
- [laughing] Hello, sweetheart.
- Hi.
Let me put these in the kitchen.
- Hey, baby doll. Mmm.
- Hey, Dad.
This place doesn't do takeout,
but your father insisted.
Well, for us they should.
The hospital board
eats there every week.
It really is excellent ltalian
food. Fantastic osso buco.
- Mmm.
- So, what's going on?
What do you mean?
You invite us over on a week night?
When was the last time she did that?
Never, I think.
I just wanted
to see you guys, that's all.
I guess it's just this story
I've been writing
about these women
who have been killed.
Makes me realize how lucky I am,
and vulnerable.
How easily it can
all be taken away from you.
So, who killed the women?
We don't know,
but they died terrible deaths, Dad.
I mean, something bit through
their faces, into their brains.
Nice dinner talk.
Every one of these women,
the killer consumed
their brain matter?
Apparently, yeah.
Must we continue talking
about this over dinner?
That's kinda strange, isn't it?
What part of the brain?
I don't know what it's called,
but it's right here.
Make any sense to you?
Only if it's not the brain he's after.
- What else could it be?
- Could be the pituitary gland.
What's that do?
It's sometimes called
the "master" gland.
It's the size of a... a pea,
highly prized
in some Asian cultures.
What for?
It controls every other
gland in the endocrine system.
Growth, sex, aging.
The myth is that
if it's consumed from a live animal,
it'll prolong life.
You're talking about cultures
that eat the glands of animals.
That's right.
But in this case, who knows?
- I've heard of stranger.
- So have l.
[phone rings]
Mmm. Excuse me.
[father] Mm-hmm.
- Hello?
- Ms. Reed, it's Marlene Harmon.
I'm sorry to call so late.
- It's all right. How can I help?
- I think I have some information
about Jennifer Owens' death
you might be interested in.
What kind of information?
Can you come over right now?
I'd like to speak to you,
in strictest confidence.
[Nyby] Ah. Here's her admitting file.
What are you looking for?
[Carl] You said someone
misfiled her case.
Yeah, I did.
I want to know who.
- Wait, you don't think...
- "Dr. Aaron Shields"
ruled her death "accidental".
The chew marks on the face,
"post-mortem predation".
- Just like Jennifer Owens.
- You were right, Alex.
Right from the start.
- Shields has been covering up?
- Yeah, for the real killer.
No doubt supplying
the anesthetics he needs,
just like Dr. Russell, 35 years ago.
I can't believe it.
Wait, who are you calling?
Hi. Is Perri there?
Do you know where she's gone?
Oh. Can you just tell her Carl
Kolchak's trying to reach her?
OK, thanks.
- What?
- Perri.
Her parents said
she had to leave for a story.
- You think it's this story?
- Well, she didn't say.
Do you have
Shields' home address?
I'll get it.
- Thank you for coming.
- Of course.
Dr. Shields?
Hello.
What are you doing here?
No more questions, dear.
[pained cry]
You're just gonna let this happen?
[ticking]
- [gunshot]
- [pained cry]
[siren]
[squealing tires]
[police radio]
You OK?
It's gonna be OK. I'm right here.
[Carl]
The past has endless stories
about tragedies that have struck
those who have come before us.
A history of tears.
But nature remains
indifferent to our suffering.
Offering only a cold, hard truth.
One that becomes harder to bear,
the more we learn to love living.
That at the very moment life
first pumps through our veins,
the clock is set... to stop.