This is where Kolchak killed his wife.
- Of course, that's not his story.
- Carl!
[woman] Who was it?
He claimed whatever it was,
it wasn't human.
Pretty convenient,
killing his wife, leaving him alive.
Kolchak,
I didn't mean to get you arrested.
But you're not sure
I'm innocent either?
Her left hand.
She didn't have it before she died.
Why kill that woman
and take that little girl?
Why kill your wife and why not you?
All these strange deaths,
they're like pieces in a puzzle,
a puzzle I'm trying to put together.
[Carl] In nightmares, they intrude
from places beyond our imagining.
Demons, monsters, killers,
who strike with no remorse or reason.
In our waking hours,
we look over our shoulder,
out the corner of our eye,
alert to the stranger
who might attack without warning.
But in all our lives,
there is a greater danger,
one even more terrifying
for being unexpected.
Not the killer we fear,
but the killer we trust.
[man] Attababy, good hustle,
Crusher. Attaboy.
[man] Come on, Jeffrey!
Hit it hard, kid!
They're keeping him in?
It's his turn.
Come on, Jeffrey, you can do it!
I know,
but this could be terrible for him.
Sweetheart, he can do this.
[man watching]
Here you go, kid.
Come on, Jeffrey!
Hey, hit a fastball, huh!
Play ball!
Strike one!
- What are you doing?
- I can't bear to watch.
It's the last inning,
there are two outs. He can win this.
[man] Here you go.
Hit it hard, Jeffrey!
Strike two!
I have to go set up snow cones.
I'll watch from there.
Jane. Jane!
The boy's way out in front of the ball.
- Remember how I showed you?
- Back elbow up,
both eyes on the pitcher,
bring the bat back as he throws.
God, he looks so much like you did.
Dad, I'm really glad
you could be here for this.
You know what you have to do.
[chatter on outfield]
- [clapping]
- [man] Here you go, Jeffrey.
Doug.
Go on! Go on!
- Safe!
- [cheering]
[children chant]
Jeffrey! Jeffrey! Jeffrey!
Weapon used
was an aluminum baseball bat.
Mrs. Linman was pronounced dead
at the scene.
Now, uh, on a personal note,
and owing to the fact I know
I'm gonna get this question
from at least one of you,
yes, I do know the defendant well.
Doug Linman has served this city
for over nine years.
He's a loyal and dedicated prosecutor.
This is a hard day... for all of us.
- Questions?
- [man] Detective!
Will Mr. Linman be given special
treatment by your department?
I'm not sure that even merits
an answer, but no. Absolutely not.
- Perri.
- Could you describe the relationship
between Mr. Linman and his wife?
Any marriage difficulties?
- Any previous acts of violence?
- None that I know of.
At this point I can't speculate
on state of mind or motive.
Have you looked at Mr. Linman's claim
that he was visited
by a dead man prior to the murder?
- Come again?
- In the statement you made,
Mr. Linman claims that he was
visited at the baseball field
by his father, Robert Linman.
Except that Robert Linman
died seven years ago.
Exactly. He did. What's your point?
Were there any other witnesses
who saw Robert Linman?
He'd be a balding man,
largish ears, five-nine, five-ten.
Uh, excuse me, who are you?
Carl Kolchak. I'm with the Beacon.
Next question.
- Hey, partner.
- Hey.
Sounded like you had your hands full.
No kidding. You ever hear
of that reporter, Carl Kolchak?
His editor is gonna get
an earful from me.
Ghosts?
Is that what you ask detectives about?
I don't recall saying "ghosts."
- No. "Dead man. Largish ears."
- I did say that.
Even if I didn't know the Linmans, l'd
have a hard time finding the humor.
I'm not making light, Tony.
I want to know why a man
suddenly bashes his wife's head in,
claiming his dead father made him.
God, isn't it obvious? He snapped.
It happens every day.
But why say his father
directed him to kill her?
I don't know, Carl.
Maybe he just broke from reality.
A man doesn't just break from reality,
kill his wife, then tell
some crazy story to explain it.
OK...
Then maybe he didn't break from reality.
Maybe this is a story he's concocting
to service as an insanity defense.
He's a prosecutor. Don't you think
he'd come up with a better story?
Ask him yourself. His attorney called.
Doug wants to talk.
And not to bolster
some kind of insanity plea.
He intends to plead guilty.
[buzzer]
[metal clanking]
I met her my first year in law school.
I married her the day I passed the bar.
T o celebrate.
I love my wife.
I love...
I need you to write that.
I need you to tell them. T ell my son.
They won't even let me see him.
Mr. Linman, talk us through
that day at the ballpark.
I did it.
I murdered her.
I still don't know why.
You told the police
you saw your deceased father.
Yes. Several times.
Before. But not since.
Did you think it was strange seeing him?
No.
It felt so... It just felt right.
I've missed him so much
in the last few years.
When he started to...
to visit me,
it was kind of like a dream.
You know?
In a dream, it feels natural.
Did he tell you to kill your wife?
Yes.
No, I mean, he didn't say, "Kill Jane."
He said to me,
"You know what you have to do."
And somehow I did.
I have to ask you, Mr. Linman.
Why are you pleading guilty?
I mean, you don't appear to me
to be delusional.
- Do you think you are?
- What else would I be?
I'm not sure,
but I think you owe it to your wife
to find out if someone else,
or if something else, is responsible.
[buzzer]
Can I ask you two
to step outside, please?
Now.
You're leading him down a path
he doesn't want to go.
He wants to plead guilty.
We're just asking questions,
Detective Granof.
Perri, you've always been
a stand-up reporter,
so I'm gonna be nice about this.
I don't care who your boss knows,
you'll have no further access
to Doug Linman. Understood?
I'm thinking I'm understanding
what this whole thing is about.
Why you're interested in this case.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
Have you seen the autopsy photos
of Linman's wife?
Yeah, I have.
And there's no mark on her wrist.
I'm not going to let this go.
There's something deeper here.
[man's voice]
You know what you have to do.
What's this?
Doug Linman's effects. His attorney
let me take a look through them.
Didn't Detective Granof
just tell you to back off?
No, he said
we couldn't talk to Linman.
He didn't say
"You can't go through his stuff."
And what exactly
do you expect to find?
- You'll laugh.
- I won't laugh.
Everything Doug Linman described:
the dreamlike state,
the compulsion to act,
even the appearance of a loved one,
matches records of...
spirit possession.
Sorry. Spirit possession.
You think Linman just jotted
all this down in his day-planner?
No. But there may be evidence
here of a trigger.
What do you mean by "trigger?"
Possessions usually take place
at a time of personal crisis,
so anything can be a trigger.
A bankruptcy filing,
a diagnosis from the doctor...
[sighs] But there's nothing here.
The only unusual reference is "AC, DC."
AC, DC? The band, battery,
or the sexual preference?
None of the above.
It's an appointment he underlined.
1 1 am, last Thursday.
What?
"AC, DC" stands for
"Appellate Court, Damon Caylor."
I happen to know he filed a writ
of habeas corpus there last Thursday.
Well, who's Damon Caylor?
Caylor was sort of
a Charles Manson wannabe.
He recruited lost souls
and persuaded them
that society was corrupt
and needed to be wiped clean.
By "wiped clean,"
I gather you mean killing people?
Specifically, the moral hypocrites.
They managed to kill one so-called
"hypocrite" before being arrested,
but they hacked off
the head of an oil executive
in a Palos Verdes
supermarket parking lot.
Nice.
And you covered Caylor's trial.
Linman prosecuted.
They never got him for the murder
his followers committed,
but he was convicted on a separate
charge of strangling his wife, T eresa.
Wait a sec,
look what you wrote here.
"Linman claimed Caylor possessed
his followers to commit murder."
He wasn't talking
about a literal possession.
Huh. Maybe he was.
No! Wai... Carl!
Linman was using the word "possession"
as a metaphor.
Maybe, but what if Caylor metaphorically
possessed his followers to kill,
and now, somehow, literally directed
Linman to do the same?
Caylor indoctrinated weak-minded people
over a period of months, even years.
It'd be a pretty neat trick
to do the same thing
to a prosecutor
from inside his jail cell.
It would, wouldn't it?
If Caylor is involved,
and I'm not saying he is,
why not consider
the more likely scenario?
Which is?
His old followers, from the outside.
Maybe he directed them to take revenge.
Either way, we need to find out.
We've got to get back in
to see Doug Linman.
- Can't.
- We can talk to the warden.
No, I mean, we can't.
Doug Linman is dead.
He hung himself in his cell
early this morning.
That's why he agreed to talk.
He intended the interview
to be his final statement.
[buzzer]
[metal scraping]
Thank you for seeing us so quickly.
Oh... not a problem.
Caylor doesn't get many visitors.
Not since he's been confined
to solitary.
[Perri] When was his last visitor?
There was only one, months ago,
uh, February maybe.
- Can I get a name?
- I can get you that.
What did Caylor do
to end up in solitary?
Well, it's what he said,
not what he did. I thought you knew.
Knew what?
Caylor made a lot of enemies here.
He told the prisoners they were
all worthless, a bunch of cowards.
Last year,
he was attacked in the kitchen.
Somebody threw hot oil in his face.
Permanently blinded him.
Caylor's blind?
You see why we can't put him
back in the general population.
Half the gangs in here still have
a standing death order against him.
Mark here will be outside
the whole time.
- That's, uh, if you need him.
- Thanks.
Carl.
- Just, uh...
- What?
- I thought I could do it.
- What are you talking about?
I covered Caylor's trial
for six months and...
He's shackled and blind.
I need you to interview him
without me. Sorry.
[buzzer]
[keys jangle]
[metal clanks]
- Where is she?
- Who?
They said Perri Reed was coming.
Where is she?
She's not coming.
My name is Carl Kolchak...
I know who you are.
But I agreed to talk to her, not you.
Are you doing that?
You certainly have
an active imagination, Mr. Kolchak.
Why don't you check the batteries?
They're new.
What is it that you wanted to ask,
Mr. Kolchak?
What's the angle of your story?
The prosecutor who put you away...
He's dead.
I heard.
You're in solitary, Mr. Caylor.
How did you know that?
It's a prison. You hear things.
And you're not sorry he's dead.
You mean like all the people
you quote in your paper?
"He seemed so normal.
Such a good father."
I don't grieve for hypocrites.
You'd seen Mr. Linman recently,
hadn't you?
I don't see anyone anymore.
He opposed my writ of habeas corpus,
and it was denied.
- So this was revenge?
- I don't understand.
Oh, I think you do.
You're known as a powerful manipulator.
See, I think that you somehow directed
Doug Linman to kill his wife.
My followers were weak-minded.
Directing a prosecutor
would be a pretty neat trick...
from inside my cell.
"You know what you have to do."
What does it mean?
It means all of those
who belong in hell will find their way.
- He did it.
- Wait, he told you that?
No, but he... he knew things
he shouldn't have.
If there's one thing he's capable of,
it's manipulating you
into believing he's guilty.
Then why not come right out and say it?
Why play coy?
He's a manipulator. World-class.
Look, I don't know
what kind of game he's playing,
but I have no doubt in my mind
he's playing one.
Ah, if this is a game,
is it over? Or is it just starting?
[whistle, cheering]
Boys, no running in the house!
And wash up! Dinner in 1 5 minutes!
Collin, can you turn that down, please?
Collin! Can you turn that down, please?!
Mommy. Look what I made.
OK, sweetie. Get cleaned up.
Mommy, you didn't look! Mommy!
OK, honey, I'm sorry. I'm looking.
[voices on police radio]
"You know what you have to do."
Yeah.
[chatter]
Press is supposed to be back
behind the police tape.
I'm not asking for a statement,
Detective.
- I need to talk to you.
- Not now.
I believe there's a connection
between this murder
and the murder
of Doug Linman's wife.
Why do you say that?
Amanda Daniels
is a highly respected judge.
Doug Linman a top prosecutor.
Both of them presided
at the trial of Damon Caylor.
What's Caylor have to do with anything?
You arrested Caylor, Detective.
I mean, you know he's a manipulator,
that he directed his followers to kill.
Caylor is in prison, Mr. Kolchak.
Yeah, but both Linman and Daniels
claimed they were directed to kill
by loved ones they lost.
Judge Daniels only shared that
with me and my partner.
- How did you know?
- I didn't. But it's true, isn't it?
She claims she saw the image
of her six-year-old daughter,
who was killed
in a drunk-driving accident last year.
Then how do you explain that?
I can't. And neither can you.
Detective, you testified
against Caylor at his trial.
Yeah, so?
Have you had any visions
of a dead parent, a child...
a family member you loved or miss?
I think they need to start
upping your medication, Kolchak.
All right? And soon.
He's just not willing to believe.
Yeah, neither will Perri.
- What do you mean?
- Perri. Didn't she tell you?
T ell me what?
The role she played
in Caylor's conviction.
What role?
Linman couldn't prosecute Caylor
for the crimes his followers committed.
Not until Perri interviewed
Caylor's wife,
who admitted
that he directed them to kill.
That's why Caylor killed his wife?
The day Perri's story was published.
Katrina Ortega?
Yes.
I'm Perri Reed. I'm a reporter.
From the Beacon.
I remember you. At the trial.
I'd like to talk to you
about Damon Caylor.
You shouldn't... I...
I can get in trouble
if you come back here.
Katrina,
I think Caylor's getting revenge
on the judge and the prosecutor
who tried him.
- I don't know anything about that.
- I think you do.
- Me?
- Yeah, according to the warden,
you visited Caylor in prison
six months ago. Why?
Because I couldn't say no.
How's that for an answer?
After two years
of deprogramming and lithium,
when he called, I still came running.
Did he ask you to do anything for him?
T o contact anyone?
No. He just said he was done with us.
That he didn't need any of us anymore.
But he didn't say why.
He's blind, but he still sees, you know?
Not with his eyes. He sees inside you.
People you love, people you miss.
That's how he'd get us
to do things for him.
Get inside our heads and
then use our own memories against us.
Confuse us.
If the police didn't stop us,
it would have been my turn.
I would have killed someone, too.
Someone like you.
He hates you, you know. All of you.
He blames you
for turning his wife against him.
His hate is like this flame
burning in his heart.
It'll never go out.
Not until you're all dead.
You asked to see me.
I heard about poor Judge Daniels.
1 7 years of marriage down the drain.
So you're admitting it.
That you directed her to kill.
I have a message
the people need to hear.
I want it printed.
On the front page of the Beacon.
Do that, and I feel certain
the killings will stop.
- You're blackmailing us?
- I'm simply trying to help.
Why would I believe
you'd keep your word?
I've learned more about you
since our last visit, Mr. Kolchak.
About the death of your wife, lrene.
The bizarre story you told the police.
How did you know that?
The point is,
you're someone I can deal with.
Someone who understands loss,
like I do.
- I'm not like you.
- But you are.
These other people are hypocrites.
Claiming to be virtuous, when their real
interest is advancing their careers,
buying bigger houses, newer cars,
taking vacations in Hawaii and Aspen.
Not you.
You're in this for yourself,
and you admit it.
I respect that.
I didn't murder my wife.
You murdered yours.
I loved my wife,
as deeply as you loved yours.
But they confused her
into turning against me.
I hated what they made me do.
You're responsible
for your wife's death. No one else.
Just as Doug Linman
is responsible for his wife.
And Judge Daniels for her husband.
And the same for all of those
who will follow.
Let them live with that pain.
If they can.
I have one more condition.
He'll only give it to Perri?
Yeah, he said he's offended
by her refusal to see him.
I won't let this newspaper
become a mouthpiece for a lunatic.
- What do we tell Caylor?
- T ell him to shove it.
What?
You believed he was responsible
for the deaths.
Yeah, I do. I think Caylor's
loss of eyesight and time alone
have allowed him to strengthen his mind,
to focus it.
So you really think he's become some
kind of homicidal Amazing Kreskin?
- You can't doubt he's involved.
- I don't. Just not the way you think.
Point is, if we don't print his
manifesto, he'll keep killing people.
And I think he will, even if we do.
Perri said it.
Caylor's a games player.
This is part of a game.
Why didn't he try to influence her?
Or Granof?
Maybe he did.
We need to contact Granof's partner...
- Granof doesn't have a partner.
- Sure he does.
No. Glen Mitchell died six months ago.
He never got a new one.
Granof said he was
at the crime scene this morning.
- Hey, Pat. Wait up.
- Hey. What's going on?
We just had a disturbance call.
4400 Cloverdale.
4400 Cloverdale? That's my address.
I know.
You know what you have to do.
Thanks. They think he went home.
He's not picking up his cell.
I'll get the address.
[loud music through earphones]
[tires screech]
[beep]
- [rapid knocking]
- [Carl] Hello!
[cocks trigger]
- [gunshot]
- [beep]
What is this? What?
Pat?
[buzzer]
Are you sure you wanna
go through with this?
- I have to.
- No, you don't.
If Granof killed his wife
because I couldn't go in there...
- Guard.
- [keys jangle, gate clatters]
Please. Sit, Miss Reed.
You got what you wanted.
She's here. Now give it to us.
I said, sit.
Who do you think you're talking to?
It's all right.
I'm grateful you came this evening,
Miss Reed.
I know how hard it was for you
to walk into this room.
Oh, it's nothing to be ashamed of.
You're afraid of me.
Yes, I am.
Strange, isn't it?
Well, after all, I'm shackled.
A blind man. But you know why?
It's because I can't see you,
but I can see... who you are.
You can see, Caylor.
But what you see, you twist.
I should've been a reporter.
However you're doing it,
we want the killings to stop.
Print it on the front page
of the Beacon. As is.
No editor's commentary.
No explanation.
Does your editor
agree to these conditions?
I suppose he'll have to.
Good.
I know what you love!
I know what you fear!
[Carl] Let go! Guards!
I know... what you have to do.
- Did you get it?
- Yeah.
This some kind of joke?
What?
It's empty. The whole thing.
But I don't understand.
Why would he give us a blank book?
Because you were right. This was a game
and you were the prize.
Me?
Remember Doug Linman's day-planner?
AC-DC? The day of Caylor's
appellate court hearing?
Caylor filed a motion
knowing that it would be denied.
Why would he do that?
Because he knew that Linman,
Judge Daniels and Granof would be there.
I don't understand what this has to do
with an empty notebook.
What if Caylor needed to see his victims
in order to control them.
- T o "see" them?
- Yeah, to be with them,
to be near them.
So he could see inside their heads.
He lied about this because
he knew it would put him in contact
with the one victim
he couldn't claim until now. You.
Thanks.
I see you looking at me.
- Huh?
- I can see you, Jain.
- Stop it!
- I'm, I'm worried about you.
Go away. T oday.
OK.
- How's she doing?
- She seems agitated.
What if she stabs me with her
letter opener when I'm not looking?
Well, I think she'll only
go after people she loves, Jain,
so you're pretty safe.
Yeah. But what did Granof say?
Well, he's agreed to ask the warden
to send Caylor
to a deep isolation facility
in upstate Michigan, so...
Will moving him
make any difference?
I don't know.
I'm gonna, um, catch you later.
How are you feeling?
The way you and Jain keep staring at me,
like the most popular girl at the prom.
Yeah, I don't think Jain
wants the next dance, though.
- How's Granof?
- Better.
Uh, the doctor gave him
some anti-anxiety pills.
Which brings me to something
I wanted to discuss with you.
Medication.
- No. No.
- Just hear me out.
- I'm not taking any drugs, Kolchak!
- It's just sleeping pills.
If you're asleep, you pose no danger
to yourself or anyone else.
Look, I'm not gonna hurt anyone, OK?
I'm not seeing anybody.
- Yeah, that's just what Granof thought.
- How long am I supposed to be asleep?
Just until morning. Until the warden
gets Caylor out of state.
And what possible difference
does that make?
Look, I don't know,
but it's worth a try.
Did Jain take my letter opener?
Perri. Look, if you won't do it
for yourself, do it for your parents.
Do it for anyone you love.
I can't express enough how much
I hate the idea of this whole thing.
Think of it as a vacation
from your problems.
That's not funny.
- I feel like Caylor won.
- No. He hasn't.
He has.
He got inside my head.
I'm afraid to go to sleep.
- Afraid of what I'll dream.
- I'm gonna be right here. OK?
You know what you have to do.
[echoes]
[knocking]
Irene?
[exhales sharply]
You know what you have to do.
It can't be.
I know how much you've missed me.
The way I've missed you.
[Caylor's voice]
You know what you have to do.
I can't get through to Kolchak.
- He's not picking up?
- No. Not at Perri's or his cell phone.
Caylor might have tricked us.
- You know what you have to do.
- [T ony] How?
[Jain] Kolchak spent more time with him
than any one of us.
What if he couldn't get to Reed?
So, he got to him instead.
You get down there, I'll call Granof.
OK.
You know what you have to do.
It's not there.
It can be just like it was.
Before you were lost
and searching for answers.
When your life still belonged to you.
- Granof.
- Pat, it's, uh, T ony Vincenzo.
Could you some officers
over to Perri Reed's apartment?
Yeah, of course, but why?
We're afraid some of Caylor's followers
might target her next.
She doesn't need to worry about Caylor.
I've been talking to the warden and
we're transferring him a little early.
What do I have to do?
Hmm, you know what you have to do.
[? The Veils: More Heat Than Light]
? The Imperial disaster's
? In furious decline
? They've been burnin' down the ghettos
? Burnin ' down the ghettos
? Crossin ' all of the lines
? Everyone gets so excited...
You know what you have to do.
?... heat than light
More heat than light... ?
You know what you have to do.
Perri!
[banging on door]
Kolchak!
You know what you have to do.
[Jain, knocking] Kolchak!
Kolchak! Open the door!
- Kolchak!
- You know what you have to do.
You know what you have to do.
[lrene] You know what you have to do.
[Jain] Perri!
- What's going on out here?
- Call the cops! Now!
You know what you have to do.
[Caylor] You know what you have to do.
[alarm]
Open the door!
Kolchak!
He did what he said, it was done.
In less than a minute.
- Hey.
- Uh,... you can have this back now.
- Thanks.
- I took it.
- I know.
- So...
- We don't have to talk about it.
You saw her last night, didn't you?
I saw...
saw what he wanted me to see.
You OK?
Yeah.
Good.
[Carl] I spend long hours
looking outside for answers.
But there is a deeper understanding,
hidden inside.
About the darkness
that resides in each of us,
and how far we would go
to get back what we can never recover.