[phone rings]
[man] You were late.
Missed your chance.
[Carl] You said he could help me
find what killed my wife.
[man] He still can.
T rucker picked up a hitcher
matching Kolchak's witness.
Dropped him off near Koreatown.
She has a dream.
She will meet a man in need.
She will help this man.
She will open her heart to him.
She will find peace.
Turns out that our missing witness
is an undercover DEA agent
by the name of Victor Caleca.
They want him for the same reason they
wanted you, the night your wife died.
He's driving home with his wife,
and wham!
Something slams into them.
She still hasn't been found.
This Agent Caleca's wife,
she's dead, right?
- Right.
- Well then, who's this?
[woman] It's Linda.
I haven't heard from Victor in days.
She's alive.
Justice Department is filing suit
to make Kolchak reveal his source.
He won't.
- There is another way.
- Me.
- I need to know who you are.
- I can't help you.
- I need answers.
- We won't be speaking again.
- You don't know his name.
- The information was good.
Do you know how reckless that is?
I don't know who you are, Carl.
- What did you find?
- Two calls placed to Agent Walton
in the past 48 hours
from a market in Koreatown.
OK. You'd better get down there.
You're under arrest.
- You seen McManus?
- He's not picking up?
Edhead.
- Speaking.
- Where's Jain?
I'm not supposed to say.
Where is he?
Are you the boss?
I promised I wouldn't tell,
but he went to Koreatown.
- What for?
- Kolchak sent him.
What is it?
That's why I was looking for Jain.
T o take pictures.
- Pictures of what?
- A double homicide. In Koreatown.
[police radio]
Perri Reed, I'm with the Beacon.
- Behind the line.
- My friend's inside.
- I'm sorry.
- It's OK, they're with me.
Hey.
[camera shutter]
Jain, what happened?
I talked to him, Agent Caleca,
just before they killed him.
Victor Caleca?
- Did he send you?
- What did he say?
He said he was expecting
Agent Walton, not me.
He had just spoken to him on the phone.
Agent Walton was already dead.
I know. I told him that.
Then he said "It's a trap."
Get out of here. Now.
[gunshot]
I couldn't get the back door open,
or the closet.
I guess that man
was already hiding in there.
So I hid under the cot.
Did you get a look at them?
I heard them.
[gunshot]
[gun cocks]
I never saw their faces.
I'd like to speak with you.
[police radio]
[trickling]
[man] You ready?
[woman sobs and speaks Korean]
Ma'am.
[speaks Korean]
[buzzer]
[door opens]
What's this? A turn-down service?
It's your lucky day, Carl.
You're free to go.
Just like that?
- Yeah, just like that.
- I don't understand.
This DEA agent we were hunting for,
we found him tonight.
Shot dead in a Korean market.
[Fain]
We don't need your source anymore.
Come on, Carl. Let's go.
Get out of here.
Before I change my mind.
[buzzer]
[man] Ma'am.
Can I do anything for you?
No. Thank you.
[cash register beeps]
[distant siren]
So how long were you behind bars?
Five, six hours?
Yeah, something like that.
Fain keeps putting you in jail
and you keep getting out.
That's right.
Well, now you get to play the hero
for refusing to betray a source
whose name you didn't even know.
You know me too well.
Or rather you don't know me at all.
No. I don't think I do.
I, uh... went a little crazy
the last few days.
- I don't expect you to forgive me.
- Good. Because I don't.
I wish I could explain it.
I can only say that I thought
I was close to answers
about what killed my wife.
- And now?
- Now...
Hopes raised, then dashed
are cruel indeed.
And what if I told you...
I could raise them again?
Kolchak! Hey, man.
You OK?
Vincenzo said you nearly got shot.
Are you OK?
Yeah, yeah. I'm sorry.
I know how much finding this guy
Caleca meant to you.
- Yeah.
- But we think we found something else.
- You mean, we think I found it.
- What is it?
Before he died, Caleca's supervisor,
Agent Walton, told us a story.
Caleca survived an attack
while driving in a storm.
An attack in which his wife Linda
was killed. Sound familiar?
You know it does.
Only, unlike your wife,
Walton told us that Linda Caleca's
body was never found.
And that, my friends, was a big fat lie.
- You found her body?
- I found her. Alive.
I got this off that guy Walton's
throwaway cell phone.
It's Linda.
I know I'm not supposed to call,
but I haven't heard from Victor in days.
I'm scared, Rich.
- I'll try you again later.
- She's on the run.
If we can find her, she might be able to
give us the answers you're looking for.
I'm on it. That call was placed
from a pay phone in San Bernardino.
A pay phone?
Then how can you track her?
I've got some other tricks up my sleeve.
What about this source of yours?
The one who told you about Caleca.
I told you, I don't know who he is.
- You never saw him? Never met him?
- No.
There was just this house
that he sent me to.
Where?
[Perri] Carl?
I thought you said this was the place.
It is. I'm sure of it.
Then... where's the house?
[Jain] Do you think
someone could've moved it?
The whole house? In 48 hours?
Like on Home Makeover?
He said if I answered Caleca's
questions, I'd answer my own.
Carl, this house was never here.
The cell phone you say
you spoke to this source on...
- never activated.
- What are you saying?
Could you have been tipped off
some other kind of way?
By a police source of some kind?
A drug informant
who told you to look for Caleca.
What? And then I just twisted it
in my head? Imagined this source?
You're forgetting. Kolchak
wasn't the only one hearing voices.
- Who else?
- Agent Caleca.
He told me he spoke to
Agent Walton on the phone,
when Walton was already dead.
[Perri] It's possible Walton was alive.
Maybe he wasn't. And maybe
this isn't all in Kolchak's head.
Maybe there's something to this.
[door opens]
We are sorry.
We are no longer open.
Oh, no, no, no.
We don't want to buy anything.
We just want to talk. Are you OK?
OK. Yes.
She closing down the store?
She doesn't want to stay here
any longer. T oo much death.
- Where will she go?
- With me.
I have a house by the sea.
North of here.
Dae, this is Carl Kolchak.
He needs to ask some questions
about the man who was here.
Victor Caleca.
Did he ever talk to you about his wife?
[speaks Korean]
She did not know he was married.
- He said a name in his sleep.
- Linda.
Yeah. Linda.
Look, we need to find her.
We think the men who came here
are looking for her.
[speaks Korean]
She doesn't know anything about her.
OK. Thank you.
- She said there is something.
- [Dae speaks Korean]
He used to wear it
around his wrist.
[Dae speaks Korean]
It meant as much to him
as her wedding photos meant to her.
She wants you to keep it.
You say he wore it on his wrist.
Did you ever happen to see
if there was a mark there?
[speaks Korean]
It would've been like a birthmark.
Red. Shaped like a snake.
[woman speaks Korean]
No. She saw no mark.
Thanks.
[woman] This is where I'll be.
If you find this woman.
If there's anything we can do
to help her, please tell us.
We will. Thank you.
You want to tell us
what that was all about?
I was just asking.
That question
about the mark on Agent Caleca?
Why not?
You said that mark appears on people
after they die strange deaths.
Dead people. Not the living.
I also said this is a puzzle
I'm trying to piece together.
I don't even know what
all the pieces look like yet.
- What do you think this means?
- I don't know.
It's like that, uh, bracelet
Madonna wears, right?
- And Britney Spears?
- Those are Kabbalah strings.
This one has knots tied in it in
groups of two, four and three.
[phone rings]
It's Edhead. Hey.
Nice. We'll be right there.
- What?
- Linda Caleca.
Edhead thinks she's found her.
So the pay phone she called from
is located right here,
directly across the street from
the Travel lnn motel in Tujunga.
You think she was staying there?
Even if she did, she would've
paid cash to avoid being found.
Hard to find, but not impossible.
Even if you pay cash,
the motel takes your driver's license.
Puts your number
into the computer system.
I managed to get her credit record
which shows her driver's license number.
I8884201.
Got a match for it at the motel?
- That's what I'm saying.
- Is she there now?
She left six days ago.
[Jain] Ah... What?
Then you didn't exactly find her.
I didn't say I knew where she is
right now, but I found her.
- She just left again.
- What do you mean, left again?
She was there six nights ago,
stayed three nights.
Same thing six nights before,
stayed three nights then left.
Hey, let me see that bracelet again.
- That's what this is for.
- What?
The knots,
in groupings of two, four and three.
It's a perpetual calendar.
- I don't get it.
- Well, she's on the run.
She can't stay anywhere too long.
It's not safe to call her husband, so...
She's gone between
three different motels.
This bracelet was a way for Caleca
to know where she was on any given day.
Two knots, two nights at one motel.
Four knots, four nights at another.
- Three knots...
- Back at the Travel lnn in Tujunga?
For three nights.
If she was last there six nights ago,
she'd be back there...
T oday.
Edhead... rules.
They're on the move.
They are on the move.
[tires screech]
[helicopter rotor blades]
[man] Air Unit Six
tracking northbound on the 1 1 0.
Advise when you have
the vehicle in sight.
I'll meet you out the front.
Come on, Carl.
Why have you dragged us
all the way out here?
Anything?
The manager recognizes her,
but says he hasn't seen her.
Wait. That's her, isn't it?
You don't think
that's his source, do you?
I think that is Victor Caleca's wife.
Wait there.
- I thought she was dead.
- Yeah. So did l.
- You ready to move?
- [man] Copy that.
I'd like to check in, please.
Mrs. Caleca, I'm Perri Reed
and this is Carl Kolchak.
- Hi.
- What do you want?
T o help.
[motorbikes approach]
How did you find me?
We can explain that later.
We got trouble.
- Kolchak!
- We need to get you to safety.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
Get down!
Shots fired! Go, go, go, go, go!
[tires screech]
[siren]
Come on.
- I'm hitting these guys.
- So am l.
[tires screech]
All right. I just got off
the phone with Chief Bratton.
He assures me the authorities
are making all efforts
to locate Carl and Perri.
It's been four hours
since they went missing
and there hasn't been
a single sighting. Jain.
We think they may be
with this woman, Linda Caleca,
the widow of the DEA agent
that was shot last night.
We think that she's the one
these bikers were after.
Any idea why they want to kill her?
That's the angle we were working
when this went down.
In their absence,
it's the angle we'll all be working.
Seth, Rob, we need to find out
who these bikers are
and find Carl and Perri before they do.
- We're on it.
- Dawn, hound the LAPD,
sheriffs, and,
God forgive me, the coroner.
Anyone catches a glimpse
of Carl, Perri, or this woman,
I want to know about it first.
All right, we all know our assignments.
Let's get on it.
Could you come with me?
Sorry to drop in unannounced.
You can imagine why I'm here.
Why don't you tell me?
Three officers were gunned down
in the line of duty today.
It goes without saying,
we need answers.
Yes, it does.
We want your cooperation
to monitor calls
- in and out of the Beacon...
- Listen to our calls?
For rapid response,
in case Reed or Kolchak phone in.
We'll also need your photographs, son.
- Give you my pictures?
- I know, I know.
T ony, it is a lot to ask
but there's a lot at stake here.
Yes, there is,
and you will receive
no cooperation from this paper.
What did you say?
If something happened to Carl,
Perri or Jain,
- I would hold you responsible.
- Me?
They should cover the story, not be it.
I didn't make them the story.
You released Kolchak to follow him,
- as your stalking horse.
- You wanted Kolchak's source.
All due respect, I don't answer to you
about my investigative techniques.
No, you answer to the public.
Which is what this paper
will make sure you do,
by publishing what we know,
when we know it.
I thought we were friends.
We were.
Then, as a friend,
do you really think
that your publisher will refuse
to cooperate with the FBl?
The Crossbinder board?
I'd hate to see you fall on your sword.
Not for Kolchak.
He's not worth it.
You can go now.
Here is... my cell phone number.
In case my "friend" changes his mind.
That was awesome.
He's right.
The board might not back up my decision.
We need to find Carl and Perri, fast.
Yeah, I know, but how?
- Your friend, Egghead...
- Edhead.
Could you get her back down here?
Yeah.
- Hey.
- [owl hoots]
Well, I cleaned out the vending machine.
We've got cookies, chips
and candy for dinner.
Fantastic.
- Linda?
- No thanks.
- How did you find me?
- Your driver's license.
You left the number with the motel.
But how did you know that
I'd be coming back to that motel?
T oday?
[sobs]
Vic's dead, isn't he?
- I'm sorry.
- I knew it.
I knew it when I saw you.
I had a dream last night
and it felt... so real.
Victor came to me...
and he told me that he wasn't
ever going to see me again.
But he said it would be OK.
That I wouldn't be alone.
That I'd find peace.
Those bikers.
Were they the same ones
that ambushed you and your husband
three weeks ago?
I don't know.
Victor thought a drug lord,
Felix Morales, was responsible.
That's why he and Rich Walton
came up with the story
that I was already dead.
We wore these bracelets
so that he could find me again,
after he'd paid him for our lives.
But Morales didn't kill him, did he?
It was the bikers.
Who are they?
We don't know.
We only know that they killed Morales
and your husband and Agent Walton, too.
And now they're coming after me.
Why?
We need every possible thing
that we can get.
OK, just give us one minute, will you?
Thanks.
- Did you reach Edhead?
- Yeah, she's working on it.
- That's not why I wanted to see you.
- What is it?
[sighs]
There's a problem with this story.
- These are the killers?
- Yeah.
Well, two of them anyway.
- I've got positive lDs.
- How?
Their photos were on file, from a bank
shoot-out in Culver City two years ago.
They're ex-cons by the names
of Clayton Crans and Roy Lockard.
So that's good work.
What's the problem?
The story says that SWAT sharpshooters
took out both Crans and Lockard.
According to our files,
both of these men are already dead.
Think you can sleep?
I'll try.
We'll just be in the next room.
Perri.
You're so kind doing this for me.
I don't know what to say.
You don't have to say anything.
I know you're reporters,
but you're risking your lives
staying with me.
My colleague, Carl...
about a year ago, he and his wife
were attacked in a storm
by... something he didn't see.
Is she OK?
She was killed.
How?
She was pregnant.
Her fetus was torn from her body.
Oh, my God.
Carl was told
if he could find your husband,
he might get the answers
to who or... what killed her.
Who or what?
I don't have any answers for him.
I don't think Victor did either.
Who would tell him that we would?
[door opens]
Hey. You want some dinner?
I've got, uh, cheese,
ranch and barbecue flavor.
Maybe later.
[Carl sighs]
We're going to have
a little problem in the morning.
What's that?
I wasn't quite ready
to flee justice today.
How much cash do you have?
After what I spent on dinner?
About 60 bucks.
And I thought you were a rich man.
What do you mean?
You were right about Agent Fain
trying to pit me against you.
He told me your "motive"
for killing lrene.
Irene's estate.
I always wondered how you could
afford that house in the hills.
Yeah.
Did you give the cabin manager
your driver's license number?
Yeah, I changed it by a digit.
He seemed pretty nosy though.
I know how we found Linda,
but I'm still wondering
how those bikers got there.
I don't know.
I, uh, heard on the radio
three cops got shot,
but the bikers got away.
Who are they?
That's the question.
She can't keep running forever, Carl.
Got any ideas on where we can take her?
Well, in case you haven't noticed,
I'm kind of making this thing up
as I go along.
Yeah. I noticed that.
Hopefully, the cops will find the bikers
before the bikers find us.
And if they don't?
If they don't...
she's got to go someplace
where no one will ever find her.
[knock at door]
- Who is it?
- It's the manager.
I'm just closing up the front desk,
in case you folks need anything.
- Uh, we're fine.
- You want me to turn down the sheets?
- Got some bedtime mints here?
- No, thank you. Good night.
All right, then. Good night.
- I'll call you back. What?
- She got something.
I cloned this agent's cell number.
Been listening to his traffic all night.
Mostly dead ends...
But?
But he just got the call.
Kolchak's car was spotted
at a cabin off the Sierra Highway.
- The FBl's on the way there.
- I need a phone number.
Hey, Perri.
Just want to say thank you
for, uh, being here.
For trusting me.
In for a penny.
Yeah.
But since I am here, maybe you could
start trusting me a little bit more.
What do you mean?
You asked that Korean woman, Dae,
about whether Caleca
had the mark on his wrist.
[sighs]
- Yeah.
- Why?
Don't say you were just
asking an innocent question,
because you don't ask
innocent questions.
Why would you think that mark
would've been on Caleca's wrist?
Because...
I have it on mine.
How did it get there?
I was born with it.
I thought it was a birthmark
until lrene died
and... I saw it on her body.
I don't understand how that could be.
That's when I started looking, you know,
and I found it on other people
who'd died strange deaths.
But in each case, it appeared
on their bodies after they died.
That's right.
You never found it
on anyone else living?
Never found anyone born with it,
like you?
[phone rings]
[Carl sighs]
- Hello.
- Carl, it's Tony.
T ony? How did you find us?
The FBI beat me to it.
You've got to get out of there, now.
[motorbike engines]
I think it's too late for that.
[cocks gun]
Shh.
Look, our only chance is the car.
We'll never make it.
Not without him seeing us.
- We can go through the trees.
- They'd hear us.
But they'll find us if we stay here.
- I'm going to draw them away.
- What are you talking about?
When they start after me,
get in the car and don't stop.
They'll kill you.
If I make it to the manager's office,
I can take his truck.
You have a better plan?
It's going to be OK.
[gunshot]
What happened, Carl?
Where's Linda Caleca?
[Fain] Kolchak!
Kolchak!
- Perri, hey.
- Where is he?
In the conference room.
Oh, my God. How did you get away?
I'm not even sure, exactly.
I just kept running.
And they didn't catch you?
- No.
- I can't believe it.
I was just telling T ony how, uh, Linda
Caleca got away from us at the motel.
You didn't see where she went?
No. I didn't.
Well, we'll just have to tell that
to Agent Fain.
That we can't be of any use to them.
That's right.
And we have no indication of where
Mrs. Caleca might have gone to?
I'm hoping someplace safe.
Someplace no one will ever find her.
[Carl] Life travels a crooked path.
[speaks Korean]
A course whose shape
we cannot recognize,
except by looking back on it.
How happiness leads to heartbreak.
I' m back.
How a dark turn leads to peace and joy.
Our purpose,
like our destination, is hidden.
But goodness is a refuge.
A soft, warm light
into which evil cannot see.