Carl Kolchak.
Perri Reed, and this is Jain McManus.
- She's senior crime reporter?
- I've been here 4 years...
You are expected to get along.
This is where Kolchak killed his wife.
That's not his story.
All these strange deaths,
like pieces in a puzzle,
a puzzle I'm trying to put together.
The public has a right to know.
These are things
I need to find out for myself.
[Carl] Fear has its own physiology,
primal responses to threat.
The quickened heart,
the sweaty palm,
the panic that chokes in the throat,
making time seem to stand still.
We 're born with these instincts
to flee danger
from the world outside us, to survive.
[? hip hop]
[hel icopter]
But there 's no place to run
when the dangers come
not from outside us, but from...
ourselves.
[man] Hey.
Hey.
[muffled scream]
[hissing]
- Enough!
- What are you doing?
- Let her go.
- We're not finished.
- I said let her go!
- Not yet. She's not ready.
Get her.
[creaking]
[water pouring]
Help me! Help me!
Help me!
[spluttering]
[gasping]
[muffled]
[muffled] Help! Help!
Look who's here.
Good morning.
Don't tell me, Carl.
Let me guess why you're here.
Be my guest.
This morning,
a vagrant found the body
of Liza Valenti, age 20,
a UC honors student.
According to the coroner,
she showed signs of drowning.
Ballooned lungs, foam in the airways,
conjunctival hemorrhage...
Only there was no water
found in her lungs.
A woman mysteriously drowned,
but not drowned.
- Precisely.
- Ever hear of dry drowning?
What is that?
The larynx involuntarily seals up
to prevent water entering.
It's rare, but it happens.
She could still have drowned,
but have no water in her lungs.
So she did drown.
Not necessarily.
You're going to say that there was
no water in that bathroom.
In fact, no running water
in the entire house.
You'll say the police found a basin
of spilled water next door.
- Only her...
- May I continue?
- Be my guest.
- You'll say they found bruises
on her neck, consistent with
her being held down in that basin.
Her body was discovered in the bathroom,
not in the next room.
[Carl] Doubtless.
She ran there before she succumbed,
fleeing three men
whose shoeprints were found.
Couldn't have said it better myself.
So, setting aside why an
honors student would be in this house,
it's a simple case of homicide.
Yes.
Only it isn't.
What is that?
Here, here, and here.
Someone's taken away the candles,
but there's wax. Black candle wax.
- It's a circle.
- Suggestive of the black arts,
occult rituals. You smell that?
[sniffs] Urine?
Incense. Someone was
burning it here last night.
Is it satanic?
No, not necessarily.
There's thousands of occult sects,
some going back to pagan times.
We don't even know how long
this candle wax has been here.
- It's not brittle.
- There's no electricity in this house.
So burnt candles
don't have to mean occult.
- Why are you staring at me?
- I'm staring at the window.
Why?
There's some kind of oil on the glass.
- What is it?
- It's a symbol.
Drawn with anointing oil.
As a part of whatever went on here.
[Carl] Hey, Jain, get a picture.
[phone rings]
- [Perri] Find something?
- [Carl] Yeah, I think so.
This.
Three horns.
A horned triskele,
or the horns of death.
Horns of death? For real?
"A powerful occult symbol,
the three horns represents
three realms of existence
and for whoever leads the ceremony,
the ability to raise
supernatural forces from them."
- Aw, man!
- Let me see that.
So, you think that they raised
some kind of supernatural force?
Not so fast.
This book also says the ritual involves
the sacrifice of virgin dwarves.
Did that happen last night as well?
All I'm saying is it has something to do
with what killed her.
Not what, who.
[man] Liza loved learning.
She made even the hardest things seem...
simple.
I'm an English major,
Liza studied astrophysics.
I could never understand
how she wrapped her mind
around all that math.
Electromagnetism, quantum mechanics,
atomic and molecular physics...
- You're a reporter?
- Carl Kolchak, with the Beacon.
Oh, thanks.
Devan Harvey, UC Standard.
It's the school paper.
It's, uh... you know.
...trying to appreciate
every inch of their beauty.
- That made her feel alive.
- [Devan] Let me get you caught up.
That's Jack Mercer.
The dead girl's boyfriend.
- I gathered that.
- Oh, reporter.
- [Mercer]...and so natural.
- [both] Yeah.
Yeah. I might like a job...
at the Beacon.
- Now?
- No, not now! Come on!
I gotta graduate first.
You know, graduate.
Maybe I'll work at the Beacon,
pay my dues,
and, uh, move on to a better paper,
like the Times.
- Good move.
- Yeah.
[Mercer]...I see how
many lives she touched.
We'll never forget you, Liza.
- It's real touching, isn't it?
- Yeah.
[laughs] Are you kidding?
- No.
- Yeah, it's sad.
[man] Good evening, everybody.
We're all here to honor
the memory of Liza Valenti.
Intellectual...
Hey, you want a tip?
Ask Jack about how Liza died.
About how ironic it is.
- What're you talking about?
- Just remember, I want a job!
[man]...accomplishments would
lead most of us to believe
- that she was here for a lifetime...
- [Perri] Jack? Jack Mercer?
Hi, I'm Perri Reed
and this is Carl Kolchak.
We're with the Beacon.
We were hoping to ask a few questions.
I don't have anything to say.
We understand that this is
a difficult time for you right now.
You were Liza's boyfriend?
Did you see her the night she died?
No. I was working late
with Professor Carr.
I am so proud to see all of you here...
You don't know what
she was doing around there
or who else might have been with her?
I wish I knew.
I was told I should ask you
about how Liza died.
- The irony of it.
- Who told you that?
She was afraid of drowning.
For her to die that way...
- I have to go...
- Jack, one more thing.
You know what that is?
What's that?
It was painted with oil on the window
of the house where Liza died.
Hey. We gotta roll.
- He seemed nervous.
- You think he's involved?
Don't you?
Reporters, Jack?
What the hell are you thinking?
It'd be more suspicious
if I didn't talk to them.
We're being watched
to see how we deal with the situation.
Situation?
Is that what Liza is now?
Of course not.
But you took a vow,
to me and to the group.
Isn't it strange that we were
trying to scare her with water,
then she ended up drowning?
None of us even knew that
until we heard the news this morning.
Yeah.
There's a lot
at stake here, Jack.
Our futures.
As "masters of the universe."
If we don't stand together...
we all fall.
Remember that.
Sure your camera's not defective?
No, it's only on these six photos,
out of sequence.
The others are clean.
- Wow, look at that.
- What?
That. It's the same in every photo.
I don't see it.
Enlarge it.
A face.
And it's screaming.
- Do you see it?
- Not really.
Well, it's right there.
It looks like it's, uh... screaming.
People see Lincoln's face
in potato chips, too.
I think it's just
some sort of camera error.
Not as far as we can tell.
Well, I think I may
have found something.
Do you have more photos
of the oily window at the house?
Yeah, sure.
[Perri] So...
I kept thinking about
how you connected the dots yesterday
and when I woke up today, it hit me.
- They're not horns, they're...
- Circles.
...halos. I don't think
this is an occult symbol.
I think it's a crest,
for the Three Society.
- What is that?
- I've heard of it.
- It's a secret society, right?
- Very exclusive, very old.
So called because they initiate
three members every year.
The school's best and brightest.
Only no one knows who they are,
or anything about them because it's...
- Secret?
- Exactly.
But there were four people
at that house the night Liza died.
Three initiates and a senior member
to supervise. That makes four, total.
So, you're saying the ritual was...
Hokum. They burn candles, they chant.
It's their tradition, probably.
As is the idea of Liza
having to face her worst fear.
- Oh, why would they do that?
- T o build trust.
You share your worst fear with them,
then they help you face it.
So, this was just some super-secret
fraternity hazing gone wrong?
Well, if I'm right, Liza's death
was probably just a terrible accident.
I'm wondering.
What?
How you knew about the crest
for the secret society.
I can't say.
- You can't say?
- No.
- You can't say?!
- You were in a secret society?
- I told you, Kolchak, I can't say.
- Was it the Three Society?
- I went to Stanford.
These societies are usually
exclusive to one school.
- So you were in another one?
- I can't tell you.
Well, then you were.
OK, fine, fine.
But why, hypothetically,
would you join a group like that?
- Why not?
- They're elitist.
Cliques for snobs
who trade on connections to get ahead.
No, they're not!
They're about friendship.
- Friendship?
- Yes.
You forge a close bond
with a small group of people
and then you swear your allegiance
to them forever.
- So... you're still a member.
- Kolchak.
- Come on!
- No!
- I only want to...
- Zip it!
OK.
Professor Carr? Carl Kolchak,
Perri Reed, the L.A. Beacon.
- Sorry, I'm late for an appointment.
- Oh, we'll walk with you.
- How well did you know Jack Mercer?
- I'm his faculty adviser.
You were also his alibi
the night Liza died.
He hardly needs one. Jack's one
of the finest students at this school.
[Carl] What were you two
doing that night?
Designing a study program to incorporate
the fellowship Jack was just awarded.
And you were Liza Valenti's
faculty adviser, too?
Yes, I was.
Have you ever heard of
something called the Three Society?
I've heard whispers about members,
like everyone else.
Hear whispers about Liza
being initiated the night she died?
The night Jack said he was with you?
- Where are you getting all this?
- We can't tell him, can we?
No.
No, we told him we wouldn't.
Jack was with me the whole evening.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
- You think you rattled him?
- I think I did.
Jack!
- You talked to those reporters?
- Just once, before...
You were sworn to deny
any affiliation with this group.
That means you don't talk.
T o anyone!
The rules of this society
come before everything.
- I didn't say anything.
- He didn't...
You didn't tell them
you and Liza were initiates?
- No.
- Well, they know.
Or at least they're acting like they do.
Maybe I should have told them.
Maybe I should have
told the police, too.
- You know what you're saying?
- He didn't mean it...
All I know is that I searched that house
looking for Liza, just like you told us.
And I didn't kill her.
You think... I killed her?
- Well, did you?
- Jack...
I won't even dignify that
with a response.
[Mercer] She told me, you know.
That you tried to sleep with her,
but she turned you down.
When you wouldn't take no for an answer,
she said she'd go to the administration.
Come on, Jack!
No, it would have jeopardized
your tenure if she had told them.
Whatever our differences,
our vow binds us together.
Forever.
You break that vow and you'll
lose everything you've ever worked for.
The Society will make sure of that.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[screams]
[Perri] Why are we
sneaking into the morgue?
I want answers about
what killed Professor Carr.
- The results haven't been released.
- We're not waiting for that.
We're not?
- I have a confidential source.
- Another source?
This should be good.
OK.
Please tell me your source is alive.
About time, man, you're killing me.
- Who's she?
- Alex Nyby, Perri Reed.
She works with me at the Beacon.
Nice. Can I talk to you?
You know, man...
my deal is with you,
not the damn Beacon.
Your deal?
My man.
You said floor seats!
- What!
- They're floor adjacent!
What do you mean, "floor adjacent"?
Wait, you've been bribing
this man with tickets?
Oh, wait, this is your source?
- What are you, an orderly?
- Pathology specialist.
- Whatever. Kolchak!
- Next time, floor seats.
Of course.
The remains of Professor Richard Carr,
pronounced dead at the scene
at 2:47 p.m.
- Whoa.
- I can't even look.
This is how you look when
every bone in your body breaks.
- A human squish toy.
- Here's the thing.
No one saw him fall.
And he left no note.
He must have jumped after we saw him.
- Unless he didn't jump.
- You think he was pushed?
- Tell her what you told me.
- Oh. The blood splatter at the scene.
- It was on a 27-foot radius.
- So?
The building they think he fell from
was only five stories.
And that kind of damage only occurs
when a guy falls 50 stories, not five.
According to you... an orderly.
A pathology... specialist!
There's no building near 50 stories
on that campus.
Exactly.
Look, Liza, with no water in her lungs,
dies of drowning, her greatest fear.
Now, Carr, with no tall buildings,
dies from a high fall.
And what if that was his greatest fear?
But I thought you agreed
that this was about
a secret society,
not about raising some occult power.
Maybe it's both.
Excuse me, um, Perri Reed, right?
Do you like basketball?
[snickers]
- [door opening]
- What?
- The corpses, right?
- [door closes]
- [Carl] Working a big story?
- Yes, I am.
Hey, guys,
what are you doing here?
- We need your help.
- Oh, really?
Are you kidding?
Remember when you told me
to ask Jack about how Liza died?
Yeah.
Well, you knew drowning
was her worst fear.
Right.
Now Professor Carr dies from a fall,
which we're guessing was his worst fear.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
- Someone's got to be behind it.
- Hmm.
And you think it's me?
How did you know drowning
was her worst fear, Devan?
- Jack and I used to be friends.
- Used to be? What happened?
Jack made it into the Three Society,
and I didn't.
You tried to get into the Three Society?
I approached Professor Carr,
but he acted like it didn't exist.
So he tapped Liza and Jack instead.
- And you got revenge.
- Me? No! No! No!
- It was Craig Boyer.
- Craig Boyer?
Yeah. Jack's new buddy.
The guy who had that bruise on his face
the day after Liza died.
Why would you say he did it?
You didn't hear?
And you guys are supposed to be
the professionals...
Hear what?
Craig was arrested.
Drug possession and suspicion of murder.
The toxicology report on Liza
found that she'd taken
a powerful, homemade
psychedelic drug.
- They think Craig gave her it?
- He's a chem major.
Apparently, he made it from chemicals
he stole from the lab.
Ones that later matched
those found in Liza's body.
At least that's what I'm writing.
It's too bad you guys
didn't get there first.
'Cause then we could work
on a story together, or something.
I phoned the coroner's office.
They won't have Carr's toxicology report
until tomorrow.
- I can't believe it.
- That we got scooped by that pipsqueak?
Yeah, that too.
But I meant the idea that Craig's drugs
killed Liza, or the professor.
It makes some sense, doesn't it?
Not if that drug was intended
to be ceremonial. An entheogen.
A what?
A hallucinogenic drug
used in a ritualistic context
to heighten the experience.
Maybe Craig didn't intend to kill them.
Maybe it was just an accident.
[Jain] Hey.
You guys gotta check this out.
These are pictures of Craig Boyer
on the way to his booking.
- Come on, Jain, not again.
- Just wait.
[Jain] Look at that.
Can you mask out the image behind it?
It's a boy.
[Carl] The question, T ony, is why
does this image keep appearing?
Couldn't it be a corrupted file,
or a double exposure of some kind?
But I changed the CCD
after the first pictures.
- Whatever. We've got the story.
- Drugs?
Craig cooked them.
Liza had them in her system
and the tox screen
will show Carr had them, too.
Look, even if he did, drugs don't
explain the damage to this man's body.
Maybe they do. Can I be you again?
- Heard of "mind over matter"?
- You mean ESP? Psychokinesis?
I was thinking of something
more tangible.
Really? That's so unlike you, Carl.
People have gone into self-induced
trances, causing injury to themselves.
Like stigmatas, spontaneously
bleeding on religious zealots?
- Exactly.
- So you're saying
Liza and Carr imagined their deaths?
The drugs Craig made are a hallucinogen.
Could have heightened the effect
- of falling off a building.
- No pun intended...
- "Heightened."
- Yeah, I suppose it could have.
But you still can't explain that.
And... neither can you.
[siren]
Why did you ask me down here, Craig?
To tell you I am not
going to take the fall for you.
For me?
They're not just talking about
drug charges, but about murder.
You made the drugs, not me.
You know that drugs
had nothing to do with this.
You think I killed Liza?
I've thought it the whole time.
When Professor Carr died,
I knew I was right.
- Why didn 't you say something?
- Because I was your friend.
That was the whole point of the society.
We were supposed to
look out for each other.
I just can 't do it anymore.
What are you talking about?
- Cutting a deal.
- To tell them what?
The truth of what happened that night.
How you really felt
about Professor Carr and Liza.
Suddenly the truth's important?
We're talking about
my future here, Jack!
I might be in jail right now,
but I am not going to prison.
Not for you, not for anybody.
You're on your own.
- Guard!
- [siren]
Anything?
No, nothing that makes sense.
You know, years ago, in Chicago,
my editor sent me out
to do some leg work
on this very important story.
The murder of a union boss.
I was just off the copy desk, it was a
big deal for me, I was nervous as hell.
But I'm knocking on doors and stopping
guys at the dock, asking questions.
And this one longshoreman
tells me he'll spill, off the record.
He fills my notebook.
I ended up writing on cardboard boxes.
What did he say?
Everybody knows it was the shipping
company but they're afraid to talk.
Busted the story wide open.
I think I'm sitting on a Pulitzer.
So? What happened?
I write the story.
My hands are shaking, I'm so excited,
and two hours before we go to print,
the cops make an arrest.
You know who they bag?
My source.
The longshoreman.
Truth was in front of me the whole time.
But I was so convinced I knew
what that story was, I got lost.
Start with certainties
and you will end up with doubt.
[sighs]
Where does your story start, Carl?
[Carl sighs]
[siren]
[hissing]
[choking]
[Perri] You hear about Craig Boyer?
Crushed mysteriously in his cell?
Yeah. And that's not all.
Coroner's report.
Professor Carr didn't have
the drugs in his system.
So the drugs don't explain these deaths.
No.
What are we missing?
Look, I went back to the beginning.
- T o where this story started.
- Liza's death?
Remember what you said? The society's
initiation is the same, every year.
And the occult stuff is just hokum.
Nothing ever happens.
- Right.
- What was different this time?
[Carl] That house.
- Who are you calling?
- Devan.
For what?
T o see if he can get his old friend Jack
to meet us back at the house...
where it all started.
- I'm here. What's this about?
- Saving your life, we hope.
- What's your worst fear, Jack?
- Just tell me how they died.
Know why the Three Society chose
this house for its initiation this year?
- I'll bet you're going to tell me.
- Because it had a history.
A history far worse than they knew.
This place made headlines
in the Beacon 1 1 years ago.
Why are you showing me this?
Your life is in danger. From whatever
killed Liza, Craig, and Professor Carr.
What is it?
It's what the four of you unleashed
that night without even knowing it.
[Carl] In 1 994,
Charles Dunmore moved his wife
and three children down from Barstow
after getting a job
at the old Figueroa brickyard...
Poor neighborhood, but a big house.
Dunmore sunk everything he had into it.
[woman on TV] Why do I always
have to be the mean one?
Why can 't you be the mean one ever?
- I can be...
- But you never are! Look...
[Carl] Not two months later
the brickyard shut down.
And so did Dunmore.
A co-worker would later say
Dunmore told him
he 'd rather see his family dead
than out on the street.
Is it any wonder pride is a sin?
He started with his daughter.
She never stood a chance.
[screaming]
His ten-year-old son woke
upon hearing his sister scream.
The boy grabbed
his little brother and ran.
- Frantic, they listened...
- [screaming]
... as their father went on
to kill their mother.
The boy was brave,
keeping his little brother quiet.
Not knowing if any second
their father would find them.
They dared not breathe.
Knowing he would find them.
Knowing they would be next.
And then... he gave up.
The weight of what he 'd done
must have taken hold.
[TV] Oh, God, what happened to you?
[Carl] The boy opened the cupboard
thinking he 'd saved his little brother.
Wake up.
Only then discovering
the terrible truth. He was too late.
[Carl] He was dead from fear.
[Devan] So, you think
that's the face in the photo?
[Carl] Dunmore's youngest son.
Literally, scared to death.
[Mercer] What is this to do
with what's happened?
Ancient folklore says that in those rare
instances when someone dies of fear,
the fear that killed them stays behind.
[Jain] Like the ghost of an emotion.
This is what you wanted to tell me?
The ghost of that little boy's fear.
I think you raised it.
Do you think it attached itself to us?
This image only appeared in pictures
that included Craig, Professor Carr...
or you.
You believe this?
Look, I don't know about ghosts, OK?
But I do know that
the mind is very powerful,
and it may only matter
that you believe it.
- You're crazy.
- We're trying to help you.
Just stay away from me.
All of you.
[door closing]
[woman on TV] I can't believe
we're having this conversation.
[man on TV] The point is...
[woman] Why do I always
have to be the mean one?
Why can 't you be the mean one
once in a while?
- [man] I can be...
- [door opening]
- Hey, guys?
- [Carl] What is it?
Well, these handprints.
Do you think these are Dunmore's kids?
- Why?
- Well, there's three of them.
Their names were kept out of the papers,
but look at these last two.
Gus...
and Jack.
Jack?
Oh my God.
Jack was adopted.
Jack Dunmore grew up
to be Jack Mercer.
That's why they chose this house.
Returning here was Jack's greatest fear.
why wouldn't he tell us?
Where are you going?
What?
[Mercer] Dad, please! No! No! No!
[father groans]
[Mercer] No! No!
It's over. It's over.
It's OK, Jack. He's not here.
He never was.
[Carl] Fueled by memory,
fear takes form.
Becoming a thing that lives
long after death.
Residing not just in our hearts,
but in the hidden bonds between us.
Fear so powerful cannot be escaped,
but it can be... destroyed.