I'm Carl Kolchak.
Perri Reed.
And this is Jain McManus.
Perri is the senior crime
reporter at this paper.
- Senior crime reporter?
- I've been here four years.
Do you know how long
I've covered crime?
The two of you
are expected to get along.
You have to wonder why he's been
so interested in this case.
A man drawn to a story
that so closely mirrors his own?
All these strange deaths,
they're like pieces in a puzzle,
a puzzle I'm trying
to put together.
But no one sees it,
because no one wants to.
And when you get your answers?
I'll print them. Then they'll
believe. Then they'll have to.
[Carl] They're in the news every day.
Warnings about what you eat.
Drink. Breathe.
Think.
In the modern world,
fear of death
isn 't a distant anxiety
reserved for old age.
It's daily life.
The ordinary
no longer offers comfort.
Not when death can come
any time... from anything.
U h, that's dangerous, you know.
Your cell phone.
Static electricity could start
a fire. L-Look behind you.
[muttering]
Some punk's sweatin' me...
[continues talking]
[whimpers] No!
[cries in pain]
[screams]
[man] Someone call 91 1!
[hubbub, voices on radio]
- Hey.
- Hey. What do you got?
- Got a story. A good one.
- A gas station fire?
Not the fire, but how it started.
I overheard a witness telling the cops
that it was another customer here.
The guy who died, Theodore Fogel.
Was he smoking?
No. He was burning up.
Literally.
A witness said that this man
Fogel's body started the fire?
- Like some kind of human torch?
- Like Johnny Storm.
- Flame on.
- Witness might have been wrong.
A hundred things
could've started this.
I don't think the fire's the story.
- You read yesterday's paper?
- Of course.
Then you saw the front page.
- The T errorMaker.
- The Unabomber-type guy, right?
Yeah, a homegrown terrorist
who sent his victims wax
figurines as calling cards.
So-called "burning men."
They all died. Burned by some
kind of biological agent.
Yeah, one that seemingly burned
his victims alive...
from the inside.
No wax burning man was found.
It could've melted in the fire.
...and the TerrorMaker's dead,
Kolchak.
How could he take a new victim
when he died a year ago?
That's what I want to know.
[telephone rings]
I'm gonna go print these out.
Have you considered
this might be a copycat?
I have.
Bu that's not the story
you're interested in?
Not really.
Before he died,
the T errorMaker denied
he burned his victims
with biological agents.
That's right.
He claimed
he could summon "hellfire".
Exactly.
Yeah, um, well, I read that,
and, crazy me, I dismissed it
as the ravings of a madman.
Well, maybe it is.
Maybe it isn't.
How long you been working here?
Uh, about two months, I guess.
In that time, I have witnessed
more freaky things
than I've seen my entire life.
Thanks.
You know why you keep
finding these things, Carl?
Because I look for them?
Because you want to find them.
Keep chasing monsters,
one day they'll be chasing you.
[woman] Howard, welcome back.
Hey, there he is.
Hey, let me take the lead
in this, OK.
I know how to handle him.
I don't want Gorn bigfooting us.
Howard Gorn covered the
T errorMaker case for ten years.
he has a six-figure book deal
about it. The story's his.
Yeah, the story was his.
Now it's ours.
- Enter.
- Carl Kolchak, Mr. Gorn.
Yeah, I've heard about you.
Perri, how's the crime beat?
- Keeping you busy?
- Yeah, it's fine.
You know,
I started out covering crime.
The first Pulitzer
was for the Manson thing.
I got in tight with Bugliosi
and Polanski and all those guys.
Crime is a great beat for
beginners. The public loves it.
Right.
So, what is it you need from me,
sweetheart?
Yes, "sweetheart."
Why don't you tell Mr. Gorn?
Well, I hate to bother you,
but we were having an argument.
- About?
- Your story you wrote yesterday
talked about rumors that the FBl
killed the wrong man.
That the real T errorMaker's
still alive.
- Yeah, and so is Elvis.
- [chuckles]
You're convinced this suspect,
Robert Guttman, was guilty?
Look, it'll all be covered
in my book.
It was just bad luck, that's all.
The raid went bad when
a tear gas canister ignited,
incinerating Guttman
and his wife, Margaret.
So there was no suspect to question.
And no smoking gun.
The biological agents
he used to burn his victims,
- they were never found?
- No.
Presumably, he stole them
from some DOD lab he worked at.
And the theory is that they were
transmitted by the figurines
he sent to his victims.
So simply touching a figurine
caused them to burn up?
Within seconds.
Poof! You're dead.
- That was the theory.
- Yeah, right.
The biological agents
disappear without a trace.
There's no hard proof,
you get rumors, conspiracy nuts.
Good thing about rumors
is they help sell books.
Hmm. What about
the T errorMaker's letters,
claiming he killed these people
with "hellfire"?
What about it?
Did you ever consider
they might be true?
Oh, you mean that God gave him
the power to scorch human flesh?
No.
This guy, Perri,
he's a piece of work.
Your article also talked about
an FBl profiler, Doug Panero.
Yeah.
Is he convinced
Guttman was guilty, too?
I suppose so. It was his profile
they were working off.
But Panero's not talking, so...
Why not?
Listen, these, uh,
these questions...
Are they a part of this argument
that you two are having?
No, no, we just got
a little carried away.
Thank you for settling our
debate, Howard. Appreciate it.
- Anytime, sweetheart.
- It's been an education.
Right.
[knocking]
Mrs. Panero? Hi, I'm Perri Reed.
This is Carl Kolchak.
We're with the Beacon.
Oh, I'm sorry, my husband
doesn't give interviews.
We don't need to talk to Agent Panero.
If he could just look at this.
What is it?
It's the file of a man who
was burned to death last night.
We were hoping your husband
could tell us
if he fits the profile
of a T errorMaker victim.
He was the FBl agent
in charge of the case.
But the T errorMaker's dead.
Thanks to my husband.
Yes, we understand that.
If he could just take a look at this.
Our number's inside. Thanks.
That's the last one.
T en years this guy's
been killing people.
There's got to be more research
in these files.
There is. It's Gorn's story.
Most of it's up in his office.
Yeah. For his book.
When you get to be as famous
as he is, paper gives you latitude.
Yeah, well, that latitude's
keeping us from finding out
how this T errorMaker
burns these people.
It's already been explained.
A classified biological agent
that leaves no trace or residue?
- Right.
- So top secret
that no one's
ever proven it even exists?
Doesn't mean it doesn't.
What,
just because it wasn't found
doesn't mean it doesn't exist?
Where have I heard that before?
OK. Let's say there never were
any biological agents.
He burned these people
with "hellfire"?
The T errorMaker claimed
that biblical wrath was on his side.
That these bioweapons
were offensive to God.
- And that makes sense to you?
- I'm only saying,
admit that there may be more
to this world
than reason alone can explain.
Reason's all we have.
And if it's not enough?
- [rustling, rattling]
- What was that?
[gasps]
You haven't shown this to the FBl?
Not yet.
So, we don't know if it's authentic?
- It could just be a hoax.
- It may be.
Or it could be that the FBl
killed the wrong guy a year ago
and the T errorMaker's back.
"I'm Back" is written in the same
blood-red ink he used in the past.
So, why send it here?
Maybe he saw us at the gas
station asking questions.
That is
the "real-world" explanation.
That's where I live.
It's the explanation I'm looking for.
There could be others.
What does Howard Gorn
think about all this?
- We haven't told him.
- And why not?
Because this is our story.
Jain found it.
T ony, it does not seem fair
to just hand it over to him.
Howard Gorn is on the national desk.
He outranks all of us.
But we're the ones
who put it together.
You haven't put anything together.
You don't know this is authentic.
You don't even know if the victim
fits this lunatic's profile.
So, until you do...
I don't see any reason to waste
Howard Gorn's time with this.
Thanks for cutting us
some slack, T ony.
Try not to hang yourself with it.
The FBl's position on this
is that it's a fake.
- Well, how can you be so sure?
- The T errorMaker's dead.
This has got to be a copycat
of some kind.
Unless you're wrong, Agent Houck.
We've all heard the rumors,
but Guttman fits the Bureau's
profile to a "T"
and the attacks stopped after his death.
Did you hear about
the gas station explosion?
- Yeah, I heard about it.
- Don't think it's connected?
- No, there's no evidence it is.
- What does Doug Panero think?
Howard Gorn covered this story
for the Beacon for ten years.
Why aren't I talking to him?
Well,
Howard's the reason we're here.
All right, I'll have Quantico
take a look. I'll let you know.
- [Jain] He's here.
- Who?
That, uh, FBl agent
you wanted to see.
- Doug Panero?
- Yes. I had him wait in Photo
so that Gorn wouldn't see him.
Agent Panero?
I wanted to get back to you.
T o tell you that I checked out
the man in this file.
Was he someone the T errorMaker
would target for death?
Every victim had some connection
to biological weapons research,
which he claimed to oppose
on moral grounds.
I compiled a list of over 7,000
people that fit his criteria.
This victim at the gas station
was doing bioengineering
research at CSU,
research the T errorMaker
would've clearly found unacceptable.
You think he's alive?
The T errorMaker?
I didn't say that.
I said the victim fit his profile.
But we received
a burning man figure last night
wrapped in paper,
with the words "I'm back".
- May I see it?
- We just gave it to the FBl.
- They're analyzing it.
- Then I can't help you.
Except to say it's plausible
T errorMaker would have sent
a burning man to the press
to spread fear.
Agent Panero...
why did you come here today?
Because you asked for my opinion.
It's our understanding
that you haven't spoken to anyone
in the press since the raid.
The raid was a black mark
on the Bureau.
Questions were raised
about loss of innocent life.
Guttman's wife.
Even whether or not
Guttman was guilty.
The whole episode has made me
persona non grata at the Bureau.
But you still work there.
Not really. I don't go to the office.
I-I still don't understand though
why you came to us
instead of the FBl.
Because if T errorMaker's still alive,
if we did kill the wrong man,
I want people to know about it.
And your old boss? Agent Houck?
Let's just say the FBl
doesn't need any more headlines.
I'll, uh, I'll show you out.
I thought you'd be excited.
Sounds like we have a story.
Yeah.
What is it?
He's still got it in his eyes. Fear.
[rock music plays]
[doorbell]
It's been an hour and a half.
- Sorry. Traffic.
- Yeah, right.
Thank you.
Food's here.
- Who's hungry?
- Come on and eat.
What's this, the toy surprise?
Susan?
- Oh, God!
- [laughs]
Don't do that!
You scared the crap out of me!
[woman mock-screams]
- Gary?
- What now?
- Are you OK?
- I'm fine.
No. I mean it.
What's happening?
What's happening to me?
I'll get help!
[agonized screams]
Just got confirmation from LAPD.
- A burning man?
- Found on the patio table.
Think it got delivered
with the take-out dinner.
How did it get in there?
Same way as with
all the other victims.
- Which is?
- Nobody knows.
- You reach Panero?
- Not yet,
but the victim's
gotta be on the list.
He was an executive at a biotech
company in Manhattan Beach.
I'll see if I can get a picture
from personnel.
You want to work the phones
or start writing?
You write it.
I'll get you my notes.
I'll, uh, I'll take those notes.
The FBl called,
it's... my story.
[noise of traffic outside]
- Howard.
- I'm on deadline, T ony.
The story's theirs.
You're out of your bailiwick here.
This story belongs to national,
not to city desk.
They found it. They chased it.
They also pumped me pretty good
for information about it,
and they still don't even know
what "it" is.
The T errorMaker's back.
T onight's attack proved it.
You see what I mean?
Well, why don't you tell us then?
You can read all about it
in tomorrow's Beacon.
Well, you mean what your pals
at the FBl tell you to write?
That it's nothing but a copycat?
This is the figurine
you wanted the FBl to analyze.
The other... is from an attack
that took place two years ago.
They look the same.
Well, they're not.
The FBl says the wax is
different and so is the mold.
This one is a fake.
It's a copycat.
And I don't write
what the FBl tells me to write.
I write the simple truth.
Like I always do.
Now I'll take those notes
from you now...
if there's anything in them
worth reading.
[knocking]
Good morning.
Is your husband in?
What do you want?
Did you read the news
this morning?
I read it.
I need his help.
He's done helping, Mr. Kolchak.
You should call the FBl.
- People are dying.
- Listen to me.
My husband has helped enough.
For ten years he's chased
that monster. He's paid enough.
- It's OK, Lisa.
- Doug...
It's all right.
What is it that you need,
Mr. Kolchak?
Answers.
This is where it all happened.
Where I hunted the man down.
Lisa wants me to move past all this.
But you can't.
All those years chasing a phantom,
imagining his every move.
I never met the man,
but I got to know him better
than my friends and my family.
The day that Guttman died,
it was like my life ended, too.
The FBl didn't need
or want me anymore.
You read about the death last night?
The biotech exec? The FBl thinks
he was killed by a copycat.
But you don't believe that.
Why do you say that?
It doesn't fit with your theory
about the agent
the T errorMaker used to kill.
Well, I've seen the research.
Our government's working
on all kinds of killer germs.
Biological warfare,
it's the new combat.
But you theorized
that Guttman stole them
from a lab where he worked.
Yeah, that's right.
So, if that were true,
how would a copycat get
this same biological agent?
I don't know.
It seems next to impossible.
- What if it isn't a copycat?
- What are you talking about?
Maybe Guttman was the wrong guy.
He fit the profile.
And he worked at a lab
where he had access
to biological agents.
That's based on the assumption
that he killed these people
with a biological agent.
So what? Your saying he burned
them with "hellfire"?
You've got to be joking.
You want to put this case
behind you.
Let me help you do that,
once and for all.
- [telephone]
- [Perri] Where you been?
Why are you asking?
You still working on the story?
Who wants to know? You or Gorn?
Vincenzo. He got called into the
managing editor's office this morning.
Ooh, he got his hand slapped?
We all did.
Jain can stay on the story,
but if either of us
steps on Gorn's turf again,
we'll be fired.
Uh, they're bluffing.
They don't trust us, Carl.
They don't think we know how
to do our jobs. Not like Gorn does.
We're the only ones trying
to write this story. The real story.
They don't care.
They want us to let it go.
Well, I care.
I'll take my chances.
You can't do that.
Vincenzo is being
held personally responsible.
That's his problem, not mine.
He got you this job, Carl.
You cross the line again,
it'll cost him his.
You need to back off.
- [man] Freeze!
- [siren]
[shouting, tires screech]
Right down!
Turn him around! Now.
[officer] Come on, get up.
A little lower.
Glenn Overton,
formerly employed as a driver
- for a high-risk trucking firm.
- Trucking?
He transported biohazardous
materials for the government.
Now how'd the FBl
find him so quickly?
According to Gorn,
Overton was on the Bureau's
terrorist watch list.
They'd tracked him all along.
Yeah, they took us
back to his room.
He had, like,
a dozen figurines there,
wax molds, the whole deal.
Well, what about
this traceless biological agent?
There was something there.
They made sure I got a picture of it.
It's being analyzed at Quantico.
I hate to be the one to say it...
- Then don't.
- [telephone]
- Kolchak.
- It's Doug Panero.
What kind of crap is this?
You said you wanted answers.
Slow down,
what are you talking about?
The story in the Beacon.
Glenn Overton.
You got to be kidding me!
The FBl says he's the copycat.
They even have proof to back it up.
Overton was on my suspect list
for years.
He's a kook, a pretender.
He couldn 't burn a match.
Well, they found
the figurines in his room,
- the wax molds, the...
- So did I. Four years ago.
They're putting away
a terrorist wannabe
when you and I both know
the real guy is still out there.
I'm off the story, Doug.
I can connect you
to Howard Gorn.
Gorn 's a tool in the Bureau.
I'm not talking to him, Kolchak.
I'm talking to you.
I-l-I can't help you.
You let this story stand,
more people are gonna end up dead.
You're telling me
you're OK with that?
[man on telephone] Let me know
when you get a release on it.
- l' ll call you back.
- All right.
Kolchak!
Carl! Where are you going?
I'd prefer not to say.
T ell me you're not working
on this story.
- OK. I'm not.
- Carl.
Look, Panero says
Gorn's story is a fraud.
- Then let him tell Gorn that.
- He doesn't trust Gorn.
Oh, so he's talking to you now?
Where are you going to print it?
That's right. I forgot.
You don't care about the Beacon,
just about
getting the story for yourself.
What I care about
is getting the story right,
which you once told
me you cared about, too.
[Gorn] Perri!
I, uh, I just wanted to say
that, uh, despite everything,
there's no hard feelings.
Oh, of course, no hard feelings.
I never like to leave
a pretty lady mad at me.
Right.
And, uh, about the way
you tried to work me...
- I am so sorry about that.
- No, don't be, don't be.
I admire that.
Manipulation is an essential
quality in a good reporter.
As for your friend Kolchak,
here...
Uh, may I offer you
a bit of advice?
Be my guest.
He's a fanatic,
driven by obsessions.
Even if he wasn't crazy...
he's the kind of guy who will
just drag you down. Huh?
- Thanks for your advice.
- Any time.
- Hey, Howard.
- Hmm?
You know, I know this is your
story, but I was wondering if...
if I could help? You know,
with research, calls, anything?
I, I wouldn't expect
to share a byline.
But just a chance to learn.
Why don't you let me think about it.
Thanks.
[elevator bell dings]
This is my file on Overton,
categorically dismissing him
as a suspect.
They caught him red-handed,
Ieaving a burning man
in someone's car.
Yeah, "someone." Who?
They haven't released a name.
I guarantee you, whoever it is,
he was not on
the T errorMaker's target list.
You think he's
still alive... this T errorMaker.
Lisa used to think it was just me.
That I couldn't accept
that it was over.
But I'm sure now... it's not.
Well, well, well, look at this.
I was just doing a little organizing.
Your book research is here,
your outgoing stories are over there.
Why don't we go get a drink, huh?
I was just going to stick around here
and get things in shape for tomorrow.
Well... all right.
You know, Howard,
I was wondering what was in this
bottom drawer. It's locked.
You don't need
to worry about that.
See you tomorrow.
- Have you seen Kolchak?
- No, why?
I haven't been able
to reach him all day.
- Think he's working on the story?
- I know he is.
He's not the only one.
What are those?
Oh, Gorn's files. For his book.
Ones he kept out
of the research library.
They left me with some questions.
About what?
This so-called
"traceless" biological agent.
Look, two instances
of people burning up
without ever having received
a figurine.
Here, a case of a Wisconsin man
who touched the burning man,
didn't burn up.
These discrepancies
have never been disclosed
or explained by the FBl
or Panero.
So you think that their theory
about this pathogen is...
Oh, God, it's weak at best.
Gorn is going right along with it,
just spouting the company line.
In exchange for access to the FBl.
- No doubt.
- Why would the FBl lie?
You know, why would Panero lie?
They're not. It...
It's the only rational explanation
they could come up with.
You're not saying that you
believe that the T errorMaker
killed these people with... "hellfire"?
Do I look crazy to you? Huh?
I'm just saying
that the scientific explanation
for these attacks... doesn't add up.
Doesn't add up at all.
Guttman kept taking
the same toll road.
91 west to the Five.
Every month. Where was he going?
I don't know. I don't know
that it means anything.
Well, it says here he kept
a locker in Bellflower.
Just off the 91 Freeway, isn't it?
I was thinking the same thing,
but I checked it out after he died.
The locker was empty.
I'm telling you, it's a dead end.
I haven't seen your wife tonight.
She took a drive.
She's not happy
you're back into all this, huh?
She wants our life back.
Whatever that is.
It's been so long,
I don't even know anymore.
I get these pictures in my head
and I keep thinking
if I could put them together,
I can leave this all behind.
I could move on.
You understand
what I'm talking about?
Yeah. I do.
Did Guttman have any relatives?
No. Why?
That storage locker in Bellflower.
Someone's been paying
to keep it open this past year.
Nineteen.
It's not locked.
- [Kolchak] It's not empty, either.
- No.
- Did you touch one?
- Is it the real thing?
- Sure looks like it.
There's wax molds. Paraffin.
[exhales loudly]
Look at this.
I think we just found your "hellfire."
It's a hell of a story, isn't it?
Yeah. Writing it for the Beacon
is another matter.
The FBl is not going
to be able to deny this now.
This is proof the T errorMaker
is still at work.
Guttman was a loner.
Only a certain amount of people
he knew could have access to the locker.
I already know who had access.
What are you talking about?
I've seen this ink before, Doug.
On the paper the T errorMaker
wrote, that said "I'm back."
That note?
No one else knew
we were on the story.
It's you.
You're the T errorMaker now.
Are you crazy?
You couldn't accept Guttman
was dead.
So you brought him back.
You hid what we found
in that storage locker
because if you hadn't, questions
about this case would have stopped.
And your life would have been over.
You're saying I killed these people.
You had the list
of the T errorMaker's victims.
You knew just who to target, and how.
You're lying.
I wish I was.
I'm the one who found him.
He found you.
You spent so long
looking for answers.
When you found them,
you lost yourself.
No! I can't let you say these things.
Doug.
It's true, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- Doug!
- [sizzling]
No!
You seen this?
- Yeah, I've seen it.
- It's completely bogus.
The FBl's got it all wrong,
Gorn's reporting it as fact.
Vincenzo wants to see us. Now.
Gorn is a total fraud.
He ought to be fired.
We'll back you up on this, T ony.
That won't be necessary.
I'm letting the story stand.
[Perri] The story's wrong.
That guy Overton didn't kill Panero
or any of these other people.
This copycat was knee-deep
in stolen biohazardous materials.
The FBl has a solid case against him.
I can't believe
you're going along with this.
He is. We all are.
You were there.
You saw how Panero died.
He touched a burning man
from that storage locker!
Yeah, that's how he died.
But that's not what killed him.
Panero spent ten years
trying to catch a monster.
I think the monster finally caught him.
? Out of my head again
? Into the fire
? Faithless until the end
[Carl] Doug Panero lived
with a fear, he finally came to see.
A fear I know too well.
Of a question
that holds a terrible answer.
Should I ever look into the eye
of the monster I'm chasing?
Whose face would I see?
[unearthly sounds]