Agent Fain. What do you want me to see?
This is where Kolchak killed his wife.
That's not his story.
Convenient, killing his wife,
leaving him alive.
Look at her left hand.
She didn't have it before she died.
Why kill that woman and take that girl?
Why kill your wife and why not you?
You have to wonder why he's been
so interested in this case.
Why a man would be drawn
to a story that mirrors his own?
All these strange deaths,
they're like pieces in a puzzle.
- A puzzle I'm trying to put together.
- And when you get your answers?
I'll print them.
Then they'll believe. They'll have to.
[Carl] Before time, before light,
before life itself,
they say the Earth was formless, empty.
And darkness was over
the surface of the deep.
That darkness hovers there still.
Eternity whispering
in the crash of the waves.
Mysteries about who we are
and where we come from.
We suffer, we toil,
we live and die,
never knowing
why we 're born into this life.
Whether it's to serve good...
or evil.
[al I speak Lati n S pan ish]
[approaching engines]
[motorbike engines]
[pained cry]
[engines revving]
- [elevator chime]
- [door opens]
- Great story, Carl.
- Thank you.
Any word yet on who killed these men?
No, not much to go on, other than
the tracks they left at the scene.
This missing witness?
They have my description,
like, he was wounded, so...
I have to say, I was a bit surprised.
- Why's that?
- The death of a drug lord
is a big story, but it's straight crime.
You know, there's nothing...
"woo-ooh" about it.
Nothing "woo-ooh". Ha!
Just wouldn't expect
it to grab your attention.
- Carl, are you OK?
- Uh, yeah, I'm fine.
Ms. Perri Reed from the L.A. Beacon.
- Agent Fain.
- How you been, Ms. Reed?
If you're looking for Kolchak,
you just missed him.
I'm not.
I'm looking for T ony Vincenzo.
Bernie!
Guess I found him.
What the hell is going on?
- Oh! Nice digs.
- Thanks.
I always knew that you'd make good
in the big city.
- Congratulations, you deserve it.
- How's the FBl treating you?
No shortage of bad guys out there.
Which is, uh, why I called.
This story that Kolchak
had in the morning paper...
The drug cartel executions?
I don't need to say
how I feel about Kolchak.
- No.
- He's a hell of a reporter,
- I give him that. Damn good story.
- What's it got to do with you?
Uh, a joint FBl-DEA task force was
created last night to look into this.
- We'd like your cooperation.
- You'd like our cooperation?
These deaths completely blind-sided us.
Until he turned up dead last night,
this cartel chief, Felix Morales,
we didn't even know
he'd crossed the border.
So, what makes you think
Kolchak could help?
He got there before the cops did.
Obviously, he's got some
kind of inside information.
A source tipped him off.
We're willing to play ball.
Give the Beacon exclusives
all the way on this thing.
I suspect Carl will be reluctant
to work with you
as you're trying to put him away
for his wife's death.
That's why I came to you.
He didn't kill lrene, Bernie.
Let's agree to disagree on that,
OK, T ony?
Well,
whatever's between Kolchak and me...
this man he saw running away last night
can lD those shooters
and we need to find him, before they do.
[banging]
[creaking]
That's all you're asking me to do?
That's everything.
- Just do this...
- No!
Carl!
- Carl? What's wrong?
- I need my keys.
- What's going on?
- I'm getting stabbed in the back.
Because of Agent Fain?
What do you know about that?
- I saw him.
- When?
After you left. Looking for Vincenzo.
Vincenzo wants me to cooperate.
T o share information
so they can find this missing witness.
- What's Fain offering?
- Oh, what does it matter?
- He just wants to get to him before me.
- What, that witness?
Where are my damn keys?
Right here.
Carl, where are you going?
I'm just trying to help here, OK?
I don't want your help.
- [knocks]
- Hey.
You took pictures at that crime scene
last night with Kolchak, right?
Yeah.
- So, what happened?
- Why do you ask?
Because Kolchak's been acting crazy.
Crazier than usual, anyway.
Yeah, he was acting
kind of weird last night, too.
You have any idea
how he got onto this story?
No, but I can tell you this.
He wasn't expecting
to find those bodies.
Didn't even know who they were
until the cops lD'd them.
- Then what was he doing there?
- Looking for that witness.
The one that got away.
- He had a description of him.
- He doesn't know who he is.
- Why would he look for him?
- He didn't tell me,
but I think I'm beginning
to have an idea.
I'm listening.
Kolchak acts strange
and then Fain shows up,
Iooking for the same guy
that Kolchak's trying to find?
This story's not about
who killed the drug lord,
it's about what killed Kolchak's wife.
I'm still afraid.
[screams]
[Carl] I need you to jump...
[girl yells]
[screaming]
- [eerie whooshing]
- [screaming]
Emily Gale was pregnant.
That's why they think he killed her.
- [Carl] That's my wife.
- Carl!
- [Carl] She had a secret.
- She was pregnant.
They tore the fetus from her body.
Were you aware Kolchak claims
some sort of beast killed his wife
and that a judge ordered him
held for psychiatric evaluation?
This just came over the police wire.
- What is it?
- A trucker picked up a hitchhiker
matching the description of Kolchak's
witness last night.
Dropped him off near Koreatown.
But they don't know it's him.
All they have is Kolchak's description.
Right. However he got that.
Your idea that this man
has something to do with Kolchak's wife
doesn't jibe with what he's always said.
- That something not human killed her?
- How do bikers killing a drug lord
- relate to that?
- I don't know.
I think it does... somehow.
Unless there's some other explanation.
Well, what's that?
Kolchak spent six months in a psych ward
after his wife died.
Yeah, so?
You said yourself
he's been acting weird.
What? You think he's cracking up?
What's Agent Fain doing here then?
Coincidence?
Maybe just investigating this case,
like he said.
But somebody told Kolchak,
not you, not any other reporter,
to go to that house last night.
T o look for this man.
Then we need to find him.
Find out why.
[police radio]
[Korean]
Linda.
[phone rings]
- Hello?
- [man] You were too late last night.
- I went soon as you called.
- You missed your chance.
You told me to come here.
That you'd be here.
If you have any questions
about the story, you'd better ask them.
- We don't have much time.
- Let's start with who you are.
A friend. Someone just like you.
Someone trying to help.
Well, friend, I'd showed up
at that house five minutes earlier,
I'd be dead right now, too.
This man I sent you to find
narrowly escaped.
Next time he won't be so lucky.
Yeah, but escaped who?
Who killed that drug lord?
Not who, what.
It was four men.
They found tracks
from their motorcycles.
You of all people should know
what the police find means nothing.
[sighs] You told me this man could help
me find what killed my wife.
They're after him for the same reason
they were after you
the night your wife died.
- And why is that?
- You have a role to play.
You know that.
I don't know what you' re talking about.
I don 't have to tell you. It's on your
left wrist, hidden by your watch.
The mark.
- How do you know about that?
- You need to find him.
How do you know?
Find him and you'll get your answers.
- I don't even know who he is!
- I do.
Thank you.
- Vincenzo's not here.
- I came to see you.
About?
Kolchak won't cooperate
with our investigation.
He won't cooperate with you.
I was hoping T ony could persuade him
otherwise.
You know, it is a win-win
for the Beacon and the Bureau.
If you think you're gonna get to Kolchak
through me, you're wasting your time.
You've already written this story
in your head, haven't you, Ms. Reed?
It's Les Misérables.
I'm lnspector Javert and Kolchak
is poor, persecuted Valjean...
- Something like that, yeah.
- Only...
you don't know... what you don't know.
Perri? What's going on?
- It's nothing, Carl...
- I asked her, not you.
- Uh, just stay cool.
- Carl, it's...
- Trying to stab me in the back again?
- I'm not the one who cut his wife...
[Perri] Carl!
- Kolchak! Stop!
- [Tony] That's enough!
It's over!
- You wanted to see me?
- Yeah, come in, please.
Carl's got another exclusive
on these drug cartel killings.
That's great.
Turns out that our missing witness
is an undercover DEA agent,
name of Victor Caleca.
Until that night,
he'd been AWOL for two weeks.
Fain knew this man was DEA.
That's why he formed this task force.
The suspicion is that
Agent Caleca is corrupt
and in the employ of the drug
lord who was killed that night.
- That's the suspicion?
- DEA isn't confirming it,
but this story's going to have legs.
So I want you to team with Carl.
T ony, the story's his...
That's is the only way he's going to
keep it after that outburst yesterday.
Lucky Fain isn't pressing charges.
I see.
We done here?
Yeah, you can go.
- He doesn't want me on this story...
- It's not about him.
The FBl is pressing the matter
of Kolchak's source.
They're prepared to go to court to force
disclosure. If that happens,
I need to know that you are there
to protect this paper.
Good morning.
I found this shirt in the back.
Mine was kinda ruined.
I hope it's OK.
Yes.
Oh, you need to sit.
I'm OK. I'm bandaged pretty tight.
I, uh, I want to thank you
for taking care of me
and for not calling the police.
My English is not so good.
But you understand "thank you"?
- Thank you.
- Yes. You're welcome.
Listen, um...
I was just wondering...
I can't leave. Not just yet.
Would it be OK if I stay here a little?
I can help you...
Yes. Stay.
Yes.
- Thanks for coming.
- You said it was important.
I'm embarrassed about
my behavior with Kolchak.
- I shouldn't have baited him.
- That's not why you wanted to see me.
No. The Justice Department
is filing suit against the Beacon,
compelling Kolchak to reveal his source.
- He won't. You know that.
- I was hoping there was another way.
Using me?
I know you feel disloyal, you shouldn't.
Yeah, so you keep saying.
You know how far back Kolchak and I go?
The Freemar graft case,
the one that made his career and T ony's.
Guess who his source was?
You?
We used to be pretty tight, me and Carl.
The night lrene died,
I went to the station as Carl's friend.
And the weirder his story got,
the more I realized
that he didn't deserve my friendship.
- He killed her.
- No. I don't believe that.
I didn't want to either.
They had marital problems.
- He had a motive.
- What motive?
Kolchak inherited a lot of money
when lrene died.
- You didn't know that, did you?
- It doesn't make him guilty.
You believe his story.
[Fain] I think Kolchak has to believe
there's something strange going on.
He needs to believe it so badly,
he's cooked up this cockamamie theory
about marks on people's wrists.
All so that he doesn't have to admit...
he killed the woman he loved.
But she did have that mark on her wrist.
Which proves what?
The more you play into his delusions,
the more you enable him.
Let's forget that, OK? Let's just say...
I'm an overworked, underpaid
civil servant trying hard
to find a missing DEA agent
before the bad guys do.
I could really use your help.
Making any headway
locating this DEA agent?
I got feelers out at the LAPD,
County Sheriffs.
No luck so far.
You can report that to Agent Fain.
- Kolchak...
- That is who you went to see?
- You're paranoid.
- And you're denying it?
I'm on your side. Even though
you might be forgetting that right now.
Are you?
Or are you wondering again
whether I deserve to be trusted?
That picture.
That your husband?
Where is he?
[Dae coughs]
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to pry.
Finished.
Thank you.
What is... this?
Something very important.
Like that picture is to you.
This is very important to me.
[? blues]
Richard Walton?
Perri Reed, Jain McManus,
from the Los Angeles Beacon.
Reporters? You got to be kidding me.
You're Victor Caleca's supervisor,
right? The missing DEA agent?
- How'd you find me?
- A lot of DEA agents come here.
And your personnel photo's online.
Damn lnternet. Ruining the world.
I don't suppose you know where he is?
Well, that's the $64,000 question,
isn't it?
Questions are being asked about Caleca.
Why he was in that house
with a bag of money.
Why he's on the run now.
You mean was Victor dirty?
That's what you're asking?
Yes. It is.
You got the story all backwards,
you know that?
- Straighten it out for us.
- I would if I could.
Off the record, then.
Off the record?
Off the record,
- Vic's the victim here, not the perp.
- What do you mean?
Three weeks ago,
he's driving home with his wife,
and they get caught in this storm.
A storm?
They pull over to the side of the road,
and wham!
Something slams into 'em.
Linda never had a chance.
- Was she killed?
- They dragged her body away.
She still hasn't been found.
- Did he see what it was?
- You mean who it was?
Vic never did.
Now, I don't mean to be rude,
I got drinking to do.
? I think it's so groovy now
? That people are finally
getting together
? I think it's wonderful and how
? That people are finally
getting together
? I think it's so groovy now
? That people are finally
getting together
? I think it's wonderful and how
? That people are finally
getting together
? Reach out in the darkness
? And you may find a friend
? I think it's so groovy now
? That people are finally
getting together
? I think it's wonderful and how
? That people are finally
getting together
? I think it's so groovy now
? That people are finally
getting together
? I think it's wonderful and how
? That people are finally
getting together...
[helicopter]
Hello.
You wanted to see me?
- You lied to me.
- What are you talking about?
I spoke to that missing DEA agent's
supervisor last night.
- You spoke to him?
- He said something attacked Caleca
- and killed his wife.
- Oh, brother.
I think Kolchak's source told him
Caleca could give him answers
about what killed his wife.
- He what?
- The same thing killed their wives.
I gather that you told all this
to Kolchak.
No, not yet.
Good.
Because we know who killed
Agent Caleca's wife.
- Who?
- The cartel. Felix Morales.
The late Felix Morales.
We think Caleca was on the take.
He did something to cross Morales,
so the order was given.
Why would he go meet with the man
that killed his wife?
T o bargain for his own life.
It just didn't work out that way.
This isn't just about
a dirty DEA agent anymore.
This is about whoever killed
that drug lord and shot Agent Walton.
- Agent Walton was shot?
- Last night.
By the looks of it, it's the same bikers
who killed that drug lord.
How is he?
We don't know.
There's his blood... quite a lot of it.
No body. Not yet.
[phone rings]
- It's about time.
- I couldn't call before.
Look, no one can find this DEA agent.
- You have to.
- Why?
- What's he going to tell me?
- I told you before.
Answer the questions he's asking,
you'll answer your own.
- I need to see you.
- That's not possible.
The Justice Department's after me.
I need to know who you are.
- I'm sorry. I can't help you.
- I need answers!
- We won't be speaking again.
- [line goes dead]
- Agent Walton.
- Dick?
- Victor?
- Is this a good time to talk?
Where are you?
Are you OK? You sound strange.
The question is are you OK?
I've been worried to death.
I'm OK. I'm someplace safe.
The feebies are all over this. Tell me
where you are and I'll bring you in.
No. Not just yet.
Reporters came asking questions
last night.
I don 't know the story
you want me to tell anymore.
T ell me who those guys were.
Those bikers.
I don 't know. I hoped you knew.
I don't think it was the cartel anymore,
Dick. It was them.
They're the ones
who came after Linda and me that night.
- Why would they do that?
- I need you to find out.
- Victor...
- I'll call you later.
What's this?
The story.
I'm supposed to be working on it
with you, remember?
I'd say congratulations,
except I have a pretty good idea
who your source was.
Carl! Perri!
I wanna see both of you, now.
- What's going on?
- Who's your source?
The one who got you on this story.
You think I'd answer
that question for him?
It's not a question anymore, Carl.
It's an order.
The District Court
ruled against the Beacon.
- Well, then we'll appeal.
- No, we won't.
- Why not?
- The decision has been made.
- By who?
- Our parent company.
The Crossbinder board
has decided to comply.
Oh, they've decided?
I'm the reporter here.
I don't like it myself, but they own
this paper. It is their prerogative.
- And if I refuse?
- You go to prison.
[speaking Korean]
[Dae speaks Korean]
There's something she needs to tell you.
[speaks Korean]
Needs you to understand.
After her husband died,
she grieved and she worried.
[speaks Korean]
She doesn't know how to run a store.
She's losing money.
Her sister and mother count on her
to send money home.
[speaks Korean]
I come to see her.
I make good money as a doctor.
I want to marry her,
but she does not love me.
[speaks Korean]
She thinks maybe this is her fate.
T o marry without love.
[speaks Korean]
And then one night she has a dream.
And the dream says
a man will come to her in need.
She will help that man.
She will open her heart to him and...
she will find peace.
[speaks Korean]
When she saw you,
when she felt your breath
against her cheek,
she knew that man was you.
Now, if you go,
she fears this dream will be a lie.
If you must go, go.
But if you want to stay,
if that is in your heart...
she wants you to know...
it is in hers.
I...
I can't.
I'm sorry.
This is Edhead. Techie I told you about.
- Edhead?
- You got a problem with that?
- You didn't tell anyone else?
- I swear.
What do you think this phone's
going to lead to? Plutonium?
- What did you find?
- Nothing.
I thought she was good.
- She's the best...
- I'm damn good.
This phone doesn't show any calls
received. It's never been activated.
Well, that's not possible.
I got two calls on that phone.
Well, the only other explanation
is that maybe you just zeroed the memory
when you busted it.
What about the phone itself?
Paid for in cash at a shop in Hollywood.
So you say you're good?
That's what I said, and I don't lie.
I'm trying to locate this missing
DEA agent, Victor Caleca.
Yeah, Jain told me.
- How would you find him?
- You mean... electronically?
Cell phone, credit card,
lnternet and e-mail activity.
- Can you find him?
- Give me some time.
- That I don't have.
- [door opening]
[Jain] Perri, hey.
This is my friend, Edhead.
The one I told you about.
- Hey.
- How you doing?
Can I see you for a minute?
I wanted to let you know
we got a petition together,
signed by the staff,
supporting your decision.
- What decision?
- T o protect your source.
T o go to prison
rather than revealing it.
- Don't bother.
- W-w-wait. Why not?
- I'm not trying to protect him.
- Then what are you doing?
- You don't know his name.
- The information was good...
Do you know how reckless that is?
You don't even know who this guy is,
- or how he might be using you.
- That's my call.
Fain was right.
I don't know who you are, Carl.
I really don't.
- Agent Walton.
- You're alive.
And kicking.
- Thank God. The paper said...
- I know what it said.
Just tell me where you are.
Victor, tell me where you are
so I can get you out of there.
Koreatown.
[elevator chime]
- We got something.
- Hate to say I told you so...
- What is it?
- It wasn't easy, so I expect payback.
Those men are coming to take me away,
so talk faster.
Right. T urns out this guy, Walton,
bought a throwaway cell phone, off
the books. I figured out his pass code
- and cloned it.
- What did you find?
Two calls to Agent Walton
in the past 48 hours
from a market in Koreatown.
- You'd better get down there.
- Yeah. Right.
- Seriously?
- Everything depends on this.
I'd go, but I'm about to be
a little tied up.
What am I supposed to do
when I get there?
- T ell me if you find him.
- Right. Do you want to come?
No, thanks.
Will you reconsider?
I couldn't if I wanted to.
In that case...
you are under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you...
- Hey.
I just found this.
What?
I've been listening to messages
cloned off Walton's cell phone...
- You'll take care of her?
- If she'll let me.
- Thank you.
- Thank you... for leaving.
Jain said this Agent Caleca's wife,
she's dead, right?
- Right.
- Well, then who's this?
It's Linda. I'm not supposed to call,
but I haven't heard from Victor in days.
I'm scared, Rich.
I'll try you again later.
She's alive.
- Victor Caleca?
- Did he send you?
- Who?
- Agent Walton.
[buzzer]
[clang]
I don't know how to tell you this,
but Agent Walton's dead.
I just spoke to him.
No, I just heard it on the radio
on the way over here.
They found his body a few hours ago.
[motorbike engines]
This is a trap.
What's a trap?
Whoever you are,
you better get out of here now.
[panting]
[rattling]