[Perri] There are
countless stories in this city
about the lives lived here.
About how the fates of others
intertwine with our own
in ways we can never expect or predict.
I'm a reporter.
This is my job.
To see, to understand.
But there are stories
behind these stories.
Stories about terrors I've only
begun to train my eyes to see.
I've learned this seeing
carries a heavy burden...
because once open to the darkness...
our eyes can never be closed again.
What... What are you doing, man?
Let me go!
I said let me go, damn it!
I ain't playing with you.
Let me go!
What do you want, man?
Say something, man.
What do you want from me?
What do you want from me? Huh?
[creaking]
No. No. No, man, no!
Man, don't!
Please God, no!
No! No!
Man, no!
No, please God, no!
[screams]
No! No!
[thumping]
[Perri] Hey.
Hey.
[phone rings]
Kolchak.
- Who was that?
- Hung up.
Working on a story?
Yeah.
T odd Hoffman, USC grad student.
Three nights ago he went
to a Lakers game with friends,
then headed south on foot.
No one's seen him since.
Missing persons case. You wrote
a missing persons story last week.
And another one a week before that.
That's four people missing
from downtown inside a month.
All of them disappeared
without a trace.
- What's the connection?
- Beats me.
I'm hoping you can figure it out.
[Perri] Three men, one woman.
Ages range from 26 to... 58.
Rich, poor, black, white, Latina.
LAPD's drawn no conclusions whatsoever.
So who says there's a story?
I do.
Because?
Because, that's my angle.
T ony says I got nothing,
so I got to figure a way
how to sell it to him.
Jeez. Boring T ony
and his weird preoccupation
with printing verifiable facts.
Ha! The big words
indicate sarcasm, right?
Mm-hmm.
Carl, sometimes a reporter
needs more than just his gut.
So. What are you...
What are you still doing here?
My birthday party.
Aren't you going to go?
Your birthday party?
I don't recall you...
It's a surprise party they're throwing
for me, all the folks in the office.
I...
Well, what can I say?
I sussed it out. I'm a reporter.
And a fine one at that.
Happy birthday.
I really don't know
anything about it. Seriously.
Well. It's, um...
Pretty sure it's at my apartment.
So, I just thought maybe
you might want to...
Yeah, yeah. Maybe I'll swing by.
Cool, um,
I guess I'll see you later then.
Maybe.
[chime]
[man] Hey, Kolchak. Hey.
Can I help you?
Yeah. Yeah, what's my answer?
What's... What's my answer?
I'm sorry. Do we know each other?
What? Yeah.
I was 227, you were 223.
So give me my answer.
Sir, l... I don't have
any answer for you.
I don't have any idea
what you're talking about.
Hey, you contacted me,
all right? Don't jerk me around.
I'm not jerking you around, sir.
You say I contacted you.
How exactly did I do that?
Through your articles. The secret code.
The secret code?
Yes. Yes!
What... What did I just say?
I broke the code.
Each letter represents an integer.
Fibonacci numbers. A child could see it.
The first sentence,
one-one-two-three-five-eight,
P-A-U-P.
Minus four, based on the first numeral
of my address, again. Obvious.
P minus four equals L.
P-A-U-L. Paul.
And, you are Paul?
Hey, man, why are
you messing with me?
You know I don't have much time.
All right. Look, I think
I'm starting to understand.
Here's my question. Did you sign in
with the security guard in the lobby?
Of course not. I snuck in.
OK, see, that's not gonna work.
I'll give you your answer,
but first we have to go downstairs,
sign in with the guard.
It's procedure.
Ah. Procedure. OK, I got you.
I don't know what game
you think you're playing,
but as I told you,
I don't have much time.
- Which you know!
- Yeah.
Now, let's start again.
You've been writing about me
the last couple of weeks.
The missing persons.
The missing persons?
You keep repeating what I say,
I'm gonna put one
through the bridge of your nose.
- OK, let's...
- T o hell with this!
- I do not have the time.
- Paul, don't...
- Turn around! Turn around!
- Don't do this. Paul...
Your car keys. Hurry.
- A GT. Where is it?
- Employee parking, level two.
- What color is it? What color?
- I don't know.
It's gold and metallic.
Please don't do this.
You're not giving me much choice.
I gotta get out.
The Old Man's gonna be waiting.
You know, you should have
just given me my answer.
- [man grunts]
- [Carl groans]
[rattling]
Paul?
[hushed]
Keep it down. He'll hear you.
Now, I'm gonna take my hand away.
But you have to be
real quiet, all right?
Little mouse voice. Understand?
- What do you want from me?
- You know what I want.
I want my answer.
- I don't have any answers...
- Little mouse voice.
Yes, you do. Yes!
No, I don't. I...
I don't know who you are,
or what to tell you,
I think you've got the wrong guy.
I don't have the wrong...
I don't have the wrong guy.
You're Carl Kolchak.
You were 223, I was 227.
We talked. Lots.
I don't know what 223 or 227...
- I don't know what that means.
- Ah!
I'm sorry.
St. Elizabeth's, Carl.
Psych ward.
They had you in room 223.
I was in room 227,
two doors down.
Yeah, it was only
like a year and a half ago,
so don't act like you don't remember.
Yeah, I was in St. Elizabeth's.
- It was right after my wife died.
- Yeah. Exactly.
But I swear,
I don't remember you. I'm sorry.
They... They had me on
very heavy psychotropics. They...
It was a very bad time for me.
Ah. Whereas for me, it was Club Med.
Fine. Say you don't remember me
from St. Lizzie's.
Still, one simple fact remains.
You've been contacting me
through the secret code
you've inserted in your
newspaper articles.
Don't! Don't shake your head!
You shake your head at me
and I'm going to cut it off!
I'm sorry. I apologize.
Please, take me through this...
this code-breaking process.
Was this about the missing
persons stories I wrote?
Are you saying
that you were responsible
for the people I wrote about?
That y... you were
the reason they went missing?
I'm not responsible.
The Old Man! He's responsible!
Who's the Old Man?
Is that your father?
What?
What kind of question is that?
You keep changing the subject!
Look!
Look.
Right here, in the King's English.
"Paul, I have your answer."
You wrote that and I found it.
Undeniable.
I passed your test.
Now you give me my answer!
The answer to what?
Which... Which answer?
I mean, there's lots of
questions I can think about.
Important questions that need answers.
You know that.
That's...
That's part of my test for you.
The answer to what?
Say it.
I want...
the answer...
to how I get out of here.
[? funk]
He didn't know about the party?
- That's what he said.
- He must have known.
He was invited.
Anyway, you told him about it, right?
So how come he's not here?
I don't know, he's busy,
he doesn't like parties...
It's Kolchak. Who knows?
But Kolchak loves you.
I mean he doesn't... Well...
He doesn't "love" love you.
He "like" loves you.
Respects you as a professional.
A meeting of the minds.
Jain? What exactly
are you drinking? Hmm?
You know what? I'm calling him.
No. No-no-no. Jain.
Paul, why can't you leave?
Who's keeping you here?
[buzzing]
What am I hearing?
All right, uh...
Well, let's talk about
the Old Man. Is he here?
Course he's here. He's always here.
Where is he? I don't see him.
Why would you see him?
He's in the back bedroom.
He lives in the light switch.
- I don't understand, Paul.
- He hides there.
And here.
That's why I can't leave.
He won't let me.
He gets mad at me and
he gets bigger inside my head
and my skull splits open.
- It's unbearable.
- Yeah?
He screams in my head.
He makes me smell bad smells.
He moves around inside my body.
My shoulder, my penis.
One time he was in my toes.
I had him then.
I had him good, I thought.
Oh, God.
Once I cut 'em all off,
I realized he was right back
in my shoulder. You see?
But down the hall...
that's all his.
You cross the yellow line,
you're his forever.
That's where the others all went.
Down the hall.
The missing persons?
Is that where you put 'em?
Are they still back there?
Are they still alive?
You promise me answers,
but all I hear are stupid questions.
What are you going to do with those?
I'm going to carefully cut your
head open. My answer's in there.
- I'm gonna find it.
- Paul.
If I start screaming,
the Old Man's going to hear, right?
Huh?
You're right. He's gonna...
[laughs] You passed my test.
You passed my test
with flying colors, Paul.
[Paul laughs]
I'm gonna help you now.
Uh, my car.
Did you use it to bring me here?
Where is it?
Parked out back, in the alley.
I hid it under a tarp.
Oh, good thinking.
Look, it's got everything
we need to get rid of the Old Man.
So you check the trunk.
I got equipment in there.
And all you need to do is...
is go out and get it
and bring it back here.
And then we'll get to work. OK?
Hey!
You gotta help me!
I'm trapped in here!
I'm being held hostage.
- Who are you?
- My name is Carl Kolchak.
I've been kidnapped by the man
who lives in this house.
Paul Krieger?
Paul, yeah, that's his name.
Do you know him?
I'm Stanley Kim, his caseworker.
L.A. Department of Mental Health.
Oh, yeah. I'd say
he definitely needs you.
Look, please, just call
the police. We don't have much time.
Where is he right now?
He's in the alley behind the house.
[bleeping]
- Police.
- [Carl sighs]
Yeah, I'll hold.
- [electrical buzzing]
- [Kim groans]
- [grunting]
- [groaning]
What are you gonna do to him?
Paul, be mad at me, not him!
It was my idea.
He didn't do anything!
Paul, talk to me!
What are you gonna do to him?
I'm gonna feed him
to the Old Man.
- [Kim] Paul?
- I got no choice.
You woke him up.
Now I gotta give him somebody.
[Kim] Paul?
What are you doing? Paul, Paul.
- [Kim] Let me go. Paul! Paul!
- This is on you, Carl.
- This is on your head.
- [Kim] Let me go! No!
[Kim yells, sobs]
[Kim screams]
[Krieger] I had half a mind
to give you to the Old Man, instead.
But I need you.
I liked old Stanley.
He was OK.
Even if he was a little nosy.
Stanley. That was his name?
That was the name
of the man you just killed?
I didn't kill him.
I ain't killed anybody since 1 990.
The Old Man got him.
And when the Old Man gets you,
you're worse than dead.
Look at you.
Trying to make me feel guilty.
Trying to shift the blame.
You're way more
of a murderer than I am!
Now, let's see what you
had in your car, huh?
Cattle prods.
Glow sticks.
Climbing ropes.
Useless, useless crap.
What's this, a camcorder?
- What is it?
- It's a thermographic camera.
It takes pictures of heat.
That's it. You know what?
I'm just gonna cut your head open.
- I'm not gonna waste more time.
- What if it doesn't work?
What are you going to do then?
Think about it, Paul.
If you cut my head open, I'll die.
What if you don't find
what you're looking for?
Then you've got nothing.
You'll be alone.
It'll just be
you and the Old Man, forever.
You know, I'm understanding
something now, Paul.
I'm understanding that you're right.
The answer is up here in my brain.
But it's... It's buried deep
in my subconscious.
See, that's why it's...
it's tricky to get at.
But it's not impossible.
Keep talking.
How did I contact you
in the first place?
It was through the secret code
in my articles, right?
I mean, messages
I wasn't even aware I was sending.
Because it was...
It was my subconscious mind
communicating
through my fingertips as I typed.
So, don't you see, Paul?
You and l,
the only way we're
gonna get to the truth
about what's locked up in here...
is for you to let me write your story.
[Perri] Thank you for coming.
- [man] You're welcome.
- [woman laughs]
Jain, you gonna sprout roots,
or you gonna let me call you a cab?
- It doesn't make sense.
- What doesn't?
I left Kolchak three messages.
Why wouldn't he call me back?
It's one in the morning,
he's probably in bed.
- Maybe he turned off his phone.
- [sighs] Perri...
We are hard-charging newspaper
men in a city that never sleeps.
Since when do we turn off our phones?
You know yourself, this isn't like him.
Jain, I don't know.
I don't know Kolchak well enough
to say what's like him
and what isn't and neither do you.
Except...
You know, if he thought
that something happened to you,
or to me, even if it was just
some crazy feeling he was having
he'd check on us
to make sure we were OK.
I do know that much about him.
[Jain groans]
[door opening, closing]
I can't write like this.
You'll have to unlock my wrists.
So, now what?
Now, start talking.
T ell me about the Old Man.
When did he first come to you?
St. Elizabeth's.
Why were you there?
Prison dodge. Had a good lawyer.
He got me sent there instead of Chino.
Anyway, it's not like
I belong in a nut house. Kinda like you.
Had to play the game after
they blamed you for killing your wife.
Anyway, I was due for some good luck.
My old lady was a junkie whore.
I laid eyes on her maybe
three times my entire life.
She palmed me off on my grandparents.
Couple of real Bible-thumpers.
They never trusted me.
Ever.
One day when I was 1 9,
I was in the kitchen
and my Grams starts in on me
about how I stole some money out
of her purse, like, 1 1 dollars.
Ridiculous. So what?
But she's yelling
like I robbed Fort Knox!
Yelling in that damned
screeching voice of hers,
screeching in my head.
So the next thing I know, I got
a handful of her hair, and I'm just...
So then...
I had to go do
the same thing to Gramps.
I mean, what choice did I have?
What, was I gonna look him in
the eye? The look he'd give me?
I just couldn't stand to see that.
Anyway... I ended up at St. Elizabeth's.
And one day, when they were
giving me shock therapy...
I look up and there's
the Old Man, smiling down at me.
Showing those sharp little teeth.
Nobody else could see him
except for me.
And he says, "You're mine."
'Cause of what I'd done.
And I knew right then,
he was never gonna
leave me alone after that.
He wants me bad.
Real bad.
But I can't let him get me.
Paul, if he wants you,
what about the others?
The ones you send down in the
hallway? Why does he take them?
He's always screaming
in my head, making my head hurt.
Yelling at me to cross the yellow line.
He wants me
in that back bedroom with him.
So...
sometimes I give him
somebody else instead.
And then he's quiet for a little while.
I don't like doing it.
I feel real bad for those people.
I have your answer now.
There is no Old Man.
There never was.
- What are you talking about?
- You invented him.
The guilt you feel about
your grandparents is so overwhelming
that it makes you see
your very own devil.
One that you created,
one that doesn't exist.
Oh yeah, Dr. Freud?
Then what's waiting
at the end of that hall?
Nothing. It's just an empty bedroom.
And that's your answer.
And you and I could
walk out of here any time.
It's up to you.
You know how many
times I heard that, Carl?
Every doctor
at St. Lizzie's told me that!
But you? Out of all the people,
I thought you would believe me.
You know what it's like
to be called crazy!
We're not talking about me, Paul.
You told me your wife was killed
by monsters, and I believe you.
But what? Was that just your
guilty conscience talking? Huh?
Was that just a wild story you
confabulated so as you could sleep?
We're not talking about me, Paul.
You and I have nothing in common.
Oh, yeah? Really?
This camera sees through walls.
It takes pictures of heat.
I want you to go down the hallway,
aim it at that closed door.
And if your Old Man's there,
you'll see him.
Go on. Do it.
You're sure that Old Man's
there, prove it to me.
There.
[Krieger] See?
What did I tell you?
[Krieger] See him?
- T ell me you see him.
- I see something.
What's the matter with this thing?
I don't know. The battery may be dead.
- Anyone back there?
- Don't.
[creaking]
[panting]
Mr. Kim.
Please... help me.
- No!
- Paul, he's hurt. Let me go!
It's a trick.
He wants you to cross the line.
- What? Damn it, let me go!
- Hey!
That's the Old Man. Right there.
Plain as day. Don't you see him?
Paul, I'm Stanley. Please.
- You're the Old Man.
- I'm Stanley, Paul.
Stanley.
For God's sake,
you stabbed me, remember?
You took me in the back, stabbed me,
then dumped me out of the chair.
- You always lie. Stop lying!
- [Carl] Paul.
Paul, calm down. Put the gun down.
[Kim] Try...
Try and focus, Paul. Please.
Have you... Have you
taken your chlorpromazine?
Remember how we talk about
how you always need to take it?
- Stanley tells me, not you.
- Paul, don't.
I'm bleeding bad.
I think... I think I'm going
to die if I don't get an ambulance.
- T ell him, Mr. Kolchak.
- See? He knows your name.
How would he know
unless he's the Old Man?
Because I told him.
I told him when he first came here!
Remember how you and I always
talk... talk about Mr. Kolchak?
How you say
he's sending clues to you?
Your interest in his wife lrene?
What? What about my wife?
He's... He's fixated on her.
He was on day-release
from St. Elizabeth's
when she was murdered.
He came back talking
about Las Vegas.
Something scary in the desert.
He had blood on his pant leg...
Shut up, Old Man.
I... I never... never put two
and two together until now.
I swear to you,
I never thought he had it in him.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
No, stop! Take me back!
Let me hear the rest!
T ell me about my wife.
He's lying! That's what he does.
Paul! Don't hurt him. Paul!
Paul!
I checked the parking deck
on my way up. His car's not there.
[Perri] He left in a hurry.
His jacket's still
on the back of his chair.
Something doesn't feel right, T ony.
Honestly, if it was the Carl Kolchak
I knew two years ago, I would agree.
But the one who works for me now...
Couldn't tell you.
Why do you say that?
The death of lrene, it changed him.
He's driven now by demons
I can't even begin to understand.
But if I had to guess,
I'd say he probably just
doesn't want to be reached.
What else do you have?
How can you track him down?
I don't know.
There's nothing here.
I mean... [sighs]
What?
He got a telephone call before I left.
He said it was a hang-up.
Maybe if we could get it traced...
[Kim] No, I'm not the Old Man.
[approaching engine]
- Perri! Perri, it's me.
- Carl, what are you doing?
I'm being held hostage. Me and another
guy who needs an ambulance.
- Get away and call the police.
- Can you climb out?
- My foot's chained.
- I'm not leaving you here.
Perri, this guy is a lunatic.
He's got a gun.
Listen to me and get
the hell out of here, OK?
Come on. [grunts]
Help me, damn it!
[Perri] Move.
For God's sake.
What are you, Nancy Drew?
Oh, God. Are you OK?
Wonderful. How did you find me?
Remember we were
talking in the newsroom
and you got that hang up call?
Well, I traced it to this address.
- Well, good job.
- It's all I had, so...
You trusted your gut?
Someone once told me a reporter
needs more than their gut.
Yeah, and a nice set of bolt cutters
would be great about now, too.
Yes, I'd like to report a man with a gun
at 4809 Pampas Street.
He's holding two hostages, one of whom
needs immediate medical attention.
This is Perri Reed with the Los
Angeles Beacon. Please, hurry.
They're on their way.
Sorry I missed your birthday party.
- How was it?
- Uh, well, you know...
Uh... people drinking,
having a good time.
Friends helping me celebrate the fact
that I'm one year closer to death.
The usual.
Perri. I... I...
You know, when so many people
tell you you're crazy,
you start to wonder.
And you shut them out
to protect yourself.
And you feel like you need
to take things on alone.
But Carl, you're not alone.
You have friends who believe in you.
You got me.
Let's get the hell outta here.
- What are you trying to do?
- What do you mean?
This!
There's a message here.
Your answer!
Where's Mr. Kim?
What did you do to him?
He was the Old Man.
He went back there, and he's waiting.
I'm sending you to him
if you don't explain this, right now.
- There's nothing to explain.
- No?
Then why did you write this, huh? Why?
Uh, well, what does it say, Paul?
"Cross the yellow line."
Why would you tell me to do that, Carl?
Are you trying to kill me?
Answer me, you son of a bitch!
[Perri yells]
- [groans]
- No!
Oh, God. Oh, God.
OK, hold on, Perri.
- [Carl] Just hold on.
- How did you get loose?
Who let you out of the chair?
The Old Man?
- The ambulance is coming.
- Get away from her.
- You're gonna be OK.
- That's the Old Man.
Shut up! Shut up!
Please, don't let me die.
Carl, please...
Please don't let me die.
What? Are you kidding?
Think I'm gonna let you die
on your birthday? Come on.
You don't know me very well.
- Perri.
- Please don't let me die.
Perri, hold on.
Perri.
Oh, he is good.
You ought to win an Oscar for that one.
That was genius. Bravo, Old Man.
Don't you get it?
Don't you see what he's trying to do?
That's the Old Man,
pretending to be your friend.
Get you to turn on the waterworks.
Get you all emotional.
So you'll do something crazy.
Put me over the yellow line!
Because that's where he wants me!
Back in that room,
where he's got all the power!
Son of a bitch.
You damn lunatic!
[grunting]
[gunshot]
Is the Old Man doing this?
Huh?
Where's the Old Man now,
you sick bastard?
Huh, is he down the hallway?
Or is he in the light switch?
I'll tell you what,
- let's go see him.
- No! No!
- Let's go see him together!
- No!
[Krieger screams]
[Perri] Carl.
Perri?
[door opening, creaking]
Paul?
[police radio]
- Hey.
So, uh, I missed your birthday.
I think I understand.
The Detective said
you thought you saw me here tonight?
Yeah, I did.
He kept telling me
I sent him messages in my stories.
That I had his answer.
And he was right, I did.
But it didn't come from me.
If it didn't come from you, Carl...
where did it come from?
[Perri] If you look
into the darkness long enough
your eyes adjust.
And you start to see...
that there are evils in the dark.
But in seeing...
you learn a terrible truth.
That you have not
found these evils at all...
but rather...
they have found you.