You? You again? Get out!
Go on, I told you. Get out!
Go on! Go on!
Papa!
You filthy dog! You settle with me!
Ha...
Let's go.
Welcome to you, señor.
My name is Juan de Dios.
I am the bell-ringer.
Why are you here?
To see the Rojos? No, not the Rojos.
Is it the Baxters? No, maybe not.
You want to get rich?
Well, it's the right place.
If you use your head.
That's because everybody here
has become very rich,
or else they are dead.
What do you want to buy?
Some guns? Liquor?
You don't buy, you sell.
You sell lead in exchange for gold?
You will get rich here. Or you'll be killed.
Juan de Dios tolls the bell once again.
Saludos, amigo. It's not smart
to go wandering so far from home.
I reckon he picked the wrong trail.
- Or he could have picked the wrong town.
- His big mistake was getting born.
You want any work,
Iookin' like that,
ya could try bein' a scarecrow!
Oh, no! The crows are liable
to scare him maybe.
Ha-ha!
Hello.
Saludos.
You can't get rich like that!
At most, you will only succeed
in being killed!
We have enough trouble.
What are you looking for?
Food, somethin' to drink.
- Water's over there.
- No. No water.
Eating, drinking, killing.
That's all you can do,
just like the rest of your kind.
By the way, you'll have to mark this up.
I know, you have no money.
After all, you just got into town.
But if you don't mind killing,
you will find someone eager to pay you.
Hm-mm. My roulette wheel.
That, too, was murdered.
No-one ever comes here to play.
We spend our time
between funerals and burials.
Yeah. Never saw a town
as dead as this one.
You will never see another like it.
- What's wrong with the place?
- We've had too many killings.
You have seen the women?
None of them are women, they're widows.
The place has only widows.
Here, you can only gain respect
by killing other men. So nobody works.
- Somebody doesn't share your opinion.
- Yes.
Saludos!
You know why Piripero looked you over?
To take your measurements.
He can do it with a glance.
You will be a customer.
Hm.
I'm not joking. Those murderers
will make a corpse out of you one day.
That's why I want you to get out of here.
You don't want to stay in this cemetery,
finish up and get out.
I told ya I can't pay ya.
Be my guest.
But get out of San Miguel, will you?
- Where does that lead?
- The balcony.
Why are you going there?
Hey!
To have a look. Things always
look different from higher up.
But nothing's up there!
Go ahead and get out!
- Who are they?
- Hm. Bandits.
Bandits and smugglers.
They come down from Texas
to stock up on guns and liquor.
The cost is much less here.
They sell guns and liquor to the lndians.
Any town that sells guns and liquor
has gotta be rich.
Not the town.
Only those who buy and sell.
The bosses are the ones who clean up.
Somebody has to run the place.
Every town has a boss.
That's true, but when there are two,
I'd say that there is one too many.
Two bosses?
Very interesting.
Interesting is right. The Rojos,
three brothers who sell liquor.
And then there's the Baxters,
big gun merchants.
Ah, if I'm not mistaken,
you already met Baxter's gang.
Yeah, we met.
But you're lucky. They don't usually
limit their fire to the mule.
A man looks around for any reason,
Juan de Dios tolls the bell,
Piripero sells another coffin.
Two bosses.
They've enlisted all the scum
from both sides of the frontier.
And they pay in dollars.
Baxters over there.
Rojos there.
Me right in the middle.
Where you do what?
Crazy bell-ringer was right.
There's money to be made
in a place like this.
If you're thinking what I suspect -
I tell you, don't try it.
Which one of the two is the stronger?
Which one of them is stronger?
Well, the Rojos, especially Ramon.
Don Miguel Rojo, I wanna talk to you.
Don Miguel, I hear you're hirin' on men.
Well, I might just be available.
I gotta tell ya before you hire me,
I don't work cheap.
- Get three coffins ready.
- Huh?
Adios, amigo.
Stranger, didn't you get the idea?
We don't like bad boys like you in town.
Go get your mule.
You let him get away from you?
That's what I wanna talk about.
He's feelin' real bad.
Huh?
My mule. You see, he got all riled up
when you fired those shots at his feet.
- Hey, are you makin' some kinda joke?
- No.
I understand you were playin' around.
But the mule, he just doesn't get it.
If you were to all apologise...
I don't think it's nice, you laughin'.
See, my mule don't like people laughin'.
He gets the idea you're laughin' at him.
Now, if you apologise,
like I know you will,
I might convince him
that you really didn't mean it.
I saw it. You killed all four of them.
You'll pay, all right. You'll be strung up.
Who are you?
Don't fire a shot.
I'm John Baxter - Sheriff.
Yeah. Well, if you're the sheriff,
you better get these men underground.
My mistake. Four coffins.
Hey!
I told you I wasn't cheap,
but I think you'll find it's worth your while.
..98, 99, 100.
The rest when you're all done.
When do I start?
I'm not in a hurry, at least for the moment.
With four less Baxters,
now is as good a time to start as any.
In a few days, a troop of cavalry
will pass through San Miguel.
I wouldn't want the military sticking
their long noses into our business.
You seem to be well informed.
In these parts, a man's life often depends
on a mere scrap of information.
Hm. This thing couldn't have been
very useful to its owner.
My brother Ramon did that!
He often uses it for target practice.
With a gun in his hand,
no-one stands in his way.
The armour is one of his favourite targets.
Naturally, when he doesn't have
anything better to shoot.
Well, I'll be kinda curious
to meet this brother of yours.
Ah, this is Chico,
one of the most trusted of my men.
Follow him.
He will bring you to your room.
I would like you to feel at home.
Well, I never found home that great.
Let's go.
Who's that?
Her name is Marisol.
You just forget about her.
This one will be your room.
You gave him 100.
We've never paid that much before.
Can you explain
why you have taken him on?
To have a filthy gringo here,
and to give him 100 besides?
We have never paid anybody so much.
You cannot leave someone like that
to do what he wants!
He might do anything
and I want law and order in this place!
If that is all you want,
there is a much cheaper way.
Just snuff him out.
And who will be the one? You?
Yes. Why not?
A shot in his back
and then you would have him
out of the way in no time at all.
Listen, I could do it easily right now.
He won't be expecting it,
and I'd get back the 100.
You are stupid, Esteban!
Even if you are my brother!
A bullet in the back and it is ended!
And what happens if your hand
should tremble and he's only been hurt?
With the cavalry arriving in town,
and that Yankee so quick on the draw...
- But I was only thinking...
- Don't think! You let me do the thinking.
Go and see the Americano.
Ask if he needs anything. Make friends.
Get one thing clear.
This is going to be a quiet town
until Ramon gets back!
Is that clear? A quiet town.
I am Esteban Rojo.
My brother asked me to...
What are you doing?
Moving.
But didn't you know
all our men live here with us?
That's all very cosy, but, uh,
I don't find you men all that appealin'.
Besides, your brother said he didn't have
any need for me any more right now.
Halt!
- Sergeant.
- Yes, Capitan?
Tell the men we'll spend tonight here.
Arrange it so they can pick up
the supplies here.
Also double the guard
on the stagecoach there.
Yes, sir.
Now, what do you suppose
is in that coach?
It would be easy to find out.
Get up close and take a look inside.
If they fire at you, you know it's gold.
Not a bad idea.
Mm.
Looking for anything?
Hello.
Get out of here, Yankee. Vamos.
Why aren't you sleeping?
When I see you staring like that,
it bothers me.
I keep wondering
what was in that stagecoach.
It's something
they think is very important.
I asked a few questions of the captain
and almost was arrested.
Who's Marisol?
You'd better get some sleep. You need it.
Much too dangerous, even for you.
All I did is ask who she was.
She is a woman.
Ramon's madly in love with her.
Does that make it clear to you?
Mm. Everybody in this town
talks about Ramon.
I'm curious to meet him.
If you're smart, you'll try to stay
clear of Ramon as long as possible.
Ah! There are the soldiers.
They're moving off very quietly.
Strange. They're headed for the frontier.
Tell me,
is that the way you go to bed every night?
Don't worry. I didn't dirty the sheets.
No, wait! I'm coming, too!
I want to see
how you're going to get in trouble.
Ha-ha. All right, all right. Go ahead.
It's like playing cowboys and lndians.
- Captain.
- Welcome, Lieutenant.
There is your gold as promised.
I hope the guns you are giving us
will be equally useful to our army.
Rest assured, Captain.
We'll check 'em over together.
Get their clothes on again, and hurry.
Be sure to place them around right.
They died fighting among themselves.
Rubio!
There. It's Ramon.
This is my brother Ramon.
I think I mentioned him.
Everybody talks about Ramon.
And many speak of you, too.
My dear brother included.
Well, I hope they say... nice things?
Did you have a good trip?
It was tiring. It was terribly hard
on the road during the day.
And stagecoaches are
an uncomfortable way to travel.
Well, I'm sure you'll be
in great shape in no time.
The Americano cannot wait
to get into action!
I am sorry.
He is going to be a disappointed man.
How's that?
The Baxters accepted the invitation.
They'll come tonight, Don Miguel.
You must be out of your head!
I told Chico to invite them here.
Ramon, what is this?
I found out many things travelling.
I have decided that... it's very stupid.
We just keep on shooting at each other -
and without results.
You've gone out of your mind, Ramon!
No, I've come to my senses, Esteban.
Believe me.
Trust me.
Life can be so precious.
It's foolish to risk
losing it every minute, no?
There's enough space for everybody
in this town. Even Baxters, hm?
For this reason,
I've decided to hang my gun up
on the wall.
I think that Ramon is right.
I, too, am tired of these killings.
They must stop!
This is all... very, very touching.
You don't admire peace?
It's not really easy to like
something you know nothing about.
Stay here and you may just
profit from the experience.
No, thanks. I'll be movin' on.
Here's your money, Don Miguel.
I only used a small amount of it.
I don't like to take money
unless I feel I've earned it.
Why are you so hasty? Stay here.
You might enjoy dining with us tonight.
You see, the Baxters have four men
in the cemetery on account of me.
I don't think
they'd appreciate my presence.
- He is too smart to be just a hired fighter.
- With a pistol, no-one can touch him.
When someone with that face
works with his gun, count on two things.
He's fast, but he's also intelligent.
That makes him too dangerous for you.
Now he's gone, explain that nonsense
about hanging up your gun
and making up with the Baxters.
Is it possible that you'll never be able
to reach any conclusions on your own?
Our government and the Americanos
will find those bodies and investigate.
They'll investigate, all right.
And we'll be quiet
and peacefully bide our time.
We know nothing about a massacre
at the Rio Bravo, eh?
I arranged for the bodies to be lying
as if both companies killed each other.
But do you think they'll believe it?
Ah, yes, I think so.
Because if they don't find a guilty party,
they will call off the investigation.
Yes, but... what about the Baxters?
The Baxters?
They want nothing more
than to live in peace.
We'll let them have their own way
for a while. So, forget the Baxters.
We'll take care of them later
when the investigation finishes!
That was a fine idea that you had.
What was it again?
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes.
The Baxters on one side,
the Rojos on the other.
And you'd be in the middle.
The only problem is
that they've joined up.
Now you have no job and no money
to pay me what you owe me.
There is only one thing for you to do.
Leave. I'll forget about what you owe me.
Leave San Miguel and never come back
for the rest of your days.
Hey, Joe! I prepared the wagon
the way you asked me to.
We're sitting in the back here
with two empty coffins.
What are you up to?
Are you changing your profession?
If you want to go on living, you'd better.
In my opinion,
you will make a fine pallbearer.
Close this place and come with me.
Oh, close up, huh? It's done.
Where are we going?
I'd like to know, or is it a secret?
Down by the river, to have a look
at some corpses down there.
The Rojos say come to dinner
and we must go, but I don't like it at all.
Even if they've granted
all the guarantees we demanded.
We'll go along with it,
but don't touch anything!
You mustn't eat. You mustn't drink.
You just keep your eyes open
and keep your wits about you.
Whoa...
Are you sure that nobody has seen us?
Only a ghost or two.
No, no, no.
Don't joke about things like this.
Ghosts are better left where they are.
You look as though
this place suits you very well.
And if you go on like this, you will
soon be here permanently. Hee-hee!
Why is it, with all those bodies,
we are just burying these two?
We're not... gonna bury 'em.
We are not burying them?
That's right, we're not gonna bury 'em.
If we are not burying them, I would
like to know what we will use them for?
Why are we taking the trouble to do this?
The dead can be very useful sometimes.
They've helped me outta tough spots
more than once.
First, they don't talk.
Second, they can be made to look alive
if I manage it right.
Yeah.
And third,
if you shoot 'em, there's no worry
cos they're dead already. Understand?
It makes no sense to me
and I'm getting out!
I'm alive
and I want to remain with the living.
And when I'm dead,
I'll want to remain with the dead.
I hope that's clear.
Also, I don't like the idea
that you've placed those bodies there.
The man buried there is the only one
who ever died of pneumonia here!
Take it easy, will ya? Our friends here
are gonna help me pay your bill.
Ah, get up there!
Their only reason to start a war would be
to kidnap you from your husband's side.
He is gallant, this Rojo.
I didn't think him capable of compliments.
He's not. All that he says is false,
like his proposals.
You women! lf things aren't complicated
for you, you become suspicious.
Yes. Because to me it just didn't
seem right. It went too smoothly.
I don't trust them.
You'd like to prove me wrong,
wouldn't you? Always the same thing.
- Goodnight.
Don't worry. I'm not gonna hurt ya.
I just want ya to know why the Rojos
wanna make peace all of a sudden.
There was once a wagonload of gold
that the soldiers were takin' to the border.
John! Come up here quickly.
Sorry.
When a husband finds
a man in his wife's bedroom,
you're never sure how he's gonna react.
- Give him 500.
- How's that?
Give the money to him.
He has an interesting story. Listen to him.
That's the right idea?
I get the wrong idea only when it suits me.
Ramon! The soldiers escorting the gold...
Two of them got away.
They're hiding out in the cemetery.
The Baxters are about to capture them.
Hey! Rubio! Get the men.
You are well informed.
A man's life here often depends
on a mere scrap of information.
Your brother's own words.
Tell me, why are you doing this for us?
500.
With these two soldiers
as witnesses against Ramon,
the government
will rid the town of the Rojos.
Then San Miguel will have just one boss.
Hurry!
Let's go!
Coming with us?
No, no. When a man's got money
in his pocket, he appreciates peace.
Come on!
Whoa!
Let's leave the horses here.
Por Dios!
Who is there? Come out!
Ohh!
What do you think?
I don't know.
There's somethin' about it I don't like.
Too still to be wounded,
more like dummies.
Sure! Dummies that interest the Rojos.
Better hide. Hurry!
- What do we do?
- Circle around to the side.
Keep them busy long enough
for me to get those two.
Go on! Go on! Quickly!
Keep me covered.
I'll take care of those two.
Listen, Baxter!
You can have them now if you like!
Since dead men can't talk!
It seems they didn't like my joke.
We'll let them go home in a while.
This bad boy will be our guest only until
Baxter leaves San Miguel for the frontier.
Put him in the cellar.
Esteban, good work!
With Antonio as our prisoner,
the Baxters will have to give in to us.
Now we can make any kind of demand!
Don Miguel! Don Miguel!
What has happened? Talk, will you!
I don't know who,
but somebody shot at me.
Marisol!
Marisol! Where are you, Marisol?!
Strange... how you always manage
to be in the right place at the right time.
It's nothing serious,
a headache that will pass. She'll sleep.
Keep your eyes open. She's not to move
from that room, you hear?
I wouldn't mention I brought her here.
I wouldn't want the Rojos to think
I was on your side.
Don't be worried. I'm rich enough
to appreciate the men
that my money can buy.
I've been to talk to the Rojos.
They'll give back Antonio
in exchange for Marisol in the morning.
Very soon, you're going to be rich.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, that's not gonna break my heart.
Where is she?
You said I'd see her! Where is she?
I want to see her!
Come back here, Jesus. Come here.
Why can't I look at her? I want to see her!
Go. Go to him, Marisol.
Mama!
- Mama!
- Jesus!
Mama!
- Mama! Mama!
Julio.
Marisol.
Get Julio.
You were warned to get outta town.
Now I'm gonna make you pay
once and for all.
Let him be.
You better get goin'. Ramon's waitin'.
And you, get that kid home
where he belongs.
A pig, that Ramon!
Tell me, what's Ramon
got to do with them?
You weren't told, eh?
In these parts, the story is very old.
A happy little family until trouble
comes along. Trouble is Ramon.
Claiming the husband cheated at cards,
which wasn't true,
he gets the wife
to live with him as hostage.
The husband?
Him, there's nothing for him to do.
The Rojos threatened to kill his boy,
Jesus. He was forced to accept things.
That Ramon is smart.
Where are you going?
To the Rojos, to look for a job.
Poo!
I'm glad we have the Americano with us.
It's the best thing to happen to us.
If either government starts an enquiry,
we'll need every man we can get.
To be at war with the Baxters now is
worse than sitting on a case of dynamite.
- Where should we put this?
- Put it over there.
Come on, everybody. Drink up!
Good shooting. Very good shooting.
To kill a man, you shoot for his heart,
and a Winchester is the best weapon.
That's very nice, but I'll stick with my .45.
When a man with a .45
meets a man with a rifle,
the man with the pistol
will be a dead man.
That's an old Mexican proverb,
and it's true.
You believe that?
Paquito, take five men
and escort Marisol to the small house.
- Everything is prepared.
- Do not worry. I will return tomorrow.
The wagons are ready. We can leave.
Everyone!
Enjoy yourselves during my absence!
You heard Ramon,
let's have a good time.
He weighs over a ton.
Of course, with all he poured into himself.
Papa,
did you not tell me
no-one could go see Mama?
That's right.
Then, why does that man see her
when I cannot?
- I want Mama!
- Come away from the door. Quiet.
We cannot show ourselves.
You must stay away.
Hello.
There's somebody shooting
at the small house.
Saddle the horses immediately!
Come on, let's go!
Look out!
Take this money. It's enough to live on
for a while. Now, get across the border.
Get as far away from San Miguel
as possible.
How may we thank you
for what you are doing?
Don't try. Just get goin'
before the Rojos get here.
Why do you do this for us?
Why? I knew someone like you once.
No-one was there to help. Get movin'.
Get movin'.
Get outta here!
What do you see, Chico?
They're all dead. They massacred them.
- They kidnapped Marisol!
- This looks like the work of the Baxters.
Quick! Let's get back before
they attack our house in the town.
Chico, give out the ammunition.
Esteban, spread your men
around the house. Keep your eyes open.
Miguel, Paco, behind the house.
Manolo and Alvaro, come with me.
Stay alert!
The way they killed those men,
there must be a lot of them.
It's a warm evening.
One of our wagons lost a wheel
so we had to turn back here to get help.
One of the men tells me...
the Baxters attacked the small house.
Do you know about it?
Tell me what you know.
Oh!
Well?
Where did you hide Marisol?
Rubio.
You are thirsty? You want to drink?
No, no. It is too soon to drink.
Ooh!
Bring him over here.
You are a stubborn idiot. Tell us
where Marisol is and it'll all be ended.
In a week, you'll be back in shape,
and you can go wherever you want.
That's enough for today.
Sooner or later he'll talk.
It's just a matter of time.
He mustn't escape or die.
Otherwise, do as you like.
Wait till he comes to.
This way he hardly feels anything.
I have a poker hand waiting for me.
Now I am stuck here! I can't get back to it!
This is more amusing than cards.
Just be sure he does not die,
and also make sure
he regrets the day he was born.
The gringo is asleep, I imagine.
That's all right. I'll enjoy waking him up.
Esteban, what was that noise?
I do not know.
I heard a yell and then a crash.
It's useless to hide!
You are finished playing the smart boy.
Go up and look in the loft!
And take a look behind the barrels!
Let's get out of here!
Hurry! Hurry!
- Come on!
- You, come along with me!
Surround the town! Block the streets
leading out! Find him for me!
- Esteban, search the whole town!
- Follow me!
Get him back right now!
You've got to at any cost!
Look in the stables, in every corral,
in the store!
Look for him in the church!
Go in there! Search every inch of it!
Search everywhere! Rubio, in here!
If somebody is hiding him,
burn their house down and kill them!
You, come here!
Look for him near the Baxters',
but take him alive. I want him alive!
Alive!
Rubio,... in the bar.
He says he knows nothing.
He's being smart.
Bring him here to me.
I swear I'm telling the truth.
Well,... you know nothing, huh?
Nothing! I have not seen him!
Rubio, you take care of him!
Where have you hidden him?
I... didn't... hide...
You are the right friend
for that filthy Americano.
You'll end up the same way.
We looked everywhere.
In his cellar, in the attic, on the roof,
but there is no trace.
I couldn't find anybody in the back room.
He has taken refuge with the Baxters.
The Americano isn't stupid.
He knows that's the best place to hide.
The Baxters, eh?
Then better go and get him.
And that's for being his friend.
Curse them!
Piripero!
Eh?
- Piripero!
- Hm?
- Come here.
- I can't see anybody.
- Dios mio!
What are you doing in there?
Never mind. Get me outta here.
But you're not dead yet.
I will be, if you don't get me
outta here quick. Get the lid down.
Rubio.
I see some signs of life.
Let's be ready
when they decide to come out.
Don't shoot!
We surrender! Don't shoot!
Don't shoot! We're coming out!
I surrender! Hold back your fire!
Don't shoot! We're surrendering!
Stop. I wanna take a look at this.
Ramon! Don't shoot!
We're comin' out.
We surrender!
Listen, you've won! It's enough!
I'll get outta town!
I'll do whatever you like!
- You promise that?
- I swear it, Ramon!
You won't try any tricks?
None. No, no tricks. I said before,
I give you my word, we'll leave!
Are you sure? You had better
ask permission of your wife.
Maybe she won't be too happy!
Antonio! John!
Murderers.
They had no guns!
Murderers! I hope you rot in hell!
May you all die spitting blood!
Curse you for this!
Murderers!
Let's go. The show's over anyway.
Keep looking for him!
Search among those bodies!
The filthy Americano
has to be somewhere.
Silvanito?
Where's Silvanito?
Any news today?
I have to tell you some bad news.
I hate to tell you this, Joe, but...
Where is Silvanito?
He was captured this morning
by those men of Ramon's.
They grabbed him on his way here.
He was bringing in some provisions.
He is being tortured, but he won't talk.
He's stubborn.
Whatever they do, he won't say a word,
even if it means his life.
Listen to me.
They'll never be able to force him.
Now, old fool, loosen up your tongue.
No.
Rubio!
Get back to your shop.
You're liable to have business there.
Very good! That's what I wanted to hear.
I brought a little surprise for you.
I know how much you will need it.
It was hard to get my hands on it.
I got it by using my head.
No-one can resist two bottles of wine.
I thought you might need that pistol.
And I brought another present.
It's dynamite.
I stole it from the Rojos.
The moment's come
for you to light the fuse
and send it back to them.
Still lots of light.
Too early to be asleep yet.
Rubio, here.
I shouldn't like to ruin the rifle.
I could never find another like this one.
Later, Ramon.
Let's try it with this one now.
Gringo!
I heard you wanted to see me.
The Americano's dead.
Cut the old man down.
What's wrong, Ramon?
You losing your touch?
Are you afraid, Ramon?
If you shoot to kill,
you'd better hit the heart.
Your own words, Ramon.
The heart, Ramon. Don't forget the heart.
Aim for the heart or you'll never stop me.
When a man with a .45
meets a man with a rifle,
you said the man with the pistol's
a dead man.
Let's see if that's true.
Go ahead. Load up and shoot.
Hey. Hey, listen, Joe.
Listen, Joe, l... I...
Oh, Joe... Joe...
I guess your government'll be glad
to see that gold back.
And you? You don't want to be here
when they get it, eh?
You mean,
the Mexican government on one side,
maybe the Americans on the other,
and me, right smack in the middle?
Uh-uh. Too dangerous.
So long.
Adios.
Let me see... Five seven.