You? You again? Get out!
Go on, I told you. Get out!
Go on! Go on!
Papa!
You filthy dog! You settle with me!
Ah..
Let's go.
Welcome to you, señor.
My name is Juan de Dios.
I am the bell-ringer. Why are you here?
To see the Rojos? No, not the Rojos.
Is it the Baxters? No, maybe not even
the Baxters. You want to get rich?
Well, for that you have come to
the right place, if you use your head.
That's because everybody here
has become very rich,
or else they are dead. What do you want
to buy? Some guns? Liquor?
You don't buy, you sell.
Lead in exchange for gold?
You will get rich here. Or you'll be killed.
Juan de Dios tolls the bell once again.
Saludos, amigo. It's not smart
to go wandering so far from home.
- I reckon he picked the wrong trail.
- He could have picked the wrong town.
His big mistake, I
think, was getting born.
If you want any work, lookin' like that,
you could try bein' a scarecrow.
Oh, no! The crows are liable
to scare him, maybe.
Hello.
Saludos.
You can't get rich like that. At most,
you will only succeed in being killed.
With all the trouble, all we needed
was you. What are you looking for?
Food, somethin' to drink.
- Water's over there.
- No. No water.
Eating and drinking and killing. That's all
you can do, just like the rest of your kind.
By the way, you'll have to mark this up.
I know, you have no money.
After all, you just got into town.
If you don't mind doing a little killing,
you will have no trouble
finding someone eager to pay you.
Hm-mm.
My roulette wheel.
That, too, was murdered.
No one comes here to play. We spend our
time here between funerals and burials.
Yeah. Never saw a town
as dead as this one.
You will never see another like it.
- What's wrong with the place?
- We've had too many killings.
You have seen the women?
None of them are women, they're widows.
The place has only widows. Here, you can
only gain respect by killing other men.
So nobody works any more.
Seems somebody doesn't
share your opinion.
Mm-hm. Yes.
¡Saludos!
You know why Piripero looked you over?
To take your measurements.
He is so experienced he can do it
with a glance. You will be a customer.
- Hm.
- Don't laugh. I'm not joking.
I wanna warn you those murderers
will make a corpse out of you one day.
That's why I want you to get out of here.
You don't want to stay in this cemetery,
Finish up and get out.
I told ya I can't pay ya.
Be my guest.
But get out of San Miguel, will you?
- Where does that lead?
- The balcony.
- Why are you going there? Hey!
- Uh..
To have a look. Things always
look different from higher up.
But nothing's up there.
Go ahead and get out.
- Who are they?
- Hm. Bandits.
Bandits and smugglers.
They come down from Texas, cross the
frontier to stock up on guns and liquor.
The cost is less here. Then they go back and
sell the guns and liquor to the lndians.
Any town that sells guns
and liquor gotta be rich.
Not the town.
Only those who buy and sell.
The bosses are the ones who clean up.
Yeah, somebody has to run the place.
Every town has a boss.
That's true, but when there are two,
then I'd say that there is one too many.
Two bosses? Very interesting.
Interesting is right. The Rojos boys,
three brothers who sell liquor.
And then there's the Baxters,
big gun merchants.
Ah, if I'm not mistaken, you already
met Baxter's gang, didn't you?
- Yeah, we met.
- But you're lucky.
They don't usually limit
their fire to the mule.
A man leaves his land
and looks around for any reason,
Juan de Dios tolls the bell,
Piripero sells another coffin.
Two bosses.
They've enlisted all the scum that hangs
around both sides of the frontier.
And they pay in dollars.
Baxters over there.
Rojos there.
- Me right in the middle.
- Where you do what?
Crazy bell-ringer was right.
There's money to be made
in a place like this.
If you're thinking what I suspect..
l tell you, don't try it.
- Which one of the two is the stronger?
- Which one of them is stronger?
Well, the Rojos, especially Ramón.
Don Miguel Rojo, I wanna talk to you.
Don Miguel, I hear you're hirin' on men.
Well, I might just be available.
I gotta tell you before you hire me..
I don't work cheap.
- Get three coffins ready.
- Huh?
- Adios, amigo.
- Listen, stranger, didn't you get the idea?
We don't like to see bad boys
like you in town. Go get your mule.
You let him get away from you?
See, that's what I wanna talk about.
- He's feelin' real bad.
- Huh?
My mule. You see, he got all riled up
when you fired those shots at his feet.
Hey.
- Are you makin' some kinda joke?
- Oh, no. No.
I understand you were just playin' around.
But the mule, he just doesn't get it.
Of course, if you were to all apologise..
I don't think it's nice, you laughin'.
See, my mule don't like people laughin'.
He gets the crazy idea
you're laughin' at him.
Now, if you apologise,
like I know you're going to,
I might convince him
that you really didn't mean it.
I saw the whole thing.
You killed all four of them.
You'll pay, all right.
You'll be strung up.
- Who are you?
- Don't fire a shot.
I'm John Baxter. Sheriff.
Yeah. Well, if you're the sheriff,
you better get these men underground.
My mistake. Four coffins.
Hey!
I told you I wasn't cheap, but I think
you'll find it's worth your while.
98, 99, 100.
The rest when you're all done.
When do I start?
I'm not in a hurry, at
least for the moment.
I'd say with four less Baxters, right
now is as good a time to start as any.
In a few days there will be
a troop of cavalry passing through,
and I wouldn't want the military sticking
their long noses into our business.
You seem to be well-informed.
In these parts, a man's life often
depends on a mere scrap of information.
Hm.
This thing couldn't have been
very useful to its owner.
My brother Ramón did that.
He often uses it for target practice.
With a gun in his hand,
no one stands in his way.
The armour is one of
his favourite targets,
naturally, when he does not have
anything better to shoot.
Well, I'll be kinda curious
to meet this brother of yours.
Ah.
This is Chico,
one of the most trusted of my men.
Follow him.
He will bring you to your room.
I would like you to feel at home.
Well, I never found home that great,
but let's go.
- Who's that?
- Her name is Marisol.
You just forget about her.
This one will be your room.
You gave him $100. We've never
paid out as much as that before.
Can you explain why
you have taken him on?
To have a filthy gringo around,
and to give him $100 besides?
- We have never paid anybody so much.
- You cannot leave someone like that
to do what he wants here. He is capable
of anything, and I want law and order.
If that is all you want,
there is a much cheaper way.
Just snuff him out.
- And who will be the one? You?
- Yes. Why not?
A shot in his back and then you would
have him out of the way in no time at all.
Listen, I could do it easily right now.
He won't be expecting it,
and I'd get back the hundred.
You are stupid, Esteban.
Even if you are my brother.
A bullet in the back and it is ended.
What happens if your hand should tremble
slightly and he's only been hurt?
With the cavalry arriving in town,
and that Yankee so quick on the draw..
- But I was only thinking..
- You mustn't think!
You let me do the thinking instead.
Go and see the americano. Just ask him
if he needs anything and make friends.
Get one thing clear. This is going to be
a quiet town until Ramón gets back.
Is that clear? A quiet town.
I am Esteban Rojo.
My brother asked me to..
What are you doing?
Moving.
But didn't you know
all our men live here with us?
That's all very cosy, but, uh,
I don't find you men all that appealin'.
Besides, your brother said he didn't
have any need for me any more right now.
Halt!
- Sergeant.
- Yes, Capitán?
Tell the men we'll be
spending tonight here.
Arrange so they can pick up the supplies.
Double the guard
to watch the stagecoach.
Yes, sir.
What do you suppose they're carrying?
It would be easy to find out. Get up
close and take a look at what's in it.
If they fire at you, you know it's gold.
Not a bad idea.
Hm.
Looking for anything?
Hello.
Get out of here, Yankee. Vamoose.
Why aren't you sleeping?
When I see you staring like that,
it bothers me.
I still keep wondering
what was in that stagecoach.
It's something they seem
to think is very important.
I asked a few questions of the captain
and almost was arrested.
Who's Marisol?
You'd better get some sleep. You need it.
It's much too dangerous, even for you.
All I did is ask who she was.
She is a woman.
Ramón's madly in love with her.
Does that make it clear to you?
Mm.
Everybody in this town
talks about Ramón.
I'm curious to meet him.
If you're smart, you'll try to stay
clear of Ramón as long as possible.
Ah!
There are the soldiers.
They're moving on very quietly.
Strange. They're headed for the frontier.
Tell me..
is that the way you go to bed every night?
Don't worry. I didn't dirty the sheets.
Oh, no, wait. I'm coming, too.
I want to see for myself
how you're going to get in trouble.
All right, all right. Go ahead.
It's like playing cowboys and lndians.
- Captain.
- Welcome, Lieutenant.
There is your gold as promised.
I hope the guns you will be
giving us will be equally useful.
Rest assured, Captain.
We'll check 'em over together.
Get their clothes on again, and hurry.
Be sure to place them right.
They died fighting among themselves.
Rubio!
There. It's Ramón.
This is my brother Ramón.
- I think I mentioned him.
- Everybody talks about Ramón.
And many speak of you, too.
My dear brother included.
Well, I hope they say.. nice things.
Did you have a good trip?
It was tiring. It was terribly hot
on the road during the day.
And stagecoaches are
an uncomfortable way to travel.
Well, I'm sure you'll be
in great shape in no time.
The americano cannot wait
to get into action.
- I'm sorry. He's going to be disappointed.
- How's that?
The Baxters accepted the invitation.
They'll come tonight, Don Miguel.
You must be out of your head.
Chico followed my orders.
I told him to invite them.
Ramón, what is this?
I found out many things when I was
travelling and I have decided that..
it's very stupid to just keep on shooting
at each other, and without any results.
You've gone out of your mind, Ramón.
No, I've come to my senses, Esteban.
Believe me.
Trust me.
Life can be so precious.
It's foolish to risk losing it
every minute, no?
There's plenty of space for everybody
in this town. Even Baxters, hm?
For this reason..
I've decided to hang my gun
up on the wall.
I think that Ramón has the right idea.
L, too, am getting tired of these killings.
They must stop.
- This is all.. very, very touching.
- You mean you don't admire peace?
It's not really easy to like something
you know nothing about.
Stay in San Miguel
and you may profit from the experience.
No, thanks. I'll be movin' on.
Oh, here's your money, Don Miguel.
I only used a small amount of it.
I don't like to take money
unless I feel I've earned it.
Now, why are you so hasty?
You should stay here.
You might enjoy dining with us tonight.
You see, the Baxters have four men
in the cemetery on account of me.
I don't think
they'd appreciate my presence.
I don't like that americano.
Too smart to be a hired fighter.
- Shooting a pistol, no one can touch him.
- I see that. When someone with that face
works with his gun, count on two things.
He's fast on the trigger
but he's also intelligent.
- That makes him too dangerous for you.
- Now he's gone, explain that nonsense
about hanging up your gun
and making up with the Baxters.
Is it possible that you'll never be able
to reach any conclusions on your own?
Don't you think our government and
the americanos will find those bodies?
They'll investigate, all right. And we'll
be quiet and peacefully bide our time.
We know nothing about a massacre
at the Rio Bravo, eh?
I arranged for the bodies to be lying
as if both companies killed each other.
But do you think they'll believe it?
Ah, yes, I think so. Because if
they don't find some guilty party,
it would be a good reason
to call off the investigation.
Yes, but.. what about the Baxters?
The Baxters? They want nothing
more than to live in peace.
We'll let them have their own way
for a while. So forget the Baxters.
We'll take care of them later
when the investigation finishes.
That was a fine idea that you had.
What was it again?
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes.
The Baxters on one side,
the Rojos on the other.
And you'd be in the middle.
The only problem is
that they've joined up.
Now you're without a job and you don't
have money to pay me what you owe me.
There is only one thing for you to do.
Leave immediately.
I will forget about what you owe me.
You leave San Miguel and never come
back for the rest of your days.
Hey, Joe! I prepared the wagon
the way you asked me to.
We're sitting in the back here
with two empty coffins.
Hey, what are you up to?
Are you changing your profession?
If you want to go on living, you'd better.
In my opinion,
you will make a fine pallbearer.
- Close this place and come with me.
- Oh, close up, huh? It's done.
Where are we going? I'd like to know
where we are going. Or is it a secret?
Down by the river, to have a look
at some corpses down there.
The Rojos say, "Come to dinner" and
we must go, but I don't like it at all,
even if they've granted
all the guarantees we've demanded.
We'll go along with it,
but don't touch anything.
You mustn't eat. You mustn't drink.
You just keep your eyes open
and keep your wits about you.
Whoa.
Are you sure that nobody has seen us?
Only a ghost or two.
Oh, no, no, no.
Don't joke about things like this.
Ghosts are better left where they are.
You look as though
this place suits you very well.
And if you go on like this,
you will soon be here permanently.
I do not understand why, with all those
bodies, we are just burying these two?
We're not.. gonna bury 'em.
What? We are not burying them?
That's right, we're not gonna bury 'em.
If we are not going to bury them, I would
like to know what we will use them for.
Why are we taking the trouble to do this?
The dead can be very useful sometimes.
They've helped me out
of tough spots more than once.
First, they don't talk.
Second, they can be made
to look alive if I manage it right.
Yeah.
And third..
Well, if you shoot 'em, there's no worry
cos they're dead already. Understand?
It doesn't make sense. I'm getting out.
I want to remain with the living.
When I'm dead, I'll remain with the dead
and I would be unhappy if somebody living
forces me to remain with the living.
I don't like the idea that
you've placed those bodies there.
The man in that grave is the only one
who ever died of pneumonia in this town.
Take it easy, will ya? These friends of
ours are gonna help me pay your bill.
Ah, giddap, there!
The only reason
they could have to start a war
would be to kidnap you
from your husband's side.
He is gallant, this Rojo. I really didn't
think him capable of compliments.
And he's not. All that he says is false,
like his proposals.
Huh! You women. If things aren't
complicated, you become suspicious.
Yes. Because to me
it just didn't seem right.
It went too smoothly. I don't trust them.
You'd like to prove me wrong,
wouldn't you? Always the same thing.
- Goodnight.
Don't worry. I'm not gonna hurt ya.
I just want ya to know why the Rojos
wanna make peace all of a sudden.
There was once a wagonload of gold
the soldiers were takin' to the border.
John! Come up here quickly.
Sorry. When a husband finds
a man in his wife's bedroom,
you're never sure how he's gonna react.
- Give him $500.
- How's that?
Give the money to him. He has an
interesting story. Listen to him.
- That's the right idea?
- I get the wrong idea when it suits me.
- Ramón!
- What?
- The soldiers escorting the gold..
- Two got away.
They're hiding out in the cemetery. The
Baxters, they're about to capture them.
Hey! Rubio!
Get the men.
You are well-informed.
A man's life in these parts often depends
on a scrap of information.
Your brother's own words.
Tell me, why are you doing this for us?
$500.
With these soldiers
as witnesses against Ramón,
the government will rid the town
of the Rojos and their band.
Then San Miguel will have just one boss.
Hurry!
Let's go!
- Coming with us?
- No. When a man's got money
he begins to appreciate peace.
Come on!
Whoa!
Let's leave the horses here.
¡Por Dios!
Who is there? Come out!
- What do you think?
- I don't know.
There's somethin' about it I don't like.
Too still to be wounded,
more like dummies.
Sure. Dummies that are very interesting
to the Rojos. Better hide. Hurry.
- What do we do?
- Take two men. Circle around to the side.
Try to keep them busy long enough
for me to get those two. Go on. Quickly.
Keep me covered.
I'm going to take care of those two.
Listen, Baxter.
You can have them now if you like,
since dead men can't talk.
It seems they didn't like my joke.
We'll let them go home in a little while.
Keep this bad boy as our guest
only until Baxter leaves for the frontier.
Put him in the cellar.
Ah, Esteban, good work.
With Antonio as our prisoner,
the Baxters are going to have to give in.
- Now we can make any kind of demand.
- Don Miguel! Don Miguel!
What has happened? Talk, will you?
I don't know who,
but somebody shot at me.
Marisol!
Where are you, Marisol?!
Strange.. how you always manage to be
in the right place at the right time.
It's nothing serious,
a headache that will pass. She'll sleep.
Keep your eyes open. She's not
to move from that room. You hear?
I wouldn't mention anything
about me bringing her here.
I wouldn't want the Rojos
to think I was on your side.
Don't be worried.
I'm a woman who's rich enough
to appreciate the men
that my money can buy.
I've been to the Rojos.
They'll give back Antonio for Marisol.
It'll take place in the morning.
Very soon, you're going to be rich.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, and that's not gonna
break my heart.
Where is she? You said
I'd be able to see her. Where is she?
- I want to see her.
- Come back here, Jesus.
I want to see her. I want to see her.
Why can't I look at her?
I want to see her!
Go. Go to him, Marisol.
Mama!
- Mama!
- Jesus!
Mama!
- Mama! Mama!
Julio.
Marisol.
Get Julio.
You were warned to get outta town.
Now I'm gonna make you pay,
- once and for all.
- No!
Let him be.
You better get goin'. Ramón's waitin'.
And you, get that kid home
where he belongs.
A pig, that Ramón.
Tell me, what's Ramón
got to do with them?
You weren't told, eh?
In this part of the world, the story is old.
A happy family until trouble comes along.
Trouble has the name Ramón.
Claiming the husband cheated at cards,
which wasn't true, he gets the wife
to live with him as hostage.
- And the husband?
- Oh, him? There's nothing for him to do.
The Rojos threatened to kill his little boy
Jesus, and he was forced to accept things.
That Ramón is smart.
Where are you going?
To the Rojos, to look for a job.
I'm glad we have the americano with us.
It's the best thing
that could have happened to us
cos if either government starts an
enquiry, we'll need every man we can get.
To be at war with the Baxters now is
worse than sitting on a case of dynamite.
- Where should we put this?
- Put it over there.
Come on, everybody. Drink up.
- Good shooting. Very good.
- When you want to kill a man,
you must shoot for his heart,
and a Winchester is the best weapon.
That's very nice,
but I'll stick with my .45.
When a man with a .45
meets a man with a rifle,
the man with the pistol
will be a dead man.
That's an old Mexican proverb,
and it's true.
You believe that?
Paquito, take five men. Escort Marisol to
the small house. Stay there until I return.
- Everything is prepared.
- Do not be worried.
- I will return tomorrow.
- All the wagons are ready. We can leave.
Everyone! Enjoy yourselves
during my absence!
You heard Ramón. Let's have a good time.
? Do you remember
sweet Betsy from Pike?
? She roamed the world with her lover lke
? Ike, Betsy
? Betsy from Pike
- He weighs over a ton.
- Of course, with all he poured in himself.
Papa,
did you not tell me
no one could go see Mama?
- That's right.
- Then why does that man see her
when I cannot?
- I want Mama. I want Mama.
- Come away from the door. Sh. Quiet.
Quiet. We cannot show ourselves. You
must remember that. You must stay away.
Hello.
- Somebody shooting at the small house.
- Saddle the horses immediately. Let's go.
Look out!
Here you are. Take this money.
It's enough to live on for a while.
Get across the border. As much distance
between you and San Miguel as possible.
How may we thank you
for what you are doing?
Don't try. Just get goin'
before the Rojos get here.
Why do you do this for us?
Why? I knew someone like you once.
There was no one there to help.
Now get movin'.
Get movin'.
Get outta here!
What do you see, Chico?
- They're all dead. Massacred.
- They kidnapped Marisol.
The work of the Baxters.
Quick. Let's get back before
they attack our house in the town.
Chico, give out the ammunition.
Esteban, spread your men
around the house. Keep your eyes open.
Miguel, Paco, Vincente, Martin, behind the
house. Manolo and Alvaro, come with me.
Stay alert. The way they killed the men
in the small house, there must be a lot.
It's a warm evening.
One of our wagons lost a wheel
so we had to turn back here to get help.
One of the men tells me..
the Baxters attacked the small house.
Do you know about it?
Tell me what you know.
Well?
Where did you hide Marisol?
Rubio.
You are thirsty? You want to drink?
No, no. It is too soon to drink.
Ooh!
Bring him over here.
You are a stubborn idiot. Tell us
where Marisol is and it'll all be ended.
In a week, you'll be back in shape,
and you can go wherever you want.
That's enough for today.
Sooner or later he'll talk.
It's just a matter of time.
Watch out he doesn't escape or die.
Otherwise, do as you like.
But wait till he comes to.
This way he hardly feels anything.
I have a poker hand waiting for me.
Now I am stuck here
guarding this americano idiot.
I think you will find this more amusing.
All orders are to be sure he does not die,
and also make sure
he regrets the day he was born.
The gringo is asleep, I imagine. That's all right.
I'll enjoy waking him up.
- Esteban, what was that noise?
- I do not know.
I heard a yell and then a crash.
It's useless to hide.
You are finished playing the smart boy.
Go up and look in the loft.
And take a look behind the barrels.
Let's get out of here.
- Hurry! Hurry! Hurry with that water!
- Come on!
Hey, you! Come along with me!
Surround the town!
Block all the streets leading out!
Find him for me!
- Esteban, search the whole town.
- Follow me.
Get him back right now!
You've got to at any cost!
Look in the stables,
in every corral, in the store!
Look for him in the church!
Go in there! Search every inch of it!
Search everywhere! Rubio, in here!
If somebody is hiding him, burn their
house down and kill them like dogs.
You, come here. Look for him near
the Baxters', but take him alive.
I want him alive. Alive!
Rubio.
In the bar.
He says he knows nothing.
Trying to be smart.
Bring him here to me.
- Well.. you know nothing, huh?
- No. I have not seen him.
Rubio, you take care of him.
Where have you hidden him?
L.. didn't.. hide..
You are the right friend
for that filthy americano.
You'll end up the same way.
We looked everywhere.
In the cellar, in the attic, on the roof.
- But there is no trace. - I couldn't
find anybody in the back room.
I'm certain he has taken refuge with
the Baxters. The americano isn't stupid.
He knows that that's
the best place for him to hide.
The Baxters, eh?
Then better go and get him.
And that's for being his friend.
Curse them.
- Piripero.
- ¿ Si?
- Hm?
- Come here.
- I can't see anybody.
- ¡Dios m¡o!
What are you doing in there?
Never mind. Get me outta here.
But you're not dead yet.
I will be, if you don't get me
outta here quick. Get the lid down.
Rubio.
I see some signs of life.
Let's be ready
when they decide to come out.
Don't shoot! We surrender! Don't shoot!
Stop! Don't shoot! We're coming out!
We're surrendering! Hold back your fire!
Don't shoot! We're surrendering!
Stop. I wanna take a look at this.
Ramón! Don't shoot.
We're comin' out.
We surrender. Listen, you've won.
It's enough. I'll get outta town.
I'll do whatever you like.
- You promise that?
- I swear it, Ramón!
- You won't try a trick of any kind?
- None.
No, no tricks. I said before,
I give you my word, we'll leave.
Are you sure? You had better
ask permission of your wife.
Maybe she won't be too happy.
Antonio!
John!
Murderers.
They had no guns!
Murderers! I hope you rot in hell!
May you and your brothers die
spitting blood! Curse you for this!
Murderers!
Let's go. The show's over anyway.
Keep looking for him.
Search among those bodies.
The filthy americano
has to be somewhere.
Silvanito?
Where's Silvanito?
Any news today?
I have to tell you some news that's pretty bad.
I hate to tell you this, but..
Where is Silvanito?
Silvanito, he was captured this morning
by those men of Ramón's.
They grabbed him
on his way to this mine.
He was bringing in some provisions.
Ramón's got him.
He is being tortured, but he won't talk.
I know him well. He's stubborn.
No matter what they do, he won't say
a word, even if it means his life.
Listen to me.
They'll never be able to force him.
Now, old fool, loosen up your tongue.
- No.
- Rubio!
You better get back to your shop, old man.
- You're liable to have business there.
- Very good. That's what I wanted to hear.
And I have a little surprise for you. L
know how much you are going to need it.
It was hard to get my hands on it
but I got it by first using my head.
No one can resist two bottles of wine.
Isn't that right?
Then I thought that, well,
you might need that pistol.
And I brought another present.
It's dynamite. I stole it from the Rojos.
And now it seems to me the moment's
come for you to light the fuse
and send it back to them.
Still lots of light.
Too early to be asleep yet.
Rubio, here.
I shouldn't like to ruin the rifle.
I could never find another like this one.
Listen, Ramón.
Let's try it with this one now.
Gringo!
I heard you wanted to see me.
The americano's dead.
Cut the old man down.
What's wrong, Ramón?
You losing your touch?
Are you afraid, Ramón?
If you shoot to kill,
you'd better hit the heart.
Your own words, Ramón.
The heart, Ramón.
Don't forget the heart.
Aim for the heart or you'll never stop me.
When a man with a.45
meets a man with a rifle,
you said the man
with the pistol's a dead man.
Let's see if that's true.
Go ahead. Load up and shoot.
Hey.
Hey, listen, Joe.
Listen, Joe, I.. l..
Oh, Joe.. Joe..
Well, I guess your government'll
be glad to see that gold back.
And you? You don't want
to be here when they get it, eh?
You mean,
the Mexican government on one side,
maybe the Americans on the other side,
and me right smack in the middle?
Mm-mm. Too dangerous.
- So long.
- Adios.
SubText:
NoRMITA.326