I'm Christopher Frayling
biographer of Sergio Leone.
I'm talking about Leone's
fifth major film
Gíú La Testa Once Upon A Time
The Revolution or Duck You Sucker
The quotation from Chairman Mao
Tse-Tung that opens this film
is important for lots of reasons.
on the wall of those rebelling students
in the university rebellion of May '68 in Paris.
It was almost a sacred text amongst
left-wing students in the late 1960s.
It goes on beyond the words
that are on this card.
The revolution is an act of violence
said Mao
So they slightly pruned it
and the Mao quote wasn 't on many prints
when the film was first issued.
The film opens with someone
urinating over a colony of ants.
This scene too was missing from a lot of prints
when the film was first put out.
It was said by some critics
to be a reference
to the opening of Sam Peckinpah's
The Wild Bunch
which has children with ants
with scorpions
and setting fire to the scorpions
as an image of the anarchy of society
in the borders between
the US and Mexico.
It is in fact a reference to the
childhood of the director Sergio Leone
who grew up in Trastevere
a suburb of Rome
and used to climb some steep steps
with a gang of friends as a kid.
They'd lay plank s on the steps
urinate on the plank s
and see whose urine reached
the bottom of the steps first.
The screenwriter Sergio Donati
and Luciano Vincenzoni
were asked to make reference to this
in the opening scene.
Most international release prints
began with these shots
with Rod Steiger
as the peasant Juan Miranda
looking at a coach
coming along the road.
Rod Steiger wasn 't the first choice
of actor for this film.
The first choice was Eli Wallach Tuco
in The Good The Bad And The Ugly
The part was written for Eli Wallach
but when they looked at the budget
and size of the production
United Artists said they wanted
a bigger actor a prestige actor.
Steiger had won an Oscar in 1968
for his performance
as a Mississippi police chief
in In the Heat of the Night
So he was very hot in the early 19T'Os
so Rod Steiger it was.
Eli Wallach remained very sore
not only that he'd lost the part
but about the way in which it was done.
The coach hurtling along with all
those horses has a big story behind it.
Sergio Leone was
a great antiques collector
in common with his father before him.
His house in Rome was full of
objets d'art from the 18th century
from the Renaissance
and of 20th-century art.
He wanted the stagecoach
in the first sequence
to be the most grand stagecoach
that you'd ever seen.
He got craftsmen in Rome
to make it out of solid wood
he had genuine antique
Louis Vuitton luggage inside it
he had a lavatory inside it
like a Pullman car on a railway.
The biggest stagecoach you've ever seen
to create an impact on the screen.
Everything had to be
larger than life with Leone.
On the first day of shooting the thing
wouldn 't move it was so solid.
They tried two horses four horses
six horses eight horses
and it kept getting stuck in the dust
of the Spanish desert in Almería.
For some shots
they have the horses pulling it
and a tractor behind it
pushing the coach along.
They made a duplicate in light wood
for the action sequences
so this coach would actually move.
That is attention to detail.
Most of the film was shot
in the countryside
between Guadix and Almería
in southern Spain
in the ramblas the dried-up riverbeds
and the roads and the mountains
of that part of southern Spain
a very distinctive topography
of Andalucía.
This line was the first one to be shot
on the first day of shooting.
Steiger who was a graduate of
The Actors Studio in the 1950s
a method actor who believed in
a psychological approach to acting
and finding the motivation
inside himself
walked about a kilometre away
according to Leone
and started walking towards the set
where he was supposed to speak.
He said "My mother is dead."
He says the line over and over
to psych himself up.
All the Spanish technicians
were roaring with laughter.
Usually the words
were dubbed on afterwards
so why bother about
the psychological performance?
There was tension throughout the movie
between Leone's approach to filmmaking
post-synchronisation location shooting
using actors' faces
as part of the design
and Rod Steiger's philosophy of acting
which is find the truth inside yourself
look at the detail try and get
the truth in the first two takes.
Leone went up to
1825 takes with Steiger
to tire him out
to make the performance smaller.
He felt that Steiger was being too big
for this performance.
He also thought Steiger
was too cerebral too intellectual.
The whole point is this is
a simple peasant bandit in Mexico.
The performance had to be
reduced in size because of that.
They settled their differences
and Steiger gives an extraordinary
performance in this film.
The film is set at a very precise moment
in the Mexican Revolution of 1913.
The revolution began in 1911
went through to 1920.
But in 1913 there was
a very particular moment
when the early energy
of the Mexican Revolution
under President Madero
with lots of land reforms
and attempts to democratise Mexico
had gone into reverse
under a man called Huerta.
This film is set in 1913
when Huerta is clinging on to power
and trying to stop the revolution
from happening.
This explains some of the violence
and the cruelty and the decadence
that happens later in the film.
We're looking at the dying embers of
a fascistic regime clinging on to power
but it also explains this sequence
where the peasant
goes inside this stagecoach
this Pullman carriage on wheels and
you see the reaction of the bourgeoisie
who've recently been
dispossessed by President Madero
to the intrusion
of this member of the proletariat.
All sorts of professions
are in the carriage.
You have a cardinal
a landowner a lawyer.
They're about to comment
on this experience
of meeting a real-life peasant
in their sanctuary
inside this well-padded coach.
This sequence is shot like a Sergei Eisenstein
movie in the Soviet Union as we'll see
a collision of shots of people's faces
uncomfortable close-ups
as they say these horrible
racist and derogatory things
about the Mexican peasant
who's just joined them.
Juan Miranda
is an interesting character.
He's very instinctive. He doesn 't seem
to have much of a conscience.
He seems to be out of place
almost everywhere.
In the coach
later on at the town of Mesa Verde
amongst the revolutionaries.
The only time he feels comfortable
and relaxed and in place
is when he's with his extended family
as we'll see
which makes the tragedy
in the middle of the film poignant.
Here begin the Eisenstein -type shots.
It's like an early Eisenstein film
made in the 1920s
a film like Strike or October
or The Battleship Potemkin
where you get these close-ups
of social types
in order to make a point
about the class war
the overthrow of one class by another.
The landowner's wife's name
is Adelita in the film.
She's played by
the Italian actress Maria Monti.
The name Adelita was the name
given by the Mexican revolutionaries
to the heroines of the revolution
the soldaderas who followed the troops
of Pancho Villa and Zapata around.
They were known as Adelita. It was
the name of a revolutionary anthem.
So to give this very reactionary lady
the name Adelita
would have meant a lot to people
who knew about the Mexican Revolution.
There's always a lot of eating
in Leone films.
He himself had a gargantuan appetite
for pasta and Italian food
and there's often a scene
of people eating
but this is the only scene
in Leone's cinema
where the eating is deliberately
presented as disgusting.
Close-ups of the mouths
noises of eating noises of swallowing
the juice round their mouths.
It's deliberately physically repulsive
to represent the attitudes of the people
who are speaking as well.
A critic in Italy said that these
close-ups of mouths eating food
were like a series of close-ups
of unwiped bottoms.
A montage of what they've been saying
these racist patronising and derogatory
comments about Juan Miranda.
And he just sits there
impassive watching.
Adelita is fantasising
about this brutish peasant
in a rather unreconstructed way as
we'll see later on when the coach stops.
There are a lot of aspects of this film
which relate to Leone's early cinema.
The arrival of a vehicle.
In Once Upon A Time In The West and
For A Few Dollars More it was a train.
We'll later have an elaborate bank
robbery the blowing up of a bridge
a kind of duel in a circular space
the killing of a child
and lots of catchphrases
of the two central characters.
These were by now trademark s
of Leone's cinema
but it's a very different film
to Leone's earlier Westerns
for all sorts of reasons.
One he'd fallen out of love
with the traditional West.
After Once Upon A Time In The West
he said "I never want
to make a Western again."
He was only going to produce this film.
In fact he didn 't want to produce it.
United Artists insisted
that he was the producer.
All sorts of people were slotted
to direct it under his supervision.
There was talk of Peter Bogdanovich
who flew over from Hollywood
and stayed with Leone in Rome
to talk through the script
and discuss the direction.
Bogdanovich had just made Targets
But they had some blazing rows.
You can 't imagine two people with
such different philosophies of film.
Bogdanovich the classic movies
of John Ford and Howard Hawk s
a film buff who knew a lot about
Hollywood in the golden age
versus Leone who loved close-ups
zooms elaborate editing
who loved very theatrical effects.
They couldn 't be further apart.
So they in fact had a terminal row.
It took place in Luciano Vincenzoni
the scriptwriter's apartment
and Bogdanovich flew back
to Hollywood.
Then there was talk of
Sam Peckinpah directing this film.
Leone flew over to London
where Peckinpah was
and left with the impression
that Peckinpah might be interested.
He thought what a great idea
for the poster
Sam Peckinpah
and Sergio Leone together.
But that didn 't happen either.
Leone turned to his assistant director
on Once Upon A Time In The West
Giancarlo Santi
who was slotted to direct it
and directed the first day of shooting.
But Rod Steiger and James Coburn
said "We want the real McCoy.
We want Leone to direct this film."
So in the end Santi became
the second unit director on this film
and Leone took over
slightly reluctantly
or so he claimed as director.
So the circumstances of its making
were very different to the other films.
The other important aspect
of the context for this film
is what was happening in
the Italian Western in the late 1960s.
From about '66 to '69 a whole series
of Italian Westerns were made
with very political themes.
They were partly about Vietnam
partly about the Third World
as it was called
and they usually involved
an American or a European
going to Mexico and meeting up with
a peasant bandit the hero of the film.
The focus was no longer the cold
superhero the Clint Eastwood character
but it became the peasant usually
played by a Cuban actor Tomas Milian.
The peasant would eventually be
persuaded to take on the revolution
become a revolutionary
and would either kill or send packing
the American or German mercenary.
These were transparent political
parables of a socialist character.
Leone detested them.
He thought they were preachy
and he didn 't approve of their politics.
He wanted to make a film
about the revolution
which had a completely cynical attitude
towards revolution.
When the Mao Tse-Tung quote came
everyone knew what he was doing.
He was taking this hallowed moment
from student revolution in 1968
and saying "I don 't believe a word of it."
"I have complete cynicism about
that kind of doctrinaire socialism."
Here's a farm with the circular
cobbled threshing yard
like the ones that had appeared in earlier
Leone films as the site for the final duel.
But on this occasion he didn 't want the
settling of accounts to take place here.
He wanted a sordid and vulgar incident.
He wanted to say
"I'm doing something different."
You think Lee Van Cleef and Gian Maria
Volonté are gonna draw their guns here
but we're having Juan Miranda
played by Rod Steiger
in effect raping Adelita
played by Maria Monti
in an extremely vulgar
and off-putting way.
This sequence was missing
from the British print of the film
when it was first released.
of a piece of violence
or a moment of revelation.
You get cock s crowing at
all sorts of moments in Leone's films
at all times of day.
There's a running gag in the movie
about the size
of Juan Miranda's equipment
and how it compares to the size
of Pancho Villa's equipment.
Clearly Maria Monti is impressed.
At one point in reference to
the 1930s Hollywood movie Viva Villa'
with Wallace Beery
about the life of Pancho Villa
Juan Miranda says
"Villa had balls like a bull."
This idea of the bull
runs through this film as well.
The sexual politics are
I'm afraid not very subtle.
There was a cutaway just before this
sequence to the moment afterwards
when the inabitants of the coach
are walking past stark naked.
We were just left to imagine what
might have happened inside this shack.
This is the children the extended
family of Juan Miranda and his father
stripping the coach and the inabitants
ritually humiliating them
and of course
having built up a montage
of their horrible attitudes
towards the peasant bandit
we think they deserve it
that they too are being stripped naked
in the way that they imagined
Juan Miranda was stripped naked earlier.
which recurs later in the film.
It's a mixture of usually
a penny whistle
a banjo or guitar whistling.
It's a kind of march
of the impoverished.
This will recur in a big scene
when they get to Mesa Verde.
The music was written in advance
but because things were so rushed
there was no opportunity
to have it recorded in advance
so it wasn 't played on the set unlike
with Once Upon A Time In The West
but there are references
to the music in the film.
People whistle the main theme
using the internal music
that Morricone specialised in.
So there are references to it
in the movie.
But the music is very different again
to the earlier Westerns.
There's less of it there are more
subtle variations on the main themes
and there's a lot of emphasis
on the singing of Edda dell'Orso
the great soprano...
...whose voice is used
like a musical instrument.
At the very beginning we heard a bang
when Steiger was urinating
on the colony of ants.
Was it thunder?
No it was an explosion.
Now we hear the whistling
the theme of the character
who's about to be introduced to us
the second great character.
If one theme is the Mexican Revolution
and that turning point in 1913 when
things got completely out of control
the second theme is the friendship
between these two characters
and their effect on each other.
On the one hand
a simple peasant bandit
who's instinctive
and isn 't interested in the revolution
and an intellectual revolutionary
from Ireland played by James Coburn
who after contact with the peasant
begins to understand
there's more to life than revolution
and becomes dependent on the peasant
just as the peasant
develops a conscience
and begins to get involved
in the revolution.
So you've got a real relationship
between two human beings
making them develop as characters.
These are no longer the puppets
the icons of the early Italian Westerns.
These are human beings
who learn from each other.
James Coburn enters
not on a horse but on a motorbike.
A lot of the design of this film
was done by Andrea Crisanti
not Leone's usual designer
Carlo Simi
who was busy partly designing offices
for producer Alberto Grimaldi
and partly working on other films.
Andrea Crisanti's brief was to design
a film on the cusp of the modern world.
Horses are turning into motorbikes
pistols into automatic weapons.
There are machine guns
barbed wire armoured cars trenches.
The modern world of World War I
is about to begin.
So the whole design is
what Crisanti called "transitional".
To have one of the cowboys enter
on a motorbike is an example of this.
James Coburn in a long duster
like those worn in
Once Upon A Time In The West
The film was to begin with an animated
sequence behind the credits
which is in the shooting script
where you have a map of Mexico
ringed with flame
and you have Steiger the peasant
ploughing a field
and next to the field
is a trace of white line.
The white line goes down across the map
and it ends up at a detonator.
An animated hand comes into the frame
presses the detonator
there's a huge explosion
and the entire landscape is pulverised.
The peasant comes out look s around
and gets on with his ploughing.
The main title says in Italian
Gíú La Testa
keep your head down
keep out of it don 't get involved.
The phrase gíú la testa
was well-known Roman slang.
Actually gíú la testa coglioni
which I won 't translate. It's very rude.
In France the film was known as
II était une fois la révolution
Once Upon A Time The Revolution
a much better title I think.
In America the film
was known as Duck You Sucker
which Leone thought
was a common phrase in the US
despite the fact that
everyone told him no one used it.
When the film wasn 't all that successful
at the box office first time round
the title was changed to
A Fistful Of Dynamite
to cash in on the success of Fistful Of
Dollars and the other two Dollars films.
The relationship between
the peasant and the revolution
is central to this theme of friendship.
The explosives man
and the instinctive peasant bandit.
James Coburn with his shrug
and his insouciant smile
and his fair colouring
and his laid-back attitude
isn 't everyone's idea of an Irishman
but in this film he plays
an Irishman who's on the run
from the Irish troubles of 1913.
He's an IRA man
and this was an unusual historical slip.
If you're being pedantic
the IRA wasn 't founded till 1919
out of the Irish Republican Brotherhood.
In 1913 it didn 't exist.
But this isn 't the IRA of history
this is the IRA of John Ford's films
of the film The Informer of 1935
a huge influence on
the flashback sequences in this film
and of the film The Quiet Man
made in 1952
for the lush greenery
of the Irish landscape.
The Ireland of this film is the Ireland
of cinema rather than of the real world
just as the Mexican Revolution
in this film
is the Mexican Revolution of Hollywood
of Pancho Villa La Cucaracha
of cactus and crucifixes
Marlon Brando playing Zapata.
That's what Leone's making a film about
the Mexican Revolution of cinema.
Here's the first religious reference.
You always get these in Leone's films.
Steiger imagines that he can rob
the national bank of Mesa Verde
so a halo appears over James Coburn
and an angelic choir sings
to a church organ
because he sees that this man
will help him rob the bank.
Bank is associated
with the Holy Grail in this film
and lots of religious references
cluster round that.
There'll be a drawing
in the ruined stagecoach
of an altar with the Virgin Mary
associated with the bank at Mesa Verde.
Later when they get to Mesa Verde
the entire bank will turn in Juan 's mind
into the exposition
of the Blessed Sacrament
with the holy wafer in the middle
It's about the most profane image
in Leone's entire cinema.
The bank is associated
with the holiest of moments
the transubstantiation of the communion.
So in Juan 's mind
money equals religion.
Coburn wasn 't the first choice
to play the Irishman.
As Eli Wallach was the first choice
to play Miranda
the first choice for the Irishman Sean
was in fact Jason Robards.
But it didn 't work out and then the part
was slotted for Malcolm McDowell
the British actor
who'd just made his name in If
about a revolution in a private school
but that didn 't work out.
United Artists wanted two big stars
the Oscar-winning Rod Steiger
and they wanted Coburn
who'd made his name
in a Western in the late 1950s
and The Great Escape and had been
a spy in a series of films about Flint
a spin -off from the James Bond films
in the mid 1960s.
In terms of popular cinema
Coburn was very well known in Europe
so James Coburn it was.
Leone wanted to contrast
the two acting styles the laid-back
and now Juan in Gíú La Testa
in Keep Your Head Down
the peasant bandit who eats a lot
swears a lot
is on speaking terms with God.
He keeps talking to God
like the character Don Camillo
in the famous book s
written in Italy in the 1950s.
He seems to be on speaking terms
with God. He's very vulgar.
He stands against the high culture
of some of the other characters.
Leone's heart was
with characters like this.
He said "You can make movies
about revolution May '68 in Paris
be fashionably socialist
in the Italian Western
but my heart is with the anarchist."
The anarchist who has cynicism
and really doesn 't believe in ideologies.
This is where Leone's heart lies.
Usually associated also with the family.
We know about
Juan 's family background
just as we know
about Tuco with his brother
and Cheyenne with his mother.
There's a background for these people
because Leone's heart is with them.
Italian politics at this time
in the late '60s early 'T'Os
was in something of a mess.
It was a time of polarisation
of the rise of terrorism for the first time
of the far Left and the far Right.
There was six months
when it proved impossible
to form a government in Italy.
Leone got increasingly disillusioned
with the political culture of Italy.
He said "This movie
is saying all the things
I've been let down with
in the way of promises."
The promise after the war
that a new society would be formed
the historic compromise
between the Left and the Right in Italy
the economic boom of the 1960s
didn 't turn into stable politics.
So not only is he reacting
against political cinema
he's also reacting
against the politics of Italy.
He said "When I look at the politics
I'm left with my family
and my anarchic attitude to life."
That was the baseline.
That's partly what this film's about.
The more that Juan gets drawn
into the revolution through Sean
the more he is doomed.
Second religious reference to the bank
in this drawing of the altar.
A little votive altar
put in the stagecoach
to worship at the bank of Mesa Verde
the dream of a lifetime.
Often Leone's characters have a dream
of a lifetime that often destroys them
the most fortified bank in New York
and it destroys him.
There's a similar theme
coming through in Gíú La Testa
A lot of left-wing critics
were upset with Leone's attitude.
They didn 't like this
keep your head down keep out of it
l-don 't-give-a-damn approach
to the revolution.
It wasn 't a fashionable stance.
Many of the left-wing filmmakers
wrote saying that they thought
that by losing his innocence Leone had
moved into waters too deep for him
and that a film on this theme
didn 't do him any credit.
But interestingly Pier Paolo Pasolini
a socialist and at the height
of his powers as a filmmaker
said "Leone is incapable
of making an uninteresting film."
"This is one of the most
interesting films he's made."
There's an increasing seriousness
an interest in human beings
and less of an interest in the idea
of the movie as a puppet show.
Still an interest in the surreal.
They're sitting in the Almerían desert
on antique furniture
with Louis Vuitton luggage lying around
an extraordinary juxtaposition
the Almerían wilderness and all these
symbols of bourgeois respectability.
A heated discussion about this film was
whether it should be post-synchronised.
Steiger didn 't want to post-synchronise
his dialogue. He said
"I like my dialogue
to come out of me as I'm acting."
"You're taking away
half the performance."
Leone said "Yeah
but we want to be noisy on the set
and there's aeroplanes from Madrid
airport so can 't we post-synchronise?"
So Steiger isn 't post-synchronised
for the dialogue-only scenes
but he is during the big action
sequences and the explosions
because they couldn 't record
his dialogue at the same time.
This is the first non -post-synchronised
performance in Leone's cinema
because Rod Steiger
absolutely insisted on it.
Sean the Irish for John.
So he's Juan and the Irishman is John.
Both John.
The first flashback.
As Sean remembers his time in Ireland
before he left for Mexico.
His friend on the left played by
the New Zealand actor David Warbeck
and an Irish colleen on the back seat
played by the actress Vivienne Chandler.
These locations
for the outdoor scenes in Ireland
were done in County Wicklow in the
Sally Gap and the Glendalough Valley
the lush greenery of Wicklow in Ireland.
The soaring soprano voice
of Edda dell'Orso for Sean 's theme.
Originally
there weren 't to be words to this theme
but at an early stage standing round
a piano in Ennio Morricone's flat
Carla Leone Mrs Sergio Leone
said "Why don 't you put words to it
and say Sean Sean Sean?"
So you have James Coburn 's name
woven into the lyric of the song
the first time there'd been
a lyric with a point to it
in a Morricone theme for a Leone film.
The lyrics in the Westerns had been
completely incomprehensible.
There's a triangular relationship
between these Irish buddies
and the girl on the back seat.
Again transformation of technology.
There's a car. The horse has
turned into the horseless carriage
just as James Coburn rides a motorbike.
Nitroglycerine referred to
as holy water
another religious reference
in the iconography of the film.
As a way of signalling the fact
that he was moving in a new direction
as Leone put it this film is set
between the twilight of the American
frontier and the dark night of the city
which would be Once Upon A Time
In America that followed it.
Signalling this changed atmosphere
there are various new people
on the technical side in the movie.
Director of photography
was Giuseppe Ruzzolini
the man who worked very often
with Pasolini rather than with Leone
no longer Tonino Delli Colli who shot
The Good The Bad And The Ugly
The designer as we've heard is
Andrea Crisanti rather than Carlo Simi.
Same editor as The Good
The Bad And The Ugly Nino Baragli
but different actors different key
personnel the other side of the camera.
This is as Leone put it a prelude
to Once Upon A Time In America
Once Upon A Time In The West
was the Western to end them all
about the ending of the frontier.
This is between the frontier and
the rise of the gangsters in the 1920s.
There are lots of references written
into the film quite late in the process
to immigration to the United States
the melting pot.
They talk about crossing the border
to "the land of milk and honey".
Not to do evening classes
or make something of themselves
but because the bank s may be bigger
and more juicy on the other side.
This is the immigrants' dream
of this period the 1910s the 1920s
so the title Once Upon A Time The Revolution
Once Upon A Time In The West
The Revolution In America
Three fairy tales on an epic tapestry
of the story of America
in the first part of the 20th century
and the last part of the 19th century.
James Coburn like Clint Eastwood
persuaded Leone to reduce
the number of lines that he had.
He twigged that he'd be
the strong silent type
and Steiger would be the voice.
In fact Leone treated Coburn as he put it
as a Clint Eastwood with extra panache
attached to his performance.
He found Coburn hilarious
and very professional to work with.
Although Leone and Steiger rowed a lot on set
in fact it was during this sequence
that the row came to a head
with Steiger walking off
in retrospect Steiger said Leone was
one of the best directors of actors
he'd encountered.
So many close-ups so many
great charismatic introductions
you can 't imagine getting
a better push to your performance
than the cinematic style of Sergio Leone.
He said this at a seminar which
Martin Scorsese was present at
which introduced Martin Scorsese
to the work of Sergio Leone.
But on this day they'd worked
till eight o'clock at night
it had been a 13-hour day
and Steiger said "Enough's enough."
"We've been over these scenes.
I'm going back to the hotel in Almería."
Leone said "You do that
and I won 't speak to you again."
Steiger did go back to his hotel in
Almería which was about 15 miles away.
For a couple of days
Leone would only speak to him
through an interpreter or an assistant director
with various messages such as
"Will you tell Mr Steiger to stop
wiggling his ears so much?"
The sounds associated with Juan are
as Ennio Morricone put it
like the stomach rumbling.
It's the stomach.
It's the sound of a hungry peasant.
It's also a sound
of bodily functions and vulgarity
which will be contrasted
with other forms of music.
So Sean gets the whistling
and the Sean Sean Sean.
Juan gets the burping noises
of the bassoon.
The international release print
of this film stopped here
and cut a huge chunk
out of the end of this sequence
and the subsequent sequence
which lost a lot of material
for understanding the story
because we cut from
the explosion of the stagecoach
to Sean who seems to be
the worst for wear
he's been drinking
or he's got a hangover
or there's something on his mind
next to a detonator.
Sean is a self-destructive character.
He's a revolutionary who's
in the process of losing his ideals
and he takes it out on himself.
He's almost suicidally self-destructive
and of course at the end
this does lead to a form of suicide.
But here he's paralytic drunk
next to a detonator in Mexico at night.
We don 't quite know what's going on
except there are figures running around
who are Juan 's children
in this ruined place.
The whole of this sequence was missing.
It was only put back recently.
The wire to the detonator.
Sean has said that he work s
for a German called Aschenbach
who employs him
on behalf of mining interests.
This scene is all about
getting rid of Mr Aschenbach.
Juan wants to get rid of Aschenbach
so that Sean will concentrate on his task
which is to get to Mesa Verde
and rob that big bank.
He doesn 't want any distractions.
It's a strangely callous
and odd sequence.
So the detonator is wired up.
Coburn clearly doesn 't know
what's going on around him.
There's no narrative background to this.
Leone doesn 't give us any clues.
You don 't need to see Steiger
just his shoes and his legs.
That tells you all you need to know.
People are signalled by their clothes.
We now recognise him
by his hat and his shoes.
Juan has less of a conscience.
He's prepared to blow up
whoever's inside there.
It is in fact Aschenbach
and his mine workers
all destroyed.
Coburn has more of a refined sensibility.
But there's no explanation at this stage
of why Coburn was drinking
why he's finding himself paralytic drunk
in this part of the country
and why Juan assisted him
in this explosion.
The characteristic shape of the screen
referred to on three occasions
when a letterbox image appears
within the letterbox image
was part of the Techniscope process
that Leone had used
since his early days of making Westerns
A Fistful Of Dollars a few years before.
It's a poor man 's CinemaScope
a cheap version of CinemaScope
which was very popular
in Italy in the 1960s.
It's great for going in on people's faces
cutting off their chins the top of
their heads and great for long shots.
It had limitations but it became
a characteristic pictorial shape
for this period
in Italian popular cinema.
Later on Juan will carve
a letterbox-shaped hole to see through
when he gets to Mesa Verde.
And on the railway truck they'll
take a slat out and look through it
providing a letterbox image.
So he's drawing attention to the shape
of the screen during the story.
The expletives in the film
were also cut on first release.
Both Sean and John use
the word "fucking" quite liberally
on various occasions.
It's part of the flamboyance
of their relationship.
In 19T'1 this was thought to be too strong
so all references to that word were
excised from the international print.
They've now been put back.
This was where the cut came back in
in the original print in 19T'1
missing out the whole of that digression.
So we went from the stagecoach blowing up
to their riding along the railway line together.
The usual theme of Hollywood movies
about the Mexican Revolution
was of an American journalist
or soldier of fortune
going south across the border
and intervening in the revolution.
and countless popular films about
Pancho Villa and Emiliano Zapata.
What tended to happen
was he was a journalist
or with Robert Mitchum in one film
a soldier of fortune.
The focus of the film was on the American
and Mexico was a place where
a lot of violent things happened
a place of lost ideals of redemption.
In Sam Peckinpah's movies it's where
you go to recover your lost illusions
and drink yourself silly.
So Mexico is a symbolic place.
You cross the border into another land
where things happen to you.
But Leone wants to take Mexico
for Mexico's sake
not treat it as that kind of symbol.
The focus is not
on an American soldier of fortune.
It's on an Irish dynamite expert
and a Mexican peasant.
But he's playing cinematic games.
Just as he refers to Hollywood Westerns
in his Dollars films
he's referring to Hollywood movies
about the Mexican Revolution
and playing with people's expectations.
The third major character
played by Romolo Valli
was in fact a theatre actor in the
1950s who'd run a theatrical festival.
He was trained as a medic and he'd
appeared in two Visconti films recently
in the The Leopard
as the Jesuit priest
attached to the house of Don Fabrizio
played by Burt Lancaster
and in Death in Venice he played
the manager of the Hotel des Bains
on the lido in Venice.
He was a close friend of Leone.
Leone added the medical background
to the character of Dr Villega
as a reference to the fact that Romolo
Valli in real life was a trained medic.
A third acting style.
If Steiger is the method and Coburn
is the traditional Hollywood hero
Romolo Valli comes from a theatrical tradition.
It's very much part of his character.
The character is full of ambiguities
as we'll see.
He's the one who break s under interrogation
and causes a whole chain of tragedies
to follow from that later in the story.
In the Dollars films double crosses
and people being tortured
and the idea of capture and escape
were treated as a joke
as a picaresque fantasy a never-ending
adventure in the style of Don Quixote.
In this film such things have consequences.
When someone's betrayed when
there's violence it has consequences.
There's a seriousness about people's actions
which was completely lacking
from the Dollars films.
There are also lots of references
to subsequent events
in the 20th century in this film.
The pivotal sequence that takes place
in the grotto of San Isidro
is in fact a reference to a very famous
event that occurred just outside Rome
at the end of the Via Ardeatine
in the Ardeatine caves
where the SS which had been based
in the Via Tasso in Rome
went out and as a reprisal for a bomb attack
shot 335 Roman civilians who'd just been
rounded up off the streets.
They were put into a cave and
the entrance to the cave was dynamited.
When the Nazis left Rome in 1945
they hoped no trace of it would be found.
In fact it was dug out shortly afterwards
and it became a major piece of Italian history
the massacre in the Ardeatine caves.
The grotto later on in this film is
a reference to what happened in 1944
just as the ditches in which Huerta's
soldiers massacre people later on
is a reference to the Nazi death camps
with their ditches.
As Sergio Leone said
the ditches and death pits
of Dachau and Mauthausen
were a direct reference at that point.
He even shows an actor at one point
who resembled the young Mussolini
'cause he wanted to make a point
about the fascist regime.
Although this is a film
about the Mexican Revolution 1913
it's also about warfare and cruelty
and the end of fascism and decadence
and redundant violence
as a regime clings on to power at this
particular moment in the revolution.
So it's about the whole of the 20th century.
In The Good The Bad And The Ugly
the concentration camp sequences
referenced the 20th century.
So did the battle of the bridge like
the trenches of the First World War.
There's lots of detail
it's very historically specific
but the setups are also
about other aspects of history
which would have made complete sense
to viewers in Italy in the early 19T'Os.
There's even autobiography.
There's the opening
with the urination competition.
Also in 1944 the resistance
was in the hills outside Rome.
The revolutionary cells of Pancho Villa
referred to later
are very like the resistance movements
when the Nazis
had occupied Rome in 1944-5.
The young Leone desperately wanted
to join the resistance in the hills.
His father Vincenzo Leone
shielded some Jewish families
in order to protect them from the Nazis in 1944.
But Leone's mother
Bice Beatrice wouldn 't let him go.
He was a much-Ioved only child.
A lot of Leone's contemporaries did join
who became directors of films in the 1960s.
Part of the politics
of those 1960s Italian Westerns
is reference to the Second World War.
Now they arrive at Mesa Verde.
The location was Almería station.
It's still there
a wonderful 19th-century construction.
With their suitcases Juan 's extended
family are like a bunch of tourists
arriving at a tourist site in Spain.
Here they are in the waiting room
of Almería station.
The arrival in Mesa Verde.
These are rural people arriving in the city
where all the streets are paved
with gold or they hope they are.
These sequences were filmed
in the town of Guadix north of Almería
in the esplanade in front
of the 16th-century church of Santiago
which has a slope.
It's the old town of Guadix
which was used for lots of sequences
in particular here a wall
against which the firing squad
is shooting various partisans.
So Huerta's regime clinging on to power
against the revolutionary impulse
unleashed by Madero
are shooting left right and centre
in order to hang on.
This is the world that Juan has entered
by coming to Mesa Verde.
It's like a police state.
This scene was based on
a series of archive photographs
that Leone found
of the Mexican Revolution
in an archive near Mexico City
which had been reproduced in book s
of a famous shot of a firing squad
where someone is lighting a cigar
just before being shot
and the next shot is them lying
on the ground in their civilian clothes
having been shot by the firing squad.
Here's the letterbox reference
the first of them.
So Juan look s through the poster of
the governor and sees what's going on.
A letterbox within a letterbox.
Bernardo Bertolucci said this was
one of his favourite moments in the film
because it draws attention to the artificiality
of the shape of the image.
This is the bank in Mesa Verde
with the showing of the
Blessed Sacrament over the door
with the host in the middle
with church organ music.
This is the Holy Grail.
All the book s about Leone
and people at the time
said this was located in Burgos in Spain.
I went to Burgos and I couldn 't find it.
It isn 't located in Burgos.
Andrea Crisanti built the whole square
including the bank
and the cafe to the left as a set.
It was the square of Medinaceli in a
small village near Guadalajara in Spain.
It was a deserted village
occupied only by a colony of painters.
They built the central square
of Mesa Verde around it.
So this place doesn 't exist.
It was built to Andrea Crisanti's design.
They bought lots of fixtures and fittings
from markets in Madrid
and tiles and mosaics
and decorated the set
to make it look authentically Mexican.
The sound of motors in the background
a new sound in Leone's cinema.
He'd been used to horses' hooves
gunshots and the cocking of rifles.
But now we have the sound of lorries
and armoured cars
and more modern locomotives
and automatic weapons.
It's a different kind of sound in the
background to the story of the heroes.
Here's Sean having another drink
as we saw him having a drink
when killing Aschenbach.
Sean is luring Juan into this idea
of robbing the bank of Mesa Verde
as we discover for his own purposes
and Juan is taking the bait.
A second reference to Ireland
where Sean 's friend
the David Warbeck character
is distributing leaflets in Ireland
before Sean and friend left.
This sequence was filmed
in Toner's pub in Dublin which is still there
and is one of the more traditional pubs
of Dublin that's survived.
It's sacred turf for Leone buffs.
They have a drink there
when they're in Ireland.
The locations were found
by Sergio Leone
with help from John Boorman
the film director
who lives outside Dublin and had
made Point Blank and Deliverance
two favourite Leone films.
So Boorman located the pub
the landscapes in County Wicklow
where the rural scenes
of the flashback s were shown.
to the Westerns of John Ford
in particular those starring John Wayne
films such as Stagecoach
and The Searchers
so in this film there are references
to John Ford's two Irish films
The Informer which was run
during the writing of the film
and also The Quiet Man in the 1950s.
The script started life as a remake
of Ben Hecht's script for Viva Villa'
Leone thought he'd buy the rights
to this and remake Viva Villa'
he had a lot of time for that script
with Toshirô Mifune who played
the samurai in Yojimbo for Kurosawa
and also appeared in The Seven Samurai
playing the part of Pancho Villa.
So it started out
as a remake of Viva Villa'
Then Sergio Donati by now one of
Sergio Leone's regular scriptwriters
came up with this treatment about
an IRA man and a Mexican peasant
and the relationship between them
as a riff on the kind of political
movie being made in Italy at the time.
They worked on it together
on Once Upon A Time In The West
in the spring of 1968 and refined the story.
Then Donati wrote it as a script
by the late '60s
at which point Leone handed it
on to Luciano Vincenzoni
who added the more humorous moments.
Social comedy was very much his forte.
Then the script went back to Donati
for the final polishing-up.
So it was a script by Sergio Donati
with additions by Luciano Vincenzoni.
It's interesting that it started out
as a remake of a Hollywood movie.
Leone was getting big ideas.
He announced in 1969 that he was
going to remake Gone With The Wind
It showed the extent his ambition.
His films were getting bigger and
bigger more and more expensive.
So the gestation of this film was odd.
Leone wasn 't to direct it
the script had turned into something
different to what they started with
the music wasn 't written very far in advance
and they were actors that
Leone wasn 't used to dealing with.
But there's a maturity about the film
suggesting that it had been
on Leone's mind for a long time.
He claimed that
when he took over as director
he only had about a week
to get things together
but clearly he'd been
thinking about it for six months.
When he arrived he had every sequence
imprinted in his mind.
No storyboards but he had
an enormous visual memory.
The thing Rod Steiger
remembered most about Leone
was he had an extraordinarily
pure vision in his head.
He'd arrive tell everyone
where to put the setups.
He had an absolutely clear idea
of what he wanted.
They worked long days
and sometimes did 25 takes to get there
but he knew exactly what he wanted in the end.
For Steiger that was one of
the most impressive things about Leone.
Another setting
where Juan doesn 't feel at home
the revolutionary cell under Dr Villega
the revolutionary strategist.
He's a medical doctor
who does a bit of surgery
but he's also
a revolutionary strategist.
The idea of the revolutionary cell
the revolutionary programme
had been part of a lot of
celebrated Italian movies in the 1960s
including Gillo Pontecorvo's
The Battle Of Algiers
was written by Franco Solinas
who went on to write
either the story or the treatment
for a whole series of political Italian
Westerns in the mid to late 1960s.
The revolutionary cell
was usually treated with reverence.
This was where strategy was planned.
It was a chance to talk about socialism.
In this the point is
that Juan is completely out of place
and doesn 't quite know why he's here
and why are we listening to this?
Juan isn 't a revolutionary.
He's had no contact with the revolution.
He says keep your head down
and so does Sean
so why are we hearing about this strategy?
It's to build up the character of Villega
but it's also to show how
Juan is perhaps beginning to think
that there's more to this revolution
than meets the eye.
Juan think s he's attacking the bank
because of the money in it
something he's dreamed about for years
but the revolutionary cell has different ideas.
Something else going on
in the bank serves their interests
which is why they're using Juan
quite mercilessly
to achieve their objective for them.
Romolo Valli would have been
remembered by Italian audiences
as appearing in the two big Luchino
Visconti films of the mid to late 1960s.
There's an interesting relationship
between Leone's and Visconti's cinema.
Visconti interested in detailed production design
in a peepshow view of the past.
Layers of historical accuracy
in The Leopard to look at an estate
run by the aristocrat Don Fabrizio
in the 19th century.
In Death In Venice
the decadence of Venice in the off season.
Incredible period detail.
That they have in common.
There's a scene in
Once Upon A Time In The West
of Claudia Cardinale lying on her bed
shot from above by Tonino Delli Colli.
The camera comes down through
the lace netting of the four-poster bed
and changes focus
and goes onto Cardinale's face
which is very similar to a shot in The Leopard
where Cardinale also appeared.
Bernardo Bertolucci once said of Leone
that he's like Visconti only
he's coming at it from a different angle.
There's the sense of mise en scéne
of design of opera that the two share
but with Leone it's a Roman
petit bourgeois approach
and in the case of Visconti it's
an aristocrat looking at the past of Italy.
I would argue that although Visconti
is much revered as a filmmaker
Sergio Leone was a much better storyteller.
Visconti didn 't have that common touch
of how to tell these stories
in a way that kept the audience interested
and told these popular stories.
Visconti felt as if he was slumming it
when he made films whereas Leone loves it.
He loved the movies and was
a movie man from his fingertips.
Leone once said
"I was born in the cinema almost."
Aged 12 he visited Cinecittá studios
to see his father
Vincenzo Leone make a movie.
And Leone died in 1989
while watching a movie on television
called I Want to Live' with Susan Hayward
as his heart packed up.
His life was book-ended by cinema.
He was the most cine-literate man
you can imagine.
He could describe whole sequences
of Hollywood movies.
That is not something Visconti could say.
He didn 't have that cinematic culture.
So I'd argue against all the critics
that Leone was the better storyteller
one of the greatest filmic storytellers
to have come out of Europe
in the 20th century.
The toy train with
"Johnny & Johnny" written on it
is another Leone favourite.
Very often in Leone's films you have
characters playing with toy devices
which play a part in the plot.
El Indio in For A Few Dollars More
with the toy safe from El Paso.
Mr Morton in Once Upon A Time
In The West with the toy train
explaining how he's trying to lay track s
right across America.
Here a toy train is pulled in front of the bank
as a decoy for the explosives
to blow the entrance of Mesa Verde.
Sean knows why so many soldiers
surround the bank but Juan doesn 't.
In the background some of the tiles
purchased by Andrea Crisanti
as set dressing to give
a sense of early 20th-century detail
to this café on the corner
of the square in Mesa Verde.
The design is different to Carlo Simi.
It's less larger than life less over
the top than Simi's Western towns.
There's more realism in the backgrounds.
It's a different approach.
Andrea Crisanti had designed films
for Francesco Rosi
who was a friend of Leone and this was
his big breakthrough as a designer.
He's gone on to design
some very distinguished productions.
The March of the Beggars again
played on a flageolet
bassoon and military drums
as Juan and extended family
go into the bank in Mesa Verde
to make their dream come true
or so they think.
With these belching noises.
These are the hungry peasants.
There's a wonderful moment in this music
where these vulgar sounds
of stomachs rumbling and belching
are juxtaposed with Mozart
from Eine Kleine Nachtmusik
to mock classical music
in the way that Juan Miranda might.
It's a wonderful wordless sequence
as the march builds up
and Juan raids the bank
and slowly realises what's going on.
The sequence was based on a sequence
in Charlie Chaplin 's Modern Times
Chaplin being a great hero for Leone
where Chaplin pick s up a red flag
without realising what it is.
He starts walking and an entire workers'
demonstration has formed behind him.
That's exactly what's happening here.
Juan has broken into a political prison.
The vaults of the bank
have been turned into cells.
Slowly he begins to realise it.
A wonderful fusion
of Morricone's music and the image.
Where's the money?
This isn 't what he imagined at all.
Mozart.
Stomach noises meet Mozart.
An extraordinary version of the carnival
approach to culture Leone so often used
at the expense of classical music
rather than the classic Western.
This is a carnivalesque scene
as the carnival has its revenge.
Wonderful range of expressions
on Steiger's face as he realises what's going on.
His dream of a lifetime
is being shattered.
Organ added to the
March Of The Beggars to give it body
with the military drum.
He's now in the vaults of this cathedral
as he saw it of Mesa Verde.
What does he find in the cathedral?
Not the Holy Grail.
He's become a revolutionary
without realising it
just as Chaplin did when he picked up
the red flag in Modern Times
Is this going to be the vault
with the gold in at last?
There's 150 political prisoners now
standing there in the corridor
just waiting to get out.
Instead it leads out into the street
and he finds himself
in the middle of Mesa Verde again
being treated as
a huge revolutionary hero
for having taken the prisoners
out of their prison.
It is the most cynical thought
that this great hero of the revolution
did it by mistake and really
doesn 't want anything to do with it.
If the music is an integral part
of that sequence so is the editing.
Nino Baragli the editor who'd gone
back to the Dollars films with Leone
and Leone would sit in those days
in a Moviola suite agonising for days and days.
The editing of this film took a long time.
Leone referred to it subsequently
as a very difficult edit.
They'd sit there counterpointing
the music and the image
the dialogue and the image.
The cutting of the celluloid
was incredibly important to Leone.
A technical breakthrough
made his job easier.
He could look at the rushes
of what he'd just shot on video
which he'd never been able to do before 19T'1
so he could assemble the shots in his
mind at the time he was shooting them.
Before he had to wait until
they came back from the laboratories.
But the editing and the sound editing
is incredible.
People always reminisced about Baragli
Morricone and Leone
sitting in the editing suite putting
layer upon layer of sound onto this.
Movies in Italy were like a blank canvas.
Most of it was post-synchronised.
So you could put all sorts of sounds on
afterwards and create another reality.
Natural sounds musical sounds
amplified sounds.
The laying of the different levels of
sound was very important to Leone.
Now we cut to another reference
to the modern world.
A strange German armoured car
in the Mexican desert.
At the helm of the armoured car
a general Günther Ruiz
who look s just like
a Nazi tank commander
a panzer division in 1913
in the Mexican Revolution.
There's usually
a historical justification of sorts.
This was the most advanced
armoured car around in 1913
and Leone was keen to make reference to it.
Also the horses are wearing goggles
because of the dust in the desert.
You don 't often see horses
wearing goggles in any movies.
This was a tiny detail
that fascinated Leone.
He'd look at archive photos
read book s about the period
and steep himself in these tiny odd details.
Later some of the troops in Mesa Verde
will wear colonial pith helmets
which we normally associate
with the Indian subcontinent.
But he discovered
people wore pith helmets in Mexico
during the Mexican Revolution
of 1910 to the early '20s
and so they find a place in this movie as well.
This sequence
the most serious dialogue in the film
was written very late in the day by Leone
and added to the script of Sergio Donati
and Luciano Vincenzoni.
A debate about revolution between
the man who reads the book s Sean
and the man who can 't read Juan about
exactly what happens in a revolution.
Of course to people in the early 'T'Os
when a lot of book s were coming out
people were talking about revolution
this debate was very timely.
Juan does not like revolution.
This is the key moment in the film
where Juan has let rip
about his attitude to revolution.
Intellectuals run them the peasants die
and the intellectuals stay in control.
Sean starts thinking maybe he's got a point.
Sean a disillusioned revolutionary
on the run from the Irish Revolution
is not entirely convinced himself.
He's reading but he's about to throw
his book in disgust into the mud.
It's a book by the Russian
anarchist author Mikhael Bakunin.
An unusually bad translation.
It says The Patriotism
It should be
On Patriotism or Patriotism
Sean has thrown
the anarchist's book into the mud.
It's picked up subsequently by a soldier
who takes it to the captain...
...who takes it to the colonel
in his armoured car.
A wonderful visual link
with that conversation
about people who read the book s
versus those who don 't.
The colonel is reading the book.
It's a clue there's a revolutionary nearby.
It's like in The Good The Bad And The Ugly
where Tuco finds a cigar stub
and realises Clint Eastwood has been there.
The stub is still alight so he's getting close.
The Bakunin book in the mud shows the colonel
he's on the scent of this revolutionary
who's giving him trouble.
This bridge set in a valley built of stone
designed by Andrea Crisanti
was in fact about five kilometres away
from the standing set for El Paso
designed by Carlo Simi for
For A Few Dollars More in the hills.
Five kilometres winding track up
into the hills of Almería.
It's still there what's left of it
as are the two gun emplacements
occupied by Coburn and Steiger
as they set up their machine guns.
No one's troubled to erase them since.
Leone said "There tend to be
big explosions in my films."
There was a big explosion when the bank
is blown up in For A Few Dollars More
A huge explosion when
the battle of the bridge took place
in Good The Bad And The Ugly
Here's an explosion to end them all
but unlike in the other films
the music which accompanies it
is played against the image.
This isn 't exciting action music
to get the audience all whipped up
to give a sense of scale to the explosion.
This is romantic lyrical music
that's going to come in
because the explosion reminds Sean
of when he still believed in revolution.
An interesting use of music with action
not to punctuate it
not to reinforce it not to emphasise it
but to play against it
and that'll be part of this sequence.
There's a cluster of references in this idea
of a soldier of fortune from overseas
coming to fight in a revolution.
It relates to the work of Joseph Conrad
an explicit source for the screenplay
set in the Spanish Civil War where
Gary Cooper as a soldier of fortune
finds himself in the Spanish Civil War.
It's not just movies about the Mexican
Revolution he's touching base with
it's also movies about the Spanish Civil War
and versions of Joseph Conrad.
Why is Juan staying
when the odds look so bad?
An entire division of troops
is coming across the bridge
and there's just the two of them
at these gun emplacements.
He seems to have been machoed into it
by the James Coburn character.
He feels he won 't be treated as a man
unless he takes part in this action.
So it isn 't yet a revolutionary act.
He's not staying because
ideologically he wants to fight
the Nazi tank commander
the troops of Huerta.
He doesn 't want to do that.
It's personal between him and Sean.
He's been machoed into doing it.
A lot of the references to America
in the script were added at a late stage
when Leone took over
the direction of the film
and explicitly wanted to sew into it
a trailer for Once Upon A Time In America
Already Leone was working
on his great gangster epic
which he first read as a book in 196T'.
The project was gestating in his mind.
He sewed into this film various
references to going to America.
The people involved in the teams
in the Mexican Revolution
could have got involved in city America
in the 1920s as gangsters.
It's like a missing piece
between the Wild West
and Once Upon A Time In America
a film he wouldn 't in fact make
until the early to mid 1980s.
Here's the macho bit. Juan is saying
"Are you calling me not a man?"
Without saying anything Sean simply
look s at him with withering glances
Juan persuades himself to stay on
this suicidal self-destructive mission
against the forces of Huerta.
Sean is constantly dicing with death
and enjoying himself far too much
when it comes to these scenes.
He really doesn 't see
much point in living.
As he says later
"At one point I believed in revolution."
"Now all I believe in is dynamite."
Another conversation with God
like Don Camillo
the village priest who chats with God
in the book s by Guareschi
which were written in the 1950s
and have been huge bestsellers in Italy.
This country priest who chats to God and
crosses the path of the communist mayor
in the same way that Juan crosses
the path of the Irish ideologue Sean.
Leone reminisced that
when he worked with Clint Eastwood
Eastwood would go to sleep on the set
or put his hat over his eyes and snooze.
When the moment came to appear
on the set he'd dust himself down
get up and give a wonderful performance
as The Man With No Name.
That's what Coburn 's doing.
He seems to be having a snooze
waiting for the big action
the dynamite the explosion
the blowing up of the bridge
and the machine-gunning of the troops.
The distant sound of engines
ricocheting round the valley.
This piece of music by Morricone
which is a very advanced
almost atonal piece of music
relates to musical researches Morricone
had been doing since the 1950s.
He was involved in a group called
the Nuovo Consonanza
which started life in a series
of seminars in the late 1950s
by the American composer John Cage.
The idea of these seminars
was that all sound is music
that it depends on the context
that it's being played in.
So famously John Cage played
a silent piece of piano music
on the stage of a concert hall.
The music became the coughing
the rustling the shuffling of feet
and the eating of sweets in the audience.
All sound is music in the context of the
concert hall like a similar attitude to visual art.
You could put an object in a gallery
and the gallery turns it into art.
A lot of these experiments with music
found their way in a diluted form
into the soundtrack s for the Westerns.
The idea of using concrete sounds
whip crack s and bells and shouting
and incomprehensible lyrics in the main
title themes of the Dollars films.
We have this thunderous metallic music
as the armoured car crosses the bridge
which is like music by Nuovo Consonanza
using instruments in a strange way
and using sound as if it was music.
Morricone explicitly related the
soundtrack of this film and that theme
to his experiments
with the Nuovo Consonanza.
Juan 's not used to
this newfangled technology.
He prefers a traditional pistol.
It's all like all those scenes
in Peckinpah movies
where the Mexican generalissimo
is given a machine gun
The Steiger character doesn 't quite know
what this new machine gun is for either.
The machine guns
are there to pin down the troops
to keep them there so they'll be
in situ when the bridge blows up.
This relates to a whole tradition of
bridge blowing up sequences in movies.
The Bridge On The River Kwai
The Pride And The Passion
The Good The Bad And The Ugly
The Wild Bunch most recently
with the bounty hunters chasing the bunch
falling into the river as they go into Mexico.
There's a whole cinematic tradition.
But what's about to happen
is playing against type
because of the kind of music
that will accompany it
and the size of the explosion
like a nuclear explosion
with the amount of dust
and smoke that it brings.
Strange combination
of costumes and design here.
The heroes not in cowboy hats
but in 20th-century hats
troops in pith helmets
associated with empire movies
a Nazi tank commander in his armoured car
all in the wilderness of Mexico.
There's a lot of strangeness
about the visual language.
Andrea Crisanti the designer
related a lot of this strangeness
to the work of the Italian
surrealist painter Giorgio de Chirico
a favourite of Sergio Leone.
Leone owned two paintings by de Chirico.
De Chirico during the First World War
specialised in paintings of arcades
going back in very sharp perspective
painted under the midday sun with big shadows
and figures in front of them
out of scale with the arcades.
This bridge with the hole in the middle of it
is very like a painting by de Chirico.
So it's like surrealism rides the range.
Giorgio de Chirico out West.
And here comes
the mother and father of explosions.
Bigger than in The Good The Bad And
The Ugly almost like a mushroom cloud.
This romantic music played against it.
We're supposed to be getting
drum beats whipping the audience up
but what we get is a reminiscence
of Ireland the Sean theme - Sean Sean.
Famously in The Good The Bad
And The Ugly the bridge blew up early
in a variation on the
"Ready when you are" Cecil B DeMille gag
where someone blew up the bridge
because they misunderstood an order.
It blew up before they were ready.
This time they got it in one.
It must have taken days
for the dust to settle.
Günther Ruiz or Guttierez as he's
called in some versions of the credits
was played by Domingo Antoine
who also appears as Antonio Domingo
on some versions of the cast list.
So they can 't make up their mind about
his name as a character or as an actor.
But he was chosen for his resemblance
to the ultimate panzer commander.
Here we are at the grotto of San Isidro
where they've agreed
to recce after the explosion.
This is where the references
to the great massacre
at the end of the Via Ardeatine
which happened in 1944
begin to happen.
In the original international print
you saw Steiger's face
and you cut in faces
of lots of corpses around him
including corpses of all his children.
It's much more effective in the restored print
where all you see is Steiger's facial reaction
and we don 't know what he's seeing yet.
We'll only see it through Sean 's eyes
later in the sequence.
Sheer resignation.
His entire family has been massacred
as a reprisal for the explosion.
Whereas the explosion is jokey
in The Good The Bad And The Ugly
and the explosions in the Dollars films
are an excuse for a gag this is very serious.
Yet another action
has had consequences.
The troops get their own back by
massacring the contents of the grotto
just like the Gestapo in the Via Tasso
in the Second World War.
There was a man who served
in the Italian resistance called Cervi
who lost seven sons killed by the Nazis.
He was something of a mythological
figure in the Second World War in Italy.
In the declining days of Nazism as they
were retreating he lost his seven sons.
That's what's happening to Juan.
Another reference
to the Second World War in Italy.
Which in the early 'T'Os
was still well in living memory
and part of the folk culture
of the Italian audience going to the cinema.
And so Juan takes off his crucifix
look s up to God
with whom he's been having
conversations throughout the film
puts his hand round his neck
and removes his crucifix.
This is the absolute
moment of truth for him.
This is no longer a game between him
and Sean as to who can be more macho.
And Sean realises that
by drawing Juan into the revolution
he's been the cause of such terrible grief.
So he too has a conscience.
It was all a game in Mesa Verde
to get Juan to break into the bank
to spring the political prisoners
but this isn 't a game any more.
The reprisals have started happening.
But we haven 't seen what it is he's looking at.
We have to imagine it at this stage.
The way in which
the massacre is revealed to us
is a world away from
the Italian Westerns of 1965-9
against which Gíú La Testa was reacting.
In those films you tended to have
a Mexican peon Tomas Milian.
or Professional Gun by Sergio Corbucci
or Compañeros by Corbucci
or A Bullet For The General by Damiani
the peon figure would be a bandit
who goes through a simple epiphany
and becomes a revolutionary
so at the end he represents
the wretched the dispossessed peasants.
It's a very simple equation.
But in this one the subtlety
the modulated journey that Steiger goes on
in converting him to the revolutionary
cause or stoking up his cynicism
is a very complex journey
and is really in a completely different universe
to the Italians Westerns of the late '60s.
This is Leone's most mature film
so far in every way.
The critics picked up on this
when they wrote about it.
With this movie Leone lost his innocence.
The Left didn 't like it.
Some people liked it a lot.
It didn 't go down well in France because
it was rude about the generation of '68
the children of Marx and Coca-Cola
who had put up the barricades
in Paris in May 1968.
They didn 't like that.
But now we can see what it was
that upset Juan so much.
Amongst all these people are
his six children all from different mothers.
I never counted them before.
The sound of machine gun and gunfire
on the soundtrack not justified.
We don 't know what's going on outside.
It's a kind of musical use of gunfire...
...to accompany
the wandering camera in the grotto.
Leone at this time
where most Italian critics were concerned
with a few exceptions was treated
as a prophet without honour in his country.
Visconti Bertolucci Pasolini
Francesco Rosi Rossellini
they were the greats
the maestri of Italian cinema.
Leone was of a different order.
He'd been brought up in Rome.
His father was Neapolitan.
He belonged to southern Italian
popular culture.
He wasn 't the kind of filmmaker that
showed their movies at film festivals
in the north and in Europe
the kind that got all the prizes
in Berlin Venice London and Cannes.
He wasn 't that sort of character.
So he was rather patronised
by most Italian critics.
They couldn 't forgive him
for not making movies about Italy.
All his movies are set in the past in a
different era and they're movies about movies.
They're movies made by a cineaste
which crossed the line.
They're art films for a popular audience.
That confused everybody.
There's an art-film element
but Leone had his finger on the pulse
so they're extremely popular films.
Critics couldn 't understand this person
who straddled both those worlds
who had references to Italian paintings
and avant-garde Italian music
and all sorts of cultural references
in his movies
but at the same time made rip-roaring
action movies that everyone could enjoy.
So his reputation in the early 'T'Os...
I started writing about Leone in 1968.
Most people thought I was mad
making any claims for his significance.
All my friends went to see the movies
and said "We don 't get it."
"The design 's interesting
but these are just rot-gut Westerns."
It's taken 2030 years
for Leone to establish his reputation.
He's now treated by everyone
as one of the great Italian filmmakers.
There are retrospectives exhibitions
and book s about him.
It's a huge change in his critical reputation.
He's now amongst the maestrí,
but it took a long time.
When I was trying to get a festival
of Leone films in the '60s
the Italian embassy in London
sent this curt letter
saying they didn 't consider Leone was
a good advertisement for their culture.
If I wanted to do a season of Bertolucci or
Pasolini or Visconti fine but not Sergio Leone.
He was a Western filmmaker
and that wasn 't respectable.
But that's all changed
and now he's very respectable indeed.
This firing squad sequence in the rain
it's quite clear that Dr Villega
has been tortured
and that under torture he's broken
and he's started naming names.
There's a kind of treachery treason
that's going on here.
The whole of this sequence
was based on another painting
one of Leone's favourite paintings
that was housed in the Prado in Madrid
which he used to go and see in between
shooting the Dollars films in Spain.
It's by Goya the Spanish artist.
It's called the 3rd of May in Madrid.
It was painted in 1814 and it depicts
the soldiers of Napoleon 's army
with the firing squad shooting
at a Spanish patriot in a white shirt.
Leone referred to it
as a CinemaScope shoot-out.
It was even backlit he said.
It was as if a movie art director
had set up a sequence
set in the Peninsular War in 1814.
Giuseppe Ruzzolini and others were
shown a reproduction of Goya's painting
before shooting this sequence
which is directly derived from it.
The rain is not just the weather it's tears.
There was a sequence shot
of Villega being tortured
in the form of shadows on the wall
as he was strapped to a chair
like the torture sequence of Tuco
in The Good The Bad And The Ugly
only this time it's for real.
But they cut it and made a cut to this sequence
assuming we understand what's going on.
Leone doesn 't like being literal.
He likes the audience to work out
what's going on and here is an example.
So Coburn stands in the rain
looking at the firing squad
looking at the corpses of his fellow gangsters
lying in the street in New York
in a very similar sequence.
In this case lit by the headlights
of the armoured vehicles.
Villega's betrayal here has consequences.
Things that have been treated in
a jokey fashion in the earlier Westerns
The idea of betrayal in history
and Italian cinema went very deep.
Obviously the roots of 1943-4.
Who collaborated with the Nazis? Who didn 't?
Who turned in their friends? Who didn 't?
A famous sequence of Rossellini's film
Rome Open City
showed a man being tortured
by the Gestapo in the Via Tasso
and not breaking under that sort of interrogation.
Now we're back in Dublin in Toner's pub
as the British soldiers bring in
another man who's been tortured
and who is betrayed:
Sean 's friend back in Ireland.
When they were shooting this
Coburn remembers that Leone said
"The drink s are on the house"
and then regretted it
as everyone was blind drunk
and falling off their chairs.
But they're trying to be serious for
this betrayal which Coburn remembers.
Betrayal in the present with
the Romolo Valli character Dr Villega
and betrayal in the past in Ireland before he left.
Is he going to be betrayed?
singing like another musical instrument.
No words but just a tune to represent Sean.
Is he nostalgic or is he bitter?
He's looking at them in the mirror
to see what'll happen next.
Is it him?
And he nods.
But unlike in John Ford's film
The Informer of 1935 Sean isn 't a victim.
The character played by
Victor McLaglen was a victim
who achieves a transfiguration
in the last scene
as he gets forgiven by the mother
of the man he betrayed.
But Sean isn 't a victim he's an avenger.
He's got something on his mind
which will work its way through.
That moment of betrayal
took him to Mexico
gave him his self-destructive attitude
this dilettante of revolution
in the Mexican setting
and everything flowed from that moment.
It's a take on John Ford's The Informer
rather than a rerun.
That scene was entirely without dialogue.
Just music image and lots of rain.
Leone was getting better at dialogue.
He could speak a bit of English.
He started off when he made the first
Westerns just being able to say
"Watch me Clint."
"Watch me Lee." "Watch me Eli."
By now he had a smattering of English
but he never learnt English properly.
He loved watching American movies
which hadn 't been dubbed into Italian
but were subtitled
the sound of the words
and the catchphrases in English.
He wanted to remain an Italian
and have an Italian take on these things.
Everyone noted the fact that he never
really attempted to learn English.
Here we have another firing squad.
Juan has virtually given himself up
after staggering out of the grotto of San Isidro
and thrown himself into the arms
of Guttierez or Günther Ruiz.
Looking up. Is God gonna help him?
Every time he look s up
you know what he means.
There's no salvation there.
This is the moment. He's going to die.
He's curling up his fingers
on his hands
a reference to Leone's hand gesture.
On the set he would move his fingers
into his fists in a nervous gesture
and Steiger decided to use
Leone's hand movement.
He uses it first when the family
arrives in Mesa Verde.
Now he's using it again.
It's the nervous tic of Leone
as he was walking round
making sure that everything
was spick-and-span.
He hears a whistle.
When Peter Bogdanovich
was slotted to be director of this film
he argued with Leone "That phrase
duck you sucker nobody uses it."
Leone said "I'm sure they do.
It's a great American phrase."
They had long arguments about it.
He insisted on calling the film that.
When it came out in the United States
one reason for it not being a success
was said to be the odd title -
Duck You Sucker who says that?
A Fistful Of Dynamite is unsuitable
Once Upon A Time The Revolution
is the best of all.
This sequence of these trenches
with civilians being mown down
by the troops of Huerta
a sequence pruned beyond all recognition
in the original release prints
but has been put back
was shot at a disused sugar factory in Guadix.
The stone ditches where
the sugar beet would be washed.
It's the sugar factory of San Turcuato
just outside the centre of Guadix.
It took Andrea Crisanti's eye to spot
this would be a marvellous location
for the ditches as Leone said
the ditches of Dachau and Mauthausen
which are re-enacted in these reprisals
for revolutionary activity.
Here's a refugee train with everyone
getting out of Mesa Verde.
The railway line was extended from
the depot at Guadix to the sugar factory
in order to get the locomotive in the
same shot as the edge of the factory.
Much of this was cut originally to save time.
The movie was thought to be too long.
Most of Leone's films
had been cut for reasons of time.
A lot of background
to the American Civil War in Texas went
in The Good The Bad And The Ugly
and has recently been put back.
Here a lot of the political background
about Huerta was removed.
Part of the texture of the film
one theme is friendship
another the Mexican Revolution
this theme of the fascistic regime
clinging on to power
and all these random acts of cruelty.
Here's an actor who look s
just like the young Mussolini
who was chosen for his physiognomy.
Leone knew Italian audiences
would recognise him for a moment
which again was cut from the release
print when the film first came out.
These textures these layers these
contexts for everything that's going on
this idea of Huerta's regime clinging on
with all these redundant things.
These people don 't have to die.
This needless cruelty.
It's something that went missing
when the film first came out.
Another reference
to the letterbox shape of the image
like the poster earlier in Mesa Verde.
Steiger is watching all this mayhem
that's going on in Mesa Verde
sitting in a cattle truck another
20th-century historical reference
with ghoulish connotations
the cattle truck s that took the victims
to the concentration camps from Poland.
It's a deliberate reference.
Just as the troops massacring people
in ditches are reminiscent of the Nazis
so the cattle truck s are reminiscent
of the same regime.
It's a way of making the politics
of a distant period and land
come alive to a European audience
by giving it historical reference.
In an intuitive way Leone was good at
assembling these cultural references.
He wasn 't an intellectual.
He wasn 't a deeply read man.
He'd never been in higher education.
He'd never done history or English
or studied cinema.
He studied to be a lawyer - his father
wanted him to be a lawyer - in the late 1940s.
He was working out of his system
his own biography.
He was born in the late '20s
grew up in the 1930s in a suburb
of Rome in Mussolini's Italy
where American movies
were a model of freedom.
Wide open spaces the Westerns
gangster films fast talking of Cagney
all these things Leone has remembered
as having an impact on his psyche.
It was the land of plenty
the other side of the sea.
Then in 1944 he met American troops in person
after the Sicily landings
when they were going north.
The American troops weren 't anything
like the comic book heroes of his youth
or the movies he'd seen in the '30s.
That juxtaposition between
the American troops of reality
at a very impressionable age
and the image on the silver screen in the 1930s
was something he was
working out of his system.
He loved American movies American fairy tales
but he didn 't always like the ideology.
It's that collision that runs through his films
in this one in a very serious setting.
As the relationship
between Sean and Juan develops
we're at the point where Juan is no
longer interested in money and bank s
in robbery and this lust for life he had
in the first half of the movie.
And Sean is beginning to question
his commitment to the revolution.
We're balanced as the two
become dependent on each other.
Sean has been leading Juan a merry dance
but Juan has been a compliant victim.
But now they're beginning to see that
maybe they should both go to America.
Maybe they should get out of Mexico completely.
Sean is trying to cheer Juan up. He realises
the depth of his grief and that he caused it.
Let's cheer him up
talk about the land of milk and honey.
The trouble is that both the exits from
this carriage lead into the revolution.
Another reference to the letterbox image
as Sean look s out of the cattle truck
at what's going on beyond.
This film was shot between April and July 19T'O
a very particular moment in Italian film history.
A series of films were
being made or in the pipeline
which were revisionist versions of the
Second World War revisiting the Nazi period.
The Night Porter Salon Kitty
And Pasolini was shortly to make Salo
a film about the decaying embers
of fascism in northern Italy
where the cruelty and the decadence
and the general atmosphere of mayhem
resembles that in this film.
Sean sees the car pull up and sees
accompanied by Morricone's dissonant music
the governor Don Jaime get out of the car.
We've seen him on the poster
in Mesa Verde and we recognise him.
He's getting on the train.
But Juan doesn 't know that yet.
When the original soundtrack album
to this film came out in Italy
He'd produced scores for 25 films
in the last year alone
He was at his peak as a film composer.
Leone wrote a postcard
on the back of the album sleeve
where he said to Morricone "I have
seen you sleep on benches at school
heard you snore on the editing table
but this music is so beautiful
these sounds so magnificent
I wonder when you could have composed them."
It became a gag between them.
Morricone was used to getting up
at six in the morning.
Leone liked working in the evening.
On one occasion in the editing room
Morricone fell asleep while they were
talking about the soundtrack
something Leone never forgot
and reminded him of.
In fact he elaborated the story.
Leone liked embellishing stories.
As the story gathered momentum
he claimed that Morricone
was standing in the recording studio
and slumped down and fell asleep
at which point Leone went
to the microphone in the glass booth
and pretended to be the voice of God
"Wake up. This is the voice of doom."
It never happened. Morricone
would never be that unprofessional
but it became folklore in the Italian film industry.
Another piece of folklore surrounding Leone
was about the detail that he put
into the backgrounds of his sequences.
The story relates to
The Good The Bad And The Ugly
It became folklore at Cinecittá studios.
When they were filming
The Good The Bad And The Ugly
Leone said to the crew
"We haven 't quite finished this sequence."
"There's just the detail of the spur to finish."
"We'll do the detail of the spur
as a cutaway at some later date."
So they decided to leave the detail.
Just towards the end they decide
to film this moment of the spur.
Leone says "There's 400 troops
600 horses and a bridge blowing up."
That was the detail of the spur.
This was the reputation Leone was getting.
Bigger and bigger movies
lots going on in the background
including this ambush on the train.
By now he had very large budgets
United Artists backing him
two top-line actors on the international stage.
but an Oscar-winning actor
and a famous action actor.
He's propelled into a different league
in this big-budget action movie.
He's shading into David Lean territory
and leaving the territory
of the popular Italian cinema behind.
One might ask here we're in Franco's Spain
and here's a film about politics
a debate about revolution commitment
bandit turning into revolutionary
peasant getting a conscience
intellectual getting disillusioned.
How were they allowed
to make movies of this kind
at a time of fascist regime in Spain?
Clint Eastwood once said
that if the movie was set in the past
in a historical setting no one minded.
100 Italian Westerns had been made in Almería
since 1964 since Fistful Of Dollars
250 Italian/Spanish Westerns had been
made between 1964 and 19T'O
an avalanche of movies
but they were in the past
folklore cowboy films
no one paid much attention to them.
But sometimes hidden within them
is an interesting debate about politics
and this is a very political moment.
Will Juan shoot the governor?
And if so what would his motivation be?
Is it revenge for his family?
Is it showing solidarity with the revolution?
He's certainly got well beyond simply
wanting to take the treasure from him.
Like the Wanted poster
in For A Few Dollars More
a cinematic moment of the camera
going in on the poster
to Steiger's eyes the machine gun
sound and pictures of his six children.
A purely visual image
of what's going through his mind
constructed on the editing bench
like in For A Few Dollars More
where Van Cleef Eastwood and
the poster of El Indio meet together.
The governor realises exactly
what's going through his head
and that this means he's going to pull the trigger.
He offers Juan the treasure.
The Juan early on in the film
who saw the bank as the Holy Grail
would accept this treasure.
Revolution means confusion.
Revolution means we can take the spoils.
Like a lot of characters in the Italian
Westerns of the late 1960s.
But he's got well beyond that.
He's not interested in the treasure any more.
He's developed a conscience honour and he
has a very good reason to kill the governor.
He associates him
with the massacre of his family.
Family is so often a touchstone in
Leone's films for people's motivation.
Like the holy family in Fistful Of Dollars
Like Tuco's brother in
The Good The Bad And The Ugly
In a not very moral universe
the family remains important.
Treasure or revenge?
Juan for the second time becomes the hero.
The first time by mistake at the bank
and this time because of his personal
vendetta against the governor.
Another reference to Leone's hands.
When Leone got nervous he'd pull on
a cigarette packet or shake his hands.
A lot of very active body language.
So much to think about.
Without storyboards so much to get right
in order to implement his vision.
The letterbox image. By now Leone
is making self-conscience references
to his careful use of framing
which a lot of critics have noticed.
The way in which Leone places figures
in the frame is so cinematic.
It would never work in a theatrical context.
Now he's making jokes
about his own letterbox images.
A lyrical version of the March of the Beggars
which we first saw as the stagecoach
disgorged its contents into the pigsty
then we saw
at the political prison in Mesa Verde
as Juan fingers the treasure.
Like the blasting of the wall in Mesa Verde
they open the cattle truck
and he becomes a hero.
He may not want to be a great general
to be Pancho Villa
but somehow he's turned into that.
For the final part of the film
we have some detail about the villistas
the revolutionary cell
planning its campaign against Huerta
into which Juan has now been enmeshed.
Whereas Villega was
the intellectual revolutionary earlier
this is a soldier strategist
a soldier revolutionary.
Villega doesn 't know that they know
that he betrayed all those people
in the firing squad.
And nor does Juan.
Unusual for Leone to have
a reference to a historical character.
He tried to avoid real-life characters in his films.
He said "I don 't like
a waxwork s view of history"
a film about the past where someone wears a
costume impersonating a historical character.
Rod Steiger had recently done just that
in the Russian version of Waterloo
where Steiger played Napoleon
And where he'd had famous rows
with Serge Bondarchuk the director
that Steiger felt he was losing spontaneity
like Leone only on an even bigger scale.
That waxwork view of history
was far from Leone
so it's rare to have a reference to Villa.
That locates it in a very specific context
rather then the diffuse one
which he's been painting up to now.
Another expletive cut
in the international release prints.
The world seems to have caught up
with that kind of language today.
So we're in 1913 Huerta is hanging on
Villa is coming down from the north
Zapata is coming up from the south.
They're about to converge on Mexico City.
This is the historical context for this film.
The revolution is in the balance.
Will the social reforms be set back?
Or will Villa and Zapata get there
and continue the momentum?
Is Villa a bandit or a revolutionary?
Will he have the staying power
or like Juan will he go away with the loot?
Issues like that which had been
part of the Hollywood vision
of the Mexican Revolution
from Viva Villa' onwards
the bandit who becomes a revolutionary
but at heart is a bandit
had filtered their way into the Italian Western
but in the form of Gíú La Testa
Once Upon A Time The Revolution
it was making quite large demands
on the popular audience.
It showed in the box office takings
of Gíú La Testa first time round.
Fistful Of Dollars had been a huge success
For A Few Dollars More the most popular
Italian film till the early 'T'Os.
Once Upon A Time In The West not
so successful because it was badly cut
and the Italian audience
was a bit baffled by it in.
They didn 't know what to make of it.
Someone said going to Monument Valley
to film had had a bad effect on Leone.
He should have stayed in Italy.
He was making this strange
slow elegiac film.
So this captured a moment
Gíú La Testa in Italy.
People realised how it related
to the political context
but it didn 't feel like
a huge popular success.
From the point of violence
it was quite restrained for Leone.
It was dealing with big issues
of betrayal and commitment
and mutual dependence.
It didn 't have a huge
either critical or popular success
in Italy when it came out
but this was a story Leone liked telling.
Just after the premiere in France
he was sitting in a restaurant
and someone came over and put
a bottle of Champagne on his table.
He said "Why are you doing that?"
This man said "I'd like to thank you."
"I have two children and both have been
deeply involved in left-wing politics."
They were students and they'd been
drawn into semi-revolutionary activity.
"They went to see your movie
and decided they don 't want to do that
with their lives so I owe you a lot."
Leone said that was won'th all
the criticisms in Italian newspapers
that he'd had an effect
on two young people's lives.
In Italy various people said
this "I don 't give a damn attitude"
where did Leone's heart lie in this debate?
He's saying that revolution means confusion
and ideological revolutionaries aren 't humane.
He's saying people cling on to power
regimes come and go
but most of them are violent
and the sufferers are the peasants
so that's not an option.
The simple man Rod Steiger has been
drawn into more complex issues.
He'll never be the same again. He has
a conscience and it's destroying him.
So what in the end
is the position of this film?
There's a political position in Italy
which is l-don 't-give-a-damn politics.
"I don 't like central government.
I don 't like the state."
"I want to get on with my life.
I don 't give a damn."
This film was related to that
rather dangerous political ideology
of never getting involved in anything.
That debate about the revolution
people who read book s
pushing people around
could be interpreted
as a plea for ignorance.
So in bursting the bubble of 1968
and of the myth of political
Italian Westerns and cinema
and making a statement about politics
Leone is dangerously close
to saying leave me alone
I just want to be with my family
I don 't give a damn about formal politics.
Keep your head down
don 't get involved or committed.
That really angered a lot of critics in Italy.
They found it a dangerous position.
One should get committed.
One should be a citizen.
Here we have another flashback
as Villega has recovered from being tortured
and betraying his friends.
Sean remembers a similar moment
catching up with where we were
in the pub in Dublin.
The moment of betrayal.
Sean turns round and shoots the British
soldiers.
Again with this romantic
Sean theme on the soundtrack
which plays against the image.
He's shooting two people
but the music isn 't telling you that.
It's a nostalgic reverie but it also
is unlocking traumas about the past.
Will he shoot the friend who betrayed him?
Gypo Nolan played by Victor McLaglen
who betrays his friend Frankie to
the police in order to get blood money
in order to pay for the passage
to America so he can emigrate.
It's a very similar situation.
Leone said of John Ford's vision of Ireland
that Ford as himself
an immigrant of Irish parenthood
moving to the East Coast then to Hollywood
that his films are optimistic in the end
about the melting pot
integrating into American society.
In The Quiet Man impossibly green lush rural.
It's like a picture-postcard view of Ireland.
But this is something
very different to a picture postcard.
Sean has just shot his best friend.
Should he kill Villega?
Or has he matured to the point where
he doesn 't take his revenge that far?
"I believe only in dynamite."
All his ideals have gone
all that revolutionary fervour from Ireland.
Now he's just a technician that blows people up.
He wants to turn Villega into a manual worker
who's going to stoke the coal on the train.
This strategist who sits in back rooms
thinking how to send people into action
it's time he did something
so he's going to stoke up the train
which is gonna go full speed into
the train coming in the other direction
with Huerta's troops
in an almighty head-on collision.
The trains were craftsmen -made
scale models from Rome.
I hate to spoil this. They're not real trains.
They were models made by craftsmen in Rome.
Andrea Crisanti took a lot of trouble to get right
the verisimilitude of these two trains.
Villega realises what's going on.
He realises that Sean knows
he betrayed his comrades
and that he's setting him up.
Typical Leone moment.
Nothing's explained.
You just look at Villega's face
as it dawns on him what's happening.
He's being sent to his doom by Sean
in revenge for the betrayal.
Does Villega stay on the train commit
suicide in the cause of the revolution?
Or does he jump off
at the last minute to save himself?
"Save yourself." So in the end
Sean is humane enough to save Villega.
He doesn 't want him
to go on this suicidal mission
but Villega think s otherwise.
He hasn 't jumped.
Another Leone explosion.
He keeps upping the ante.
We have the explosion of the stagecoach
the explosion of the bridge
and this huge explosion of the train
these two forces hitting each other
like an atomic explosion
for the meeting of the two trains.
Leone likes explosions.
His brother-in -law Fulvio Morsella
one of the producers of this film
and who helped to write the treatment
once told me that Leone had this
spectacularising tendency in movies and in life.
In his life he liked to embroider
stories he'd heard like Falstaff
and make them a little bit better in the telling.
He enjoyed telling after-dinner stories
and smoking Havana cigars
and guffawing with laughter with film friends.
In the movies he had
this spectacularising tendency.
As his career developed
each film revisits situations
he's looked at in the past in a symphonic way
this time taking them in new directions
and making them more spectacular.
The set of the town of Flagstone
in Once Upon A Time In The West
cost more than the entire budget
of Fistful Of Dollars
So one set cost more
than the whole budget of Fistful
Here a huge budget movie
with lots of action sequences.
The traditional Italian Western
has one or two big action sequences
to give body to the film
to give the impression that it is big budget.
Here the action sequences
are sewn through the film.
This is an international
Hollywood Italian production.
The spectacularising effect gets bigger.
Fulvio Morsella said Leone would have
made a great director of operas.
He was very often offered operas.
which was the first spaghetti western
which premiered at the Met in New York
just before the First World War.
But he wasn 't interested in people
singing before getting on their horses.
He wanted people to get on with it
where character is action
and people are defined by what they do
so he turned down offers of operas.
He was offered Carmen
which Francesco Rosi went on to make
but for the same reason Leone turned it down.
Although his films have been called
operas in which the arias are stared
and they're also called horse operas
and you could argue the relationship
with Morricone is like
director and musician
composer for the opera
in a literal sense
Leone didn 't have much time for opera
but he certainly had a taste for spectacle.
By now he was brilliant at logistics
at working out an extremely complex set
with an idea of the story in his head.
If this was an Italian Western we'd be
building up to a duel at this stage
where the two characters would meet
and one of them would finally
get his revenge on the other
and the whole thing would be resolved.
This is too complicated a world for that.
Sean is shot in the back several times
and Juan look s completely lost.
The dance of death
the duel at the end of Leone's films
becomes a different kind of dance
as Guttierez gets shot
by Juan 's machine gun.
By the time Leone reached
Once Upon A Time In America
the duel is explicitly rejected in the last scene
where Noodles played by
Robert de Niro is given the gun
but refuses to take up the challenge
of a settling of accounts.
Life is too complicated for that.
That was fine for the world
of the Italian Western
but this is a movie about friendship.
It's a more complicated movie
than those Dollars films.
It's Juan 's turn to cheer up Sean for once
remembering the land of milk and honey.
"What's going to happen to me?"
Juan realises he's become
dependent on Sean
just as Sean has become
dependent on Juan.
They're locked into this relationship.
Juan will be lost without him.
"A great grand glorious hero
of the revolution"
first used after the raiding
of the bank in Mesa Verde
where Steiger becomes a reluctant hero.
Another theme that recurs. "I don 't want
to be a general" said Steiger earlier.
Sean 's about to light
one of his strange cigarettes
which he often uses
to light the fuse of his dynamite.
In his hand is the crucifix
which Juan took off his neck
at the grotto of San Isidro when his family died.
For the rest of the story
Sean has been hanging on to it
to give back to his friend just before he dies.
"I gave you a royal screwing."
He has a conscience about the way he led Juan
getting him involved in the revolution.
But Juan says no it was won'th it.
They've become good friends.
Leone had wanted to cast Coburn
ever since Fistful Of Dollars
He wanted him for The Man With
No Name but couldn 't afford him.
James Coburn wasn 't sure
whether to get involved
but he had dinner with
his friend Henry Fonda one night.
Henry Fonda said
"You must work with Sergio Leone."
"He's the finest director
I've worked with in my entire career."
Which is something for the man
who'd worked with all the greats.
Coburn said "You're joking."
Fonda said "No."
"He is an amazing experience."
So Coburn accepted took on the role
and became part of Gíú La Testa
It was not the success
everyone hoped it at the time
although it's achieved
this huge reputation since
so it didn 't do wonders
for Coburn 's reputation.
Flashback in the greenery of Ireland.
The two friends and the Irish colleen
in slow motion
representing the dreams of revolution
when the two of them were comrades.
She is in some strange way
a symbol of the revolution
that they're both part of in Ireland.
The sense of a ménage á trois between them
which makes the betrayal
and the shooting even more poignant
and in a way is the final piece
of Sean 's psychology that we need to know.
It wasn 't just shooting a friend.
It was a very close bond
between the three of them
and Mother Ireland.
This flashback was missing from
the Italian print when it first came out.
It made the ending particularly enigmatic
because there was no resolution
of what was on Sean 's mind
and no resolution to the Irish theme
which had been sewn
through all the flashback s.
This was one of the longest and most
elaborate flashback s in Leone's cinema.
With Once Upon A Time In America
Leone even dared
to finish the movie on a flashback
creating the impression in the audience's mind
that the entire movie had been a fantasy
of the Robert de Niro character
sitting in an opium den in New York.
The Italian distributors were worried
that with a flashback of this length
in slow motion with this music
at the end of a movie
that the audience would get up and
walk out before the flashback finished
and miss the climax of the film so they cut it.
It's only recently been restored in Italian prints.
Part of it was there in international
release prints but not at this length.
The Sean theme by Morricone is about
to make way for another theme
for the final part of the flashback.
This is the point.
She kisses
the David Warbeck character as well.
So the bond between them
this triangle is very deep.
And Sean 's quite happy about that.
Out of focus. We're exiting the flashback.
Which has been shared by Juan
in some strange way.
We think he was imagining it too
but then there's a huge explosion
as that strange cigarette makes contact
with the dynamite inside Sean 's coat.
So he's blown himself up.
"What about me?" Duck You Sucker
So in the Italian version
Juan look s at the audience
and says "What about me?"
And up comes Gíú La Testa
keep your head down don 't get involved.
None of this would have happened
if you hadn 't got involved in the revolution.
You'd still have your family
your way of life intact.
What about me? Gíú La Testa
It's an extraordinary ending
addressed directly to the audience.
The next film that Leone made
would be an even darker film.
There's an increasing melancholy
about his films as he got older.
Just as this one is between the twilight
of the frontier and the dark night of the city
his final film Once Upon I Time
In America which came out in the 1980s
is about the gangster era of the 1920s
the '30s and the 1960s
and is a very dark film indeed.
It's really about two characters
who sleepwalk their way into oblivion.
It's surprising that Leone was only
in early middle age at this time
but he's having autumnal thoughts.
It's like the movie of an old man
looking back that kind of melancholia.
But he was still a relatively young man
born in 1928.
It's not like Visconti making
one of his autumnal films.
This is the film of a young man the
most mature film he'd made up to now.