¡Andale, caballo!
¡Señor!
- Tighten up that girth.
- Señor, I must go to San Felipe.
My mother is dead!
Straight down the road about 50 miles.
Please?
Yeah, get outta here.
Hey. Hey, amigo.
Come here.
Perfect.
You're perfect!
I swear to God, boys, he's just right.
I'm gonna put you on that stage and
watch those faces when they see you come in!
Move.
- By God, I...
- Never mind, dear.
Over there.
Not that door, the other one, there.
Pull. Pull.
There you are. Now just sit down
and be quiet, like a good little boy.
You see? He does understand.
Who knows, perhaps he can even talk.
Now, now, even the peasants...
A bit of mustard?
Thank you.
Even the peasants are entitled to their rights.
After all, they have won a revolution.
Or at least, almost.
Animals, that's what they are. Animals.
Even animals can be tame and harmless.
Personally, I consider them unfortunate brutes.
Yes, brutes. Quite right.
Precisely, my dear lady, precisely.
I hate saying it,
but you should hear them in the confessional.
- You would never imagine. Did you know?
- I can imagine, Father.
I can imagine.
Living in such promiscuity,
all of them in one room,
male and female together,
lying in a heap, like rats in a sewer.
At night, when the lights are out,
all their inhibitions disappear.
You never know who is next:
Mother, sister, daughter... goat.
Every country has its own plague.
- Just like them niggers we got back home.
- Just like animals. That's what they are.
Exactly. Which is why they're half-wits.
Hey, you. Do you know who your father was?
Do you know how old you are?
He doesn't know.
Do you know how many kids you have? Huh?
Do you know how many kids your mother had?
He doesn't know anything.
It was to benefit scum like this
that the Agrarian Reform was imposed.
And that ass, Madero, wanted to give
the government and our land to idiots like this.
We are all pawns in the hands of Almighty God.
Fortunately, Divine Providence
has disposed of that rash individual Madero.
My dear Monsignor, let us be realistic.
What you call Providence, I call General Huerta.
He put the peasants in their place.
Which is the best place for animals
because that's what they are.
Animals.
I can imagine.
- I can imagine, living in such promiscuity...
... wanted to give the government and our land
to idiots like this!
- Goats.
- Animals.
- Rats!
- Just like them niggers we got back home.
- Half-wits!
- Animals!
Divine Providence has disposed...
Just like them niggers.
Animals. Because that's what they are. Animals.
...like them niggers.
- Brutes!
That's what they are, animals.
- Like them niggers.
- Brutes!
Animals!
- I consider them unfortunate brutes.
- I can imagine...
Niggers.
- Brutes!
- Niggers!
...like them niggers.
- Idiots!
- Niggers!
...like them niggers.
- Idiots! Half-wits!
¡Anda, caballo anda!
¡Anda, caballo!
Hey, you, give us a hand and push.
- Move, you lazy bunch of greasers!
- ¡Anda!
Think they'd get off their asses to help us,
the bastards? Hell, no!
¡Anda! ¡Caballo, huyo!
Haaaahh!
Take him away before he dirties everything.
Now, ladies and gentlemen, you will give
everything to my niños, without any trouble.
We kill them all, OK, Papá?
I've told you, Chulo,
no shooting unless Papá pulls the trigger.
Come.
Come, come, come, come!
You wanted to know my family? That's my sons.
Each one of them from a different mother.
And now, you kneel.
Kneel!
¡Papá!
This is my father. I think.
- Pleased to meet...
- Go inside before Chulo kills everyone.
My mother had the blood of the Aztecs,
which was before your people.
And now I ask you a question.
Can you make a baby?
That's sad. But we will fix that.
¡Señora!
Let me go! Let go.
Go on.
Go.
Go... go... go... go... go!
Pretty good, huh?
Oh, Jesus, help me, I'm going to faint.
No, no, no, no, no.
You faint now and you miss the best part.
Juanito, you get everything?
You'll pay for this, you bastard!
- I'm a citizen of the United States of America!
- You're an American son of a bitch.
Understand, Yankee?
Thank you.
Thank you. For everything.
Have you a light?
Duck, you sucker!
There is a hole in the roof.
Hey!
- I wouldn't do that if I were you.
- Why?
You pull that trigger and shoot me, I fall.
And if I fall, they'll have to alter all the maps.
You see, when I go,
half this bloody country goes with me.
Including yourself.
- You understand now?
- Ah, sí, sí, sí, sí, sí, sí. I understand.
¡Sí!
It's like a miracle of God.
You, you are a great magician.
I stop your motorcycle,
you do the magic with my coach. We are even.
- Even?
- Sí.
No, we're not even.
To fix my motorcycle would be even.
I'll be inside.
Oh! We kill him now, Papá?
No. First we fix the motorcycle. Shh!
- It's whisky.
- Thank God for that, huh?
Where are you going in this contraption?
Well... Where are you going?
- Shaver Mines.
- Oh-ho.
Lucanina, huh? I know that place.
I know the man who owns it,
that fat, German son of a bitch!
That crazy tub of lard, Mr Aschenbach,
who wrings our people dry like slaves,
even his personal servants.
One girl had an ass:
Her cheeks were hard like drums.
I got her pregnant and he...
Oh, Jesus Christ!
Will you shut up and go and fix my motorcycle?
OK.
Anything you say, Firecracker.
Take your hands off that. Now!
Well, good for you, Firecracker.
Not even one lousy peso!
I don't know why I named you Napoleon
when you have no imagination. This is a bank!
- Mesa Verde.
- Sí, Papá, Mesa Verde. Mesa Verde.
If we can get this Firecracker to come with us,
we will be rich.
Where does he come in?
The dynamite's right here.
No, no. You need an expert for that.
You only need matches and balls.
And I got those.
- ¿Sí?
- ¡Sí!
See that tree over there?
Short fuse.
Now you understand
why we need the firecracker?
Huh?
- Where the hell are we?
- What kind of work you do for the German?
Listen, I asked you a question.
What do you do for the German?
- I've been looking for silver for him.
- Silver?
You know something? I don't understand you.
Why do you waste your time and your holy water
looking for silver? To me, that's a sin.
- Have you any better ideas?
- Sí. Gold is better than silver.
There isn't any gold in these hills.
Yes, there is.
In Mesa Verde.
Mesa Verde? It's a city.
Of course.
Whoever heard of having a bank in the country!
Uh-huh. A bank?
Not a bank. The bank.
The most beautiful, wonderful, fantastic,
gorgeous, magnificent bank in the world.
When you stand before the bank
and you see it has the gates of gold,
like it was the gates of heaven.
And when you go inside,
everything, everything is gold.
Gold spittoons, gold handles. And money.
Money, money is everywhere.
I know, 'cause I saw when I was
eight years old. I went there with my father.
He tried to rob the bank. They caught him,
but they won't catch me. ¿Eh, Papá?
Right.
Listen, Firecracker, you listen to me.
Listen, why don't you come with me
and we will work together?
And we will become rich.
What the hell is your name?
John.
What?
- What is your name?
- John.
That's fantastic. That is incredible.
My name is Juan and yours is John.
Juan and John.
So what?
Can't you understand that is, that is the...
Oh...
Destiny.
No. And I mean it.
Why?
You want more money? I'll give you more
than half. I don't care about the money.
As long as we can work together.
Listen what I'm telling you.
We are like two brothers.
You make the holes with the holy water
and then I walk in and do the dirty work.
Listen, it takes one bandito to know another.
- So you can read?
- You don't have to read.
I see a man's picture, I see a price,
I know that man is in trouble.
Hey, what kind of trouble are you in?
- Oh, we fought a revolution in Ireland.
- A revolution?
Seems revolutions are all over the world,
like the crops.
We had a revolution.
The brave people went in.
What it did to them was terrible. Pancho Villa,
the world's best bandit chief, two balls like a bull,
he went in the revolution as a great bandit,
came out as what? Nothing.
A general. That, to me, is the bullshit.
Wait a minute.
You come here to join the revolution?
No, no.
One was enough for me.
Stop! You dirty...
...son of a bitch!
Gringo... bastard!
Hey!
Duck, you sucker!
- Say, which way is it to Lucanina?
- Fuck you! Go find it yourself!
Mexico is big,
but for you, it is going to be very big!
John, where are you? It's us!
Come on, come on, you.
Come on in there.
Just a little further inside.
That's right, heathen bastards.
What's this?
You crazy? You talk to yourself now?
Oh, my friend, didn't I tell you Mexico was big?
Oh, shit.
Who are those people inside?
You mean, who were those people inside?
Who were they? Who were those people inside?
Chulo!
Who were those people, for Christ's sake?
Well, one of them was Aschenbach,
then there was three soldiers and one captain.
Everybody dead in there.
Will you keep quiet
and go get our friend's equipment together?
Anyway, when I went to Aschenbach
and I told him,
I said you wanted to see him,
he wouldn't believe that.
I said, "That's too bad
because he's discovered silver. "
Then he was ready to come running.
The other one, the captain... I think the captain
and Aschenbach were working together.
The captain says, "I want to see the man. "
I said, "How can you see him? He's blown off
his hand with dynamite, he is bleeding to death. "
When they heard that,
they broke their asses to get here.
Anyway, it's no problem because
there are diamonds here, no questions.
Also, you have no contract, so... you are free.
There will be one little problem, with the army.
They will have a hot ass
when it comes to the death of a captain.
But don't worry.
I am your friend Juan and I will help.
I will do anything, say anything...
No, no, no. I don't need any help from you
to know I've been screwed.
You fuckin' chicken thief.
What do you want with me?
Nothing.
I just thought that maybe...
...we could go to Mesa Verde.
The bank. Isn't there anything else
you remember about Mesa Verde?
Yes, there's a place
where you can sit down and eat.
- When you look in front, you...
- See the bank.
That's right. How do you know?
Listen, Mesa Verde, that's only the beginning.
Let me tell you, it will be Juan and John,
the two especialistas in banks, eh?
We'll call it Johnny and Johnny.
That's more American.
Amigo, we go to America,
there are banks all over the place.
In California, Colorado,
Kansas City, Texas and Austin.
You have to think of the big future
that we have ahead of us.
I'm thinking of the big train behind us.
Hey! Out of the way!
Hey, you.
I know that face.
Where have I seen you before?
Stop right where you are!
Drop that knife, you bastard.
I have family.
I have a family too.
Beautiful, eh?
My children!
¡Uno, dos, uno, dos, uno, dos!
¡Pelotón... izquierda!
¿Tienen algo qué pedir?
¿Ytu?
Listos.
¡Armas!
¡Preparen!
Apunten.
¡Fuego!
Hey, God, you're sure this is Mesa Verde?
Do you have your beans with chilli?
I don't want nothing from you.
- Aw, come on, have some beans.
- Listen, you son of a bitch!
You pull that trick on me again,
I break your goddamn head!
Well, for Christ's sake.
A train comes along and I take it.
- Been waiting in your Mesa Verde ever since.
- It's not my Mesa Verde.
- This place is covered with soldiers like flies.
- Just the way we like it.
Just the way we like it?
If it's a revolution... it's confusion.
What are you talking about?
Revolution, confusion?
Where there's confusion,
a man who knows what he wants...
...stands a good chance of getting it.
- I don't understand you.
This him?
That's him.
Him who?
- Do you trust me?
- No.
- You want to get inside there?
- Sí.
Well, I'm going to see to it
you have that chance. Come on.
Don't move, goddamn it!
Hold him still.
That does it. Relax now. Relax.
It's all over.
If you'd let this infection go any longer,
your widow would be paying my bill.
Mallory!
You've hardly joined us here in Mesa Verde.
Already, you're front-page news.
"Irish dynamiter wanted for murder. "
You have a real talent for making friends.
You've stirred up a hornet's nest.
I'll grant you the captain, but...
...till now, nobody dared
take a crack at foreign capitalists.
Not even Pancho Villa.
It seems even His Majesty's Secret Service
would like to get their hands on you.
And yet, you are an asset to us.
Even if sometimes, you do drink a bit too much.
Who says I drink too much?
Your liver does.
What about that one, him?
He's all right.
Except that when operating,
he cuts deeper than I do.
What the doctor means is,
one time we did a little work together.
And now, to our work, friends.
I have good news.
In two days, Villa and Zapata
will attack simultaneously from north and south.
We here, like those in other cities,
must begin parallel actions of harassment.
Pereto's downfall is just a question of weeks.
Whereas Miguel's is only a question of hours
if he doesn't stop smoking.
Easy to say.
We'll attack in four places at the same time.
Antonio, you hit the city hall and old prisons.
You will need to divide into two groups,
one of them under the command of José.
Jesús, the railway station
and the marshalling yards as planned, right?
Get in position in good time in small groups,
so you won't attract attention.
And act like ordinary travellers,
or railroad employees.
You, Manolo, together with Juanito, will attack
the army barracks with our main forces, agreed?
This is their point of maximum concentration,
and is the key to the success of our plan.
You must create
the impression of a massive attack.
And if necessary,
be prepared to make the final sacrifice.
The fourth and last target,
Ortega, the post office.
When the enemy is busy on four fronts,
we'll move against our real objective.
Do we still agree?
- You'll need men.
- I only need one man.
One?
Sí.
Him?
Him? Him?
What is with this "him"? Him who? Who him?
To do what? That's what I want to know!
To attack the bank.
The bank?
We will take care of the bank.
That's why we're here,
so don't worry about that.
Well, then, what can I say?
Except... I hope you make it.
Me too. And him.
Well, we'll meet again tonight to discuss details.
I have to go now.
I left a woman in labour
and she can't wait till the revolution is over.
- Tierra y libertad.
- ¡Tierra y libertad!
Leave one at a time and keep out of sight.
Speaking of sight, how's your cataract?
At least I have a good eye. With the other...
Shh! You don't have to say anything.
I understand everything.
¡Tierra y libertad!
Ylibertad.
¡Capitán! ¡Avíselas, Capitán!
¡Pronto! ¡Hola, muénvase!
Go.
Psst, psst! ¡Oye!
Bravo, Chulo.
Take it, take it.
There must be a lot of money in the bank,
look at all those soldiers.
- You know how this works?
- Sí. It's a...
...short fuse.
- No.
- No?
Normal rate.
30 seconds.
Sí. 30 seconds.
- What did you find?
- Nothing but scrap paper.
Wait a minute. Hey, it's pointing down there.
Psst!
There is the safe!
Duck, you suckers!
- Where are you going, for Christ's sake?
- I don't know, but something's wrong.
I went into the bank.
There's no money there, nothing.
The bank and the money were transferred
to Mexico City a month ago.
They've been using this place
for a political prison ever since.
- What? A political prison?
- I never said a thing about money.
All I asked was if you wanted to get inside.
But this bank is my life, this is my dream.
The reality is, you've just liberated 150 patriots
through sheer courage in the face of danger.
Ah, yes...
...you're a grand hero of the revolution now.
- I Vívela, Juan!
- I don't want to be a hero. I want the money!
The money!
- You taught me one thing.
- What?
How to get fucked!
- What's that?
- It's a map.
It's your country you're lying all over.
Not my country.
My country is me and my family.
Well, your country's also Huerta...
...and the Governor and landlords.
And Gunther Ruiz and his locusts.
- This little revolution we're having here.
- Revolution?
Please don't try to tell me about revolution!
I know how revolutions start.
People that read books
go to people that don't read books and say,
- "The time has come for change. "
- Shh!
Shh! Shh! Shh! Shh! Shh! Shit, shush!
I know what I'm talking about
when I'm talking about revolutions!
The people who read books go to the people
who can't read and say, "We need change,"
so the poor people make the change.
The people who read the books sit around
big polished tables and talk and talk and eat.
But what has happened to the poor people?
They are dead!
That's your revolution.
Shh.
So please, don't tell me about revolutions.
Then what happens?
The same fucking thing starts all over again!
¡Capitán!
¡Vamos!
I don't like it either.
Only Gunther Ruiz is less than 20 miles
from here, on the road that leads to that bridge.
They will comb the area bush by bush.
So the order is to pull back,
hide in the San Ysidro caves.
Oh, that's a brilliant order.
Here we are, facing it.
You, and the rest of you dreamers,
want to piss it up against the wall!
Not everybody can fight.
There are those who must organise,
co-ordinate.
Yes, yes, of course.
Yeah, well...
...don't pay any attention to me.
It's personal.
Sorry about those orders. I'm staying.
I don't give a fuck about your revolutions.
I'm tired of running up and down these
mountains and getting nowhere, so I've stopped.
Right here, at the bridge of San Jorge.
Maybe it's out of spite for you
and your slow dream, or maybe...
Ah, maybe my feet are sore.
If he's gonna stay, I'm gonna stay.
Maybe 'cause my feet are sore too, huh?
¡Hombres! Me and irlandés are gonna catch
ourselves a couple of fucking locusts.
¡Atente! You go back and hide in the grotto.
If things go bad here, every man for himself.
You move your asses! ¿Comprenden?
If something happens
and your father doesn't come back,
then I pray that the great God in heaven
takes care of you.
Well... Good luck.
Thank you.
Listen, when they are out of sight,
we will make a run for it. ¿Sí?
No? You can't mean to stay here? All those
explosions must have gone to your head!
Remember John and Juan?
America.
The millions.
No?
No.
I don't understand!
Wasn't that was a trick for us to get out?
- What can we do against those locusts?
- You'd be doing me a favour if you'd leave.
If I had a choice between a chicken thief
and ridding the world of a few uniforms,
I'd not choose the chicken thief.
OK.
No!
Oh, no, no. You will like that, huh?
Well, you listen to me, you Irish piece of shit!
You think you're the only man
with the balls to stay? You are wrong!
I have the balls and I stay.
He says there's no danger,
just watch the bridge from a long way.
No matter how I look with them,
I'm still too close to the bridge.
Why am I mixed up in this revolution anyway?
God, why didn't you strike me down
instead of letting me say, "I stay too"?
Oh, look at him! All because of him.
He acts like a tourist, only he's staying.
Look at him.
What the hell does he care?
He is having fun.
I'm glad he's having fun, God,
because I am not having fun.
Oh-ho, no.
Hey...
What's this?
Now he goes to sleep, huh?
Go ahead, you sleep, sleep.
I tell you something, when he's asleep, I'll go.
Shh!
May the good Lord watch over you.
Stop over there, Sergeant.
Hey!
God, only an idiot could sleep at a time like this!
Abandon the trucks!
Break ranks and take cover under the bridge!
Artillery, fire. The bridge!
All of them.
Six.
I've never counted them before.
No, Juan, no.
No, for Christ's sake.
They're waiting for you out there.
¡No se mueven!
¡Capitán!
Hold it!
Move that bastard out of the truck.
See that he gets to the camp alive!
¡Uno, dos, uno!
¡Uno, dos, uno, dos!
¡Uno, dos, uno, dos, uno, dos!
¡Pelotón alto!
¡Izquierda!
¡Posición de tiro!
¿Tienen algo qué pedir?
Pelotón...
¡Preparen!
¡Armas!
¡Apunten!
¿Tienes algo qué pedir?
¡Posición de tiro!
¡Preparen armas!
¡Apunten!
Duck, you suckers!
¡Preparen! ¡Armas!
¡Apunten!
¡Fuego!
But for the rich, you sing.
Oh, Jesus, Juan.
Anyway, if they ever get this thing under way,
you might be able to...
...might be make the border by, what,
some time tonight, don't you think?
America. It's America, Juan!
Oh, Jesus, if it's as great as they say it is,
filled bags stuffed full of dreams...
Juan?
Oh, Jesus.
Jesus, Juan.
What is it, Juan and... John?
Johnny and Johnny?
I make the holes and you get in. 50-50, right?
What's happening?
Oh, they're just moving the train around.
Seems we'll be leaving shortly.
The uniforms have loaded the last of their shit.
Get out of the way.
What do you want from me, you scum?
Let me by.
It's yours.
There's a fortune inside.
Money, jewels...
...pearls.
¡Jóvenes, a México!
Well, this will not be going to America.
Maybe the train won't, but we will.
Hey...
Which way is America?
Well, it's sure as hell not that way.
That's the way.
Well, then...
...let's go.
Even Pancho Villa's heard much about you.
He's always saying,
"I want to meet this Miranda. "
Me?
That's right.
The military junta commander
told us everything that you've done.
Whatever you heard, I assure you,
they were only words.
Words cannot describe
what Juan has done and suffered for the cause.
Hey, doctor.
How you been, eh?
This is a man who should talk to Villa.
Hey.
John.
Doctor.
We thought we'd lost you, doctor.
Have you got a light?
Listen, Gunther Ruiz is after us
and Villa wants to talk to me.
We should get outta here.
Jesus, Juan, you can't leave now.
You're a glorious hero of the revolution.
Can I tell you something?
Fuck you!
That's all.
A military train carrying over 1,000 soldiers and
heavy weapons is heading straight towards us.
What about Villa's troops?
He met resistance in the Sierra,
and asks us to hold out for 24 hours.
- Where the hell are we?
- Approximately here.
Ah, it's a beautiful desert there.
Not a stream or a canyon in 100 miles.
- How long you think it'll take them to get here?
- Three hours, more or less.
Three hours.
Well, it looks as though
we'll have to stop 'em right here, doesn't it?
All that takes
is unbolting a couple of yards of track.
But then what? They'd still slaughter us.
Wait.
There's more than one way to stop a train.
- How much dynamite have we?
- Maybe 200 Ibs.
Is that enough for you?
Oh, yes. It'll have to do all right.
- But I also need a locomotive and a man.
- Sí, sí, sí. OK.
OK.
- Someone who's brave and loyal to the cause.
- Never mind that. What do I have to do?
Someone like Dr Villega.
Well...
- I... I'm honoured.
- I don't doubt it, doctor.
Also, because an old friend of ours
is in command of that train.
A Colonel Gunther Ruiz.
Let's get shovelling, man.
We'll never get up enough pressure that way.
Come on, put your back in it, Villega.
Let's stop pretending, right away.
You know everything, don't you?
- You sensed it, or guessed it.
- Simpler than that, Villega.
I saw you, that night in the rain.
I see.
You've already judged and condemned me.
That's why you brought me with you. To kill me.
It's easy to judge. Have you ever been tortured?
Are you sure you wouldn't talk?
I was sure. And yet I talked.
Some men died because of me.
What should I do? Kill myself? Why?
The dead remain dead, but I have not changed.
I still believe in the same things.
I can still serve the cause.
Shut up, Villega! Shut up, for Christ's sake.
When I started using dynamite,
I believed in many things. All of it!
Finally, I believe only in dynamite.
I don't judge you, Villega.
I did that only once in my life.
Get shovelling!
The end of the line, Villega.
And I can't help you now.
Just close your eyes and jump.
For Christ's sake, save yourself!
¡Dios mío, frena!
Oh, shit...
God...
Hey.
Man, remember, huh?
You remember what you told me, huh?
You told me about America.
And the banks and the gold.
Like you told me on the train, remember?
Hey, hey.
Hey.
No, you son of a bitch. Come on,
you son of a bitch. You know, you told me that.
You leave me now,
what the fuck is gonna happen to me?
- You'll make it, General.
- Oh, shit, I don't want to be a general.
Come on, talk to me.
Keep talking.
Talk. Tell me about Villega, Villega.
Remember Villega?
- Villega?
- Sí.
He died.
He died a great...
...grand, glorious hero of the revolution.
OK.
Easy, easy. I'll go, I'll get help, huh?
General?
- Have you a light?
- Sí.
Oh, my friend...
...I'd hate to give you a royal screwing.
I go get help.
Johnny!
What about me?