Hey, listen. I know I'm not the usual big shot
you're used to dealing with,
but a deal this small?
I can manage on my own.
I've got connection in In-sa-dong.
In-sa-dong is great.
Since it's my first time,
I wasn't sure what to do.
But I'll make sure to give you a fat commission.
Thank you for that.
Let's see the goods.
Sure, sure.
Ahh, now,
this is called the Blue Dragon Tea Cup
used by the Ming Dynasty nobles.
I hear it goes at 300 million Yen in Japan.
- How much?
- 300 million Yen
I own this tiny shop,
so I go to China to get merchandise.
Last trip to Guangzhou,
I bought this off an old Chinese man.
Then as soon as I get back to Korea,
that old man gets arrested by PSB
- For smuggling cultural properties
- Oh yeah?
This old man,
he'd run errands for Japanese scholars during the war
and stashed away a few artifacts.
Not knowing its worth,
he gave it to me for nothing.
Wow, you lucked out.
The timing was impeccable.
At first he didn't want to sell.
Why?
Some Korean dude
begged the old man to sell the goods to him.
I was like, 'This is it!'
'This is the stuff.'
So I called higher.
- How much?
- 5 grand
Haha, you lucky bastard.
High-five!
Whoever he was,
what a poor schmuck.
Let me shake your hand, man.
That's me.
What?
That poor schmuck.
That was me, you jerk.
Wait, wait...
It took me over 2 months to locate the stuff.
Then you showed up,
and I missed it by two hours?
What's this?
Blue Dragon Tea Cup
Don't you think I know that?
Where is it?
- At home
- Where?
At home,
at home, home...
I hid it at home.
No one knows.
Not even my wife.
Mr. Chang-In Ghang!
It's the police.
Did you call the cops, huh?
- Are you Chang-in Ghang?
- Yes
Chang-In Ghang,
you're under arrest
for violation of cultural protection act.
Where's your warrant?
Show me the warrant.
Where are you taking me? It hurts!
Call it in.
Let's go.
Check the roof, go!
Man down.
Male, mid-30s.
John Doe.
Fell from the roof top during the arrest.
Villain and Widow
You're in 80 km/h zone.
Please slow down.
Turn it down!
Alarm disabled.
Welcome.
I'm never going to see the grandparents again,
not even for the holidays.
I don't know why we keep going.
Dad's not around anymore.
That's enough.
You have to weed the yard after it rains...
Your home is now secured.
Your yard's full of weed.
What?
You need to weed it out to grow something.
We don't grow anything anymore.
We buy everything from the store
with pesticide all over them.
Why do I even bother...
Room Available to Rent
So, Mr. Ghang's never seen the goods in person...
The Chinese who sold the stuff
got caught by PSB for smuggling.
It was just bad timing.
Didn't you guys look into it?
Yeah, we figured out what's going on.
Well, then.
We just bring you the goods,
get it appraised,
And if it is good,
you pay us.
If it isn't, you don't.
What's the big deal?
I believe my boss is entitled to an explanation.
Entitled?
Not that I doubt your abilities,
Mr. Ghang
I just want to make sure if you need any help,
say, more people
No, I don't need more people.
Well, if there aren't any questions,
we'll see ourselves out.
He's paying us 2 million dollars.
Was it so hard to be nice?
Is he really the president of this company?
What do you mean?
Why is he handling things directly?
Is that a problem?
He needs to delegate to his people.
He's too exposed from the start.
He's just really desperate.
He's got a gallery at the headquarters.
He took 10 million from arts
budget behind his father's back
for money laundering and lost
everything in bad investment.
So he needs something to make up for it,
right away.
Pardon me.
My name is Mr. Song.
If you need anything,
please call me any time.
Who's the midget?
Some punk.
Mr. Ha takes him around as his bodyguard.
Show off at the clubs,
you know.
Real mature.
Don't underestimate residential security system.
You can go in and out of a jewelry shop in a minute,
but this takes at least 3 to 4 days.
You look into the security company.
Who's got time to research all that?
Delaying will upset Mr. Ha.
Why should I care,
he hasn't paid me up front.
Can't you just tie them up and go through the house?
It's only a woman and her daughter.
Sure, because when I untie them,
she'll say 'Thank you'.
Just like that. Sure.
Just make sure they won't want to call the cops.
How do I do that?
- You know how.
- Seriously, how?
You know... just...
Must I say it out loud?
What if it goes bad?
I'd have to rot in jail for another 5~6 years.
Chang-In, life is all about preparing for the future.
That requires money.
This is my last chance.
I'm old.
This guy is paying us 2 million at once.
In cash!
Opportunities like this don't come again.
This is literally, 'show me the money'.
'Show me the money!'
How about just 3 grand?
It must be hard for you, too.
Anyone interested in renting my spare room upstairs?
That's not an easy sale.
It's just a room,
in someone's home.
Don't young people look for studios?
Why would kids want to live in your neighborhood?
They want to live in the city.
Mom, I want to get my eyes done.
Mom, please?
Can I?
Please?
Your eyes are just fine.
You're not ugly.
I am ugly.
No wonder I can't get any parts.
You didn't fail your auditions because you're ugly.
It's because you can't act.
I want cosmetic surgery!
I have no money.
You always say that.
Come on, mom.
Please?
Just once?!
- I got no money. None.
- Surgery!
No money. No money.
Your mom never has any.
Who is it?
I'm here to check out your room.
This room is really perfect for just one person.
I don't mean to be rude,
but what kind of work do you do?
What do I look like I do?
Since you came all the way out here for a room,
You probably need a quiet work space
You're right.
I'm a writer.
I see,
what kind of writer?
I write trashy comments on the Internet.
Excuse me?
I'm kidding.
I write novels.
Oh, you're an author.
No, not a big author.
I'm a bit peculiar.
I just can't write in hotel rooms,
and the city is too loud.
This neighborhood is really quiet.
Oh yeah?
Well, the room seems just fine.
Could I trouble you for a cup of tea?
How long does it take to write?
Well, it depends on the book.
This one,
I think maybe about a month.
So you're looking for short-term lease.
Yes, I am.
Wow, you have a nice view.
Hmm?
Yeah.
How are the neighbors?
Do they visit each other often?
No, not really.
They're mostly old folks being concerned.
Here's your tea.
Thank you.
Hmm, this tea is Tie Guan Yin.
You must know a lot about tea.
Not at all.
I just enjoy tea from time to time.
- By the way,.
- Yes?
It's customary to charge two months' rent upfront.
One month rent is impossible to find, anywhere.
You're home.
How was school?
What's this?
Where are your manners?
- I'm really sorry. Excuse me.
- Sure.
What is the matter with you?
Who is he?
He's here to see the room.
That guy? Alone?
Are you crazy?
Who are you calling crazy?
Can't you tell?
He's a writer. A gentleman.
No way.
Why not?
Where else will we get money from, huh?
I can't exactly afford to turn him down.
Well, I don't like him.
Send him back.
Send him where?
Keep it down.
I said no.
He'll hear you. Be quiet,
Seong-Ah Hahm!
Get him out, now!
He stays.
Settle down!
I don't like him.
Be quiet,
Seong-Ah Hahm! Hush!
I don't like him!
I said be quiet!
Oh, you really don't have much stuff.
All a writer needs are his laptop and a desk.
What else?
You're annoying.
Who rents a room to steal a piece of china?
This is the only way to discretely
look for it without the fuss.
I can't afford to get in trouble by tying up those girls.
Do you want the table here?
Oh, you're here.
Shouldn't we sign a lease or something?
Should I ask the realtor?
Oh, no problem.
I don't care if we do.
I just don't want to waste any money on brokerage fees.
I'm only here for two months.
Hey, you must be uncomfortable.
I should show you some ID.
Oh no.
I didn't mean it like that.
No, no.
We should be clear on this.
My publisher says even authors
need business cards nowadays.
Hyeong-Gook Park,
Author Mangook Publishing
- Well, make yourself at home.
- Okay.
- See you later.
- Bye.
Did you get a tenant?
I saw a man.
Yes, I rented out the room upstairs.
A man moved into a house of two girls.
He's a writer.
He writes novels.
A man who's a writer moved into a house of two girls.
What's up?
- Um, sir.
- Yes?
- I'm really sorry, but...
- Yeah?
- I've been thinking and...
- Well, ma'am,
I paid you two months' rent upfront, right?
Yes, two months.
Then I have the right to live here for two months, right?
Why, of course...
Did you want to say something?
Um, would you like some dinner?
I only eat fruits when I write.
- How about some tea?
- No thank you.
Well, you should get some rest then.
Okay, then.
Good night.
Who's she think she's dealing with?
I love you.
Seong-Ah Hahm!
- Oh my...
- He's so hot, isn't he?
Look at you pretending like you don't know.
I really don't know.
- You really don't know?
- I don't.
- You went karaoke-ing that time.
- How would I know that?
Then she's all mine.
Let's see who wins this battle.
- You're home early.
- Yeah
It isn't much,
but this is Bolay tea.
I thought you might appreciate gourmet tea.
Oh, thank you.
I haven't tried it yet...
I haven't had that tea, yet.
Oh, would you like some tea?
No, you don't have to.
Thank you.
- Give me a minute.
- Sure.
You have a lot of plants here.
Yeah.
It's interesting to put them on the steps like this.
- By the way, sir.
- Yes?
What kind of story are you writing?
Well, that's...
What I'm writing is...
about a woman.
Once she had many dreams.
She was pretty.
But one day,
she looked back
and those days were gone.
This isn't the life she wanted.
She's like my sister,
crying in front of a mirror.
That's what I'm working on.
Speaking of,
Could I come down to interview you sometimes?
Me?
Yes.
I think you're similar to the character in my novel.
Well, I don't have much of a story.
No, no.
Everyone is the main character in their life story.
Oh that.
I put up bricks and plastered with cement.
- Cement?
- Yeah.
You plastered the wall with cement?
Yeah, so it's quiet.
- The whole wall?
- Yes, completely.
- Have a seat, sir.
- Okay.
- Well, sir.
- Yes?
I'd hate to bring this up again,
but I asked around and
even a short-term tenant
should pay a deposit.
- Really?
- Yes.
If you can't come up with the deposit right away,
maybe you can pay more rent?
Isn't it like 100 dollars more for every 10 grand?
Well, you're right.
I will get it to you.
Good.
I will write up the lease.
I thought I told you I don't need the lease.
Hey, Seong-Ah.
Sorry about her.
She's going through puberty.
No worries.
Not like it's the first time she's being rude.
Where did you learn to behave like this,
in front of an elder?
How would that make me look?
He's hanging out here now?
Don't overreact.
He's just having tea.
I hate him.
Make him leave.
Why are you acting so weird?
He must feel so uncomfortable.
Why are you treating him like he's fecal matter?
How nice,
comparing me to shit.
Why can't you be considerate of others?
Whatever. I hate him.
Send him home.
How come you hate so many things, huh?
Hey, you're still up studying.
I just came out for some air.
I couldn't write.
Alright then.
Here, buy yourself a book.
No discipline around here, huh?
What do you mean,
you can't get through the stairs?
She brick-walled it and plastered cement all over.
And you moved in without even checking that out?
Don't get upset.
I'll take care of it.
We assured them it'll only take 3~4 days.
Tell them to wait a few.
And send me money for the deposit.
Wow, it's really nice in here.
Did you decorate it yourself?
With my husband.
Here.
What you asked.
By the way,
I need to use the Internet for research,
but I don't get Internet connection from my room.
Could I use the computer downstairs?
Well, the computer...
The additional deposit.
Two months worth.
Thank you.
I'll only need to use it for 3~4 days.
That's not going to work.
What?
It doesn't look good if you're
downstairs by yourself during the day.
Well, I'll be quiet during the day.
Who's going to see me?
There used to be some unique items
here when the husband was around.
The husband died in a unique fashion last year.
Did I say something wrong?
It's okay.
You didn't kill him.
If it's Internet fee,
I will pay you.
I even gave you the deposit.
Wait a minute.
I rightfully deserved that deposit.
Come on.
Seriously, I only need a month to finish writing,
but I paid rent for two months.
Then you asked for more deposit,
which I paid.
Still, you won't let me use the Internet?
Nowhere in this country can
you rent a room for one month,
not unless it's a motel.
There's a cyber cafe down the street.
How can a writer work in a cyber cafe?
There are loud kids,
playing games.
Why are you yelling at me?
When did I yell?
It's just the Internet.
Just go to the cyber cafe, go!
It's been a while.
You must be out of your prescription.
It must be half-life.
The pills are not working anymore.
You still can't sleep without drinking?
But I don't drink hard liquor.
I only drink wine or beer.
It doesn't matter what kind of alcohol you drink.
I told you many times.
Drinking every night isn't good for you.
Do you still often get irritated?
But, that's not depression.
Getting angry with people around you,
saying things you regret.
That can also cause you to feel depressed.
Doctor, please.
Stop staring at me like that.
What?
It feels like your eyes are shooting sharp knives at me.
I know it's rude of me to say,
but your eyes don't look right.
Just when I'm ready to share with you,
I see your eyes and shut up.
I was just walking by and saw,
Jeong-Shim Kim, Psychiatrist
and thought you were a female doctor.
What kind of man has a name Jeong-Shim?
Honestly, if you were a woman,
Maybe I'd feel more comfortable sharing.
But when I'm with you,
I feel like a kid getting scorned by a teacher.
Why can't you make your patient feel at ease?
All you do is criticize and pick me apart.
It's not too late.
Feel free to go else where.
To a female doctor.
And my apologies my family named me a girly name.
Do you angry?
Next time,
try this doctor.
She is really feminine.
Got Milk?
Girl Seong-Ah Hahm Today
Did you put shit in your milk?
Mom, the kids are...
Yeah?
Nothing.
Goodnight.
Go to sleep.
What are you doing here?
What if someone sees you?
How is your writing coming along?
How can I write,
when I can't use the Internet?
- Hey, Mister
- Huh?
- Can you buy me a drink?
- What?
What is your name?
Oh, it's Yeon-Joo.
Yeon-Joo Choi.
Yeon-Joo Choi...
Yeon as in "become" and Joo as in "jewel"
Joo as in "house"
Joo as in "house" because you own the house.
You know, sir.
Do you really think my story can be used for your book?
Sure.
I'm not good at logically telling
a story about my circumstances.
No, no, no.
I can totally relate.
I haven't said anything, yet.
Desperation.
Something that desperately asks me to hear you out.
That's hit my imagination.
Hit you?
When did I hit you?
Listen, lady.
You must be my muse.
I will repay you with a great story.
Excuse me.
I have to go to the restroom.
Okay.
How long to copy this?
I'll try to be back by dawn.
That's too late.
Just keep her occupied.
You're good at it.
I got married straight out of high school.
No wonder...
I thought it was weird you have a kid in junior high.
Thirty-five.
I'm an oldie in her mid-thirties.
So weird.
Koreans just love it when you say
they look a year or two younger.
If they love looking younger so much,
let's count our age the exact way,
like they do in European Union.
Then you can be in your early thirties.
Early thirties.
Feels different, right?
You're really good with words.
You know, us writers,
we keep a hundred,
no thousands of thoughts in
our heads to get one thing out.
- You're like a con artist.
- What?
Nothing.
Hey, here.
One more.
It goes in,
but keeps getting errors.
I know,
but I'm in a hurry.
What, depression?
At first,
I couldn't figure out what I was feeling.
It was all so sudden,
new emotions. I was going crazy.
I know.
Steel doesn't get rusty overnight.
It takes a lot of time,
being exposed to sun,
and getting rusty by rain.
Sometimes, even washing dishes
seems like an impossible task.
Fatigue.
Simple routine life.
It's easy for homemakers to get depression.
Work out.
Before going to bed,
if you run an hour on the treadmill,
you'll fall asleep like a baby.
I thought this was my interview.
Shouldn't you be listening to me?
Stop interrupting.
I was just trying to help.
Who asked you to help?
Since you're a writer,
I thought you'd be a good listener
But I guess not.
All Korean men are the same.
Any old guy can just tell you what to do,
like they have a license to give advice,
issued by government.
What?
You've never seen a woman smoke before?
- Sir!
- Yes
It's my interview.
Let me do the talking.
Okay.
You know, lately
I can't sleep,
at all.
My body is so tired,
but I can't fall asleep.
But I can't just get up again.
It wears me out all night.
By the time I close my eyes it's already morning.
Then when I wake up,
I feel depressed all over again.
'I should get out of bed.'
'I should shower first.'
'I have to send the kid to school.'
'I have to do the dishes.'
But I just stay in bed crying.
'Here's another terrible day.'
Hey,
Where are you going?
Let's have one more drink.
Just one more.
I've already had too much.
But I'm not done interviewing you.
Later.
Do it later.
What are you doing?
I want to know more about you.
No, don't.
Do you want to know how to slow down time?
You have to experience something new.
Something you've never experienced before.
You're still in early thirties.
Early thirties.
According to EU.
You're still young and beautiful.
I'm beautiful?
Young and beautiful, Yeon-Joo.
Don't be sad.
A woman as beautiful as you deserves to enjoy life.
I've been meaning to tell you.
I like how your voice resonates.
I feel like I'm in a bathroom.
Yeon-Joo.
Yes, sir.
Am I late?
Where's the girl?
In my room.
I gotta get back.
Is this why you moved in?
Have your cake and eat it, too?
Bastard.
- Yeon-Joo
- No
Yeon-Joo
I have to go back before she wakes up.
Oh, Yeon-Joo
Sir, I have to send her to school.
Okay.
Yeon-Joo.
See you later tonight.
Promise?
Man, that was close.
Nothing in life is easy.
What are you doing?
I missed you, Yeon-Joo.
Last night didn't happen, okay?
Yes, I found something in the
same shape with different print.
Yes, two.
I'll bring them over.
- Any word?
- Not yet.
They said it won't take long.
Could he be of help?
Sir, there are a lot of eyes watching.
Having someone like him come to the office is a little...
He's a hard worker.
Why are you being mean?
I wasn't being mean, but...
Hey, Mr. Song!
Why are you so frigid?
Hey, Seong-Ah.
What are you doing? Be quiet.
I didn't do anything!
Mr. Upstairs
Landlady
Why aren't you in school?
Seong-Ah Hahm,
don't you hear me?
Let go of me.
Do I have to get called in to school?
Then don't go.
Then stay out till sundown.
Don't come home and get on my nerves!
I came to get my bag.
Nicely done.
Good job.
Don't skip out on your after-school academy!
Your home is now secured.
Mister.
I've been so worried.
You weren't around for days,
not picking up your phone.
The door was open.
I'll leave now.
What's wrong with you?
Oh my...
what happened?
I'm not that great a woman.
Ah, Yeon-Joo...
I'm really tired.
I know.
I know what you mean.
No, Yeon-Joo.
That's not...
- Mister.
- Yeah
Don't say anything.
No, Yeon-Joo.
It hurts me, too.
Yeon-Joo.
You're choking me. It hurts.
So it wasn't in the basement?
I went through everything.
It's not there.
You didn't answer your phone for days.
They thought you bailed and went ballistic.
Don't worry about them.
They want it,
they can wait.
How could I not worry?
They kept asking for the address.
You didn't pick up the phone...
Hurry up.
Nothing seems to be missing.
Has this happened before?
No, first time in this house.
Any new faces lurking around the house?
No one's home during the day,
so I don't know.
Even at night,
not sure...
There's one upstairs.
The writer guy.
Who is he?
No, he's not.
Don't worry about it.
How can I not worry?
A man moves in with my neighbor and they get robbed...
Why don't you mind your own business?
Where were you during the day?
Did you see anybody suspicious?
Think about it.
A man moves into a house with two girls...
then something like this happens.
- Goodnight!
- You, too.
Hyeong-Gook Park
Hyeong-Gook Park, author
No search result
Mr. President.
What are you trying to do here?
Our people underestimated it
because it was a residential house.
I apologize.
Stay out of grown-up business and
go play with your friends,
okay midget?
Mr. President.
Do you think I don't know how to handle a girl?
Your whole stunt was caught on security camera.
If any one of them talks,
your name will come up.
A rich kid hires thugs to steal a piece of china...
Your dad will be proud.
Mr. Ghang.
Think of Mr. Ha's position.
Wrap it up.
Mr. President.
Do you really want the Blue Dragon Tea Cup?
Yes, of course.
Mr. Ghang, I want it.
Then if you'd just let me be as I asked,
it will all be resolved soon.
Why are you being uncooperative?
If this is what you want,
let's call the whole thing off.
Don't be like that now,
Mr. Ghang.
Just hang in there, okay?
Keep it up.
Mr. Ghang.
Let's go now, okay?
He's the one not keeping his word,
isn't he?
I can understand where Mr. Ghang is coming from.
Whose side are you on?
I'm not siding with him.
It's just...
If things go wrong,
it won't be good for the company
Stop it.
Man, you're frigid!
You should lay low until this gig is over.
What's this?
Chang-In Ghang
A few years ago,
you did some work with Mr. Kwon?
That was ages ago.
Mr. Kwon is in custody.
Everyone is getting arrested.
Dumbasses.
You keep stalling,
you'll be caught too.
I was planning on leaving the
country after this gig anyway.
You know the kid from back when
he's got a golf club in the Philippines.
He said he'll let me in,
if I brought a few hundred grand.
Wake up.
He's playing you.
Mind your own business?
- What?
Should I stay home tomorrow?
Why?
You know why.
To be with me?
You should go to work.
Modern women are beautiful when they're at work.
Come here.
I'll tuck you in.
And you'll go to work tomorrow.
Okay.
Alarm disabled.
Welcome.
Shouldn't you be in school?
Well, how do I say this?
When I was your age,
I didn't want to go to school either.
You can stay there,
you know.
There were some difficult times.
Wait!
- Yeon-Joo.
- Hi, sir.
Your daughter is home.
So?
Shouldn't she be in school at this hour?
Pay no attention.
She'll be fine in a few days.
A few days?
No.
In EU,
not sending your kids to school is
considered child endangerment.
Watch yourself!
No, as a member of UNICEF,
I must say something.
Send her to school.
That's the right thing to do as a parent.
Why did you skip school again?
You made me look bad.
What's going on with you lately?
Since when do you care about my school?
When have I not cared?
What other mom drives her kid
to the school every morning?
You wanted to practice driving.
What's gotten into you today?
Don't even think about getting your face fixed.
Fix your personality first!
My face can be fixed,
but not my personality.
Because I was born mean.
Mom, you've got it better though.
You're pretty even with bad personality.
What a thing to say to her mother!?
Seriously, what's wrong with you?
You've never done anything for me.
Why start being a mom now?
Some mothers toss their kids off the balcony,
Because they don't want to raise them.
You should be thankful.
And she calls herself a mom.
I was only nineteen years old.
If I hadn't given birth to her...
You shouldn't say such a thing.
That miserable bastard.
My father-in-law.
I had dreams.
I wanted to do things.
Which is more the reason to focus on Seong-Ah.
Send her to school and
I was always by her side when she was little
and going on commercial shoots and television.
I thought she was going to become a huge star.
She was pretty like me when she was little.
She's still pretty,
just as long as she doesn't skip school...
Yeah, she's pretty.
She's okay,
but her personality is not pretty.
Whenever I saw her father's face in her,
I just...
Full of stupid hopes to run a big business,
investing in all kinds of failure
All he left me is just the tiny store.
What am I supposed to do now?
Yeon-Joo, calm down.
Just focus on Seong-Ah.
We should've bought an apartment building,
like I said.
A house with a yard.
A yard?
When he was obsessed with getting a yard,
I should have stopped him,
And bought an apartment!
You know the quarterly financial
meeting at HQ on Monday?
So?
Gallery purchases will be included.
Isn't the gallery spending not open to public?
Your father gave the order.
Dad?
No one should suspect I touched the slush fund.
Can Mr. Ghang be trusted?
Is the Blue Dragon Tea cup worth it?
Yes, it is.
It was in the newspapers in China.
I mean,
Can I rely on Mr. Ghang and just wait forever?
I already ate.
- A kiss?
- Come on.
I'm embarrassed.
Really?
A crazy customer?
I know right?
- Hey Yeon-Joo?
- Yeah?
I'm writing a really important part.
- Can I call you back?
- Okay.
Okay, I'll call you right back.
Why won't it go through?!
Stop texting.
Let me get some work done.
Landlady
Who invented mobile phones?!
Hello?
Yeon-Joo, I miss you.
You're coming home?
Now?
- What is it?
- What were you spying on?
What do you mean,
spy on?
You kept watching.
What did you see, grandma?
Who are you calling grandma?
Me?
Where do I look like a grandma?
You're not exactly middle age,
so what'd you see, grams?
Who cares what I saw?
How am I a grandma?
Look!
Look at me!
Let's be careful, neighbor. Damn!
You be careful, son.
Wow, you've got a lot of stuff.
What's good for a housewarming gift?
How much is this?
That's for me.
That man who moved in your house,
the writer.
What about him?
I let it go then because you said it was okay.
But I googled him.
There was no writer with that name.
You can find anyone on the Internet.
Isn't that strange?
He's not a new comer,
but there are no books.
How old is he?
Don't you know?
Are you here to buy something or ask questions?
Well,
How much is this?
$250
Really?
This chunk of metal?
It's not even the silver candlestick from Jean Valjean.
Then, don't bother.
I will buy something next time.
Hyeong-Gook Park,
Author Mangook Publishing
- Yes?
- Is this the publishing house?
What?
Oh, yeah.
This is Mangook Publishing.
You're close to your destination.
You've arrived at your destination.
Re-routing.
Entering Mangook Publishing
Mangook Antiques
Hey, Yeon-Joo. You're home early.
My publisher...
Show me everything you've written.
You said this place helps you write better.
What's going on?
Why didn't you want to sign the lease?
I told you.
I'm only here for two months.
I didn't want to waste brokerage fees.
Show me your resident ID card, then.
Alright, alright.
Look at me.
Ah, you came from the publishing house, right?
I was just borrowing a phone number from a friend.
My office is going to officially open in the city next month.
You're going to come, right?
- Are you a gigolo?
- What?
Have I been played by a gigolo?
No wonder,
you can smooth talk.
Well, guess what?
I don't have any money.
The mortgage on this house isn't paid for.
That one shop?
It's all debt.
- Come on, Yeon-Joo.
- I've got jack.
Yeon-Joo!
You're my sapphire,
my emerald,
and my crystal.
Oh, my lovely pessimist.
Mr. Hyeong-Gook Park
- So, you're a writer?
- Yes?
I'm a big reader myself,
yet I've never heard of you.
That name is my pen name.
Is that wrong?
- Isn't it a bit strange?
- Like what?
You just happened to pick this
town and this house to write?
I needed a quiet place to work,
so here I am.
Is that illegal?
Wouldn't you find a quiet place
in a temple or by the beach?
Fine then.
Help me understand how a grown
man rents a room for a short-term
from a mother-daughter family at their home?
What are you,
the house guest?
You have ulterior motive for being here, right?
Have you nothing to say?
Must I say it out loud?
The two of you!
You don't look good together.
I'm asking you, man to man.
Let go of Yeon-Joo.
I want to let go of her, too.
- Let's go.
- What?
Come on,
to have sex.
Yeon-Joo.
Just hear me out.
There's been a misunderstanding.
Let me explain.
Come on.
Don't do this.
This is not what I wanted.
No...
There's no misunderstanding.
I've been thinking.
What great romance could a widow like me dream of?
Just sex every now and then.
Isn't that right?
At our age?
How old are you, sir?
What do you need my age for?
I'm 43,
actual age.
What have you been doing with your life?
You googled me.
Is it what this is about?
Are these black spots on your hand?
Leave it alone.
- Did you dye your hair?
- You're hurting me.
Seriously, how old are you?
45? 47?
- Fifty?
- What?
Oh my...
you're over 50?
Come on.
I'm not even 50!
Holy crap!
How'd I end up with an old gigolo?
Old gigolo... what?
Yeon-Joo!
December 3, 1967...
why am I telling her my Date of Birth?
You're certain the Blue Dragon Tea Cup is in that house?
I'm sure of it.
All I need is a day or two.
Come on.
Help me out here.
I want to get the hell out of here, too!
Yeon-Joo.
Just talk to me.
Regardless, you should go to work.
Times like this,
you need to move your body.
Are you doing this because of me?
No, it's not you.
It's because of me.
You know I...
You know how I've got problems.
No, it's all my fault.
- I think it's come back.
- No, it's all my fault, okay?
You should go to work, though.
Don't say anything.
I'm not going to school!
Fine.
Do whatever you want!
No, Yeon-Joo.
She has to go to school.
Go, go to school.
Hey, you. Hey!
No, no, no.
It's not like that.
And I'm not a bad guy, okay?
You have to go to school,
and be a better person.
Come on, Yeon-Joo.
You have to send her to school!
Can we just forget about the two of us?
Honestly, being with you makes me feel really old.
It drives me crazy.
Stop!
Enough with that old talk!
Why am I old?
I'm not!
This place is just crap!
Don't go to school.
Quit! Go make money!
Crappy family,
damn you!
Sit down.
I had a hard time getting your number.
No one in your class knows your number.
I don't give my number out.
Did you know who I am?
Of course, I know you.
You always stare at me.
I'm kidding.
I saw your pictures on the Internet.
- You were the "Got Milk?" girl?
- Yes.
I used to have such a crush on you.
I told my mom I wanted to marry you.
You like me,
don't you?
What?
Yeah, yes.
- Why?
- Just...
Because I'm good looking?
- Yeah, you're handsome.
- I know.
Um, okay.
Here, a present!
For me?
Try it on.
Let me help you.
- No, don't.
- Don't move.
- Hey, stop.
- Hold still.
I don't want to!
You used to wear this outfit.
Stop it!
- You're the "Got Milk?" girl!
- I said STOP!
- Stand still!
- No!
Hey, what are you guys doing?
We're just talking.
What'd you say?
Hey, who's hiding back there?
Come out! All of you, go home,
before I call your teachers.
You should be studying!
I'll come check on you.
This is going to be blow up the Internet.
Forget it.
It's no fun.
Sir, Mr. Song has to go.
What else am I supposed to do?
I have to report to my father in 2 days!
Like Mr. Ghang said,
what if things go wrong with the thugs? What then?
I won't ask you to take responsibility,
so don't you worry.
Mr. Song!
Good morning, sir.
Can you round them up?
I should have listened to you.
I should have gotten rid of them.
What are you talking about?
They already know your face.
I'm about to lose it.
That bitch!
Get it together and stop drinking!
Who are you?
Hello, old man?
Take it easy.
You know what I don't get...
Why you're doing this to me.
If you keep this up,
the deal's off.
What deal?
Hey, Mr. Ghang.
If you took the payment in advance,
shouldn't you deliver?
Money or not, if you want to live,
bring it to me by tomorrow morning.
What payment are you talking about?
What payment?
Is 50K not money enough for you?
Do you think all rich boys just hang
out with millions in their pockets?
Sir, let me handle it from here.
Koreans have a twisted prejudice against corporate heirs.
If I hadn't met you,
I'd still be having those wrong ideas.
Hey, you're wearing heels.
I thought you looked taller.
Shut up,
you bastard.
High heels do hurt,
I see.
He's getting away!
Get him!
Hold it!
Stop right there!
Do you see that, kids?
That's what our Mr. Ghang's been emphasizing,
security camera.
We cannot cross this line, understand?
Yes, sir!
You got until tomorrow.
No point in running.
Catching a loud-mouth,
old rat in this country...
easy as pie.
Where is it?
Where did you hide it?
What are you doing?
I'm trying to kill myself.
You can't die like that.
Then how can I die?
What have you got to die for at your age?
Because life is hard.
Here, drink up.
Now, tell me.
Why did you do that?
Because I am ugly.
Really, that's it?
Take off those glasses.
Why?
Just do it.
Come here.
Let me see.
I see.
The glasses are great for you.
They cover up your flaws well.
I was just trying to hide bags under my eyes.
You shouldn't be thinking about
killing yourself over nothing.
There's a Japanese writer,
Murakami Ryu said this once.
Sex over suicide...
I'm only in middle school.
Cheers.
Confess my love.
Don't confess.
Confess.
Don't confess...
Go, Mr. Song.
Go!
What is it?
Mom
Come over here.
What did he do to you?
Hey, Yeon-Joo
What'd you do to my daughter?
What the...
Ugh, my back.
No, Yeon-Joo.
Don't get me wrong.
What are you doing, mom?
No, it's not like that.
You got it wrong.
Open up!
- You're wrong.
- You're hurting me.
You're giving me a hard time.
You're wrong.
Ugh, my back.
Listen, there's a misunderstanding.
Let me explain.
I'm calling the cops.
You can explain it to them.
Why are you calling the cops?
Why not?
- Don't call the cops.
- Why not?
- Just don't!
- Why?
Don't, don't.
Just don't!
Friggin... argh!
How could you do that to a little girl?
- Do what?
- It's not like that, mom.
You just stand back.
Hey, you're a real piece of work.
Your kid is having a life or death situation,
Yet, here you are passed out drunk.
And what do you do?
Wrongfully accuse me?
What do you mean she was dying?
She tried to kill herself.
You daughter, Seong-Hwa. Okay?
It's not Seong-Hwa.
It's Seong-Ah!
Why would you want to kill youself?
What is he talking about?
Tell me he's lying.
Why do you care if I live or die?
You already wish I were never born.
How could you tell her that?
You did.
When you got drunk and had a fight with dad!
Come on, Seong-Ah.
You know I'm not well.
What are you,
blame it on the depression?
Do you know why you're depressed?
It's because your body isn't busy enough.
Women today don't do anything.
Your depression could be cured
by working out every morning.
Don't get smart with me.
Really, I'm sick of your family.
Your husband,
Gi-Soo Hahm.
Didn't he kill himself too?
He didn't want to live with you.
So, he fell off the roof.
Good job,
Gi-Soo Hahm.
How'd you know?
What?
That my husband fell to death.
You told me.
No, I didn't.
How'd you know his name?
You.
You killed my husband.
No, no!
I didn't do it.
Come on,
just hear me out. Stay still.
You're hurting your kid...
- Go away.
- I will explain everything.
Stop throwing things.
Calm down.
I will explain everything.
Don't!
I am sick!
What are you doing in my house?
Stop throwing things.
Look at me. I'm hurting right now.
Let me explain.
Why am I here?
Well, because I am a writer.
I'm here to write.
You must have a reason for coming here!
You really want to hear it out?
Okay, do you know of the Blue Dragon Tea Cup?
It's a tea cup this small.
I don't know what you're talking about...
I think you do.
Don't Don't!
- Well...
- Don't.
Get the hell out of my house.
Your husband told me.
He hid it in this house somewhere.
As soon as I get my hands on it,
I will leave your house,
even if you tell me not to.
I really don't know anything about it.
It's 2 million dollars.
Two!
Mom, let's find it.
With that money,
the store will be okay.
The mortgage will be paid for, too.
And I can afford my cosmetic surgery.
Nothing to lose, mom.
Yes, we're keeping on eye on him.
Over there,
get him!
Get in,
you idiots!
Get closer.
Come on!
Hurry!
Turn around!
Hey you!
You jerk!
Let go of me!
Let go of me.
Let go!
Hey hey!
Get in!
Come back here, punk!
So this is the Blue Dragon Tea Cup?
Can we repair it?
No, we can't.
Can we get something similar looking?
We can't get something like this.
It will have to be of a certain class
to look like a $10 million piece.
I believe Mr. Song took the company car out.
What about it?
We have dozens of eye witnesses and a security camera.
Security camera.
What shall we do now?
You know I'm frigid.
Mr. Cho!
Well, we can report a stolen vehicle
and make sure Mr. Song doesn't come near the company.
Can't get too wrong from here.
Okay, then don't let him near here.
Then you told me not to let Mr. Song come to work.
Mr. Song,
Mr. Schmong.
I need to figure out what to report to my father.
Can we draw up some paper work?
You mean,
fix the book?
Yeah, let's give accounting
100~200 grand and go from there.
Then, let me fire Mr. Song first,
and I'll look into accounting.
Is there really no way to repair this?
Now, no one will be interested in your house.
No matter how long it takes,
go through every inch of your place.
I'm going into hiding for a while.
Call me as soon as you find it.
Go into hiding, why?
Do I really have to explain that to you?
Don't yell at me!
Walk me through it,
step by step.
Okay, missus.
I have to hide out,
because I am wanted.
Does that make sense, missus?
Pull yourself together.
It's 2 million we're talking here.
Without me,
you can't even sell this.
Don't let others take it away from you.
Stay focused!
I'll be going now.
Hey
What about my car?
Seriously, you're worried about your car?
You really annoy me,
you know that?
He was transferred to holdings, yesterday.
So he wasn't really a writer?
He was a cultural property smuggler.
With a long list of priors.
I know I called you out of suspicion,
But I never thought...
- What if he...
- Don't you worry.
He's going to think he got real unlucky and got caught.
He will never suspect you for turning him in.
I did some thinking myself.
Thank you for everything.
Could I have a cup of coffee?
We don't drink coffee.
Oh, Okay.
Did he say anything else?
Like what?
It's nothing.
Never mind.
You want us to do all of this?
What are you saying?
All of these are ours.
Your dads, okay?
Come on.
Give me a hand.
It's cold.
Seong-Ah, don't come out.
I was a gentleman to you two.
Out of respect to your husband,
I offered to split it 50:50.
I'm really sorry.
By the way,
you must know,
There are security cameras everywhere.
You were filmed on your way in,
down the hallway,
in the elevator.
Do you think I care?
Those few minutes on your security
feed isn't going to stop me.
Nice digs!
You got here.
2 million,
my ass.
I got exactly 200 grand.
I know you have a million left,
So don't even think about it.
What's wrong?
When did this begin?
I haven't been able to sleep.
I haven't slept all week.
I think I'll be fine if I can sleep,
But I feel awful.
My life sucks.
I know how you feel.
Do you sleep alright now?
Yes, I sleep just fine.
I don't even take pills anymore.
Bitch, you got better alone.
Can I get a drink?
I quit drinking.
Not fair.
Really, not funny.
I'm doing okay for now,
But who knows?
I'm sorry for hitting you earlier.
We can call it even on the china price.
What china price are we even on?
Look at you,
so coy.
As soon as the bank opens tomorrow morning,
we're going together to get my money.
I'm going to lie down here.
I can't move an inch.
Are you hungry?
What do you want?
Your surgery went well, huh?
Not really.
It's going to be fine,
once it settles in.
It's all settled in already.
Well, the sun will come out again some day.
It's just life.
Warm milk will help you fall asleep.
Damn, I had just fallen asleep.
Man, it's loud in here.
So, is he going to move in with us now?
What?
You know,
we have to split it in half,
And we don't have a room to spare.
Why don't you let me worry about that, alright?