YOUTUBE AND RIDLEY SCOTT AND TONY SCOTT PRESENT IN ASSOCIATION WITH LG
A SCOTT FREE FILMS PRODUCTION
LIFE IN A DAY
[solemn music]
WE ASKED PEOPLE AROUND THE WORLD TO FILM THEIR LIVES AND ANSWER A FEW SIMPLE QUESTIONS
WE RECEIVED 4500 HOURS OF VIDEO FROM 192 COUNTRIES
ALL SHOT ON A SINGLE DAY: 24TH JULY 2010
woman: Isn't he pretty?
[man howling]
[howling continues]
[chuckles]
woman: Can you--
man: Hello.
woman:
Can you speak English?
man: Yes.
woman: What--
man: [chuckles] Oh-ho.
woman: What day is it?
man: Yes.
I like to move it move it.
woman: You know.
man: All right.
This is best day
of my life.
woman: No. I'm asking--
man: Oh, what day?
woman: Yes.
man: Uh, it's, uh...
Wait a minute.
[laughs]
A stupid question.
"What day is it?"
Ah. Sorry.
woman: Okay.
man: It's 24 July.
[laughs]
woman: And what a day it is.
man:
It's the best day ever.
woman: You might be wondering
why I'm up at this ungodly hour.
Like others, I believe
that the time
between 3:00 A.M.
and 4:00 A.M.
is one where the veil
between this world and the next
is the thinnest.
Often during this time
of the day,
I hear the sound
of my name uttered
by an unseen presence.
[dog barks]
[rooster crows]
woman: Good morning.
[woman #2
speaking native language]
[woman laughs]
man: Whoa. [laughs]
[speaking native language]
That's nice.
man: And here we go
into the garage.
That's right.
We're going to ride
in the elevator.
All right.
Let's ride it.
Here it is.
That's right.
This is the elevator
at the Market Parking Garage
in Roanoke, Virginia.
This elevator has been made
famous right here.
Here we go.
Here we are at six,
which is burned out.
Just your basic
Dover elevator.
For all of those of you
at Dover Elevators,
a good brand of elevator.
Now we're gonna go back down
to one.
All right. Now it's time
to go off to work.
[engine turning]
Wasn't that fun?
Gray: You know how much strength
it takes to rebel?
Ha. So this is a night
in the life of S. Gray, man.
You know what I'm saying?
Sleeping on the coach...
with nobo--
Grinding my ass off
every day.
Shorties not enjoying
their mother.
Man not enjoying his wife
or his woman--his lady.
[baby wailing]
Just bullshit, man.
Alpha male trapped in
and locked in
through religion
and politics.
Soon enough, man,
my plans
will all come into perfection.
[celestial choir]
[man snores]
[phone rings]
[toy rattles]
[alarm beeping]
[rooster crows]
[phone rings]
[celestial choir]
woman: [softly] I love you.
man: [softly] I love you too.
[man coughs, gags]
[triumphant
orchestral finale]
[boat horn blows]
man speaking native language:
You need to have a pee.
Tai-Chan.
If you don't pee, you can't
watch TV, can you?
Hmm?
Hey. Here we go.
boy: Why do you have
lots of hair growing?
man speaking native language:
Because I'm a man.
boy speaking native language:
What about women?
man: Women don't have hair,
not as much.
[man speaking native language]
Say good morning to mummy.
boy speaking native language:
Good morning.
man speaking native language:
Here's the incense.
boy speaking native language:
I don't want to.
man: Daddy will do it
alone then, Tai-Chan.
Tai-Chan, here,
sound the bell.
When daddy has put
the incense in,
you can sound the bell.
[bell rings]
Not yet.
When daddy has put
the incense in here.
[bell rings]
That's it.
Good morning, mummy.
boy speaking native language:
man speaking native language:
Good, now put the incense out.
Good.
boy speaking native language:
All done.
I want some water.
[man speaking native language]
[woman laughs]
[man coughs]
man: Today we're gonna
videotape Sasha
doing his first ever shave.
Sasha: Oh, boy.
man: Sasha is how old now?
Sasha: Uh...15.
man: All right.
Sasha: 15.
man: The first thing
Sasha's doing
is getting the water hot
to put a hot cloth
on his face.
Sasha: Yes.
man: So that it'll warm up
your face
and moisturize your skin.
Does he have, like, a nice,
warm face now?
Sasha: It's always been hot.
man: All right. Yes.
Whatever
you say there, dude.
Actually, we should probably
do a close-up of your--
those whiskers.
They're really long now.
[chuckles]
Sasha: Thank you.
man: You need to, like, really
lather it up.
Sasha: Okay.
man: I don't think you need
to put it on your nose.
Sasha: Yeah. Yeah.
man: [laughs]
Sasha: Five-blade razor,
which we got as a sample.
Schwing!
Is it time?
man: Go ahead.
Sasha: Okay, you're shaving
for me.
This is embarrassing.
I'm bleeding.
man: Yes. Don't worry.
You will survive it.
Sasha: Wow.
man: Don't worry.
It will be all right.
Sasha: Oh, wow.
This is torture.
Ow!
man: Does it hurt?
Sasha: Yes.
man: It'll sting
for a little while.
There,
just dry yourself off.
And let's take a look
at the nice...
Sasha: Meh.
man: Nice clean shave.
Good job, buddy. Here.
Sasha: This is not clean.
man: Here's what we do.
Sasha: Agh.
man: Don't--give me--
face the camera here.
And we put a little piece
on there.
See? And it sticks
to the bloody part.
And voila, he's done.
Hey, wait.
High five, buddy.
You survived it.
[animal bells ring]
man: Guys, it's not good
to fall in love with girls
You have wives,
so you are all right.
Whereas I don't have a wife.
Bitch.
man: What day is it today?
man #2: The 24th.
man speaking native language:
No way.
man #2: Then what day
do you think it is?
man: The 25th.
man #2: It's not the 25th.
man: It's the 25th.
man #2: 24th.
man speaking native language:
Oh, dear God.
[man speaking native language]
[man cheering]
man: We're documenting
everything.
Bobby: Wha-ah-ah!
man: Shh.
Bobby: Dah dah dah dah
nah nah nah nah!
Nah nah nah nah
man: Bobby,
let Mommy sleep.
[Bobby laughs]
man: Are you feeling okay?
Cathy: Yeah, I'm just
really tired, you know.
man: Okay.
Bobby: You feel weird?
Okay, this is how
you'll be weirder.
Whoa, tch.
man: Okay,
let's let Mommy sleep.
Bobby: Okay, Mom.
Dah dah dah dah
dah dah dah dah!
man: Bobby, get down.
We're gonna let Mommy sleep.
Bobby: Son of a cuss.
Cathy: Thank you.
Thank you.
Um, I do have
a question, though,
'cause I--my biggest worry
is, you know, of course,
my bandages and stuff.
But I've been taking a sh--
I know I can take a shower,
but I haven't.
But I thought maybe I could
at least try to take a shower
before you got here.
Is that okay if I just go
ahead and do that?
Oh, good. Okay.
Bobby: Dad,
can I come down?
Cathy: Bobby, can we have
a talk, though?
Please, please, please?
Bobby: Oh.
Cathy: I just need
to have a talk, okay?
Because Grandma
is telling me--
all the grandmas,
all the friends are saying
what a great boy you are.
And of course I know that.
And I know that it's hard.
I've never been in a hospital.
I've never been
like this before.
I just need us all
to help each other, okay?
And I know that sometimes
when we ask you
to do something to help,
sometimes it's 'cause
you don't want to go upstairs
'cause you get scared.
And that's fine.
I understand that.
Bobby: Dad's fault.
Cathy: If it's because
you're scared
to go upstairs by yourself
or downstairs by yourself,
just tell me that.
Bobby: I will. Sometimes...
[speaking indistinctly]
And stop videotaping!
Cathy: Bobby...
man: I was gonna give you
a camera too.
Cathy: We're gonna do
a project--
a family project, okay?
Can we all agree
to do the family project?
If not, then we can't do it.
man: Do you want a camera?
Cathy: Okay?
Bobby: What?
man: Do you want a camera
to videotape me?
Bobby: Mm-hmm.
Cathy: It's gonna be
a family project.
I need to have a happy boy
today, okay?
man: You have to be happy
if you have the video camera.
Bobby: Why?
man: Because it's
a happy film.
Cathy: All right?
man: And it has
a happy ending.
[sizzling]
woman: Kompiang,
was I a naughty child?
woman #2 speaking
native language: No.
woman speaking native language:
Truly?
woman #2:
Well, maybe a bit.
[woman speaking native language]
woman: How long have you been
working for our family?
woman #2 speaking native
language: Over 25 years.
woman speaking native language:
What are these offerings for?
woman #2:
To celebrate the full moon.
woman speaking native language:
The full moon?
[woman #2
speaking native language]
woman: What's this one?
woman #2: Pelungsur cake
to indicate that
the ceremony has ended.
[rooster crows]
woman speaking native language:
Which God is this for?
woman #2 speaking native
language: This is to Vishnu.
The water is an offering
for Him.
woman:
Okay, we're coming in...
Okay, first of all--
and I'm sure he hears me
by now--
let me explain something
to you.
Everyone, can you hear me
loud and clear?
My son was supposed to be
cleaning his room yesterday.
Come on, boy!
boy: Woman!
woman: [chuckles]
Woman!
Oh, this is gonna be
a long day, as most are.
boy: [groans]
woman: He's always a bundle
of joy when he wakes up.
Come on, come get in the shower,
get the day going.
We got things to do,
places to go.
boy: Yeah.
woman: People to see,
futures to make.
[lighthearted music]
man: I had
a major heart operation.
I'm very thankful
to the beautiful staff.
No job is too big
or--or too small.
And even down
to a few minutes ago,
just wiping my bum,
because I had my first--
first poop...
[chuckling]
in about a week or so.
So one of them came
to the rescue and said,
"Listen, would you like me
to trim that up for you, sir?"
So I said, "Yes."
And a very--very, um, courageous
young lady in my case,
I think,
did the job.
And just, uh,
all in a day's work.
[chiming faintly]
I'm very, very grateful
for these people
that have treated me like...
Just treated me so well.
In a short--short while...
I-I will be on the road
to recovery,
and I'll be out there again
doing crazy things
and enjoying life.
[overlapping chatter]
man: 56, 56...57.
61 Rupees.
61 going once,
61 going twice.
Sold!
[overlapping chatter]
[ultrasound pulses]
Amanda: I'm Amanda.
What makes me joyful
this Saturday is this...
And a little terrified
and really excited.
woman: Oh, my God,
did you feel that?
Let's try again.
[speaking native language]
Have a listen
if he's sleeping.
[water dripping]
woman: What's up, Beatrice?
[bird chirping]
man: Oh, oh, oh, oh...
[speaking native language]
[relaxed instrumental music]
woman: All right, then.
Oh! Come over here!
What a little miracle you are!
Goodness.
Now your mama has made herself
a little copy of Mama.
[woman speaking
native language]
man singing:
I want to drink
from the clearest water.
I want to eat
the things I ought to.
I just want to know
that I feel strong,
you know.
I want to reach
the greatest mountain.
Climb, if I want,
without all the shouting.
I just want to know
that I feel strong,
you know.
And clouds really
should be white at least,
and oceans should meet us
at the beach,
and I don't want
to overreach
when I know what's in store,
raw love.
Life, a day at a time,
my love.
don't know.
Love.
Life in a day
and life in a day
and life in a day...
I want to drink
from the clearest water.
I want to eat
the things I ought to.
I just want to know
that I feel strong,
you know.
I want to reach
the greatest mountain,
climb, if I want,
without all the shouting.
I just want to know
that I feel strong,
you know.
And clouds really
should be white at least,
and oceans should meet us
at the beach,
and I don't want
to overreach
when I know what's in store,
raw love.
Okhwan Yoon:
Good morning, everyone.
Bonjour.
Buenos días.
Namaste.
Salaam alaikum.
My name is Okhwan Yoon.
I was born in Korea.
It doesn't matter
South or North Korea.
I'm traveling
around the world by bicycle.
[dog barking]
[man shouting
in native language]
Yoon: Today it's been
9 years and 36 days.
[bus horn honking]
This is Kathmandu, Nepal.
I have been in
190 countries so far.
I've been struck by cars
six times.
Five times, surgery.
There are so many careless
drivers in the world.
I have seen many
different sizes of fly.
In North Africa,
smaller fly than here.
And Turkey,
But this size
is same fly in Korea
and in Japan and China.
So I feel very emotional.
[car horns honking]
[door bangs]
[easy jazz music]
man: Travel toothbrush
and toothpaste--
essential if you're spending
a night with the goats.
[wind whistling]
man speaking native language:
3D glasses.
A box with medications
which I need every day
in order to live.
man: Oh, and I have
this plastic glove
from when I was at work
the other day.
man: 50 pesos. Sweet.
man: A 500 rupee note.
2BA 596135.
I still remember the number.
woman:
First is a Canadian flag,
because some of my ancestors
were from Nova Scotia, Canada.
Next is a German flag,
because some of my ancestors
were from Germany.
Some of my ancestors lived
in Wisconsin.
Some of my ancestors
were from Poland.
Altai man that came
in a chocolate egg.
An electric die.
It's an anti-evil
eye protector.
Randy: Metal saw.
Metal eagle.
Metal wheels.
Anybody want some granite?
My name is Randy Raisides,
and this is
Kenneth V. Fletcher's house.
Giant I-beam...
basket with grapes...
pipe bender...
a billion boxes.
He's kind of a hoarder.
I moved here four years ago,
a terrible drug addict.
And in four years,
Ken has done two things.
He has sobered me up,
and he has lost everything.
Good morning.
Ken: Good morning.
Randy: Kenneth V. Fletcher.
Ken: Loser.
Enabler.
What else?
Destitute human being.
Randy: Tomorrow Ken leaves
for the Canary Islands,
where he has gotten a job
as a massage therapist.
And I go back to Nebraska,
where I'm going to be living
with my folks.
He's one of those guys
that has a billion ideas
and never completes
any of them.
Ken wanted a piano
as a kid.
Ken couldn't get a piano
So three years ago, we looked
on Craigslist all summer
and went over
to the Twin Cities
and got pianos!
[Ken playing mid-tempo melody]
The man's a genius. He just
never quite had the time.
It looks like
the auctioneer's here.
[creaking]
[crash]
man: What's in my pocket?
Well, it's a key.
And it's got a really neat
little logo there.
[engine turning, revs]
This is a Lamborghini.
And this is my life in a day.
woman: Here's my wallet
from Marc Jacobs.
There's a Marc Jacobs key chain
that I love.
Mirror.
woman: My iPod,
which is my soul.
man: Rosary.
Very good way
of spending your time profitably
in the eternal dimension.
Telephone headset.
Extremely good way
of wasting your time
in the earthly dimension.
[laughter]
[man speaking native language]
man: It's a small branch
from the Neem tree.
man #2 speaking native language:
What do you use it for?
man speaking native language:
For my teeth.
man: I have nothing
in my pockets. Zero.
man speaking native language:
There's nothing in my pockets.
They're empty.
boy speaking native language:
Money, lots of cash.
man speaking native language:
How much is a lot?
boy speaking native language:
Two-fifty.
man speaking native language:
How much?
boy speaking native language:
Two soles fifty.
[man speaking native language]
man speaking native language:
Is that box your daddy's?
boy speaking native language:
It's my brother's.
To make a lot of money.
man speaking native language:
Hello, Abel.
Are you well?
It's Saturday again.
[men speaking native language]
man: The cold weather is here
and August will be worse,
so you have to
keep warm, Abel.
boy speaking native language:
Hey you, this is my patch.
[men speaking native language]
boy speaking native language:
Sometimes I make five soles.
When I was little, I once
earned 20 soles in a day.
[men speaking native language]
man speaking native language:
Bye. See you next Saturday.
man: What do you have
in your pockets?
It's my knife.
Okay, you can go ahead
and judge me all you want,
but there are some crazy people
in the world.
woman:
My Ruger P94
.40-caliber handgun.
I take this with me
wherever I go.
man speaking native language:
Keys.
Phone.
Syringes.
man speaking native language:
All this is the cemetery.
[keys jingling]
man speaking native language:
Is there anyone living here?
man #2 speaking native language:
Yeah, I will show you.
man speaking native language:
Can I talk to them?
man #2 speaking native language:
Yeah, yeah.
[goat bleats]
man speaking native language:
My story is, I can't work,
because who else would look
after my kids?
My wife passed away,
my children's mother.
I've got a 20 year old son
who is sick.
He's a retard.
We have to tie him up all day
to stop him wandering off.
Fourteen people
live in this place.
We have no electricity,
no water, no drains.
But we are still alive.
God will not forget us.
He created us.
That is what I believe.
God wouldn't have created this
population just to forget us.
[muffled chatter]
[man speaking native language]
Ayomatty:
My name is Ayomatty.
I've been in Dubai
for 13 years.
I work as a gardener,
and I am very happy.
man speaking native language:
There is no work at home.
It's more profitable
to come to Dubai.
I'm here to earn money
to send back to my kids.
man speaking native language:
Pray, be seated.
woman: All you think about
is your belly.
[man speaking native language]
man: Did you see the fence
fell down in those thistles?
Goddamned thistles everywhere.
And you think I'm a prick.
[laughter]
man: This is how
brynza cheese is made.
When all liquid is removed,
the cheese becomes very good.
Nearly as good
as the Dutch cheese.
It even has holes,
in just two, three days.
woman speaking native language:
Oh, come on, stop boasting.
Lunch!
[children panting]
[shrieks and laughter]
[woman singing
in native language]
[all singing in
native language]
[gunshot]
[singing continues]
[singing ends]
man: This is balut.
Only in the Philippines.
man #2: Balut.
man: You see that?
woman: Ew.
man: Oh, gross, huh?
Look, let's put some salt
right there.
That's salt.
And then watch this.
[laughter]
[women singing
in native language]
man speaking native language:
How does it work?
man #2: Well, it goes in
and out again, like a needle.
It doesn't fire bullets.
Nothing comes out of the gun.
man speaking native language:
Ah, I see.
[gunshot]
[clanging]
[women continue singing]
[man groans]
[singing continues]
Jack: Today is Saturday,
the 24th of July.
For the last three years,
I've been away from home
to do my degree.
And as soon
as that finished,
I ended up getting a job
at a very demanding company.
So I don't really get
to see my old man that much.
But whenever I do see him,
we always go to the same place
and do the same thing
and have a catch-up.
man: I just phoned you.
Jack: Yeah, I just got it,
actually.
I was about
to phone you back.
man: How you doing?
All right?
Jack: Yeah, not bad.
man: Mouthful?
Jack: I'll have a mouthful.
man: You sort the tire out?
Jack: Um...
man: That tire's fucked.
Jack: I haven't had time.
You'll get done for that.
Seen it?
You got a rip in it.
Jack: Is that a rip?
man: Why don't you film
down there, Jack?
Let's see if we see a cup.
Come on, that's it.
Jesus.
You're not a student now,
you know.
You're a working man.
There's no excuse.
Just here.
man: Is this
where we're going?
Jack: Yeah.
man: Two small beef burgers,
believe it or not.
Imagine what the large ones
are like or the medium ones.
Ridiculous, isn't it?
Unbelievable.
Anyway, here you go, Jack.
This way.
I'm gonna sit in the car.
[seagulls crying]
What do you got?
Jack: This.
man: Oh.
Is this bit a photograph
of you at uni?
Jack: Yeah.
man: Fantastic.
That's fantastic.
I'm gonna get
a lovely frame on that,
'cause Nina's got a frame
like that.
[laughs]
That's really cool, Jack.
Thank you.
Now, you should be very proud
of yourself, Jack,
considering you almost
got chucked out of school.
You was lucky there,
weren't you?
Yeah, you've matured, actually--
actually, in the last year or so
quite good
into a real proper lad,
a real gentleman
and a nice boy.
[engine turning]
Thanks for that, Jack.
man speaking native language:
Who do you love a lot?
boy speaking native language:
My dad...
because he brings me fruit.
He cooks my lunch,
makes me breakfast.
He prepares everything,
all the food we eat.
He cares more about me
than his work.
The thing I love the most
is my laptop.
In Wikipedia, there are
stories, history, math,
science, religion.
It has everything.
It is a giant library.
[birds chirping]
man: I love being me.
I love life.
It's all such fun.
man speaking native language:
Myself, I'd have to say...
woman speaking native language:
Placing my feet in wet sand.
It has to be wet.
woman: Grass, dirt...
dirty river smell.
Mm, the smell of a campfire
that gets stuck in your hair.
man: Coated chicken
baked in the oven
with seasonings.
man:
What do I love the most?
Well...
you're looking at her.
[crying]
man: I really love my family,
my brothers and sisters.
woman speaking native language:
Being with my children.
And taking care of them.
man speaking native language:
And now I'll introduce you
to the person I love
most in the world.
Hello.
girl speaking native language:
man:
What do you love the most?
man: Women.
So much.
man: I love you, Uliya.
You are my only love.
You are my first love.
For me, love is all about you.
woman speaking native language:
Do you love your husband?
woman #2:
Yes, you have to.
man: I love my wife.
I love my son.
I love my land.
I love my animals--
my dogs, my ferret,
my chickens, my horses
in the background.
I love my life.
But what do I love the most?
I love my Lord,
my heavenly Father,
my Creator,
from whom all blessings flow.
man: I love doing
about 150 miles an hour
down a motorway
in a good car.
man #2: [giggles]
man: I love football.
I think football
is the only sport
that bring people together.
woman speaking native language:
I love...
cleaning something that's really
dirty so you can see the result.
man: I actually love
my refrigerator.
It's such a cool thing.
It remains at one corner.
It keeps its mouth shut.
I love my refrigerator.
Nothing else
but my refrigerator.
man: What do you love?
man #2: Women.
man #3: Freedom.
man: What do you love?
man #4: Power.
man: [laughs]
woman: I love the word
"mamihlapinatapai."
It's from the Yaghan language,
which is now a dead language.
But it was spoken
in Tierra del Fuego,
the very southernmost point
of South America.
I've never heard the word
said properly,
so I could be pronouncing
it wrong.
But the meaning
is quite beautiful.
It means that moment
or feeling
when two people both want
to initiate something,
but neither wants to be
the one to start it.
It can be
perhaps two tribal leaders
both wanting to make peace,
but neither wanting to be
the one to begin it.
Or it could be two people
at a party
wanting to approach each other
and neither quite brave enough
to make the first move.
[birds calling]
Can hear the kookaburras now.
[line ringing]
man: Currently,
I'm calling my mom
to ask her what I should say
to Emily today.
[line ringing]
woman: Hello?
man: Do you have a second
to talk to me?
woman: Sure.
man: Tonight I am hanging out
with Emily.
woman: Okay.
man: But I was planning
on telling her
exactly how I feel about her.
And then I don't know.
So I was calling my mother
to see--
what should I say to this woman?
[woman laughing]
Okay.
I don't know.
I just think that, you know--
just concentrate
on the fact that, you know,
you have very, very high
feelings of esteem for her,
that she's somebody
that you've always admired.
man: "Esteem"?
Is that the word I should use?
Esteem?
You think she'd like that?
woman: Yeah. Whatever.
man: I just don't know
if that's--
woman: You hold her
in very high regard.
man: Ok--I don't know
if those--
woman: She's a special person
in your life.
man: Okay.
I'll try all that.
Hey.
I am on the train now.
This is my friend Emily.
[romantic music]
Uh, hello, "Life In A Day."
I'm still with Emily, and we're
still hanging out in Chicago.
Um, this is...
We--we just came out
of this place, which was cool.
But, uh, I'm gonna
leave this thing on
in case anything
gets climactic.
man: Theresa, look at me.
Theresa: [scoffs]
Oh, my God.
Aah!
[romantic music continues]
man: Well,
so here's the deal.
Uh, I asked her
if she wanted
to go on a romantic date
with me sometime,
and she says, "No."
Just--just no.
That's really all she said.
Just "no."
She didn't want any of that.
Ever, possibly.
Never, ever.
And so, uh...
Well, actually, I said,
"What about the possibility
of a possibility?"
And she said--
She said no to that.
No possibility.
None.
woman: Okay, let me say
that it is meant
for women to kneel down.
For example, a woman is supposed
to kneel down for a man.
man: Mm-hmm.
Do you want to show us
how you do it?
woman: Yes.
man: So you greet Moses, like,
traditionally.
[Moses speaking
native language]
man: Wow. Wow.
Moses,
how do you feel about it?
She comes, and she kneels down
every day?
Moses:
Yes, because I'm a man.
She has to respect.
woman: It's the culture.
[upbeat music]
[cheers and applause]
man singing: Wise men say
only fools rush in.
But I can't help
falling in love with you.
David: Hi, Grandma.
It's David. How are you?
I'm good. I'm still--
Yeah, I'm in New York.
It's--Yeah, it's been really
hot here, but I'm having fun.
Uh, anyway,
I wanted to call you,
because, uh, you know my friend,
uh, Nick, that I--
that you've met a lot...
Yeah. Yeah, I know.
He's a very nice boy.
Uh...
Well, I wanted to tell you
that he's, um, not--
not just my friend.
He's--he's my boyfriend.
Um, and it's something that I've
wanted to tell you for a while,
but I wasn't really sure
how you would react,
so I was a little nervous
to tell you.
Um...
I-I love you too.
Yeah.
I love you too.
And I'm hoping that--
that maybe
you can love Nick too,
um, because he's
really important to me,
so I'm hoping
he can be really--
really important to you too.
Yeah.
Well, that--
that means a lot to me.
Yeah. Thank you.
I--Yeah, I love--
I love you too.
I do. Yeah.
Yeah, my parents know.
Yes.
Well, Grandma,
they call it being gay now.
You don't have
to say "homosexual."
It's not--Yeah.
Yes, it's not a disease.
Thank you.
man: Here, throw some cheese
to those ducks.
Get closer to them.
I'm taking a video, Sarah.
Sarah: They might bite me.
man: No, they won't bite.
Ducks don't bite.
Come on.
I'm making a video.
Walk on out into them.
It'll be a good video.
man #2: Would you like me
to take both of you?
man: Oh.
man #2:
Take another picture of you?
man: Thank you.
man #2: Just tell me
what do you want me to do.
man: Just...just...
man:
So marriage truth number one--
uh, love is a battlefield.
[laughter]
Um, listen, you two are going
to fight like hooded roosters.
Let's just get it out there.
It's science.
You know, place any two animals
in a contained area together,
um, you know, there will be
awesome tenderness,
but also there will be blood.
[laughter]
Tristam: That is my pocket
Walt Whitman.
He was surely one of the
greatest poets that ever lived,
and if my babies can read
Walt Whitman day and night
and learn from him,
I'll be very happy.
After all, babies, he did say,
"I am August.
I do not trouble my soul
to vindicate itself."
No, he didn't say "soul."
He said, "I do not trouble..."
woman: That's enough, Tristam,
you'll use up all the memory.
This is self-indulgent, and--
Please stop.
They need winding.
Please stop, Tristam.
Tristam:
"I do not trouble my spirit..."
woman: Stop being so selfish
and putting yourself first.
Please, I've been looking
after them all day.
Just stop it.
Tristam:
"I do not trouble my soul to--
"I do not trouble my spirit
to vindicate itself
or be understood."
woman: Okay, fine.
man: Ann and John
are today renewing their vows
in the light of their 50 years
experience of marriage.
Rather unusually,
each of this special couple
has agreed to write
the vows of the other.
That is,
Ann has written John's vows,
and John has written Ann's.
man speaking native language:
Pull, pull.
woman speaking native language:
This one doesn't lift me up.
[man laughing]
woman speaking native language:
There is a new one over here.
[man speaking native language]
man speaking native language:
Oh, gosh.
You have to pull on this one.
Can you manage it?
woman speaking native language:
Nope.
man: You have to pull
using your dorsal muscles.
woman speaking native language:
It won't budge.
[man speaking native language]
woman speaking native language:
IT WON'T BUDGE.
man: John, it is necessary
to address
one or two shortcomings
in, uh, the physical side
of marriage.
Surely no one would argue
that there are certain
physical demands
a wife can request
of a husband,
and Ann asks you that you
address these issues right now.
[laughter]
Do you agree to wash
the windows inside and out?
[laughter]
man speaking native language:
It's like at the gym.
You grab here,
you grip there,
and you position yourself
with parallel feet
so you can use
your dorsal muscles.
Then you pull.
[woman laughs]
woman speaking native language:
Oh, really?
man: Ann,
John asks if you will agree
to let him do that thing
you once told him you would
let him do on his 40th birthday,
but still not have yet done.
[laughter]
So, Ann, in anticipation
of your previous answer,
John says, "I suppose
an occasional blow job is..."
[laughter]
woman: Are you trying
every possible way?
I told you it won't move.
It won't move.
So, what was it
you were saying?
[laughter]
man: Finally, in spite of men
obviously being from Mars
and women from Venus,
do you both promise to love
and treasure each other
and enjoy your lovely
family life together
here at Appletree Cottage
for as long
as you both shall live?
both: We do.
[applause]
[clock ticking]
[dog snoring]
[clock cuckooing]
[timer dings]
man speaking native language:
Hey, get up.
What are you doing?
[man speaking native language]
man speaking native language:
So let's go.
Are we going?
Let's go.
[cat meows]
[P.A. announcement
in native language]
[horn blares]
girl speaking native language:
Helmet.
Good-bye, grandpa.
[laughs]
Climb up, skinny!
[man speaking native language]
[horns blowing]
[band playing lively song]
man speaking native language:
Climb up, Virginia.
Go, go, slowly.
[man speaking native language]
[whimsical music]
man: Whoo!
[boy crying]
[cheers and applause]
[helicopter whirring]
[laughter]
man: Do the jerk.
Please do the jerk.
By the end, I'm gonna try
to get the commander
to do the jerk.
man #2: Aah!
man: Why you always
got to stick your tongue out?
Punch Eason in the face
right now.
man #3: Oh, my God!
man:
That's the Rebel Alliance.
And there's the Empire.
Masood: Hi.
This is my room.
And this is our garden.
So my name is Masood...
I live in Afghanistan, Kabul,
and I'm a news photographer.
Here is my house.
And he's my father,
drinking tea.
My mother is praying.
Farid, my brother, is just--
again is staring
in the refrigerator, as always.
Right now I'm in my car,
going to Kabul's old city,
to take some pictures.
Sometimes I like
to just walk around there
looking for a good shot.
These are like my two babies.
I carry them everywhere.
[woman speaking
native language]
[Masood speaking
woman:
Here I am by myself,
because my husband is
a half a world away,
going to work,
fighting for us.
What shirt should I wear?
Which one do you think
will Phil like better?
Hmm?
Which one do you think?
That one?
Is that one the best?
Masood: Here is the market
in the old city.
Most foreigners
think that it is dangerous
to walk around
the streets of Kabul,
but as you can see,
there is no danger...
for us, anyway.
woman: Waiting game.
Waiting game.
[birds chirping]
Masood:
So this is a street
that's normally selling
birds like this.
They call them lovebirds
because they are always
kissing each other.
Sharon: Oh.
Where are you?
Ooh.
Phil: Hi, Sharon.
Sharon: Hi!
Phil: Hi.
Sharon: How's it goin'?
Can you see me?
Phil: Yeah. You did get
all dressed up, didn't you?
Sharon: Yes. Of course.
It's our date night.
[children chattering]
Masood:
Afghanistan comes--
the name of my country
comes with the conflict, war,
suicide attack,
and all the negative points
that we--I mean hear
and listen in the news.
But there is another side
of Afghanistan
that you don't normally see.
These girls make me
feel optimistic
about the future
of my country.
Phil: I love you.
Sharon: I love you too.
Stay safe.
Phil: I will, honey.
You too, okay?
Sharon: Okay.
Phil: Bye.
Sharon: Bye.
[sniffling]
man speaking native language:
It's not easy
to explain motivation.
Can I do something
to reunite Korea?
It looks impossible.
It looks out of my hands.
But impossible is possible.
Bobby: Dad, do you see
my war?
Oh, and the red is bad,
the white is good
of the helmets.
[imitates gunfire]
Oh!
[humming]
man: Oh, it's not so bad.
Cathy: No?
Is there something that's
bleeding under my arm?
Let's see if we can
just get this.
man: Ew.
Cathy: Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, what is it?
[man chuckling]
Cathy: What is it?
man: Looks like
some kind of--
Cathy: Did that
come out of your hair?
man: No, it was on my bag.
It's a ladybug.
Cathy: Oh.
girl: Any kind of monster
or ghosts
or a witch.
boy: Zombies.
man:
What do zombies do?
Okay.
You do a great zombie.
girl speaking native language:
Snakes and ghosts.
[man speaking native language]
man speaking native language:
When I come to work at 1:00 A.M.
and I hear little noises
here and there.
That scares me a little.
woman: I have a fear of dogs.
woman speaking native language:
Cats.
man speaking native language:
Rats.
boy speaking native language:
Lions.
woman: Wasps.
woman: Spiders.
girl: I fear...
robbers...
rapers...
girl: I fear growing up.
man: I'm afraid
of losing this place.
woman speaking native language:
Cultures I don't understand.
man speaking native language:
I am scared of Allah,
nothing else.
woman speaking native language:
I fear nothing.
[woman #2 speaking
native language]
woman speaking native language:
God only.
girl: I'm afraid for all the
people that don't know God.
People who don't get saved
are going to hell.
man:
I afraid of homosexuality.
Homosexuality is like...
is like disease,
and I'm afraid of disease.
man: I stay in my room,
and all I can think about
is whether in a couple of years
someone else is gonna live here,
someone who is not Israeli,
maybe...
maybe someone Palestinian.
man: I guess politics
scares me more than anything.
I wonder if we're gonna get
in another war.
man speaking native language:
When I leave home
in the morning, I'm not sure
if I'll return home safely.
No Afghans expect to
return home safely.
woman speaking native language:
Time is passing,
and I don't have
a boy or girl
and no one will ever
call me "mummy."
man: One of the things I fear
more than anything right now
is that my hair's
starting to fall out.
woman: This is me.
This is what I'm afraid of.
woman: That my husband
will leave me for another wife
because of a lack
of you know what.
child speaking native language:
Divorce.
Divorce. How awful!
woman: I fear loneliness.
man: Not waking up
one morning...
and nobody finding you
for a week.
That'd be interesting.
woman:
Losing someone you love.
That's why I find it
very hard
to really, really connect
with someone.
Because, what do you do
when they're gone?
girl: Because what if God
isn't real?
I believe in Him,
but what if God isn't real?
And we're just going to lie
in the ground, dead forever?
woman: And that's what
I'm afraid of,
being in this grave.
Life is so freakin'
short, you know?
man: Dying, I guess.
[animal bells ringing]
[thunder rumbling]
[dog growling]
[man speaking native language]
man: The dogs are
frightened of thunder.
man speaking native language:
Yeah, they're scared.
man: Vasya, we need to find
some fireworks somewhere.
Because in autumn,
wolves will come.
man: We need to hurry home.
It's going to rain!
all:
3...2...1...
[cheering]
man: Welcome
to The Love Parade.
[electronic music playing]
woman speaking native language:
Look ahead!
[cheers]
[overlapping shouting]
man speaking native language:
Unreal. Unreal.
Look at the side.
What are they doing there?
Look at the fighting there.
We can't get out.
man speaking native language:
Not normal, bruv.
[overlapping shouting]
[sirens blaring]
man speaking native language:
Dickhead.
man: I don't want to
move out of the way.
man speaking native language:
Stop this shit!
[overlapping shouting]
man: A tunnel
has become a death trap.
At least 18 people were kicked
or crushed to death
in a stampede during
The Love Parade in Duisburg.
woman: Many of the hundreds
of thousands of revelers
were unaware
of the tragedy unfolding.
[uneasy musical buildup]
man singing:
I want to drink
from the greatest water.
I want to have
all the things I ought to.
I just want to know that
I feel strong, you know.
I want to reach
the golden fountain,
beat everyone
without all the doubting.
I just want to know that
I feel strong, you know.
And clouds really
should be white at least,
and oceans should be there
at the beach.
And who needs books
when we've got speech?
And who knows what's in store
for raw love?
Life, a penny at a time.
Oh, love, life
a penny at a time.
Love, life
Oh, love.
[fireworks whistling,
popping]
man speaking native language:
When I close my eyes,
I can see all different people
in the world
from town to town,
from country to country.
I can feel it, I can touch it,
I can see it.
I feel like born again
because of my haircut.
It's time to continue
my journey.
man: Who do you love?
Cathy: My silly boys,
the Bobby-ells.
Okay. What do you fear?
man: Well, I guess...
I'm fearless now.
I guess my fear was
that you'd get cancer,
and you did.
That you'd get it again,
I mean.
And you did.
But it's over with.
So I'm fearless.
[haunting music]
[overlapping chatter]
[thunder rumbling]
woman: July 24, 2010.
It's nearly midnight now,
and I'm running out of time
to make this.
I worked all day long,
on a Saturday--yeah, I know.
The sad part is...
I spent all day long hoping
for something amazing to happen,
something great,
something to appreciate this day
and to be a part of it
and to...
show the world that
there's something great
that can happen
every day of your life,
in everyone's life.
But the truth is,
it doesn't always happen.
And for me, today...
all day long,
nothing really happened.
I want people to know
that I'm here.
I don't want to cease
to exist.
[thunder rumbling]
I'm not gonna sit here
and tell you
that I'm this great person,
because...
I don't think I am...
at all.
I think I'm a normal girl,
normal life.
Not interesting enough...
to know anything about.
But I want to be.
And today...
even though...
even though nothing great
really happened,
tonight I feel
as if something great happened.
[thunder rumbling]
[water dripping rhythmically]
man singing:
I want to drink
from the clearest water.
I want to eat
the things I ought to.
I just want to know
that I feel strong,
you know.
I want to reach
the greatest mountain.
Climb, if I want,
without all the shouting.
I just want to know
that I feel strong,
you know.
And clouds really
should be white at least,
and oceans
should meet us at the beach,
and I don't want
to overreach
When I know what's in store,
raw love.
Life, a day at a time,
my love.
Life a day at a time,
don't know.
Love.
Life in a day
and life in a day
and life in a day...
I want to drink
from the clearest water.
I want to eat
the things I ought to.
I just want to know
that I feel strong,
you know.
I want to reach
the greatest mountain.
Climb, if I want,
without all the shouting.
I just want to know
that I feel strong,
you know.
And clouds really
should be white at least,
and oceans
should meet us at the beach,
and I don't want
to overreach
when I know what's in store...
[instrumental and chorus]
[rhythmic dripping,
haunting melody continues]