Релиз подготовлен
специально для сайта firebit.org
[laughing]
[grunts]
[animal]
- Sorry!
- Hmm. Sheesh.
Релиз подготовлен
специально для сайта firebit.org
[squawking]
[panting]
Ooh! Ooh!
Wait for me!
Hold the boat!
I'm coming!
Noah! Mr. The ark,
I'm here.
Oh, barely made it.
For a minute,
I thought you'd leave without...
Oh, oh.
Gee, Mr. Noah... Sir.
I'm gonna come too.
What are you anyway?
Oh. Good question.
Technically speaking,
let's say,
put me down as a "whatever."
What do you mean?
What is your species?
Well, I-I...
I don't know.
I guess there's only one of me.
Then you are doomed!
[gasps]
[thunderclaps]
Wait, wait!
Oh.
[door opens]
huh?
Um...
yes, sir?
You may need this.
But, but, but...
But?
Ooh!
Oh... No!
No!
No, no, no!
I don't wanna be alone!
No!
[muttering]
no, no.
No, I don't wanna be alone.
No, no.
- No!
- [screams]
I don't wanna be alone!
You're not alone.
Who said that?
Gee, I don't know.
Maybe it's the rat who's
hanging out of the window!
- Rizzo?
- No, it's Santa.
But I forgot my reindeer.
I'm sorry, Rizzo.
Yeah, right.
Ah, boy.
I had that
weird dream again.
Oh, yeah? The one
with the goat, the dwarf
and the jar of peanut butter?
No, it was the one where...
ah, forget about it.
You wouldn't understand.
I'd understand!
Come on, we're roommates.
Hey... Hey, hey.
I'm here for you, man.
Well, okay. It's the one
where I'm talking
to this Noah guy.
And he won't let me
on his boat
because I'm all...
[snoring]
Alone.
Good night, Rizzo.
- [clucking]
- [alarm ringing]
- [whistle blowing]
- [buzzing]
[ringing]
Ahh!
Morning!
# she's a brick house #
# she's mighty mighty
just lettin' it all hang out #
# she's a brick house #
# the lady's stacked
and that's a fact #
hey, man.
# she's a brick house #
[grumbling]
[screams]
# when we're together
everybody knows #
# this is how
the story goes #
[grunts]
[growling]
ahh!
[growling continues]
Oh! Ah!
# how can she use
the things she use #
# 36-24-36
what a winning hand #
[toilet flushes]
# she's a brick house #
# she's mighty mighty
just lettin' it all hang out #
# she's a brick house #
# the lady's stacked
and that's a fact #
# ain't holdin' nothing back #
# she's a brick house #
[yelling]
[yelling continues]
[grunting]
I do it all for you,
ladies.
[grunts]
[squawks]
# she's a brick house #
# the lady's stacked
and that's a fact #
# ain't holdin' nothing back #
# shake it down, shake it down
shake it down now #
shake it down now
shake it #
Scrunch it and right,
then left.
Suck in those tummies,
ladies.
Hmm?
Huh?
# oh, a brick #
# house #
That was great.
Way to get down
with your bad selves.
Pass the bagel.
Good morning, Rowlf.
Good morning.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning, Kermit.
Hello, little people!
What an absolutely
splendid day!
How are you this morning?
Oh, late! I start
my fabulous new job today.
We megastar TV journalists
have to be punctual, you know.
TV journalist? Since when... got to
run. Bye, Kermie. Kissie, kissie.
# [humming]
Is breakfast over?
No. Why?
'cause I think the bacon
just ran out.
[laughing]
The raspberry flapovers
will be out in a moment.
Hey, uncle Kermit,
what are you gonna do now
that you're on vacation?
Robin, as soon as I get
those housepainters started,
I'm going to kick back
and relax.
Kermit?
When will you fix the oven?
What's wrong
with the oven?
- [explosion]
- that.
Yurski burski
popovers kaboofed!
I'll put it
on the top of my list.
There is a menu correction,
okay?
We will now be serving
bologna sandwiches.
[everyone grumbling]
but no bread.
- Eew!
- I'm already gone.
Gonzo, aren't you performing
at that bar mitzvah today?
Nah. The electric mayhem's
covering for me.
Shalom!
[grunting]
oy!
But you never miss the Chance
to shoot yourself out
of a cannon. Something wrong?
Nah.
Okay.
It's just that I'm sick
and tired of being
a one-of-a-kind freak.
Gonzo, you are not
You're a...
A...
a whatever?
Well... Yeah.
You see?
You see what I mean?
I don't even know where
I came from or who I am.
Yo, Kerm.
You weren't waiting for
some housepainters, were you?
Yeah.
They're just driving away.
- What?
- Animal bit one of 'em.
Oh, no! Wait, guys!
Don't let 'em go!
You know what you are,
Gonzo?
What?
Distinct.
[car engine revving]
[Kermit]
wait, guys. He didn't mean it.
He's just a musician.
[animal]
musician! Musician!
[Gonzo]
distinct, huh?
More like extinct.
Oops.
[Gonzo]
"watch the Sky"?
Hey! Hey!
Rizzo, come here.
I think my Kap'n Alphabet
is sending me a message.
I know what you mean.
I had some guacamole and
it's still speaking to me.
No, no, really!
Look, look.
I'm not kidding.
It was there just a second ago.
I swear, Rizzo.
It said, "watch the Sky."
Are you sure it didn't say
"you need help"?
But, but...
Maybe you and your cereal
would like to be alone.
[grunting]
oh, boy!
# my bologna
has a first name #
# it's o-s-c-a-r #
Cool!
Huh.
"are you there?"
Rizzo!
[Rentro]
"C.O.V.N.E.T. Top secret
national security facility.
"mission: Investigate threat
of extraterrestrial attack.
Cleverly disguised
as a cement factory."
[sinister laugh]
General Luft, welcome.
I'm on a schedule, singer.
What have you got?
Hard evidence.
We finally got 'em.
[singer over intercom]
Rentro?
Yes, sir?
The remote.
The goat?
The remote!
The remote.
I thought he said "the goat."
Over the past few months,
We have received
some unusual communications.
Communications, sir,
that are not of this Earth.
Really?
Sorry about that, general.
Here you go.
Here's your remote.
Thank you, Rentro.
[singer]
we believe that aliens
are using a contact on Earth...
To plan their invasion.
This same message,
"are you there,"
Has appeared
all over the world.
We've been lucky enough
to capture these instances
on film.
The Pyramid at Giza.
Stonehenge.
Okay, this one says...
"are you three,"
but we believe that to be
a simple spelling error.
This could be vandalism,
a practical joke.
Now, you see that?
That's what I said, general.
These photos are...
I'll just
be over here then.
Right this way, general.
When I plotted these anomalies
sequentially,
a pattern emerged.
A spiral.
Do you see the spiral?
Sir, they are out there.
They are coming here.
Do you have any idea
what you have here?
Well, sir,
I have an inkling.
Bubkes!
"bubkes"?
Good day.
But, sir,
we have to take action now.
Singer, I hired you
to find me an alien.
And you bring me
doctored photos
and a spiral.
You are on thin ice, boy.
I gotta hand it to you.
I thought your presentation
was just wonderful.
And... hmm.
Yeah.
Oop, there it is.
Roberta. Dolores.
No.
Whoo!
Shannanay!
[chuckles]
Yo, Kerm,
what should I do
with the bills?
Just leave 'em inside.
All right.
Gonzo, do you want
your new issue
of insanity fair?
[Gonzo]
nah, I'll get it later.
[dog barking]
[clock chiming]
what is he doing up there?
His breakfast cereal
told him to sit on the roof.
Ooh! Talk about
whole grain and nuts!
Cool!
Aah!
Whoa!
Hey, hey. Yeah!
# when you wish
upon a star #
Cool!
# your dreams will take you
very far, yeah #
[imitates motor revving]
# when you wish upon a dream #
[laughing]
# life ain't always
what it seems, oh yeah #
# shining star #
whoa!
This could be painful!
[laughing]
it is! It is!
Gonzo! Gonzo!
Look at Gonzo!
[together]
greetings, Mr. Gonzo!
Greetings!
What are you guys?
Space fish?
We are cosmic
knowledge fish.
We know many, many things.
Would you like some tea?
No, thanks.
Mr. Gonzo, your people
have been trying
to reach you.
My people?
Are they fish too?
[together]
no, no, no, no.
We are not the same as you.
We are highly
evolved beings.
Now, if...
what was I saying?
My people.
Oh, yes!
Excellent!
You must mow the lawn
if you wish
to find what you seek.
I should mow the lawn?
Mmm.
A lawn that is cut
in your own words, Gonzo.
A message that
can be seen from space.
So trim it well.
Good-bye, Gonzo.
And may the fish be with you.
Thanks, guys.
Thanks for
the cosmic knowledge.
Good-bye, Mr. Gonzo.
# what your life
can truly be #
Aah!
[grunting]
[laughing]
That's it!
Come on, Rizzo.
It's time to bet, okay.
All right, prawn cracker.
I'll see your
Maryland crab cakes...
And I'll raise you
a 1958 cheddar cheese,
never been sniffed!
Crab cakes and cheese,
huh?
Can't beat that.
Hey, guys!
The cosmic fish
have spoken to me.
I'm from outer space!
Oh, yeah, yeah,
that's great.
[Rizzo]
Pepe, are you in or out?
Si, I'm in.
I'm an alien!
Have you been tap dancing
on the barbecue again?
No, no, Rizzo.
I'm just fine.
[screaming]
Whoa! Whoo, whoo, whoo!
My cards!
Somebody get
a fire extinguisher.
Not my cards!
Oh, no, no!
Gonzo, are you sure you're okay?
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
But I have to respond.
Gotta make contact!
Ah!
- Where's he going
with those keys?
- Who cares? Flying saucer.
Dos deuces.
The prawn cracker wins.
Pair of twos!
I swear, I had four aces!
I really did!
# you got to know
when to hold it #
No, no, no!
# know when to fold it
know when to... #
- [lawn mower engine starting]
- [Gonzo] yeow!
# get up off of that thing
dance and you'll feel better #
and dance, sing it now #
# get up off of that thing
dance and you'll feel better #
and try to release
that pressure #
# get up off of that thing
shake and you'll feel better #
and shake
say it now #
# get up off of that thing
and try to release
that pressure #
# wait a minute
hold it #
[Rentro]
well, just a few things for today, sir.
Let's see.
Oh, here's a winner.
Your platinum buns
workout tape.
[laughing]
And let's see.
That new satellite photo
is here.
My Captain Kangaroo pajamas.
What? What satellite photo?
Huh?
"I am here"...
Mowed in the lawn.
Who did this?
This is not good.
No.
Poor Guy!
He's hallucinatin'.
Gettin' weird messages.
Hearing things.
He listens to voices
and does what they say.
Hold your horses.
What?
I think
I've got an idea.
You're scary.
Okay. Yeah.
I have to call Luft.
Ooh!
- Wait. Careful.
- Careful.
Baby steps.
- We need more evidence.
- More evidence!
Remember.
We're just watching.
Watching.
And waiting.
Waiting.
[snoring]
[Pepe]
build it and we will come!
Build what?
Build a jacuzzi
and we will come, okay.
[laughing]
shh.
I'm up. I'm up.
[grunts]
Must build jacuzzi.
[laughing]
well done, pal.
Gracias, amigo.
[music, laughter,
chattering]
Put a little more paprika
on those, okay? Thank you.
Well, that's everything.
[laughing]
whoa!
He built it.
And we came.
All right, remember.
I built this new jacuzzi
for my alien family,
So please
no eating in the spa.
We gotta tell him
the truth, Pepe.
You tell him,
and I will smack you.
I will smack you
like a bad, bad donkey,
okay.
Sal.
Yeah, Johnny.
There are no cannolis here.
Yeah, but have you tried
this cake? This is a beauty.
That is nice!
Would you...
Gonzo, Gonzo!
Hey, go easy on the buffet,
fellas. I just want...
Who cut the cake?
Who cut the cake!
What?
Who cut it?
I don't believe that!
Who cut this cake?
Who would've...
that's awful.
I can't believe it.
The guests of honor
aren't even here yet.
Hey, great party!
Yeah.
I just wish
they'd get here.
[Sal]
hey, you, did you cut
Gonzo's cake?
[Waldorf]
I wonder if there really
is life on other planets.
What do you care?
You don't have a life
on this planet.
[laughing]
[laughing,
groaning]
[TV announcer]
Earth, are you ready?
The galaxy channel presents...
U.F.O. Mania live,
with close encounter expert Shelley Snipes.
Hello, I'm Shelley Snipes.
Coming up
on UFO Mania live,
I'll be taking a hard look
at some compelling new data.
Have you seen something in the Sky,
but were afraid to talk about it?
[Gonzo]
I don't understand why
they didn't show up last night.
Perhaps we can be
of assistance.
We can help you contact
your alien brethren...
By boosting your
newly-enhanced conductivity.
[Bunsen]
okay, Beakie, let her rip!
Me-me-ee.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Wait a minute.
I think I'm picking up
a signal.
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
[Snipes]
if you have had contact
with an alien...
Or if you are an alien
and want to tell your story,
Write to us
or come to our studio.
[Snipes over speaker]
...Or come to our studio
at 6577 broadcast Lane now.
The mother ship
is calling me home!
[gasps]
[laughing]
thanks, guys.
Oh, the mother ship!
It worked.
The mother ship.
[laughing]
good, good, good.
Beaker?
You said you were going
to tell him.
Pepe, the jacuzzi thing
was your idea,
and you have to tell him.
Si.
I will tell him.
Right. Here he comes.
They are
calling me!
Hey, Gonzo...
I can't talk now.
You should've told him.
I wasn't supposed to.
You were!
You said you would.
When I said "you,"
I meant you.
# so funky #
# yo, what's up
get up off of that thing #
# and dance
and you'll feel better #
# get up off of that thing
and try to release
that pressure #
Hi, guys.
I'm here.
Just leave the tractor
here in front, okay?
And that's the way it is.
This is Miss Piggy
saying good night
and have a great...
[Sandy]
where's my coffee?
I-I'm coming!
Coming!
Coming! Coming!
Hey, Piggy,
I'll take one.
In a minute.
Light, no sugar.
Shelley's stuck at the airport.
She'll never
make it back on time.
Okay, I am not
gonna panic.
Who am I kidding?
Yes, I am!
No. No, I'm not.
Okay, I'm panicking.
Who can we possibly get
at the last minute?
[Miss Piggy grunting]
Cappuccino?
[woman]
stand by, everybody.
Roll tape please.
And cue I.D.
We're on in five, four, three, two...
[gasping]
Look!
It's Piggy's new show.
Ahh...
Read! Read!
Oh, oh, oh!
"hello again.
I'm Shelley Snipes.
Today on UFO Mania: Flying saucers
and their extraterrestrial pilots."
Hmm. Wish I could find
my pants.
[Pepe]
Kermit, you should come
to see this.
"I'm sure
you've often wondered...
Piggy!
What might those
alien creatures look like."
People of Earth,
do not be alarmed.
My message will be brief.
I am Gonzo.
Gonzo! Hmph!
Piggy?
I don't have a Gonzo.
- There seems to be
some sort of mistake.
- Better get down there, Kerm.
Relax. No one is
going anywhere, okay?
You see, I was contacted
through my breakfast cereal,
And later it was confirmed to me
by the cosmic fish
that I am from outer space.
So you wanna go now
or wait for the commercial?
Now.
Come on.
What are you doing here?
I'm making contact.
What are you doing?
- Um...
- interview him.
I'm interviewing...
I'm interviewing you!
[Gonzo]
great!
What would you like to know?
The whole tearful tale
of your inner struggle, Gonzo.
Oh.
[Gonzo] I want my people to know
that I've received their messages.
And my response to them is: I am here!
"I am here."
Bingo!
I'm at 44 Bronson Lane,
and I can't wait
to meet you.
And I can't wait
Me too. He's very charismatic,
don't you think?
Freeze that!
[singer] I want him here
and I want him now.
[Rentro] yes, sir.
So, you're our fancy
little landscaper.
- Wrap it up.
We're gonna take a break.
- Oh, oh, yes. [chuckles]
We are going to pause here,
and be right back with Gonzo,
the geek who fell to Earth,
With moi, Miss Piggy.
And we're out.
Ninety seconds, folks.
[groans]
Now that is TV!
The phones are lighting up
like Vegas.
What power! What heat.
You're a hit!
Oh, thank you!
- Not you! Him.
- Me?
- Gonzo, you've got it.
- Sure wish we could find
a cure for it.
- Rizzo?
- Gonzo?
- Kermie?
- Piggy?
What the heck's goin' on?
[Kermit] listen, Gonzo.
Aren't you taking
this alien thing
a little too far?
Kermit, I realize it may
be hard for you to accept me
as an alien,
But I didn't choose
to be one.
I've always had alien
tendencies, and this
just makes sense to me.
Beautiful, big "g."
I see a whole follow-up episode.
Me too!
"the alien in my life."
a Miss Piggy special report.
- What are you talkin' about?
You're the coffee pig.
- Huh?
Here's how we see it.
Kermit,
he's such a joker!
We'll take this
from here.
We're with the society for the
prevention of cruelty to aliens.
We feel your pain, Gonzo.
They feel my pain!
I've got a paper cut
that's a doozy.
Do you feel my pain too?
Can you guys help me
make contact
with my alien tribe?
Yes, we can, Gonzo.
Well, somebody believes me.
Come on, fellas.
Take me to my leader.
But, but, Gonzo!
I don't like the look
of these guys.
This rat smells a rat.
The limo's
right this way.
Thank you.
Did he say "limo"?
Wait a second,
I'm his translator.
Now wait.
You know this Gonzo, right?
Um...
- If the price is right.
- The price?
Look.
I deliver Gonzo's
exclusive live story, okay,
If you make moi
your new anchorwoman.
[woman]
we're back in 15 seconds.
Well?
What about Shelley?
Shelley's smelly.
Yes, yes!
Go!
All right!
Oh! Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Hoo-hoo.
Studmuffin, hold it.
I'll deal with her.
Yeah, come on.
[laughing]
oh, you'll deal with moi!
Look, chumpo,
I'm just trying
to get a story.
How 'bout this story?
It's about a big, bad wolf
and a little pig.
- No, that's three pigs.
- Not in this version.
Hey, wait a minute.
You're not part of that
alien protection agency.
Who are you?
Where are you taking Gonzo?
Hey!
Hai-ya!
I'm impressed.
Ahh.
Black belt,
third degree.
Hai-ya!
Platinum belt... With
an unlimited line of credit.
I like this party.
Oh!
Tough Guy! Tough Guy!
Ha, ha!
Come on, show me!
Oh, look, Cindy Crawford!
Huh?
[groans, laughs]
Where have you been
all my life?
Is that all you got?
Is that all you g-got?
Not the noogie!
Hey!
[groans]
[yelling]
mama!
[crowd chanting]
Gonzo! Gonzo!
What the hey?
Oh, no.
There are no aliens here.
Only good, old-fashioned,
hard-working Americans.
[clucking]
Good grief.
Now, get off
my Kentucky bluegrass.
Look!
It's a little green man.
Ah, excuse me.
But what are all you people
doing here?
We were drawn here
by the alien.
Yuck!
That's all I know.
Let me get
this straight.
This government agency,
C.O.V.N.E.T.,
has abducted Gonzo,
And taken him
to its top secret facility?
Yes, Miss Piggy.
Thank you, darling.
You've been most helpful.
At last!
A real story!
Intrigue, danger,
new outfits.
And it's mine, mine, mine!
All mine!
[laughing]
[grunting]
Ah, come on, please.
You think Ted Koppel
never gets excited?
[Rizzo]
so this is the car that
takes us to the limo, right?
[Rizzo grunts]
you should have somebody
look at those shocks.
At least they carried our stuff.
Don't hold your breath
for a tip.
[Rizzo]
oh!
As ambassador of Earth,
I welcome you.
Ah, yeah.
I'm Edgar.
But I want you
to call me ed.
That's ed.
Oh, yeah.
It's an honor to meet you,
Mr. Gonzo.
Yeah, yeah, me too.
Hors d'oeuvres!
[laughing]
please.
Won't you sit?
Oh! Thanks.
Careful, careful.
You'll get gas.
Hmm?
So when do we begin, ed?
I'm very excited about all this.
Ah!
Me too, my friend.
Me too.
Yeah!
Kermie!
Oh, Kermie, Kermie!
Yes!
Yoo-hoo!
Kermie! Everybody!
Come here, come here!
Oh, oh, oh!
Listen, everyone, listen.
I've got great news!
Gonzo has been kidnapped
by the government,
And it could be a
life-threatening situation.
How can that
be great news?
Because...
# I've got the story
I've got the story #
Oh, I need to change!
Something that says
"journalistic integrity."
Oh, oh,
I've got to pee!
Oh, brother.
What are we gonna do?
Okay, guys,
it's up to us.
We have to save Gonzo
from a whole army
of government agents.
Well, I have
a joke book.
Drumsticks!
I have some
loose jell-o, okay.
Okay.
Well, that settles that.
In circumstances like this,
there's only one place
to turn.
Okay, what
do you got, Bunsen?
Oh, there you are.
Mr. Kermit, here at Muppet Labs,
we have come up with
a number of devices...
That should aid you
in your covert operations.
Excellent.
This seemingly ordinary
rubber ducky actually
contains invisibility spray.
However the effect
is sadly temporary.
[mumbles] sadly temporary.
Ha, ha! The old
rubber-ducky-with-invisibility
spray trick. Check.
And, beaker, if you would.
Here is something
we're very excited about.
Me-me!
"door in a jar"?
Me-me-me-me.
Whoo.
That's absolutely right,
Beakie.
All you do is open the jar,
fling the contents
onto the wall... And poof!
- Poof!
- Instant door.
What is this?
A secret communication device?
No, that's scotch tape.
Very useful
if something tears.
Ahh!
[Miss Piggy]
ahem.
Um, what do you have
for... Moi?
Ahh!
[Bunsen]
well now, Miss Piggy.
For you we have
Muppet Labs mind mist.
Simply spray it on
the subject,
And they will obey
your every command.
[laughing]
I... aah!
Me-me-oo-oo.
Oh.
I doubt I'll need any.
- Okay, guys,
let's go get Gonzo.
- Come on, come on.
[Pepe]
we'll find him, okay.
Gonzo, Gonzo, Gonzo!
Yeah!
I've been looking
for something like you...
All my life.
And now, at last,
my search...
Has come to an end.
May I?
Before you answer that,
you better be clear on the final
destination of that finger.
Ahh.
Thanks.
Hmm.
No nostrils.
How do you smell?
Awful.
Trust me,
I'm his roommate.
[laughing]
huh? Huh?
That's a killer.
[everyone laughing]
[laughing]
Don't...
Laugh at me!
[gulps]
I hope I'm not imposing.
I thought you were great
on TV. Think I could get
your autograph?
- Rentro?
- Yes, sir?
- It's not a good time.
- This is probably not
a good time. Yeah.
Forgive me
my Earthly manners.
But do you have any idea
what it's like...
To be laughed at?
Yeah, sure I do.
To be called names
like "wacko"?
Uh-huh.
- And "freak boy"?
- Oh, yeah.
- And paranoid
delusional psychopath?
- Got me there.
To feel...
[neck cracking]
Completely alone
in this world?
Yeah, I think we're starting
to get the general idea, ed.
Yeah.
It's wrestling legend
Hollywood Hulk Hogan?
Have the rat sent down
to Dr. Tucker for some tests.
Tests? But I Haven't studied.
I don't even have
a number-two pencil.
This is for all my
N.W.O.-ites out there.
I will continue
to dominate wrestling.
I will continue to make
your back crack, your knees
freeze and your liver quiver.
I will continue to put
so much pain on you,
you'll be come my "painiac."
Hollywood, would you mind?
The rat.
- Oh, yeah.
- Where're you goin'
with my friend?
What are your fans gonna think?
What are you gonna do?
I'm a bad guy now.
Gonzo, help me!
Help! Help!
Rizzo!
Shh, shh, shh.
He's gonna be fine.
[Rizzo screaming]
- Huh?
- [groaning]
Yo.
How you doin'?
I'm bubba.
Hey. Rizzo.
Nice to meet ya.
Nice to meet you. How'd you like
to meet some of the boys? Sure.
- Up there, that's fast Eddie,
harmonica extraordinaire.
- Hi.
- How you doin', ed?
- Well, I ain't dead.
Over here's Troy.
This back here, that's shakes.
Hi. Hello.
How're you doin'?
Welcome.
They're doing a new
caffeine substitute on him.
- Up there's the birdman.
- Where are you?
Gladys, here, baby, sweetie.
He don't bother nobody.
He's been here forever.
Gladys,
the guys are watching.
He just likes to hang out
with his birds.
You know what I mean?
So, that about does it
for all of us here
at medical research.
Medical research?
Yep.
But that would mean
that we're... Lab rats!
Gonzo, get me
outta here!
[singer]
now, Mr. Gonzo.
What can you tell me
about these?
Whoa! They really
have been looking for me!
And they are coming to Earth,
aren't they?
I don't know.
How many of them are there?
When will they be here?
And don't you dare tell me...
That you don't know.
I know not?
[gagging]
But maybe
I could find out?
Could you?
Okay.
Well.
Okay then.
I'll keep in touch.
Thanks.
Oh. So,
back to the limo?
It's a shame, really.
Huh?
I really need
that information.
So, I am afraid...
We're gonna have to perform
an invasive quadra-lobal
brain probe on you,
And pluck it
from your head.
The information?
No.
Your brain.
Take him away.
What?
My brain?
But just a second.
I...
Rentro, get me general Luft.
Where're you taking me?
I need my brain!
Fozzie, tell me again.
Why are we doing this?
To save Gonzo.
Gonzo! Gonzo!
That's right, because
Gonzo's one of us.
And no matter what happens,
no matter what obstacles
we face,
We never forget one
of our own.
I love it
when you take charge.
Hey! We left Bunsen
and beaker back
at the gas station.
Okay, from this point on,
no matter what happens,
We never forget
one of our own.
Mmm, that's right.
Hmm.
Cheese twiddle?
So what is this,
movie time?
[gasping]
So you're the new guy.
Yeah.
From this moment on,
If I say you're hungry, you eat;
if I say you're sleepy...
I eat?
Ah, you shouldn't have...
what?
Well, well, well.
We got a funny boy here.
Is that bad?
Very bad.
Funny boy's gonna go
to the maze.
Since we don't want funny boy
to get lonely, you're all
gonna do time in the maze.
I'm sorry.
See, no one's ever escaped
from the maze, funny boy.
No?
And even if you did,
it's four feet to the ground,
Twelve feet to the door,
and four feet to the doorknob.
That's 18 feet.
Twenty.
Funny thing about doorknobs...
rats can't turn 'em.
No opposable thumb.
[laughs]
Right.
Not the maze.
# help me, help me
help me, hold me #
# survival #
# survival of the fittest #
this is ridiculous.
# gotta get with it #
# 'cause there ain't no time
no time to scurry around #
Hey, Riz, watch out
for them red circles.
What's wrong with the red...
[screams]
Nobody ever listens.
Red circles.
Right.
[coughs]
Let me see.
Cheese, rat poison.
Duh!
What do you guys think,
I'm crazy or something?
This is a no-brainer.
This ain't so bad.
A little breezy.
Oh, boy.
Whoa. Whoa!
Whoa, whoa!
Auntie em,
it's a twister!
This is just like one
of those carny rides.
You just gotta hang on,
and at the end
I get some cotton candy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[screaming]
I'm gonna hurl!
They're just trying
to play mind games here.
But I know the cheese is safe
'cause you think I'm going
for the poison, right?
Huh? Huh?
- Psst.
- Huh?
Room service.
[laughing]
hey there, little fella.
How're you doin'?
While they're warming up
the brain sucker for you,
I brought you a sandwich.
I cut off the crusts
for you.
There you go.
Oh, gee, that's nice.
Thanks.
Anything for a celebrity.
[laughing]
Oh, hey,
do you like jalapenos?
Sure.
Okay!
# jalapenos
jalapenos #
- [sighs]
- hey, Mopey!
[screams]
W-who said that?
I did.
But you're
just a sandwich.
Nah, I'm just channeling
my voice through this sandwich
to deliver this message.
Great!
What's the message?
Ahem.
We arrive at midnight tonight.
Really? Do all of you
look like sandwiches?
Forget about the sandwich.
All right,
I'm sorry.
# jalapenos, jalapenos #
# gettin' my friend
some jalapenos #
[sandwich] here's the plan.
We're landing at your house.
What?
No, no, wait.
Those guys know
where I live.
They're not
the best examples
of Earthlings.
Oh, gosh.
Where else can we land?
Um, let's see.
Uh...
I know! At the beach.
Go to cape doom.
Look for the lighthouse.
[sandwich] the lighthouse
at cape doom it is.
Boy, I didn't hear that.
Oh, this is great.
But how do I
get out of here?
I'm just a sandwich.
Some things you gotta
figure out for yourself.
Oh, by the way,
go ahead and eat me now.
You're gonna need
the energy.
Won't that hurt?
No, it's fine.
I'm goin' away now.
Oh. Well...
Cape doom, right?
Yes, yes.
Cape doom.
Are you there?
Hello? Hello?
Huh. Well...
[cell door opens]
Aah!
Wow!
Just a little
further up, Fozzie.
Stop, Fozzie.
Stop here, Fozzie.
That's it.
Oh! Oh!
Sorry.
Aah!
Animal.
Huh?
Sorry.
[frightened squeals]
Stand back, boys.
This is a job for a woman.
Hmm.
A woman!
Woman!
Shh!
Hello!
What's a nice man like you
doing in a guardhouse
like this?
I'm buffalo hunting.
What does it look like
I'm doing?
This is a restricted area.
You gotta go.
Oh, no.
Look deeply into my eyes
and tell me
you want me to go.
I want you to go.
Understand?
Now.
Ahh...
Okay.
I thought I told...
What was I saying?
You were saying
you were going
to open the gate.
Open the gate.
Of course, open the gate.
Come on in. Welcome.
[whistles]
Come on, guys.
Oh, boy!
Uh... now tell me
I'm beautiful, sweetheart.
You are beautiful,
sweetheart.
Oh, thank you.
[laughs]
Oh, boy! He fell on you
like a ton of bricks.
Naturalement.
Have a nice time.
Oh, I like your tie.
Very nice.
Thank you.
So long.
Bye-bye.
[chuckles]
what a handsome family.
Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow.
Hey, rodents!
You know all that cheese
I promised you...
After you ran that maze
and took those tests?
Yeah.
It was delicious!
[wicked laughing]
No cheese?
[door closes]
All right, that does it!
We're bustin' out
of this joint, boys.
Even if we got over the wall,
we couldn't turn the doorknob.
Yeah.
Who needs doorknobs?
Doh!
Heh-heh-heh-heh.
Wow!
Huh? Huh?
[together]
yeah! Yeah!
[excited chattering]
Shh!
Very nice.
[wicked laughing]
Okay, guys.
We gotta get through
that door.
Should we ask permission
from those nice men
with the rifles?
Those are the bad guys!
Oh!
All right, everybody.
It's time to get invisible.
Fozzie,
get the duck.
Ooh, the duckie!
Me first.
Here it goes.
[duck squeaking]
okay.
Hey, I look thinner.
[Kermit]
spray yourself, Fozzie.
Okay.
[squeaking]
Wow! Oh, hey!
I like this.
[Kermit]
all right, lose the duck.
Yes, sir. Listen up. This stuff doesn't
last long, so let's go.
Yes! Yes!
[Kermit]
ooh, you're squashing me.
[Miss Piggy] sorry, Kermie.
[Pepe] come on, Kermit.
I will help you up.
Oh, Kermit,
you're so soft and plump.
[Miss Piggy]
you got one second to get
your hands off me, shrimp.
Ooh, sorry, Piggy.
[Kermit]
come on. Let's go.
Shh, shh.
[Fozzie] I have to go
to the little bathroom.
[Kermit]
oh, Fozzie!
[Pepe]
smoking is very bad
for you, okay?
Bob,
didn't know you cared.
[female on P.A. System]
paging Dr. Van neuter. Report
to alien surgery number 5.
Hello.
I'm Dr. Van neuter.
I'll be your
brain surgeon today,
if you don't mind.
Get it?
"brain surgeon. Mind."
[laughs]
ah.
Oh, feeling a little nervous,
are we?
Of course I'm nervous.
Don't worry.
Everyone is before having
their brain sucked out.
Now, don't you go away.
[sighs, grunts]
[toilet flushes]
Okay, Kermit.
I'm ready.
[Kermit]
Fozzie, tell me
you didn't wash your hands.
Of course I did.
Mom said, "always
wash your hands."
Yes, but not
when you're wearing
invisibility spray!
Mom said,
"no exceptions."
Never ever.
Uh-uh.
What...
stop! You!
Hands... Up!
Oh! Oh!
All right.
Remain calm.
I'm gonna have to take
you two into custody.
Wait.
Let me explain, lady.
You don't have... no!
Where...
where are your forearms?
[growling]
[screams]
[animal] woman! [Kermit] animal!
Animal, get back here!
Animal!
Woman! Woman!
Oh, dear.
Give me a second
to think.
He doesn't seem to be
on this floor, so he...
[embarrassed mumbling]
[grunting]
oh!
# la, la, la, la, la
la, la... La #
Wow.
I should, uh,
go change, okay.
Come on, everybody.
We need to find
better cover.
# la, la, la, la, la
la, la #
Just ahead here,
general Luft, sir.
Here we go.
Ah. This is our new
retinal scanner, general.
Oh.
[beeps]
Yeah.
[chuckles,
clears throat]
[beeping]
[yelling]
[moaning]
General Luft, sir.
This had better be good.
Whoa.
Come on, fellows.
Let's go.
Shh.
Whew. Aye.
Hey, Riz, Riz?
Where you goin'?
You guys go ahead.
I gotta go find my friend.
What? You could
get caught! Are you nuts?
[together] yeah.
I guess I'll take
my chances.
It was nice meetin' you guys.
See you later, huh?
[mice mumbling]
so long, Riz.
Bye, Rizzo.
Good luck.
Kid's got moxie.
[shakes]
yeah, moxie.
What is "moxie"? [Dr.
Van neuter] before we get started...
Let's see here.
Do you now
or have you ever...
Experienced any achiness
in your tentacles?
I don't have tentacles.
Oh, good!
No achy tentacles. Good.
Head ever come off?
No, I don't think so.
Good, good, good.
Any gingivitis?
No.
Great!
How 'bout that beaky thing
you've got there?
Ever had any problems
with that? Itching?
Swelling? Flaking?
Some flaking
a couple years ago.
Who cares?
It's show time!
# doot, doot, doot #
Here we go.
Oh, brother.
Excellent.
# [humming]
w-what's that thing?
I don't know.
Here we go.
Just stay... Like that.
Okay?
This way.
[Miss Piggy]
whose bright idea
was this, anyway?
[Fozzie]
which way, Kermit?
Kermit, this way.
[Miss Piggy]
I can't breathe in here.
Come on, Kerm.
Okay, here we go.
Wait! Wait!
- What is it?
- Are you sure this is covered
by my H.M.O.?
Huh?
Good question.
I'll check.
[sighs]
Psst. Gonzo?
Rizzo! You're alive!
Where have you been?
You don't even want to know.
Sit tight while I see if I can
chew through these straps.
Yeah, yeah.
Good. Good.
Ah, good news!
You're covered
with a $10 co-pay.
Okay, hold still.
And remember,
If you experience
any sort of unpleasantness,
please let me know.
- I would hate to miss it.
- Hmm? Hmm?
Do you mind?
Oh, excuse me.
Wait!
Oh, good lord, a rat!
I hate rats!
Then today ain't
your lucky day, doc.
Oh! No!
Doc, ready for
an operation?
A little experiment.
Forward, Piggy.
Forward.
[groaning]
# [humming]
Doctor.
Doctor?
Oh, doctor. Doctor.
Just a couple of doctors.
Doctors in the hallway.
Whew!
That was close.
[Gonzo groaning]
to the right, Fozzie.
Forward, Piggy.
Too fast!
The door, the door!
Stop!
- [yelling] no! No!
- What in the world?
This is big, general.
I think we should notify
the president.
I'll be the judge
of that.
As always, sir.
No, don't tickle me!
What do we do?
Will you get me out
of here?
Mmm! Hmph!
[Dr. Van neuter laughing]
no, no, no!
I can't breathe!
Hey, guys! Quick!
Get me out of here.
Today, sir,
We must think
with a big mind.
Behold.
Irrefutable evidence
of extraterrestrial life.
Release me.
Ooh.
This looks worse
than it is, general.
Obviously...
Get off of me,
you vermin!
The alien is loose
in the building.
- But not to worry, because...
- don't bother.
You're terminated.
Uh...
When you say
"terminated"...
You need help, singer!
Find some!
Mm-mmm.
How'd that go for ya?
Okay?
[elevator bell rings]
sorry I got you
into this mess.
Thanks for coming
to save me.
Thank us when we're
safely out of here.
All right, quietly.
Right. Shh.
[female guard]
stop! Come back here!
[excited chattering]
Help! Help me!
Please, listen to me!
You can't leave me.
I need you.
[together]
oooh!
Yah! I go now.
Fine. Go on, go.
You're all alike.
Hmm?
Animals.
[sobbing]
Ahh.
Call me.
[Kermit]
psst. Animal.
Come here.
Yeah? Yeah?
Way to go, Romeo.
Let's get out of here.
Yeah, let's go.
I'm gonna kill somebody.
Whoa. Now, now.
Remember, calm blue ocean.
You let it go.
Baby steps, remember?
Baby...
find the alien!
Now!
Y-yes, sir.
[shouting]
Try that door.
It won't budge.
Forget that door!
Come on!
[all gasp]
this way.
Quick, the door
in the jar.
It's right here.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Um, "open jar
away from face."
Will you please
just open the jar?
Hurry, throw it!
Gee, that's
disappointing.
Perfect. Somebody knock
and see if Barbie's home.
Works for me.
Adios.
What?
Oh, I cannot believe
that little shrimp
left us behind.
I am not a shrimp!
I am a king prawn!
Let's go. Come on.
Hurry, hurry!
Come on, guys, hurry!
We have to go! Aaah!
Keep going, everybody.
Don't look back. Run! Run!
[guard]
you're new, eh?
Did you have a good time?
Bye-bye.
[animal]
bye-bye, nice man.
[laughs]
[siren wailing]
what the heck is goin' on?
We did it!
[Kermit]
see that, guys?
When we pull together,
we can do anything.
You bet we can.
Now we can meet
my alien brothers
at cape doom.
Um, what makes you think
aliens are landing there,
Gonzo?
Oh. A sandwich told me.
- Oh, no.
- [Rizzo]
I'd give it a rest, buddy.
Do you mean that you guys
still don't believe me?
Well...
All right, fine.
Stop the bus.
I'll get there by myself.
No, wait, Gonzo.
Look.
It doesn't matter
what we believe.
I mean, if you believe
that you need to go and
meet your alien brothers,
Then I say, well...
I say we're goin'
to the beach.
Right, guys?
- To the beach, okay.
- To the beach.
Great! Thanks, guys.
Beach ball!
Get the crew
down to cape doom
on the double.
This is my exclusive,
so don't tell anyone!
Okay, I've got it.
Pack it up, guys.
The space ship
is landing at cape doom.
[excited chattering]
[singer]
where is he?
Well, I didn't overhear
anything. I...
Did I ask you
if you overheard anything?
No, sir.
Because if you did
overhear anything,
I'm sure
you would tell me.
Y-yes, sir.
Or do I have to remind you...
Of Mr. Jumbo's circus town
and wild animal revue?
Where is he going?
Oh, look.
Sunday's half price
at the petting zoo.
Okay, okay, okay!
They're goin'
to cape doom.
Good. Good.
Get me the subatomic
neutro-destablizer.
Hmm?
The subatomic neutro...
oh, the really big gun.
The really big gun.
Yes, sir.
[laughing, grunts]
Really big gun!
Clip.
Wow.
Let's head for my car.
Oh, problem there, sir.
Uh, remember those
parking tickets you asked me
to take care of for you?
And I said that...
oh, just say it.
Car's impounded.
Ooh! We can take
my company car.
Fine.
Great.
[Rentro]
# sixty-six bottles of beer
on the wall #
# sixty-six bottles of beer #
[singer]
excuse me. Excuse me!
Can this thing
go any faster?
I'm doin' 30.
You wanna slow down
there, buddy?
Lotta traffic tonight.
Safety first.
[crowd cheering]
[chanting]
Gonzo! Gonzo!
What's with all
these crazy people?
[chuckles]
Can I help it if moi has such devoted fans?
ah.
- [chanting continues]
- all right,
everybody back off!
Make way for the alien.
Let his royal weirdness
through.
[Pepe]
everybody be cool.
Stay back. Be cool, okay.
Gonzo! Gonzo!
Get your Gonzo t-shirts
right here. Ten bucks.
[Bunsen laughing]
ooh.
Good-bye, rainbow.
And stay groovy.
[chanting]
Hmm. Got cold.
Yeah, sure did.
[Miss Piggy]
midnight.
The lone alien
stands before a naked Sky.
The mood is tense.
My hair looks great.
What?
I don't believe this!
Oh, Shelley. Bonjour.
You backstabbing,
underhanded little
coffee pig!
What?
This is my show!
My story!
My microphones.
This is Shelley Snipes
reporting. Please ignore
the little sow.
Disregard this woman.
[screams]
hai-ya!
[shouting]
What am I doing?
Um...
You are about to give me
your job and get everyone here
a cup of coffee.
Oh, yes.
Of course.
Right away.
Ohh.
I love this stuff!
How ya doin'?
Excuse me, buddy.
And a happy Halloween
to ya, as well.
Ooh! Ooh!
[yelling]
Riz, take it easy.
It's all right.
What do you mean,
it's all right?
You don't understand.
We let him slide,
and he gave us a ride.
Yeah, yeah.
I love all my new
rat friends now.
Who wants this next
marshmallow?
You believe that?
Look at that.
Fellas, look who's here.
[together]
hey, buddy!
Too bad Dawson
isn't here for this.
Tell me about it.
This whole situation
is like something out of
one of his sci-fi movies.
But this is a Muppet movie.
It's much more realistic...
And romantic, okay.
Right.
What's your deal?
You some sort of alien?
No, baby.
Me and Gonzo are very tight.
In fact,
we gonna be chillin'
in our hot tub later on.
Perhaps you'd like
to partake in the "partay."
Geeks.
All right,
don't answer right away.
We'll be here.
Oh, she'll be back.
1:00 a.m.
The alien is still
standing over there.
My hair still looks great.
And one
can only wonder...
What Gonzo's feeling
right now.
They're not comin'.
Well, maybe they're
just running late.
It's a no-show.
What?
Wait a second.
I believed you, man.
Yeah. I stayed up
all night dancing,
And didn't study
for finals because of you.
I'm cold.
Come on. Let's go.
Uh... uh...
What a bust.
I'm outta here.
[gasps]
look!
Boy, they're
really tiny.
But tiny is not
a bad thing, right?
Uh, no. Yeah, yeah.
Tiny's good.
Wait a minute.
Are you telling me we came here
in the middle of the night
for a stupid egg?
Shh. It could be
full of chocolate.
[crowd]
ooh!
Shoot it!
Hokey-pokey!
Please, big boss.
I never disobeyed my mother.
And I never carried the plague.
Not even once! Ohh!
Are you okay, Gonzo?
Great.
Never felt better.
Let the one
who is called Gonzo...
Step forward.
That's me!
I-I mean,
I'm Gonzo.
Step a little closer.
Come a little further forward.
Could you lean into the light?
There you go.
Lean in.
A little further.
Yeah.
That's him!
[spaceship door
closes]
[UberGonzo]
Gonzo!
Many zotons ago
you were lost to us.
We've come a long way
looking for you, little brother.
[gasps]
[UberGonzo]
we know of but one way
to express our happiness...
At having found you.
# [rock]
#
# whoo-hoo #
Ha, ha, ha!
# now there's a party
goin' on right here #
# right here #
# a celebration #
That's my family!
# so bring your good times
and your laughter too #
- # we're gonna celebrate
your party with you #
- look at 'em!
# celebration #
# let's all celebrate
and have a good time #
come on.
# celebration #
# we're gonna celebrate
and have a good time #
# it's time
to come together #
# it's up to you
what's your pleasure #
# everyone around the world
come on #
# celebrate good times
# it's a celebration #
Ha, ha, ha!
# whoo-hoo #
# it's a celebration #
Yeah!
Ha, ha!
# celebrate good times
come on #
Come on, Gonzo.
Wanna see you up here
on the stage!
Me?
Yeah, you boy.
Ha, ha, ha!
# bah, bah, bah
bah, bah, bah, bah, bah #
# whoo-hoo #
Look at him go, guys,
look at him up there.
# celebrate good times
come on #
[cheering, applause]
[alien singer]
yeah, it's the great Gonzo!
This way.
Gonzo, it is time
to take...
Your righteous place
amongst your brothers.
- Oh, thanks...
- here you go.
[UberGonzo]
by surviving and thriving
alone on this alien planet...
You have proven yourself
audacious, courageous and
distinctly one of a kind.
# [drumroll]
we welcome you back
with our most ceremonious...
Of ceremonies.
[Gonzo]
what's that?
We gonna blow you up,
baby.
[male singer]
# it's your thing
do what you wanna do #
# I can't tell you
who to sock it to #
yes! Ha, ha, ha!
# it's your thing # [together]
ahh!
Ha, ha, ha!
Arriba.
# do what you wanna do #
[laughing]
I love these people!
Comin' down.
Cowabunga!
[yelling, laughing]
Oh, no!
Uh-oh.
Where's he gone?
Ta-da!
[cheering]
hey, buddy!
He's okay.
He's all right.
Now that is what I call
"the great Gonzo."
[cheering continues]
Ha, ha! Yeah!
My hero!
[Gonzo]
yes! Yes!
Yeah! Yeah!
[singer]
hold it!
- Hold it.
- Wha...
Get outta the way,
you freak.
Very, very moving,
my little alien friend.
But I'm afraid
your timing is off.
Now, you're coming
back with me...
In my c-cement truck.
[chuckling]
What's so funny?
[laughing]
Don't laugh at me.
Don't laugh...
all right.
- I'll show you laughter.
- No.
[computer voice]
please load weapon.
Please load weapon.
Ah, come on.
Come on!
[laughing]
Aah!
Ooh! Ooh!
This certainly is good.
That was a close one.
[clears throat]
Not as close
as you think, my friend.
"please load weapon."
ahh.
[sobbing]
We are honored to meet you.
A most extraordinary performance.
What are you
talking about?
Gonzo of Earth, who is
this most entertaining
friend of yours?
That's ed.
Hi, ed.
Hello, ed.
The cape.
The cape!
The cape for ed.
Ed, because of
your comic instincts,
We have chosen you
as ambassador to our planet.
Get down.
You mean you want me
to go with you?
To...
Boldly go where
no man has gone before.
It would be
our great privilege, ed.
Uh, may I call you...
Zongo?
[mumbling]
Zongo.
To travel the stars
like a modern-day Magellan.
To be up there with
John Glenn, Neil Armstrong.
Yeah, okay.
You better get goin'.
They're waitin' for ya.
Run along now.
This way, Zongo.
Zongo.
Baby steps, sir.
Ha, ha.
Baby steps.
Time to beat feet.
Come along, little brother.
Ah!
Oh, boy.
This is happening
so fast.
Gee. Well, guys,
you know,
I'm gonna miss you,
and I'll be thinking about you.
Rizzo, buddy...
no, no, not me.
I do not do good-byes. Well,
I just wanna tell ya...
I just want you
to take care of yourself.
Hey, don't worry about me.
I... I can always get
another roommate.
Ah, buddy.
[sniffling]
Take care.
You too.
And Kermit,
you're the best friend
any alien could ask for.
Well, w-we love you,
Gonzo.
So, you'll write?
Oh, yeah, sure.
I'll write.
There's probably
a mail box
every couple of light-years.
[chuckles] yeah.
Hey, adios, Mr. Spaceman,
okay.
Hey, man, you keep
sayin' good-bye, and
you'll never get home.
Oh, yeah. Home.
Home.
Time to go home.
Ah. Ahh.
[crying]
The stars beckon.
Shall we go home?
I don't think so.
Gonzo?
Thank you for going to so much trouble
to find me.
But I can't go.
I love these guys.
My life is here.
This is my home.
If that is your decision,
Then we shall abide by it.
We will miss you.
So, good luck, Gonzo.
Yes.
People of Earth!
Later.
- Yes!
- [all chattering]
Oh, boy.
Good-bye!
Ha-ha!
You're back!
People of Earth,
This is one small step
for man,
And one giant step for...
Well, forget it.
[Gonzo]
what a great day.
Mm-hmm.
That was probably
the best day
of my whole life.
There's just one thing
I still don't understand.
What's that, Gonzo?
Why did they ask me
to build a jacuzzi?
[chuckling]
Релиз подготовлен
специально для сайта firebit.org
# when you wish upon a star #
# your dreams will take you
very far #
# when you wish upon a dream #
# life ain't always
what it seems, oh yeah #
# what do you see
on nights of clear #
# in the Sky so very dear #
# you're a shinin' star #
# no matter who you are #
# shining bright to see #
# what you can truly be
you can truly be #
# shining star
comes into view #
# to shine its watchful light
on you #
# give you strength
to carry on, yeah #
# make your body
big and strong, oh yeah #
# born a man-child
of the sun #
# saw my work
had just begun #
# found I had
to stand alone, yeah #
# well, bless it now
I've got my own, oh yeah #
# so when you find yourself
in need #
# why don't you listen
to these words of heed #
# be a giant
grain of sand #
# words of wisdom
"yes, I can" #
# you're a shinin' star
no matter who you are #
# shinin' bright to see
what you can truly be #
# you're a shinin' star
no matter who you are #
# shinin' bright to see
what you can truly be #
# you're a shinin' star
no matter who you are #
# shinin' bright to see
what you can truly be
what you can truly be #
# shinin' star for you to see
what your life can truly be #
[Pepe]
good morning to you, George,
okay.
Too funky.
# I lay me down to sleep #
# ooh, I just can't find
the beat #
# you need a flashlight #
# space flight
ooh #
# space flight #
# ooh #
Funky.
# da-da-da-dee
da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da #
# oh, it's no use #
# space flight #
# oh, space flight #
# neon lights #
# oh, starlight #
# I lay me down to sleep #
[Pepe]
it's way too early, George.
# just can't find the beat #
# ooh #
# put your hands together #
[Pepe] okay.
I got six of them.
# help me find the funk #
# you need the funk #
# I need the funk #
# help him find the funk #
thank you very much.
# most of all
he need the funk #
I need the funk.
# help him find the funk #
please somebody help me, okay.
# help him find the funk
most of all he need the funk #
most of all he need the funky #
# help me, help me #
# help him find the funk #
# da-da-da-dee
da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da #
# flashlight #
# space flight #
I'm going to fly.
# neon light #
# street light #
The street light!
# everybody's got a little light
under the sun #
# under the sun
# yeah #
# everybody's got a little light
under the sun #
# under the sun
# most of all he need the funk #
# help him dance the funk #
get out of here, George.
# space flight #
# neon light #
I like this neon light.
# red light #
# ooh, stop light #
# stop light #
I can't believe I did this.
# ooh, oh lay me down
to sleep #
It's way too early, George.
# I just can't find the beat #
# space flight #
# red light #
# neon light #
# stop light #
# everybody's got a little light
under the sun #
# under the sun
# ooh #
# now I lay me down to sleep #
it's a good idea.
Me too.
[Pepe snoring]
Buenas noches.
Релиз подготовлен
специально для сайта firebit.org