What is it?
What is that light?
I don't know.
You stay right here, Edna.
Don't leave the house.
I'm gonna take a look at it.
Come on, Dutch.
Chicken.
Holy mackerel!
This is earth probe Zunar
J5 calling mother ship.
Zunar J5 calling mother ship.
Come in, mother ship.
This is earth probe Zunar J5
calling mother ship.
Zunar j5, this is mother ship.
Have you completed emergency landing?
Affirmative, mother.
Request repair party.
Negative, Zunar J5.
You'll have to effect
emergency repairs yourself.
And rendezvous with us at grid dissect 8304.
At 69 hours minus 17.
That's an awfully tight squeeze, mother.
Unavoidable, Zunar.
Next mission to this galaxy due in 115.
- Days?
- Years.
Good luck, Zunar J5.
Over and out.
Yeah.
So long, mother.
I don't see any hammer and sickle.
Do you, Colonel?
Maybe it's on the inside, General.
No sign of life, either.
Get me the Pentagon, red priority.
I wanna speak to the chiefs, Colonel.
Captain?
Sergeant.
Yes, sir.
Sequoia here.
Come in, Rover.
Rover?
Wipe it out of your minds. You understand?
You've seen nothing and heard nothing.
Yes, sir.
We'll want them later for debriefing.
Take their names.
Colonel?
Captain.
Sergeant.
Yes, sir.
Names, please?
Name's Charlie Cooney.
General Stilton!
We're ready when you are, sir.
Bullhorn.
Yes, sir.
On to Hopscotch.
All right, men.
Let's move it!
Let's move out.
Colonel.
Captain.
Sergeant.
Yes, sir.
When we get to Hopscotch,
I want mark-four
priority security.
Armor, personnel, guard dogs, the works.
And not one word to public relations.
Not one word.
- You got that, Colonel?
- Yes, sir.
- You got that, captain?
- Sergeant?
- Got it.
Well?
It's a brilliant technological
achievement, General.
There's absolutely nothing like
it in the state of the art.
You trying to tell me something, Allison?
It's definitely not one of ours, General.
How about Russia?
Certainly not Russia.
It's far beyond the capabilities of...
Okay, Allison.
Lay it on the line.
Whose is it?
I don't know, General.
Well, we better find out.
I wanna know who made that thing,
Who flew it and where it came from.
Colonel?
Yes, sir.
Contact Sigcomm on our radio.
Get Hungerford at air.
Call Steinmetz at Johns Hopkins,
Lasser, Billings, Cranhammer.
Get them iqs off their tennis courts.
Yes, sir.
Double pronto!
Because if we don't find out
where that thing came from,
This country could be in trouble,
Big, big trouble.
Colonel.
Captain.
Sergeant.
Yes, sir.
You say it's not
man-made, Allison.
What's that leave us?
Outer space.
With no sign of the pilot.
Big, big trouble.
While you and I are talking
this very minute,
Some slimy green-headed, 12-legged creep.
Could be crawling into the White House.
Big, big trouble.
We're up against genius.
We'd better come up
with some genius of our own.
I believe, General, you've already met.
My administrative
assistant, Dr. Corday.
And I'd like to introduce some of
the other members of our team.
Dr. Robeson of Caltech, who's
our expert on fossil fuel.
Professor Hurakawa of Johns Hopkins.
Dr. Elizabeth Bartlett,
who heads thermal.
Dr. Norman Link, who's been
doing some intriguing work.
In garbage research.
- So what?
- Dr. Link.
Just a second,
Dr. Heffel.
I have to relay some vital
information to a colleague.
Yes. This is our hard-water man, Dr. Leach.
Right, Ernie. The Lakers by a
point and a half for 100 bucks.
When will you have the line on
Philly and the New York Knicks?
I'd like you
to meet Mr. Jurist,
Who also is involved in thermal.
And of course I'm sure
you're familiar with our...
And there's Dr. Banford,
Professor Epstein,
Doctors Davidson and Barrett,
And, of course, this is Dr.
Humphrey, our head of nuclear.
Mr. Stallwood, our head of
procurement and supplies.
Stallwood, what are you doing here?
Well, sir, when the call went out.
For an emergency meeting,
I naturally assumed...
You assumed wrong.
Scientists.
Double-A clearance only. Out.
But Dr. Heffel, I might have
a contribution to make...
If we need any sharp
pencils, I'll send for you.
But, Dr. Heffel...
Out.
Sorry, General.
Where was I?
Yes. Professor...
Dr. Heffel, I didn't
come here for a roll call,
I came to pick some brains.
Are they all here?
Yes. I'd say these
are our top people.
Then let's get to it!
I understand, General.
Attention, everyone.
Dr. Link.
Well, that's it, Professor. I'll
call tomorrow with more input. Bye.
All right, sergeant, open it.
Drapes.
Ladies and gentlemen, what you
are about to see is top secret.
The united states government
will countenance no leaks.
Now...
What's holding it up?
Nothing.
It's amazing.
Where did you get it?
What is it?
A propulsion unit of some
sort, ladies and gentlemen.
Never mind where we got it.
We have other experts working on that.
What we want to know from you is,
What makes it tick?
Okay, let's have your hypothesis.
The energy source could be atomic.
We've checked on that.
Negative.
Direct conversion, utilizing thermionic...
Checked out. Negative.
It's not propelled by garbage, I know that.
Jellyfish calling Olympus.
Come in, Olympus.
I'll call you about it later.
Mr. Olympus?
This is Jellyfish.
I think I'm on to
something very big and very...
Jellyfish.
Your man in ERL?
Yes, sir. That Jellyfish.
I think I'm on to something.
No, sir. I think you'll
find this a great deal.
More interesting than my last report.
Right now, Dr. Heffel
is in a secret meeting.
With a four-star General and a
whole gaggle of scientists.
What are they meeting about?
Well, I don't know, sir.
It's a secret.
Get in there and find out?
Do any of you have a solid evaluation?
Not a guess,
A solid premise?
Do you?
Well?
Do you think it might be fruitful.
To bring Dr. Wilson into this
discussion, Dr. Heffel?
Wilson?
Yes. He might very well come
up with an applicable theory.
Don't be ridiculous.
Who's Dr. Wilson?
He's in my carpool.
That is, we live in the same building.
That certainly qualifies him.
No, what I'm trying to say is,
He's a very bright, young physicist.
Who's come here recently
on loan from Caltech.
A loan, I might add, that is
bearing absolutely no interest.
He's a little unorthodox,
but a brilliant theorist.
Dr. Bartlett, General Stilton
isn't interested in...
Get him.
What?
Get him. His output couldn't be any
less than what we've gotten so far.
Yes, General.
He really has an unusual mind.
Well, Dr. Wilson?
It's beautiful.
Don't you have any other observation?
Only that it looks like an artichoke, sir.
We know it looks like an artichoke, Wilson.
What makes it tick?
Mayonnaise?
Negative.
No, no, I was only joking, sir.
I do have a theory, sir,
Actually in line with
the work I've been doing.
I have a hunch it's tapping the
primal mainstream, General.
The "primal mainstream"?
The primal mainstream, yes,
it's everywhere, General,
Only on different frequencies.
The whole
electro-magnetic spectrum.
Cosmic, gamma,
X-rays, ultraviolet,
visible light,
Infrared, radio waves...
And do you know.
How much we finite human
beings can probably tune into?
With our senses?
Less than five percent.
The universe makes its own energy, General.
We even make it ourselves.
Yes, take biofeedback, for instance.
Why, if I taped terminals
to your head, General,
Your brain could run an electric train.
Electric train?
I'm sorry, General, I thought...
Perhaps electric train
wasn't the most apt...
That'll be all, Wilson.
Thank you very much.
You let me have that for a
couple of months, General.
And I promise you...
Thank you.
A couple of months?
Dr. Heffel?
Yes, General?
I want action.
You know, Drexel,
I've seen the most amazing thing.
Amazing.
But don't ask me to tell you about it.
It's classified.
Thank you, Drexel.
Well. How did you
get in here?
Now, look, you're asking for trouble.
Dr. Heffel isn't too crazy
about animals in the building.
Fact is, he isn't too crazy about
people in the building either.
What's your name?
Charlie? Cuddles?
Jake? Yes, yes.
You look like Jake.
That, Jake,
Is the Van Allen Belt.
Oil and coal is not
going to do it, you know.
And one of these days, that sun of ours
is going to turn into a big black hole.
You know where it's really at, Jake?
Electromagnetism.
We're loaded with it.
You know, it's crazy,
but you almost look like.
You know what I'm talking about.
All right, give me a hand
with this, Sergeant.
Easy, easy.
That's it.
Stallwood, administration emergency!
Hey, that's some fancy collar you got there.
Maybe I'll take you home with me.
My neighbor, Liz, has a cat named Lucybelle.
She's really cute.
And the cat's not bad either.
Liz! Hi... Ouch!
I've... We were just
talking about you.
Were you?
This is Jake.
I'm going to take him home with us.
You won't have to drive Professor Link
and myself home tonight, Dr. Wilson.
Heffel's called a late meeting.
I don't mind waiting.
That won't be necessary. We've
made other arrangements.
How... How about a cup of coffee? No.
Chocolate chip cookie?
No!
Hey, are you sore or something?
Sore? Sore?
Well, whatever gave you that idea?
What is it?
What did I do?
Nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
Mayonnaise?
Electric trains?
Well, now, look, really, all that...
That was just a joke, doctor.
Well, nobody laughed.
Especially the General.
Has he had water?
The General?
The cat.
Water?
Cats do get thirsty, you know.
Do you have a bowl?...A bowl.
Right here.
Yes. Here.
Here.
Water?
Yes, right, water.
Look, Liz...
Dr. Bartlett.
Just because some General.
Lacks a sense of humor,
now that's no reason...
Well, anyway, all I was trying to convey...
I'm really not interested, doctor.
Well, besides, I wasn't trying to be funny.
It's just that.
The magnitude of what the General
showed us this afternoon.
Just bowled me over.
It did?
Completely.
Black.
What? Didn't you offer me a cup of coffee?
Right. Check.
Coming right up.
I just... I really don't
understand, that's all.
The man who wrote the article you did.
For The Scientific Quarterly, July 12th...
You read it?
Well, of course.
It was brilliant.
There's something I've
been wanting to tell you.
We don't get much chance
to talk in the carpool,
But I've been following
your work in thermal.
You have?
Closely.
It's very impressive, very innovative.
Very attractive. I mean, it's
bound to attract attention.
Well...
I am writing an article at the moment.
And I would love to have your criticism.
Maybe at lunch or, even
better, at dinner sometime?
Yeah, I'd like that.
When?
Tonight?
No, that's right, you've
got that late meeting.
Well, that may not go all that late.
I should be out by 7:00.
Is that too late?
7:00 is beautiful.
Good.
Well...
Thanks for the coffee. It was delicious.
I think she digs you.
I sure hope so.
Who said that?
I did.
And, Frank, we'd better get down to business.
Sit down. We've gotta talk.
I'm running out of time, and it
looks like you're the only one
I can depend on to help me.
It... It's you?
It's not the mouse.
Now, sit down.
But your lips aren't moving.
You're not speaking.
Thought transference. Nothing exceptional
where I come from. Now, sit.
My name is
Zunar-J-5/9 Doric-4-7.
Zunar...
Why don't we just stay with Jake, okay?
Frank, last night, at 03 hours plus 13,
I made an emergency landing in a
spaceship from another galaxy.
That so-called artichoke,
it's from my craft.
But... You're a cat.
Granted. But you see,
Frank, in our civilization,
That's as far as we needed to evolve.
We developed our brain to a fine point.
Now, man, on the other hand,
rose off his four legs.
And developed tools, machinery, agriculture,
And a chronic pain in his lower back.
We developed tools for the mind.
This collar here, it amplifies brain power.
It... It does what?
Well, it provides energy by which we...
Look, let me give you a demonstration.
Not a bad little tune.
Frank, this is really delicious. What is it?
It's chopped kidney.
It's all they had at the deli.
It really hits the spot.
I'm gonna take a couple of
cases for my trip back.
Sure beats the blah I've been eating.
Well, now back to my problem.
Frank, I need an answer.
What do you say?
Say about what?
Can I count on you to help
me repair my spaceship?
Why me?
Because I like the way you think.
Your equations rather interest me.
In fact, they're really not bad at all.
For a human.
Really? I'm on
the right track?
Quite definitely.
But years away from a solution.
Frank, on my planet, we have an expression.
"you rub my fur,
I'll rub yours."
How would you like to make a quantum jump?
You help me, and I'll give you
a push in the right direction.
You're serious?
I'm serious.
You're telling me the truth? The truth.
You really are from outer space?
I am from outer space.
Even though you're a cat?
Frank! Is it a deal?
It's a deal.
That's...
We better get moving.
I've got to make repairs.
To my ship by 5:13
Sunday for liftoff,
Or I'll miss the rendezvous
with the mother ship.
Right...
I'll get my sweater.
Do you think that you can find
your way back to that airport?
No problem. I made
a memory imprint.
With the collar?
Right.
Fantastic.
How developed does your brain
have to be to use that collar?
Not very. In fact,
you could handle it.
You wanna try?
Well... Do we have time?
Why not? Look, just...
Just grab hold of it.
Easy! Don't take it off.
I mean, without that collar,
I'm just an average cat.
Right, right.
Right. Okay?
Okay.
Now just concentrate.
Concentrate.
Think levitation.
Levitation.
You're as light as a feather.
Look at me.
I'm floating!
It's just plain incredible!
Hey, look, one hand.
Watch it, Frank! You're
losing your concentration.
Yeah.
Hi, Frank.
Gotta use your set.
The ball goes crosscourt to Brown.
He brings it up into the front court...
What were you doing up in the air?
Astronaut exercises.
Link, I'm busy.
Yeah. Well, just
forget I'm here.
It's the last minute of the game,
And Francine throws me out of the apartment.
Why does she throw me out of the apartment?
For one lousy cigar burn on the chair.
When did you get a cat?
Jake's not my cat.
He's just visiting.
Hi, Jake.
Link, I'm afraid I'm gonna
have to ask you to leave.
Do you mind, Frank?
Okay, I am back in.
Remember, the score's tied at 108.
Atlanta has the ball
and a basket could win it.
Win it? Man!
And I gave a point and a half.
Well, there goes my 100 bucks.
Come on, defense. Come on, guys.
Man to man, we'll...
The crowd is really on its feet now.
He's alone in the baseline
and closely guarded by king.
King steals the ball.
What a play!
Here come the lakers to the attack.
Five seconds left.
Pete Burt puts up a shot. But
a prayer, there's no chance.
Wait...
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
I don't believe it.
He scores!
He made it in the last second, and
the Lakers will win it by two.
Unbelievable!
Frank, did you see that?
Yeah.
Yeah. Link, I'm really gonna
have to ask you to leave.
Yeah, I could use another beer, Frank.
Yeah, I'm out of beer, I'm sorry.
Okay. How
about a ginger ale?
I'm out of that, too.
Could I at least finish my cigar?
Link, please.
Frank, I'd like to have
a little celebration.
I haven't won a bet in two weeks!
I'll see you later.
The basketball game?
You did that?
Frank, any friend of yours
is a friend of mine.
Besides, it seemed the fastest
way to get rid of that flake.
Now, let's go. I've got less
than 36 hours to liftoff.
Right...
Do you think I ought to carry you?
I mean, just so people don't suspect
you're not an ordinary cat?
Good thinking, Frank. Besides, my
left paw's been acting up again.
An old football injury?
Actually, no. Polo.
Now let's go.
You...
What about getting into Hopscotch?
It's got to be heavily guarded.
I'll handle that, too.
It's fantastic.
Hi. Hi, this is Lucybelle.
What'd you say you call him?
- Jake.
- Jake, right.
Jake, this is Lucybelle.
I thought they could get
acquainted while we're at dinner.
At dinner?
Yeah. It was
tonight, wasn't it?
Right...
Right. Right, yes.
And... I was just
about to call you.
Something came up.
And I'm afraid you're going to
have to give me a rain check.
Well, of course.
It really doesn't matter.
But it does. It matters a lot, Liz.
Dr. Bartlett.
You see, what happened was...
It's Jake. He took sick.
Suddenly. Out of the blue.
Really? What is it?
I think it's...
Tasmanian croup.
You poor thing. You know,
he sounds terrible.
Yeah. You'd better not
let her get too close.
Stop milking it.
What?
I said I was about to rush him to the vet's.
The vet. That's a good idea, Frank.
Hey, do you know there's a very good vet.
Who lives right in the building?
A Dr. Wenger.
He specializes in cats. I'm sure
he'd be glad to take a look at him.
Yeah, well, Jake prefers.
A General practitioner.
Look, I'm sorry about dinner, Liz.
I'll make it up to you.
How about a picnic?
I'd love it! Tomorrow?
You handled that situation very well, Frank.
I didn't enjoy lying to Liz.
She's a very unusual person.
Her kitty-cat's
not too bad either.
There's plenty of time for that.
That's all right for you to say.
But I've been confined to
a spaceship for five months.
The ship's in that big hangar.
There's got to be a way in.
It's locked.
No problem.
Come on, come on.
Right, right.
The coast is clear.
Let's go!
There she is.
Somebody's coming.
Somebody's coming, Frank!
I know, I know.
What's happening?
It's all clear.
Let's go!
It's this way.
Forget it. Forget it.
It wears off in 20 minutes.
It's harmless.
He won't remember a thing.
Come on, let's go.
Incredible.
An older model, but in pretty good shape.
For a rig with nearly
a trillion miles on it.
Well, now let's see what we can do
about getting it operational again.
We've only got 34 hours left.
Right. Through here?
Put me down.
It's just incredible.
The artichoke.
I was right.
What's this?
Control panel?
Sort of.
And this?
Computer.
Then this must be the readout?
Frank, later.
I'll explain it all later, I promise.
First, we have to disengage
the transducer system.
But how?
Take that neo-mag
neutralizing intercog,
And you'll find the transducer
switch on top of the ship.
Just coordinate with me.
Well, how do I get up there?
Fly.
Fly?
You mean use your collar?
Don't be ridiculous.
We carry a spare.
Just concentrate, and when you get on top,
Engage the switch with the intercog.
And thought-project
"seven max triad."
Seven max triad.
Right. The computer
will do the rest.
Seven max triad. Right.
Hey!
Hey, Frank, what are you doing up there?
What about the intercog?
Frank?
Jake, I'm ready to plug it in.
Right. Go ahead.
It's in.
Okay. Thought-project.
Seven max triad.
Okay, Frank.
Come on down.
Amazing.
I was afraid of that.
The focal terminal on the
microtransformer's vaporized.
It happens in these older models.
You're sure?
Positive.
But I'll double-check.
Just what I thought.
That's where the focal terminal goes?
In that little thing?
Acts as a catalyzer. I'll need
a small amount of org 12.
What's org 12?
What the focal terminal's made of.
About six cubits ought to be
enough for emergency repair.
You don't have org 12 on this planet?
Never heard of it.
Is it like mayonnaise?
You probably call it by a different name.
Now, stand back, Frank. I'll
run it through the computer.
Hey, Tom!
You all right?
Tom!
Org 12. Ductile yellow metallic element.
Melting point, 1,063.
Tensile strength, 19,000.
Tensile strength what?
19,000.
Atomic weight, 196.967.
Wait a minute.
That's the atomic weight of gold!
Wow!
Out! Out!
Everybody out!
What is that?
Come on, let's go.
Follow me!
Holy cow.
Give my collar room, Frank.
You can't zap the whole base.
Let's get out of here.
Over here! Follow me! Move out!
Watch it!
Hey!
Come back here!
Where are you going?
Hey, hey! Come out of there.
You're under arrest!
Look out!
What is it?
Get it off of me!
Get it off!
Was anybody in there?
Back it out. Back it out.
Look out. Who's driving?
Corporal of the guard!
Yes, sir?
What's going on here?
Who sounded that alarm?
I did, sir. We have an
intruder, and his cat.
Cat? Cat? Cat?
Yes, sir.
Here's his collar.
Jake!
Excuse me.
Jake, are you all right?
Frank, shut up and move this thing.
That's him, sir!
Halt!
Get that thing out of here! Get it out!
Move it out!
Now what do we do?
Now you hang on.
17 times...
Five of...
Now cosine of...
Yeah...
Hey, Frank. This is even better
than the stuff I had last night.
What's it called?
Tuna.
Tuna? Love it.
Keeps coming out the same way
and it doesn't make any sense.
What doesn't?
Well, according to your figures,
We're going to need $120,000 worth of gold.
So?
Jake, forgetting the money,
which I can't forget,
You know how much gold that is?
It's that much. And you want
to put it in a space that big?
You folks are still operating on the
bulk system as opposed to content.
I'll reduce it to the size I need.
And still retain all its properties.
How?
I'll get into that later.
First buy the gold.
Buy it? Jake, in order to
buy $120,000 worth of gold,
You need $120,000.
So? Is that a problem?
A problem?
My entire capital is tied up
in my next paycheck.
Then what's the alternative?
I don't know what
the alternative is. I...
Hi.
Traditionally known in horse racing...
Boy.
What are you doing?
Borrowing your tv.
Just bring me a beer and forget I'm here.
Hi, Jake.
Link...
Wife's worked out an equitable
tv schedule for the day.
The Peachtree Derby and the
football game's on your set,
And the metropolitan opera on mine.
Can't you see I'm busy?
Doing what?
Playing with your pussycat?
Link...
Franklin, please.
I've got a bundle bet on the Peachtree.
Frank, we've got problems
to solve, things to do.
What?
Link, I'm sorry but I'm
gonna have to ask you...
They're at the post.
You want a peanut?
No.
Come on, Sweet Jake.
Let's go.
Sweet Jake?
Yeah, it's a hunch bet.
100 on the nose at 15 to 1.
I tell you, if she comes in, tiger,
And I'm gonna be 1,500 in front,
And you'll be licking mackerel fillet.
Did you forget my beer or
did I drink it already?
Never mind, I'll get it.
I'll try to get rid of him.
Wait a minute.
Did you hear what he said, Frank?
If Sweet Jake finishes first, he wins $1500.
So? So if Link can win $1500,
Why can't we win 120,000?
No, no, no. Wait a minute.
He just made a bet.
He could win 1500.
It doesn't mean he will.
With me on his side, he will.
Did you say something?
No, nothing.
Okay, okay.
Let's pipe down.
I got 100 big ones riding on this nag.
And they're off.
It's Denny's Doll breaking on top.
Attaboy Star. Daddy's Poppa on the outside.
Booky Baby on the rail and Seabottom...
Where's Sweet Jake?
Sweet Jake is still in the gate.
At the clubhouse turn, it's
Denny's Doll by half a length.
Attaboy Star, and Daddy's Poppa.
Sweet Jake is finally out of the gate.
Sweet Jake is moving. He's
way behind, but he's moving.
I think he stopped to have lunch.
I don't believe this.
Eat on your own time!
See what I mean?
Now, it's Attaboy Star...
Sweet Jake! I should have bet
on the Metropolitan Opera.
Daddy's Poppa moving up, and Seabottom.
It's Attaboy Star by a length. Booky
Baby, Denny's Doll and Seabottom.
Sweet Jake's finished
eating and started running.
And, ladies and gentlemen, is he running!
But not even Silky Sullivan could
come from this far behind.
It's Booky Baby taking the lead.
Daddy's Poppa moving into
second, and Attaboy Star.
And making up incredible
ground is Sweet Jake.
I have never seen anything like this.
But can he catch the pack?
At the top of the stretch.
It's Booky Baby in the lead.
Daddy's Poppa.
And turning for home, it's Sweet Jake.
Come on, Jake. Come on.
Give him the whip, dummy.
Racetrack, and he's flying!
Attaboy! Here we go. Come on.
Come on. Come on, Jake.
Attaway. Come on, Jake.
Come on. Come on, boy!
That's it! Hot dog money.
We got it! Hoo!
Yee-haw!
The story here today, ladies and
gentlemen, is Sweet Jake. Never in...
Fifteen hundred smackeroos!
That calls for another beer.
How about you?
I'm buying.
No. No, thanks.
Incidentally, Frank, you
could use another six-pack.
I got a feeling I'm gonna murder
them on the football games.
Frank, that's the solution to the money.
No, no, it's ridiculous.
It won't work.
Why won't it?
Well... In the first place, I don't
know anything about placing a bet.
I wouldn't know where to go, what to do.
I gotta call Ernie with my football bets.
The Rams, Patriot game starts in 25 minutes.
I guess we're gonna have to
take in another partner.
Who?
Him.
Did you say something, Frank?
Link? Do you
think that's wise?
Do I think what's wise?
Who are you talking to?
Ask how many football games we can bet on.
But... Who are you talking to?
Ask him!
Frank?
It's crazy.
Buddy?
What?
Who?
How many football games on tv today?
Three pro games. East,
midwest, far west. Who?
Brief him.
Frank, have you got a tape
machine going or something?
I don't think it's a good idea, but okay.
You know, if I didn't know better,
I'd say you were talking to the cat.
I was.
Right.
Look, Frank, listen, this can happen
to anybody in government service.
That's why they have staff psychiatrists.
First thing Monday...
Link, take a deep breath.
Okay.
Remember that artichoke?
Well, it all started when this spaceship...
Spaceship? ...From another galaxy.
Landed in a field, out near Palmdale.
Frank, let me get this straight, okay?
Now, you're trying to tell me.
That your little pussycat
came from another planet.
From another galaxy in a spacecraft,
And landed right here on Earth?
Is that what you're trying to say, Frank?
That's right.
You're squeezing, link.
See? You heard him talk.
Look.
I mean, I don't know how
you're doing your...
Your little trick, you know.
But I gotta tell you something, pal.
It's dumb. Very dumb.
So, you know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna drink your last beer,
Then I'm gonna watch three football
games on your television set,
And then I'm going home,
because this is dumb, Frank.
Real dumb.
Now, that's dumb.
Aw, Link, look. Listen to me for one minute.
I don't want to hear it, Frank.
He was trying to prove...
I don't want...
Something...
To hear it, Frank!
Okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
All right.
That does it, Frank!
I'm going home.
And watch the Metropolitan Opera.
Now, Link. We need your help.
Jake needs your help!
I don't want to hear about it!
We need money to fix... Frank, I...
You're the only person I know
who knows how to place a bet.
I don't anything about placing...
What kind of a spaceship?
Hey, you're beautiful.
Well, you're down 200, sucker.
Would you like to double it?
Earnest Ernie's Sporting Club.
Weasel speaking.
What's your pleasure?
Yeah. Give me four balls.
I'll double it.
What do you say, Sarasota Slim?
I say give him five.
The man says, "give him five." you got it.
Honest Harry holds.
Link, can you make it fast?
We got a hot one on the rotisserie.
Can I trust him?
Would a crook have a name like Honest Harry?
You wanna bet what?
Hold on.
Hey, Ernie.
Ernie, come here.
Yeah.
Ernie, it's Link. He wants to take
all his winnings from Sweet Jake.
And parlay the three football games.
You're kidding?
A three-game parlay?
Yeah. It'll come to 120 g's if he makes it.
It's like taking candy from a baby, Weasel.
He's down.
You're down.
Hold it right there.
General? General?
Fingerprints. Fingerprints, sir.
They found fingerprints.
Well, now.
On top of the hull,
Inside the cabin, everywhere.
And they are the prints of a human being.
In other words, whatever power
brought this ship here,
They were aided and abetted
by some disloyal American.
Gentlemen, we are dealing
with a collaborator.
I want the face that matches these prints.
Put it through the computer.
Double pronto, sir.
General!
Look at this.
Sir, they found more.
What in blazes is that?
Fine hair, sir. The pilot
was wearing a fur coat.
But even more important,
we found tiny prints.
In a claw-like pattern,
like a... Like a pussycat's.
Pussycat?
Why aren't I hearing
some tickety-tacks?
What about those fingerprints?
There's a printout about
to come through, sir.
Sir...
What do you want me to do with this?
Get it checked, sir.
Coming through, sir.
"I.D. Wilson,
Frank. Doctor.
"Social security, 631070829.
"1951 to '55. US Navy.
'55 to '62, Caltech.
"Current employment,
theoretician. ERL"?
That's my Dr. Wilson!
The scoundrel.
We'll have him in the slammer
within the hour, sir.
And blow the whole ball game?
Gentlemen,
we're after Mr. Big,
And this double-crossing
fink is gonna lead us to him.
To find the rat, tail the cat.
Cat?
It's just an expression.
Want a peanut, Jake?
No, thanks. I'll wait
till Frank gets back.
The Rams still ahead?
Ahead? Frank,
the Rams won the game.
And without Jake's help.
Without your help, buddy.
Great, let's break open the six-pack.
What will you have, Jake?
Did you get some more of that tuna?
Yeah, yeah.
Coming right up.
There's
the two-minute warning.
Oilers leading 21-19,
Houston driving.
Another one in the bag, Franklin.
Come in.
Frank?
Hi. Lucybelle
insisted on coming, too.
- Coming?
- Yeah, the picnic.
The picnic.
Beer, Liz?
No, thanks.
Is something wrong?
Is his croup worse?
Whose?
Jake's.
Yeah. Right.
I was up all night.
Really?
Yeah.
It's gone into hyperzemia.
What's hyperzemia?
It's what Jake's got.
What did your doctor do for him yesterday?
He gave him two aspirin.
Two aspirin?
What's that?
What's happening, Frank?
I don't know.
Two aspirin. No wonder you're feeling worse.
How did he get the ball?
Interception, I guess.
What this cat needs is some expert help.
Get him.
Dr. Wenger.
Yeah, okay. I'll go get him.
I'll be right back.
Get him.
Somebody tackle him.
Hi, sweetie. Can I get you anything?
Okay. Out of bounds
on the 30.
Jake, why didn't you do something?
And spoil everybody's fun? Look,
guys, there's plenty of time.
Anybody ever tell you, you got
a terrific set of whiskers?
Jake, for heaven's sakes,
will you pay attention?
They're within field-goal range.
If they make it, we're sunk.
No problem, believe me.
A little tuna, sweetheart?
Jake, concentrate, please. The
next few seconds could be crucial.
Takes a time out.
Time out.
I appreciate it, doctor.
At least you could have waited
till the game was over.
I have $10 on chicago.
You've got it on.
What's happening?
Time out.
This is Dr. Wenger.
Dr. Wenger,
here's the patient.
I definitely think he needs your attention.
All right.
How did they get to the 30? Interception.
Happened while we were in the elevator.
Or are they gonna try for a field goal?
What do you think, doctor?
I think they should try for a field goal.
About the cat.
Well, he's tense.
Yes, he's very tense.
The shoulder muscles are all bunched up.
Where do you wanna do the examination?
Right here will be fine.
Okay. Let me get
this out of the way.
Also, let's... First thing,
get this collar off.
Hey!
Good thinking, Chicago.
This year. He's never missed
inside the 35-yard line.
Get through that line now.
That guy can't kick a ball 60 yards.
Block that kick.
Will you calm down now?
Hold the cat, please.
Jake, you better do something.
What are you doing?
Where's his collar?
Block that...
It's right here, Frank.
Give it to me, Liz.
Give it to me.
Frank, I'm just gonna hold the...
I'm gonna give him a sedative.
No, no, don't do that!
Frank, let go of the cat.
There's the snap.
It's down. The kick is up.
It's long enough.
It's straight enough. It's...
It's...
It's flat!
I've never seen anything like it. We won!
The ball just flattened out in midair.
And there's the gun.
Jake?
The Oilers have won it 21 to 19.
I told you not to do that!
I only came up here
as a favor to a neighbor.
As a rule, I do not make house calls.
You sure picked a dumb
time to break your rule.
Dr. Link!
Look, Dr. Wenger, please forgive him.
He's a new cat-owner...
Jake. Jake.
It's me, Jake.
Frank, we're finished. He's blotto.
Well, look on the bright side.
San Diego could still win.
Yeah, and San Diego could still lose.
And where does that
leave this poor little guy?
He's blown his rendezvous,
and my 1500 clams.
That was very rude, Frank.
Liz, butt out.
What?
Cancel the bet.
Call Ernie.
He'll never buy it.
Look, what's going on here?
Jake, we got problems, Jake. Speak to me.
Is everybody crazy?
Frank, the line is busy. We'll never
get through. He's taking bets.
We'd better get down there. Like yesterday.
Now, look...
Just a minute, Frank.
I would like... No, I demand an explanation.
What's going on?
Later, Liz.
No. Now.
Liz, we have got exactly six
minutes before that game starts.
Watch it, Link.
I'm a black belt.
Okay. We'll tell you
in the elevator.
Remember that meeting we had with Dr.
Heffel.
And General Stilton at the ERL?
Outer space?
Frank Wilson, are you putting me on?
No, no. Remember that artichoke? Well, yeah.
Dydee one calling Hopscotch.
Come in, Big Cheese.
This is Big Cheese.
Go ahead, Dydee One.
Do you still have contact with the subject?
Yes, sir.
Also that garbage expert.
And the dame from the car pool.
And they're all going into
Earnest Ernie's pool hall.
Looks like a mafia
tie-in, General.
Mafia?
What kind of an operation you
running down there, Heffel?
Lucky!
Really lucky.
Ernie? Ernie?
Excuse me. Ernie?
Hi, Ernie.
Well, look who's here.
Hiya, doc.
Ernie,
I wanna cancel my Chargers bet.
You wanna cancel your Chargers bet?
Yeah, cancel my Chargers bet.
Really? Why?
I don't know.
Just a hunch, sort of.
Hey, not a bad hunch. The
Chargers are 10 points behind.
Already?
16, boss, 16. Steelers
just scored another one.
Sorry, doc.
Is he taking a nap?
Yeah.
Is that tv picture still out?
Well, there goes 120,000.
1,500 of which is mine.
Isn't there anything you can do?
Not while Jake is out. Jake, Jake, wake up.
We need you, Jake.
Frank, is he breathing?
He's snoring.
Okay. Okay. Isn't there
anything else we can bet on?
Yeah. Yeah. Maybe we could get lucky.
Another football game?
Next Sunday.
Basketball?
Tuesday night.
Hockey?
Hockey.
Ernie, Ernie, is there a hockey game today.
That we could put a few bucks on?
Sorry.
Horse race?
Boxing?
Demolition derby?
Anything to get even.
No.
But, hey, if you want a little action,
There's always my good friend Sarasota Slim.
Sarasota Slim?
Yes.
He indulges occasionally
in a friendly pool game.
With a slight wager on the side.
Nothing doing.
Why not?
Well, he's a hustler.
Who isn't?
Okay, it's a bet.
Frank.
What are the odds?
You against Sarasota Slim?
Right.
Frank.
Well, because I want to give
you a chance to break even.
And because I like your style,
Let's say 8 to 1.
That's all?
What about him?
Me?
Link?
Well, considering the shape
he's in, I'd say maybe 10 to 1.
What about the lady?
Me?
Liz?
Considering the shape she's in, 20 to 1.
Okay, you got a bet.
Frank!
Arch, set 'em up. Another
sucker just swam into the net.
Frank, I don't know
anything about this game.
Frank, are you bananas?
That guy can make a pool ball
sit up and do the boogaloo.
I know, but I've got the equalizer...
The collar.
How are you gonna do that?
Jake's out.
I've used it to repair the spaceship.
You? Yes. I've flown and everything.
Charlie, give me the special,
and heavy on the onions.
Taking a nap?
Yeah.
Throw in a few chili peppers?
Frank, I don't want to take the risk...
Liz, you've got to do it.
I'm desperate.
No money, no gold.
No gold, no liftoff.
But...
But if we deliver,
look what we get in return.
The solution to half the
problems on this planet.
Just show me how to hold the pole.
Good girl.
Now, we need a stake.
I've got about 12 bucks.
It's in my hip pocket.
Will you get it for me?
Yeah, okay, that's 12.
Now, how much do you have?
Me? I think I got 20.
20? Liz?
I just have my mad money.
Give it to us, please?
Come on.
Boy, when this dame gets mad, she gets mad.
I was going to buy
a whole spring wardrobe, Link.
Okay. Ernie.
Boss, here's the bankroll.
Ernie, we bet 300 at 20 to 1.
Check.
Not in your lifetime,
Ernie. Honest Harry holds.
All right, you want Honest
Harry, you got Honest Harry.
300 at 20 to 1.
That's 6,000 clams.
And here's our 300.
Earnest ernie, 6,000.
The mark, 300.
6,300.
And may the best man win.
Or woman, as the case may be.
Young lady, it's your break.
Come on, Charlie, don't be
so stingy with the onions.
Here, take the collar, Liz.
Okay, here.
Link, keep your eye on him.
If he blinks just once...
Miss? Do you mind? We're waiting.
Now, that's a sandwich. Right?
Right.
Taking a nap.
Naturally.
Nice break, young lady.
Very nice.
Unfortunately, you didn't sink anything,
But there's always tomorrow.
Show her how to do it.
Okay, Slim, go get her.
I can't watch this.
Frank, I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
It's not your fault.
Attaway, Slim.
Attaway, baby.
I guess we are licked. If only
Jake hadn't got knocked out...
Frank! Frank, look.
Jake!
Jake?
Frank, he must have just woke up.
Jake, are you all right?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm okay.
Where am I? What happened?
I'm Liz Bartlett. I'm
responsible for your being...
Liz, Liz.
Well.
Jake, we have got to win this pool game.
That's money
in the bank. Look at it!
Honest Harry, guess who's here?
Ernie?
Here's our last 60 bucks.
What are the odds now?
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
No bet.
No bet?
It's part of my code of ethics.
Always leave the sucker rent money.
That's not fair!
Honest Harry?
If the mark wants to go complete top city,
He's got a constitutional right.
And I stand on it.
The odds, Ernie?
It's ridiculous. But if I
didn't have no principles,
I'd say 100 to 1.
Suppose... Suppose she gives
Sarasota Slim 12 balls?
What a sense of humor!
300 to 1.
And the break.
The break?
500 to 1.
And blindfolded.
What?
Blindfolded!
2,000 to 1.
You're on.
$60 at 2,000 to 1.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
Are you seriously serious?
You're not thinking of welching, are you?
But I thought you was putting me on.
Earnest Ernie, it would not do
your reputation any credit.
If word was to circulate that you reneged.
On a wager duly offered and accepted.
Get the big bundle, Weasel.
But, boss, that's a...
Get it!
All right.
Let me understand this. Slim
gets 12 balls and the break?
And she shoots blindfolded.
She'll never get to the table.
120 g's, boss.
Don't put it away, Honest Harry,
you ain't gonna hold it long.
All right, Slim.
Show 'em no mercy.
Nice. Nice break, slim.
Unfortunately, you didn't sink
nothing, but there's always tomorrow.
I believe I'm up.
Hold it.
Blindfolded.
Could you back off?
Thank you.
It was nothing.
You did it, Jake.
You did it.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
It was really nothing.
Thank you.
Frank, we won! Thank you. Thank you.
Thanks, all of you. Thank you.
I'm sorry about things being
upside down, Mr. Olympus,
But I took these pictures
at risk of life and limb.
There's the cat, sir.
Notice his collar?
Well, well.
What did you think
of it, Mr. Olympus?
It's just mind-boggling,
isn't it?
I mean, it boggled my mind.
Did it boggle yours, sir?
Thank you, Omar.
Yes, Mr. Stallwood,
you are quite correct.
It is "mind-boggling,"
as you so graphically put it.
The possibilities are infinite.
A revolution in transportation,
space exploration,
Colonizing the planets.
The man who owns the secret of
this device could control...
The world, sir?
The universe.
My!
Well, then, sir, I don't suppose it would be.
Out of place to suggest a bonus.
A bonus?
A small bonus.
Mr. Stallwood, if I gain
the secret of that device,
You may well become a very rich man.
I may?
Sir, I...
Really may?
Omar, prepare the copter.
We leave at once.
I must have that collar.
I will have that collar.
Okay. All set, General.
Is it fully programmed?
All the pertinent information fed in.
Everything we know.
Question number one, sir.
Question number one.
Who is the pilot?
It is a pussycat!
This machine is having a nervous breakdown.
Get on the ball, young man.
Feed that information
through again. Reassess.
Yes, sir.
General Stilton, sir.
What is it, Sergeant?
That purchase Dr. Link made this
afternoon, we checked it out.
It's a large quantity of gold.
Gold?
Yes, sir.
It's a Machiavellian conspiracy.
Radio.
This is Big Cheese calling Dydee One.
Where are you, Dydee One?
Outside the suspect's apartment.
Don't let them out of your sight.
Another printout, General.
Of all the...
Wait a minute. Radio.
Dydee One.
Yes, sir.
Didn't they carry a cat into that pool hall?
Yes, sir, they did.
Gentlemen, it's time to move in.
Colonel.
Captain.
$120,000 in one lump sum.
Jake, how'd you like to
hang around for a few days.
And watch me parlay this into a fortune?
I wish I could hang around.
I'm sorry, Jake.
The time?
Yeah.
Sorry, Lucy.
Well, I guess I'd better reduce the gold.
Reduce it?
What are you talking about?
It's a whole new concept
in calculating mass.
You see, on Jake's planet, they
use a system based on content,
Rather than on the quantitative scale...
Frank! You've got a whole
lifetime to explain that.
I've got less than an hour.
Now, stand back, everybody.
All right, don't move!
All hands in the air!
In the air!
Hey! What are you doing?
Dr. Frank Wilson?
What is this?
You can't butt in here!
Dr. Frank Wilson,
you are under arrest.
And the pussycat, General.
And the pussycat.
Read them their rights, Colonel.
Captain?
Sergeant?
You have the right to remain silent.
Never mind.
Anything you say can be used
against you in a court of law.
You have the right...
Good heavens.
Frank...
What happened?
They're frozen.
Holy mackerel!
Well, now that they're on to us, how
are we gonna get into Hopscotch?
You can't zap the whole base.
Yeah, well, I'll think of something.
They've probably got
the whole place on alert.
First things first, Frank.
Let's get this gold reduced, then we'll
worry about getting on the base.
Now stand back.
Okay. Here goes.
That is unbelievable.
Jake.
Are you all right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, come on.
Let's get out of here.
No. Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I think I've got the perfect
way to get us onto the base.
Maybe we ought to give 'em a buzz.
Think we ought to give 'em a buzz?
Yeah, give 'em a buzz.
Dydee One calling Big Cheese.
Come in, Big Cheese.
Come in.
Dydee One calling Big Cheese.
What's the military doing here?
This could be complicated, sir.
What isn't?
Get that door closed!
What does it all mean?
It means it's exceptionally complicated.
Dydee One calling Big Cheese.
Come in, Big Cheese. Come in.
Here comes General Cheese.
I mean, Stilton.
Wait a minute. Here.
Hold Jake for a minute.
Yes.
How do I look?
Could you hold lucy for a minute?
Do I look like a General?
Well...
Frank, you look very commanding.
That'll have to do.
Let's go.
Okay.
He got the cat.
That's the cat!
Where's the General going with those two?
That's the General?
It's not?
Open your door!
Open the doors!
Halt! Halt in the
name of the us...
Fantastic.
Listen, good luck?
Yeah, be careful.
Bye, Lucybelle.
Thanks for everything.
Yeah, yeah. Let's go.
Bye.
They've escaped?
Yes.
But, fortunately for us, they left
something very valuable behind.
General Stilton?
Of course!
Of course.
I'll sign you in, sir.
General Stilton and cat.
Is the cat cleared, sir?
What do you think?
Sorry, sir.
I want the hangar open and all personnel out.
We're moving the ship.
But, sir, if we order 'em out of
the hangar, how are you gonna...
Soldier!
Out of the hangar, sir.
Yes, sir.
Get the hangar doors open.
All personnel out of the
hangar on the double.
First, let's get the ship out of the hangar.
Check.
To talk to a lawyer and have
him present while you're being...
Colonel?
Yes, sir.
Hold it right here, Frank.
130 to countdown.
Hurry. Insert the gold
in the microtransformer.
Right, right.
Got it.
Good. Now let's see if we have contact.
Zunar-J-5 calling mother ship.
Come in, mother.
Where's the microphone?
How do you transmit?
Frank!
Okay, okay!
Zunar-J-5 calling mother ship.
Come in, mother.
Hi, there, fella. See you made
it with nothing to spare.
We had problems.
We are 105 to liftoff.
Coming in on ray 0392.
Adjust transmuter.
Adjustment made.
- Countdown starts at 20.
- Set clinometers.
Clinometers' set.
Give me a printout, please.
Coming your way without delay.
That's another cat?
Yeah.
A real mother.
I gotta get to that spaceship right away.
Sir, who are you?
A friend of Frank...
I mean General Stilton.
A very good friend.
Let's go.
Open the gate.
My car!
Them, too.
Never mind them.
Let's get down to Hopscotch.
Sergeant.
Captain.
Colonel.
General.
Get in!
Counting down.
Hey, Frank!
Hold it, sir, right there.
General, this man says...
Hey!
You're not General Stilton.
Hey, Frank. Link! What are you doing here?
Frank, it's a nightmare. Liz has
been captured by stallwood.
What... Have you been
hitting the beer?
Stallwood of supplies and purchasing?
He's an agent, Frank. For
some guy named Olympus,
A power-crazed creep
who's trying to...
Frank, he's holding her for ransom.
Lucybelle, too?
Yeah, he wants that collar, Jake.
It's the collar or Liz.
Are they out of their minds? Where is she?
I'm going with you, Frank.
No, no, no, you don't want
to get stuck here on Earth.
And you've got a responsibility
to your mission.
But I'm the reason for the mess they're in.
Do you know where they're taking her? Yeah.
To some place called Dailey's airport.
Do you know where it is? Yeah.
Let's go.
Frank... Jake, you're going home.
Now, get in there.
So long, buddy.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Five, four,
Three, two.
Ignite.
Bye, Jake.
Drop us a card.
Okay, you clowns. Let's move it. Let's go.
Jake!
Jake, this is insane. You're
here forever, on Earth.
You're wasting time.
The airport!
General, look!
Good heavens!
That's my car. Get the police on the radio.
Hello, Sequoia...
Turn this thing around!
Here comes a car.
It's Wilson.
Yeah, and Link.
And the cat! They're here. They've come!
Naturally.
You knew they would.
You knew it. We've won.
Now they will have turn over the cat.
And we will turn over the girl.
We will?
We won't?
It might be difficult to explain
your part in this affair.
After the young lady's gone to the police.
Dear.
You wouldn't dare!
Frank, that must be the chopper.
It's the police, sir.
It's a trap.
The fools!
Get us airborne.
Watch it!
They're getting away! They're leaving!
Yeah, yeah.
But look who's arriving.
The army and the police.
Jake, we have to follow that copter.
What... What kind of an airport is this?
Where are the planes?
Follow me.
You can't fly this, Jake. It's a wreck.
Look at that propeller, it's half gone.
Are you coming or staying?
I'm coming.
I'm staying.
Okay, Tovarisch.
Quoi?
All right,
Dr. Garbage Expert.
Who's your accomplice?
Who's flying that plane?
General, you're not gonna believe this.
There they are.
It's Wilson and the cat.
How did they get that wreck in the air?
The power that cat possesses is awesome.
You betcha, Charlie,
And if you know what's good for you,
You'll land this thing, and let Lucybelle...
Quiet!
Okay.
Faster, Omar, faster.
Get close. Use the collar
to force them to land.
No chance. It's taking all I got.
Just to keep this crate flying.
Don't panic. We'll think of something.
What's happening? Why aren't
they doing something?
Of course! They're afraid
of harming the girl.
Turn on them, Omar.
The advantage is ours.
What's happening? Why are
they turning around?
Straight at them, Omar.
Drive them down.
Frank!
Jake!
Jake. Jake!
Jake! Jake!
Jake! Turn this thing over.
Jake.
Jake. Jake!
Frank, are you okay?
What are they trying to do?
They're trying to force us down.
They probably figured out
that we've got a problem.
Hold on!
Here they come.
They're still on our tail.
Don't panic.
On top of them, Omar.
Smash them down!
I see 'em. I see 'em.
Look out. Jake! Jake!
Here they come again. Jake!
Yeah, yeah.
Fruitcake.
Frank, watch out!
Jake, Jake!
Boy.
Jake.
Dear.
Jake!
Break off!
Buzz them again, Omar, and this
time, everybody open fire.
What happened?
You happened, you imbecile!
How bad is it, Omar?
He got the controls.
They're locked.
When the fuel runs out, we're through.
Shall we bail out, sir?
We have no choice.
Bail out?
Where are you going? I
haven't got a parachute.
Then you have a problem.
I haven't got a parachute, either.
Then you have the same problem.
Wait! No, wait!
Wait a minute!
I... I don't
want to die!
Swell.
Frank!
Yes, Mr. President.
Absolutely, Mr. President.
We're just waiting for them to land and
we'll pass that on, Mr. President.
Yes, sir.
What'd he say?
Your friend, Jake is to be treated as
the representative of a friendly power,
With generous borrowing credit.
In exchange for bases, of course.
Look, sir, chutes.
They bailed out.
Holy mackerel! Who's flying the chopper?
Frank!
Easy, Liz. Don't panic.
What are you gonna do, Frank?
I don't know, but I have to do something.
Hand me Lucybelle!
Careful, Frank!
I got her.
Just hold on, honey, and we'll get Liz.
Get us up closer to the copter.
Right.
Liz, when we get close enough, grab my hand.
Frank, you're too far away!
Closer, Jake. Closer!
Okay.
All right.
Grab my hand,
liz. Grab it!
Grab it! Liz, careful.
Okay.
Now grab my hand.
Grab my hand.
All right.
I'm... Yeah.
Good. That's good. That's good.
Now grab my hand and step off.
Step off?
Liz!
Frank, I don't think this is gonna work.
All right.
We'll try it again.
Never mind. We'll try
something else.
All right, put your feet on my shoulders.
What?
Put your feet right there, on my shoulders.
No!
Liz, do it!
Okay. Okay.
You see? Everything's gonna be
okay, Lucybelle. Just relax.
Jake!
Jake, what are you doing?
You know, when I saw you up
in that chopper, I just...
Well, honey, looks like
you're stuck with me.
Don't just hang there.
Get me out of this.
Don't worry, Mr. Olympus.
I'll get you loose.
What are you doing with that?
Well, fortunately, I never go
anywhere without my swiss army knife.
Idiot!
All rise.
Hear ye, hear ye, hear ye.
The United States District Court,
The Honorable Judge Alvin Horsham presiding.
Please be seated.
You have made application for citizenship.
Of the United States of America.
It is a signal honor,
Which implies not only rights,
But duties and obligations,
Bearing arms, serving on juries, voting.
Who is sponsoring this applicant?
I am, your honor.
Does the cat have a name?
Yes, sir. Zunar-J-5...
Jake, your honor.
Please stand, Jake.
Repeat after me.
I, Jake...
Pledge allegiance to the flag.
Of the United States of America.
Of the United States of America...
And to the republic for which it stands...
One nation, under god, indivisible...
With liberty and justice for all.