Close your eyes
and begin to relax
Take a deep breath
and let it out slowly
Concentrate on your breathing
With each breath
you become more relaxed
Imagine a brilliant white light
above you
Focusing on this light
as it flows through your body
Allow yourself to drift off
as you fall
Deeper and deeper
Into a more relaxed state of mind
Now as I count back from ten to one
You will feel more peacefull and calm
10, 9, 8...
You will enter a safe place
were nothing can harm you
If at any time
you need to come back
All you need to do
is open your eyes
Safe in the light that surrounds me
Free of the fear and the pain
My subconscious mind
Starts spinning through time
To rejoin the past once again
Nothing seems real
I´m starting to feel
Lost in the haze of a dream
And as I draw near
The scene becomes clear
Like watching my life on a screen
Hello Victoria...
...so glad to see you
My friend
Susconscius Strange Sensation
Unconscious relaxation
What a pleasant nightmare
And I can`t wait to get there again
Every time I close my eyes
There`s another vivid surprise
Another whole life`s waiting
Chapters unfinished, fading
Closer now
- Slowly coming into view
I`ve arrived
- Vlindling sunshing beaming through
There`s a house I`m drawn into
Familiar settings, nothing new
There`s a pathway leading there
With a haunting chill in the air
There`s room at the top of the stairs
Every night I`m drawn up there
There`s a girl in the mirror
Her face is getting clearer
Young child won`t you tell me...
...why I`m here?
In her eyes
-I sense a story never told
Behind the disguise
- There`s something tearing at her soul...
Tonight I`ve been searching for it
A feeling that`s deep inside me
Tonight I`ve been searching for
The one that nobody knows
Trying to break free
I just can`t help myself
I`m feeling like I`m going...
...out of my head
Tears my heart into two
I`m not the one...
...the sleeper thought he knew
Back on my feet again
Eyes open to real world
Metropolis surrounds me
The mirror`s shattered the girl
Why is this other life
Haunting me everyday
I`d break through the other side
If only I`d find the way
Something`s awfully familiar
The feeling`s so hard to shake
Could I have lived in that other world
It`s a link that I`m destined to make
I`m still searching but I don`t know what for
The missing key to unlock my mind`s door
Today I am searching for it
A feeling that won`t go away
Today I am searching for
The one that I only know
Trying to break free
I just can`t help myself
I`m feeling like I`m going...
...out of my head
Tears my soul into two
I`m not the one...
I thought I always knew
I just can`t help myself
I`m feeling like I`m going...
...out of my head
Uncanny, strange Deja Vu
But I don`t mind
- I hope to find
The truth
All your eyes have ever seen
All you`ve ever heard
Is etched upon my memory
Is spoken through my words
All that I take with me
Is all you`ve left behind
We`re sharing one eternity
Living in two minds
Linked by an endless thread
Impossible to break
Alone at night
I feel so strange
I need to find
All the answers to my dreams
When I sleep at night
I hear the cries
What does this mean?
I shut the door
and traveled to another home
I met an older man,
he seemed to be alone
I felt that I could trust him
He talked to me that night
"Lad did you know
a girl was murdered here?"
"This fatal tragedy
was talked about for years"
Victoria`s gone forever
Only memories remain
She passed away
She was so young
Without love
Without truth
There can be no turning back
Without faith
Without hope
There can be no peace of mind
As the night went on
I started to find my way
I learned about a tragedy
A mystery still today
I tried to get more answers
But he said,
"You`re on your own"
Then he turned away and left me
As I stand there all alone
He said,
"You`ll know the truth...
...As your future days unfold"
Without love
Without truth
There can be no turning back
Without faith
Without hope
There can be no peace of mind
Now its time to see how you died
Remember the death is not the end...
...but only a transition
[Headline:] "Murder,
young girl killed
Desperate shooting
at Echoe`s hill
Dreadful ending,
killer died
Evidently suicide"
A witness heard a horrifying sound
He ran to find a woman dead and
Lying on the ground
Standing by her was a man
Nervous, shaking,
gun in hand
Witness says he tried to help
But he`d turned the weapon on himself
His body fell across that poor young girl
After shouting out in vain
The witness ran to call for assistance
A sad close to a broken love affair
Our deeds have traveled far
What we have been is what we are
She wanted love forever
But he had another plan
He fell into an evil way
She had to let him down
She said
"I can`t love a wayward man"
She may have found a reason to forgive
If he had only tried to change
Was their fatal meeting prearranged?
Had a violent struggle taken place?
There was every sign that lead there
Witness found a switchblade on the ground
Was the victim unaware?
They continued to investigate
They found a note in the killer`s pocket
It could have been a suicide letter
Maybe he had lost her love
I feel there`s only one thing left to do
I`d sooner take my life away
than live without losing you
Our deeds have traveled far
What we have been is what we are
All that we learn this time
(What we have been is what we are)
Is carried beyond this life
All that we learn this time
(What we have been is what we are)
Is carried beyond this life
Our deeds have traveled far
What we have been is what we are
All that we learn this time
(What we have been is what we are)
Is carried beyond this life
All that we learn this time
(What we have been is what we are)
Is carried beyond this life
She never really had a chance
On that fateful moonlit night
Sacrificed without a fight
A victim of her circumstance
Now that I've become aware
And I've exposed this tragedy
A sadness grows inside of me
It all seems so unfair
I'm learning all about my life
By looking through her eyes
Just beyond the churchyard gates
Where the grass is overgrown
I saw the writing on her stone
I felt like I would suffocate
In loving memory of our child
So innocent, eyes open wide
I felt so empty as I cried
Like part of me had died
I'm learning all about my life
By looking through her eyes
And as her image
Wandered through my head
I wept just like a baby
As I lay awake in bed
And I know what it's like
To lose someone you love
And this felt just the same
She wasn't given any choice
Desperation stole her voice
I've been given so much more in life
I've got a son, I've got a wife
I had to suffer one last time
To grieve for her and say goodbye
Relive the anguish of my past
To find out who I was at last
The door has opened wide
I'm turning with the tide
Looking through her eyes
Shine
-lake of fire
Lines
take me higher
My mind
drips desire
Confined
and overtired
Living this charade
Is getting me nowhere
I can`t shake this charade
The city`s cold blood
calls me home
Home
it`s what I long
for back home
where I belong
The city
it calls me
Decadent scenes from my memory
Sorrow
eternity
My demons are coming to drown me
Help
I`m falling
I`m crawling
I can`t keep away from its clutch
Can`t have it
this habit
It`s calling me back to my home
I remember the first time she came to me
Poured her soul out all night and cried
I remember I was told there`s a new love that`s born
For each one that has died
I never thought that I
Could carry on with this life
But I can`t resist myself
No matter how hard I try
Living their other life
Is getting them nowhere
I`ll make her my wife
Her sweet temptations
calls me home
Home
it`s what I long for
my home
where she belongs
Her ecstasy
means so much to me
Even decieving my own blood
Victoria watches and thoughtfully smiles
She`s taking me to my home
Help - he`s my brother
but I love her
I can`t keep away from her touch
Deception
Dishonor
It`s calling me back to my home
Her story
it holds the key
Unlocking dreams from my memory
Solving
this mystery
Is everything that is a part of me
Help
Regression
Obsession
I can`t keep away from her touch
Leave no doubt
to find out
It`s calling me back to my home
It doesn`t make any sense
This tragic ending
In spite of the evidence
There`s something still missing
Heard some of the rumours told
A taste of one`s wealth
Did Victoria wound his soul?
Did she bid him farewell?
One last time
We`ll lay down today
Until we fade away
One last time
We`ll lay down today
We slowly fade away
Away...
Here I am inside his home
It holds the many clues
To my suspicions
And as I`m standing here right now
I`m finally shown
what I have always known
Coincidence I can`t belive
As my childhood dreams alowly come true
Are these her memories
Awakened through my eyes
This house has brought back to life
An open door
I walk on through
Into his bedroom
Feeling as cold as outside
The walls disappear
To some woman who`s screaming
A man pleads forgiveness
His words I cannot...
...hear
Where did we come from?
Why are we here?
Where do we go when we die?
What lies beyond
And what lay before?
Is anything certain in life?
They say
"Life is too short"
"The here and the now"
And "You`re only given one shot"
But could there be more
Have I lived before
Or could tis be all that we`ve got?
If I die tomorrow
I`d be allright
Because I believe
That after we`re gone
The spirit carries on
I used to be frightened of dying
I used to think death was the end
But that was before
I`m not scared anymore
I know that my soul will transcend
I may never find all the answers
I may never understand why
I may never prove
What I know to be true
But I know that I still have to try
If I die tomorrow
I`d be allright
Because I believe
That after we`re gone
The spirit carries on
"Move on, be brave
Don`t weep at my grave
Because I`m no longer here
But please never let
You memories of me disappear"
Safe in the light that surrounds me
Free of the fear and the pain
My questioning mind
Has help me to find
The meaning in my life again
Victoria`s real
I finally feel
At peace with the girl in my dreams
And now that I`m here
It`s perfectly clear
I found out what all of this means
If I die tomorrow
I`d be allright
Because I believe
That after we`re gone
The spirit carries on
You are once again surrounded
by a brilliant white light
Allow the light to lead you away
from the past
and into this lifetime
As the light dissipates
you will slowly fade back
into conciousness
remembering all you have learned
When I tell you to open your eyes
you will return to the present
feeling peaceful and refreshed
Open your eyes, Nicholas
Friday evening
The blood still on my hands
To think that she would leave me now
For that ungreateful man
Sole survivor
No witness to the crime
I must act fast to cover up
I think that there`s still time
He`d seem hopeless and lost with this note
They`ll buy into the words that I wrote
" This feeling
inside me
Finally found my love,
I`ve finally broke free
No longer
torn in two
I`d take my own life
before loosing you"
Feeling good this friday afternoon
I ran into Julian
Said we`d get together soon
He`s always had my heart
He needs to know
I`ll break free of the Miracle
It`s time for him to go
This feeling
inside me
Finally found my love,
I`ve finally broke free
No longer
torn in two
He`d kill his brother if he only knew
Their love renewed
They`d rendezvous
In a pathway out of view
They thought no one knew
They came a shot out
of the night
One last time
We`ll lay down today
Until we fade away
One last time
We`ll lay down today
We fade away
As their bodies lie still
And the ending draws near
Spirits rise through the air
All their fears disappear, it all becomes clear
A blinding light comes into view
An old soul exchanged for a new
A familiar voice
comes shining through
This feeling
inside me
Finally found my love
I`m finally free
No longer
torn in two
I learned about my life
by living through you
This feeling
inside me
Finally found my love
I`ve finally free
No longer
torn in two
Living my own life
by learning from you
We`ll meet again my friend...
someday soon...
" news in London, France, Russia and Italy
have deleted their lead story,
all anticipating the outcome of the man
considered to be a member of American nobility.
And as you can imagine, as the skies
have grown darker here over Washington,
the mood has grown darker as well and people
here are beginning to resign themselves...
to the possibility that they are witnessing
yet another tragedy in a long string of misfortunes.
Reaction from everywhere, from Washington
and certainly from around the world has guess..."
"Open your eyes, Nicholas"
Subtitles by subRAF
Buenos Aires - Argentina © 2002
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
uploaded by f1dz for subscene.com