The day shift.
The workers' city, far below the
surface of the earth.
And high above, a pleasure garden for the sons of the masters of Metropolis.
"Freder!"
"Look, these are your brothers."
"Who was that?"
"Just the daughter of a worker."
The great machines, far underground,
yet high above the workers' city.
"Moloch!"
"Such acidents are unavoidable."
"Why was my son allowed to go
into the machine-rooms?"
"Why did you go down there?"
"I wanted to see what my brothers
looked like."
"It was their hands that built this
city of ours, father."
"In their proper place---
the depts."
"What will you do if they turn against
you some day?"
"The foreman from the central dynamo
room is here with an urgent message."
"More of those plans, sir."
"They were found on two of the men
who were killed today."
"Joseph, why was it not you who
brought me these plans?"
"You are dismissed. Go to the G-Bank
for the balance of your wages."
"Father, don't you realize what it
means to be dismissed by you?"
"Joseph, I need your help."
"I have far to go today
-- alone, into the depths
-- to my borthers."
"The machine! Someone must stay
with the machine."
"I will stay at the machine."
In the middle of the city was an old house.
Here lived, Rotwang, the inventor.
"At last, my work is ready."
"I have created a machine in the image
of man, that never tires or makes a mistake."
"Now we have no further use for
living workers."
"Isn't it worth the loss of a hand to have
created the workers of the future -- -- the machine men?"
"Give me another 24 hours, and I'll bring
you a machine which no one will be able to tell from a hum
"As always, when my experts fail
I come to you for advice."
"For months now, we have been finding these
plans in the workers' clothing. What do they mean?"
"At two -- at the end of this shift.
She has called another meeting."
"These are the plans of the ancient catacombs
-- far below the lowest levels of the workers' city."
"What is down there that interests the workers?"
"Today I will tell you the story of the Tower of Babel."
"Let us build a tower whose summit will touch the skies--"
"-- and on it we will inscribe: 'Great is
the world and its Creator. And great is Man.'"
"Those who had conceived the idea of this tower
could not build it themselves, so they hired thousan
"Between the brain that plans and the
hands that build there must be a mediator."
"It is the heart that must bring about
an understanding between them."
"But where is our mediator, Maria?"
"Be patient, he will surely come."
"We will wait, but not for long."
"Rotwang, make your Robot in the
likeness of that girl."
"Hide the girl in your house, I will send the
Robot down to the workers, to sow discord among them a
"Leave me here, John Fredersen."
"Until tomorrow--- in the cathedral."
The Seven Deadly Sins.
Maria was a prisoner in Rotwang's house.
"Come, I am going to make the
Robot look like you."
"Maria!"
"Where is Maria?"
"She is with your father."
"The copy is perfect. Now go down to the workers
and undo Maria's teaching; stir them up to criminal
"Maria!"
"Now we shall see whether people believe
the Robot is a creature of flesh and blood."
"John Fredersen is looking for an excuse
to use violence against the workers."
"Maria, you always pleaded for peace -- but now the
Robot in your likeness has been commanded to inc
The workers accept the Robot as Maria.
"I have preached patience --"
"But your mediator has not come --
and will never come."
"Maria is inciting the workers to revolt."
"She has told them to destroy everything."
"I cannot believe it."
"You have waited patiently too long.
The time has come to act!"
"Why should you sweat yourself to death
to benefit the Lord of Metropolis?"
"Who keeps the machines going?"
"Who are the slaves of the machines?"
"Let the machines stop!"
"Destroy the machines!"
"You are not Maria!"
"Maria pleads for peace, not for
violence. This is not Maria!"
"John Fredersen's son!"
"Kill him!"
Not one man or woman remained behind.
"To the central power house!"
"The workers are destroying the machines."
"What shall I do?"
"If they destroy the power house,
the workers' city will be flooded."
"Open the doors."
"Have you gone mad? You are
flooding your own homes."
At last Maria managed to escape.
"Yes, you are the real Maria."
"To the airshaft -- quickly !
The reservoirs have burst."
"Where is my son?"
"Tomorrow thousands will ask in
anguish -- where is my son?"
"Save the children -- I will tell the
workers that they are safe."
"Where are your children?"
"The entire workers' city is under water."
"Who told you to destroy the machines,
you fools -- and thus to destroy yourselves?"
"The witch! She's to blame for all
this. Find her! Kill her."
"Let's watch the world going to the devil!"
"Maria!"
"If the mob sees you they will kill
me for having tricked them."
"The witch, the witch!"
"Where are our children?"
"John Fredersen's son has saved your children."
"Save my son!"
"Thank heaven!"
"There can be no understanding between
the hands and the brain unless the heart acts as mediator."
THE END