Boys Before Flowers
Episode 19
Gu Jun Pyo!
You again...!
We're so right for each other!!
I had a feeling that if I suddenly
came home I would see you.
Did you fry and eat your cell phone?
Call and ask for permission before
going to someone else's house.
Did you not learn that?
Ugh, I'm so tired.
Thinking back... I don't
think I ever learned that.
Just like you.
Hey, Monkey get up!
Why are you laying on someone else's bed?
Get up fast!
Get up!
I said get up!
Do you wanna bet with me?
What bet!?
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Win!
Yay! I won!
I'm not going to go easy on you.
Win! Fighting!
I won again! Yeah!
I'm not playing anymore.
The buttons don't work! What is this...
Hey!
Stop drinking, you won't
get better if you continue.
Get better?
Get better and do what.
What if I don't do pottery for awhile?
I can just toy with girls anyway.
Don't you think?
Yi Jung you've coped well all this time,
why are you doing this?
Sir, your Mother again...
What happened?
She's at the hospital and
she wants to see you.
Tell her I'm busy.
Where are you going?
If you don't want to see
me go crazy, let me go.
Ga Eul.
You said you wanted a date with me right?
Am I still eligible for that date?
If you're going to leave after this
then you shouldn't have asked for a date.
You still haven't seen the highlight yet.
You said your name was Ga Eul right?
Eat plenty because the
Foie Gras* here is the best.
*French food product made of
duck/goose liver.
Thank you.
It seems like you fancy Ga Eul.
She's cute and innocent
what isn't there to like.
I guess I am similar to you father.
Even though Mother is at the hospital,
you have your son dating,
and you yourself offering
foie gras to cute girls
even when mother is dying in the hospital.
I guess we can't fool our blood.
Let's keep our household
stories for later...
What should we talk about then?
I think this young lady is of your taste,
should I lend her to you?
Yi Jung sunbae!
Why so serious?
Her age is similar to that girl from before.
How about it Ga Eul?
My dad is alright isn't he?
Please excuse me.
Today you crossed the line son.
Why did we come here?
The loser shall be quiet or
did you forget our bet?
Today, you promised to be my servant.
What! When?!
Wow...!
What I hate most is someone that says
"Two things with one mouth".
A man must always keep his word.
Do you not know that saying?
A man must always keep his word?
So hush and follow me.
A man must always keep his word...?
A man must always keep his word!
Hey. Why are you buying that many?
Hey, hey, hey!
HEY!
- I don't want to eat it.
- Just one bite!
It's good right?
Yeahhh sure.
It's good?
Wow, you're so pretty
you look great with him.
Thank you!
Did you hear that? I'm pretty!
You believe that?
Thank you!
He's just trying to sell these.
Oh, Sir it's not that.
No, he's not!
Thank you...
HEY!
Hey Monkey here..
Jan Di said she moved and she's
with her brother so yeah.
Come on let's go!
Here you go.
I just received today as well...
Today I also received.
Do you want to come in and have some tea?
I can give you some green tea.
Ahh...
Grandfather...
The Sir left already of course.
Just wait, I'll get the tea ready.
Ji Hoo is this fun?
Yes, Grandfather!
Let's go fishing now!
I will fish a big big shark!
Fishing? Sure Ji Hoo.
When should we go?
Right now!
Sure, let's go!
Wahhh the smell is incredible.
Me first!
What!
If I let you be you're going to pour
all this down in the blink of an eye!
Pour all this down?
Dongseng, this woman here is a food god.
Block her now.
What, you can't be like that now!
Did you forget who bought this!?
Just eat that, just eat that!
Hey, hey!
HEY!
Why aren't you eating?
Well because I always eat ramen.
Aside from ramen then,
what would you want to eat?
Pizza!
Pizza for days until I grow bored of it
and I won't have any more cravings!
What kind of a guy has a wish like that?
Ah, don't eat this, eat something good.
Ughh, I'm so full.
Why isn't Jan Di coming?
Hey Dongseng call her!
She doesn't have a cell phone.
WHAT! She doesn't have a cellphone!?
Well she gave it to my parents so
they can call during emergencies.
Ugh... you guys..
Ohhh so that's how it is.
Let's go!
Where now?
What!
Come here quick.
Hello.
Can you give me this one?
This product. Okay, please wait.
It's this one. It's this one!
- Sir show me this.
- Oh, we came for this too.
Hey!
Looks like you're working hard lately!
It's cool.
So the cellphone...
Ji Hoo!
Please excuse me.
Ji Hoo, I am sorry.
What?
It should be me who is sorry.
I killed your son...
and your son's wife.
And only the child survived.
It is not your fault.
Ji Hoo!
15 years.
15 years ago, you should've said that.
Did you know that!?
How long the child waited
for his grandfather?
Ji Hoo..
You didn't know did you?
How bad the child wanted
to cry on his grandfather.
Child...
Do not call me that again.
Ji Hoo!
Grandfather!
Grandfather, grandfather!
I am okay...
Go. Go and find him.
Find him.
Ji Hoo Sunbae!
Grandfather!
GRANDFATHER!
I was scared that child might cry.
Like his father...
Like his mother...
I was afraid that child
might cry because of me.
So I ran away.
What kind of woman are you
to spend the night out!
Oh.. that...
Why is he mad!?
Did I do something bad?
Hey, that's my lifestyle ok!
Do you not know what privacy is?
Hey Gum Jan Di if you're going
to use it, use it properly.
It is not privacy. It is p-r-i-d-e.
Do you not know pride?
What...!?
Hey, you! Where do you think you're
going when I'm still speaking?!
Privacy or Pride...
I'm GOING TO LOOK IT UP! WHY?
HEY! Are you not going to tell me
what you've been doing!?
NO!!
Not much has happened?
Yes.
And Jun Pyo?
He went to school.
And with Jae Kyung?
While you were gone,
she came to visit a lot,
and spent quite some time
with the Young Master.
That's fortunate.
But...
Don't you have anything else to tell me?
Pardon?
Chief Jung.
I understand that you're busy
taking care of things instead of me,
and although you understand that
Jun Pyo isn't an easy kid to manage...
Don't you know that things are
still unknowingly happening?
I'm sorry.
I was being careless.
Look into it immediately.
Yes, Ma'am.
You're really trying hard.
Why don't you return to
your neighborhood now?
I told you that this is all
part of the getting use
to the wild independent living experience.
Hey.
You ride your car in the morning and night,
go home to change your clothes, order meals.
Which part of this is independent and
which part is the wild living experience?
I sleep, I sleep!
With the cockroaches, and in a
booger-sized room infested with fleas.
These long legs are suffering,
what more do you expect?
Who told you to do that?
No one was expecting you to do that.
Stop making yourself suffer.
Are you really not going to tell me?
What?
I'm not curious about...
what... pride. No, privacy,
But it's because I'm like your
older brother or guardian...
HEY!
A human is talking to you.
Hey!
- Are you Geum Kang San?
- I am Geum Kang San.
Come this way.
[Kang San, Be Strong! ^^]
[Eat it all.]
Go ahead and eat to your heart's content.
Jun Pyo hyungnim?
Is it good?
Eat a lot.
Kang San! Me too! Me too!
Get in line!
Welcome.
Ji Hoo sunbae.
What are you doing here?
I went to Jan Di's.
Oh, you don't know yet.
Jan Di moved.
Moved?
You guys eat a lot too.
It's worrying me that it's quiet.
Hey! Why aren't you turning on?
Hey!
Chief Jung, why isn't this turning on?
What do you mean what?
I'm talking about the flame!
The flame's not turning on.
Hurry up and do something about it.
He came really fast.
Chief Jung...
Let me go. I said let me go.
Let go.
Kang San.
Hey.
Who is it?
Hi.
Hey, yo.
Sunbae!
What happened?
I heard you moved into a new house,
so we came for the housewarming party.
On a housewarming party the owner
is supposed to invite you for you to come.
But are you two really living in here?
It's a lot better than it looks.
It's quite and safe.
And...
The rent fee is really cheap.
Almost free.
But Jun Pyo...
Excuse me.
Who is it?
Geum Jan Di is popular.
Wait a second.
Who is it? Who is it?
How did you...
I almost want to disbelieve my eyes,
seeing you guys here in
the middle of the night.
Jun Pyo's not here.
I know where and what my son is doing.
What's your reason for coming here?
Shouldn't even a commoner know
that when an adult comes to visit,
the first thing you should do is
greet them and then invite them in.
This is why good upbringing is important.
Then, would you like to come inside?
No, thanks.
I'd rather stand outside than to lay
a foot inside a house like that.
I knew you weren't an ordinary girl,
but you sure do have a
talent in seducing men.
President Jang.
It's not like that.
If you feel victimized by
my misunderstanding,
why don't you try to justify yourself?
I'm not doing anything wrong
to be hearing things like these.
Over there.
I'm still suspicious even after I found
out who did what over there.
After you called a man with a
fiancée to live next to you,
What?
You're not doing anything wrong?
I really had nothing to do with that.
That was all done on Gu Jun Pyo's accord.
That's usually the excuse
that girls like you use.
The girl was doing nothing and the guy did
all of it, what's there to do about it?
So, I came to ask a favor.
If my Jun Pyo comes to see you,
please stop meeting him.
Like you said,
You and Jun Pyo...
are people who have nothing
to do with each other anymore.
I can trust you right?
Your great pride, I'll try to trust it.
This is why...
I'm against you meeting with my Jun Pyo.
For your family's sake,
please get things sorted out.
Let's go Chief Jung.
Yes, Ma'am.
Geum Jan Di.
There's no reason to take
Jun Pyo's mom's word to heart.
She's always saying things like that.
She's the same way with us.
But what's this about Jun Pyo?
What is all this?
Geum Jan Di.
This is our housewarming present.
What?
Ready.
The President has ordered that you should
grounded for the time being, Young Master.
It might be good to stay quiet for awhile.
How did that Witch find out?
I was being too careless.
I'm sorry.
Miss Jae Kyung has come.
- Why did she come?
- What do you mean why?
Is it weird for a fiancée
to come to her fiancé's house?
I'm not in the mood to play with you.
Just go home.
Oh, really?
I was going to ask if you wanted
to go Jan Di’s house with me.
But I guess not.
Then I'll just go alone.
What?
Where are you going?
Jan Di’s house.
Remember we ate ramen
together there last time.
I have to give this to her.
Well...
If you insist, I can go with you.
- Really?
- But...
You have tell the Witch about it.
Don't worry about that.
I already told her we're going on a date.
Let's go.
Ah, it's so annoying.
Come on, let's go.
- I really don't want to go.
- Come on, let's go.
Kang San.
Do you want more sausages?
He's sleeping.
San, if you sleep like that,
you're not going to grow tall.
San, hey!
This feels great.
It's been a while since I felt like this.
Doesn't it feel like we're at a MT?
Since it's a little boring,
You don't mean... we start
kissing or anything, right?
Although I'm all for that.
Do you want to play a game?
Game?
When you're staying up at a MT,
there's something that can't be left out.
What's that?
The truth or dare game.
Truth or dare game?
Me too! Me too!
In order, you ask a question to the person
you want to know something about.
How do you know if it's a truth or a lie?
You can't lie.
Instead, you can have a "not talk".
A "not talk".
If you don't want to
answer to that question,
As a punishment to that person
who asked the question...
You have to kiss them.
Why are you even doing that?
What? It's fun.
All right, since we're doing it,
how about French-kissing?
No way!
Then, a peck on the forehead?
That's pretty decent, right?
Unless...
Do you want to hit?
That sounds good too.
Let's just kiss.
Is it me?
Yoon Ji Hoo.
Besides Seo Hyun,
can you love another person?
I suddenly want to do it now.
Do what?
Hey! That's not a hard question.
Don't come.
Go away.
Is it my turn?
Yeah.
Jun Pyo.
If the person you love is having
a hard time because of you,
would you let her go?
No.
I won't let her go.
I can't let her go.
I'm going to hold on to her tightly...
and make her happy.
It's my turn now.
Geum Jan Di.
The promise we made on the street...
Is it still intact?
Even if something happens...
You can't run away from me.
I promise.
I promise that your mother won't
be the reason for it at least.
No.
The person who made that promise...
and the person who heard that promise..
don't exist anymore.
It's me now?
Woo Bin sunbae.
Me?
If F4 were girls,
who would you marry?
What?
I'm really curious.
Who would it be?
No way. I wouldn't have any.
I wouldn't allow it.
Obnoxious, strange, and
a cold-blooded Casanova.
You want me to live the rest
of my life with these people?
I'd rather just go live at a monastery.
What did you say?
Obnoxious?
Strange?
A cold-blooded Casanova?
I mean...
I can't help it.
How else would I describe you guys?
Go away!
Everything's good, right?
I'll be going.
Wait.
What now?
I want to do it too.
Do what?
The truth or dare game.
I just want to ask you one thing,
will you answer me?
The game's been over for awhile now.
Love and friendship.
Between the two, which one would you choose?
Both.
There's no such thing as
giving up in my dictionary.
Go and sleep.
Stupid.
If you keep choosing things that I like,
What do you expect me to do?
Noona.
The ground is shaking.
I'm shaking too.
Is it an earthquake?
You think this is Japan?
Earthquake?
Good, you were home.
Hurry and start packing.
We're demolishing this building.
Demolishing?
All of the sudden?
We don't know all the details
and we're only following orders.
So hurry and pack up.
We were ordered to demolish
this place by today.
By who?
How should we know?
Just hurry and pack.
After you called a man with a
fiancée to live next to you,
What?
You're not doing anything wrong?
Noona.
What are we going to do now?
It'll be okay. Don't worry.
This lady seems like your type.
Would you like to borrow her?
Yi Jung sunbae.
Good job today.
- Good job.
- See you again.
You're working hard.
I want to make something worthy quickly.
Then, I'll be going first.
- See you.
- Yes.
What's that?
It's so unique.
I made it when I was little.
Wow, it even has letters on it.
It's pretty.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Teacher, can you let me borrow
this for a couple of days?
I wanted to make something like this before.
Since that's not too hard,
do you want to try making it?
But it's really special to me,
so you return it to me safely.
Yes.
It's pretty.
- Then I'll see you tomorrow.
- Yes, see you.
There's too much strength in your wrists.
Yi Jung sunbae.
Noona, you're jealous huh?
From tomorrow on, I'll be eating
a lot of fresh sushi, squids and clams.
That's so unfair.
You get to eat lots of good food
and sleep with Mom and Dad.
You're so lucky.
Should I just go too?
No way.
You said you were going to graduate
Shinhwa High and go to Shinhwa Med School.
What are you thinking trying to follow?
Are you sure you'll be all right?
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of Mom and Dad.
I'll be going.
Noona.
Don't just drink milk in
the mornings and eat rice.
What?
Rice!
Jun Pyo hyung still seems to like you!
I think he still likes you!
I'm always on your side.
Be strong! Fighting!
Geum Jan Di!
I'm sorry Noona.
I can't carry you.
Geum Jan Di!
I'm sorry. When I say Geum Jan Di,
I get all weak-hearted.
I'm going to go crazy.
Sorry, but we have to go quickly.
Do what?
I was going to eat it...
Can't I just eat it?