Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Next, we have news about Shinhwa Group.
Shinhwa Group, which went into crisis
when Gu Bon Hyung passed away,
has announced the plan
of an international resort
based in Macau and Inchon.
Stating it to be a turning point
that will change the crisis into bliss,
Implementing a worldwide ambitious plan.
What makes it special is the person
in charge of the plan.
The future successor
of Shinhwa Group, Gu Jun Pyo,
and this has raised a
lot of unusual attention.
- Episode 13
There is still no news?
It's already half a year.
No matter how busy or tired,
he should have called.
Also you haven't been contacting F4?
Seems like everyone is a bit careful.
Seems like everyone is busy.
They are all busy after attending
university, right?
Yah, it's obvious without even thinking.
They’ve probably forgotten
all about so-called friends
and gone girl-crazy
Even their souls have left them.
Hey, what are you doing?
Really old-fashioned.
I also went to the Blue House!
Why are you like this?
Not staying in the kitchen
and all you know is sleep.
Your restaurant business is
really that good? Tsk, tsk, tsk
That grandfather is here again.
Grandfather,
what are you having today?
ShinSeolRo. (Korean royal cuisine)
Shin, shin, SeolRo?
What is that Grandfather?
Isn't he a bit much?
Grandfather,
why are you acting like
this in a porridge shop?
The things he ordered, were either
noodles with soybean paste
or spicy soup with sheatfish.
half dried saury, 3 combination...
And what else?
(Sam Hab: 3 combination of Fermented Skate,
Kimchi, Pork - Eat 3 together with chopstick)
The soup... that soup...
What was it?
Ahh, soup...
Just like your boss,
so young and ignorant.
It's Tang Pyung Chae, you idiots!
Ah, Tang Pyung Chae.
(various steamed and seasoned vegetable)
Stop grumbling and talking back to an elder.
Quickly get something to eat here.
Grandfather...
Is it that delicious?
What delicious?!
I'm afraid that I will go
to hell if I waste food,
so I ate it half-heartedly.
Can't you see?
Being half-hearted twice, then you
should have eaten the bowl as well.
Tell this to your Cook,
it is a waste of the bowl.
It is not the Cook, but Master.
What is that that he Mastered?
Grandfather!
It is raining outside and you did
not bring your umbrella right?
Please remember to return
it to us next time.
No matter how I look...
Face of a lotus.
Lotus?
Do you know why the lotus
flower blooms in the mud?
Huh?
This is your homework till
we meet again next time.
Bye.
Jan Di.
You better remember.
What?
He is not one that will
speak without reason.
Understand?
What?! Really.
Master, do talk about it.
We are not even playing riddles here.
[Blue House Head Chef Bom Seong Chan]
Blue House is the Presidential
Residence (like the White House)
Noona.
Do you think it resembles Jun Pyo Hyung?
Look!
Curly hair.
Pouting lips.
What resemblance?
Since when is that kid so cute, and gentle?
The cat will get angry hearing that.
Yes, yes, don't even look like it.
For Mr. Jun Pyo, he looks
more like a tiger. Right?
Noona.
Is your shoulder in pain again?
No, it's ok.
My shoulder hurts too.
Curling my legs together
and doing this thing everyday.
It's so painful, at least Jan Di
can relax by swimming.
Wife.
Why don't we help you relax?
- Kang San, let's go!
- OK!
Come.
Kang San, Kang San?
Be gentler Kang San.
Pain, pain! Kang San, be gentler!
Stupid!
You didn't go to the moon.
Why can't you just give a call?
You.
When you come back,
you are going to die.
I will be back soon.
Stay put and wait for me.
I love you, Geum Jan Di.
Hello?
Yes, I am.
Really?
Mom! Dad!
Why are you screaming in
the middle of the night?
Is it Jun Pyo? Did he call?
Mom, Dad is being accepted!
What?!
I just received the call.
Hello?
Yes, I am Geum Il Bong.
Yes, I know. Thank you!
Yes, 8 am tomorrow morning.
Yes. I know, I will be there!
Yes! This is great!
Yes, Section Chief.
Thank you.
Please do not let the people on
that side know, and handle it well.
Shinhwa Group, which went into crisis
when Gu Bon Hyung passed away,
stated it to be a turning point
that will change the crisis into bliss
implementing a worldwide ambitious plan.
It's been tiring.
Are you okay?
Yes... I'm fine... Thank you.
Wife!
Why are you in a daze?
- Husband.
- In the day...
have you seen a ghost?
Pinch me.
I only heard that he looks
like a living statue,
so it is true.
You have not been to the hospital?
I went.
I went already.
He said it was alright.
What are you doing?
So, say it now.
Say what?
The things that you want to tell Jun Pyo.
Someone is going over to Jun Pyo.
Ever since the funeral,
We haven't contact him as well.
But it will definitely reach this time.
Sunbae, this is too sudden.
I... have nothing to say.
Here, let's start.
I don't really know how to do this.
Gu Jun Pyo.
Can you hear me?
While you have been away,
I've thought of you everyday...
But why do I only remember us fighting?
Still, isn’t it strange?
I only remember us fighting and
getting mad all the time,
but when I think about you, I laugh.
Gu Jun Pyo.
you’re okay, right?
When are you going to come
back and fight with me?
Am I that handsome?
That's right, there's not one woman who
doesn't get smitten at this sight.
Who is smitten?
I came because I have something to ask.
About Jun Pyo and Jan Di?
Yes.
Say it.
What?
Is it still the same?
Waiting for the love that
occurs once in a lifetime.
This does not concern you.
Do you think Jun Pyo is
the one love for Jan Di?
Is he really her soulmate?
That?
Ga Eul, you, just pushed your
dream into Jan Di's mind.
What did you say?
If it were me, I’d spend my whole
life looking for my soulmate
although I’m not even sure
stuff like that exists.
Seems like I have really came
to the wrong place.
Then I shall leave first.
Sunbae believes it too right?
Soulmates, may be life's
one and only real love.
Sunbae, you also believe that it exists.
What?
They say a strong denial
is like an affirmation.
I think I understand now.
Sunbae, you do believe they exist.
You’re afraid that they do.
Why is that?
Don’t act like you know me so easily.
Today’s the first time I feel like Sunbae's
a real person.
I’m glad I came after all.
As for Jan Di's problem,
we will talk about it next time.
That's all...
Please eat.
Hey kid!
The food may be sectioned off in the plate
but look at the food's presentation!
Look at this presentation.
Looks appetizing.
Why don't you both try as well?
Really?
- Delicious!
Have you done your homework?
Homework?
Yes.
There is a call.
Ji Hoo sunbae?
Now?
I'll leave first.
Sunbae!
Aigoo, this is really unappetizing.
That?
What kid?
What should I prepare for you next time?
So much rejections is still not enough?
What you are best at.
Do something that is not
worse than your dad.
Yes!
Kid!
It's so sudden. What's up?
Bring you to a place.
Where?
You will know when you reach.
You have such an acute shoulder injury,
why didn't you attend to it earlier?
If you start treatment now,
it will not effect your daily life,
but for swimming...
I know it clearly.
I’m not pretty.
I’m not smart.
I’m not rich.
But...
There was something I liked,
that I could do better than other people.
They say I have to quit.
I cannot swim anymore.
What do I do now?
What can I do in the future?
Start looking for a new one now.
Sunbae does music.
Yi Jun Sunbae does clay modeling.
Gu Jun Pyo and Woo Bin sunbae will
definitely take over the family business.
Everyone is walking towards
their destined path.
But I don't know what I can do.
I will help you.
Let me help you.
Let’s figure it out together.
Sit down.
It is because of me.
That accident.
Huh?
I can remember it vaguely.
While playing in the back seat,
I covered the eyes of my
father who was driving.
Both of them held me so
tightly in their embrace.
Everyone said it was a miracle.
Later Grandfather...
Never came back to this house.
He must have hated the grandson
who killed his own son.
That time...
She held my hand,
allowing me to start afresh.
That person.
This time is probably...
My turn.
What are you doing?
Sunbae, you can only do this much?
Go after her!
If that person cannot be here,
then can't Sunbae
go to be by her?
Didn't you say you love her?
Is waiting Sunbae's love?
Do you have the right to
say you love her like this?
Ga Eul, this is what
Oppa just did. How is it?
That's why.
Ah, this better be delicious.
How's the taste?
That I... Uh...
Can you pay me in advance?
Huh?
Pay in advance.
Jan Di, did your dad
get into trouble again?
No.
I need it for something.
How much do you need?
2 million.
Why do you need 2 million, so much?
I want to buy an air ticket.
But an air ticket?
Are you thinking...?
Jan Di, can't you see this?
To a flower boy, skin is their life.
I had pimples these few days due to stress.
I also really want to give you...
But this has to sell well
before I can give you.
Hmm, this smells so nice.
So if I sell one, you'll give me 500 won.
If I sell 100, then 50,000 won.
If I sell 1000, then 500,000 won.
Let's do it!
Here you go!
Jeul Pan!
What's Jeul Pan?
It means Jeulguhoon (exciting)
Panmae (sales).
- Fighting!
We have a new kind of porridge!
Try some!
How are you going to sell
all of it like this?
You have to eat some porridge,
valued customer!
He has to eat porridge in the morning?
It's cold.
Please come eat!
Customer! One-plus-one!
We have warm porridge for you!
We'll take responsibility for the taste!
Are you really going to take
responsibility, Miss?
Of course...
Come inside and eat some!
The warm porridge is inside!
Thank you very much!
You like this?
You'll probably like it.
Good job.
And Jan Di will do the calculations?
Wow.
I really didn't know I was
going to earn this much!
But I didn't earn this on my own...
Is it really okay for me to have it all?
You can take it.
It was pretty fun for us too.
But... why did you suddenly come and visit?
You have to come somewhere with us.
Swimmer, on your mark.
Get set.
Go!
Now...
Now,
We will start the retirement ceremony
for athlete Geum Jan Di.
First, we will present the
Award for Excellence.
Award for Excellence, Shinhwa High,
Geum Jan Di.
We present this award to the above person,
who has innate nosiness and
the foundation of weeds,
who has attended the brutal aristocratic
Shinhwa Intuition as its only swimmer
and an active participant in the event
of training F4 and Gu Jung Pyo
with the refusal to obey,
expressing unique abilities that highlighted
the athlete's pride and dignity.
On behalf of the F4.
Geum Jan Di.
You know that an end signals
a new beginning, right?
Now go to Macau and give Jun Pyo
what he rightfully deserves.
Thank you.
Jan Di.
Have a safe trip.
I'll return safely!
Macau Airport
19,700 won!
Isn't that too expensive?
How can I ride a taxi for 19,700 won!
This is all Gu Jun Pyo's?!
They did say Shinhwa is inside the resort,
but it's only hitting me now.
But... where is the entrance?
Gu Jun Pyo!
I'm right!
Ask him!
Okay, I'm going! I'm going!
Gu Jun?
It's delicious.
Can I try this?
This is perfect as appetizers
for Dad when he drinks.
How much?
Return the wallet while I'm still nice.
Wallet?
My Wallet!
Robber!
Are you Korean? Thank you!
Stay still.
Hey, you!
You speak any English?
I'm a black belt holder of Taekwondo.
You know.
You know Taekwondo.
Fine.
Let her go while I'm nice.
You're still not letting her go!
Your crime is getting serious by the minute.
You were a simple pickpocket a second ago,
but now you're holding a hostage!
Go! Get away!
You're such a frustrating man.
I gave you a chance.
If you hate me afterwards,
that's just unfair, okay?
When I count to three,
bite his arm with all your strength!
Huh?
Do you not know Korean?
I... I do.
- 1... 2...
- Wait!
What?
Is it 1, 2, 3 and bite or 1, 2 and bite?
You're a weird girl, aren't you!
1, 2, 3…NOW!
Huh?
You want to kill me?
Your wallet.
Thank you.
Let's run for now.
It'll be complicated if we get caught.
I don't know how to thank you.
I know how it feels to meet a
Korean in a foreign country now.
Is this your first time abroad?
It's my first time alone.
Why Macau of all places?
I came to find someone.
Ah! Your boyfriend?
Yeah? I guess.
I'm envious.
It's not really a situation
to be envious of.
Oh, yeah?
Honey, you wanted beef jerky, right?
Follow me.
Honey?
- One sheet for 10 dollars?
- True
We'll buy 10, so give it
to us for 70 dollars.
No, no!
Hey! Then I'm not going to buy.
I'm not going to buy
Okay, okay.
Great, then 70 dollars!
I bargained 30 dollars off for
buying mine and yours, honey.
There's no business without bargaining.
It was nice meeting you.
Be careful when you travel.
Wait! Can I get your name?
Me? Jae Kyung. Ha Jae Kyung.
Hey! My name is Geum Jan Di...
Is this a hotel or a cathedral?
Sorry, are you OK?
O... Okay.
He didn't see me.
Even if he did, he probably
didn't know it was me.
That's right. It's weird for me
to just suddenly show up in Macau.
That's the weird thing.
That's really, most definitely weird.
Are you okay, Young Master?
What?
Just now, Miss Geum Jan Di?
When is JK Group coming?
If that goes wrong, the Witch might kill me,
So keep reminding me.
Cheap!
You have a cheap room?
It's okay. I'll carry it.
No it's okay, I'll carry it.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Stop right there!
If I catch you, you're dead!
Hey! Stop!
Stop right there.
Give me back my bag!
I have a little brother just
like you, so I'll let you go.
So give me my bag.
You idiot
How dare you wave your finger at me?
Do you want to die?
Give it! Give it back!
You play so dirty?
What!
We'll get at least 3,000 for her.
If you just listen to us, we'll
send you to a good place.
GU JUN PYO!
Do you know Il Shim Hwe*?
*Il Shim his mafia family name.
Hwe means an association or group.
Then you're Prince Song?
Yeah!
We're sorry.
Please look past this.
Get the hell away.
What happened?
We knew this was going to happen.
We thought you would be crying like this.
Jun Pyo must really be busy.
Even after I said we're here,
he can't change his schedule.
What's this?
You don't think he's matured
during this time?
His father passed away.
It was unavoidable for him to mature.
It suddenly feels so realistic and lonely.
What does?
The reality that now he's not F4,
but the owner of Shinhwa group.
Jan Di, did you meet Jun Pyo yet?
Huh?
No, I didn't.
He looked like he was busy and hectic.
How could I meet him?
How do you know if he
looked busy and hectic?
Ah, that.
I... I had a feeling.
He has to take care of this amazing place.
If he's not busy, that's just strange.
I'm sure we'll meet him at one point.
So while we wait, do you want
to go relax our bodies?
Okay! Let's go! Let's go!
The rest, Director Kim said
he'll post up the report.
When he posts up the report?
Yes, I will.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Main Translators: veggieleaf, lilshinhwafreak
Spot Translators: saturn, javafiend, javabeans
Timer: xCHELLy
Editor/QC: puela
Final QC: annchong
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
You should take some time to
meet with your F4 friends.
Do I look like I have nothing to do?
Then should I just forget my
schedule and play with them?
He has really changed.
Whatever it is,
I came here to hear it directly from him.
I'll have to take to confront him.
Then you were being sincere?
I was always a guy like this.
I just pretended that I wasn't.
Hey there, ugly lady,
please buy ice cream from me.
Give me your day today.
Ji Hoo, you like that girl.
What?
Ji Hoo, when you look
at that girl, you smile.
Get on.
What?
I do a lot of things for the
first time because of you.
So... thanks.
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get this for FREE @ d-addicts.com