Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
With you, I will leave.
Con te partiro.
Episode 14
Countries I never
Paesi che non ho mai
saw and experienced with you,
veduto e vissuto con te,
Now, yes, I shall experience them.
adesso, si, li vivro.
With you, I will leave
Con te partiro
on ships for seas which, I know
su navi per mari che, io lo so,
no, no, exist no more.
no, no, non esistono piu.
With you, I shall experience them.
Con te io li vivro.
What's that noise?
Wow, that singer should definitely be fired.
How could a tone-deaf person...
That person...!
Is she someone you know?
What?  Surely, she can't be Korean.
That would be an embarrassment to our country.
It's true.  She's Korean.
But she's a really cool person.
How do you know her?
She's my life saver.
What?  But that's us!
Hello, how are you?
Hello. Welcome.
I'm very pleased to finally meet you.
Hello, how are you?
You must be very pleased
to have such a handsome son.
I too was waiting for Jae Kyung.
I'm disappointed to not meet her.
Right now, she's probably
wandering around Macao by herself.
She's used to doing things her own way, so
even we've thrown up our hands in defeat.
I heard that she's an extraordinary girl.
I'm looking forward to meeting her more and more.
Please don't expect anything.
Madam President, everything is ready.
Then, we should go.
Shinhwa's long-term ambition until 2020 is
to build a 2nd Potain Resort town in Incheon, Korea.
The ultimate resort city in Asia with luxurious hotels,
entertainment venues, and all other amenities.
For this project,
we need the cooperation of JK Group, which has
successfully built resorts in Las Vegas, Macao and Dubai.
If we combine Shinhwa's power as Korea's premier conglomerate with JK Group's on-site knowledge and skills,
we can achieve this goal that much faster.
It will signal a new era for Korea.
Ah, I'm hungry.
Let's go eat.
OK.  Jan Di, just wait.
Because there's a killer restaurant here.
Let's go.
Welcome.
What's wrong?  There's no table?
Don't worry, buddy.
As soon as they hear Jun Pyo's name,
it will immediately be "OK".
Let's go someplace else.
Why?  You feel like you're in Venice,
so you're craving Italian food?
Ah, that's true.  There's a
killer Italian chef here too.
Come on, guys.
But there's plenty of...
[Connection in progress]
[Photo has arrived.
Attempt connection?]
We should make a toast.
To Shinhwa Group and JK Group,
cooperating as one.
- To cooperation!
- To cooperation.
Are you OK?
About what?
Coming here.
You don't regret it?
When will I ever come to a place like this again?
It was my dream to go backpacking alone.
So what's your plan?
I don't have anything planned.
Right now, just to see him
and say, "Have you been well?"
"Me, I've been well."
Well, greeting him like that would be nice.
Isn't it strange?
What is?
It seems like it was ages ago
since we were all together.
If Gu Jun Pyo acts like he doesn't know me,
I'll wonder if I just dreamt it on my own.
It's not a dream.
If it were, it wouldn't have been so difficult.
What?
After sending you here, I realized...
That I hadn't done anything.
By the time I came around,
you were already on the plane.
So, it's not a dream.
Because right now,
you're right in front of me.
Sleep well.
"J"
Ah...
Ah! O...OK.
OK! That's enough!
Ah, go. Stop already.
You, really... If you weren't
the chief manager, I'd fire you.
Keep standing.
At 10:00, there's an inspection at the construction site.
And at 11:00, you'll be taking
the jet to visit the Singapore branch.
At 5:00, you have a meeting with the Mayor of Macao.
Also...
"Also" - what more?
Why stop in the middle of a sentence?
If you could make some time
to meet your F4 friends...
I have no time.
But they've been waiting since yesterday.
Am I someone with time on my hands?
So should I disregard today's
schedule and hang out with them?
If that's okay, then I'll see them.
Should I?
No.
Geez! Who maintains grass* like this?!
(*In Korean, "Jan Di" means "grass")
Seriously! Nothing's going right!
[Young Master Yi Jung]
Yes?  It is I.
What kind of mayor asks to meet
at a place like this?  Is he a former athlete?
I'm sorry.
No need for you to say "I'm sorry".
Hey yo!
How have you been?
It's been a while.
You guys came?
If we want to see the world's busiest man,
Shinhwa Group's heir, we have to come.
How else can we see you?
Nice to see you.
Really?
Because you don't seem that pleased.
What's with you, when we're
meeting after all this time?
Oh, Geum Jan Di also came with us.
That's not right. Actually,
Geum Jan Di came first to see you.
You haven't seen her, have you?
Why would I see her?
What?
Girls like her don't mean anything to me now.
Gu Jun Pyo...
So your not contacting Geum Jan Di
even once... You did that deliberately?
Deliberately or not, I don't have
time to think about stuff like that.
"Stuff like that"?
Jun Pyo, you really mean that?
We meet after all this time and
all you can talk about is silly stuff like this?
And you call yourself a man?
Why?
You guys meet and break up with girls all the time.
I can't be like that a little?
Even if we date and break up 20 times,
we don't do it like you!
Hey, really...
Let me go!
You... When we tried to stop
you before, what did you say?
You said that a real man takes
responsibility from beginning to end!
And you believed it?
You guys, surely...
You didn't think that she and I would last, did you?
This bastard...
Whose fault is it that
Geum Jan Di can't swim anymore?!
Stand up.
Yi Jung, calm down.
Do I look like I can calm down?
Listen to what that bastard is saying!
You...
Did you start, not knowing that it would be like this?
Didn't I warn you?
I told you not to carelessly
lead her on, you cowardly jerk!
What's with you guys?
Did you stop being my friend and all rush
to be Geum Jan Di's knights in shining armor?
Gu Jun Pyo...
If you came as my friends,
then have fun and go.
But if you even think about mentioning her name,
then leave immediately.
Why have you changed so much?
700,000.
What?
Within the Shinhwa name,
the employees and their families
for whom I am responsible,
are just short of 700,000.
Try carrying 700,000 lives on your shoulders.
And see if it doesn't change you.
An unbelievable challenge.
An unimaginable reality.
Asia's Venice.  Shinhwa stands for "the Legend".
Jan Di!
Is Jun Pyo doing w...
What? Is something the matter?
It's OK.
It's just that guy has become really strange.
- What...
- Geum Jan Di should know as well.
As you know, during this time, many things changed.
And the stress is nothing to joke about either.
He... won't see me?
You... How did...
You knew all along?
You don't have to worry so much.
Because whatever it is, I came
to hear it from Gu Jun Pyo himself.
I have to face it.
After all, you are Geum Jan Di!
The night air is sooo nice!
Hey! Do you remember?
- What?
- What we used to do when we were young.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Ji Hoo, you go that way.
Jan Di, you go that way,
and I'll go this way, okay? Go!
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One!
OK, I'm coming for you!
As a friend, I need a favor.
Tell me.
Meet her just once.
Why should I do that?
Didn't I say that it's a favor, as a friend?
And if I ask why you're asking for that favor?
Because right now, that's
the only thing I can do for her.
I'll be going.
What's the matter?
I was just heading out to the airport.
I just wanted to say "goodbye" here.
Because before I left,
I wanted to tell you something.
After today, I'm not sure I can say these words.
I’m really glad that I got to know you.
I'll be back.
Oh, Sunbae...
Sorry to wake you.
What's the matter?
We need to go somewhere.
Right now, at this hour?
I've heard of gymnastics on a moonlit night,
but what's with the stroll at dawn?
We're here.
Huh?
From here, you need to go by yourself.
It should be on that bridge.
I'm talking about the reason why you came here.
Uh, Sunba...
Hi.  I'm here.
Yeah.
What brings you all the way here?
I was really worried after I heard about your father.
Thanks.
But...
You came all the way here to say that?
Now, I guess you can feel better.
What?
As you can see, I'm doing fine.
As you know, I'm a busy person.
Now that you know, go.
Don't bother worrying about my well-being.
What?
Is there anything else left to say?
Do you really mean it?
What is it that you want?
Surely not...
"I'm sorry",
"Forgive me",
"I'll be back so wait for me".
What?  Were you expecting something like that?
Why are you being like this?
I’ve started to wake up to reality, that’s all.
I get it. I understand now.
Pretending to not see me,
and not wanting to see me...
You're saying that you really meant it.
So to you, I'm...
Like a stain I want to erase.
You're cruel, Gu Jun Pyo.
You're really cruel.
No.
I've always been this kind of person.
I just pretended that I wasn't.
I'm leaving. Take care.
Just worry about yourself.
Hey, pretty girl.
Are you okay?
Excuse me.
You are my special lucky lady,
because you're my first today.
Lucky lady?
Song... song.
Could you sing me one?
No, no. It's my treat.
With you, I will leave.
Con te partiro.
Countries I never
Paesi che non ho mai
saw and experienced with you,
veduto e vissuto con te,
Now, yes, I shall experience them.
adesso, si, li vivro.
With you, I will leave
Con te partiro
[Gu Jun Pyo <3 Geum Jan Di
Our first night!]
Starting today, let it be known that 2nd year
Geum Jan Di in Class B is my girlfriend.
Can you see it?
My heart?
Let go!
Young Master.
You can leave us.
Are you satisfied now?
Is President Kang satisfied now
that everything's the way you want?
I don't know.
Merely hearing about the likes of that girl
doesn't make me happy.
She's not just "that kind of a girl".
I...
Your SON!
She's the first girl that your son has ever loved.
Alright.
So what are you going to do?
Do you want to throw everything
away and run to her side?
Shinhwa Group, its employees, your future.
Fine.
But what about your father?
Stop it.
Your father, who tried his best
until the end for this company,
something that you would
toss away without hesitation.
Are you planning on throwing him away too?
Stop it.
What shall I do with that girl, Jan Di?
Should I make it so she can't live anywhere in Korea?
Be quiet.
I told you TO STOP!
Don't mess with Jan Di.
If you break your promise,
I'll destroy everything.
Can this pretty lady buy an ice cream from me please?
I'm sorry, but my Chinese is not good...
What did you just say?
Uh, ugly girl, please buy some ice cream.
Do you really think you can
sell anything with that line?
But you’d still buy it, wouldn't you?
How much is it?
Today.
What?
Give me today as payment for the ice cream.
Jan Di must be doing well, right?
No news is good news.
She's probably busy having fun with Jun Pyo.
Kang San!
If your stomach hurts, go to the bathroom.
Don't squirm around like that.
- What's wrong?
- Kang San.
Kang San.
San.
Where does it hurt?
What's wrong with him?
Oh dear!
Get a grip on yourself!
Get him on my back.
Kang San.
You're eating well, right?
Yes.
You're also sleeping well?
Hm, your blood pressure looks good.
Hannah.
Yes?
Should I give you a piece of candy?
Yes.
There you go.
You're so cute.
Let's shake hands.
You're so pretty.
Bye.
Yes.
- Goodbye.
- Yes.
- Excuse us!
- Doctor!
- Over here!
Is anyone here?
- Please help us!
- Doctor!
Something's wrong with him.
Please look at him.
It's pretty.
It's time to go.
Let's go.
This is mine.
I got it first.
I had my eyes on it first.
Get your hands off of it.
I won't.
Let go.
Miss, I'm sorry.
I sincerely apologize, but could
you please give this one up?
Why?
Do you know her size?
Size?
Hey, try these on.
Hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Hey!
They fit perfectly.
Take them off.
I don't want to.
You're not taking them off?!
Come here.
Who is that guy?
Is he crazy?
Are you alright?
Why do you only show up now?
They had some business so they left first.
What should we do?
We should be leaving too.
Let's leave on the first plane tomorrow.
What is that girl doing right now?
Are you asking about Geum Jan Di?
Young Master Yi Jung and Woo Bin
left for Seoul this afternoon,
Young Master Ji Hoo and Geum Jan Di
are planning to leave tomorrow.
It seems like she finally learn to let go.
Where is Jun Pyo?
He's been in the conference room all night.
It looks like he has finally found his place as well.
Gu Jun Pyo.
Can you hear me?
I thought about you everyday,
but how come I only remember us
fighting and arguing with each other?
Isn't it odd?
Even though, there're only memories of us fighting,
yet whenever I think about you, I always smile.
Gu Jun Pyo.
You're doing fine, right?
When are you going to come back and fight with me?
Jun Pyo!
Let's go together.
Have you seen this plane before?
Isn't it a beauty?
Look at it.
This is the propeller that spins.
In the future, you have to fly this.
Let's get in.
If this is a car, then this is the steering wheel.
This is the handle.
Aren't there a lot of buttons?
Yes.
When you learn how to fly a plane,
you must fly this one.
Who are you?
Gu Jun Pyo.
Jun Pyo is...
Dad's son of course!
What will you do when I’m not around?
What do you have to do?
I’ll take care of Mom, Noona, and Shinhwa Group.
Gu Jun Pyo.
Let's makes a man-to-man promise!
Yes, Sir!
Promise!
Hey! Ji Hoo!
Ji Hoo! Hey!
Min.
Ji Hoo!
What are you doing here?
When did you come here?
A couple of days ago.
Long time no see.
Why didn't you tell me that
you were coming here to Macao?
Did you know how much I missed you?
How long are you going to stay?
I'm on my way back.
You can't!
You can't.
We can't separate like this.
Ji Hoo, let's go to my house.
I can't. I have company.
Who?
She's not your girlfriend, is she?
If this lady gives her permission, will you stay?
I'm Ji Hoo's friend, from Juilliard's
Oh, you are?
Nice to meet you.
I'm sick right now.
It's really serious.
So please grant me this request.
Excuse me?
Let's go to my house.
Just for one day.
Uh, sure. Alright.
Let's go.
It's no big deal if we leave a day later, right?
It's really been a while.
Right?
Let's go.
Okay.
This looks really delicious.
I've prepared a sumptuous meal.
You even know how to use those words?
You speak Korean really well.
Ji Hoo is Korean.
Did you learn Korean because of Ji Hoo sunbae?
No!
This... is only for Ji Hoo's use.
This looks so delicious.
Let's enjoy our meal.
Ji Hoo, eat a lot.
Eat up.
That girl is not pretty.
She's short and flat-chested.
And she eats way too much.
What do you want to hear?
That girl... Ji Hoo's girlfriend?
What do you think?
Ji Hoo, that girl... you like her.
What?
Whenever you see her, you smile.
Like before.
Before?
Whenever Ji Hoo see Seo Hyun. Like that.
Find out Geum Jan Di's room number for me.
What?
She checked out?
Alright.
Young Master, it's time for us to leave
for the meeting with the president.
When did Ji Hoo leave?
He's still in Macao.
Really?
Didn't he check out?
I heard that he and Geum Jan Di
went to his friend's house.
Friend? Which friend?
Shall I find out for you?
No, it's fine.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: Javafiend, Beeni
Spot Translators: saturn, javabeans
Timer: melliemelll
Editor/QC: jtranla
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
She's really enjoying it.
Next time, I'm not bringing doughnuts
since it's affecting our filming schedule.
You need to take this off too.
It's hurting now!
Why is he pinching my face?
Call Jun Pyo. Jan Di's in danger.
Hold on.
Are you going to pick me up?
Food, food, food!
Cut.
Don't hesitate, just touch her lightly with your lips.
Why are you opening your mouth?
After that, you look at her.
Cut, okay.
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get it for FREE @ d-addicts.com