Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Episode 2
Who are you?
Let go!
- Shut up!
- Let go! Let go!
Are you guys having a group training?
What?
That...
You didn't forget anything in the
pancake recipe you gave me?
What?
I did as you instructed.
But it didn't rise.
Did you add baking powder?
Yes.
That.
And they sell the pancake mix.
Let go.
Why are you guys still here?
That... Jun Pyo sunbae...
None of your business.
What are you doing? Let's go.
You're getting goose bumps.
Baking powder... Now I know.
Seems like I have to try again.
Sunbae.
Thank you for helping me.
I wasn't helping you.
I just couldn't stand seeing
these annoying acts.
What? Ji Hoo?
Yes, he had to appear right at that moment.
Who asked you to do these things?
Didn't you say to let Geum Jan Di suffer?
I just told you to scare her
so that she would admit her mistake!
- Who told you to do that?
- Sorry. It's our fault.
Do you guys want to leave school too?
Get lost! I don't want to see you!
Get lost!
Jan Di, are you really alright?
It's nothing big.
That's still nothing big?
Those F4.
I thought of cutting them some
slack because of their good looks.
I didn't think they were really so bad.
Birds of a feather flock together.
The four of them are always together right?
It's not really like that.
Why not?
One of them is a little different.
One person?
Who's that?
She's so pretty in this advertisement again.
Sunbae likes her too?
No matter what, touching the advertisement
like that would dirty your hands.
She's really pretty right?
She's just like a goddess who
descended to Earth.
Goddess?
Not only is her face pretty.
She's very smart too.
She donates almost all the
money she earned as a model.
Not long ago, she passed the
French International Lawyer exam.
You know this woman?
Of course! She's my idol.
Idol?
Although everyone thought that
she would take over her parents'
company after she graduated...
I didn't think so.
I've always thought that
she would do something even greater.
On every school holiday,
she would go to Africa, Afghanistan.
Oh, she went to Tibet not long ago too.
Though this is just my imagination,
I hope she marries someone of royalty
status or someone who may become president.
Like Diana or Audrey Hepburn to be a
princess who contributes to world peace.
Something like that.
She's just a model.
Why?
Didn't the French president
divorce his wife to be with a model?
Who would know?
Maybe the next French president
or some European prince,
would fall in love with Unni at first
sight and ask for her hand in marriage.
I think there's a high
possibility of this happening.
Don't you think so?
Every time I see you,
I find you so noisy and irritating.
I just...
What would you know?
Hey Kang San! Aren't you going to eat?
You've been on the computer all day long!
Can the computer give you money or food?
He just faces the electron
wave for the whole day.
San, be careful!
Or your family line will be cut*.
(*can't have a baby due to the electron wave)
I can earn money and get food!
How dare you look down on the Cyber Arbeit King?
Cyber-what?
Cyber Arbeit*
(*Internet addicts who work online)
It may be the rich and
wealthy who supports the world,
but to make this world
more rich and exciting,
you'll need depend on a maniac like me.
You just keep staring at
the computer screen.
How dirty.
Hey! What is this?
Hm jom moo...?
Hey you...
I've lived for so long and it's the first time
I'm hearing about a worm-eaten (jom) radish (moo).
Honey, it doesn't mean that.
It means, "a radish which has a small (jom) scar (hm)"
Hm jom moo is...
"Hmm, if this is the truth,
then it would be a little scary."
That's what it means!
What?
Noona! This would totally make headline news!
Headline?
It says that a female student
in your school is pregnant!
What?!
Where? Where?
Isn't it written here?
Miss K, a second year student
in Shinhwa High School,
has been spotted going in
and out of the obstetrics hospital.
Second year, Miss K.
Jan Di! Then there's a possibility
that she's in your class.
If it's Miss K, is her surname Kim?
It can be Kang.
Kwon. There's still Miss Kwon.
The world is in a mess now.
How can a second year student in high
school get pregnant? Oh my...
How can such a thing happen to a
prestigious school like Shinhwa High School?
Oh, my! What's wrong with these rich kids doing such a thing?
The rich are actually more cunning and scarier!
Really?
Of course.
Urgent news. Second year student,
Miss K, has appeared.
What are they looking at?
Didn't you rich people cause trouble too?
I want to see which of you did it.
Oh, my. I didn't think a commoner
would actually be like that.
Just a commoner.
She has dated a truck load of guys before.
How dirty. She's crazy.
Roll here and there. Crazy!
How vulgar. Go and die, Jan Di!
She should leave while it's early.
Who's the kid's father?
Forbid abortion!
Why is it so quiet today?
What?
2,500 Won (Jan Di)
Wait and see. She'll appear in no time.
That girl who doesn't know her limits.
What prank have you pulled this time?
Why, so you can save her again?
What does that mean?
You shouldn't push it too far.
But since when did you care about all of this?
If you aren't going to help,
then mind your own business.
Making life difficult for a girl
is ridiculous and childish.
Does she look like a girl to you?
She completely disregards people,
just like a horse or a dog.
Whether she's a horse or a dog,
she defied the Great Jun Pyo-nim.
So, I must teach her a lesson.
Don't you know the rules?
You want to erase it? What's the use?
What can you do about this?
Urgent news! The true identity of
the second year student, Miss K,
has been confirmed to be Geum Jan Di!
Kids! Don't you smell something really gross?
How dirty is it? To have this gross smell.
I've only heard of how gross
the dirty clothes smell...
It really suffocates.
Sunny, give me the perfume.
How can we study in this kind of classroom?
I can't take this.
I can't take this anymore!
You can't take it?
So what are you going to do about it?
What can you do?
Speaking of the devil...
Who?
Who else? I was right, wasn't I?
She came looking for me.
If you came to apologize,
you're too late.
I would not quietly tolerate it anymore.
Warning. The outcome.
These words are all prepared for you, you know?!
Did you know?!
Hey, laundry girl.
Is that how you apologize among your people?
Then among your people,
must the victim apologize to the culprit?
What did you say?
You... What are you doing?
I told you, I won't sit back
and take it anymore.
I said it. I told you clearly already!
Did you see me sleeping around with a man?!
Did you even see me holding hands with a guy?!
How dare you spread all those rumors about
a chaste and pure girl,
who hasn't even had her first kiss yet?!
You...!
If you keep up these filthy tricks,
I'll really kill you then!
Why is he so amused?
She actually dared to pull a spinning
back kick on the Great Gu Jun Pyo.
It has been a while since
our school's life were so fun.
But, don't you think she reminds you of someone?
You're right. I was thinking of that too.
Who is it?
Jun Hee noona!
What? Don't joke!
No, no. There're some
similarities between them.
What similarities?
How can you compare that
countryside girl to my sister?
Whether she's like your sister or not,
you'd know best.
Shut up!
But why were you laughing
to yourself just now?
Did something get to your head?
Haven't you guys caught on yet?
What?
That chick...
no matter how I think about it,
is totally into me.
What?
Gu Jun Pyo, how in the world
did you arrive at that conclusion?
You guys.
How can you call yourselves
experts at love or Casanova?
Girls always say what they don't mean.
Though that chick appears
to hate me on the surface,
she's actually totally infatuated with me.
Think about it.
She didn't want the guy
she likes to misunderstand,
so she came herself to
insist she was pure and innocent.
Following that logic...
...saying she hasn't had her first kiss...
...is her way of saying she's
waiting for her first kiss from me.
Bravo.
Impressive, Gu Jun Pyo.
You're my friend, but
that's really something.
That goes without saying.
There would be a day where
Gu Jun Pyo's charisma hits home.
I knew it was strange.
The answer's the opposite.
She thinks she could fool me by acting mad.
It would be burdensome too
if she was too straightforward.
Wouldn't it?
Even if it's like this,
I still have to come to school.
Ah, seriously.
That's why I need to kick
this impulsive bad temper.
Why must I go and agitate them?
Are you Miss Geum Jan Di?
Yes, I am.
Can you come with me for a while?
What? Where to?
I'm a little busy now.
We received orders to take you with us.
From whom?
You'll know when you come with us.
I have to go and work.
I'll leave first. Sorry.
Ahjussi! Why are you following me?
- She's not over that side?
- No, she's not.
We'll search one more time.
You go look over there.
Yes.
Let's go.
Ahjussi! Let go!
Let go!
- Stop moving!
- What are you doing?!
Stop moving!
Are you guys trying to kidnap me?
Let's move off.
Ahh, what a nice fragrant.
Just like a garden full of flowers.
Warm and gentle.
And someone is making my body... My body...
Someone is massaging my body!
There's no need to do liposuction right?
It's not even fat, it's just muscles.
There'll be not effect even if you do it.
You've prepared the laser already right?
We'll have to wax her before that.
Everyone is very curious as this
is the first time such a thing happened.
It's the first time our Young
Master has brought a girl home.
Can I ask something?
Yes.
So, this is in our country, Korea, right?
Yes, that's right.
Is this CheongWaDae* or something?
(*Korean President's house)
No.
Can I ask another question?
Yes, go ahead, Miss.
I'm not a Miss.
Just call me Jan Di. Geum Jan Di.
Yes, Miss Geum Jan Di.
Why am I here now?
I'm not sure about that too, Miss.
Where are we going now?
We've reached already.
He's waiting for you.
Waiting for me?
Who?
Ji Hoo sunbae?
You!
Why are you here for?
What's so strange about me being in my home?
My home?
So, this is Gu Jun Pyo, your house?
Yes.
Why?
What are you thinking of doing again?
I've done what I wanted to already.
Look.
You, yourself, feel shocked right?
See, money can turn even
an ugly duckling into a heron.
Don't you mean swan?
Well, it doesn't matter anyway.
What are you up to now?
Who asked you to do this?
Hey, commoner.
If you like me, just say so.
What?
Right, you like to talk in
opposites, don't you?
Gu Jun Pyo.
There's a limit to the jokes you make.
This is illegal kidnapping!
It is an extremely terrible crime!
Nobody's around, so you can be
open about liking me here.
From now on...
I'll be willing to make an exception
and recognize you outside of school.
Why?
Did this explosive proposal scare you silly?
Shall I repeat myself?
If you just do as I say...
When nobody's around,
I can treat you as the
Almighty Jun Pyo's girlfriend.
Understand?
You're crazy right?
You're really crazy, huh?
Has your brain been addled
by too much greasy food?
Who? Become whose? What?
Forget it. I'm leaving.
You're the one whose brain
has something wrong.
Move aside while I'm being nice.
Do you know how much was
spent on you from head to toe?
100 million Won.
What?
100 million Won?!
That's right.
But that's nothing.
If you're with me, you can enjoy
more than that every day.
Are you saying you don't want it?
Are you crazy?
Being kidnapped by a psycho like you here,
can I still be in the right state of mind?
The moment I see your face, it feels
like bugs are crawling all over my body.
Get me my uniform now!
What is this?!
Throw it away!
What are you doing?
Didn't you hear me asking
you to throw it right away?
Yes, master.
And fire them all.
What?
Fire all those who waited on her today!
What's with her hair?
Her clothes too!
Can they only do such an
old-fashioned style?
Find other people.
Find some top notch people!
All those who came today are the best staff.
Then just find even more expensive people!
I understand.
Hey! What's that?
Bee! Hurry up catch it!
Ah, bee! Hurry catch it!
Hurry!
Has it left?
Yes, we chased it out.
That tea.
Did you brew it?
Sorry, Young Master.
Fire her.
Why is the toilet even bigger than my house?
But, Geum Jan Di...
why were you so stumped over there?
And one more thing.
Seems like you don't know,
but friends can't be bought by money.
You use your heart to reach out to them.
There's nothing that can't
be bought by money.
Tell me.
If there's such a thing around.
Is there really something that
can't be bought using money in this world?
If you're that confident, tell me right now.
Commoner...
How embarrassing!
I'm really going crazy!
You again?
That's my line.
Are you going somewhere?
Home.
You?
I'm going home too.
In this manner?
Some situation cropped up.
Why?
Every time I see you,
you're in a dramatic situation.
It's a little like that right?
Can I ask you something?
Is there something in this world
that cannot be bought using money?
Even if you give millions of dollars,
you will never get it.
There isn't right?
There isn't something like that right?
Air.
What?
Oh, air.
So, that's it!
Why didn't I think of it?
You're a really interesting kid.
Wear it.
If you walk like that around here,
you'll get caught.
Who is this?
Isn't this Gu Jun Pyo's mortal enemy,
Wonder Woman?
Why are you here?
Jun Pyo isn't here now.
Why would I come and find someone like him?
Isn't that Ji Hoo's sports shoes?
Help me return it to him.
Wait a moment.
Have a cup of tea before you leave.
Did you really say that to Jun Pyo?
Wow. You're really amazing.
No one has ever shown such
anger to him before.
Oh, it's Seo Hyun.
She should be coming back already right?
Ji Hoo would be really happy.
That...
The four of you have known
each other for a very long time?
Yes, from kindergarten till now.
You seem to have something
that you're really curious about.
Ask us. We'll tell you if we know.
Take it that we're repaying you.
Repaying?
It has been really fun for us lately.
All thanks to you.
Are Ji Hoo sunbae and the model,
Min Seo Hyun, acquainted?
Acquainted?
When Ji Hoo was 5,
he got into a car accident.
His parents died on the spot,
leaving him behind.
Then, he retreated into autism,
ignoring everyone.
The person who pulled Ji Hoo back
to the normal world was Min Seo Hyun.
To us, she's just our childhood playmate,
our noona and our friend.
But to Ji Hoo, she's like his
first love, girlfriend and mother.
How pretty.
How can someone be so pretty?
Her parents must be really happy,
having a daughter like her.
She so pretty in women's eyes already.
What more men.
Min Seo Hyun.
Mom, that woman is Min Seo Hyun right?
God is really unfair.
Some people are pretty,
smart and have a good family background.
Yet, others...
Why?
She has broad shoulders.
You're done eating?
A stress of alpha girl takes
away her strong appetite.
That's right.
You have eyes too.
Why don't you think of going on a diet?
But is she going to be a lawyer or a model?
Of course she should be a lawyer!
She passed such a difficult exam.
I prefer her to be a model.
That's why people say this
is the naivety of men.
When she's young, she should be a model,
when she grows older,
she should be a lawyer.
That's my mother!
Jan Di!
You aren't eating your orange too right?
This is to be packed in Jan Di's lunchbox!
Dad.
What is this?
That...
What's this?
Thunderbird, 5,000 Won
Typhoon, 20,000 Won.
Speeding, 30,000 Won
You!
I'll really win it this time!
Get out!
You might as well go to the horse
race track and live with them!
If I believe you one more time,
my name would be changed to Thunderbird!
Get out!
Mom, Thunderbird is the worst.
The lousiest.
You pick something else.
She's like his first love,
girlfriend and mother.
Hey! Geum Jan Di!
Blood.
Serves you right.
You did well.
Her nose's bleeding.
Well done!
Don't move.
What were you thinking of?
Letting yourself get hit in the face.
Don't be like that.
What?
Don't cry.
It doesn't suit you.
What is it to you?
Do I have to get your permission to cry now?
And weren't you the person who was
the happiest to see me crying and hurting?
Is that all you can say
to the person who came to help?
Who asked for your help?
Who asked for your help?!
If everyone died and you were
the last person on earth,
I still wouldn't accept your help.
I'd rather bleed to death
than be indebted to you.
Hey.
W... what is it you hate so much about me?
What are you not satisfied about me?
I'm good looking.
I'm tall, I'm smart, I'm rich.
How...
How can you hate Gu Jun Pyo?
Are you really stupid?
Seems like you still don't know,
I dislike everything about you!
The way you look, the way you walk,
and your stupid curly hair!
I hate everything.
Did you eat the wrong medicine?
I haven't finished speaking.
It's such an eyesore to see bunch of you
wearing whatever you please to school.
And picking on weak kids for fun
with your red cards or whatever and
your thoughtlessness.
That's the worst!
You...
You want me to repeat myself?
All in all, Gu Jun Pyo,
I hate everything about you!
Hate everything!
A month long school trip to
Europe for second and third years.
School trip?
What?! 20 million won?!
That school is really amazing!
How can a school trip be 20 million won?
Are all the students going?
No, I'm not.
You want to go quietly,
without me knowing right?
Where can we go?
So, what do you intend to do?
What can I do?
It'll just be like a month
long school holiday.
I'll work hard and earn some money.
Ah, my father! My father
caused trouble again!
My family is completely broke now!
South. Aren't you going to the South?
South, what South?
Hurry go cook your porridge!
The two of us decided not
to join the English Village.
Let's plead our parents to
let us go on a holiday.
I wonder if there's any way
where we can play and earn money.
It's the South Sea!
Yeah, Mom?
Really?
I can go.
But can I go with Jan Di?
Really?
You'll plead Aunty right?
But you must guarantee the 70000 Won pay!
See, didn't I say you girls would go.
You're going to the South Sea right?
Hey! Are the two of you
going to keep pacing up and down?
- Isn't Jun Pyo sunbae really handsome?
- He's exceptionally handsome today!
Gu Jun Pyo!
Are you waiting for someone too?
Waiting what?
Since we have to take a long plane flight,
I must do sufficient exercise first.
Hey.
But why must you insist going together
with the rest of the students this time?
Don't you want to use your
private jet and not suffer all this?
This is a school trip.
Such suffering would be
a memory of my high school life.
Isn't it, Ji Hoo?
What?
Yo, yo, yo. Let's go.
Why isn't that girl coming?
Wow. Isn't that Min Seo Hyun?
Wow, she looks great!
We're so lucky.
Take a picture for me.
Look here, look here.
Her face is really petite.
Her skin! Wow.
Ah, it's Min Seo Hyun!
She's so pretty!
Sign for me, please!
Thank you. Thank you.
- Have you been doing well?
- Yes.
Let's go.
I don't like that picture.
Hello.
Excuse me. I'm sorry but you can't
use your mobile phone on board.
W... What?
Wh... Where did she go?
To catch fish, we went to the ocean.
- Put them in a cage
- Fill up a cage.
Isn't it put them in?
Isn't it fill it up?
To catch fish, we went to the ocean.
Hey, Dry Cleaner.
Ah, ahh. Can you hear me?
Commoner!
What was that?
Ka Wol, am I having a dream now?
I don't think so.
But I keep hearing that
irritating guy's voice.
I heard the commoner went to the sea.
Look at yourself.
Hey! Why are you guys here?
Aren't you supposed to go
to North Europe or Fjord?
We've gone there one or twice.
Sick of it already.
We wanted to look for some new
place and somebody recommended here.
What a total coincidence, huh?
I had no idea you'd be here, Dry Cleaner
Then go on your own route!
Pretend not to know me and
I'd be really grateful!
That boat is just made of wood.
Will it be OK?
Even though it's small, it's still a boat!
None of your business!
Really?
True. You wouldn't drown
even if it capsizes.
You know how to swim right?
Then, let's move off!
You... this jerk! Gu Jun Pyo!
Gu Jun Pyo!
So cold!
Isn't that Min Seo Hyun?
Hey, Dry Cleaner.
What now?!
Honestly, you're very happy to
meet me at a place like this, right?
Tell me.
You were very bored on
that fish-like smelling boat.
I was very happy before I met you.
No matter what,
since you're a student of our school,
come if you want to.
Though I don't know where to,
I don't have any intention to go!
There's a welcome party for that person.
It'll be fun.
You should come too.
You'll come right?
Yes, I'll come.
I'll definitely come.
Hey! You!
I know what you're going to say.
I don't really want to go too.
Come on.
Both Jun Pyo and Ji Hoo
have extended their invitation.
You must come.
Am I right?
Yes.
But, they left out something.
Left out something?
Why? Why?
Come here.
Let's go.
Is this really OK?
It's OK. It's OK.
Once you go in, there'll be some
even more exaggerated than yours.
This doesn't even count as anything.
No, but it's so embarrassing.
What?
This concept fits you to the tee!
Don't worry.
Geum Jan Di, fighting!
Let's go. I should just go back.
Love can only be obtained
by those with courage.
What kind and beautiful? Try getting
caught by me, you're dead!
Geum Jan Di, why did you
believe what they say?
You're so stupid. Stupid.
Geum Jan Di!
You!
You're late.
We didn't know that you're here.
We have been looking for you.
You haven't taken off your coat.
Don't you feel hot?
It's not hot. I'm still feeling very
cold from the sea breeze.
Is it because your dress is too thin?
The latest designs are really pretty,
but they expose a little too much.
Is yours like that too?
Hurry take it off!
Let's not waste time. Take it off for her.
Wonder woman? What is this?
Oh, my. What is this?
Isn't this Wonder Woman?
You were hailed as Wonder
Woman on the internet.
Now you can't even differentiate
between reality and your own imagination?
If you didn't have a dress,
you should've said.
I understand that you're
trying to stand out.
But this is a little over the top, commoner.
Maybe the commoners enjoy doing this lately.
She's really dressed as Wonder Woman.
I know why you did this.
But do you know that this
proves how low you are, not her?
What are you doing Ji Hoo?
Hurry help her to my room.
This Ji Hoo. Why is he doing
these unfathomable things?
I don't know what this is about
but isn't it fun?
Thank you.
You don't have to go to this extent.
It's what I'd like to do
so don't feel burdened.
This isn't a place where I'm
supposed to be from the beginning.
Ji Hoo invited you right?
If you're Ji Hoo's friend,
then you're a precious friend to me too.
No.
That was just out of courtesy.
Ji Hoo is not someone like that.
And to stand up for someone like this,
it's that first time I'm seeing him do that.
Ji Hoo sunbae has always been so attentive.
Ji Hoo is attentive?
See what I mean.
That's because Jan Di is a special person.
I heard you've suffered a
lot because of Jun Pyo.
I heard that you swore that
you'll never bow down to him.
That's...
It's because he's lonely.
What?
He's wrapping his loneliness with violence.
Gu Jun Pyo is lonely?
How can that be?
He can be with his parents
only a month per year.
From the moment he was born,
he wasn't a normal son or friend.
He was treated as their
heir of their company.
Can you imagine how it feels?
Don't lose to him.
What?
I like Jan Di, so I'll cheer you on.
We're done.
Get up.
They're so pretty.
To women, shoes are the most important.
Why?
Good shoes take you to good places.
You're ready.
Shall we go out now?
It's not gentlemanly to
ignore such a beautiful lady.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translator: pickles
Spot Translator: saturn
Timer: julier
Editor/QC: puela
Final QC: knitoe
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
You finished drinking all of these?
Hey. Wake up, you... this woman!
Yes, I'm a woman.
I can't do anything.
Geum Jan Di is a sly snake
hidden under an innocent demeanor.
When I first saw her, I knew it already.
A person that Ji Hoo would smile
whenever he mentions would be Jan Di.
Geum Jan Di is pretty when
she dolls herself up.
It's not like an ugly duckling became a swan.
Ji Hoo would have liked you
if he met you first.
What gives you the right to do this?
It's because Sunbae is in so much pain.
What is it to you?
Get lost!
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get it for FREE @ d-addicts.com