"We offer condolences to Jang Ja Yun,
and we pray that you rest in peace."
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
Episode 18
What?
- Let go.
- I don't want to.
I'm not letting go.
Hey, Monkey.
Okay. You call me "Monkey",
so I really want to become a monkey.
Even if it's the only way,
I really want to cling to you forever.
The man who is right for you...
...is out there somewhere.
You...
...aren't so ugly.
I don't want someone else.
If he's not Gu Jun Pyo, then he won't do.
I'm sorry.
Is there someone you like?
Yeah.
Aren't you going to ask who it is?
I don't want to hear.
I don't want to hear anything.
I can't hear a thing.
I don't hear anything.
Did you see a ghost?
N-no!
I-I didn't see anything.
I really didn't see anything.
Let's go.
Where to?
If I leave you alone,
You're going to jump in the water again.
This stupid thing won't stop.
Why am I like this?
It's not stupid.
So...
Don't scold it too much.
Why Macau of all places?
I came to find someone.
Ah! Your boyfriend?
Yeah, well...
Gu Jun Pyo
I'm leaving first.
Song Woo Bin.
You better hurry and get down from there!
Hey, So Yi Jung.
Why are you my friend?
What?
Tell me the truth.
It's embarrassing to have me,
son of the mafia, as a friend, right?
Stop talking nonsense and
get down from there now!
I'm embarrassed, so I can only
imagine what it must be like for you.
It's because of you I get by.
The others from "great" families
don't even consider me a person,
even I know that.
Song Woo Bin, you really...
But, I'm...
...only embarrassed in front of you guys.
My boss...my path...
I don't care what others say,
but to you, in front of you,
I'm occasionally embarrassed.
I get so annoyed for being embarrassed.
Did you know that? Did you even know that?!
You jerk!
To you,
is that all we mean to you?!
Do you think we're better off than you?!
If you're like this, then what about me? Us?
If you're embarrassed once in a while,
can't you show that to your friends?
Is that so?
Does that really make us friends?
Brothers? F4?!
Tell me, you bastard!
Oh my.
Hey, what do you think you're doing there?
Get lost!
Yi Jung.
Why did you drink so much?
Ah.
Yi Jung, are you okay?
Master, should we take care of this?
Don't interfere.
I'll take care of the bastards
who hurt my friend myself.
Do you know how much his hands are worth?
I don't know.
Even if I can come back in life,
I wouldn't exchange for his hands.
Do you have any idea what you've done?!
Just hang in there.
Good morning!
Did you sleep well too, Unni?
I couldn't sleep a wink.
Last night was a historical night
for Gu Jun Pyo and Ha Jae Kyung.
Jun Pyo was embarrassed, so he left first.
Things looked good between you two yesterday.
See. It was a good idea to come here, right?
Just like how a thread follows a needle,
I'll get going too.
You two have fun and come back later.
Ji Hoo, please take care of Jan Di, okay?
Uh, Unni, we too...
[Yoon Ji Hoo]
[Geum Jan Di / Prayer for acceptance]
[Yoon Ji Hoo / Prayer for constant happiness]
Supposedly, you'll get accepted if you drink this.
She has a good face.
The young lady's face can make muddy water clear.
Be sure to treasure her.
What?
That girl will give you a family.
How come I don't see that young girl today?
Grandmother, that child doesn't work here.
Of course she's not a child.
She's a grown woman.
I adore her to pieces.
Ah, yes.
If I had a grandson, I'd love to make
her my granddaughter-in-law.
No, that's not possible
since she has already been taken by someone.
Now, please be careful.
Have a safe trip home.
I'm back...
Mom, what is all this?
Was there a war?
Jan Di, sit down.
We have an important announcement to make.
An announcement?
Geum Jan Di, my eldest.
Listen well to what I'm about to say, okay?
What is it this time?
Dad, you got into trouble again, right?!
You think I get into trouble all the time...
You're right.
So...
in order to remove the source of the problem,
I've made a crucial decision.
Decision?
Yeah.
Tomorrow morning,
Mom and Dad have decided to
head to where your uncle lives.
What?
It's hard enough getting by.
There is no hope for our family here.
Mom and Dad will head down
and work on fishing boats,
and we can send you money for living expenses.
It won't cost us anything if we go there.
But what about Kang San and me?
You have to stay here and attend school.
Geum Jan Di, take good care of San.
From now on, you are the head of our family.
Was there ever a time
when Noona wasn't the head?
Come on, Mom.
Dad.
I'm sorry, Jan Di.
Listen to your big sister.
Make sure to wash properly, and...
Oh, my poor baby.
- Hey.
- Yes?
What's going on?
Well, that is...
Give that to me.
And this one...
Hey, Monkey.
What are you doing in someone else's house?
Oh, my husband is awake?
You're hungry, right?
Let's eat breakfast.
Here, have a seat.
What's all this?
What do you think it is?
I prepared this for you.
We have chefs in my house.
I know, but there isn't anything
I can do for you even if I want to.
You and I are similar. What we want,
we buy and we get everything.
So I thought what if it was me.
I thought, "What do I long for the most?"
What was it?
First of all, I wanted a happy,
fulfilling breakfast table.
I hated eating by myself at a huge table.
Since you prepared it, I will eat it, but-
Really? Then, start by eating this.
This is really good. This is good, too.
This one, this one.
Try this one.
Alright, before it cools down,
you have to eat it while it's warm.
I was really happy when someone
boned the fish and put it on my rice.
You've never done this, right?
Is it good?
That's a relief.
Eat this also.
And this one too.
Do you want to try this?
*Ya Shim Jak.
*Ya Shim Jak means a masterpiece
Have some roots too.
After this, there's dessert.
Have you tried the soup?
I made it really delicious.
Is there anything?
No.
Of course there isn't.
A place with no deposit, cheap rent.
Decent enough for a junior high
and high school student to live...
Of course there isn't.
Can't you just come to
my house and live with me?
What about Kang San?
Oh, yeah. There's Geum Kang San.
There's no answer.
I'd better get going.
You're the one who needs help.
Have some tea.
How's your shoulder?
It's better now, but now my knee is aching.
I'll get a hot pack for your knee.
Where did such a sweetie come from?
What is this?
You're looking for a room?
Yes. I'm looking for a cheap place,
but it's not easy.
Wait a moment.
- I'll get you a hot pack for your knee.
- No. No.
When did you get in here?
Here.
What is it?
It's late, but it's our engagement gift.
Gift?
The one the parents got is not my style.
But I really wanted to share
this with you, so I made it.
J J?
Yeah. Jun Pyo and Jae Kyung.
No. Jae Kyung and Jun Pyo.
Even our initials are fated, right?
Put it on for me.
Where are you going?
I have to go somewhere.
Where?
You're my fiancée, not my wife!
Just go home!
Stop it.
No, I'll do what I want.
It's really fascinating.
How can something like this
be made from regular dirt?
You're more fascinating.
What kind of girl who has no other
interest aside from pottery?
Then what about you?
Is there something you like more than pottery?
There is.
A girl?
Hm. Girls are like math problems.
In the beginning, I wonder how to solve it.
After I study and follow through,
there's a solution.
It's simple, but it's still a wonder.
Why are you looking at me like that?
To me, you're...
like a problem with no solution.
What?
A problem that starts off
completely twisted and unsolvable.
Hey, you'd better come here.
Jung.
Why did you act like that?
According to Woo Bin, your hand...
It's over.
Seriously?
The swimmer had to give up
swimming because of a bum shoulder
The potter has to give up
pottery because of a broken hand.
Doesn't it seem like some documentary
about overcoming obstacles?
What's that supposed mean?
Are you talking about Geum Jan Di?
Is there any other swimmer
we know besides Geum Jan Di?
So Yi Jung.
Be straight with me.
What do you mean by a bum shoulder?
Was this what you were talking about in Macau?
Come to think of it,
you really came to your senses in Macau.
For people like us,
stuff like love or innocence was
never meant to be from the start.
I told you to tell it to me straight!
Do you remember when she
got hit by the chair meant for you?
You don't know how much Geum Jan Di cried
after hearing she couldn't swim anymore, do you?
Is that...really true?
No matter how you tackle it,
the result is always the same.
People like you and I have nothing
to give the women we love but pain.
Here, Kang San. Right here.
Will you be okay?
- Just the two of you here...
- It's okay.
The view is great and it's cozy too.
Right, Noona?
Thanks Ga Eul.
It's getting really late.
- I'll leave then.
- Thanks!
- Kang San, bye!
- Go home safely!
Kang San, will you be okay?
Just don't overdo it yourself.
Let's do our best, so Mom and Dad
won't have to worry.
- Fighting!
Let's start now.
Start cleaning!
- Noona, over there.
- Let's get started.
Here?
Whose fault was it that
Geum Jan Di can't swim anymore?
Why aren't you swimming?
I quit.
Why would a swimmer quit swimming?
It's none of your business.
While I'm gone, please take care of Jun Pyo.
Do you understand what I mean?
I understand.
If anything out of the ordinary,
contact me right away.
Don't worry and have a safe trip.
Hey, delivery girl!
Give me a milk carton.
Hurry and toss over my milk.
Jun Pyo hyung-nim?
Hey, Gu Jun Pyo!
What are you doing here?
Why?
Is it strange seeing me at my own house?
Your house?
I decided today that I'll live here.
Why?
Why would you live here?
To experience being independent.
Should I call it ‘standing on my own'?
Why would you do something like that here?
Don't you ever watch dramas?
Usually for thoughtful royal family or clans,
the heirs must go through trainings like this.
Haven't you heard stories about
sons being thrown off a cliff?
Where was it...
S... S....
- Sparta?
- Yes! There!
Hey little bro, don't just study for yourself,
but help your sister study too.
I can't communicate with her, because
she lacks common knowledge of 'Su Sa'*
*Su Sa means investigation. (Jun Pyo said wrong word)
Common knowledge of 'Su Sa'?
Common knowledge of 'Shi Sa'*
*Shi Sa means current affairs
Whether it's standing on your own or
being independent, can you leave now?
We are a bit busy.
What's this?
It wasn't planned, but we're neighbors now.
I hope we can help each other out.
If you need anything, I'll help.
Can I refuse?
What I just showed you is the spinning wheel method
and what everyone is doing is the coiling method.
Pay attention to the details, please.
Okay, that's it for today.
You all did a good job!
Just confess to him.
Huh?
Ga Eul, tell him before it's too late.
It's just that...
I'm afraid.
He's very different from me.
Love doesn't work if you hold back.
And it won't remain hidden
even if you try to hide it.
So...why did you break up with that person?
I wanted to stay with him,
the way he wanted me to.
But I couldn't.
I kept wanting more and it became too hard.
Did you confess your feelings to him?
I don't know.
Did I confess?
If you don't want to regret it later like me,
how about trying to be more courageous?
What is all this?
Hey!
Why does a student come home so late?
When school's over, you should
hurry up and come home.
Hey!
Did you bring all this here?
Oh, this?
I couldn't use it all
so I threw it away here.
Threw it away?
Anyway...
What's this smell?
Let's eat, let's eat, let's eat.
It looks so good.
Kang San, blow on it because it's hot.
What? Why?
Yours looks tastier.
I didn't cook it separately.
It's the same as that.
Give that to me.
Hurry up and hand it over!
Hey.
Hey. No!
This is so good!
Little brother, isn't there anymore?
I only ate one chopstick full because of you.
Hey, you guys are keeping this
delicious food all to yourselves?
That's a petty way to treat your neighbor.
Are you done eating?
Then leave. Go!
Little brother, do you have any more ramen?
What's up?
I don't like visitors coming over without a purpose.
I have a purpose.
Will you...
Will you go out on a date with me?
Date?
We did that before.
Not a fake one, but a real date.
Miss Ga Eul, did something shocking happen to you?
Or...
Did you get dumped by another guy?
I'm not kidding.
I...
I like you, Yi Jung sunbae.
Thanks.
Thanks, but...
I have a couple of rules when dating a woman.
Rules?
One, I won't date nice girls.
Two, I won't mess with foolish girls.
Three, I definitely don't get involved
with girls connected with my friends.
You know that all these rules apply to you, right?
My answer is no.
Sunbae...
You know the way out, right?
AHHH! WHAT IS THAT!
SOMEBODY SAVE ME!
WHAT THE HECK IS THAT!
WHAT IS THAT!
SOMEBODY SAVE ME!
DON'T COME HERE!
Hey, Gu Jun Pyo!
What's going on? Are you okay?
You little...
Hey! That...
Are you okay now?
I can't study because of your loud screaming.
You're a big nuisance to this neighborhood.
If you do it again, I'll call the police!
- Hey, Geum Jan Di.
- What? What now?
Can you... stay for a little while?
Unni.
Jan Di!
Why didn't tell me you moved?
How did you know?
I went to your house, but you weren't there,
so I asked Ga Eul.
Oh yeah. I heard about your parents.
Are you okay?
But what is all this?
They're housewarming gifts.
Housewarming gifts?
Chen, can you wait in the car?
Yes, Miss.
So this is what they call a rooftop house.
This is so romantic.
Sorry. If that offended you, I'm sorry.
That's not what I meant.
I know.
It's cold. So why don't
you've some tea before you go?
Is it okay?
Sure, sit there.
I can do that, right?
[Henri Matisse]
Is this a new way of interrupting someone's nap?
I didn't know you had an interest in art.
Oh, this?
I've to write a report on some art exhibition,
but it has ended now.
But the ticket was so expensive,
I probably couldn't afford to go anyway.
So I thought I would look at pictures
in this book and write it.
When is it due?
Huh?
Your homework, when is it due?
Information: no exhibition today
Come on in.
Do you like that?
No.
I'm fine with this.
By any chance, do you know the answer to this?
Why the lotus flowers blossom in mud?
What?
The young lady's face can
make muddy water clear.
Be sure to treasure her.
What?
That girl will give you a family.
Now you're using me as
a model without permission?
You're awake?
Had I known ahead of time,
I'd have kept a charge account.
What type of charge account?
To collect from Geum Jan Di,
the transportation fee, coffee fee,
performance admission fee, and modeling fee.
If I add it all up, it should be a hefty sum.
First. Here's your modeling fee.
You drew it so well,
that I might have to pay you.
Here.
They say that even though
lotus flowers bloom in mud,
they make the world clean and fragrant.
Their name is pretty, and so are their actions.
You are like that.
Huh?
Oh yes!
Homework solved!
Homework?
The more I see you, the more
I'm reminded of the lotus flower.
Lotus flower?
Do you know why the lotus flowers bloom in mud?
Huh?
That'll be your homework until next time!
I happily accept your present.
What about the witch?
She's still in Vancouver.
Please help me cover things up.
- Yes sir.
- Gu Jun Pyo!
- Please, you really can't do this...
- Please, you can't go in...
Gu Jun Pyo!
You again?
We definitely have some kind of a connection.
I suddenly felt that if I come here,
I would be able to see you.
Did you boil and eat
your cell phone or something?
Didn't you learn to call and get
permission before visiting someone?
Now that I think about it.
I don't remember ever
learning anything like that.
Jun Pyo, do you do that?
Hey, Monkey.
Aren't you gonna hurry and get up?
Why are you lying on someone else's bed?
Hurry and get up.
Get up, come on!
I said, get up!
Do you want make a bet with me?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: ahsieee, lilshinhwafreak
Spot Translators: saturn, javafiend, hjkomo
Timer: selvaspeedy
Editor/QC: jtranla
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
It worries me now that it's so quiet.
I just want to ask you one thing,
will you answer me?
Friendship or love.
If you had to choose between them,
which would you pick?
You're putting too much pressure on your wrist.
Yi Jung sunbae.
This...
Oh, that. It's quiet pretty, isn't it?
I think Jun Pyo hyung still likes you!
Don't you have anything more to report to me?
Yes?
Find out what's going on immediately.
This is Geum Jan Di,
who'll be staying here from today.
Where did you get an idiot
who doesn't even know the menu?
Please look kindly on me.
An exclusive... maid?
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get it for FREE @ d-addicts.com