Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Everything looks so yummy!
How about I buy something for you?
Where'd it go?
It's fine! I can still afford this.
How much?
Six for thirty.
Where are you from?
Korea.
Oh, what a lovely pair of newlyweds!
What?
This is free.
Oh, thank you!
You're welcome.
Thank you.
It's so good!
Thank you!
Bye bye.
Episode 15
What is this?
Excuse me. What is this?
This is a dragon amulet that
will bring good fortune.
It's a lucky dragon amulet.
Oh... an amulet.
Let's buy one.
My wallet!
What should I do?
Wait for me here.
Oh, Sunbae!
I'm sorry.
Can I borrow your guitar?
Why? You want to play?
I'm sorry. I will pay you with my egg tarts.
Can I borrow your guitar... just once?
- Okay.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
When I look toward you,
a thought suddenly appears.
Some day, I'll wait until the sky is clear,
Just as it was on the day you left.
You will quietly return to my side.
The you in my heart.
Can you really never see me again?
I'm really such an idiot,
you're the only one in my heart.
You, who have eyes for someone else,
You probably don't know how I feel.
Your day probably will not include me.
Not even your memories.
It's only me, the one watching you,
Who is silently crying.
Watching the shape of your
back is a kind of happiness to me.
Even though, to the very end,
you do not understand my heart.
When I want to see you,
At times when I really can't bear it,
The words "I love you"
are always lingering on my lips,
I am alone, crying for you.
I am alone, missing for you.
This is more than enough, right?
This rascal's probably acting up
now that we're in Macau.
Nope. I'll have to walk barefoot.
Let's go.
I'll give you a piggy-back ride.
What?
Or should I carry you?
No... that...
Okay.
- Thank you.
What is Sunbae thanking me for?
I should be the one saying thank you.
This is the first time in my life,
that I've earned my own money.
Right.
Because of you, I've experienced
many things for the first time.
So..
Thank you.
Bye bye, never say goodbye,
Although I cannot grab hold of you.
Let's just go back.
I need you. I cannot say anything.
Just a bit longer.
I want you.
Even if it's just wishing and wishing.
When I want to see you,
At times when I really can't bear it,
The words "I love you"
are always lingering on my lips,
I am alone, missing for you.
In the days when I really miss you,
The days when my heart aches,
Young master.
The words "I miss you"
always linger at my lips.
Let's go.
I am alone, crying for you.
I am alone, missing for you.
Baby I love you.
I'm waiting for you.
You didn't lock the door.
Geum Jan Di.
Hurry up and come out.
Are you planning on spending
the entire day in there?
Okay.
Then I'm going out for a bit first.
I'm going out.
Come out and eat.
[Memory erased.]
[Memory cleared.]
[18:00 flight to Seoul]
[Gu Jun Pyo.]
First?
This is first class?
Yes.
So expensive.
I can just take the normal one.
Hurry and return this.
Normal?
You mean... economy class?
I think it's too cramped for my legs,
so I can't ride in economy class.
What?
Long... they are long.
I can ride in economy class.
It's so hard to see Jae Kyung.
It's because that child is ever illusive.
We just verified it. It seems like she's
on her way back from Hong Kong.
We're truly sorry.
Making you wait so long when you're so busy.
Ahh, it's nothing.
What's more important than
letting the children meet?
Isn't that right, Jun Pyo?
Gu Jun Pyo.
Yes?
Ahh, yes, of course.
What's wrong?
The Singapore branch needs
the Young Master immediately.
What kind of occasion is this?
The prime minister...
It's fine.
They'll be able to meet very soon.
For an entrepreneur,
what is more important than business?
Go ahead.
Please excuse me.
This is...
Do you like them?
What is this?
I always wanted to use the first
money that I earned on my own
to buy you something.
Sunbae.
Why have you come?
I am not under any obligation to answer you.
You, on the other hand, why have you come?
Do you think you have the right to ask...
A question like that?
Yoon Ji Hoo!
Because I consider you my friend,
I backed off.
Because she's my friend's girl,
I stopped thinking about it.
And even to the very end,
I still gave you a chance.
From now on, I won't yield anymore.
You rascal.
Enough!
Why have you come?
Do you have something to say?
Okay.
I understand.
I'm leaving.
I'll be waiting for you.
I no longer want you
to see my painful tears.
You let me know.
A love like lies.
I won't give it up.
Because it's you.
Please look at me, like those stars.
Young Master.
Can you become the man in my heart?
Stand up.
I'll be waiting for you.
I no longer want you
to see my painful tears.
You let me know.
A love like lies.
I won't give it up.
Because it's you.
Come. Order up on the congee!
Please enjoy!
Miss.
This isn't abalone congee.
Oh, I'm sorry, madam.
I'll bring you some abalone
congee immediately.
I'm really very sorry.
I'm very sorry.
Sorry.
Ga Eul.
I must be really dumb.
I should get all my energy together
and figure out how I'll continue my life.
But I'm always creating trouble like this.
Jan Di.
Go deliver, take-out.
I'll go. I'll deliver it for her.
Where is it?
Jan Di. You go.
Once you deliver it, until he finishes it,
don't budge a single step from that place.
Then bring the bowl and
the chopsticks, understand?
Before he finishes, don't even think
about coming back to the shop.
We're done.
Please wait just a moment.
Okay, there's no problem
with your blood pressure.
Come... say ahhh.
The girl standing outside.
Me?
Don't just stand there. Come in and help.
Aren't you going to come in?
Can you not see that
the patients are waiting?
Okay.
You must be very cold.
Drink some hot water.
Thank you, miss, thank you.
- Yes, please drink some.
- Okay, okay.
Thank you so much!
- Thank you.
- Yes.
Say something!
Whenever I'm tired, lucky in my life
You come by my side like a dream.
Whenever I'm sad, lucky in my dream.
Look at this! This! What is this?
What is this?
You always warmly surround me.
Look, no more!
No matter when,
I will always smile like this.
No matter how many trials
there are in this world, I'll definitely
Never let you see my tears.
Even if you don't understand my heart.
Even if you're far away,
I'll still be happy
because of your smile.
Can you take a step closer to me?
This girl! If you want to sleep,
you should go home to sleep!
Oh, this.
Until you finish this, I can't go home.
Please enjoy.
Uh... Grandpa.
What exactly do you do?
How do you know our master?
Grandpa, you ARE a doctor, right?
You're not perhaps... practicing unlicensed?
Do I look like a quack?
Is that what you mean?
No, no... kind of.
Doctor Grandpa... my stomach!
Doctor! My stomach hurts!
- Come, come, Come, stand up.
- My stomach hurts! I'm going to die!
- Just bear it for a bit. You're here now.
- My stomach hurts.
Bear it a little while longer,
a little while.
There are guests here too?
Sunbae.
Here.
Are you extremely happy about something?
How could you tell?
It's written all over here.
Hold her hand! Hold on to her hand!
Okay.
Push once more.
We're almost there. One more time.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, that did it.
Okay, okay. Good, good.
Come, you've worked hard.
I gave birth to a child.
You did very well. Very well!
My baby is here.
Pretty, huh?
My entire body was trembling.
As if I gained insight to a world that
I hadn't been known to me until yesterday.
For the first time, whether
it was Jun Pyo, swimming..
I couldn't think of anything.
Other people might say I'm crazy.
A dummy like me, even if I say
I want to be a doctor,
people would still laugh at me, no?
Geum Jan Di...
You really have gone crazy.
You really are crazy.
You've found something that you'd
be willing to be called "crazy" for.
Do you know how difficult that is?
What does it matter what other people say?
When did Geum Jan Di started
to care about that too?
Sunbae.
If you want to do it, then go do it.
No matter how many years it takes?
No matter how many years it takes.
To Jan Di's newly-discovered dream..
Cheers!
This is only the beginning of
Shinhwa Group's leap forward.
Please look forward to it.
Jan Di?
I was right!
I heard you went to Macau
Truthfully...
I needed to clear things up with Gu Jun Pyo
so that I can continue living my life.
I think it was a good thing I went.
I've organized myself now.
I wanted you to be near our Jun Pyo...
That's unfortunate
Can you still think of me as an
older sister, despite Jun Pyo?
Yes, of course.
What happened?
Why are you a star and me a moon?
Geum Jan Di is a moon that can never
fall apart from the star Jun Pyo.
Even if something happens,
I'm not going to let this moon go.
It's okay.
Don't hold it in and just cry.
Just pour it out.
Unnie, I lied.
I'm not fine.
I went because I wanted to see Gu Jun Pyo.
But he's changed into a
completely different person...
that I can't believe it.
Jan Di.
Thank you.
I'm really happy that you've told me this.
Listen to me carefully.
Jun Pyo will definitely come back.
So don't give him up like this.
Believe me and give him another chance.
Can you do that for me?
Ga Eul!
[As the Shinhwa Group Executive Director
Gu Jun Pyo meets his 20th birthday]
[we will be holding an
elegant birthday party.]
[We ask that you to attend
and have your presence shine.]
[Place: H Hotel Grand Ballroom Hall.]
Jun Pyo sunbae's birthday party?
Yeah.
You want me to take Jan Di here?
Why? Why should I do that?
Jun Pyo sunbae, no that person,
dumped Jan Di.
There's just something that bothers me.
I just want to check up on it.
If something wrong happens,
it'll be Jan Di who'll be getting hurt.
Ga Eul.
Listen carefully.
If Jun Pyo leaving Jan Di is all an act,
then that's fortunate.
Even if he was being sincere,
it was something that Jan Di needed.
It's not just killing someone twice?
If it's a person you have to erase,
then it's better not to painfully
keep him in your heart.
Didn't I tell you that last time?
What's all this?
If you're going out to the battlefield,
you need weapons.
I don't want to. Why should I?
Are you seriously not going
to see him again?
Are you just going to end it like this?
He came back to Seoul.
It's his birthday. We can just
congratulate him and leave.
Do you really have nothing to say to him?
The part that hurts the most
isn't him ignoring me...
or not holding onto me until the end.
I didn't even get to say thank you.
I didn't even tell him I liked him.
The fact that I can't tell him that now.
Welc...
Hello, Geum Jan Di.
Hello. Maybe I help you?
Today is Young Master Jun Pyo's
birthday party.
Did Gu Jun Pyo send you here?
No.
Madame President eagerly
awaits your presence.
Madame President?
It's F4! They're really handsome.
You came.
I didn't want to run away so
I managed to come with my pride
But I feel like I shouldn't have come.
Geum Jan Di, you should at
least get something to eat.
If you cowardly leave by yourself,
Ga Eul will be fidgety all night.
Geum Jan Di, aren't you all about loyalty?
Aren't I right, Ga Eul?
For everyone who came tonight
to congratulate me,
my son Jun Pyo, and Shinhwa Group,
I welcome you wholeheartedly.
As you know, the reason why we've
managed to get by the toughest of times
is due to everyone who is here today.
Until the day Shinhwa becomes
the number one group,
I hope that we will still have your
undivided attention and interest.
Now I will introduce
today's man of the hour.
Shinhwa Group's future, my son Gu Jun Pyo.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear Jun Pyo.
Are you okay?
I think I should go soon.
I shouldn't have come in the first place.
It's been awhile, Geum Jan Di.
Thanks for responding to my invite.
Invite?
Since you are here,
is it okay if I ask you to sing
a birthday song for Jun Pyo?
What?
I know you as a smart young lady
who has been raised by excellent
parents with the right education.
It won't be impolite for me to ask you
to play a piano piece, would it?
That's impossible.
Can Geum Jan Di play piano?
She probably can't right?
I was wondering why she invited her.
She sure is something.
We were just about to...
I'll do it.
You invited me.
It's the least I can do for this meal.
Everyone, Geum Jan Di from Shinhwa High
will be performing for us.
Can we give her a round of applause?
The moment you stood by my side,
I love that look in your eye.
Yesterday I cried but today because of you,
Tomorrow I'll be happy.
It's not...
It's not your face...
It's not your style...
All I needed was your soft loving.
To forget all of my past...
Now I can't do anything without you...
I only know...
I only know about love.
I think I might have ruined the atmosphere
by asking for too much.
It shows that people should take
notice of their situation and know
when and when not to present themselves.
I apologize instead.
Everyone, you've waited for a long time.
Now I will make the most
important announcement,
one that holds the future of Shinhwa Group.
Important announcement?
At this moment,
the young lady who is my
son Gu Jun Pyo's fiance?
and will be the future head lady of
Shinhwa group is here in this room.
What? Fiance!?
What is that Witch saying?
Everyone, I'll introduce her to you.
The heiress to the worldwide
investment company,
JK Group, Han Jae Kyung.
Let me go! Let me...
Don't you know I hate this kind of thing?
What are you talking about engagement?
Let me go!
I'll go myself. Hey!
Shoes?
You!
Engaged?
Can't believe it's JK Group.
It's so like Jun Pyo's mother.
Is it that great?
It's Korean-based, but it's an investment
company that contributes to ones in America.
It's not only investment,
but also oil fields and resorts.
It's a global company that has everything.
I should have known when they were in Macau.
I thought you guys were just
a bunch of trouble makers,
but you analyzed it correctly.
Now do you understand?
The spot to become Shinhwa Group's
head lady has to be filled
with that kind of reputation, or nothing.
What kind of scheme do you have now?
What's this sudden engagement?
And why are you here?
Do you think I wanted to come here?
I invited her.
What?
It's an introduction to
the wife of the future.
As a friend, she should come to
congratulate you, don't you think?
Are you stupid?
Where do you think this is that you
just show because you were called?
Jun Pyo.
Don't do this here,
but go somewhere and talk.
I have nothing to say to Gu Jun Pyo.
You're finally beginning to
understand the situation.
What would you have to say to a
man who has a fiance?
Um... about that engagement...
It's not like this is some surprise show...
Are you being serious?
I'm sorry for surprising you,
but it has already been discussed
with your parents.
But this is the first time
I'm hearing about it.
Hey shoes!
Be quiet.
And you.
You have nothing to say to me?
Well, I do.
So just shut your mouth and follow me.
You still don't know after
suffering that much?
It's about time for you know that
it's a trap when the Witch calls you out.
Hey wait...
How come there's no growth in your learning
abilities even when you're one year older?
How could you come so easily when the Witch,
not even me, called you out?
Hey wait!
Isn't it obvious that she was
trying to torture us both?
I don't understand what kind of girl
falls into every trap laid out for her.
Hey! CURLY HAIR!
What? Curly hair? Now you're...
Do you understand that now
you have to get rid
of your false expectations and hopes?
I'm glad that there was a good
result in inviting you today.
Then...
Jan Di.
Is that person...
What's wrong with him?
Is he really marrying her?
I'll take Ga Eul home.
Ji Hoo.
Let's meet later at the lounge.
I'll try to figure out what's
just happened until then.
Why are you here?
You dragged me here.
So why did you get dragged here?
I knew that you were a weird
person since Macau,
but you really are strange punk!
What? Punk?
If you have eyes, take a look.
I'm wearing a backless dress
in the middle of winter
And I'm getting dragged everywhere barefoot.
Shouldn't you be saying sorry first?
So who told you to follow me?
Who are you saying followed you?
Okay then.
Keep going your way then.
If you follow me again, I'll kill you.
That little... HEY!
What's this? Hey!
Say you're sorry, you jerk!
Aren't you going to come down?
Apologize! Hurry!
Apologize!
This crazy monkey!
You better come down.
What did you just do?
But... why is your face so red.
What's this...? Do you...
Shut up and go away.
Why does this girl keep bothering me
after I told her to leave me alone?
What?
Give me some money.
What money?
I need to at least catch a cab.
Don't you see that because of
you I came out with nothing?
I don't have any.
I don't have any money.
Your cell phone.
Cell phone?
Hey!
What are you doing?
Where do you think you're touching?
What's wrong with you?
What's this?
Let me go.
Do you know who I am?
Are you okay, Miss?
Let me go!
Are you in that much shock?
Huh?
Jun Pyo's engagement.
No.
It doesn't matter if he's engaged or not.
You know that better than I do.
Jun Pyo probably didn't know either.
If it was true about the engagement,
He would have at least told us about it.
No...
That girl...
is someone Gu Jun Pyo knows.
How do you know?
I've seen her before, in Macau.
I'll be going now.
Geum Jan Di.
The thing I told Jun Pyo in Macau.
I know.
It was just something you said
because you were mad at him.
You're right.
Nothing's wrong with me.
Don't worry.
Geum Jan Di.
Sometimes the things you
see might not be real.
Some things...
Are visible only through faith.
I'll just be going.
I can go alone.
Sleep well.
Good bye.
Yoon Ji Hoo,
What are you doing?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: asiandreamer117, lilshinhwafreak
Spot Translators: Javafiend, CheshireKiwi, meju
Timer: Zealousy
Editor/QC: puela
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
- I found him!
- Why is that girl here?
It was a piece that Queen Elizabeth liked.
Thank You! If I use this as our Leon's dish,
he'll definitely be really happy!
I've seen plenty of women before, but it's
the first time I've seen someone like her.
Now let's get our emergency plan going.
Emergency plan?
It's interesting.
What is?
The way you do everything wholeheartedly.
Ji Hoo!
What?
You're doing what with Yi Jung?
Date.
I bet you don't know that Yi Jung's
nickname is 5-second kill.
5-second kill?
NO!
So what do you want me to do?
Jun Pyo is in the hotel right now?
I keep getting greedy... What do I do?
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get this for FREE @ d-addicts.com