Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Young Master.
You need to wake up, Young Master.
You need to wake up now.
Young Master.
Young Master!
I said you need to wake...!
Hey, just what are you doing?
5 minutes.
Let me stay like this for just 5 minutes.
Then I'll wake up.
Even though I'm holding you like this,
I can't believe that you're here.
Hey, Jun, I'm here.
We...
Jan Di.
What's going on here?
That's...
I mean, there's...
Jae Kyung.
Waking our Jun Pyo isn't easy.
Already?
Hold on. You?
How are you here...?
In that attire...?
Speak.
Exactly who was it?
Who was the insolent fool
who brought you into this house?
That would be me.
Grandma...
Grandma, why are you...?
It's been a while, My Lady.
No, I should address you as "President" now.
I guess I'm not used to it yet.
What's going on here?
You haven't forgotten, have you?
Under the wishes of the late President,
the administration of personnel
in this estate is under my jurisdiction.
In addition, that contract can't be
voided by The Lady or anyone else.
The fact that you're present,
Grandma, is not an issue.
But why is that child here?
I cannot allow for an instant
someone like that in my house.
Remove her immediately!
I cannot do that.
Grandma!
It is within my authority to employ her.
The same goes for dismissing her.
I do not think that this is a process
that you may take part in, President Kang.
Moreover...
While that child may
be inexperienced in many ways,
I think that it's another
reason to not dismiss her yet.
This elderly gentlewoman's apprentice
being so unsatisfactory,
could this austered household's
dignity still stands?
Grandma!
What are you doing?
Jan Di, hurry up and follow me.
There are mountains of work to get through.
Yes, Madam.
Thank you very much.
I didn't do that to receive your gratitude.
Don't misunderstand.
Excuse me?
I didn't do that because
of Miss Jun Hee's request.
Even after leaving this house,
I would always worry about
Young Master Jun Pyo.
He always had such a delicate nature.
But I couldn't prevent him from
becoming more violent as he grew up.
I heard something similar
from Seo Hyun unni a while back.
That Young Master...
He has changed.
I believe that it was because of you.
I have a great debt to this household.
And I live believing that assisting Young Master
as best as possible is my life's final mission.
I'm in my 80's.
My one pride is my great eye for people.
Even now, all I can do
is trust that instinct.
Sunbae-nim...
Don't we...
need to have a talk?
You look very pretty.
I didn't realize that a
maid outfit could be this pretty.
Unni...
I...
I know.
It must have been hard to tell me.
I know your circumstances.
If you think about it, it's not
something that I wouldn't have understood.
I'm sorry.
But...
wasn't I your friend before
I was Jun Pyo's fiancée?
It would have been nice if you
talked about it with your friend beforehand.
I'm sorry.
But please don't misunderstand.
I won't misunderstand.
But I'll also say one thing.
I won't give up Jun Pyo.
No, starting now,
I'm going to really give it my all.
I'm going to do my best
so I don't have any regrets.
I just wanted to tell you, Jan Di.
I'm going now.
Yes?
Jae Kyung.
Don't have any unnecessary impressions.
You saw earlier so you know.
All this was because that
Grandma just did as she...
No.
Please don't worry about it.
That's such a relief.
This is why I like you, Jae Kyung.
I will do something about
that child immediately so...
Please don't do that.
I would appreciate it
if you just left Jan Di alone.
Jae Kyung.
Also, I have one more request.
We'll end class here today.
Thank you for your hard work.
What is it?
Do you have something
you want to talk to me about?
Ah, no.
Teacher.
How did you break up with him?
It's me.
I'm heading over now.
I know.
If you eat it all and don't leave me any,
I'll really get angry.
Okay.
This isn't working.
I'm not doing this.
Alright, alright.
One more time.
I'll teach you properly.
Yeah?
Yi Jung?
Yeah.
Been well?
I've been well.
Hey, you!
Don't you miss me?
Even if you're busy,
you should really put in some face time.
Sorry.
Listening to your voice...
You sound like something good happened.
Yeah.
Stop by sometime if you're curious.
There's someone you need to
meet and I need to tell you something.
Someone I need to meet?
You'll be really surprised.
And really delighted.
Feel free to look forward to it,
little brother.
- Hyung.
- Hm?
You...
You're happy, right?
Yeah.
Sorry that I'm happy by myself.
Yi Jung?
Hey, Monkey...
What is all that?
Everyone, I look forward to being with you.
Starting today, I will be learning
"proper wife etiquette" here.
I'm Ha Jae Kyung.
What?
President.
Oh?
Is it ready?
Jun Pyo-Jae Kyung wedding invitation
What is this?
I spoke with Jae Kyung's parents
and we decided to move your wedding up.
You're both already adults.
And honestly,
for our companies' business together,
it's better for the wedding to
be held as soon as possible.
Is it okay to do this
without even asking us?
I agreed.
What?
Jae Kyung will be living
with us until the wedding.
She'll pick up the way our family runs.
And Jae Kyung's parents gave special
permission because we were moved
by her dedication to prepare in becoming
the next mistress, so that's that.
And one more thing.
Chief Jung.
Yes.
Young Master and Lady Jae Kyung.
The two of you will be featured
in the new Shinhwa's phone commercial.
What?
On who's whim?
The images of you two from that
last launching show were so wonderful
that the web and magazines just couldn't
stop their praises. Didn't you know?
The results from our PR
department's analysis shows
You two are the best models who will
appeal to our products' high-class image.
Jae Kyung.
It's some extra work,
but you can assist us, right?
I would be more than happy.
I can't accept this.
Jun Pyo.
Give and take.
You know that fundamental
rule of business, correct?
Will you come to my room for a bit?
How do I look?
Pretty.
Incredibly pretty.
My mother gave me this.
She said it's over 20 years old,
but it's still wearable, right?
I'm thinking about just wearing this.
Oh!
Come look at this too.
She said she won't give me pearls yet.
She's saving those for
when I have my first child.
My mother's getting really
ahead of herself, huh?
But isn't it really funny to think about?
A child resembling Gu Jun Pyo
and Ha Jae Kyung.
Jan Di.
I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Promise me that you'll do it first.
Be my maid of honor.
Huh?
It can't be anyone else.
I'd like for you to do it.
You'll do it, right?
Full shot. Take one.
Hey.
Paste bait won't work in winter.
Use worms.
This one's been broken in.
Take it with you.
Would you like to go?
I'll leave in 10 minutes.
Hey Ji Woo...
No wait, that's right...
Your mother was really good
at making maeuntang.
Today is their...
Your parents'...
Wedding anniversary.
I can still see it clearly.
She received that from your grandmother
and had such a smile on
her face as she put it on.
I asked her what was so
great about getting an old ring.
"It's the only one in the world.
Why wouldn't it be great?"
She said.
Child.
I'm sorry.
I took that mother away from you.
It was my stubbornness.
For you who have been chosen.
Shinhwa Call.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
My head's so muddled.
It's like a bomb went off in there.
What should I do?
What can I do?
You need to find out.
That answer...
You need to find that on your own.
If it was like old times,
the answer in this situation
would have definitely been to get married.
How did we turn into guys
who have to worry about the obvious answer?
In any case,
we're suddenly gonna be groomsmen.
You alright?
What?
You know what.
Jan Di.
This time, it's actually marriage.
You know marriage isn't like
meeting for a couple of months
then breaking up
or anything like that.
That's their future.
That's the spot Gu Jun Pyo needs to fill.
Yeah, Mom.
Dad.
You're all doing well, right?
San as well?
What?
You need to eat well.
You can't get ill.
Geez, really.
Yeah.
Don't worry about me.
I'm saying to please take care of yourself.
Don't be so miserly.
Eat some meat.
You got it?
Yeah.
Yes, Grandpa?
Now?
Oh, I'm sor...
What are you doing here?
What are you doing here, Sunbae?
Grandpa called me...
Grandpa also called me...
Ah. What the?
Geez, what is this?
Excuse me.
What's going on right now?
Oh, it's a wedding picture couple contest.
They're tallying points with stickers
and the cutest couples get a prize.
And you get to wear a
wedding dress for free.
Prize?
I'm saying to please take care of yourself.
Don't be so miserly.
Eat some meat.
1st Place, Jeju Do trip,
2nd Place, Healthy Beef Set,
3rd Place Acne Treatment Machine
I'm bored.
Wanna try it?
Huh?
Let's go.
Now, keep smiling and
maintain your poses. OK.
One, two...
It's an F4!
The next two!
OK, that's good.
One... oh, a little more, a little more.
And a little more naturally.
Get into the mood. OK!
That's good.
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Oh, Sunbae!
Excuse me but it's just that
we have no reason to go to Jeju Island.
Could we exchange prizes?
Of course we can.
- Thank you very much.
- Please take it, Oppa.
Thank you.
Here.
Sunbae!
You really...!
Thank you, thank you.
To all passengers, we will shortly
be arriving at Jeju International Airport.
Please secure all table
trays and fasten your seatbelts.
Are you OK?
A day like this actually does come.
Jan Di came with us.
Do you guys think that
any of this makes sense?
Be it the monkey who asks
her to be the maid of honor,
or the girl who agrees to do it?
Right now, who do you think
is having the most difficult time?
Jan Di.
You came.
You actually came.
Thanks.
I know.
That Jun Pyo and you
really liked each other.
Unni...
No.
Even now,
I can't tell if you still
really like each other.
I'm sorry for pretending that I didn't know.
I'm not usually like that,
but Jan Di, I was a little
cowardly towards you.
No, that's not it.
It's because I couldn't
be honest and tell you.
Well,
it's not that you didn't want to.
You couldn't.
Also,
even if you had told me,
I doubt anything would have been different.
I...
probably couldn't have given up Jun Pyo.
like you very much.
If someone asked me to pick the
two most precious people to me,
it would be Gu Jun Pyo and Geum Jan Di.
Unni.
That's why I'm really sorry.
For making your heart ache,
I'll die trying to make it up to you.
Forgive me.
Hey, Jun Pyo!
Stop already and come over here!
Keep it up and you're gonna collapse.
Who knows, he may be
trying to really collapse.
Can we really leave him like that?
How did you break up
with that person?
I don't know.
How do you think we broke up?
A while back, you asked me
if I confessed to him?
I did confess to him.
I tightly packed up more than
10 years of fighting with myself,
and just once, I mustered some
courage. On Valentine's Day.
Believing that if it were destined,
my sincerity would be understood,
it seemed as if I risked everything.
So what happened?
I wasn't able to reach that person.
My heart, that is.
The really amazing thing was,
after doing that,
my heart completely emptied.
Like the low tide receding.
I thought "So, it's only to here".
That moment that I let him go,
I felt liberated.
Like solving a math problem
after working on it for a long time,
I felt refreshed.
And you weren't hurt?
Because I did everything,
without any regrets,
it didn't hurt.
So Ga Eul, you too should do everything
so that you don't have any regrets.
Strolling through a field of flowers.
Isn't the situation too urgent for that?
At this day and age, to suddenly
have a marriage of convenience?
It doesn't seem like reality.
In our world,
well, it's nothing to be surprised about.
Sunbae,
do you also accept this
kind of future as a given?
I don't know.
This future or that future,
there seems to be no difference.
With only one life to live,
how can you be so irresponsible?
Sunbae, because you're like this,
no one can stay with you.
Now that you know a little about
my family, my weaknesses,
you think that you know everything?
Why didn't you meet her?
3 years ago, on Valentine's Day.
It's cold.
Let's go somewhere inside.
Today may be the very last day.
Jun Pyo.
If you want to hold on to him,
there's no more time left.
Since getting to know you,
I've wished for only one thing.
That you'll be happy and not cry anymore.
Like the first time we met in the stairwell,
smiling brightly.
After tomorrow, you may not smile anymore.
So I'm afraid.
Don't worry.
I'll be able to smile.
I will smile.
Because Sunbae...
Sunbae will be watching me.
I must have been out in the wind too long.
My eyes are watering.
That's OK.
Sunbae, because you
keep wiping them away,
they're losing their discipline
and have no backbone.
Oh, you scared me!
What are you doing?
Who says I did anything?
But this woman...
It's useless to play so hard to get.
Because in any event,
as of tomorrow, you'll be mine.
Yours? Who will be yours?
Stop being so cranky
and come downstairs.
Our parents are waiting.
Ah, yes.
As of tomorrow, we will
truly become one family.
That's true.
For Shinhwa and JK,
and also for our children's happiness,
shall we make a toast?
How far are you willing to go?
Noona!
When did you arrive?
No need to happily greet me,
because I didn't come for your wedding.
I know. I'm pathetic, aren't I?
Gu Jun Pyo.
I asked how far you are willing to go.
How far does it have to be?
Everything.
Family, Shinhwa Group.
And maybe, even the name "Gu Jun Pyo".
I couldn't do it.
After throwing everything away,
what would Gu Jun Hee be?
To live as nothing but one man's woman?
I didn't have the courage to do that.
Noona.
That one moment of cowardice
made things very difficult for me.
I thought that I could forget.
But I couldn't.
Do you still feel that
sorry for that person?
No.
He's not the one I feel sorry for.
It's the 20-year old Gu Jun Hee
whom I thought
would always be dignified
and innocent.
Little brother,
whatever you decide, I'll understand.
And wherever you go or whatever you do,
you'll always be my beloved little brother,
Gu Jun Pyo.
And that truth won't change.
Ji Hoo.
Say it.
You're a brother to me.
You were in the past.
And going forward, you will be too.
I sometimes thought...
that you probably could
live just fine without me.
But how would I be without you?
Surely,
you're not gonna ask
me to help you
run away from the ceremony
tomorrow, are you?
Hit me once.
What?
I'm not joking.
I should be hit by you.
Jun Pyo.
Jan Di...
I don't think that I can let go of her.
Which one seems better?
This one? If not, then this one?
They're all pretty.
You can't say that!
You have to tell the bride,
100% dispassionately and honestly.
Saying that you like
everything is of no help.
I'm sorry.
But honestly, they're all pretty.
I have something to tell you.
Bride Ha Jae Kyung,
do you swear to take groom Gu Jun Pyo
as your husband, in good times and in bad,
to cherish and love forever?
I do.
Groom Gu Jun Pyo, do you swear
to take Bride Ha Jae Kyung as your wife,
in sickness and in health,
to cherish and love forever?
I can't.
I can't do it.
Gu Jun Pyo.
This is just a game.
Why are you so serious?
It's not a game, Monkey.
No.
Ha Jae Kyung,
You can't get married to me.
Jun...
I'm sorry.
Saying "I'm sorry" is enough?
Then in this world,
why do you think there are laws and police?
There's a woman I love.
My first since I was born.
And until I die,
she'll be the only one for me.
Knowing that, do you still want to marry me?
Are you crazy?
I know that the woman is Geum Jan Di.
But...
I want that part of you even more.
It might be laughable but I like that
you're sincere and whole-hearted.
And because you're someone who
knows what love truly is.
I like you even more.
That rival being Geum Jan Di...
I can tolerate it.
I'm sure that it won't
be easy to forget her.
However,
if I wait...
if I wait and see,
then wouldn't the next time
be a chance for me?
You can love me like that.
Ha Jae Kyung.
That'll be enough.
I see there's more than enough
value in that investment.
Gu Jun Pyo.
Forgive me.
No.
Listen carefully.
Tomorrow, in this place,
we're going to become husband and wife.
Whatever the past may be,
for the rest of our lives until we die,
we're going to promise to love each other.
Therefore, even though
you beg me to forgive you,
there's nothing for me to forgive.
It's gotten late so quickly.
Because of the make-up tomorrow,
they begged me to go to sleep early.
I'll leave first.
Jun Pyo!
It's time.
We should head down now.
Woo Bin.
I need a favor.
What is it?
Just break my arm.
What?
Jun Pyo.
There's no time.
With your skill, one blow should do it.
Are you serious?
What are you doing right now?
Don't worry about it. Go outside.
All that thinking and
this was the best you could do?
If this is the only way that
you can stop the wedding,
then maybe it's better that you go.
Geum Jan Di.
You're being a coward.
You're not being dignified
in front of anyone.
You're not confronting, you're running away!
If you run away like this,
someday, everything will happen again.
Then tell me not to do it.
Tell me not to go!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: CheshireKiwi, Javafiend
Spot Translator: meju
Timer: julier
Editor/QC: annchong
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Cut! OK.
Talk!
- We have to shoot it again.
- Do I have to go up to there?
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, please.
My shoulder is slippery so...
Did I fall asleep?
Did you shoot that?
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get it for FREE @ D-addicts.com