Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
I was wondering how I was
going to bother Gu Jun Pyo,
but an offer came up where I was
catching two birds with one stone.
Who put you up to this?
And why?
Isn't it funny just imagining it?
Gu Jun Pyo got so furious after
he got his girl stolen by me,
but when he finds out that
his mom paid me to do it...
Mom?
The person who ordered this to
happen is Gu Jun Pyo's mother?
If you had only agreed with me,
I was going to give you half my money.
You should have done better.
What's that supposed to mean?
The moment you rejected my proposal,
the goal of this game
became only Gu Jun Pyo.
Why are you doing this to Gu Jun Pyo?
Why?
Everyone here probably have at
least three to four reasons
why they want to take
revenge on Gu Jun Pyo.
You want to hear all of them?
Tell the truth!
Why are you doing this to Gu Jun Pyo!
And tell me what Gu Jun Pyo did to you!
To be exact...
He wronged my brother.
Brother?
Do you remember?
My older brother who was more loving to his
despised half-brother than my own father.
Jan Di sunbae,
Take a good look at me.
Don't I remind you of someone?
This isn't a school. It's hell.
NO!
No way...
The rooftop?
Bingo.
I'll tell him how you're doing.
Although he's gotten very
weak from what happened.
He still smiles when he talks about you.
You!
That's right.
I wanted revenge.
But...
As I got closer to you,
I thought if you came to me,
revenge wouldn't matter.
I had thoughts like this.
I was really like that...
Go in already!
Geum Jan Di! Are you okay?
Shut up!
Gu Jun Pyo! Gu Jun Pyo!
Geum Jan Di, you're okay right?
Nothing happened right?
Gu Jun Pyo.
Why did you come?
What are you going to do by coming here!
Did you check?
Yeah, he's all alone.
Idiot with no fears.
I bet you didn't know it was
your death day today.
Let the girl go.
Even though you're going to die soon,
you still have to act cool.
Too bad, that's not going to work out.
You're going to be drenched in blood and
unable to move a finger because of someone.
The female protagonist has to keep her
eyes open and watch such a momentous scene.
Don't you think so?
Start.
Gu Jun Pyo...
Stop it!
Gu Jun Pyo!
Stop! Stop! Stop it!
Save him! Someone save him!
Gu Jun Pyo! Gu Jun Pyo!
Stop.
Does it hurt?
Now start begging to live.
Try getting on your knees and cry.
No... Gu Jun Pyo. Don't do it.
Don't do it!
Gu Jun Pyo.
STOP IT!
Now say that you're going
to give up Geum Jan Di.
Hurry up and say it.
I don't think that's possible.
What?
What are you deaf?
I said that's not possible.
Do you want to die?
I don't want to die.
But if you're going to kill me,
what can I do.
Say it.
Hurry up and say it!
Geum Jan Di.
Jun Pyo! Gu Jun Pyo!
Geum Jan Di!
Gu Jun Pyo.
Go outside.
Jun Pyo, are you okay?
Geum Jan Di... Jan Di...
Geum Jan Di.
Are you awake?
Gu Jun Pyo.
You idiot.
I thought I was going to
die of shock because of you.
I should be saying that.
You're the real idiot.
Why did you just take the hits?
You said you could take on
ten guys like that and be fine.
Such a liar.
Idiot. Stupid.
Double-digit-IQ dummy
What?
How could I do that when you were captured?
I'd rather have my ribcage broken,
than have those guys touch even your finger.
But when I was purposely
getting beaten to death for you,
why did you butt in?
What if something horrible had happened?
You and your nosiness.
Idiot. Stupid.
Double-digit-IQ dummy.
What?
HEY!
You're always beating patients!
You're always hitting girls!
I'm in pain!
I'm in pain too!
You're always hitting girls...
You're always beating up girls
when you get the chance!
I'm home...
What are we going to do?
What's this?
What happened?
What's all this?
Kang San, stop crying and explain!
The loan sharks took Dad.
What?
Jan Di, what are we going to do?
What if your dad dies?
If we don't pay our debts, they said
they were going to sell his organs.
What if your dad dies?
What are we going to do about your dad?
May I help you?
Yes... I came to see Madam President.
Come this way.
Madam President.
What is your business?
Help us, please.
What are you talking about?
The offer you gave us...
No, even a quarter of that is even fine.
Please save our family.
No matter how hard I thought,
the only person to save our family
was you, Madam President Kang.
So I shamelessly came here.
That doesn't sound like a hard thing.
But in business, there's such a thing
as an orderly procedure.
An orderly procedure?
Wrongs must be apologized for,
debts repaid, and
then help rendered.
I'm a businesswoman,
so I cannot abide
calculations and procedures
that are not conducted properly.
Yes, that must be done.
Last time, I did something
that was a deadly sin.
I apologize for insulting you
without knowing my place.
Please forgive me.
Ma'am, please don't...
Please forgive me!
I was wrong.
Forgive me, please, forgive me.
Thank you.
I'm home...
Dad!
Yeah, Jan Di.
Are you okay? Everything's okay, right?
Of course! It's okay.
That's a relief. I was so worried!
Why is everyone like this?
Dad came back safely...
Did someone die?
Could this be...
It's not could it... it is.
Mom.
What? Should I have left your father to die?
Where were we going to get
this much money immediately?
I said to return the money.
What?
Return it!
No. I can't.
Do you know how I got this money?
And if we return this money, what are
we going to do about the aftermath?
I'll fix it.
I did this to us, so I'll fix it.
I'll do whatever it takes
to repay everything!
Jan Di, take this back.
What are you going to and how?
I said to return it!
If you disobey my words...
then... you're on your own!
It's cold.
You didn't even wear your jacket.
Here.
Hurry.
Jan Di...
Yeah?
You...
Really like Jun Pyo, don't you?
Answer me.
You’re more important, Dad.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for being a burden
on my pretty daughter's love.
Who said anything about love, Dad.
It's love.
This is love, Jan Di.
That makes him as dear a
person to you as your dad.
If I’m not sure of that myself,
how can you know?
I’ve been Dad to my pretty daughter
for 19 years, how could I not know?
Dad!
Madam President.
Geum Jan Di is here to see you.
Oh really?
Welcome. What business do
you have with me?
I came to return the money.
I heard your situation was hard.
Don't you think it's wiser to
not let your pride get in the middle of it?
It's not pride, but the
decision my family made.
Sorry for the trouble.
I can give you more if
the amount is too little.
After seeing you for awhile, you seem
to be skilled in business transactions.
I'm for it. Let's do it.
Let's make a deal.
From now on, please stop
insulting my family or me.
I'm asking you.
What's this?
Then are you really going
to date my Jun Pyo?
That...
Is a matter between Jun Pyo and me,
just the two of us.
All right.
Let's be more honest with each other.
I'll admit that I have made things
troublesome for you and your family.
So you should just accept that
you and Jun Pyo are not suitable.
Yes.
Jun Pyo and I are so different,
I'll admit that.
But, do you know this?
We're both standing at the same place,
and looking at the same thing.
I made a promise with Gu Jun Pyo that we
wouldn't break up because of you.
This money is the price of your mother
kneeling down in front of me.
Are you going to just throw all that away
because of your thoughtless pride?
This is an unprecedented opportunity for
the price of a worthless common family.
Don't you think you'll regret it?
I didn't know pride had a price.
Then, how much is your pride?
Unbelievable...
I hope you can change the belief that
you can buy a commoner's pride.
And you can't buy a person's heart, either.
Madam President don't know that, do you?
But Gu Jun Pyo does now.
That's all...
Isn't it funny just imagining it?
Gu Jun Pyo got so furious after
he got his girl stolen by me,
But when he finds out that
his mom paid me to do it...
You called 911?
I came to put out the fire.
They're hotcakes.
You need to make it with flour, eggs,
and of course baking powder.
When you're sad, this does wonders.
I ate well.
Then should we get going?
Where?
Hey, make your legs straight
Yeah, like that.
Hey you idiot!
Stupid.
You're so stupid.
It's F4! It's F4
Isn't that... Geum Jan Di?
Let us hurry and tell Jinju!
(Ginger's real Korean name)
What's that?
It's nothing.
What do you mean nothing?
Hey!
I smell whiffs of a proposal
when I look at it.
What do you mean proposal?
She keeps going off and
getting into trouble
that I felt that I should give
her a collar or something.
Is Geum Jan Di a pet?
But I worry that with your personality,
you won't be able to
deliver it well to Geum Jan Di.
Well he says it's a collar and Geum Jan Di
is not one to take that well.
Maybe we'll see another spin-kick soon.
Geum Jan Di's kick of death?
Now that I think about it,
I do miss it a little.
Can you guys knock it off?
You're so annoying.
A playing fee.
I was going to turn the pages for you,
but you didn't have any sheet music.
Instead, want to do an errand for me?
Hey, Yoon Ji Hoo!
Why do you call a person out into
the cold and treat me like a dog!
Gu Jun Pyo?
Geum Jan Di.
Here.
It's cold. Wear this.
You... put your hand deep
in here and stay still.
There's something in here.
What's this?
Can't you tell? It's a necklace.
Hey! This isn't right!
I know your taste is unique
but this is totally a girl's!
You idiot...
It's yours.
What?
There's only one like it in the world,
so if you lose it,
you’re really dead this time.
Only one?
Yeah.
Is there really only one?
Because I personally designed it.
Look carefully.
This is I.
And the one inside is you.
Why's that?
Why are you the star and I'm the moon?
Because Geum Jan Di
is the moon, which can never escape
from the Gu Jun Pyo star.
Because whatever may happen,
I'm not going to let go of this moon.
See!
Did something out of character
and you caught a cold.
It's not that I caught a cold.
I just sneezed.
It's cold.
Look over there...
Look at all the twinkling lights!
Isn't that a satellite?
It's pretty.
It really is a one of a kind necklace.
Isn't it a bit too romantic?
Romantic or whatnot,
I hear that and bam! I feel burdened.
Oh, what if I lose it already?
I'm so worried I could die.
- Geez, such happy worries.
- What?
Hey! If someone, saying
"I made it especially for you",
and gave me a one of a kind token of love,
even if it were a piece of glass,
I would be so happy.
- Let's go.
- Where to?
What to you mean "where to"?
We have to go ski.
Let's go!
Oh... my... God...
What did she just say?
A one of a kind necklace?
And she got it from Jun Pyo!
Oh, I can't stand this.
I absolutely can't stand this!
Girls, do you think a girl like Geum Jan Di
has a right to get something like that?
No way!
I'm not like this because it isn't me.
Don't you think Geum Jan Di
is just intolerable?
Yeah!
Girls, go on.
Geum Jan Di, you're so dead.
Oww, my stomach hurts...
Jan Di!
Are you OK?
Go on ahead!
Oh, Geum Jan Di!
I didn't know that it was you.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm alright.
Are you OK?
Yeah, I'm OK.
You should be careful.
Are you OK?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
You should be careful!
Be careful!
Are you OK?
You should be careful.
- I'm fine.
- Are you OK?
Get up.
Are you OK?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
It's all right, go. I'm fine.
OK, we're off then.
See ya!
Jan Di, are you OK?
Yeah, I'm fine.
How about you?
Oh, Ga Eul!
Ga Eul, look out!
Ga Eul, are you OK?
Wake up!
Do you hear me?
Ga Eul!
Ga Eul...
Are you OK?
Honey, about that...
Fine, I take responsibility for it.
So don't you say anything.
Understand?
What's important now isn't you or me!
Are you just going to
give up Shinhwa like this?
Given how your father built...
Honey...?
Honey?!
Madam President...
The situation is not good.
Jun Pyo...
For now, please find Jun Pyo.
He needs to fly over there
with me immediately.
I understand.
Here, this has more chocolate.
Jan Di...
Where's your necklace?
The necklace is...
The necklace!
Hey...
Where could the necklace be...?
What's with you guys?
Sunbae, by any chance, did you
give Geum Jan Di a necklace?
How do you guys know about that?
A moon within a star...
that's right, isn't it?
I asked how you guys knew that!
You should ask Geum Jan Di
if she still has it.
What?
Not sure if she dropped it or threw it away,
but she probably lost it
on the mountain earlier.
How can she so carelessly lose your heart?
They say that one thing reveals ten more.
Geum Jan Di takes Sunbae for granted... Oww!
Geum Jan Di, now you're dead!
Did you lose something?
Huh?
Uh... I just wanted to organize my stuff.
The necklace... Why aren't you wearing it?
The necklace...?
The thing is...
Gu Jun Pyo, I'm sorry.
I definitely had it on.
I don't know when I lost it.
I really don't know.
And it's not that you wanted to lose it?
What?
You do this every time.
Whenever I try to get closer to you.
You trample on my heart like it’s nothing.
Do I still mean so little to you?
Gu Jun Pyo, don't misunderstand!
It's really not like that.
- It's really not...
- A girl like you...
really knows how to wear a person out.
Idiot!
Moron!
Dummy!
Die!
Hey, Geum Jan Di!
Do you know how expensive that piece was?
I got you a one of a kind...
What's this?
We have an order from Madam
President to bring you home immediately.
Don't want to.
Young Master, the President...
I don't care what the
Evil Witch said, I'm not going.
Convey that to her.
Let go.
- You won't let go?
- I'm sorry.
Young Master, the President...
I said I'm not going!
I said I'm not going.
Let's go.
Better let go.
This is breaking news.
Due to the heavy snowstorm in
the Kyunggi Kangwon area,
all roads and transportation
have been shut down.
We've got a big problem!
Ga Eul!
What's the matter now?
Jan Di...
Jan Di went up the mountain...
As soon as I find the necklace,
I'll be back. -Jan Di-
Necklace?
Where's Jun Pyo right now?
Privacy.
A note to the driver for
privacy to not listen to his call.
Yo...
Some irritating matter came...
What?
I need to use the restroom.
Geum Jan Di!
By any chance, did you
lose a star necklace?
How did you know that?
So it was yours...
Do you want me to tell you where it is?
A cabin cafe worker picked
it up during the day
and left a memo saying he'll hold onto it
Go and see.
Really?
Where do I need to go? This way?
Thanks!
Now what?
It's getting worse and worse.
If this keeps up, it's not like
something bad will really happen, right?
Something bad? What?
This is something she had coming to her.
How can a commoner like her get our Jun Pyo
sunbae's one and only token of love!
That's right. If she had
only known her place,
we wouldn't have done
something like this.
"Something like this" - what?
Ji Hoo sunbae!
What did you guys do to Jan Di?
[Men's Restroom]
You're going to follow me into the restroom?
Isn't he taking too long to come out?
Geum Jan Di, looking for the necklace,
went up the mountain alone.
Gu Jun Pyo, do you hear me?
Geum Jan Di. I can't help but to
think that she's in an accident.
STOP!!!!
There’s only one like it in the world,
so if you lose it,
you’re really dead this time.
The only one?
This is I.
And the one inside is you.
Why's that?
Why are you the star and I'm the moon?
Because Geum Jan Di
is the moon, which can never escape
from the Gu Jun Pyo star.
Geum Jan Di, don't worry.
You can never escape from me.
Geum Jan Di!
Jan Di!
Answer me!
Geum Jan Di!
Jan Di!
Hey...
Geum Jan Di...
Wake up.
Jan Di...
Gu Jun Pyo...
Yeah... it's me, Gu Jun Pyo.
Are you coming around?
I... I came to look for your heart.
I didn't lose it on purpose.
Hey you idiot, who told you
to do something like this!
Do you think you can stand up?
Get on.
Jan Di...
Do you hear me?
Hey, you can't lose consciousness!
Hey, Geum Jan Di!
Because of the weather conditions, the
rescue team said it'll be too difficult.
- Ji Hoo, where are you going?
- I can't leave it alone like this.
Do you want to make
this problem bigger?
The road's blocked
you can't even approach it.
Geum Jan Di...!
Jan Di's out there.
She's out there alone in the snow.
- Let go!
- Ji Hoo...
Calm down.
Jan Di, are you OK?
Geum Jan Di!
Geum Jan Di...
- What are you doing?
- You have to take this off.
- It's dirty?
- Take everything off.
Ah, Jun Pyo...
If you don't, then you'll die!
Do you want to freeze and die because
of your stupid stubbornness?
There's no use trying to resist.
Because I'm not going to let you die.
Don't worry. It's OK.
It's going to be all right.
I’ll protect you.
Hurry up.
I'm sorry.
If you're are sorry, that's good enough.
Don’t forget I saved your life this time.
How should I repay you?
A lunchbox.
Hm?
There's that thing you eat every day.
The rolled up egg?
That...
Actually...
the first time I saw it,
I wanted to try it.
Why are you laughing?
Because I'm wondering
if this is the Gu Jun Pyo I know.
Are you teasing me right now?
I'll make it for you.
Let's make lunchboxes and go
on a picnic... The two of us.
The two of us.
Jan Di!
Jun Pyo!
Jun Pyo, are you OK?
Hey, are you guys OK?
Yeah, we're fine.
Shinhwa Group Chairman Gu Bon Hyung
in Critical Condition
As the investigation on
Shinhwa Group draws near.
News arrived that Shinhwa
Group Chairman Gu Bon Hyun,
who is currently visiting China,
is in critical condition.
According to internal sources in
Shinhwa Group, Gu Bon Hyung collapsed
and lost consciousness
after a sudden shock this afternoon
and was admitted to a hospital in Beijing...
Hello?
Sunbae!
Get on quickly!
Why? What's the matter?
It's urgent.
What?
We have to hurry if you're to see Jun Pyo.
Sunbae...
Everything's is ready.
Madam President.
They said that Jun Pyo's father collapsed.
What?
The plane's taking off in 30 minutes.
But I have yet to thank him.
And I have yet to tell him that I like him.
I'll be back soon.
Stay there, and wait for me.
I love you... Geum Jan Di.
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: lilshinhwafreak, Javafiend
Timer: Ahoxan
Editor/QC: annchong
Coordinator: mily2, ay_link
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get this for FREE @ d-addicts.com
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.