Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
Episode 3
A man, who leaves a beautiful girl
standing by herself, isn't a gentleman.
Is this a dream?
I feel like I'm standing on a cloud.
It would be nice if you could take your feet off my shoes.
She looks like another person.
Definitely Min Seo Hyun's work.
Maybe I should take her to
the next exhibition as my partner?
What is that?
Oh, annoying!
Help me!
He fell in!
Jun Pyo...
Gu Jun Pyo sunbae fell into the pool!
Hurry, hurry!
What is it?
Why are you so nervous?
He can't.
What?
The one thing Jun Pyo can't do is swim.
Gu Jun Pyo!
Gu Jun Pyo, wake up!
Open your eyes!
Hurry up and breathe, Gu Jun Pyo!
Gu Jun Pyo!
Wake up!
What?
You are such a scum.
You deceitful bastard!
I'm sorry, Young Master.
I'll prepare a new one.
Please forgive me.
What?
Do you have a cold?
Should I call Dr. Kim?
What cold?
I feel great.
Prepare the car. I need to quickly get to school.
You want to leave this early?
It's never too early for a student to go to school.
Don't you know the saying,
note: The saying is
"The early bird catches the worm."
"Bugs who wake up early die early?"
I will fire this maid immediately.
Why?
Yes?
Butler Lee, aren't you too picky?
Take it easy, take it easy.
The weather is so nice.
What is this?
Gu Jun Pyo!
Don't let me catch you!
I definitely won't go easy on you!
He asked us here so early and
he's been like this the whole day.
This is the first time I've seen
him work so hard at something.
But the question is, why
torture a poor transfer student?
Also, didn't she save his life?
"Don't bite the hand that feeds you."
You should apply that in this situation, right?
What are you saying,
"don't bite the hand that feeds you?"
This is my way of telling her thanks.
Why else would I do such boring
things for someone so lowly?
Normal people won't feel grateful for something like this.
Be quiet!
It's your turn to scold me since Ji Hoo isn't here?
Really!
Where is he?
Ever since we came back from Guam.
I don't what happened.
He's completely slipped into a depression.
It must be a lovers' quarrel.
What else could it be?
Min Seo Hyun is so hard to please.
He's beating around the bush.
If you like a girl, you should
just grab her and kiss her.
How hard can it be?
I'll leave after I do this.
Jun Pyo sunbae isn't enough for her,
she wants Ji Hoo sunbae as well!
You are really digging your own grave.
Hurry and go!
She looks sly as a fox!
She is the type of girl who won't back off.
Stupid girl, what should we do now?
What time is it? Why are you here so late?
As a swimmer, how can you not focus on your practice!
Be careful or I'll fire you.
I think they've been together for a while now.
Yes, why else would Ji Hoo sunbae protect that weed?
So as time passes,
what if your friendship is destroyed because of that girl?
You know now, right?
That weed looks innocent,
but her actions are those of a snake.
Shut up!
If you say one word, I will snap your neck.
This is the newest model.
Are you disappointed that it wasn't
the person you wanted see?
- Gu Jun Pyo, why are you?
- What?
I can't come here?
Have you two rented this place?
- Where are you going?
- I have nothing to say to you, I'm going home, why?
I have...
- What do you want?
- I have something to say.
Say it and let me go.
Who are you?
You think you can toy with me?
Toy with the great F4.
Who's toying with who?
Let me go!
I'm letting you go because
I think you are cute.
Am I a joke?
I don't know if you know...
I'm not the kind of person who
repays what is given to me.
I'm dissatisfied repaying an equal amount.
What are you doing?
I don't want to!
Am I that loathsome?
Geum Jan Di, are you not going to school?
I'm not going.
Do you want to get hit and then go to school
or go to school now?
I'm not going. Hit me.
You, really!
I'm not going!
I can't go!
I rather break the ice of Han river than go there.
I am not going to that school.
If want to see me die then force me to go.
- You,
- Isn't today a no school Saturday?*
*(In Korea, there's no school on 2nd & 4th Saturday every month)
Also,
An ahjussi told me to give this to you.
What's this?
What?
[Invitation: Hello, I want to invite all of you to my
home for my 23rd birthday. Please attend. "Min Seo Hyun"]
Party?
Then that means our Jan Di is
finally making her way into society!
Oh, Honey!
Honey! Honey!
Let me see.
Hurry, give it to me.
We shouldn't be like this right now.
Dress.
Honey, dress, dress.
I'm sorry Jan Di, your father is useless.
I can't even provide my daughter with a proper dress.
This poor neighborhood
can't even bring in one decent outfit.
Can't she wear this hanbok?
Is she going to visit her in-laws for New Years?
They are having a party, party.
Usually, at a time like this,
in dramas the prince would always buy an outfit.
Hello.
This is Ms. Min Seo Hyun's gift to Geum Jan Di.
This!
This is pretty.
- She should be wearing it like this right?
- Yes ,yes.
Pull it down a bit.
Why didn't you call me for your last exhibition?
You said you would contact us, but you never did.
It's the same with me.
Who did you come with today?
It seems like you don't have a partner.
Why don't I be yours?
Why are you like that?
I already set my sights on him.
Don't touch him!
- What are you doing?
- You are really funny.
Excuse me for a while, sorry.
Honey, why are you so late?
Why did you get here so late?
Why are you here?
It's because Seo Hyun unni invited me here.
Did you empty a department store?
She came late last time too.
Geum Jan Di,
she's pretty when she's dressed up.
Right, right.
You look the cutest here today.
Who's cute?
Can a pumpkin turn into a
watermelon by drawing lines on it?
Gu Jun Pyo,
actually said the right idiom.
Happy birthday to you...
Happy birthday dear, Min Seo Hyun.
Happy birthday to you.
Thank you everyone for attending
my 23rd birthday celebration.
I would like to thank my dad and mom for their care.
And the love of my friends.
I want to use this gathering to tell you something.
That's why I'm having party,
which isn't like me.
Where did that punk Ji Hoo go?
Are they announcing their engagement?
I will be returning to Paris next week,
and I don't think I'm coming back.
My modeling firm and I have arranged everything.
What is she saying?
Thanks to my parents, I can enjoy life
without having to work hard.
But I want to use my own abilities,
so I'm choosing a new road.
I won't be inheriting my parents' law firm.
What I want is,
a life where I'm able to experience a broader world.
If I didn't do this,
I don't think I would've been able to
convince the people around me.
So I set this stage...
Everyone,
you must be happy.
Min Seo Hyun, really is a bomb full of surprises.
Ji Hoo,
did he already know about this?
Now we know why he's been depressed all this time.
So cool.
Really is cool, but...
what about Ji Hoo?
Hello.
You still have it.
That was the first summer
we spent apart from each other.
You still remember.
It's from that time onwards,
that you stopped calling me "Noona."
What am I to you?
Our Ji Hoo is really angry.
I feel like I'm being thrown away.
If there's anything here
that can't be thrown away...
it's you.
Don't lie to me!
If I was lying,
I wouldn't mind you looking at other women.
What do you mean?
When you ran towards that girl,
I didn't understand why my heart suddenly sank.
It's funny, right?
I'm not in the mood to listen to you joke around.
I felt pleased, however.
I didn't know when our Ji Hoo became a man.
Don't joke!
You always do what you want.
I can't stay close, nor can I stay away.
You'll wind me up one day,
then ignore me another day.
I'm only a toy.
If I lost you, I wouldn't be able to sleep.
Then tell me who is looking at whom?
For the past 15 years, I've only looked at you.
Isn't that enough?
I'm also a man.
I want to hold you,
like a man.
I know.
I'm sorry, Ji Hoo.
I'm really sorry.
If you faint here, it will really be embarrassing.
It's not like you to faint.
You know that, right?
Who's going to faint?
Jan Di, you came.
Since you came, why didn't you come in?
That... so...
I wanted to say thank you.
I was about to go in.
The party is boring, right?
We are going for a drive.
Do you want to come with us?
Eh?
No, it's okay.
We have another place to go.
We?
Yes.
This punk and I,
we're also going for a drive.
Drive! We are going for a drive!
Seo Hyun unni, goodbye.
I will see you later.
Let's go!
Unni!
I have paid my debt.
What?
You saved me from the pool.
I'm your savior!
How can you repay me this way?
Do you want to go back?
10%.
You have repaid that much.
50%.
25%.
Oh, this is great.
But why isn't there a single customer?
They were chased away.
Why?
I booked this place till morning.
Just do what you want.
What do I want to do?
To cry or to scream out.
We can call in the security guards outside
if you want to beat up someone.
But why would I want to do that?
After you saw Ji Hoo and Seo Hyun,
didn't you feel that your heart was breaking?
Oh, that's impossible.
No, a person like me could never
be Min Seo Hyun unni's rival.
I'm not pretty.
My brain is bad as well.
My family is really poor too.
There's nothing great about your figure either.
Your temper is really bad.
Right.
So how could such a messed up person
be jealous of Min Seo Hyun?!
I didn't have the qualifications from the start.
Although there's no comparison,
you're not the messed up one.
You have the qualifications.
What?
Ji Hoo, that fool.
If he had met you first instead of Seo Hyun,
he would have liked you for sure.
Are you sincere?
Family... your looks too.
Your brains... though all of these are zero,
you are the first woman
recognized by Gu Jun Pyo.
Your qualifications get full marks.
I have to go to the washroom.
It's really hot.
I'm really warm and thirsty.
Water...
I really did everything.
Hey, Dry cleaner.
Hey, what's wrong?
And so, why is she like this?
Well, look here.
- She drank it all?
- Yes...
Hey!
Hey, get a hold on yourself woman!
Woman...
Right...
I'm a woman.
An ordinary commoner is not a woman?!
With no background, looks nor brains.
I know it all too.
There was no need for you to be so frank.
I feel it every day within my bones, you jerk.
Jerk?
No...
I...
I have no time to be thinking these things.
Actually, I'm a busy person who has lots of work to do.
I don't have the appropriate birth right,
but I have to attend such an aristocratic school.
Being bullied by others.
I have to work part-time jobs because
my dad often gets into trouble.
The school fees.
And I have to make time to swim for my scholarship.
I..
I haven't the time to accompany rich boys
like you to play the game of love.
You alcoholic.
Hey, gangster!
Wake up!
Ah!
I...
am a little sad today.
I'm a little upset.
Gu Jun Pyo, you punk.
Why are you smiling?
I feel good.
I'll let you off this once.
50.
I'll give you a discount since you saved my life.
Thank you, Gu Jun Pyo.
You saved me today.
I can't do anything for you, so instead...
I know that this place must be
really expensive just by its smell.
You are a complete wipeout.
How did I become like this?
Why am I here?
I brought you here.
I'm asking you, why am I at
my place instead of yours!?
Don't you remember?
It's a world famous brand.
It's a Gucci designed by the Milan designers.
It was first shown in their
new Spring/Summer collections.
It just arrived the day before, by air from Milan.
- The price is...
- Enough...
You want to scare her?
I don't feel like hearing you gloat
about your clothes right now.
That was the suit that I wore yesterday.
Why does the suit you wore
yesterday concern me at all?!
I wore it for the first time yesterday.
But it became the last time
I'll be wearing it, because of who?
Did you remember a little right now?
You came to my place of course,
since you were in that condition.
If not, did you want to go back home?
Sorry...
I already made a call to inform your parents.
It seems that they aren't worried about you.
Then, I'll be leaving now.
Sorry for creating so much trouble.
It's best that you go back to being yourself.
Sir...
- What's up?
- Madam, she...
What about that witch?
She has already arrived.
So early?
Why is she here so early?
Where is Jun Pyo?
On the second floor.
I have to make him help out with the event.
Arrange someone to follow him,
so that he doesn't slip away.
I got it.
What are you doing?
Hey, emergency!
What?
The witch came back suddenly.
Jan Di is in my room right now.
I have no way of getting her out.
What?
Jun Pyo, once she finds out...
You are finished.
There is a strange girl in my son's room.
And it's just a "Geum Jan Di."
How is she going to react?
It's really making me curious.
Tomorrow morning...
Jun Pyo...
is going to be sent to Alaska.
$1000
Me?
Dispatched to Se Jong base, $3000
But first, she'll employ a hit-man.
What?
Really?
She is that scary?
When we went to summer camp in sixth grade,
we escaped that day.
Don't you remember?
We really almost died that day.
So how could we forget about it?
Don't move!
Bonjour. Noona.
You are Yi Jung, right?
How can you be so good-looking?
Noona, you are Korea's Vivian.
Everyone has been saying it.
What do you want? Say it quickly.
What do you want from me?
You knew it...
That's why I like you so much.
The Seoul branch has sent over the concept
application of helping kids with kidney stones.
Reject.
The education resources,
and Shinhwa school too.
Reject.
You didn't let Jun Pyo escape, right?
Yes.
Who is she?
Hello.
She's my guest, so it's none of your business.
She's my guest as well
since she's come to my home.
Isn't that so, Miss?
She is our friend.
Friend?
Yes, she's our school junior.
We let her join F4 specially as our mascot,
because she looks so cute.
Well, it's like that.
Which family's daughter are you?
- I'm...
- What work does your father do?
- My father is...
- He's a businessman.
Yes, is that so?
What kind?
Well, clothes.
No, no... The fashion business.
He's quite famous in the clothing world.
That's quite interesting.
And so, are you interested in today's auction?
Yes, not only is she interested.
She brought with her Bella Song's new work
which will be the dark horse for the auction tonight.
It looks like your mother has very good taste.
What work does she do?
Chairman, it's time to welcome the guests.
Jun Pyo, you stay behind to guard your position.
You guys too...
It's for a good cause, help out as well.
Yes...
How can you lie?
How are we going to do damage control?
We should have told her the truth.
Then be honest by saying that your dad runs a dry cleaner
and your mom operates a public bath?
But then, not only you, but your family as well,
will encounter things no one can guarantee.
You will lose your life once she singles you out.
This is not a joke.
That...
is it hereditary?
The auction item this time,
will make everyone's eyes light up.
The item is now here!
Everyone's attention on it please.
The auction item this time is...
Marine Boy Swimmer, Park Tae Hwan's goggles.
Swimmer Park Tae Hwan's goggles?
Now, the starting price is from 500,000 Won.
1 million.
1 million Won is called out.
2 million.
2 million Won is called out.
7 million.
7 million Won is called out.
Now is anyone willing to pay 7.5 million Won?
8 million.
8 million Won is called out.
Is there anyone for 8.5 million Won?
Yes, 8.5 million Won.
10 million Won over here.
Yes, 10 million Won!
Just now, someone telephoned
with a bid of 10 million Won!
Is there anyone who wants to bid a higher price?
If there isn't, then...
Then the auction is going to close.
One!
Two!
Three!
The deal is sealed for 10 million won.
The auction item this time...
Everyone's attention please be on it.
It's now here.
The auction item this time,
is the work of a young ceramics artist.
So Yi Jung's new work,
"Object".
The starting price is 5 million Won.
The auction item this time, is the Pavioni suit
worn by Gu Jun Pyo of the Shinhwa group.
The suit's most highlighted aspect is it's so light,
you feel as though you're not wearing it.
The starting price for it is from 10 million won.
Yes, 10 million Won is called out.
Now, let's continue. Is there 15 million Won?
Yes, 15 million Won is bid.
This striped suit was the one which influenced
Paris fashion and Prêt-a-porter suits.
Right, anyone for 20 million Won?
What are you doing? Let's go quickly.
Your turn is next.
If you wear it for 10 years, it'll still
be elegant as though you just bought it.
25 million won! Anyone for 30 million?
Yes, there's 30 million won!
The auction item this time
is really brightening eyes.
- Bella Song's new collection.
- I can't do it. I can't, just this once.
Everyone, please pay attention.
The pale elegant lemon yellow
will highlight your attractiveness.
The shining gold accessories on the
dress will increase your elegance.
Bella Song new design's starting
price will be 10 million Won.
Yes, 10 million Won, going once!
How about 15 million Won?
Yes! 15 million is called.
What has Jun Pyo been doing lately?
He's more well-behaved these days.
And he is taking school more seriously.
Then, do you know that female student?
Bella Song's eye catching new dress,
will transform you perfectly. Now...
I finally meet the famous wonder girl.
I'm happy to meet you.
I wasn't the one who pushed him, really.
Assistant Kim.
Yes...
According to what I know, she is a
transfer student at Shinhwa High School.
Check out which family's daughter she is.
I got it.
The feel of the fabric of Bella Song's new design
will make you look more glamorous.
This is the dress that's really
popular this season in Paris.
Oh, my.
Is this for real?
Are these the goggles that
Park Tae Hwan used before?
Hey, this is not a joke at all.
Noona, Noona, you are going to be rich for sure.
Superbly rich this time.
What again?
Park Tae Hwan's goggles will fetch you
2 million Won if you were to sell them.
2 million Won?
A pair of goggles are worth 2 million Won?
Sell them, sell them right now.
Where else can you get 2 million Won?
No, these are really expensive!
Well, what I meant is...
Their worth can't be measured with money.
I meant that.
Sell them! 2 million, 2 million!
We are selling them even if it's 20,000!
I really don't know what you are thinking about.
Oh, really...
But still, selling them is a little...
I don't care anymore.
Good night.
Jan Di!
Hey, girl!
Wait, look at her. Don't block me, hey!
I'm leaving.
Anyway, thank you.
What?
I can't hear it.
Thank you.
What?
I said, thank you!!
Just a simple "thank you" would've been enough.
Why did you have to add on "anyway"?
That's right, you are rather prideful
since you are a commoner.
You were pretending when you'd heard me already.
Cancelled.
What?
I'm canceling my thank you.
That's right, people won't change that easily.
I'm leaving.
Hey, Jandi baht*...
(*grass field)
What?!
Don't you ever drink when I'm not around.
Seo Hyun unni, why are you here?
I came here because I had
to process my school withdrawal.
I wanted to see you one more time before I leave,
so I came here to try my luck.
I was lucky.
Leaving school?
You really aren't returning?
I'm afraid so.
When will you be leaving?
Tomorrow.
Why so soon?
There's no time to say thanks to you.
I still haven't returned the favors I owe you.
I'll be really disappointed if
you keep saying things like that.
I knew from the first time we met,
you are the person that our Ji Hoo
always smiles when mentioning.
It's you, Jan Di.
Well, Unni.
Jan Di...
What are you doing?
I was a fan of yours for a very
long time, even before I met you.
And so, I understand why you made
such a decision more than many others. But still...
I'm begging you not to leave.
Get up quickly.
I know really well that I'm not qualified to beg
you and there's no reason for you to listen.
But I don't know what to do besides this.
Is it because of Ji Hoo?
I don't know anything at all about Ji Hoo sunbae.
But...
I know,
how precious you are to him.
When I see him, why does he
always have an unknown sadness?
But he will still smile sometimes,
and can melt other people's hearts.
It is really warm.
Unni, you are the only person
that can make him smile.
If you are to leave like this,
there's a possibility he may never smile again.
Just get up quickly.
Jan Di...
Whatever decisions I've made
are similar to shopping overseas.
There won't be another chance
if I don't remain firm at that moment.
I know clearly how cruel those feelings of regrets are.
Ji Hoo is a really precious person to me as well.
I believe he feels the same way too.
And so, I feel that Ji Hoo wouldn't want
to see me living with regrets as well.
How do you feel about this?
Sorry. I'm sorry.
No, I'm really happy that you
are telling me these things.
Thanks.
Unni...
Oh, wait.
You are going to give me these?
I told you before, right?
Shoes are the most important things.
I hope that these shoes will bring
you to a good place for sure.
I have something to request from you as well.
Let our Ji Hoo regain his smile again.
What are you doing?
Who are you to do this kind of thing?
Did anyone ask for that kind of favor?
That isn't even a favor. It's groveling.
Don't you have any pride?
It's not because I don't have pride.
It's because you were hurting too much.
Because you were about to die from sadness.
What does it matter to you?
It has nothing to do with you, does it?
Get lost.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: saranghae<3, yeohweping
Spot Translator: saturn
Timer: melliemelll
Editor/QC: sayroo
Final QC: melica
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Tell me what a real man is like?
A man who is responsible from the beginning 'till the end.
Geum Jan Di, you and I...
No, this is impossible!
Mom, Dad, please forgive me.
Isn't he the heir of Shinhwa group?
It's the next flight.
Luckily both of us are on the flight.
When do we have the right to love freely?
The final decision lies in the hands of our parents.
You haven't forgotten it, right?
You only talk about being a real man?
Is it true between you and F4's Gu Jun Pyo?
To lie to Senior Jun Pyo is
equivalent to lying to all of us.
Geum Jan Di...
I don't know you from now onwards.
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get it for FREE @ d-addicts.com