Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
Is that all you got?
Come on!
Bring it on!
Throw them!
Stop! Stop!
Help me.
There isn't anyone.
There won't be anyone else to help me.
If only there was just one
person who could give me a hand.
Screw off!
Gu Jun Pyo.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't me.
It really wasn't me.
I don't care. Don't talk right now.
You still don't believe me, do you?
I do. I believe you.
I'll do it.
Do you want to sit still
or do you want me to tie you up?
Are you addicted or are you just clueless?
You've gone through so much
crap and you still haven't learned?
In a situation like that, obviously
the best of 38 strategies is to just walk out.
Your brain is really useless.
Your IQ isn't even 10, is it?
Your ability to learn is barely that of an orangutan.
An orangutan?
Isn't that right?
Look at this!
It's all because your brain's useless
that your body had to go through so much crap.
It's not the 38 strategies,
it's the 36 strategies!
Clueless rascal.
I don't want to get scolded by a person like you.
Close your eyes.
Ahh, that hurts!
Wipe it yourself!
You rascal, really!
[Gu Joon Pyo,
Yoon Ji Hoo, Song Woo Bin, So Yi Jung]
[Oh Min Ji]
[Jun Pyo, Min Ji]
A bug, a bug!
Go away!
Go away, go away!
It's okay now.
[Jun Pyo, Min Ji]
What are you doing? Don't be like this.
You're so ugly, and you still want to be my bride?
Do you not want to go to daycare anymore?
Don't. Don't be like this.
Don't be like this.
You look like a pumpkin.
It'd be impossible with someone like you.
Disappear!
Go home, you ugly pumpkin!
No, don't be like this.
Don't be like this. Don't be like this.
How I lived after that...
You guys will never know.
I was terrified to step out of the house
Because of the deep fear in my heart.
It was painful,
and yet I was too ashamed to face people.
After three years of being in pain,
I went to Germany.
Plastic surgery once every two years,
That taste of pain is even worse than death.
Do you know how I got through those years?
Yup, it was that expression.
Where you guys treated me like a bug,
The expression with which you guys
laughed at me, as if I were a freak.
I haven't forgotten it for a second.
Even though I don't remember,
I'm still very sorry.
No!
It's not that!
"Sorry" isn't what I want to hear from you!
Hey.
Calm down.
Look at me.
Aren't I beautiful?
I've become so beautiful.
Don't you like me?
Who did I come back for?
This is the moment I've
been waiting for for years!
Say it!
Say you like Oh Min Ji!
I'm begging you.
Say you like Oh Min Ji.
Hurry and say that you like Oh Min Ji!
How pathetic.
I can't watch anymore.
You know why?
It doesn't matter if it
was the past or the present.
You're still just a freak.
No, you've become worse than before.
At least, the girl back then,
Her heart and soul were beautiful.
Why are you here again?
What do you want now?
Of course I came for a reason.
Reason? What reason?
I don't want to hear.
What are you doing?
Always randomly just...
Dragging people into your house.
You mean to say that with
your torn-up arms and legs,
And your wounds just treated with medicine,
I should still take you home?
Your parents would be absolutely thrilled.
I've already told someone to
call them and tell them not to worry.
And also.. your clothing and
backpack have already been thrown away.
There's no use in searching for them.
Thrown away?
You threw them all away?
We could've just tidied them up and washed them.
Without my permission,
how could you throw them away?
How could you still wear something like that?
Why wouldn't I be able to?
Don't forget,
I'm the daughter of a dry-cleaning family!
So noisy!
How can a tiny and skinny
rascal have such a loud voice?
Did you eat a train's heart?
What?
It's not a heart! It's a train's smokestack!
How could that be?
Hey, look at it from a logical perspective.
How can a person eat a train's smokestack?
If he's going to eat anything,
of course it's going to be a heart.
What are you doing?
Stay away from me!
Come over here.
Let me see.
Whenever I'm tired, lucky in my life,
You come by my side like a dream.
Whenever I'm sad, lucky in my dream.
You always warmly surround me.
I always smile like this.
No matter how many trials there are in this world,
I'll definitely never let you see my tears.
Even if you don't understand my heart.
Even if you're far away,
I'll still be happy because of your smile.
Just take a step closer to me.
That hurts so bad.
Your school uniform, shoes, and other accessories
Have been prepared during the night for you.
It's just that...
That...?
There's only one thing
that we need to apologize for.
But this one is a bit different from mine.
My bike wasn't this expensive!
Mine was one of those average,
extremely, extremely, extremely average bicycles.
I'm very sorry, Miss.
The young master gave orders to buy Miss
things that were exactly the same as the old ones.
But that bike,
it was impossible for us to find that same model.
We've already tried our best.
Can you not find it in your
benevolent heart to accept these gifts?
But...that's still...this price.
This is what the chef prepared especially for you.
Kobe as well as barbecued beef
In a Piemonte Alba truffle omelette.
Alba tru...
Truffle.
A truffle.
But, why haven't I seen Gu Jun Pyo?
The young master left early this morning.
Where'd he go?
Noona?
[Gu Jun Pyo]
Has Jan Di come back?
Gu... Gu... Gu...
What's wrong?
I asked you whether or not your sister came back.
Shin... Shin...
Why are you stuttering?
Didn't Dad tell you that one day something bad would
happen because of these electromagnetic waves?
-F... F...
-What?
What is this?
Oh, whose son is this? He looks so handsome.
He's here.
- What?
- F4!
What is that?
The heir of Shinhwa group, Gu Jun Pyo!
Shinhwa Group.
What?
You mean that person has
come to our house? Right now?
Wife!
It doesn't matter how loudly you scream.
There's only one piece of saury.
This...
Do you eat this as a food?
What kind of bug is that?
It's not a bug... it's a seafood.
What kind of seafood is that tiny?
Uh... that... that...
The ones that are called anchovies are that small.
Ahh...it sounds like you haven't heard of them.
Uh, that's... just because we didn't know
what kind of foods the sons of rich families eat.
Uh... then just eat this first.
Oh, I know what this is.
It's that... sau...
Sau...
- Ry!
He knows what saury is!
How does he know that?
Oh yes, this...
That's not how you eat that.
Oh, where'd she get that done?
It looks so good!
Darling!
Go look at that.
How could that Oh Min Ji do that to you?
Even backstabbing has its limits.
Whose fault was it that
you had to go through this pain?
Let me through.
That's so scary.
Vicious, that's too vicious.
They say that with that kind of plastic surgery,
After you get it done once,
It'll be because it was too painful,
That you couldn't possibly
go through it a second time.
If we all risked our lives
like that to get the surgery done,
Who wouldn't be just as beautiful as she is?
That's right.
Is that... the face of a human?
If I looked like that,
I would've committed suicide a long time ago.
Your eyes.
Your nose.
Your cheekbones.
You paid money for all of that, didn't you?
If there's something you want,
Don't you just buy it with your money?
Can't the same be done for beauty?
Hey!
Haven't you all gotten plastic surgery?
Then why are you still picking on Min Ji?
If it's okay for people who are already
beautiful to want to be more beautiful,
Why isn't it okay for
ugly people to want to do it?
She didn't just do it for no reason.
She paid a tremendously painful price.
So what about it?
So what?
Can anybody say that that's not Min Ji's?
If you can, step up.
Step up and let me see!
I won't beg you for forgiveness.
Nor can I apologize.
Don't think that I can forgive you.
Jan Di.
Thank you.
We'll see each other again later.
From the places where I used
to sit and play with Geum Jan Di,
You can hear the sound of washing clothes.
Talking about my love, Jan Di.
Everybody listen up!
In the name of Shinhwa High School's F4,
There is something that I want
to clearly announce to all of you.
From today on, second-year Geum Jan Di of Class B
Has become my, Gu Jun Pyo's, girlfriend.
I'm formally announcing this here.
Ahh, congratulations!
Ginger! Ginger!
No! No!
What is this?
Silence!
So from now on,
Geum Jan Di's words and actions will be,
The same as those of Gu Jun Pyo, me.
Nobody had better get fresh with her.
Understand?
Yes.
Yes!
I object!
- Ji Hoo!
I'm back.
But isn't it too soon for
that prince to be coming back?
Then for him to come back so early means...
Did something happen over there?
Maybe.
If that's the case...
Can't you go into the bathroom
and scream in celebration?
No?
Ohh, now since that Gu guy
is still the leader, you can't.
It's not like that.
Then why is your face so pale?
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know what to say.
In any case, they've gotten weird.
My feelings.
What feelings?
It's like something has changed.
That's because he's come
back after drinking Paris' water.
It's no surprise that he must've got hotter.
I already told you it's not like that!
Oh, Geum Kang San.
What's wrong?
He says there's a family emergency.
Mom!
Dad!
San! Where are you?
Noona, right here.
Dad's over here too!
Jan Di!
Come over and take a look at all this.
What is all of this?
It was Hyungnim who sent it over.
Hyungnim!
Hyungnim?
Jun Pyo hyungnim!
Dining table, sofa, TV, and kimchi refrigerator.
He sent it all over!
As for the beds, because our door was too small,
we had to send them back.
You know that kind.
I mean, those lacey princess beds with the canopies.
Ohh, it was such a shame!
We should've knocked down
the door to get that bed in here.
How can you just accept everything he sends over?
But, Jan Di...
Dad wanted to send it back too, but...
What did the delivery man do wrong?
We had to accept these,
so that those people could go back.
Why should we send them back?
This isn't just for our family.
This is also for the reputation of their family.
If we're too poor,
that'll cause Young Master Jun Pyo to lose face.
What do you know, you dumb girl?
No, there's not even a way to get through...
how can we live like this?
Do you want to get stuck living in the cracks
between the couch and the refrigerator?
Okay, I know, I know.
Just rewrap all of these.
And send it to the warehouse
of your uncle in the countryside.
When you get married, we'll use it as dowry.
Okay? Okay? Okay?
Dad!
Okay, I know.
Even though it's a shame,
we'll just have to send these back.
Just go tell him nicely.
We appreciate the thought.
Don't even accept the thought.
Noona, let's at least keep the TV, okay?
You little rascal, Geum Kang San!
Let's talk.
Oh.
You've come in person?
What kind of reason made
you run all the way over here?
Do you not understand what I'm saying?
I told you to talk to me.
Move.
You're not going to move?
Really!
What?
What's wrong with this?
I was about to get a high score,
fat chance for that now, thanks to you.
What the heck do you want?
I should be asking you what the heck you want!
Without getting permission,
how could you turn my house upside down?
Oh, that.
Is there anything that you're not happy with?
Tell me. I'll get you a new one.
Hey!
My family has beds too, and chairs.
Washing machine,
refrigerator, TV, we have all of them!
Isn't it great to replace them with new ones?
Why are you replacing them?
What the heck are you?
What could I be?
Starting yesterday, I'm your boyfriend!
Are you like this whenever you have a girlfriend?
Buying clothing, cars, replacing furniture.
After a while do you change houses too?
Actually, I had wanted to change the house first.
Secretary Jung said that since
it's connected to the dry cleaning store,
He told me to search again later.
What do you take a person for?
Am I Shim Chung,* being sold to you?
[*Shim Chung was an ancient filial daughter]
I told you.
You don't buy friends with money,
you earn them with your heart.
Though I don't know how
you treated girlfriends before,
I really hate stuff like this.
None.
My previous girlfriends
or whatever…there were none.
That...
Then I'll let you slide this time...
just be careful from now on!
That crappy temper of yours.
Why is it that every time I
want to be good to you, you flip out?
Who asked you to be good to me?
Nice shot!
Find the right position and throw it.
But...do you lounge around like this every day?
What, are you worried?
There's a party today, so this is a special case.
I usually don't let women in.
Flies? What flies?*
[Note: Homophones with "party"]
What's up with that rascal Ji Hoo?
Is he back after becoming a real man in Paris?
Seeing how he slept all day like a cat,
I thought he hadn't matured at all.
Now he's a bit more human.
It's been a long time since I've
been able to tolerate him like this.
Jan Di, do you want to join our equestrians club?
Jan Di, can you be our captain?
Jan Di, today's my birthday party!
You have to come!
Jan Di! Jan Di! Jan Di! Jan Di!
Hold on!
Look, over there!
This is even scarier than
when they were bullying me.
Why are they like this?
Nowadays you don't scream and shout anymore?
Sunbae!
Habits can be really scary.
This place is just the same as before.
But it's too quiet.
How strange.
It doesn't feel right.
When are you going back?
I'm not going back.
And you?
Are you really dating Jun Pyo?
Uh...that.
Looks like it's true.
Uh…actually.
Did I come a bit too late?
Eh?
I was hoping to ask you to go out with me.
What?
I'm kidding.
Then how about...
We date secretly behind Jun Pyo's back?
Sunbae...
It's still the same.
The Jandi Baht here.
[Note: Jandi Baht means grass]
I've missed it.
Would you look at that?
Picking up a 500 won coin
could make you that happy.
What are you doing here?
You threw such a fit complaining about
how you hated the furniture and electronics,
But with one coin,
you're grinning so big your lips can't even close.
That's because it's a lucky...
What?
Did you drop this?
As a reward for your efforts, I threw one to see.
Pretty good results, no?
Take it.
You keep it. Didn't you say it was lucky?
From the moment I saw you,
my luck has gone bad.
No,
Your luck is good.
Extremely good.
What?
Let's go.
Hey?
Can you not see that I'm here to work?
It's only for a bit.
If you get fired, I'll take the responsibility.
Hey, can you not mention the
whole "taking responsibility" concept?
I get goosebumps just thinking about it.
Ahh, you ramble so much.
Seriously.
- Come on!
- What are you doing?
Hurry up and get in the car!
Oh, Jan Di.
Ga Eul...
What's going on with Jan Di?
Throw them all out.
Young Master.
Doing this without prior notice is a bit...
If you have to get permission and beg for understanding
in everything, what kind of leader are you?
Cut the crap. Clear out the place.
They'll close before 6pm.
Please wait three hours.
Are you asking me to wait three hours?
I'll make other arrangements.
Forget it. I'll take care of it myself.
Where is it?
What?
Are you talking about... that?
But that is...
Do you not even know what that is?
Please wait just a moment, sir.
Fire her immediately.
Sir, sir!
Fire, fire!
Fire! Fire!
Stand by me,
Look towards me.
Even though I don't understand love yet
Stand by me.
Watch over me.
I'm not wearing this!
Let's go.
Even though I'm not good with love.
Together make it love.
Forever making you smile.
Filled with your happy smiles.
Together make it love,
Forever making you smile.
Hold on now, hold on to my hand.
Stand by me.
Look towards me.
Even though I don't understand love yet.
Stand by me,
Watch over me.
Even though I'm not good with love.
Let's go.
Did you really have to take it that far?
I'm already on my way.
You have to keep your promise.
Tang dynasty ceramic design, white porcelain.
From now on don't give me any
more crap about wanting to go back.
Mmhmm.
Turn around.
Why isn't she here yet?
Ga Eul.
You're not allowed to leave
me behind and run off too.
Where could I possibly go?
Jan Di's not here either.
You really won't leave, right?
Welcome.
Do you need something?
I'm not Jan Di. I'm Jan Di's friend Ga Eul.
Hurry. It's an emergency.
What's wrong?
Did something happen to Jan Di?
What happened?
Was there an accident?
If we're late,
you might not be able to see her again. Hurry!
Oh, what should we do?
Parents.
We have to contact her parents.
They've already been told.
What are we going to do? Jan Di.
Let's go.
Jan Di!
What's going on?
We're going on a trip.
A trip?
Mmhmm.
How can I do that?
I haven't even talked it over with my parents yet.
I told them already.
What?
I've already gotten their permission.
I was worried you'd feel awkward if you
went by yourself, so I brought your friend too.
Are we good now?
This is ridiculous.
Come on, let's go!
Almost paradise,
More brilliant than dawn.
Your love for me,
Is like being on top of the world.
We switched planes?
I heard there was a one-year waitlist for planes
like this because there were so many reservations.
Shinhwa really is different.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome aboard our Air Shinhwa
Flight 001 from Seoul to New Caledonia.
New Caledonia time is two hours faster than Seoul
and it's 3 ‘o'clock in the afternoon over there.
Local temperature is 27 degrees Celsius.
- Caledonia?
Are you so surprised that you
don't know how to breathe anymore?
Do you need an oxygen mask?
Gu Jun Pyo.
Is my relationship with you
one where we can go traveling together?
Even if it is a relationship
where we can travel together,
Shouldn't you ask me for my opinion?
You should've at least
confirmed the schedule with me.
Did your Shinhwa preschool
not teach you this common sense?
I wanted to go somewhere nice with you.
All the preparations have been made.
Just because you're gone doesn't
mean chaos will erupt in South Korea.
What's the problem?
I don't know about South Korea.
But our congee shop might have some problems.
If they find out that both of us are gone...
No.
Let's go.
Would you take a seat please?
In my life.
It's like a dream in my weary life.
If I can forever be in love
with the image of you walking toward me.
Filled with your angelic smile,
Our paradise.
I'll use flowers that are only for you,
And fill it forever.
Seafood congee is ready!
Here, here!
Our congee.
Over here, let's get some food!
Waitress!
Aldebaran.
Epsilon Eridani.
Beauty like that
shouldn't exist on this earth.
Long live F4!
Manager.
- Four abalone congee specials.
- Abalone congee...four?
Okay!
Waitress!
This is your captain speaking.
We will be arriving to Maré Island shortly.
We wish you a pleasant trip to New Caledonia,
French paradise.
We're here.
Wake up!
Stand by me,
Look towards me.
Even though I don't understand love yet.
Stand by me.
Watch over me.
Even though I'm not good with love.
The more I look at you, the happier I am.
Absentmindedly, I'll start humming.
Suddenly I want to buy a rose.
I think that this me is rather new.
My thoughts are all on you.
The world has become beautiful.
If you can feel this too.
Please wait for me.
Together make it love.
Forever making you smile.
Filled with your happy smiles.
Together make it love,
Forever make it your smile.
Hold on now, hold on to my hand.
Stand by me.
Look towards me.
Even though I don't understand love yet.
Stand by me,
Watch over me.
Even though I'm not good with love.
The better I understand your heart,
the more excited I get.
All I do is smile.
I want to quietly kiss you just once.
That way, will I get closer to you?
Is this feeling of mine love?
Right now I'm still rather shy.
Right now it's still impossible
for me to completely express how I feel.
Please wait for my love.
Together make it love.
Forever making you smile.
Filled with your happy smiles.
Together make it love,
Forever make it your smile.
Hold on now, hold on to my hand.
Stand by me.
Watch over me.
It seems like I'm still not very good with love.
It feel like its floating on the ocean.
It is floating.
Really?
Come with me.
Huh?
How can this be?
It's hard to wrap my mind around.
Where are we again?
This is Maitre Island.
This belongs to our resort only. It's our island.
Our?
Mmhmm. It's Shinhwa group's.
Yi Jung bought an island too. It's in Dubai.
To be completely accurate, I bought a manmade
island which has the shape of Korea.
But those rascals missed Dok Do island.
So we're gonna make it ourselves.
Then, besides F4,
This is everyone else's first time here.
Let's take a little tour of the island.
Almost paradise.
Even warmer than the sun.
The gaze with which you look at me
Is like being on top of the world
In my life.
It's just like sunlight in my weary life.
As long as I can have
the love you give me forever.
If you can love me forever.
Grab your hand and shout to the world,
Swear by the sky,
That I will only love you forever.
Like the starlight in the night sky.
A beautiful dream that only belongs to us.
Let's go to paradise.
I only want to be with you.
I can go anywhere, to my paradise.
The days when I lost you,
Forget about all that pain,
Right now is the beginning. Being with you.
Let's start traveling.
Let's start running.
Loving you forever.
Almost paradise.
Even warmer than the sun.
The gaze with which you look at me,
Is like being on top of the world,
In my life.
It's just like sunlight in my weary life.
As long as I can have
the love you give me forever.
You are all of my love.
You are all of my life.
I will love you with my everything.
Give it to the one you love.
What?
Love. Love?
They look like Koreans.
Excuse me.
Yes?
What is that?
Oh, that's a native woman. I think they
say she's a very accurate fortune teller.
She's really accurate.
- She tells fortunes?
- Yes.
Fortunetelling?
Oh, oh, okay,
I see a man.
Man?
Your future husband.
Husband.
Husband, husband.
Where? Where?
Who is it?
Here with you.
What?
And soulmate.
Soulmate?
That's great!
A soulmate turning into your husband.
That's great, that's great!
That's like an added plus!
Two different men. Two!
What does she mean now?
That means...the soulmate and the future husband...
Are two different guys?
You're losing something important.
Losing?
Important?
As a woman!
As a woman...important.
Could that mean...?
What's wrong?
It was a dream.
Ga Eul...I...I had...I had a dream.
What kind of dream?
It was a dream...a dream.
Thank goodness.
You and I went to a fortune teller.
A lady who looked like this.
We went to her to have our fortunes told.
But that lady told us...
We have to be careful.
You have to go somewhere with me.
Where?
You'll know once we get there.
- Hurry up and come with me.
- Hey, hey.
Ga Eul!
Jan Di!
Please.
Ga Eul!
Jan Di!
Take care!
It's not like she's going to a battlefield.
Wow, it's so beautiful.
Hey. Take a picture for me.
You've done all of the typical tourist things.
Are we good now? Let's go.
What a sec!
You've looked over there.
You've taken a picture. Aren't you done now?
How could I be done?
Let's go look from up there.
We have to go up there?
Hey! This is already my ninth time here,
But you're the first person to go up there.
Why am I stuck babysitting such a hillbilly?
Take it. White porcelain, white porcelain.
Isn't it a good thing that you came up here?
You...
This is your punishment for lying about something
happening to Jan Di and for dragging us here.
It wasn't completely a lie.
Sooner or later something
will happen between the two of them.
No!
What are you thinking about?
Who says I'm thinking about anything?
Let's go back down.
What?
Why isn't there a single person here?
Is this a deserted island?
Aren't the two of us here?
What is your purpose in intentionally
dragging me to this deserted island?
Purpose?
I don't have any of that. Only intention.
Gu Jun Pyo!
I'm warning you.
If you're using this trip
as an excuse to mess around with me,
Don't even have such a dark heart.
Dark heart?
A person's heart isn't like pencil lead.
And also,
With you always twisting things
around and being suspicious of everything,
Can you say that you have a white heart?
Come with me.
How did you do this?
Didn't I say this before?
The things that you can't even imagine,
I can show you every day.
Jan Di. You're so tough on the outside,
But little things like this can get to you?
Is this a little thing?
It's like magic.
Are you a genie?
Genie?
Who is that rascal?
Is that guy more handsome than me?
No, the genie is the spirit in the lamp in Aladdin.
He can make anything happen.
Ohh. I was wondering who you were talking about.
But...can that guy really do anything?
No. Even the genie in the
lamp has things that he can't do.
Like killing people, or saving dying people, and...
And?
And making someone fall in love with someone else.
He can't do that.
How are there so many
things that a genie can't do?
Rascal. He sounds weaker than me.
I can do it.
No matter if it's killing someone,
or saving someone.
If I set my mind to it, I can do it all.
So as long as you say the word.
Of course you can do it.
Oh, right.
I almost forgot.
Hello, I'm Gu Jun Pyo.
We're in New Caledonia.
Jan Di Baht...
No...Geum Jan Di is here with me.
I'll put her on.
Mom!
Jan Di! Geum Jan Di! Are you doing well?
You're doing very well, aren't you, Jan Di?
Aigoo, my daughter! Keep it up!
Dad, I'm doing really well.
Noona! Noona! Is it fun over there?
Have you eaten a hairy crab? Hairy crab?
Sorry, San.
I'm sorry that I'm the
only person who got to come here.
No! No! Don't worry about us!
Have a good time! Have a good time!
Hey, hey, hey! Jan Di.
You have to be nicer to Young Master Jun Pyo.
This camera was sent over by his secretary.
Go for it!
Noona! Noona! If you guys develop, I want to eat
10 hairy crabs, and then wrap one for Yong San.
Hey, Geum Jan Di!
The Geum family's glory is in your hands, okay?
Got it? Go for it!
Aja! Aja!
Did I do something wrong again?
I just...
No, Gu Jun Pyo.
Thank you.
Then why are you crying?
Because this place is too wonderful.
I don't know when my parents would
be able to come to a place like this.
If my family could see this,
they'd definitely be very happy.
Then we'll come together.
What?
Why don'we just come again with your family?
Once you're done being touched,
we should get to the main course.
Main course?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translator: asiandreamer117
Spot Translator: saturn
Timer: julier
Editor/QC: docmitasha
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
Dad! Dad!
From now on, don't swim by yourself.
And don't take walks by yourself.
You!
Did you come to give me this?
If you're going to throw it away
like a cheap good, you're dead for sure!
Have you accepted my feelings?
What?
Don't make me wait too long.
Gu Jun Pyo. Starting today,
your name goes on the list of players.
Does all of this need to be eaten?
Where'd it go?
What?
The thing I gave you.
Oh, that...
How'd he leave?
He left this morning by plane.
Geum Jan Di…do you not have any feelings?
I don't expect that apologizing
will make things okay.
You'd better remember this clearly.
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get it for FREE @ d-addicts.com