Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Episode 22
Then, tell me not to do it.
Tell me not to go.
Miss Jae Kyung is looking
for Miss Geum Jan Di.
The groom is taking too long.
Here comes the groom.
Here comes the bride.
We shall begin...
with the holy matrimony of the groom,
Gu Jun Pyo, and bride, Ha Jae Kyung.
Marriage is...
a sacred oath between two people,
in front of those whom you love and cherish.
If anyone objects to this marriage,
please speak now.
Or forever hold your peace.
The Lord...
What is she doing?
What are you doing right now?
I...
I object to this wedding.
Jae Kyung!
Jae Kyung, what do you
think you're doing?!
I, the bride, Ha Jae Kyung,
object to this wedding.
W-what?
Is there anyone else who objects?
I also object.
I object as well.
I do too.
Me too.
I object as well.
Huh? What is this...
Jae Kyung.
I think this joke is too much.
It's good to have fun, but...
President...
Also Mom and Dad...
This isn't a joke.
I...
can't marry Gu Jun Pyo.
No matter how I look at it, I don't think
I'm ready for marriage right now.
I'm sorry.
To cause so much trouble for my fickleness.
Dad.
Everything is my fault, so please
continue your business with Shinhwa Group.
President Kang...
and...
Gu Jun Pyo...
I'm truly sorry.
Please forgive me.
I can't believe this.
What's going on?
I've always been a pretty cool person.
Unni!
Oh yeah, Chen...
Chen, what happened?
We're taking her there right now.
Gu Jun Pyo.
Jan Di.
How long are you going to cry?
If someone saw you...
They might think you're in mourning.
Can anything be any
more moving than that?
Jae Kyung unni is so cool.
That day...
You asked why I didn't
go that day, right?
I...
don't believe in happy endings.
Ah!
Are you okay?
This is why I always
tell you to be careful!
Sorry.
I'm okay.
You have guests, so I'll leave.
Weren't you waiting because
you'd something to tell me?
I have a favor to ask.
Jan Di...
I can't let her go.
Rather than making things hard for her.
I'd thought it might be
better to send her to you.
I didn't even want to imagine it,
but if I had to...
I thought the other person has to be you.
You were the only one it could be, Ji Hoo.
That's what I thought.
Gu Jun Pyo!
But still, I can't do it.
The grass lawn here is still the same.
I missed it.
Don't you regret it?
How can I not?
The moment I let Gu Jun Pyo go,
I've been regretting it terribly.
I was rooting for you, Ji Hoo.
But now that I've given up...
I can't even do that anymore.
Not so long ago...
I asked Jun this...
Between friendship and love...
If he could only choose one...
Which one would he choose?
He said he wouldn't give
up either one of them.
There's a saying that people generally
get as much as they strive for.
Neither you nor I are ambitious enough.
I'm leaving for New York tomorrow.
Can you give this to Jan Di for me?
That J J...
How much I'd hoped it stood
for Ji Hoo and Jan Di.
Ji Hoo, you probably didn't realize it.
Good luck.
Take care.
She prepared it so you both could
spend the night comfortably.
Then...
Excuse me.
Please deliver this message
to Jae Kyung unni.
If it's okay with her...
that nothing has changed
with me being her dongseng.
Eat.
Miss Geum Jan Di.
Would you like to dance with me?
I can't dance.
I've been wanting to ask
you this for a while.
What is it?
Why me?
I'm not pretty, and I don't have
money or status. I have nothing.
Why did you like me?
Because I have all that.
What?
Money, status, looks...
Because I have all that.
I don't need that from you.
Geum Jan Di, all you have
to be is Geum Jan Di.
Wow, it's really pretty.
Do you see the brightest
star over there?
Yeah.
It's the Sirius star,
aka Orion's big dog.
The brightest star in the winter sky.
You can say that its existence
is very like Gu Jun Pyo.
What?
Then I am... That one.
That one. That one. That one.
I want to be that one.
You sure do know how to pick them.
That's the second
brightest star, Procyon.
Fine, I'll be nice.
Always wandering all over
the place and barking non stop...
It fits you perfectly.
What?
But...
How did you come to like stars?
When I was young...
My dad sent me a telescope for my birthday.
He wrote on the card,
"Study the stars well, so we can
go watch them together next time."
So you went to watch
the stars with your dad?
No.
Huh?
We never went, not even once.
Why not?
Believing in that promise...
I studied so hard, I could
have become an astronomer.
Do you know what I got for
Christmas a few years later?
Another telescope.
That's when I realized he didn't send the first
gift or the card, but that his secretary did.
Do you know what my dream is?
Going to watch the stars with your son.
You're so simple-minded.
To not make promises I won't keep.
Jan Di.
Yeah?
I'm sorry for hurting you.
Jan Di.
What now?
I love you.
I can see love is in the air.
When did you get here?
Jan Di!
Ga Eul!
Why do you need that?
That's what I am saying.
It's a relief.
What is?
You're smiling.
Here.
This is...
I don't know why she had it. But...
She asked me to give it to you.
What about Unni?
Where is she right now?
She's going to leave soon.
Miss, it's time to go in now.
Unni! Jae Kyung unni.
Hey, Monkey!
Jan Di!
Gu Jun Pyo!
How did you get here?
How can you leave like this?
You weren't going to say
goodbye to your dongseng?
How can a big sister act like that?
Sorry.
Honestly, I'm really
bad at saying goodbye.
So the fierce Ha Jae Kyung
has a weakness too?
That's right.
Take care.
And...
Thanks.
If you guys break up, I'm going
to feel so wronged, I'll die.
So if you want to break up, report
to me first and get my approval.
Understand?
Unni.
Let me give you a hug,
my Jan Di dongseng.
I have to go.
Have an enjoyable flight.
This is mine.
I picked it out first.
I had dibs on it first.
Better let it go now.
What's up with you?
Hey!
Say that you’re sorry right now, jerk!
Get off me!
Apologize, quickly!
I know these were Jan Di’s originally.
But let me have just this one...
Give me just this one thing.
Don't you think I should have at
least one memory to cherish as well?
As complications arise between
Shinhwa Group and JK Group merger,
the international markets are
focusing their attentions on them.
In an effort to minimize the negative reaction
toward the cancelled marriage between
Shinhwa Group and American-based
JK Group, Shinhwa Group is...
Hey, open up.
Hey.
Open the door!
I said to open the door!
Hey, do you not hear me?
Don't you think you should come
over to my place this time?
What's the point of finding
another house again?
You don't know if that witch will demolish it
or kick you out in the middle of the night.
I need to pack all my stuff right away.
It's really a big problem.
There's no need to do that.
I knew you were pathetic,
but I didn't take you for a child
who'd act innocent and then
pull this stunt behind our backs.
I’m truly at loss for words.
It was my mistake for not getting rid of the
roots of evil like you from the beginning.
How much I regret that mistake.
Excuse me.
Why are you acting like this to my Jan Di?
Jan Di didn't do anything.
She even try to help them
out with their relationship.
If you have eyes, then look at that.
[Shocking engagement cancellation!
JK Group & Shinhwa Group merger scrapped.]
[Indications of Shinhwa Group's stock
price crashing, could this be the 2nd crisis?]
Do you know how much has been lost
because of a worthless child like you?
The scale and amount of the damage caused
cannot be comprehended by the likes of you.
Take a look at what you've done to our family!
I'll not let this matter slide by.
It's best for you not
to expect me to let this go easily.
I'll make you realize exactly
who you're messing with.
And make sure you
regret it to its fullest.
Isn't this what you wanted?!
Really!
Those words are too harsh for a child!
Grandpa!
Sir, what brings you here?
It's been a long while, Hee Soo.
Or should I call you President Kang?
You sure have changed a lot.
Let's talk about us later.
First, let's discuss about that child.
How do you know that child, Sir?
She is going to become my granddaughter.
What do you mean?
She’s the child that I've my sight set
on for becoming a partner for my Ji Hoo.
Grandpa...
Are you serious?
Up until now, I've only
watched from the sideline.
But now she's no different
from my family.
So I'd like ask that you don't
deal with her so harshly.
Jan Di, what are you doing?
Get your bags and follow me!
Y-Yes.
Sunbae.
She'll be staying with
us from today on.
What?
Ji Hoo, what are you doing?
You should show her the room.
Alright, then.
I came because Grandpa
dragged me here.
But I can go to
Ga Eul’s house tomorrow.
You kids!
Who said you two grown kids can be
alone in a room with the door closed?
Grandpa.
I'm sorry.
And I thank you.
I'm just going to stay for tonight
and...
Don't you dare think
about running away.
There’s no need to
be thankful either.
You're the one who shoved me into this
house with that child over there.
I brought you here because you're
impertinent and I want to punish you.
What?!
Do you know how hard
to always watch how
you act and speak in
front of your grandchild?
But Grandpa and Sunbae...
If you've started something, then
you should finish it through to the end.
But Gra...
Jan Di might be
uncomfortable staying here.
It's not you, who's uncomfortable?
I don't know anything about how
you guys feel towards each other.
It'll probably depend on destiny.
But that child has nowhere to go.
So I want to provide her
the roof over her head.
There's no need to like her
or feel uncomfortable.
But I am against a bright
girl like Jan Di...
being together with someone
so brusque like you.
When I think about it,
it was the first time
Eun Jae'd ever asked a favor.
Do you know what...
I was doing that night?
I have a favor.
Favor?
Go to the location written on
there by 7:00 am tomorrow.
Don't ask the reason.
Cha Eun Jae.
What is this?
I'm going to go.
Yi Jung.
I really... hope that you’ll come.
[Mom]
What is it now?
A family trip?
What's the point of
dragging him into it?
Mom, can’t you just
let him go now?
Please. Just give up now!
Please come with me.
Actually, I have a request...
A favor.
Favor?
As a part time job.
Will you come and act as his
companion whenever you've time?
M-Me?
All you have to do is tell him stories
or show him your face once in a while.
Who is this person?
He’s like an older brother
to me, just like family.
I see.
B-But why are you asking me...
Because this person needs
someone with a warm spirit.
Jan Di is the warmest person
I've ever met in life...
Would it be sufficient as an answer?
Of course, I'll pay you for your time.
Oh, no need.
If I can be of any help,
then I'd definitely do it.
This is a personal request.
So you must not mention it to
the President or Young Master.
Sure.
Okay.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Geum Jan Di.
Although I’m lacking in many ways,
I’ll become a good companion to you.
Let's try our best starting today.
Fighting!
Fighting...
Young Master.
What happened to Jan Di?
Is she alright?
Professor Yoon has taken
her to his house.
To Ji Hoo's house?
For now, that's the safest
place for her to stay.
Let me borrow your cell phone.
[I’m relieved knowing that
she’s staying at your house.]
Jun Pyo...
But why do I feel so unease?
I feel afraid.
[Gu Jun Pyo]
The number you called is not
answering. To leave a message...
Jan Di.
Woo Bin sunbae!
I feel like dying these days.
Yi Jung goes around
like he's an invalid.
Jun Pyo is locked up.
It's so stressful.
Look, even my skin's suffering.
Hey, don't worry too much.
It's nothing too serious.
He's just not allowed to go out.
He messed up the wedding
in front of that great person.
It'd be strange if there
wasn't any consequence.
I'm going to visit Jun Pyo.
Do you have any message
you want me to pass on?
How about Jan Di, are you alright?
I'm doing very well.
What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
It's just...
You and Ji Hoo both seem so at ease,
with you staying at his house.
Geum Jan Di, Gu Jun Pyo,
and Yoon Ji Hoo...
I don't know what kind of
fate awaits for the three of you.
But my life's a bit
complicated too lately.
I'm just saying.
Hang in there, Geum Jan Di.
And, thanks.
For what?
Ji Hoo.
I’ve never seen him looking so
relaxed as he has been these days.
And finding his grandfather for him too.
It's all thanks to you.
No.
Of late, I'm the one
who's being a burden.
Okay, let's clean your hand.
It feels good, doesn't it?
The most unfortunate encounters are
like those with fish bones.
The longer the encounter, the more
the fishy smell sticks with you.
Encounters to be most cautious about
are like a flower blossom.
Because it brings exuberance during
full bloom, but gets discarded when wilted.
The most beautiful encounters are
like those with handkerchiefs.
They wipe away your sweat
when you're tired,
and your tears when you're sad.
I really like this verse.
Encounters like a handkerchief.
What do you think, Mister?
I hope to be like a handkerchief
type of person for you.
Right?
Right, Mister?
Then...
Let me read you something else.
Want me to do it for you?
Huh?
No, it's okay.
If I leave it to you...
you'd not be able to go to
school from tomorrow on.
You can't cut it there...
I don't need my hair cut in the back!
Not in the back...
Let me help you.
It's okay.
I'll do it.
You have to let me repay you
for cutting my hair.
It's a car wash!
Hey, it's a car wash!
I wanted to tell you.
That I...
love you.
I wanted to shout it aloud.
That's all.
Are you just going to give up?
Are you really going to
run away like this?!
Do you think this is
what she wanted?
It doesn't matter anymore.
It matters to me!
In order to have a heart that's strong,
and will not break easily...
It has to be turned
upside down, stepped on,
and able to withstand
the heat in a kiln.
That's what you said.
You said that that's the only way
you won't have any regrets, Sunbae!
I must’ve been talking crap.
It's not over yet.
You haven't done everything yet!
I won't give up like this.
This hand. I'm going to make
it move again at all costs.
Hurry and leave.
Just this once.
Go over there!
Thank you.
Goodbye!
Hey, Ga Eul!
What's wrong?
Hey. Are you okay?
Hey, what on earth have
you been up to lately?
You don't sleep at night, and I heard
you come to work really early too.
Tell me. What's wrong with you?
Is it something
I can help you with?
Don't worry.
Just a little bit more,
and it'll be over.
Huh?
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Okay. Let's move out.
1...2...3!
I'm going out with my friend.
I don't care if you are
going to follow us or not.
Then, we will follow you.
Representative Lee.
You're ready, right?
Move your car!
What the hell is this?!
You almost caused an accident!
Don't worry, just go.
I'll take good care of him.
Mommy will be back later.
Have fun with Noona, okay.
I'll leave him to you.
Say, goodbye Mommy.
Bye Mommy!
Bye!
Let's have fun with Noona, okay?
Hold on a second.
Gu Jun Pyo!
Are you okay?
R-Right now?
I'm so tired!
What's that thing?
It's not a thing, but a child.
How long since we last been on a date,
and you drag along this rug rat?!
Did you adopt him from somewhere?
Noona, let's go over there. Yeah?
Alright, let's go.
I wondered why all of a sudden,
you want to meet at the zoo.
Do you like this 3rd wheel
more than me?!
If you don't want to be a 3rd wheel yourself,
then stop whining and just follow me.
Let's go.
Hey, wait for me!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: ahsieee, Beeni
Spot Translators: rameninmybowl, javabeans, meju
Timer: knitoe
Editor/QC: jtranla
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
It's strange.
What?
It feels like I'm in a scene
in a hazy dream right now.
The preparations are going well, right?
What are you thinking of doing?
We have to take this opportunity
to yank out the roots.
It's fortunate there's something more
important to that foolish girl than money.
I didn't raise you to be so pathetic.
Thanks.
I may be cool,
but I'm not a good guy.
Please get rid of the misconception
that good girls always want good guys.
Really?
She forced Ga Eul's father into
early retirement without warning?
This is all...
An attempt to get rid of Geum Jan Di.
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get it for FREE @ D-addicts.com