Boys Before Flowers
Enjoy:)
Episode 20
This...
Ah, isn't that pretty?
It looked unique and not complicated,
so I thought I'd try making one too.
Where did you get this?
Why?
Tell me!
Where did you get this?
The teacher here...
Because to me, that friend was my kiln
and my spinning wheel.
Because that kid night cry,
I was afraid.
Like my father...
Like my mother...
Because that kid might cry
because of me,
I ran away.
I can't believe it...
Go away!
Hey you, I saw it first.
You should stop now, don't you think?
This...
Do you know what an insult this is
to that person?
Giving money to help someone
is an insult?
Guess you didn't think of it that way?
In all my life, it's the one wish
that I've truly wanted.
Just this once, couldn't you just
give in?
How?
How does a man like that become
your wish?
You're the heiress to Shinhwa Group.
You're in a position where the best men
in Korea, no in Asia, aren't good enough.
Come to your senses.
To me, that person is the best.
Because I love him, no one,
no matter who they are, can replace him!
Pathetic fool.
For sentiment that will disappear in a
few years, you'll gamble away your life?
That won't do.
Mom!
That's right! Because I'm your mother,
because you were born into Shinhwa Group,
I can't permit you to gamble on your
childish love.
Do something like that in your next life.
Hey!
Miss!
Oh, this young lady!
What do we do?
Miss!
Why is she like this?
Are you OK?
What should I do?
Hello?
The thing is, the young lady has fainted.
Here? We're at...
Are you waking up?
How...?
It could have been really bad.
Jan Di, you fainted on the street.
But how did you...
If I hadn't called you at that moment,
what would you have done?
How can someone be so foolish?
If you had a problem, I told you
to think of me as a big sister.
Being sisters, did you think those were
empty words?
It's not that.
You made a mistake, right?
Then, from now on, you have to
listen to me.
From now on, Jan Di, you're my guest.
Until your parents return, you can't
ever leave this house. Understand?
Unni, that's a little...
Regardless of Jun Pyo, didn't you say
that you'd think of me as a real sister?
Um, still... Madam President...?
You don't need to worry about my mother.
For the time being, she's away on a trip.
So now, you don't have any other
excuses, right?
Then, despite my sense of shame,
I'll stay for a while.
That's right! You should've been like
this from the start.
But I too have one condition.
Condition?
I don't like to eat for free.*
*meaning receive charity
To cover room and board here, let me
do some work.
What?!
No matter how much I think about it,
there's something I'm curious about.
What?
The reason why you're so good to me.
Honestly, it's a little odd.
Gu Jun Pyo is now engaged.
Also, being so good to me, if
Madam President came to know...
Are you really that curious about it?
Here, finished!
It's a present.
Starting today, this is the new
housemaid, Geum Jan Di.
She may be no different from my younger
sibling, but she insists on working here,
I expect all of you to help her out.
My name is Geum Jan Di.
Please kindly assist me.
There is no need to request assistance.
Grandma, please take good care of her.
If that one needs to request assistance,
then it may be better to not even start.
Oh, Grandma, a little gently. Hm?
No, it's fine. I will be diligent!
Please treat me the same as the others.
Diligent is not good enough.
Perfect. In this house, anything less
than perfect will not be tolerated.
Are you ready?
The answer is always "Yes", "I understand",
politely and in a moderate tone!
Yes... I understand.
Soon, I'll be going to the States.
Will you be OK by yourself?
Please don't worry about me.
You, newcomer!
What are you dreaming about,
you're not coming?
Yes, Grandmother.
"Grandmother", you say?
How can I be Miss Geum Jan Di's
grandmother?
Then, what should I call you?
Here, you and I are at our sacred
workplace. You call me "sunbae".
Sun... Sunbae?
How long are you going to blankly
stand there?
If you're to learn from the ground up,
even a minute is precious.
Quickly come along.
Uh... yes!
In this house, a maid is not merely
a housekeeper.
She's a specialist who works to perfectly
match her employer's needs and be prepared.
Ironing a shirt's cuffs and sleeves
in one minute is a must.
From knowing how to dust an
expensive painting,
to knowing how to organize a wine list,
she must exercise perfect care.
Chanbatin.
Chambertin.
Now, this time, we shall go over the
dinner menu.
Shrimp carpaccio with white
truffle aïoli.
Shrimp...carpa!
Asparagus-garnished skirt steak.
A...aspara..gan!
Bell pepper chutney lined arugula, topped
with smoked duck.
Duck?
I'm hungry. Give me some food first.
Basil oil drizzled...
Len...
L-le...
Lentil beans.
Oh, you scared me!
Grandma! You are still alive?
Yes. Regretfully, I could not yet
pass away.
I... no, what I meant was...
It's just that I haven't seen you
for a long time.
What happened?
Didn't you say that you were going to run
a housekeeping school or something?
The household was such a mess, I couldn't
sit back and watch, so I came back.
Butler Lee, in the meantime, will be at
the school on my behalf.
Why?
Do you have a problem with that?
N..no.
But who's she?
Is she your trainee?
Where did you find the idiot
who doesn't even know the menu?
An unavoidable situation arose so
I am helping her out.
Let me introduce you.
Please turn around.
Nice to meet you.
From now on, this is the person on whom
you will wait, Young Master Jun Pyo.
Please look kindly upon me.
Geu... Geum Jan Di!
Starting today, this is Young Master
Jun Pyo's personal maid, Geum Jan Di.
Personal... maid!
Please! I will do everything that
you tell me to do.
But what's this about Gu Jun Pyo's
personal maid...
"Gu Jun Pyo", you say?
In this house, there is no one who can
address him like that.
Whatever relationship you two may have
on the outside,
while you're working in this house,
address him as "Young Master".
Ah... yes. Yes.
So that's why, please reconsider my being
Young Master's personal maid.
Grandmother... Sunbae.
Please, I beg of you.
Did you forget already?
An employee cannot do only what
she wants to do.
As I expected, it wasn't right to come here.
Even now, could I say that I'm leaving?
If you had a problem, I told you
to think of me as a big sister.
Being sisters, did you think those
were empty words?
Ah... Geum Jan Di! Gu Jun Pyo's
personal maid, Geum Jan Di, respond.
Gu Jun Pyo?
Yeah. Geum Jan Di, come to my room
immediately. Over.
What?! This is really...
Hey!
What do you think you're doing right now?
It took you 3 minutes.
Next time, try to get here within
one minute.
What?!
This is really...
An order to Gu Jun Pyo's personal maid,
Geum Jan Di.
Immediately cook up some delicious ramen.
No!
Because of your sister, I can do nothing
but try to tolerate this.
Within 10 minutes, bring the ramen.
Transmission ended.
Gu Jun Pyo... do you really want to die?
To whom are you replying so carelessly
and informally?
I understand.
What is this?
Oh, you told... me to cook ramen for you.
But there's no lid!
Lid...
Are you satisfied now?
- Where are you going?
- Why... !
W..why?
Until I finish eating, sit over there.
There's a button. Push it.
Y...you! I mean, Young... Master.
What are you up to now?
The chair is so uncomfortable.
I'm in the process of testing it so just
do as I say.
What time is it, you're still in bed?
Quickly get ready and go to the
Young Master.
Excuse me?
Starting from the morning?
Oh, this is a problem. He's being
difficult again.
If this keeps up, won't we all get fired?
Seriously.
- What should we do?
- I don't know.
You're not leaving?!
Know that if you wake me one more
time, you're fired! Got it?
Don't cry.
It'll be alright.
Young Master Jun Pyo, you should
get up now.
Didn't I say that if you wake me one more
time, then I'll fire you?
Do you want to die?
Gu Jun Pyo.
You're not gonna get up?
Because of you, people have to even fear
for their jobs? Get up!
Ah, what is this?!
Geum Jan Di.
I'll get up. If I get up, then
it'll be fine...
About being fired... I take it back.
Excuse me? Young Master, thank you!
Truly, thank you!
Now it's over, right?
- Jan Di!
- Thank you!
You're the best!
Is there anything you want to eat?
I'll make it all for you!
Yi Jung!
Why are you here?
I always did the hiding, and never had
to do the seeking.
Turned out to be pretty difficult.
Cha Eun Jae.
Didn't you hide a little too well?
I almost gave up playing hide and seek.
Yi Jung.
Why the hell nothing turns out well
for us?
What's worse? Your luck in working as your
ex-boyfriend's personal maid?
Or my luck, ultimately reuniting a guy
with his first love
after finally deciding to make an effort
with him.
Comparing such things is too sad.
Welco...
Jae Kyung unni!
Jan Di, did you move again?
Where happened to your house?
There's absolutely nothing left of it.
Oh, that... a situation kind of came up.
So where did you go?
Let's have another housewarming!
I'll buy something delicious to eat
and bring it.
Ga Eul, like the last time, we can play
the truth game again. Sounds good?
Where is it? Tell me.
The thing is, my situation is...
It's my house!
Huh?
Right now, she's sharing a room with me.
So we can't have a housewarming and we
can't even invite you over.
I'm sorry.
So it's like that. Still, it's a relief
that you're staying with Ga Eul.
You could have stayed with me also!
Thank you for saying that.
Oh, Ga Eul, pack up some porridge for me.
Porridge? Why?
After the trip, I couldn't see Jun so I
called, but he said that he was sick.
So I'm going to visit him.
Jun?
Wait, Gu Jun Pyo is sick?
This morning, he was...
Jan Di, isn't it time for you to
go volunteer?
I'm right, aren't I?
Oh, oh, it's over.
Well, his breathing sounds fine.
There is a bit of a fever but overall,
he's healthy.
Thank you!
Goodbye.
Take your mother's hand.
Goodbye!
Doctor!
Doct...
Grandfather!
Grandfather! Grandfather, are you OK?
Yes, I'm fine. I know my own disease.
Oh, there's no need to be afraid.
You're not fine.
What would you have done if I weren't
here, like last time?
You're right.
I can't let you keep living by yourself.
Are you saying you're going to put me
in a nursing home?
Yes.
This girl!
Sunbae!
What's up so suddenly?
What is all this?
They are stuff for moving.
By any chance.. are there any empty
rooms in here?
Hurry up! Hurry!
Wait a moment.
Hurry hurry!
Haha, I have no clue what you are up to.
How come my personal maid isn't here?
Hm?
Geum Ja...
My new personal maid.
Her master is having a dinner,
but how come she's nowhere here?
Your personal?
Today is a Saturday, Young Master.
So what?
Miss Jun Hee assigned Geum...
She planned the rookie maids' work hours,
so they would not interfere her school
and her part-time jobs.
Also only for five days per week.
That is why..
Five days per week?
What kinda rule is that?!
She ain't working for the government.
Miss Jae Kyung has come.
What?
Jun!
Jun?
Our little Jun was sick? I will take
good care of you!
Let's eat porridge.
Jun Pyo, are you sick?
Here.
Ah~ Ah~
What are you doing Jun Pyo?
Your fiancée tells you to say ah~
Oh my, you're eating well! Is it good?
Sit down, please.
From now on, this is your house.
This girl!
How can things go so fast as lightening
at a time like this?
Listen. my feelings need to adjust...
You've been doing it for the
last 15 years.
Preparing your heart for this.
Do you need more?
From now on, if you don't listen to me,
I am going to let everything out!
What?
About your sickness, Grandfather.
Is it alright to do that?
You've learned all the bad things!
That's what someone else told me!
They said I'm good at covering distances.
Good night.
Hey, Jan Di.
Yeah?
Do you think he will forgive me?
What are you so afraid of?
You are his grandfather.
If he doesn't listen, you can just grab
a stick and hit that boy in his cheeks.
Good night.
All right.
What do you think you're doing?
For grandpa, and Sunbae too,
you all need family.
All I did was find one for you.
Jandi, I am not yet...
You are not ready yet?
Because Grandpa said the same thing.
How long do you need to prepare
your hearts?
Aren't they all useless in the end?
You said before, Sunbae,
that no one can know everything about
one person.
But the person we know, at least we know
what kind of person he is.
The Ji Hoo sunbae I know, really loves
his grandfather.
That is the reason he can forgive him.
Geum Jan Di.
Answer, Geum Jan Di.
Gu Jun Pyo's personal maid!
Did you fall dead somewhere?
You are still not home?
WHAT?! I am not working right now!
Run to me right now.
Call me after 5a.m. on Monday.
I'll pay you overtime then.
What? Do you want ramen?
Hey!
Sit down here.
What? what?
Don't say anything and just sit.
What is this?
It's starting.
I'm leaving.
Geum Jan Di.
Hey! Gu Jun Pyo! We are in big trouble!
Jae Kyung unnie...
Jae Kyung unnie is coming right now!
What?
What are we gonna do? What do we do?
What do you mean what do we do?
Just be quiet.
You know what, we'll just stand up
and say the truth.
Ah, I dont know!
Where are you going?
Hey!
What are you doing?
Hey, why are you going in there?
Gu Jun Pyo, please close the door.
Hey, I'm asking why you're going in there.
Jun, Jun!
Where are you?
I'm here.
You were here!
Hey, monkey, don't you ever sleep? Why
come so late to someone else's home?
It's not someone else, but my partner.
What?
It's so corny, huh?
My father always say that there's
philosophies in every famous lyrics line.
Before, I had no clue what that meant,
but these days, I understand thoroughly.
Is it because I'm dating?
D-dating?
Why did you come anyway?
To spend the night together.
To spend the night?
We should watch this together.
I wanted to watch it but it was too scary
to watch alone.
Sounds good? Let's go.
I realized you liked these when you
were younger.
Let's eat.
I'm not hungry.
At least take this, then.
Unnie, what's going on...
Jan Di, why did you do it?
Why did you trick me?
I thought of you as my real friend.
I wanted to spend my life with you
as sisters.
But how can you do this to me?
Unnie...
That's not it. I'm sorry.. to be honest...
the thing is...
You lied to me, and you scarred me for
life that can never be removed.
Unnie... please calm down and listen...
Jan Di, Jan Di, what are you doing today?
I... I'm really busy today!
Really really busy!
In fact, I was just about to leave!
Really? Alright, bye.
Bye!
Both of you slept well?
So early in the morning...
What is up?
Oh me? I wanted to leave for work
with both of you!
Since it's three of us, let's take
the car.
Let's go! Let's go!
Hurry!
Here it is. Be careful, it is very hot.
Oh! Your temperature is normal.
Here you go.
Oh, Grandma! Grandma!
No!
Miss Kim Mi Ok!
Can you hold the baby for a second?
Oh, please wait a moment.
Sunbae!
Young man! Tea, please!
Yeah, we need a refill.
How can you be so good looking!
I should drink some too then.
Yes, it looks fine.
You can leave this way.
Wait just a second.
It's been long since I've been here.
Do you remember? That time we got scolded
by Grandfather because we were playing
hide-and-seek in the authentication room?
Of course! As a punishment, we had
to scrub the oven.
Right.
And the time you said it was cold,
so I started the fire and then it became
a disaster.
The one who complained
it was cold was you.
No way, it was obviously you.
Wait... was it me?
Your mother is doing all right?
Same as usual.
Want news about my father?
How about you, Yi Jung?
You're doing well, right?
Curious? Were you even curious
about that?
Why did you do that?
What?
How could you just vanish in the air
with no warning whatsoever.
Do you know that feeling?
Like air,
an existence that always stayed by my side
just disappears into thin air,
the bewilderment can't be
described in words.
If you knew, you couldn't have done
that do me
I was not your air.
What?
I wasn't the air, Yi Jung.
I was probably more like a wind, but you
mistaken me as the air.
I was also foolish enough to think
I was the air.
I thought I could stay there as long
as you wanted.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Winds can never return back to their
original place once they fly by.
Oh, it's you, Ga Eul.
I want to sleep so...
Can we get back later?
Sunbae, this is all you experienced
and endured,
and you acted so strong and mature in front of me?
Can you shut that mouth and leave?
No. If I shut my mouth now, I'll have to
see you live this stupid life forever.
Sunbae, you are a liar, a whiny, and
an absolute coward.
What?
You said you acted like you didn't know,
because you thought she would get hurt?
No.
You were just afraid of getting hurt
yourself, Sunbae.
Because you were scared for her to
realize you are pathetic.
Chu Ga Eul...
I know that So Yi Jung's mighty and cool
side is just a mask.
But the So Yi Jung I like is like a child
that is scared to loose love.
Children never hesitate in front of
something they like.
They know that if they lose it,
their tears will burst.
Thank you for today.
You did something you've never done
because of me, right?
Get in, I'll give you a ride.
No, it's fine. Ill go by myself.
Oh Grandfather, that must be very heavy.
Shall we go, Doctor?
Outside the hospital, I shall return
back to old grandpa again.
- Be careful.
- All right.
Put on your seat belt.
Drive carefully.
Be careful on your way home!
Young Master.
You have to get up, Young Master.
You should wake up now.
Young Master!
What do you think you're doing?
5 minutes.
Let me stay like this for just 5 minutes.
Even though I'm holding you like this,
I can't believe that you're here.
Jun! I'm here! Let's...
How do I look?
Jan Di... I can't let her go.
By any chance, you are not going to ask me
to help you run away from the wedding
tomorrow, right?
Gu Jun Pyo.
I am asking the point of your limit.
And how much do I need to deal with?
All of it.
I will repay everything that made
you suffer, Jan Di.
Please forgive me.
Break my arm.
What?
Jun Pyo.
If this is the only way you can stop
this, then just do it.
We're going to become a couple tomorrow
at this very place.
Regardless of our past,
we are going to promise to love
one another until our deaths.