Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Final Episode
Abracadabra...
Gu Jun Pyo, you will
remember Geum Jan Di.
You will remember!
Abracadabra...
Now!
Oh, you scared me!
Hey kiddo, what are you doing?
You must've been too stressed lately.
Getting a pimple on that handsome face...
And what's this?
Can't you tell? It's a lunchbox.
A lunchbox?
Is it good?
This...
- Did you make this?
- Huh?
Yeah. If you like it, then I'll make it again for you.
You may get thirsty.
Should I get you some water?
I remembered something.
What I forgot... it's you, isn't it?
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Yes, goodbye!  Please come again.
Welcom...
One abalone porridge, please.
For me, a pumpkin porridge.
Sunbae!
What brings you all the way here?
Can't you tell?  We came to eat porridge.
Oh, it's hot!
Ah, I'm full!  That was good.
Now, tell us.  What's going on?
For Geum Jan Di who can't take care of
her boyfriend because of her part-time job,
We prepared some news.
Huh?
Jun Pyo finally got discharged.
Seriously?
How can you save something so important
until you finish eating porridge?!
Hurry up and go.
Ga Eul, stay here.
- I'll be back.
- Go.
Sunbae, you're not going?
No.  My reason for coming concerns you.
They look happy.
The dishes in there, I mean.
Instead of being weary from the heat, I get the feeling that they're happy.
Why?
Because they're hoping that if they endure
and turn out well, then they'll be loved.
Just like Ga Eul.
Now, tell me.
I'm ready.
You have something to tell me, don't you?
Today... again, bad news first?
I'm...
Leaving.
But then again, that might not be bad news for you.
To where?
Sweden.
When... no.
For how long?
Soon.  Maybe, around 4 or 5 years?
That's good.
You'll go and become an even better clay artist.
Now that I think about it, this could also be good news.
So what's the other news?
That when I come back,
You'll be the very first person whom I'll seek out.
Sunbae.
Well, I meant only if you still haven't
found your soulmate by then.
Put in more firewood.  Do you think
that it'll ever reach 1300°C like this?
Gu Jun Pyo, congrats on getting discharged...
Oh, it's Jan Di unni.  Unni, hi!
Oh... hi.  Yu Mi, you're here too.
What are you doing here?
Ji Hoo isn't here.
I heard that you got discharged
so I came to say "congrats".
Jeez, that's really touching.
Just look out for your boyfriend.
Does Ji Hoo know what you're doing?
Hey!  Watch what you say.
What?
There's no reason for Ji Hoo sunbae
to hear such talk from you.
Then be careful to not humiliate him.
You're right.
I was wrong to come here.
Be sure to take care of yourself.
What's with you, Oppa?
That's not nice.
Unni, don't go.
Soon, they should be bringing in the tea.
Oppa's tea tastes really great.
Have some before you go.
The tea is ready.
Yes, please bring it over here.
Unni, come here and sit down.
Oh, it looks delicious.
I'll eat it myself.
Is it good?
- It crumbled.
You eat it.
Mmm, it's good.
I'm leaving.
You.
Don't come back.
Whenever I see you, I get into a really bad mood.
I mean, you get on my nerves.
Fine.
I'm sorry.  I won't come again!
Unni!
The person whom Jun Pyo oppa has
to remember... by chance, is it you?
So it is.
But as you can see for yourself, it seems
that seeing you isn't good for him.
Because whenever he sees
you, his condition gets worse.
So for the time being, it may be
better if you don't come here.
Don't worry.
At every opportunity, I'll try to get
him to remember you on his own.
Well, see you!
Make that for me.
What?
The lunchbox that you made before.
Lunchbox?
Yeah.
The egg rollups that you made
when I was in the hospital.
Make that for me again.
Ah, that?
OK, Oppa.
But there are so many tastier dishes here.
Why do you want to eat that, of all things?
My apologies.
Sunbae.
Don't run away.
- Please let go of me.
- You can't.
You can't back down now.
Jan Di!
It's all over now.
It's all useless.
Even though he lost his memory...
Even if we had to start over again...
I had believed that he would remember me.
But... I was wrong.
- It's not like that.
- No.
It may be upsetting and unfair,
but I have to acknowledge it.
The Gu Jun Pyo whom I liked...
The Gu Jun Pyo who loved me...
He doesn't exist anymore.
I told you.  You can't
be the mermaid princess.
You two breaking up because
of this absurd situation...
I can't allow that.
It's not because of Yu Mi.
In the end, Geum Jan Di and Gu Jun Pyo...
Were only...
This must have been all that we were.
Try it.
What?  It doesn't taste good?
This isn't it.
Huh?
It's not the same taste as before.
That one... Did you really make it?
Of... of course!
Who else could've made it?
It's probably because every time it's made,
the taste comes out differently.
Next time, I'll make it properly.
Is something bothering you?
That girl.
Whether it's Jan Di or Jap Cho...*
*wordplay: "jan di" = grass; "jap cho" = weed
That girl's expression...
I can't seem to erase it.
That's too much!
How can you be like that?
Ever since the hospital until now,
I'm the one who's been by your side!
But it's the expression of that unni who sometimes
comes by and irritates you which gets to you?
Your friends treat me like I'm
a pain and always take her side.
And her boyfriend ignores me as if I had some disease.
But still...
Because of you...
Because I was worried about you, I tolerated all of it.
But if you're like this too...
Then what's Yu Mi* supposed to do?
*character's habit to refer to herself in 3rd person
Hey...
What's the matter?
Jun Pyo and Yu Mi invite you!
Surprise Pool Party!!
Unni!
You came.
Been well?
That's good, because I had
something to report to you.
Report?
Seems that Oppa doesn't remember you after all.
Really?
Also, one more thing.
I hate to say this to you,
but Yu Mi likes Jun Pyo oppa.
What?
It wasn't on purpose.  But
somehow, I came to like him.
To the point that I can't be separated from him.
Oppa feels the same way as Yu Mi.
Sorry.
But you understand, don't you?
A person's heart, by its nature, doesn't
always do what we want it to do.
Oh... it's already that time.
I have to tell everyone the
reason for tonight's party.
Reason?
Unni, come over in a bit, OK?
Don't break down here.
Let's go.
And hear whatever it is.
We had special news to tell everyone.
That's why we asked you to come tonight.
Gu Jun Pyo and Jang Yu Mi.
The two of us have decided to go together
next month to study abroad in America.
What?
What's that girl talking about?
Study abroad?
I will continue with my harp studies.
And Oppa will study business administration.
During the time that we can't see
each other, please don't be too sad.
And until we meet again, please be happy.
Looks like she's is no ordinary girl.
She's cunning, stabbing us in the back like this.
Let's go.
I'll get you a glass of warm water.
Gu Jun Pyo!
Do you remember this?
What's that?
The names on this... you don't remember?
"JJ"?
How am I supposed to know this?
I'll give it back.
Take it.
Why would I take something like this?
If you want to throw it away, do it yourself.
Fine.
Gu Jun Pyo.
Just one thing...
I'll ask you just one more thing.
Now what?
Do you know how to swim?
Swim?
I don't do things like swimming.
Don't or can't?
Because of a bad memory from childhood,
I don't swim.  I never learned how.
No.
You know how to swim.
Who are you?
What do you think you know
about me, to go on like this?
You're not scared of anything in this world,
but bugs make you shudder.
Rather than have one finger on his girlfriend broken,
you're the idiot who prefers to have his ribs ripped out.
Even though you can't tell the difference
between "privacy" and "pride",
You're the ignoramus who insists that there are
38 strategies, loudly as if you ate a train's heart*.
*referring to one of his past misquotes
You say that you hate kids.
But with your own son,
You want to see the stars with him,
and be an attentive father.
You're a lonely guy with much affection.
What are you?
That's precisely you... Gu Jun Pyo.
I'm asking what the hell your point is!
Call it out.
My name.
Do we not have another chance?
I still think about you.
But you probably don't know that.
Ultimately, is this it?
Are we going to end like this?
Is this fine with you?
I don't think that I can make it.
A love like yours…
Even if I die, I don't think that I'll have it again.
What do I do?
If my heart isn't yours, then
there's no one who can hold it.
Please, hold onto me.
You know that no matter
how much I try, I can't erase you.
Please, hold onto me.
What do I do?
Even now, I live each day
broken by your single word.
Tell me.
If being like this is wrong.
Like me, are you living each day in pain?
Tell me.
You and me.
Is it already too late?
Do we not have another chance?
Jan Di...
Geum Jan Di.
Jan Di!
Even though I tell it not to go.
Even though I tell it to stop.
My heart keeps going towards you.
It doesn't wear out.
It doesn't decrease.
Why is my love like this?
One by one, I count and count the memories.
My heart can't rest for even a moment.
Like baggage which becomes hard to control,
Why can't I even throw them away?
Hey, Geum Jan Di.
Wake up!
Really, something must've happened to my heart.
I must've become a fool blinded by love.
Just one place, every day one place.
Looking at the sad light that is you.
Jan Di.
Geum Jan Di!
My tears won't stop.
Just one thing... just that you love me.
Can't you tell me?
Are you OK?
Do you remember now?
Geum Jan Di.
Scare a person like that again
and you’ll really be dead!
You do remember.
I’m sorry.
I'm sorry.
Say it again... my name.
Jan Di.
Even my tear glands must be broken.
My tears won't stop.
Just one thing... your heart, that one thing.
Can't you share it with me?
Can't you love me?
Shinhwa High!
Seems like only yesterday you entered
high school but you're already graduating.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Unlike others, I can’t get a job or go to college.
Noona, you don't have to take
a test for Shinhwa University.
It's not the same for the medical school?
In order to get a scholarship, you have to take the test.
No, your life has been so complicated.
Now, do what you want to do.
Anyway, what are you going to wear
to the graduation party tomorrow?
I'm not going!
Why should I?
What?
Aren't you a Shinhwa High graduating student?
Why aren't you going?
Please don't worry about it.
Come outside for a little bit.
Congrats on graduating.
Thanks.
Do you really have to go to medical school?
Why? What are you going to say now?
With your head, there's no guarantee
that studying for another year will help.
There's none.
Even if it did, what if there really were a doctor like you?
You'd probably cut people up.
What?
What, am I wrong?
Even if you don't have a scalpel, you still cut people.
You...
You're not here to congratulate me on graduating, right?
You came to aggravate me, right?
Oh, what?
Hey, Geum Jan Di.
Tomorrow...
Got it?
If you're late this time also, you're dead.
Go in and go to sleep.
Oh, it's F4.
What are we going to do?
It's really them.
Grandfather.
Hmm?
After I throw out the garbage, I'll get your tea.
Oh, you do that.
That little rascal is really…
She's here.
Geum Jan Di.
Why did you come so late?
Well, I was…
Surely, you weren't planning to just
skip this last event, were you?
We're not even in high school,
so why do you think we're here?
Huh?
The great F4 have waited all day
to dance with Geum Jan Di.
Miss Jan Di.
Will you do me the great honor of dancing with me?
Me?
Let's go.
Wait, hold on a minute.
Of the F4, always strong and considerate,
who was like the elder, Woo Bin sunbae.
You were always one step behind,
offering others your help and support.
I know that now.
Although you act cold and mean,
You're actually warmer and
more innocent than the others.
Thanks to you, Yi Jung sunbae, I think
Ga Eul has become a really lovable woman.
Isn't it about time for you to give her up?
Rascal.
What do I do? When my clothes are like this?
It's perfect.
Geum Jan Di's clothing style.
To end your high school career,
don't you think it's the best?
Like Alice falling into a strange land,
If I went to the emergency exit,
then I could meet you, Sunbae.
Do you know what a huge comfort
that was to me, Sunbae?
You were like someone sent from heaven, like a bonus.
I'll never be able to forget you.
My soulmate…
Ji Hoo sunbae.
Thank you.
What happened to Jun Pyo?
And his phone is turned off.
What if something happened again?
You, tomorrow...
Got it?
Saturday.  4pm.  In front of Nam San Tower.
I... have to leave first.
Seriously!  To the very end, this crazy bastard...
Geum Jan Di!
I didn't know that I'd be like this.
Flustered, carefully, I keep calling only you.
Even if you urge my heart like this,
If you brush by my side,
And also laugh like that, I can't do anything.
Didn't I say that if you're late, you're dead?
Do you want to be late even on a day like today?
You always do whatever you want.
I laugh by myself.
On a night like tonight, what do I do?
I wish you're my love.
Come to me now.
Without knowing it, I get excited.
Today, I'm like this again.
It's not some kind of magic.
This kind of thing...
is quite easy.
Compared to taking care of the lawn*.
*wordplay: JAN DI baht = lawn
Come over here.
The only person to whom I'll promise forever...
... is you.
This coffee costs 36,300 Won, so enjoy it.
Let's go.
It's been a really long time, huh?
But...
This place isn't open?
How come I don't see anyone?
I rented it.
What?
I bought it until morning.
Oh, yeah.  I have something to show you.
- Come here.
- No.
- I said there's something I have to show you.
- No!
What's wrong with you?
There's something I want to show...
You… already knew?
You!
Did you do this so that I can't get married?
You just need to marry me.
Who else are you going to marry?
Move over.
I said, just move over!
Gu Jun Pyo loves Geum Jan Di.
“Our first night!”
It's still here.
Now, you can't get married.
Geum Jan Di.
From here on, listen carefully to what I say.
That's scary…
What now?
We…
Let's get married.
Married?
Yeah.
Married.
Why are you suddenly joking around like this?
I'm not joking.
I just graduated from high school, you know.
I...
Have to go to America.
America?
This time, not because of my mom.
And not because of the company.
I made the decision.
Killing off a perfectly fine father...
Forcibly marrying off her children.
And lobbying all the time to survive.
I don't want that kind of corporation.
I'm...
Going to do my best.
So...
If I can save the company, then that's a relief.
But if I can't...
Then I will shut it down with my own hands.
How long will it take?
4 years.
At least 4 years.
That long?
Which is why...
Come with me.
I can't.
What?
Why not?
When you went to Macau,
I made a decision too.
Regarding my dream and my future.
What I want...
And what I want to do.
Like you...
The thing for which I want to risk
everything and do my best...
Is right here.
So?
Go.
What?
I said go.
After 4 years, if you come back
as a really amazing man,
then I'll think about it again.
Geum Jan Di.
Are you serious?
You...
If you let me go, you're going to regret it.
Hey.
You're the one who'll regret letting me go.
I lose.
But I already know.
That if I let go of you, I'll regret it until I die.
Gu Jun Pyo.
You.... might not be completely stupid.
Do you wanna die?
I shout to the world "I love you", I love you.
For you to become my girl.
[4 YEARS LATER]
Dazzling, always you're my star.
I'll protect you.
I can always you waiting for you.
At the end of an exhausting day,
the one person who makes me laugh.
[Shinhwa Group's Managing Director, Gu Jun Pyo,
on the cover of 3 international economic magazines]
Today, we have the Managing Director of
Shinhwa Group who was successful
earlier this month in his new strategy
in revisiting the software market,
which has been internationally recognized
and brought Korea into the spotlight.
We have Shinhwa Group's Gu Jun Pyo.
Thank you for coming on our show.
Hello.
Not too long ago, I heard that you are the first Korean
to be on the cover of 3 international economic magazines.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Dazzling, always you're my star.
I'll protect you.
I can always you waiting for you.
What took you so long to come to me?
I feel like I have the world.
We'll change the topic a little now.
The viewers, especially the women in Korea,
would like to hear some personal information.
Of course, you're managing an international company,
but you're also a bachelor in your 20s.
So I'm sure that you have had lonely moments.
How do you overcome that?
Dating or love... It seems that you're
curious about these aspects of my life.
You certainly have a faster
understanding of things than others.
Yes.
Well, I would be lying if I said that
there were no lonely or difficult times.
But because of a promise I made with someone,
I was able to rely on that and endure.
Just watching you talk about it,
It seems that you have someone special in your heart.
Yes, well...
A lover... ?
It's just that lately, there's been
a lot of rumors about your marriage.
Since you're already here,
Could you tell us a little about
what kind of person she is?
I pray that you'll allow me.
Accept me as your man.
I promise you that, until the day
I die, my heart won't change.
I can always you waiting for you.
Baby, I will forever with you.
Forever, I'll love only you.
Making it is easy.
Try making it.
You're doing a good job.
- Is that a grape?
- Yes.
There's still too much pressure in your hands.
Yi Jung sunbae.
Hi.
Who is he?
Is he Teacher's boyfriend?
Ahjusshi, by any chance, did you
come back from another country?
Oh, how did you know?
Then...
Did you come back from Sweden?
Little miss, you're really amazing.
Then you're him.
Our teacher said that her boyfriend was there.
You can't say that.
Oh...
Oh.  Wait!
Wait! Wait!
Thank you!
Hey, third year.  Late even on a day like today?
Jeez, that's just like you.
Not a day goes by without you causing trouble.
I'm sorry, Sunbae.
I'm sorry.
Do you think it'll end just like that?
Sunbae!
[Shinhwa University Medical School
Medical Care Service Corps]
- Hey, Geum Jan Di!
- Yes!
Can't you do this properly?
What is this?
- I'm sorry.
- Do it again.
I'm sorry, Sunbae.
You came?
By the look on your face, seems
like you made another mistake.
Sunbae, since you entered on time,
you're already in the graduating class.
When am I, a third year...
Going to finish and in what
millennium will I become a doctor?
The future looks dark.
And flunking out doesn't worry you?
Sunbae!
It was because of you...
That I didn't become an outcast.
When you go to the hospital, when I
think of what I'm going to do then,
The future looks dark.
Then, should I repeat too?
Aigoo, that's alright.
That's scarier than joking about flunking.
But I'm not joking.
Sunbae, you have to hurry and become a doctor
and reopen your grandfather's clinic.
That's why you went back and studied hard.
That wasn't the only reason.
What?
Doctor prince, my throat hurts.
Doctor prince?
Yeah.
Later, Sae Byul is going to marry Doctor prince.
Sae Byul princess.
You can get married next time.
For now, say "ah".
Commoner, can you hear me?
Geum Jan Di, respond.
Geum Jan Di, are you there?
If so, hurry and come meet me on the beach.
Gu Jun Pyo?
It took you 5 minutes!
Can't you walk faster?
Gu Jun Pyo.
What happened?
What do you mean?
Gu Jun Pyo came to Geum Jan Di's office.
Wow.
Seeing you in a white gown...
I guess even an ugly duckling can become a crane.*
*messes up another saying
You are Gu Jun Pyo.
You really are Gu Jun Pyo.
I missed you.
To the point of death.
I'm not going to let go of you again.
You promised, didn't you?
That when I returned, you'd take responsibility for me.
Look here, Mr. Gu Jun Pyo with the bad memory.
To be precise,
I said that when you returned
in 4 years, I would think about it.
I didn't say that I would take responsibility for you.
Your memory is bad too, but you remembered that well.
I recall...
That there was another condition.
What?
About you coming back as a really amazing man.
Can you say that with the Gu Jun Pyo in front of you?
Geum Jan Di.
Please marry this Gu Jun Pyo.
I object to that proposal!
I add to that objection.
Me too!
You two...
Without our permission, it's not
going to happen that easily.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators:  javafiend, ahsieee
Spot Translator:  ahsieee
Timer:  knitoe
Editor/QC:  sayroo
Lyrics Translation:
javafiend (Ji-sun - What Do I Do?)
crazykyootie@soompi (all other songs; edited by javafiend)
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
This is a FREE fansub.  NOT for SALE!!!
Get it for FREE @ d-addicts.com