Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
Episode 6
What's this about?
I've said before right?
You can enjoy things that you would
never have imagined before everyday now.
* (grass field)
Jan Di Bahnt*, I thought you were really strong,
but you're actually very easily
touched by such insignificant things.
This is considered insignificant?
If you're done with being touched,
then let's move on to the main point.
Main point?
What do you think you're doing now?
Don't take your clothes off.
What is he up to?
I said not to take them off.
If you take off your clothes, you're dead!
If you take off your pants,
you're really dead!
I said not to take off!
I already told you not to take them off!
He's still taking them off.
Hey!
I told you not to take them off!
Idiot.
- You're dead.
- Hurry come, idiot.
Do you want to die?
Scared me!
Gu Jun Pyo.
Don't move.
Just stay still.
What's wrong?
Don't move!
What is it?
What's wrong?
There's a snake under your feet.
What?
Under your feet!
Under your feet.
Snake!
I hate snakes the most!
You run quite fast, Gu Jun Pyo.
Continue running!
What's this?!
Run further!
You run quite well!
Madam, this is the rice
wine that you've ordered.
Place it over there.
Yes.
Please enjoy.
Tip.
Thank you, madam.
- Wait a moment.
- Yes, madam?
If you've got the time,
could you help me apply this?
This is my forte, ma'am.
Mom!
The chicken store ahjusshi said that,
if we aren't going to order fried chicken,
then we should quickly return the umbrella.
What?
The price of a fried chicken is enough to feed
our whole family a few bowls of chicken soup.
Take it away!
Honey, what about this?
Kang San.
Isn't our Kang San pretty?
Why are you doing that to him?
Do you want me to help you apply?
Forget it.
My baby totally has baby skin.
What's this?
Jan Di!
Hey! Stop swimming!
Come out for a while!
Jan Di!
Stop swimming!
Seriously.
Hey!
Jan Di!
What's wrong with her?
- What happened?
- Jan Di!
How?
What's this?
What's wrong?
Something's wrong with Jan Di.
She has leg cramps!
Jan Di!
Jan Di, wake up!
Can you hear me?
Chairman.
Where did Jun Pyo go?
According to the report from the private jet
that took off at 5pm, he went to New Caledonia.
Whatever for?
Most probably to relax over the weekend.
OK.
Wait a moment.
Have you confirmed who went with him?
As always, with his F4 friends.
F4 again. When is he going to stop
being the leader of this childish group?
You may go.
Save me!
Mom!
Dad!
Noona!
Save me!
Why would such a great person
like him not know how to swim?
He was kidnapped when he was eight.
What?
When he was young, his parents
entrusted him to the care of a hyung.
He was a bodyguard and a driver.
You're saying,
that person was his kidnapper?
The car that was surrounded by the police
was driven into the water eventually.
Don't tell me…
That's right.
Jun Pyo was inside the car then.
Is everything OK?
OK.
What's this about?
I especially prepared this for you guys.
Doesn't seem it like. It seems like
you prepared this for a special someone.
What does it matter?
It looks delicious.
Come here.
Why?
Let go.
It hurts!
Eat everything here.
Do you think of me as Godzilla?
It's good for your body, so eat more.
You're eating those weird worms everyday.
That's why your leg cramped up.
Strange worms?
In any case,
does it make sense for
a swimmer to almost drown?
A sudden cramp can happen anytime.
*(rat and cramp sound the same in Korean)
Whether is it a rat or a cat,
I can't stand seeing people
around me being so weak.
So don't talk so much, just eat.
You hear me?
How are you?
Your girlfriend is not with you?
This is for your girlfriend.
Are you going to finish that all?
Jun Pyo doesn't like fat girls.
What?
But, the sleepwear that I brought
along should be of some help.
Sleepwear?
Though he is completely into Jan Di now,
you should never belittle his character.
What are you saying now?
Men who have been
rejected are very vulnerable.
I think it's worth giving it a shot.
What in the world are you talking about now?
Don't you like Jun Pyo?
Ridiculous.
Excuse me, I'm a person
with standards too, alright?
Then just now, you said that Jun Pyo
and Jan Di may cause trouble.
Why were you so sensitive?
Don't tell me, you like Jan Di?
That's because Jan Di has
someone else in her mind!
Hey, hey, hey.
So Yi Jung, hurry come here.
Hurry.
Show time!
Gu Jun Pyo, from today onwards,
I allow you to enter the player list.
What is she doing in there?
Hey!
I thought you fainted in there!
You aren't old fashioned till you scrub your body.
Why did you take so long?
You!
This fella's asking to die!
He'll die today!
This is not your room.
It's my room!
Who said it isn't yours?
Then why are you here?
Have you seen me come and go with a purpose?
Purpose?
What purpose?
You're losing something important.
Important?
As a woman...
As a woman.
Is it…
Gu Jun Pyo.
What in the world are you...
Cheap stuff really does fit you well.
You came here to give me this?
Then? Did you think that
I'd do something to you?
If the girl doesn't like me in return,
I won't touch her.
Close your doors tight before you sleep.
Lizards may crawl in.
It may be cheap but if you lose it,
you're dead!
Ga Eul, are you asleep?
Ga Eul!
Do you know what lily of the valley means?
You'll definitely be happy.
So, it's for lovers to give each other.
You know about it?
At the market, earlier today.
I used to come here
frequently with that person.
She said it's very similar to
New Zealand and likes it here.
Is she doing well?
She should be.
Did something happen?
Why did you ask me to go after her?
That…
I finally realized.
What a pathetic man I am.
There was nothing for me to do but
wait all day in an empty apartment.
But, just spending time together
would've been very blissful.
Do you know what it's like being nothing
but a burden to the woman you love?
You called them pathetic fools who
can't do anything on their own.
That was...
You're right.
I can't do anything other than
love one woman like a habit.
What a pathetic fool.
Take it.
I don't want to.
This is meant for Seo Hyun unni.
Sunbae should give it to her personally.
I'm leaving.
You shouldn't stay out here for too long.
You'll catch a cold.
It's cold.
It's so cold, I can't take it.
You should've told me if you were going
somewhere! You got me all worried!
Am I a kid?
I can go for a walk by myself!
What's wrong?
I was afraid that you fell into the pool
or got bitten by a snake or something!
How can I not worry?
Gu Jun Pyo.
I'm sorry.
You.
From now on, don't go swimming by yourself.
Don't walk around by yourself too.
Got it?
Why?
Oh?
It's hot.
Be careful.
Do you want some too?
No, it's okay.
Where is it?
What?
The thing I gave you.
Oh, that…
It's in my room.
I'm afraid that I'd lose it when I'm outside.
Would you let me off if I do?
It's alright if you know.
Hold it tight.
Hold it more.
Mine!
OK!
What's that?
It doesn't suit you.
Really?
I liked it.
What?
It's Jan Di's.
She dropped it last night.
Return it to her.
Play ball!
Jun Pyo!
Why aren't you playing?
Shit.
Am I a kid?
I can go for a walk by myself!
What's wrong?
Oh, that…
It's in my room.
I'm afraid that I'd lose it when I'm outside.
Would you let me off if I do?
Jun Pyo!
The ball!
Are you OK?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Hey!
Where did Ji Hoo go?
Over there.
Are you going somewhere?
Fishing.
With this boat?
So long as there's a white sail and wind,
I can go anywhere I want to.
Do you want to come along?
Can I?
If you promise to be quiet
and not scare the fish off.
You let it go.
You're just going to let it go?
Can you bear to eat a fish
that lives in a place like this?
Goodbye, fish!
Bye!
You're trying really hard.
Why do you keep following me?
It'd be hard to paddle alone.
Though your legs do seem strong enough.
So,
shall we continue with what
we were saying last night?
What were we saying?
You said that Geum Jan Di likes another guy.
Is that true?
Since when did I say such a thing?
Who is it?
Stop saying all that useless stuff.
Paddle properly!
I'm sure he's the bad boy type.
I understand women very well.
Girls like Geum Jan Di
have a thing for bad boys.
It must be that kind who wants to depend on
strong women and take advantage of them.
That's not it!
That person may very
well be Jan Di's soulmate.
Soulmate?
That's why I say women can't make it.
Do you really believe in those things?
Yes, of course.
Playboys like you can't understand,
but there is such a thing as a true
love who stays with you all your life.
So, have you met your lifetime match?
Not yet.
But when he shows up, I won't let go,
because I'd regret losing someone
like that for the rest of my life.
Why aren't you paddling?
I've been paddling by myself.
Where are we going?
I've something to show you.
There, look down now.
Wow, it's a heart.
It's really shaped like a heart.
I told myself that when I found a girl
whom I like, I must bring her here.
Did you see?
My heart?
What's up?
Ji Hoo's in an emergency.
Look.
It says that he's of a
strong political background.
I heard that he's a strong candidate
of the next Prime Minister election.
Ji Hoo seemed to know about it even
before he returned from Paris.
I didn't see him the whole afternoon.
His luggage is still in his room though.
What should we do?
He'll be alright.
I know him.
Now I understand why your prince was dumped.
Ga Eul,
what should I do?
What?
What I said came really came true.
Ji Hoo sunbae must be really angry with me.
Though this is just my imagination,
I hope she marries someone of a royal
status or someone who may become president.
Like Diana or Audrey Hepburn,
be a princess who contributes to world peace.
Something like that.
She's just a model.
Why?
Didn't the French president
divorce his wife to be with a model?
Who would know?
Maybe the next president of
France or some Prince in Europe
will fall in love with Unni at first
sight and ask for her hand in marriage.
How did you come in?
Did you forget who
the owner of this place is?
Geum Jan Di.
My heart... have you accepted it?
What?
Don't make me wait for too long.
Is it true?
It's just a rumour right?
It was reported wrongly right?
I'm sorry.
I really didn't...
It seems like you understand her better than I do.
Sunbae.
He's someone who is very
compatible with Seo Hyun.
I would never be able to compare with him.
It's not like that.
It can't be like that.
Please, be happy.
Please tell me that you'll be happy.
If Sunbae's suffering,
I'll suffer too.
Why didn't I like a girl like you?
Eventually, this is it?
Gu Jun Pyo.
Don't be like this.
- This is...
- What is this?
This is something you don't know?
You fell into a trap again?
I wanted to believe you.
I didn't want to misunderstand you again.
I tried my hardest.
I'm sorry.
That…
I showed you my sincerity.
But, this is your answer?
It's not like that.
It's really over now.
Geum Jan Di.
Don't act like you know me anymore.
Jun Pyo!
Shut up!
If you say one more word,
I'll kill you.
What did he take?
What time?
Oh.
What?
I get it.
So what?
He really left?
Yes. He took the plane
off early in the morning.
Crazy fella.
What is the reason this time?
Geum Jan Di.
You really can't think of any reason?
I'm back.
Jan Di!
Jan Di, it's been hard on you right?
My daughter!
How is it that your first trip overseas
was to the South on a private jet?
What great fortune is this?
You've suffered, my daughter.
Looking at you with such accomplishment,
I can die without regrets.
Why should you die?
This is just the beginning.
When Jan Di becomes part of that family,
we should enjoy some of the riches,
then we can have no regrets.
I have a lot of regrets.
Dear.
Noona, I heard that the island
belongs to Jun Pyo's family.
Really?
That island is theirs?
How is it that the Shinhwa
Group owns so many things?
He's totally like a king.
King? Then, when our Jan Di marries him,
what would she be?
Queen, of course.
Oh, queen.
Please calm down, bubu-in.
I'm bubu-in?
Dad, Dad, then what am I?
Whenever I watch Sageuks, it's always the
Majesty's brother that causes trouble.
Geum Kang San! You watch out!
Heard me?
Such a thing would never happen.
Why?
That family and I...
No, I mean, Gu Jun Pyo and I will
not have any relationship in future.
Please wake up from your dreams!
This girl!
Why is she…
That…
It's pretty, right?
I bought this from the market.
It's supposed to be given to the person
you want to spend your life with.
Maybe it's like asking them not to run away.
Don't drink without me around.
If it's snowing, you should go indoors!
Are you a statue?
I thought you'd come!
This is the first time in my life
that I'm waiting for someone.
It's a heart!
Did you see?
My heart?
I'm sorry.
Sorry, Gu Jun Pyo.
Sorry.
Sit down.
Don't need to look like that.
You're in an emergency situation too.
But then again, you're
always in such a situation.
I'm sorry about what happened on the island.
What should you apologize?
If I didn't go and find you...
That's what I wanted to say.
The person who should apologize is me.
It was me who hurt Gu Jun Pyo.
Jun Pyo should be like that now right?
No.
His expression would be this black.
His face wouldn't be straight.
His hair would be so curly.
I'm sorry.
It's alright.
In the name of F4,
I have something to announce.
Yoon Ji Hoo is no longer part of F4 anymore.
What?
Jun Pyo.
And, in a week from now, Yoon Ji Hoo and
Geum Jan Di will be expelled from this school.
Expel?
That's right. Expel.
Don't you know what that means?
Quit school!
It doesn't make a difference for
a person like you to quit school.
But because of you,
Ji Hoo sunbae was kicked out of F4!
How are you going to
take responsibility for that?
Ever since your entered our school,
problems keep cropping up.
It's the first time that Ji Hoo and Jun Pyo
sunbae have seen such a poor person like you,
so they pity you.
It's because they're all too kind.
Take responsibility.
It's because of an ignorant girl
like you that our F4 is split up.
You need to take
responsibility for all of this!
I'll take the responsibility.
How should I take responsibility?
Sunbae.
Please wake up.
Aren't you people the
ones who need to wake up?
Ignorant girl?
Saying that make you seem ignorant!
Sunbae!
If you act like this,
we can't take your side.
Who asked you to?
You'll regret. Really.
Don't put on such
a despondent face so early.
This time we're both in an urgent situation.
I don't mind if I get expelled
or have to quit school.
But that can't happen for you.
Even if he's Gu Jun Pyo,
he can't do that right?
He can.
Jun Pyo has the Shinhwa Group backing him.
And did you forget who owns this school?
Don't put on such an expression.
I won't stand back and do nothing.
Do you have a plan?
I'll have to find one,
because now I have a reason not
to sit back and concede quietly.
That's right.
Kicking you out of F4 is not
something that can be tolerated.
You're really silly.
What?
I don't care about that.
That expression again.
I'm back.
Hurry come in.
What's all this about?
Where have you been?
Coming back at this time only.
We're shorthanded!
Hurry change your clothes
and come back down.
What's up all of a sudden?
As the saying goes,
good things begets more good things.
This is all thanks to
our daughter's good fortune.
Sending your uniform to our laundry
can let you meet a rich guy.
This news has spread to other people.
What?
Look at this.
Hankook Girls High, Han Gang Girls High,
Moon Hwa Girls High.
They even send from across the Han River.
Wow, we've hit the jackpot!
I've only heard of such things in the past.
This is the first time
I'm experiencing such a thing.
Noona, you're not dating Gu Jun Pyo.
But you're dating Yoon Ji Hoo,
another F4 member, right?
Where did you hear that from?
The Shinhwa uniform was the first to arrive.
It doesn't matter whether it is
Gu Jun Pyo or Yoon Ji Hoo.
I don't care.
Ever since you entered Shinhwa High School,
everyday has been like a dream for me.
Honey, this is not a dream that
I'd wake up from tomorrow right?
Wait a moment.
Sorry.
Didn't I say this before?
Everything would work out fine.
The Shinhwa Group is not the only chaebol.
The legend of laundry business!
We will become chaebols too!
Chaebol! Chaebol!
Speak.
No matter what you did before,
I could understand.
Honestly, there were times when
I couldn't stand Jun Pyo too.
I never expected to be saying
these things to you now.
This is not like you.
Why did you do it?
I just felt like it.
Jun Pyo liked Jan Di...
And I knew it.
Yoon Ji Hoo!
Even if you hooked up with my sister
and dumped her after three days,
I wouldn't be this mad.
You don't have a sister.
I'm not joking.
I can't tolerate you messing
with a friend's girl.
I feel sorry towards Jun Pyo.
- But...
- But what?
I can't let Geum Jan Di
be kicked out of school.
So, what do you intend to do?
I have to do something.
There's no turning back.
You're not going to have
anyone on your side this time.
Don't be disappointed.
I understand how you feel.
But Jun Pyo,
expelling them from school is too much.
Too much?
That should only be used when I kill them.
Ji Hoo is not in his right mind.
You know very well how much
Seo Hyun meant to him.
Given his character,
he even chased her to Paris.
Suddenly hearing that she's getting married
is enough to drive him crazy.
Exactly.
That guy doesn't even like
Geum Jan Di sincerely.
It's because of Seo Hyun
that he's using Geum Jan Di.
I can't forgive him for that.
You know?
Jun Pyo.
Don't side with that fella anymore.
If you say one more word, you're out too.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translator: pickles
Spot Translator: saturn
Timer: selvaspeedy
Editor/QC: yuns
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
Let Jan Di go.
What if I don't let her go?
I'll protect her.
I remember the friend whom I've
watched this movie with for 11 times.
I never thought this would happen.
Hey you stupid fools!
How can I go into the water?
It doesn't matter to you
whether he wins or loses.
But Jan Di...
...would probably be expelled.
What's wrong with those kids?
Shouldn't you be glad that
Jun Pyo has such friend by his side?
The heir to Shinhwa Group
doesn't need any friends.
It's not too late now.
I just need one word from you.
Just tell me that you like me.
I won't regret.
I definitely won't regret.
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get it for FREE @ d-addicts.com