Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
I came here only because
your house was the closest.
Because of the fight we had in Macau,
Yi Jung would have something to say.
And at Woo Bin's place, the women are too noisy.
What about me getting punched?
What are you gonna do about that?
Uh... fine.  Hit me!
If I take one, then we'll be even.
Hurry up and just punch me.
What's with the engagement?
Ah, who knows.
How could I possibly know everything
that the evil witch schemes up?
Engagement?  Whatever.
Where did she get a girl like that?
Did everybody... get home safely?
If you're curious about Jan Di,
she got home safely.
Who said I was curious?
But you!
It's your friend's birthday so
why don't you give him a present?
Quickly give it to me, the present.
What is it?
Gu Jun Pyo,
Happy birthday.
I'll pray that this birthday isn't lonely,
and is a day filled with happy things.
Geum Jan Di.
What I said to Jun Pyo in Macau...
I know...
You only said that because
you were mad at Gu Jun Pyo.
Hey you...
Hey you... hey, Beef Jerky!
It's you, isn't it? It's you, Macau's
Miss Beef Jerky?
Uh... hello.
What are you doing here?
What's this? I'm the one who saved
your life,
but you don't look happy to see me.
When I'm really happy to see you.
I am happy.
But... why did you come here?
I just came to find someone.
Gu Jun Pyo?
Oh? How did you know?
Do you know that rascal?
Oh, right. Your name is...
Jan Di. Geum Jan Di.
Ah, Geum Jan Di.
Do you remember my name?
Ha... Jae... Kyung.
Seeing that you're wearing a uniform,
you must still be in high school?
Junior? Senior?
Senior.
I'm also planning on attending
Shinhwa University.
Worked out well.
Do you want to become sisters?
Huh?
Oooh, so cute!
Ever since I first saw you,
I thought that you were cute as a mouse,
so I liked you, little sister Jan Di.
Little... sister Jan Di?
But where is that rascal hiding?
Oh!
Why is that woman here?
Oh, found him!
What?
What do you mean "what"?!
Your fiancée, of course!
Hey! Hey! Let go!
What?
You don't like my greeting?
Then should I bite your ear like
last time?
You're like a crazy monkey.
What are you doing?
You're not going to buzz off?
I'm only going to say this once,
so listen closely.
My name is Ha Jae Kyung.
From this day forward, I'm your fiancée.
You got it?
Also, it's over.
What's over?
From now on, I'm gonna tame you.
Bang!
Jun Pyo... starting today, he'll be
attending Shinhwa University with us.
Then you are ok with it?
About what?
That woman!
The woman called his fiancée
is clinging onto Gu Jun Pyo like that.
And you don't care?
What does that have to do with me?
And besides... that unni.
Unni?
She seems like a cool person.
No. She is a really cool person.
Who?
Who's a cool person?
How... how did you get here?
Hi!
I'm Ha Jae Kyung.
Are you Jan Di's friend?
I'm Jan Di's friend too!
Nice to meet you.
Eh?
So this is where you work?
Seems like fun!
I too wanted to do something like this.
Then please do it!
A gorgeous beauty like you
is welcome anytime!
For now, I'll borrow these friends
for today.
What?
Chen, don't think about following me
and take care of this place for me.
Jan Di. Ga Eul.
You're gonna leave me here and
go somewhere again, aren't you?
Don't worry about the
porridge shop and go ahead.
Pretty, no?
You know what? I really
wanted to do something like this.
Chat with my girls, say bad things
about our boyfriends.
And talk about dating and relationships.
Do you… not have any friends?
Oh, no. I don't have any friends.
Eat!
Ever since I was young,
India, Europe, Africa...
We went to so many places.
I didn't have any time to make friends.
Uh...
What type of girl does Jun Pyo like?
This is pretty.
Bags! There, there!
Let's go over there.
Pretty, huh?
Mmhmm.
That one is cute too.
Jan Di.
A feminine style?
If not, a boyish style?
Or would he like a cute style?
That guy...
From head to toe,
he's only concerned with his own
appearance.
He probably wouldn't remember
what style a girl dresses in.
I'm liking that rascal more and more.
I like a man who is abrupt and blunt.
Tell me more about him,
little sister Jan Di.
Haughty and self-centered, he'd be
disappointed
to take second place to anyone else's
arrogance and pompousness.
He acts like he knows everything,
but actually, he's really naive.
Also...
If he likes something,
then he'll ignore others' opinions,
and stubbornly go after it.
Like a bulldozer.
When he's angry, he's incredibly scary.
But when he's good to you,
he's affectionate.
Uh… anyway,
what I'm saying is.. he's an immature,
elementary school, overbearing big devil!
Just think of him like that.
Jan Di, you know Gu Jun Pyo well.
That's great!
Then I'll officially ask you.
Uh... what?
I really want to get along with
that rascal.
Jan Di, from today on,
be my dating coach.
As a favor. Hmm?
That girl's character has quite the
impact, don't you think?
No doubt about it.
Think that she's Geum Jan Di's strongest...
What's so amusing that you guys are
cracking up?
We're talking about your fiancée.
She's interesting.
Fiancée? Whose fiancée?
Why? I like her.
For a tycoon's daughter, she's not boring.
Isn't that a good thing?
But when you guys get so close?
Before, didn't she clearly say
something about biting your ear?
Jun Pyo...
Isn't that your weak point?
To be more accurate,
it would be his sensitive point.
Hey, you guys think that this is
entertaining?
Is it funny?
Supposed to be my friends... seriously!
Hey, move!
Really, what should we do?
No matter how you look at it,
Jun Pyo seems to be caught.
Even if you take away the fact
that it's an arranged engagement,
what if she has real feelings for him?
And don't forget, it's the JK Group.
If we don't think of something fast,
then it's only a matter of time before
Jun Pyo enters the wedding hall.
You guys can just get involved.
- What?
F4's Don Juan and Casanova.
Try putting some of your skills into
action.
Um... we can go by ourselves now.
Today was fun.
And also...
From now on, you two are Ha Jae Kyung's
"BF" (best friends), okay?
- What?
And also... this.
This is Jan Di's.
This is Ga Eul's.
What is this?
Bribes to thank you for being my friend.
Good night!
She...
Seems a little strange, that unni.
Yeah, a little.
Still, her character is hard to dislike.
Ahhh... it's cold.
You're back?
What's... wrong with everyone?
Did something happen?
Young Master Jun Pyo's engagement…
is it true?
How did you find out about that?
[Shinhwa Group Becomes In-Laws with
Global Investment Group JK]
It's true.
What do we about this?
During this time, we thought
no news was good news and waited.
What will happen to our Jan Di now?
What do you mean, what will happen?
What do he and I have to do with
each other?
What?
Are we in mourning?
What do you mean,
nothing to do with each other?
Until last year, the position of Shinhwa
Group's daughter-in-law belonged to you.
How can it have nothing to do with you?
Wait a minute. Now we're ruined.
Where exactly did this girl roll in...?
They say that the rock that rolls
displaces the rock in place...
Wait a minute. You have to find out
exactly what kind of girl she is,
First figure out her name.
Hello!
Hi!
There's all sorts of stuff in here.
This is really...
My name is Ha Jae Kyung.
Jan Di and I decided to be BF...
No... from now on we're sisters.
Please take care of me.
Ha Jae Kyung.
Oh my, even the name is quite pretty.
Your face is pretty too.
And now that you've become sisters
with our Jan Di,
That means you're part of our family too!
Isn't that right, honey?
From now on, just think of this as your
home too. Come visit often.
Thank you!
Then... can I sleep over tonight?
Eh?
It's strange. Don't you get a feeling
of déjà vu?
Yeah... Dad's been thinking about
that too.
Jan Di. Where's your room?
It's just like a pajama party!
I always wanted to have one.
This room is really cozy.
Really?
It's really miraculous.
What?
In Macau, when I ran into Gu Jun Pyo
and you,
I feel like it was destined.
So you've known Gu Jun Pyo since Macau?
I... probably fell for him when I first
saw him.
Engagement, they say!
Any other time, I would've hit the
road running.
But while looking at that guy's face,
my heart began to sting.
Jan Di, do you know that feeling?
No, wait. Do you like someone?
Like... a first love.
So you do!
What's he like?
Just... kind of a blank person.
A blank person?
When I looked at him, I would go blank.
He was that kind of person.
Ahh... I got it.
He's someone who makes people feel
comfortable and warm?
Gu Jun Pyo is just like wine.
Wine?
Red and aromatic.
Once you drink it, all your blood
just boils,
that kind of numb feeling.
Wait. That rascal doesn't like anyone,
does he?
Well, it doesn't matter.
From now on, I'll just make him fall
for me.
It's been a really long time,
s ince I've wanted to make
something mine, no matter what.
What?!
Do you have something to say?
Why aren't you swimming?
I gave it up.
Why would a swimmer give up swimming?
None of your business.
This is what you followed me to say?
I can't tolerate being unfairly wronged.
So I have to clear up what needs
to be cleared up.
What?
The engagement or whatever…
none of it has anything to do with me.
It has nothing to do with me either.
Gu Jun Pyo, you've become a lot friendlier.
Explaining something like that
to the stain that you want to erase.
Over there. Your fiancée's coming.
Why is that monkey here again?
Sunbae!
Can you give me a ride?
Seeing the two of you together, it was
almost like it was planned!
Jan Di and Jun Pyo, you two are
really close, huh?
Oh... this person...
This is Ji Hoo sunbae.
Why are you introducing my friend?
Hey, monkey. This is my friend
Yoon Ji Hoo.
You like him?
At least you can spot the good
looking ones.
I understand.
What?
It's this person, right?
Uh... what?
Jan Di, the person that you like!
Oh, Unni, it's not like that... we're...
That's wonderful. The four of us,
let's go hang out.
How about that? Good, right?
- No.
- No, it's fine!
But... why not?
I have to quickly go somewhere.
Unni, you two go have fun.
Sunbae, quickly, let's go.
Now what should we do?
Do what?
Let's go together!
Now, you work here too?
It's not work. It's volunteering.
I just... clean and run errands.
I feel comfortable here, and I can
concentrate more on my studies.
How mysterious.
What is?
How can you work so hard at everything
you do?
I'll go in now. Go safely.
Geum Jan Di.
I'm really good at cleaning too.
Oh, hello!
Hello!
- Why is the beauty coming now?
- I just got out of school!
- Hello!
- Hi!
Just a second, please.
Hello!
Ah, yes. On Sunday, come here to eat.
Understand?
Yes, be careful on the roads.
Ji Hoo! Ji Hoo!
What?! That scheming...
No… that Doctor Grandpa's grandson..
Is Ji Hoo sunbae?
But if...
Ji Hoo sunbae is President
Yoon Seok Young's grandson... then...
That grandpa is President Yoon Seok Young?!
That makes no sense!
Then how come the two of them
haven't been in touch?
It's not that they weren't in touch.
It's that they couldn't get in touch.
What do you mean by that?
And what's your relationship with
that grandpa?
Jan Di, those two. Please help them.
What?
Oh, welcome!
Hi!
Ga Eul. Get me some water.
Me too.
What's with everyone?
This is a piece that Queen Elizabeth liked.
Do you like it?
Whoa, are you giving this to me?
Men or dishes, both are waiting for
the woman who will properly appreciate them.
Thank you! If I use this as our Leon's
dish, he'll definitely be really happy!
Leon?
It's the name of my pet lion!
Lion?
Hey, lady.
You have killer style.
Why don't we go have some tea?
It's kind of cold.
Are you laughing?
It looks like this lady isn't afraid.
Guys.
Why don't you let go?
And who are you?
You shouldn't bother pretty young ladies.
Stop messing around and buzz off.
We saw her first.
Right now, it's time for the little kids
to go home.
Go on home.
You'll get hurt.
It might get kind of noisy. My apologies.
Ow, ow! What are you doing?
Miss, are you okay?
Thank you for helping me.
These idiots.
That's not even the worst of it.
Is there more?
Don't bring it up.
That woman... is definitely a monster.
I've known plenty of women.
But this is the first time I've met
someone like her.
So what do we do now?
That unni... we can't do anything
about her.
We have no other choice,
except for the last emergency method.
Emergency method?
Forget about Miss Monkey and get the
two idiots together.
The two idiots?
So...
Ga Eul.
You need to help us a little.
I'm the one who killed them.
The one who made that child an orphan…
It's all my fault.
Yes, hello?
What?! Yi Jung sunbae and you are
doing what?
Date.
No! No, you can't, Ga Eul.
Why? Yi Jung sunbae isn't a
bad person.
Uh, that is… he's not a bad person.
He's not a bad person, but...
that person is F4's best…
Best?
Anyway, Ga Eul.
Ga Eul, I think it would be a good idea
if you think this over.
I don't know. He said he was going to
pick me up early tomorrow morning.
That's why I'm going to sleep early.
Although, I doubt I'll be able to sleep.
Good night, Jan Di. Bye.
Uh… Ga Eul…
So Yi Jung?
So Yi Jung?!
Ji Hoo sunbae, pick up your phone.
Please!
The number you've dialled is unavailable.
Ga Eul
Hi.
No… No… Absolutely not!
Yo. Geum Jan Di, what's up?
Sunbae, Gu Jun Pyo. Where is Gu Jun Pyo?
Gu Jun Pyo!
Hey!
Oh, Sunbae!
You asked where he was. You didn't ask
what he was doing.
What the hell are you doing?
Gu Jun Pyo.
Help me.
There's big trouble!
Big trouble?
It's impossible on my own.
I don't have any money or a car.
And if something happens, you might have
to use your body.
Body? Use my body to do what?
What if they end up at a hotel?
What are we gonna do?
Hotel?
Geum Jan Di, I know you must be shocked
because of that monkey,
but why are you not acting like yourself?
It's because Yi Jung sunbae is going
on a date with Ga Eul.
Now that you mention it… Yi Jung did say
there was a girl he was stuck on.
I wonder how long Ga Eul will take…
Two days? No, he could probably
finish her off in a day.
One day?
Geum Jan Di, you didn't know that Yi Jung's
nickname is “5 seconds kill,” right?
“5 seconds kill”?
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Ga Eul…
NO…
NO!!!
Is Yi Jung on drugs?
To date Ga Eul…
What's that supposed to mean?
To be honest, Ga Eul is definitely not
Yi Jung's type.
Yi Jung won't date anyone,
unless she has a body like Lee Hyori
and a face like Lee Tae Hee.
But with Ga Eul?
Isolate them in a room for 3 nights
and 4 days,
and see if anything happens.
No, he actually said
that there's something really cute
about Ga Eul.
See! Now what do we do?
What are we going to do?
So what do you want me to do?
Come here.
Come closer.
I don't know.
Why not?
Oh. He's here. He's here.
Are you ready?
Yes.
You and I both made the wrong friends and
are paying for it.
Do you think we can pull this off without
getting caught?
Don't worry about that. Just follow
my lead.
We've already acted together before.
Hey! Sit.
Don't be nervous.
Hey, start the car. Hurry, hurry.
Start, start!
Ah, really.
Okay.
I'm going.
Grandfather probably still hates
me, right?
All of the people I like didn't
stay by my side.
I was going to start living my life
thinking I didn't need anyone,
but I keep getting greedy.
What should I do?
Are you okay?
It was tiring, right?
No, it was fun.
Oh, oh! Who wouldn't say he's a player.
Yi Jung sunbae...
is totally full of himself.
Then you'd rather he doesn't pay attention
to whether Ga Eul freezes to death or not?
No, that's not it.
Just look at how blue those lips are.
You'll freeze to death first trying to
save your friend.
Come here.
- Hey, Hey. What are you…
- Stay still.
I'm fine.
See, I told you it'd be effective.
Really.
Then, should we slowly head towards
the climax?
You're ready, right?
Why do you guys put on firework shows
like they are party poppers?
That kid. He's cool.
Was it so cool when I did it too?
Anyway...
What did Yi Jung sunbae say at the end?
What do you think he said?
In this situation, I don't need to hear
to know what he said.
What's that?
Should we go up?
Go up where?
No.
NO!
Although he's my friend, Yi Jung's really
the player of all players.
How can he come all the way to the hotel?
I was wondering why he would be skating.
Man, I didn't realize there was such
planning behind it.
Shut up!
Be quiet. I can't hear what they're
saying!
Do you know how many stars this hotel has…
Do you think you'll be able to hear them?
Then what?
Why don't you go outside and stand guard.
Oh, alright. Alright.
Hey.
Gu Jun Pyo! Gu Jun Pyo!
What's wrong?
Hey. Hurry, hurry, hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Why?
What do we do?
Looks like Yi Jung sunbae prepared that.
Do something!
What?
That's definitely an operational prop.
We can't let it go into the room.
Hey.
Let's bring that here.
What?
Hurry! Hurry!
Jeez.
Hey.
Go quickly.
Thank you.
Our plan was successful.
Do you think things will work out?
Who knows…
Since they're a pretty impossible couple.
We've done all we could, so we just have
to wait and see.
You worked hard all day, Ga Eul.
Yeah, Woo Bin.
Yeah, we're about to head out.
Alright.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
Though it's late, happy birthday.
Though it's late, thanks for the present.
You got the present?
Although it's the cheapest present
I've ever received,
I've accepted it because it's the
thought that counts.
Though it's late...
congratulations on your engagement too.
I said not to pay attention to that.
Unni is a good person too.
Unni?
She really...
really likes you.
I see you still can't mind your own
business.
Alright.
You wouldn't be Geum Jan Di if you
didn't piss me off.
So what?
Now that it happened, do you want me
to get married right away?
Would that make you feel better?
Ah, what is Cho Ga Eul doing?
I'm going to go out and see.
That useless girl.
Nothing's going on, right?
Yes. All the preparations are going well.
That's right. Master Jun Pyo is in one
of the rooms.
Jun Pyo is in the hotel right now?
Yes.
What is this?
Why can't I hear anything?
They couldn't possibly…
You there.
What are you doing here?
H... hello.
You're a girl I can't put up with,
even though I try.
Or…
are you showing your true colors now?
This is why I was so careful from
the start,
in not allowing him to mix with kids
from such ill-bred families!
Your words are too harsh.
We are not an ill-bred family.
If a young girl follows a boy so willingly
to a hotel is not ill-bred, then...
Hey, Geum Jan Di. You...
Why?
Did you become anxious because Jun Pyo
got engaged,
so you decided to just throw your body
at him?
You detestable and audacious little...
Stop it!
Please.
Just stop it.
Bring Jun Pyo and come out.
Young master.
Let's go, Young master.
[Send to Yoon Ji Hoo]
[Send]
[In the process of sending your message
to Yoon Ji Hoo]
Hello?
Where are you?
Uh, I'm at home.
Nothing's wrong, right?
There's nothing wrong.
Yes…
Yes...
Sunbae.
This place has become Geum Jan Di's home.
I couldn't sleep at all and...
I thought I could get some air and get
some studying done…
Yeah, mom.
What's wrong?
Mom!
Was there an accident?
Mom! Mom!
What is it now?
Honey.
Look at this.
If you have any eyes, look at this.
What are we going to do now?
We're already having a hard time paying
off our interest.
How could you consider paying off someone
else's debt?!
You see, this was before the situation
became so bad.
- That friend asked to borrow my name.
- Just your name?!
You just lent him your name, how could there
be repossession stickers everywhere?!
Honey.
Oh, my head.
My head.
Hello?
Oh yes, this is Geum Il Bong and
Na Gong Ju's house.
The art center?
Oh yes. I'm sorry, but my parents aren't
feeling well.
Could I do it on their behalf?
Well, it's troublesome for us if they
don't work for this long.
I'm sorry.
I'll do everything that's been piling up.
Could you be a little lenient until
they get better?
I'm going easy since you're such an
admirable young woman, alright?
Then, I'm leaving it to you.
Thank you!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
Main Translators: asiandreamer117, ahsieee
Spot Translators: Javafiend, meju, saturn
Timer: xCHELLy
Editor/QC: snoopyvkd
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get this for FREE @ d-addicts.com