Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
Episode 8
Where are you going this late at night?
I'm on my way to go to practice. Why?
Do you want to win that badly?
We don't have a choice.
We?
Why, does it have to be Ji Hoo of all people?
If it wasn't Ji Hoo...
Gu Jun Pyo.
It's not too late even now.
Just one word.
Just one word... saying that you like me.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Do you know what you're doing right now?
The almighty Gu Jun Pyo is hanging on to you.
I don't have a choice.
How could I have liked a girl like you?
You just threw away your last chance.
It's no use if you cry tomorrow,
because I'm not going to let you off easy anymore.
That's what I expected.
Of course.
That's more like Geum Jan Di.
Fine.
Let's see how far we can go.
I'm not going to regret it.
I won't ever regret it.
So, if he loses this time,
Yoon Ji Hoo is dismissed from F4...
And Geum Jan Di is expelled from school...
That's what you were about to say, right?
But what if he wins?
Try saying something that makes sense.
You didn't place your bet on the other outcome, did you?
No.
No one would bet on that outcome unless he was crazy.
But what if he wins in a 1 out of 10,000 chance?
That's headline news.
Hey, gambling is not a miracle.
Oppa!
We shall now start the last competition.
Athletes, please step forward.
Ready.
Hey, Geum Jan Di!
It's the end for you now!
Yi Jung sunbae, fighting!
Yi Jung is alive!
Jan Di, use your strength!
Just a little more!
Who is it?
Who on earth is it?
Did you see?
Who did it?
Through this, Jan Di's expulsion and Ji Hoo's
dismissal will be as if it never happened.
Nobody has any objections, correct?
You were cool.
Thank you.
I think I should be the one thanking you.
Excuse me?
Because I think my nasty little brother
is growing up decently thanks to someone.
I'll see you again.
It's a relief. Such a relief.
Right?
Geum Jan Di.
That was an awesome competition.
Me too.
We'll be off to Jun Pyo.
Thank you.
Thanks to you...
Geum Jan Di.
Do you want to go on a date with me?
Gu Jun Pyo...
you certainly are repaying a debt.
Why are you mumbling to yourself,
as if you're out of your mind?
The impact was pretty big though.
Do you remember when I broke
Ji Hoo's robot, in kindergarten?
Robot?
The one made out of wood?
Yeah.
Ji Hoo, gave this to me.
No.
Give this to me. I'll give you all my toys.
I can't give you that, Jun Pyo.
You're so cheap.
What can't be mine?
It's mine now.
They say Ji Hoo's deceased father
had made that robot himself for Ji Hoo.
After that, I've always thought
that I had a debt to him.
You're saying that you're going to repay it
with what happened this time?
Because,
I can't ruin Geum Jan Di,
so that nobody can have her.
Rascal.
Jun Pyo.
Do you want to go on a date with me?
Date?
Jan Di.
Hey!
I'm going out to get some fresh air and exercise.
Dressed like that?
Actually...
You're going out to go on a date
with Ji Hoo hyungnim, correct?
How'd you know?
Although giving Young Master
Jun Pyo a scar was bad of you,
love doesn't always go as planned, does it?
Of course, of course.
If you get blocked, then you can do a u-turn.
If you go far, you can go to Seoul.
What is that supposed to mean?
That is...
It means that you have to look good
in Young Master Ji Hoo's eyes.
Isn't that skirt a little too long?
Can't you dress a little sexier?
Jan Di, your lips are much too dry.
Lick your lips a little bit.
For a woman, her fragrance is important.
A fragrance of seduction that nobody can reject.
Seriously!!
I'll be off.
What did they say he has?
Su Am Culture Foundation.
Real Barcelona! Hana Dolphins!
And the past president's grandson's wife?
What time is that you're still like this?
Let's go out.
I don't want to.
Yo, do you want to go to a shooting range?
- I'll pass.
- A drive?
I'm too lazy.
Then... shopping?
I told you I'm not interested.
The weather is this nice, and
you're just going to sit in here?
That rascal Ji Hoo.
He must be feeling like going on a date.
But... if Ji Hoo and Geum Jan Di meet,
what do you think they'd do?
I really can't imagine it.
You're right.
Don't you think they'd go somewhere with a
lot of sunlight and take a nap together?
Resting their heads on each other’s arms, too?
Hey, let's go out.
Let's go!
The first Christmas present she gave me was this.
She gave you a horse as a present?
When I was small,
I had to beg my parents for four
days and three nights for a puppy.
What happened?
I just got beaten up.
How about a horse instead of a puppy?
Geum Jan Di.
Want to ride that?
Young Master, I brought the
coffee that you requested.
Here.
30,000 Won coffee.
How is it? I was right, wasn't I?
It's the same as drinking coffee in a hotel sky lounge.
Do you want to drink something?
No, I'm fine.
It's my first time riding this.
Have you ridden this before?
Gu Jun Pyo <3 Geum Jan Di
"First Night Together"
Are you not feeling well?
Huh?
No, I'm fine.
She's probably doing well, right?
Let's not bring that talk up.
I'm sorry.
If everything works out by saying sorry,
then why would there laws in the world
and why would there be police?
Where is this place?
My house.
Yoo Ji Hoo / Min Seo Hyun
I don't see anyone here.
It's uncomfortable with people around.
They all come and leave when I'm not around.
I see.
It's kind of strange.
I don't feel uncomfortable
when you're around though.
I'm comfortable without any reason,
and it's amusing in an odd way.
You're warm everywhere.
Me?
I think I know...
why Jun Pyo likes you.
Geum Jan Di.
Oh my! This is Seo Hyun unni.
Ji Hoo sunbae is in here as well.
It's that horse that I saw a while ago.
Maybe that's your Christmas present?
Hey!
What the guys say might be true.
If Seo Hyun's incident never happened,
I might not have turned out with you like this.
What about Seo Hyun unni...?
She said that she's not marrying that man.
Then...?
But that doesn't change anything.
How does it not?
I think,
it's time that I let her go.
Sunbae.
Anyways, thanks.
Thanks to you,
I think I'll be able to let her go.
My first love.
Sunbae.
They say that,
there are ties in this world,
where no matter how many times you break up,
you somehow meet again.
You'll be able to meet her again.
Because the both of you...
because...
Because...
thanks to Seo Hyun unni,
I think I'll be able to let him go.
My,
first love.
Goodbye, Ji Hoo sunbae.
I might regret it once again.
But I should send her away, right?
What's up with him, again?
It's probably because of Geum Jan Di.
Geum Jan Di is with Ji Hoo...
it looks like the record will be broken tonight.
[Let's meet at the ice hockey rink.
Anybody up for a game?]
Who is this rascal to tell who to come and go?
You should be dating.
What is this to be calling people out in the middle of the night?
You're right.
I was about to do that,
but it got a little boring.
So, I ran away.
What?
I don't like easy girls.
I thought she was a complete guy,
but she turned out to be like a woman.
Ji Hoo, what's up with you?
She followed me all the way home.
She just wouldn't leave.
Hey, stop.
I was a little shaky because of Seo Hyun,
but she couldn't be more than just child's play.
That bastard...
Hey, are you okay?
Let go!
Say that one more time.
What is what?!
She wasn't bad for just child's play.
You really want to die?
She doesn't have anything to do with you now anyway.
She does.
Even if she doesn't, she does, you son of a bitch!
Let go. Let go!
Let go!
If you hurt Geum Jan Di, I'll kill you
regardless that you're my friend. Got it?!
You should've said it from the start.
See?
You can't let go of Geum Jan Di, right?
See how good it would've been if you came out honestly?
I wouldn't need to do something like this.
You crazy son of a bitch.
You picked a pretty strong strategy.
Why didn't you tell us sooner?
He had a debt to repay.
He broke my robot, remember?
Cheap stuff suits you the best.
If you lose it because it was cheap, then you're dead.
Just one word.
Just one word... saying that you like me.
[Gu Jun Pyo]
I don't want my feelings to get hurt because of you.
I'm feeling really...
Yi Jung sunbae?
Huh?
What did you say?
Gu Jun Pyo
Get up.
Gu Jun Pyo, get up.
Geum Jan Di is here.
Get up, you rascal!
This doesn't make any sense.
You're lying, right?
Why would he suddenly...?
What happened?
He ran out saying that he was going
out to see you, and then...
Gu Jun Pyo, get up.
Why are you being like this?
I have a lot to tell you.
I have a lot of things to fight with you about,
and I have a lot of things to teach you too.
What are you?!
He was being depressed all day, and
he suddenly said that he needed to go apologize.
I should be the one to apologize.
Gu Jun Pyo, I'm sorry.
I lied to you.
When you asked me
to do say that word one time for you...
I regretted it after I sent you away.
Gu Jun Pyo.
Gu Jun Pyo, get up.
I think I can tell you the words that you wanted to hear now,
so how can you be lying here like this?
Get up.
Really?
Hey, Geum Jan Di must've been really surprised.
Look at her shoes.
Jun Pyo, you must be feeling happy.
They say it's -10 degrees Celsius. Aren't you cold?
Geum Jan Di, I'm so moved.
If I was Jun Pyo, I wouldn't have any
complaints even if I died right now.
Sunbae...
Sorry. You two are beyond stubborn.
Tell me quickly what you were
about to say a little while ago.
What?
The words that I wanted to hear.
"I think I can tell you the words
that you wanted to hear now..."
You want to die?
You're hitting a patient?
You're a patient?
What is this?
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four.
Two, two, three, four!
What are you doing in someone
else's neighborhood this early?
The roads are slippery, so you should
be at home. Why are you running  around?
I'm exercising right now.
You exercise, that shows you're poor too.
Get in.
Why?
You said that you were exercising.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Get in.
Nice shot.
You try it too.
Bend your knees.
A little more, a little more.
Straighten your back.
Good shot.
Nice shot!
Hey, Gu Jun Pyo!
Hey!
I'm full.
If you're done eating, let's go.
You go ahead.
I'll be right back.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Thank you. I'll come again next time!
Oh my, who is this?
Isn't it Geum Jan DI?
What are you doing here?
- Do you know her?
- No.
What is that?
Oh god, the smell!
Are you taking care of the restaurant's trash?
Oh no, what to do. I think she's taking some other person's food home.
So trashy.
Would you wait a moment?
You can take home our leftovers.
What are you guys?
Why are you sitting here like this?
Jun Pyo, long time no see.
Your tastes have changed since the last time I've seen you.
Who is she?
Your housemaid?
Do you want to shut your mouth quietly?
Or should I make it so that
an article comes out tomorrow morning
saying that your company closed doors?
Sorry.
Not to me.
I apologize. Please forgive me.
What should I do?
I can't swallow my saliva naturally.
How should I start so it seems natural?
Why is it so hot?
If I take my jacket off saying that it's hot,
she'll probably go berserks, right?
Gosh really...
Why is that kind of scene coming out all of a sudden?
Gu Jun Pyo, now is the time.
Turn your head!
No!
Please don't look at me now!
Gu Jun Pyo, if you turn your head, you're so dead!
I really can't do it.
Gosh really, let's just eat some popcorn.
Pick up the phone, please~
Hello?
Jan Di!
I'm home.
Honey, that's eel.
Eel.
The eel that gives you a lot of energy?
Where did all this come from?
It's so obvious. Why do you ask
every single time you see it?
They say Jun Pyo hyungnim ordered it for us.
The hotel chef himself brought it.
He brought a tune this big and sliced it here himself.
I knew it was a tuna because he told me.
I originally thought it was a whale!
Eat up, honey. Eat a lot.
Honey, let's die tonight after we eat!
Let's eat and die!
Give it to your father.
I'm telling you this because you might get mad again,
But... it's not for you.
Don't even eat a single piece!
So I was walking,
and then someone from behind tapped my shoulder.
Oh my, oh my.  And then, and then?
Do you want to go see a movie with me?
That's so cheesy!
Jan Di, is there something wrong?
[Gu Jun Pyo]
Hello?
Oh, Gu Jun Pyo?
I can't really hear you well.
I'm at the porridge shop, and I'm super busy.
There are so many customers.
Excuse me, could you give us one abalone porridge?
Yes, customer.
You heard that?
I'm so busy that I think I'll have to work all night,
so I don't think I'll be able to see you for a while.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Jan Di, which porridge shop are you talking about?
Excuse me, could you give us some more kimchi?
Yes, in a moment please.
Ji Hoo sunbae.
Thank you.
It's warm.
You're practicing even during break?
Just because.
It didn't seem like just because.
I thought you were at Taereung
National Training Village.
I feel refreshed after I exercise.
Are you feeling uncomfortable somehow?
What about you, Sunbae?
Why did you come out to school?
I left some sheet music here.
Yeah, Jun Pyo.
Me? I'm at school.
I'm with Geum...
Okay, then. I'll wait.
Alright.
Jun Pyo says he's on his way.
If you wait, you'll be able to see him.
I see.
But why...?
I'm really busy today,
so I need to go home quickly.
I completely forgot.
Sunbae, I'll see you later.
Thank you for the drink.
What? You were with someone?
Huh? No.
It's all cooled.
From plentiful steamed Galbi, all land, sea and sky are coming out.
(Yuk Hae Gong: land, sea, sky which means meat, fish and birds... all kinds of food)
Looks good.
It really is a catastrophe... We've ruined our
taste buds by eating only delicacies.
Is Noona going on a date anytime soon?
You're right.
I hope she goes to a Chinese restaurant
this time. Don't you?
We have to get Italian.
A luxurious European full course meal.
You're right.
Those snails.
Escarrrrrgot.
That's French.
Who is it?
If they came to collect a bill,
tell them your parents aren't home.
The...
They came for the dishes?
Did you guys order something while I wasn't here?
Ju...
If they're from the landowner,
tell them that your parents passed away.
Jun Pyo!
Jun Pyo hyungnim!
What?
S-s-shinhwa...?
Young Master.
Can I go in?
What are you doing here this late at night?
What do you mean late?
It's only 10 o'clock.
It's the early evening.
Father.
Father. Did you hear?
He called me father.
And Mother.
Honey.
Please let me sleep here for one night.
What?
Are you crazy?
Why are you sleeping here when you have your nice house?
And by who's permission?
Father's permission.
Mother's permission.
Mom!
Of course you must sleep here.
It's so late.
It's already past 10.
Where are you planning to go this late?
Hyungnim, sleep with me.
No!
They're like shorts on you.
They're perfect!
My word... whatever you wear, it's so cool.
You're a complete model.
Don't you think that this style will become a trend?
Everything is ready.
Ready? Ready for what?
Tada~
Honey! Those blankets!
Our first night together during our honeymoon.
We slept together in those blankets.
Mom!
Gu Jun Pyo.
Are you really going to come out like this?
I came here without thinking,
but it turns out to be really fun.
What?
How can the masters bedroom
be smaller than our restroom?
Your restroom is the one that's abnormal.
What's even more amusing is that
five people sleep together like this.
Is it amusing to you?
Then, is it not?
Then, keep being amused.
Don't regret it.
What, regret?
It's like a refugee camp experience,
so I'm feeling thrill 10,000 points.
I'm going to sleep.
If you talk to me, you're dead.
Doesn't it seem like some kind of family,
since we're sleeping under the same blanket?
Hey, Cleaner. Are you sleeping?
Are you really going to sleep first?
Hey, Cleaner!
Cleaner! Jan Di Cleaners is here!
Snails, bird's nest...
Sweet and sour pork is good too.
Mom.
Honey.
Sweet and sour pork...
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translator: Beeni
Spot Translator: saturn
Timer: melliemelll
Editor/QC: sayroo
Final QC: jtranla
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get it for FREE @ d-addicts.com