Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
Episode 11
Hello.
He..hello.
Is anybody here?
What are all these?
They smell great right?
It’s very good for the skin.
Because of Geum Jan Di,
even the pool gets a special treatment.
But how long will it take to finish all these?
Wouldn’t it be faster just to fill it with hot spring water?
Why didn’t I think of it?
But for a guy preparing to surprise his girlfriend,
Why do you look so somber?
It's only these...
It's all I can do for her.
It's frustrating.
Very good.
By the way, is it alright to take pictures like this?
It’s okay.
Very good. Very good.
Looking sexy is the current trend.
As innocent as a high school student,
and this cute image really suits you!
It’s really good.
I am a high school student.
Ah. Yes, a high school student.
You said that you go to Shinhwa High right?
But isn’t that a school for rich kids?
Isn’t the economy in a recession now?
It’s hard isn't it?
But don’t worry.
This industry does not get affected by it.
No.
It actually does better in a recession.
That’s right, Representative. That’s right.
Really.
Let’s shoot the next series.
Next series. Okay.
Next series?
Yes.
Hey, I’m sorry.
But I can’t wear this.
Don’t be shy. Come out.
We said it’s alright already.
You people, really...
Are you really shooting for a Hagwon Academy brochure?
Who would wear this kind of clothing?
Don't be like that.
What's going on?
If you started something, then you have to finish it.
What's going on here?!
You crazy freaks!
Don’t come near me!
This girl is feisty.
Get away from me.
I’m dangerous you understand?!
I'll kill you!
Let's go, quickly!
Uh, your name is?
Forget about it today.
Huh?
We will meet soon again.
What?
When we meet again, I will tell you.
Good night, Miss Geum Jan Di.
Goodbye.
Miss Geum Jan Di?
How...
Really?
That means he knew you.
That’s right.
Either way, that's pretty cool.
What?
He is like the genuine Black Knight.
My Ha Je is out!
Doesn't he look awesome?
It was only the other day,
you're saying the Prince of Andromeda was the best.
You've got no loyalty.
Ha Je?
Jan Di, don't you know?
He is the most sought after model today.
His birth is a secret, surname unknown,
and a hidden private life.
He's a mysterious hot model.
Every magazine, with him on the cover,
would sell out within the day.
I went through a lot to get this limited edition bottle.
Great, isn't it?
So moist.
Ah, I'm so hungry!
I get hungrier doing nothing.
I should go nap at the swimming complex.
The noodles are done.
How can you just leave it like this!
The noodles will get soggy.
You... You...
Let me introduce myself,
Geum Jan Di sunbae-nim.
Sunbae?
My name is Lee Je Ha, Shinhwa High 1st year.
Oh.
Actually, I have always been a fan of yours.
Fan?
The Joan d'Arc of Shinhwa High.
You are the commoner’s hero who stood up to F4.
I am not considered a commoner’s hero.
But dressed like this, I can’t recognize you.
It’s a concept.
Concept?
Non-star concept.
Star?
Honestly, I hate all the students here.
And I don't want any of them as a friend either.
My goal is not to attract attention.
And to last till I graduate.
You can say it’s a concept to isolate myself.
- Why are you laughing?
- Because you are like me.
You think!?
I thought so too.
I always believe,
you and I are from the same world.
The same world?
I ate your ramen.
Hello Sunbae.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Get lost.
Thank you. Thank you.
I'll help you get a part-time job.
It's an assistant position at a photo studio.
The pay is pretty good.
It’s hard trying to get to see you.
Gu Jun Pyo.
Get in.
To eat crab in Hokkaido?
Why must we go to Japan to eat crabs?
Isn’t it the weekend?
We can enjoy the winter scenery.
If you don't want crab,
we can go to Sapporo for udon or ramen.
Go to Sapporo, just to eat ramen?
Let’s go.
- I'll call your parents on the way.
- Hey! No!
Why do you always say no?
Yes! Just say yes!
Why can't you ever just follow obediently for once?
I...already have plan.
What plan?
Today is Ga Eul’s birthday!
What?
So I'm spending the night at Ga Eul’s place.
This is an important event,
and it is our long standing tradition for many years.
You give in okay.
Am I more important or Ga Eul is?
Ga Eul.
I'll call you.
Hey!
Not even glancing back.
Yi Jung?
Got it.
Happy Birthday.
I heard it's your birthday today.
Huh?
You're here?
Oh, you're here. Hello.
Oh, you're here?
- Oh, Je Ha is here.
- Hello.
- You're here already?
Everyone seems to know you.
I've been working here for a long time.
You're next. Get prepared.
Okay.
Oh, Noona!
She is the one I mentioned to you on the phone...
Ah, your Sunbae?
Hello.
Please follow me.
- Then I’ll see you later.
- Don't worry, just go.
It’s a mess isn't it?
Please clean up and put everything back in order.
Yes.
Please work hard!
Wow. It’s Ha Je.
You look great!
Ha Je oppa always look amazing!
Looking fabulous in any style!
- Wow, so handsome!
- Check out Ha Je!
You're so good looking!
How do I look?
What's going on?
Were you surprise?
Yes.
Unbelievable.
Ha Je, shooting has started. So hurry.
I'll see you later.
Hyung, take a picture of us.
Wow, that's not bad.
Who's this young lady?
My girlfriend.
Hey!
No.
Miss, would you be interested doing some modeling?
What?
Me?
Why not? We're shooting that concept
layout for the magazine next month.
Resembling a movie or drama.
We still haven't found your female partner yet.
Hey, the feel is just right.
Let's go for it, Sunbae.
How can I?
Really that much?
A person like me will look okay?
Of course. No problem!
Can you understand her?
Did she have an ancestor who died during dating?
She runs off whenever the subject of dating comes up.
Weekdays, she needs to work, and
weekends, celebrating her friend's birthday.
She sure comes up with a lot of excuses.
Do you know how many jobs she has?
Delivering milk, delivering papers...
It's not like she's in a delivery contest or something.
I just wanted her to rest for a while.
She even said her friend is more important than her boyfriend.
Yummy!
It's my treat, so do eat a lot.
What?
I was thinking, my hyung would like this.
Je Ha you have a hyung?
Yes.
Speaking of which,
you're the type of girl my hyung would like.
So that’s why I like to get to know you better.
Is your hyung an undergraduate?
No.
He is in ill health, so he is convalescing now.
Looks like you're really close to your hyung.
He is the only family I have left.
Oh, no!
What's wrong?
I'm late!
Deliveries!
Quickly, quickly!
Let’s go.
A poor lady became the mistress of a wealthy lawyer,
And gave birth to his sons.
A plot ending that everyone can guess.
No need to look at me with pity.
Thanks to that, I didn’t grow up to be
a materialistic snob from high society.
I'm very thankful.
Wow, you're really touched!
Women always fall for this story.
Hey!
You!
This dude is really...
Hey!
Not that side, it's this side.
That side? Ah, this side.
That side, that side. The house on that side.
That side.
This side, that side.
Sunbae!
You're Yoon Ji Hoo sunbae right? I am...
Are you okay?
Yes.
Jun Pyo came over last night.
He was sad for being pass over for Ga Eul.
Ah, that is...
Today,
I'll pretend that I didn't see you both.
Jun Pyo is quieter these days.
What?
Geum Jan Di.
About not seeing her, can't get a date.
You were complaining a lot.
I'm changing my strategy.
How so?
I will play hard to get, and make her feel anxious.
Who believes this is will work?
Who doesn't?
You guys!
What is this? This is not your style.
This?
There's a little tacky.
But it is really warm.
Jun Pyo, thanks to you,
I was so embarrassed with Ga Eul.
What did I do?
Tall. Hot bod. Handsome.
What an eye candy!
Is she crazy?
That bitch!
With our beloved Ha Je...
Unbelievable!
Bitch! She'd better watch out!
Low life!
How could a girl like that be a model!
- What a pisser!
- I won’t let her get away with it.
Wait till Geum Jan Di is here, I’ll show her.
- Ah! I'm so pissed!
- Our Ha Je...
Geum Jan Di, you’re so dead!
Geum Jan Di!
I am so sick of you already!
Jun Pyo and Ji Hoo sunbae, and now Ha Je!
How in the hell did you get to know Ha Je?
After you stole F4 away from us,
Ha Je was our only hope during our suffering.
- Why does it have to be Ha Je?
- With a low life like you!
I really don't care about giving you gals hope.
Ha Je!
Sunbae, let’s go.
NO WAY!
Gu Jun Pyo sunbae.
What's with all the commotion?
Sunbae, have you seen this?
What's that?
Is this really Geum Jan Di?
Yes.
Get out of my way!
Get away from that hand.
Gu Jun Pyo.
Do it NOW!
Not only were you taking those worthless pictures,
but you've been avoiding me to be with trash like him?
Gu Jun Pyo, it's not like that.
Geum Jan Di, you've grown a lot.
What?
Now that you're on a magazine cover,
you think your some kind of hot model?
Tell me.
The reason you couldn't go with me to Hokkaido,
was it because you're doing this with him?
What?
Why don’t you insist that he’s Ga Eul?
Or was it his birthday that day?
I’m sorry for lying.
I was wrong.
I can explain everything.
It’s...
Did you just laugh?
It's kind of funny.
Do you have so little confidence in the girl you like?
And before getting jealous,
shouldn’t you first try to
understand your girlfriend’s situation?
Get up.
Say it again!
What did you say?
What do you know to talk like that?!
It's a shame.
What?
I'm saying Jan Di sunbae is wasted
on the likes of you.
This punk must be crazy!
Stop!
Stop it.
Please.
He helped me outside of school.
And at school, he's the only friend
I feel connected with.
The only one?
Say that again.
What does that jerk mean to you?
I can't breathe.
Say it.
It's hard for me.
I want...
I want to stop it now.
Hey Geum Jan Di!
F4 and Gu Jun Pyo,
I want to go back to before I knew about you.
It’s up! It’s up!
Geum Jan Di, the red card!
This is the first time anyone’s getting it twice.
Don’t worry about it.
From now on, I’ll protect you.
It’s Geum Jan Di.
There's no desk.
Your desk must have disappeared.
Your chair is gone too.
Goodbye, Geum Jan Di
Watch out, Sunbae!
It’s Jun Pyo sunbae.
It can't be.
Look up there!
That’s outside the F4 private classroom!
Gu Jun Pyo wouldn’t do that.
He’s the one putting up the second red card.
Gu Jun Pyo is the type that
would do this without a qualm.
No.
It's not true.
He wouldn't. No way.
Sunbae!
Thanks.
It’s been 15 years.
Huh?
Since I’ve known Jun Pyo.
Really.
I don’t think anyone can
know someone completely.
But I believe that I know
what kind of person he is.
Do you think Jun Pyo is behind it all?
I want to believe in him too.
It’s up to you to decide
if you believe in him or not.
But.
I let you go because it was him.
I didn’t pursue you because it was Jun Pyo.
Don’t make me regret it.
[Classroom changed to the science lab]
What’s this?
Help!
Somebody help me!
Help me!
Sunbae! Are you okay?
Move away!
Sunbae!
Are you okay? Sunbae!
I told you I’d protect you.
I’ll always protect you.
The person you're calling is not...
[Gu Jun Pyo]
[Yoon Ji Hoo]
Yes, it’s me.
Of course.
Do you know where Geum Jan Di is right now?
Would you believe me if I told you
she was sleeping in my bed?
Just prepare to transfer the money.
Ah...
The high and mighty president wouldn't
do the dirty work herself.
This kid is pretty impressive.
President, shall I pour you some champagne?
That sounds great.
Jun Pyo. Anyone able to get hold of him?
I called every place that I could think of, but no luck.
What’s Geum Jan Di's relationship with that guy?
Are they really breaking up this time?
Oh my. Who are you to look for F4?
I said, I've business with them!
Ga Eul.
What are you doing here?
Please help me.
She didn't show up at work.
And didn't pick up her phone since morning,
so I called her house.
So you're saying, your boss called
and told them she was out with F4.
Master never made that call!
I know that.
What are we going to do?
What’s happening to our Jan Di?
What if someone kidnapped her or something?
It'll be a relief if that someone was Jun Pyo.
Hey, Chief Lee. It's me.
I need you to find someone urgently.
Two people.
Yes.
Get everyone out searching for them.
Call Jun Pyo.
Jan Di is in danger.
Before getting jealous, shouldn't you first try
to understand your girlfriend's situation?
Chief Jung.
Prepare the helicopter.
Do you feel better now?
Where am I?
My house.
Your house?
You went into shock after inhaling all that gas.
You didn't wake up once since yesterday.
Yesterday?
Then, I didn't go home
but stayed here for the last 2 days?
I called your house just in case they're worried.
I told them you went on a trip with friends.
Friends?
I mentioned F4, and they didn’t seem to worry.
I'll be leaving now.
Thanks.
Do you still believe in him?
Even after all that you've gone through,
Gu Jun Pyo...
Does your heart still ache
when you think about him?
He tried to kill you, twice!
He's a bastard who would destroy you,
if he can't have you.
Watch your words.
There are things about Gu Jun Pyo
that you don't know, that I know.
No.
There are things I know that you don't.
Why are you like this?
Way before you even knew him,
I know what kind of person he was.
He doesn’t see anyone outside of F4 as people.
He's someone who doesn't consider
other people's happiness or lives.
No.
He was like that before, but not now.
That's not all that he is.
If you get to know him...
Stop it.
You weren't right for each other from the start.
Just come to me.
We understand each other.
You and I...
We’re from the same world.
You saved my life, and a friend I could lean on.
But...
No.
You can't still believe in him, can you?
Even after everything you've gone through?
I do.
I believe in him.
Because...
Gu Jun Pyo did too.
He would have.
You’re going to regret this.
Please come to your senses!
My mind has never been more clearer.
Thanks to you,
I now realize what I've done wrong.
And what Gu Jun Pyo means to me.
I’m leaving.
Je Ha’s world.
Jun Pyo’s world.
There's no such thing.
Being able to look at the same thing
from the same place...
That should be enough.
I warned you that you'd regret it.
Young Master, why didn't you contact us?
Your F4 friends have been worried.
Why would they worry about me?
It’s not that, but about Miss Geum Jan Di.
Jan Di? What about her?
I don't know the details.
I've been instructed to give this to you right away.
[If you want to save Geum Jan Di, come alone.]
What’s the matter?
N..Nothing.
Butler Lee, I’m tired so I’m going to bed.
At this hour?
Tell everyone not to disturb me.
Why am I so sleepy?
- Jun Pyo is here right?
- Is he in his room?
The Young Master asked not...
Young Masters!
Don’t worry. If he gets mad,
we will deal with it.
Jun Pyo?
Gu Jun Pyo!
Jun Pyo!
Jun Pyo! Wake up!
Are you really going to be like this?
Something’s weird.
- Jun Pyo!
Jun Pyo!
Hey, look.
Over there.
As soon as he got home, a strange letter...
A letter?
You guys go see if he's here.
You look like you have a lot to say, Jan Di sunbae.
Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
I had a reason.
Actually two.
Two reasons?
The job offer,
the red card,
the science lab...
They were all my doings.
It was perfect, wasn't it?
Jan Di sunbae.
Take a good look at me.
Don’t I remind you of someone?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
Main Translators: veggieleaf, lilshinhwafreak
Spot Translator: javabeans
Timer: blog234
Editor/QC: jtranla
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
I told you I am not going!
Then do you really mean to date my Jun-pyo?!
I think that's between the two of us,
Jun Pyo and I.
This is me and inside, this is you.
Because Jun Pyo the Star
won’t ever leave Jan Di the Moon.
Let’s go.
- Where?
- What do you mean where?
Skiing of course!
Ga Eul! Watch out!
Ga Eul! Are you okay?
Wake up!
I’m really sorry.
I was definitely wearing it around my neck.
You do this every time.
Whenever I try to get closer,
you trample on my heart like it’s nothing.
We've a problem! Jan Di is out on the slope...
Where’s Jun Pyo?
Young Master, we're ready to leave.
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get this for FREE @ d-addicts.com