Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Gu Jun Pyo!
Hey!
Stop!
You!
How did you!
Let's talk Gu Jun Pyo.
I have nothing to say.
And I told you to never talk to me again.
I have something to say.
I don't.
I do!
Hey!
Stop! Go away!
I said I have nothing to talk about.
I said I do!
Hey!
- Gu Jun Pyo!
- Move! Move!
Gu Jun Pyo.
Gu Jun Pyo!
Get away from me you Sticky Girl!
I said I have something to say!
Gu Jun Pyo!
Hey!
Hey, Gu Jun Pyo!
Gu Jun Pyo, where are you going!?
Gu Jun Pyo!
Get in.
What?
Hurry and get in.
You have to catch him right?
Yes.
Do you have a death wish?
Stop it! Stop!
You still haven't had enough?
Who taught you treat girls in that way?
Noona, you don't even know anything!
Noona?
Sorry. I'll apologize for
my immature brother.
Lets go home first and
you can tell me all about it.
I...
She's banned from my house!
Do you want to get banned?
Let's go.
I said she's not allowed in the house!
Careful on your drive back.
Eat a lot you guys.
It's been so long, hasn't it?
He refuses to come down.
He won't die from skipping a meal.
So?
The thoughtless child that has decided
on fasting has started a juvenile war?
And you guys all consented?
I'm against it.
I can't standby and watch
F4 split up like this.
I'm not exactly for it either, but...
Okay, that's enough.
Butler Lee.
Yes Miss?
Beijing Duck, Shanghai crab and
Beluga caviar that my honey sent
bring them out all.
Oh...
Don't forget a bottle of Cristal.
Yes, I understand.
I'll bring that out right away.
Jan Di, eat a lot okay?
If you're going to go against that idiot,
you're going to need your strength.
For the idiot bachelor upstairs, cheers!
I am really thankful for today.
I'll accept that thanks later.
But...
Why are you being...
So nice to you?
You've met my mother right?
Yes.
It's probably just as hard
to get into heaven as
it is for a rich person
to have true friends.
But, my mother even believes
that you don't need a friend.
Why?
No one would be ever good
enough to be a friend to the
heir of the Shinhwa group.
Nor could there be a friend.
But Gu Jun Pyo has F4.
That's right.
For someone with such a high status
and is lacking in nothing.
It's more like a miracle to
have something like F4.
I'm sorry.
It's because of me that he's losing F4.
He would leave his friends like this.
Plus, I'm actually thankful to you.
Excuse me?
You opened up a road for
him to be more human.
If friendship is a sufficient condition,
love is a necessary condition.
Get yourself ready.
Starting tomorrow,
it'll become really hectic.
Goodbye.
Bye!
Let's go.
How can they not say one word about eating?
Butler Lee, this old man
doesn't even bring me a snack
I'm so hungry.
Young Master.
Are you really going to be like this?
I'm sorry.
Take it back.
Ah! I'm so hungry!
Let's talk.
Do you remember how many times
we've seen this movie together?
It's been at least ten times.
I'm sorry.
I know an apology isn't enough.
But...
But?
Leave Jan Di alone.
What are you going to do if I don't?
I'm going to protect her.
I have to protect her.
It's been eleven times.
If you remembered that we're
friends that have seem that movie
eleven times together...
then something like this
should've never happened.
You better be prepared.
It's Gu Jun Hee!
Are you going to expel them or...
Or?
Should I fire you first?
Won't you stop!
How dare you! You're insane!
Why are you bothering me even at school?
How dare you try to fire the principal?
Sure, go ahead.
Then should I be the next principal?
How would you like to graduate under me?
Don't even make such a dumb joke.
My little brother.
We may have bad tempers.
But we're really not the type to make
such useless jokes, now are we?
Shut up and follow me.
Noona! Noona!
You guys follow me too.
Noona! It seriously hurts!
Who is that?
Isn't that Gu Jun Hee sunbae of Shinhwa?
Yeah!
The legendary "Charisma Queen", Gu Jun Hee!
Her pose is even different from ours!
She's wife to the man that owns
the greatest hotel in the world!
She's so praise worthy.
The type of guy I hate the most?
A disgraceful guy.
A stingy guy.
A guy that can't let go of the past.
A guy that brags about himself?
A disgraceful guy.
A guy that never forgives his friends?
A stingy guy.
A guy that can't accept his defeat?
A guy that can't let go of the past.
Okay, then.
You two will have a competition.
Gu Jun Pyo, Yoon Ji Hoo.
You guys can compete with
sports and the loser will have
to consent to the winner.
What competition?
Who said I would do it?
I'm against it.
I agree.
No matter what I agree...
I agree too.
Thanks Noona.
Who said you guys have the right to vote?
It's a void.
It makes no sense. No!
Five to one.
Bang Bang Bang.
Pass.
How can you do that!
Then, I get to decide what we compete in.
But that wouldn't be fair.
Don't worry.
I already have everything ready.
You can bring it in now.
The ten balls in here all have a paper
with a different sport written on it.
Some of them you have attempted,
and some you have not.
What's that!
Do things we've already done before!
No matter what category, one would
have an advantage over the other.
So technically, the competition starts
from the decision of each category.
You've heard that luck is skill too, right?
Is the competition only once?
Wouldn't that be a bit disappointing?
Two out of three, how does that sound?
I'll accept.
I'll do it! Okay?!
I'll announce the category two days
in advance of each competition day
in front of all of you.
No matter how disadvantageous you
may be because of a category,
you must consent.
Okay?
The three in the triangle, come up.
Come up!
Three triangle?
Me?
Me!?
Then we'll start.
Jan Di, you can press the button.
Ji Hoo.
Jun Pyo.
Horseback riding?
That's what it is.
Who's better at that?
Ji Hoo.
That's great!
That means you two have a
better chance at surviving!
Ga Eul.
I've told you once and I'll tell you again.
Fates aren't that easy to predict!
Then, did you get a sign from them?
What did they say?
The possibility...
Possibility?
It's 50/50.
Ugh!
Just don't say anything if
you're going to be like that!!
You never help, never.
What is this?
Young Master!
Are you alright?
In Jupiter's condition, it's pushing it!
Why don't you use a different horse.
No.
I can't do it if it's not him.
Coach Park.
Yes, Young Master.
Tell me the truth.
Do you think I'll be able to win?
Nevermind, I'll make my own destiny.
Are you sure it'll be okay if
you don't try him out first?
I've been asking him to do well for
me tomorrow since it's really
an important race for me.
Take care of him for me.
Young Master.
Must... you do this?
If I could avoid it, I would.
I didn't train you guys to see you fight.
Sorry.
Horse!
Horse? Horse!
Ready!
Go!
The mountain trails would be too
much for him in his condition.
If he were to go that way,
it may be fatal to him.
Let's go!
Go!
What's their record?
About 49 wins to 1 loss?
In favor of who?
No one out of us can beat Ji Hoo.
What a relief.
That's...
It's Gu Jun Pyo!
That's a surprise.
I wonder how he won!
What are we going to do!
Want to pet him?
Can I?
His name's Rui.
Hi Rui.
My name is Geum Jan Di.
Rui.
It was hard wasn't it?
You did a good job today.
Thank you!
What?
Really?
He said he wants to give you a ride.
Are you sure?
I'm pretty heavy!
He won't be able to run anymore.
No!
Do something.
Do something Coach!
I'm sorry, Young Master.
You may have won the game,
but you lost the battle little brother.
I hope you learned something from this.
Or else Jupiter's efforts would
have been for nothing.
Next, it's time to open up Ji Hoo's, right?
Mother!
Car... car...
No!
Mother!
Good morning!
Why are you guys here
so early in the morning?
Butler Lee.
This soup tastes great!
Jun Pyo, are you really going to do it?
That lot wasn't drawn by me, you know.
He drew that lot himself, what can I do?
This is all his luck, you know.
What do they call it?
Luck is a strength.
Yes, that's it.
Ji Ho...
That guy will not be able to do it.
There's no need for him to
insist on doing it, you know.
After all, he can just forfeit then...
How do they say it?
Win without fighting.
That's right, win without fighting.
If that happens, I win two times in a row.
Then, there's no need to
continue the challenge.
I just knew this was how it'd turn out.
"In Gan Ung Bo Sa Pal Gui Jung*"
(*he says it wrong)
What is he talking about?
In Gwa Ung Bo*
(*Causes and consequences).
Sa Pil Gui Jung*
(*Truth wins out in the long run)
My brother.
You're that happy?
Yes, I'm happy,
Overjoyed.
That's great, isn't it?
Noona!
Is this funny?
Are you laughing?
You must be mentally prepared, you know.
What do you mean?
Ji Ho sunbae will never win this.
That means this challenge
is going to end right here.
Geum Jan Di, you'll be expelled
just as expected.
Why don't you get your bags packed already?
The result will be apparent only at the end.
I believe in Ji Ho sunbae.
It wasn't that long ago you were telling
Jun Pyo sunbae about believing in you.
You're really thick-skinned.
Are all those in poverty always
swaying with the wind?
Just the thought of Ji Ho sunbae
suffering for someone like you,
I'm so mad, it makes my hair stand on end.
What are you saying?
I should go and stop him.
Isn't there any other way out?
Oh, yeah!
What if you go beg that noona..?
She already helped us a great deal.
So you're just getting ready
for the expulsion?
If it makes Ji Ho sunbae suffer this much,
I should just get expelled.
Ji Ho sunbae, will he just give up?
What's this?
If you can't stop him, you should
just go and cheer him on.
Right?
Hurry up and go.
Thanks, boss.
- Geum Jan Di, fighting!
- Fighting!
Ga Eul, when is competition day?
Why are you asking?
If I went there...
Prince Andrew will be there too, right?
What should I wear that day?
Ga Eul, how's my complexion?
It's gone bad, hasn't it?
This is not the time for
me to act like this,
I have to go in and do some upkeep now.
He's so ugly. Ugly!
Why is he like that? Really!
Stand by me, please look at me.
Even though I don't know about love yet.
Stand by me, please focus on me.
Even though I don't know how to love yet.
There's something I'd like to ask you.
Go ahead.
How did you get your driving license?
You heard about it?
Seo Hyun taught me.
I thought I was going to die.
But I didn't want to be embarrassed.
That's how I got the license.
You should stop now.
Why must I stop?
There's no more value in going on.
Anyway, I didn't come to
that school voluntarily.
Stay with me.
I don't know if I can win but...
I'll try my best.
Now, I want to win.
That...
Is that for me to eat?
Ah!
Do you want to try it?
Together make it love.
Forever make it your smile.
Happy smiles that fill you up.
Together make it love.
Forever make it your smile.
Now please hold, please hold my hand.
Delicious!
Stand by me, please look at me.
Eat more then.
Even though I don't know about love yet.
Stand by me, please focus on me.
Even though I don't know how to love yet.
Oh, there!
Do your jobs well!
What's wrong with the car?
Do you want to be fired?
Whenever I'm tired, lucky in my life.
Like a dream, you come to my side.
Whenever I'm sad, lucky in my dream.
You always surround me with your warmth.
No matter when or where
I always smile like this.
No matter how much more
troubles on earth, I'd never...
Let you see my tears.
Even if you don't know my heart.
Even if from afar.
I can see your smile, I'd feel very lucky.
Can you come one step closer to me?
Yi Jung, is the preparation for
your exhibition going well?
Yes.
When is it supposed to be?
I think, probably next month.
Over here!
The weather is great, right?
Come sit over here.
What would you like to drink?
We have an in-house formulated cocoa,
want to try that?
Yes.
Your friend too?
Don't say no, it's a great drink, you know.
Butler Lee,
Please bring us some cocoa.
Here you go.
- Eat.
- Yes.
Hey, buddy.
I'm asking you a favor.
It's not too late to change your mind now.
Be careful.
Don't force yourself, just stop now.
Are you worried for me?
Please, be careful.
Hey, you know if you lose this round,
It'll all end.
Any strategy...
No,
A secret weapon or something,
do you have that?
You do, right?
You must.
Secret weapon?
I have it.
Stay still.
It may be a little childish
but this is our strategy.
Just cooperate with me.
Jun Pyo, I'm sorry.
Even if I have to do this,
I must watch over her.
Yoon Ji Ho...
You must be completely mad.
Not just once but twice,
No, including this one, it's three times!
You must die today.
Hey!
Jan Di!
Look at that.
Hey!
Really!
These kids,
when did they become so adorable?
Exactly so.
Ah, it was a good decision
to return to Korea.
Much better than going to
Hollywood, you know?
Yes, an old man like me has more to do now!
Die, die! You die!
Sometimes, a monkey can
fall off a branch too.
Who said cornering was his strength now?
Blowing his own horn.
In the end, Ji Hoo...
Managed to hold the steering wheel.
Yes.
If it wasn't for Geum Jan Di,
He would never do it.
Did you see it?
How did they move along so quickly?
They're quite affectionate too.
Go die!
What's this?
It's not working
Hey, it broke down.
See how he's pressing it,
of course it'll break down.
This is the final determining round.
Shall we see Jan Di's lot?
[Swimming]
Ridiculous!
What's this? Invalid!
Hey, Geum Jan Di,
You did this on purpose, didn't you?
Say it.
This is all a setup, right?
I won't do it.
I won't.
Up to you.
I'll take it as you forfeited the challenge,
So Ji Hoo wins this round, any objections?
What do you mean by that?
I told you.
Whatever the outcome may be,
you must respect it.
I was afraid something like this may happen.
I...
Well, although it was initially agreed upon,
But to end it like this,
to Jun Pyo or to the rest of us,
It's not fair.
And so?
If you'd agree to it, I nominate
myself to take his place.
What?
For this matter,
I'm unwilling to let him off so easily too.
This does sound rather reasonable.
Then, if everyone agrees, I'm okay too.
What do you think?
I agree.
I unconditionally agree.
I agree too.
I'm against it.
What?
Hey, Geum Jan Di!
This fella, even at the end...
I want to take part too.
In place of Gu Jun Pyo,
Yi Jung sunbae is taking part.
So for this round, I'd take
part in place of Ji Hoo sunbae.
Your competitor is Yi Jung, you know.
He's a guy and he's a strong guy too.
This matter involves me too. I can't
just be watching from the sideline.
Stop sticking your head into
this matter, will you?
How can a girl join in this competition?
This involves whether I'd be
expelled from school or not,
I want to put in my best effort too,
then I won't feel so grieved.
Then, let's make it two-against-two.
Who? Me?
I agree too.
Jan Di, if that's what you want,
let's do it.
So it's a done deal just because
you two want it that way?
Gu Jun Pyo, we won't let up
just because she's a girl.
It's my duty to target Ji Hoo.
Fine, until the end of the competition,
there's still about 70 hours.
Almost paradise.
More glorious than dawn.
Your love for me.
Feels like I own the whole world.
In my life.
Like a dream in my tired life.
I hope I can treasure your love forever.
I hold your hand
and shout to the world.
Hey, that's not your fastest speed!
I won't swim anymore.
I swear to heaven.
Hey, you fool,
Even I swim faster than you!
I will love only you.
Like the stars in the night.
A beautiful dream paradise
that belongs to us alone.
I can go anywhere, to my paradise.
Days without you.
I'll forget all the pain.
This is only the start, being with you.
Ah! I'm so tired.
Ah! Ten more minutes, just ten minutes!
Start to travel, start to run.
Loving you forever.
Almost paradise.
Warmer than the sun.
Long ago, there was a poor
little girl named Geum Jan Di...
Why must you be so headstrong
and say those things?
I don't know,
Why did I do that?
Don't you know?
You have an incurable disease.
Defending the weak against the strong.
It's all my fault that Sunbae
is being ostracized.
So if you lose, it'll be alright?
That's why I must win.
Are you confident of winning?
Really!
How will it turn out?
If only I had a time machine
to see the outcome right now.
Jan Di, faster, faster...
Even faster, faster!
3... 2... 1!
What is it?
What's your dream?
Was it about Jan Di?
A dream about the challenge!
Who won?
Well...
Up until just before the end,
it was just about...
Just about?
Then just when you reached your
hand out, at that moment...
That moment?
It became all dark.
What?
All dark.
Nothing.
Then I woke up.
What's that?
Just a daydream.
Oh, really!
You're not of much help at all.
This won't do.
That Yi Jung or Three* Jung,
(*Yi sounds like Two)
No matter what ploy I must use on him...
What ploy?
Put some laxative into his
porridge or something.
No!
Ga Eul,
How could you think of that?
Ahjusshi, you're the one!
You have four eyes but you
still can't tell who's the enemy.
That's not it.
How can you use the sacred porridge
in such a devious ploy?
No, no, never.
Understand?
All along, porridge brings...
health to those who are sick,
consolation to those who are weary.
Such sacred food,
how many times must I say it?
He exploded again, really.
I know, I know.
Then, I'll just use a bicycle and
crash into him from the back.
Ga Eul!
See!
I told you he likes him!
So?
You're asking me to lose to her on purpose?
Since it doesn't matter whether you win
or lose, it's nothing to you anyway.
But Jan Di...
She'll be expelled.
A guy challenging a girl and having
to settle who wins or loses,
Don't you think it's embarrassing?
If a guy challenges a girl and loses to her,
that is really embarrassing!
So...
So you're going to win no matter what?
Although I don't intend to die trying,
I won't settle for just muddling through it.
Hey you!
Listen,
I don't think you have the
right to yell at me, you know.
What did you say?
I warned you, I yield to soft approaches
rather than hard ones.
I went to your rice shop and chatted
with you amicably, you know.
It's not a rice shop but a porridge shop.
Birds of a feather flock together,
that saying is so true.
What do you mean?
Geum Jan Di's habit of defending the weak,
Is that contagious?
Hey, you rude fella!
The exit's that way.
So cold.
I'm back!
Get over here.
Hurry.
What is it?
What do you mean 'What is it'?
Is something wrong?
That's what we wanted to ask you.
Hey, what's this about a challenge?
And what's this about an expulsion?
Oh.. that...
Shut up!
Just answer my question with
a 'Yes' or 'No'.
Mom, that is...
You're going out with that
hyung named Yoon Ji Hoo,
And you're acting dubious so
Gu Jun Pyo hates you now,
so you're being expelled, is that the truth?
Well...
'Yes' or 'No'?
Yes!
What will we do?
Oh! Dear heavens!
Hey, don't you know how difficult
it was to get into that school?
School? I can just go back
to the previous one.
Pre... pre... previous school?
Previous school!
In your previous school,
is master Jun Pyo there?
Tell me! Tell me!
Honey, calm down.
Right from the start, I knew for us,
this would be an impossible fate.
But for us, we still have the
laundry shop, don't we?
So long as we continue like now...
Dad!
If Noona gets expelled, those uniforms
won't come to us anymore.
Everyone will think it's unlucky,
we'll even lose our regular customers.
This mustn't happen to us now.
Let's go and apologize right away.
Honey, straighten your hair.
Kang San, prepare the cushions*.
(*for kneeling)
Noona,
Why is it I don't remember
teaching you any of this?
I'm so disappointed.
Dad!
You!
If you get expelled, from that day on,
your fate with us will end.
No matter how I think about it,
it must be all your fault.
What kind of fool are you!
How dare you cheat on the guy!
Honey, you have no right to scold her.
She must have learnt it all from you.
Hey, you!
What?
Mom, you...
Hey, watch what you say!
Jan Di...
I've been through it so I know,
To be cheated on,
that feels really terrible.
Even so,
if the girl takes it on
herself to apologize,
Then,
he'll feel helpless but he'll still
forgive you, that's how guys are.
So...
So?
Say sorry!
Gu Jun Pyo?
Where are you going so late at night?
To practice, why?
You want to win that much?
We have no choice.
'We'?
Why must it be Ji Ho?
So long as it's not Ji Ho...
Gu Jun Pyo!
It's still not too late now.
Just say this one sentence.
Say you like me...
Just that.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: christykorea, ai*
Timer: knitoe
Editor/QC: puela
Final QC: knitoe
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Geum Jan Di!
Shall we... go on a date?
Date?
Ji Hoo and Geum Jan Di,
It's hard to imagine them.
They must be somewhere sunning
themselves or taking a nap.
I'll get the wind and a good workout too.
Wearing just that?
You know, love...
Does not always happen as you planned it.
Where is this?
My house.
What?
I always thought that I
owe something to Ji Hoo.
Geum Jan Di,
I can't do what I did in the past,
just so that no one else can have her.
I'll go and destroy her myself.
What?
What did you say?
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get it for FREE @ d-addicts.com