Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Episode 17
- Oh...
- Giddyup, giddyup!
Grandfather, faster! Faster!
Oh, alright.
Sir, I will do it instead.
Eh? Giving a horseback ride to a grandson
is a grandfather's pleasure.
Why would you try to take that away?
- Ji Hoo, having fun?
- Yes, Grandfather!
- That's good.
- But let's go fishing.
I'll catch a gigantic shark!
Fishing? OK, Ji Hoo.
- When should we go?
- Let's go now.
OK, let's go.
- Oh, that boy...
- Sir, are you that happy?
Ah, you! Become a grandfather
and you'll know the feeling.
Yes?
What did you say? There's no mistake?
Give a straight answer.
Is it definitely Ji Hoo?
- Sir...
- Yes?
Due to talk of a tie-up between
Shinhwa and JK Group,
the prices of Shinhwa related stocks
are hitting new highs every day.
The two groups consummating
the strategic merger
are expected to become blood-tied...
Do you know what that means?
If tomorrow, things fall
apart with JK Group,
what do you think will happen?
In one morning, our company's stock
could become worthless paper.
Your grandfather, your father...
shed blood and sweat to protect Shinhwa.
But because of your childish love,
does it have to be tossed aside
for you to come to your senses?
That's enough!
- Jun Pyo, go outside.
- I'm not done talking.
Jun Pyo, as of tomorrow, you will act
like Ha Jae Kyung's fiance and mean it.
Understand?
You can't answer me?
Didn't I tell you to get out?
Was I not enough?
- Don't get involved.
- Need a hotel, sell a daughter.
Need investment, sell a son.
The next time you need something,
what will you do then?
Because you don't have any more children.
Everything has been for your sake.
And who decides that?
Who the hell says that everything is for us?
I have never once thought,
that you've done anything for our sake.
Your world of happiness,
who do you think gave it to you?
Happiness, you say?
Do you even know what happiness is?
I have no reason to hear your complaints
caused by too much luck.
Jun Pyo... Please let him be.
I already told you that this
is none of your business!
This time...
I will not just sit back and watch.
Su... Sunbae!
What...
[Su-am Foundation]
[Su-am Art Center]
And you, what are you doing at this hour?
I... a situation kind of came up.
You're doing all this by yourself?
I'm in the middle of doing all this.
Now what are you doing?
I told you... I can do some cleaning too.
Thank you.
Here.
I can't split the money with you.
So instead, I'll be responsible
for the coffee and the drive.
Drive?
Jan Di... Jan Di...
Wake up! Can you hear me?
I'm OK.
Get up!
Get on!
It's overwork and malnutrition.
With some rest, she'll be fine.
Thank you.
I'll just do this for you and leave.
Because you were my friend, I backed off.
Because she was my friend's girl,
I even gave up.
Also, to the very end, I gave you a chance.
Now, I'm not going to hold back.
What? Now that Jun Pyo's engaged,
you got anxious so you decided
to throw yourself at him?
- You detestable and audacious little..
- That's enough!
Your grandfather, your father...
shed blood and sweat to protect Shinhwa.
But because of your childish love,
does it have to be tossed aside
for you to come to your senses?
Noona, someone said they're
waiting for you at the playground.
Wh... what's the matter?
Jun Pyo...
Gu Jun Pyo...
Did something happen to Gu Jun Pyo?
He wants to officially date me.
Because I was so happy...
Because I thought I'd go crazy,
I ran over here to tell you.
You're going to congratulate me, aren't you?
Congratulations.
Falling in love with one's fiance...
Isn't it just too romantic?
Thank you.
Having a friend to whom I can
tell these kinds of things...
It makes me so happy.
Hello.
I got a matching phone as a present.
Ah, yes...
Let's go.
Please look this way.
Look this way. One more time, please...
Seeing them standing side by side like
this, aren't they a well-matched couple?
That's true.
Jun Pyo, in such a short time,
you've gotten more dignified.
Jae Kyung, now stop being frivolous
and be careful not to disgrace Jun Pyo.
Oh, that's not so.
Now, isn't it about time to change the image
of Shinhwa Group's head wife?
Jae Kyung, going forward,
please continue to brighten things up.
Thank you.
Then can we leave now?
And where would you go?
The significance of the first date
and you want us to be followed?
Oh, alright. Alright.
Please take good care of her, Jun Pyo.
Then...
Over there!
Jeez! This kid learned
bad habits somewhere...
I'm not doing it! I'm not doing it!
Shall we go?
But I want to stay with Grandmother.
Whose grandmother?
My mother.
Hey, Jun!
"Jun"? You think that I'm a puppy...?
- Oh, what do you mean, a picture?!
- Look up there.
Oh, let go! Let go.
Buy this for me.
Wait for me!
Come on.
I don't want to!
I told you that I'm not getting on.
If you want to ride it,
then get on by yourself.
We're on a date so why
should I ride it by myself?
Ah, you're afraid of heights?
That's it, isn't it?
That really doesn't suit you.
Who's afraid of heights?
If you 'fess up,
then you won't need to get on.
You and a cable car...
Ah, save me!!!
Is it like that?
This monkey, turning someone into a patient!
Oh, get on! If I get on,
then this'll be over with.
[Gu Jun Pyo Loves Geum Jan Di]
["First Night Together"]
Studying going well?
If I study like this and
get into medical school,
that will be a real miracle.
But you're the miracle girl.
Eh?
You don't remember?
Wonder Girl Geum Jan Di.
Even if I can't go to medical school,
at the grandfather's clinic, I can still...
Couldn't you make up with your grandfather?
We never fought.
I'm the one who was abandoned.
It's not like that.
Grandfather is also suffering a lot.
Also...
"Also"?
Sunbae...
He thinks about you a lot.
What?
Who would've thought that Geum Jan Di
would sense things better than I?
That person.
And Grandfather too.
I... just...
Are you really going to be like this?
I'm always the one begging.
Even when we're together,
it doesn't even seems like it.
You're really being annoying.
If you're that discontented,
then you can just stop chasing after me.
It's because I'm uneasy.
What?
I keep... feeling uneasy.
If you make me believe...
If you reassure me,
I'll stop chasing after you.
I'll wait politely.
What do I need to do?
Kiss me.
Hey, Jun, wait for me!
Hey, Jun, I said wait for me.
Now what?
You're annoying so just go away.
But when I get a boyfriend,
I've wanted to do 99 things.
You're already annoyed?
99 things?
I'm not interested,
so do them with another guy.
I'm busy.
Fine, then let's do one thing each day.
So when 99 days passes and it's the
100th day, we'll be like real lovers.
Talking about a 100th day...
You planning on sticking to me until then?
Then, because today's the first day,
how about 2 special things?
Can you take me somewhere?
You must’ve been an otter in your past life.
Me?
You're similar.
You’re diligent, clumsy, and cute.
Even the part where you
can’t live without water.
Can’t you tell me that
I’m like a mermaid or something?
You can’t be a mermaid...
Not the part about not
finding love and it turning into bubbles.
a pun with the fairytale
"The Little Mermaid" and water bubbles.
It’s too sad.
Otter must be hungry.
Let’s go. I’ll buy dinner.
Monkey, why do I have to go to places
like this? You go by yourself.
I’m telling you to try it.
It’s really good.
Jun Pyo.
It’s Jan Di!
Jan Di, how are you here?
We totally had telepathy, don't we?
Hello. My name is Cha Eun Jae.
Excuse me for a moment.
Welcome!
I welcome you to the world of pottery.
Thank you.
I’m the one that’s thankful.
Huh?
Only middle-aged ahjummas
usually visit here.
I’m really happy to see
someone around my age.
How did you become interested in pottery?
Someone I know makes pottery.
Do you like that person?
Excuse me?
Because you want to get to know him
Learning what he does and
wanting to do it with him
because you want
to know him better...
I know that feeling very well.
Do you by chance have...?
He was my playmate.
While the other children played house,
we played pottery.
Did your boyfriend become a potter?
He did become a potter,
but he didn’t become my boyfriend.
There’s no need to feel sorry for me.
Thanks to him, I got a lot stronger.
This teacup.
Do you know that even though it looks
very thin, it’s very strong in the inside?
After it gets spun, stepped, and carved
thousands of times on the spinning wheel...
1,300 degrees.
You’re right!
It has to endure 1300 degrees in the kiln
to form the strong spirit that it has.
But... how did you know that?
There was a time when I
overheard it somewhere.
To me, that friend was my
kiln and my spinning wheel.
Have you forgotten that person yet?
Bring your friend over sometime.
I’m curious.
This is my studio.
Please do your "work" someplace else.
Work - a pun for flirting
and picking up women.
Son, you work here as well.
Let’s be thoughtful to each other.
If you’re going to come and go like this,
I’m going to move my studio.
You can’t do that.
I may be able to leave, but you can’t.
Have you forgotten?...
The fact that the head of pottery
in the So family is not me,
but you, Yi Jung.
I never said that I wanted to do it.
You never said that you
didn’t want to do it either.
Isn’t that so?
Why do you live like this?
Because I’m bored of it.
I’m bored of living, Son.
Has there even been one second
where you lived to the fullest?
There... was only one woman
that made me wanted
to live the right way.
After you lose that kind of woman,
they’re all the same.
They’re all just meaningless repetition.
To Mother...
Don’t you feel that you’re
being too cruel to Mother?
That's why I’m wishing my
life would pass by quickly.
But things just don’t happen
the way I wish them to.
Do you know why you became a
potter setting all things aside?
It’s because you are like me.
It’s cruel, right?
Don’t forget.
The "real one" only comes once.
Another cruel reality.
The two servings of kimbab
that you ordered are here.
Event: For great women that can finish
our free jumbo ramen within 20 minutes,
we offer you coupons for
50 free bowls of ramen as a prize.
Please enjoy.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Is that for real?
Yes?
But it’s pretty difficult to pull off.
Do you want to do it?
If I really succeed, will you give me
a free coupon for 50 bowls of ramen?
Of course.
But who’s going to do it?
I am.
Hey, monkey. What are you doing?
Jan Di, you want that, don’t you?
Okay. I’ll win it for you.
Don’t do it. Are you some kind
of eating god to eat all that?
What are you going to do if I succeed?
What?
If I win, then all three of you have to
listen to one wish that I have.
Wish?
I’ll do it.
Yes!
I challenge the jumbo bowl of ramen.
Start!
Five,
Four,
Three,
Two,
One!
Success!
Jan Di, a present.
Now, you guys have to listen to my wish.
What is that wish?
Let's go on a trip!
What?
The four of us.
Jan Di, Ji Hoo, Jun Pyo and me.
Let’s have the two couples
go on a doubles trip. To our resort.
Hey, monkey.
I hate going on doubles.
What kind of excuse is that? You agreed
to listen to my wish no matter what.
Jan Di, you’re going to go with me, right?
Let’s go.
What are you!?
How can a girl eat all that?
You’re not even some kind of glutton.
Jan Di, let’s go. Hm?
Ji Hoo, let’s go.
Mom, please don’t die.
Don’t die.
I found you.
Do you think Mom will die?
She’ll be okay.
So Yi Jung, where are you?
Yi Reum oppa’s calling.
How did you find me?
Wherever you are, I just know.
You can’t go until I fall asleep, ok?
Can I sleep a little?
Eun Jae.
Can’t you...
find me again?
You were the one...
who always found me.
Good morning!
Hey, monkey.
Why are you here first thing in the morning?
What kind of speech is that to your fiancee?
It’s okay.
I think it’s his way of showing
affection, so I don’t feel bad.
I’ve already grown accustomed to it.
You make a perfectly able person a mutt.
This is why well raised
ladies are different.
Because Jae Kyung, a kind heart like yours
can't be bought with money or taught.
No, that’s not true.
I've recently made a friend,
who's pretty and strong willed,
even though she has a difficult life.
Friend?
Hey, monkey?
Aren’t you going to go?
If we are late, then the cars
will get backed up.
Then we’ll go.
Have a good time.
We have to go this way.
Hello. How are you?
Wait right here.
Tada.
How is it? Is it pretty?
Do you think Jun Pyo will like it?
I usually get goosebumps
over stuff like this,
but I think people really do change.
I keep wanting to mark him as my man.
J J?
Jun Pyo and Jae Kyung.
When I got it engraved,
it felt a little strange.
I wondered if this guy
is really my other half.
J J.
I see.
Now…
How is it?
It’s good.
It doesn’t taste good.
Could you prepare us dinner?
Yes, a BBQ.
Jan Di, eat up.
Here.
I don’t have any.
Jan Di.
Geum Jan Di, are you okay?
Get a hold of yourself.
Are you coming to?
Gu Jun Pyo.
You can’t swim.
I can now.
What happened?
I learned.
You don’t turn your head.
How many times are you turning your head?
Don’t bend your knees.
Kick, with force.
Instead of letting some other guy save you,
I realized I'd rather die.
So I learned for you.
What happened?
Is Jan Di okay?
She’s okay.
That’s a relief.
I’ll take her from this point on.
Yeah. Take her so she can rest.
Are you okay?
I’m okay.
Two cups of latte.
Enjoy.
- What cakes are good?
- Cakes?
We have chocolate cake and cheesecake today.
I think the cheesecake would
suit better with the latte.
Please give us two slices of cheesecake.
Two? Ok.
Do you need anything else?
Why are you like this? Are you crazy?
No.
I’m so clearheaded.
That’s why I finally understood.
What? What did you finally understand?
Do you remember?
The story that our grandpa
told us about the Kiln God.
What are you trying to say?
The bowl that the Kiln God selected
is not mine, but yours, Yi Jung.
Hyung.
You don’t know...
how much I wanted
these hands.
Do you?
So…
you’re saying you’re going to give up?
You’re saying that you’re
going to go out on your own?
You're running away!
You’re saying you’re leaving
me alone in this house,
with all the responsibility?
And run away all by yourself!
Are you okay?
I keep forgetting that I shouldn’t
be swimming anymore.
Do I have to be a firefighter
and a lifeguard too now?
I lost something, so I’ll be back soon.
Don't worry.
I won’t get into any more accidents.
I’ll take her from this point on.
What are you doing?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: Javafiend, Beeni
Spot Translators: ahsieee, plegend2007
Timer: Ahoxan
Editor/QC: annchong
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get this for FREE @ d-addicts.com