Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
What are you doing?
Who are you to do this kind of thing?
Did anyone ask for that kind of favor?
That isn't even a favor. It's groveling.
Don't you have any pride?
It's not because I don't have any pride.
It's because you were hurting so much.
Because you were about to die from sadness.
What does it matter to you?
It has nothing to do with you.
Get lost.
Episode 4
The energy around you is so dark.
What use is it even if
the F4 emits our own light?
There really is no black hole other than you.
Gu Jun Pyo,
can I ask you something?
Are you not going to ask me
if I tell you not to ask?
Just act like you usually do.
It doesn't suit you.
Would suppressing your emotions
and not expressing them,
for the sake of the person you like,
be the right thing to do?
Right thing, my foot!
- Huh?
- What is that?
Then that's being a complete stranger.
How is that liking someone?
If the world goes into pieces tomorrow,
then you'd probably die
first because of regret.
Gu Jun Pyo,
What?
you might not be completely stupid.
Did you know that just now?
It's better to regret your actions, instead
of regretting because you didn't do anything.
That's my philosophy.
It looks like Ji Hoo isn't going
to show up till the very end.
Be well everyone.
And don't cause any trouble.
Goodbye. We'll visit.
Don't come visit.
Come to have an exhibition.
Take care of yourself.
Being too kind is your disease.
If you treat someone too well,
the scars run deeper, Casanova.
Must you do that lawyer or NGO crap, Noona?
I really can't understand women.
Do you know it's been ten years since
you've sincerely called me Noona?
Anyway, it's the truth
that it's pretty cool,
so I decided to accept you as a Noona.
Are you complaining?
Jan Di.
Please don't forget my favor.
Please take care of yourself.
Be well everyone. I'm going.
Go, take care of yourself.
Ruthless bastard.
How can he not come to the very end?
What did I tell you?
You guys tell me that I have
the cruelest personality,
but I told you that the
real cruel one is Ji Hoo.
He looks so serene, but once he
turns his back, he's the scariest.
Isn't the talking behind
my back a little too harsh?
- You...
- What is this?
- How long have you been here?
- Since three hours ago.
What? So you were here before us...
and you didn't even come out for a peek?
What are you doing right now?
Were you someone who is only this good?
Chase after her!
If she can't stay next to you,
then you can go next to her.
You said that you liked her.
Does your love only consist of
looking out from behind a pillar?
Do you still have the right
to say that you love her?
It's for the next plane.
I already sent along my luggage.
Yoon Ji Hoo.
Rascal, he has a skill
for surprising people.
How did you suddenly
get the heart to do that?
Thanks to this little lady.
What?
What? Rascal.
Come here, come here.
Cute rascal!
Thanks.
I came to realize it thanks to you.
That I have to earnestly spend time with her.
You taught me to possibly have
the courage to hang on to her.
It's a relief that I got
to know a child like you.
I'm going.
Geum Jan Di.
What? What are you going to do now?
Listen to my words very carefully.
I'm only going to say this once,
so listen very carefully.
Geum Jan Di. You and I...
What did he say?
Aren't you getting in?
Saturday at 4 o'clock.
In front of Nam San Tower.
If you're late one minute, you're dead.
We must get it at all costs.
Come quickly!
As soon as it opens at
4 o'clock, run for this.
And if you find something that you
think will fit, just stuff it in the cart.
Wouldn't it be better
if we just went together?
Mom needs to go to the cabbage blowout sale.
If the clothes shop was the civil war,
this cabbage shop is
World War II.
Right.
You know, the lady who was standing next
to me last time. Her teeth were out too.
Really?
Three months worth of our shop's
profits are in our hands.
Got it?
Aja!
It's snowing.
Hey, Dad must be waiting for us.
Let's go home quickly.
Saturday at 4 o'clock.
In front of Nam San Tower.
No way... no, no.
That can't be.
What are you murmuring about?
Mom, there's no way someone
would wait outside in the snow,
for four hours, when I didn't
say that I'd go, right?
How can someone do that
unless they're crazy?
Let's go.
Hold on.
Crazy guy...
Mom, hold this.
Mom, go on ahead.
Jan Di! Where are you going?
I'm going somewhere!
That girl!
Do you know what time it is?
That's what I'm supposed to ask.
Do you really have nothing else to do?
Didn't I say that you'd be
dead if you were late?
Did I say that I'd come?
You're here now.
That's because...
I was thinking that maybe there'd
be a chance that you'd be waiting.
So what would have happened
if I didn't come by?
But anyways, you came!
And whose fault is it that
I went through all this?
What have you done so well
that you're getting all huffy?
It's cold.
Get up.
I'll buy you something warm.
Steam's coming off from your body.
Get up.
Quickly.
You wanna drink tea?
Or do you wanna just go?
Here.
It's 30,000 Won coffee.
Thug, are you scamming people now too?
And I can't drink this kind of crap.
Just try it.
The coffee tastes excellent.
Do you want me to tell you
why it's 30,000 Won coffee?
Follow me.
Wow.
How is it?
Wasn't I right?
It's just like drinking coffee
from a hotel's sky lounge.
Would someone even be
able to leave a drugstore
in your hands with
your poor calculations?
What?
36,300 Won.
Huh?
If you're going to take money, you might as
well count in the labor and extra fees.
So a wealthy person CAN do
those kinds of calculations...
I'm just acting like I don't.
If I really didn't know, then how
could I become a wealthy person?
Wow... there are so many stars.
Hey, those aren't stars.
They're satellites, you stupid girl.
Are you an idiot?
Are there THAT many satellites?
Are you kidding me? They're satellites.
I don't want to hear that from you.
- What, you idiot?
- What, are you dumb?
- This clueless girl.
- You're even more clueless.
Hello?
You're at Pork restaurant?
Don't budge. I'll be there.
- Why is it like this?
- What is it?
Why is it dark?
Ahjussi!
Ahjussi! There's someone here!
Hey, hey, hey.
What is it?
- The door's locked!
- Really? It's really locked?
Ahjussi!
Stop acting so tacky by being so panicked.
I can call someone, so just keep still.
I really need to go!
I'll be killed by my mom!
Where's my cell phone?
You don't have a phone?
What about you?
I don't have a phone to begin with.
What kind of girl doesn't
even have a cell phone?
We're locked inside because of you.
How is that because of me?
If it was cold, you should've
gone into some place warm.
Are you a statue or something?
I was pissed off.
It was the first time in my life that
I waited for someone like that.
What?
What are we going to do?
Ahjussi!
What are you doing?
Should we go in there?
It's cold.
Hey, move over.
I don't want to.
Sorry.
What?
I'm saying I'm sorry.
In the end, it's become like
this because of me.
At least you know your place.
So what?
Why is a plutocrat like that?
You were standing outside
in the cold for four hours.
Nobody at your house said anything?
Your advisor, your bodyguards,
your chauffeur...
What did all those people do?
- I sent them all away.
- Why?
I wanted to match the level of a commoner.
You really are trying way too hard.
Hey, grass patch.
What?!
Can I be honest with you?
Honest about what?
What is this?
Hey...
Tell me from over there.
Right now, I think I might be...
This guy... He does this every chance he gets.
Pervert.
Do you really want to be this way
in this kind of situation?
Get off of me.
Hey, get up.
If you don't get up in three seconds,
I don't know what I'll do to you.
One.
Two.
Two and one eighth.
Three!
This rascal, really...
Hey.
Why is he burning up?
Hey. Are you okay?
I'm sick.
Sick?
Yeah, you're really burning up.
It'd be strange for you not to be sick.
It's cold.
You're cold?
What are you doing?
My mom told me that if you wrap
your head like this, you'll get warm.
Get in, I'll take you home.
It's fine.
I need to think of excuses for my mom.
I'll walk and then ride the bus.
Should I teach you?
Your excuses?
Hey!
I'm sorry!
I won't ever do it again!
Mother, Father,
- I've committed a deadly sin.
- One, two, three!
Deadly sin?
What kind of person have you saved?
A person who's going to
inherit the Shinhwa Group.
And what kind of group is Shinhwa?
Korea's greatest company.
Then saving the inheritor of Shinhwa Group
is the same as saving Korea's economy.
How is that a deadly sin?
It won't be enough even
if we give you an order.
So instead of order, we got this!
Doesn't this suit me well?
What is all this?
And how did you know?
What do you mean, how did I know?
Young Master.
Hold on. What was Young Master's name?
Jun Pyo. Gu Jun Pyo.
- Gu Jun Pyo
- I know, I know.
Young Master Jun Pyo sent us all this.
He told me to not scold you too much
because you were with him all night.
He sent us all this as a repayment of his debt.
Because he's the Young Master
of the best plutocrat,
he was so well-mannered.
He said that next time, he would
come himself to say hello.
But it was so motivational,
that tears just...
Mom, don't cry.
Honey, how can you
cry on such a happy day?
Since I was with you for one whole night,
tell them that I'll take
responsibility for you.
Hey! They say that Geum Jan Di
and Gu Jun Pyo are going out!
They say Geum Jan Di's boyfriend
is Senior Gu Jun Pyo!
Geum Jan Di has been enthroned
as Gu Jun Pyo's girlfriend.
Commoner Jan Di has ascended in identity.
Enthroned as Gu Jun Pyo's girlfriend.
They say Geum Jan Di has been enthroned
as Gu Jun Pyo's new girlfriend!
Jan Di! Hi!
You look pretty today.
Geum Jan Di. Hi!
Jan Di. Hi!
Glad to see you!
Jan Di!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Jan Di!
Jan Di, do you want to go
shopping with us today?
Geum Jan Di, you have to come to my
birthday party this weekend.
Here, drink this.
Thanks. Thanks.
Bye! Bye!
Geum Jan Di.
She has...
Bad intentions.
Jun Pyo, is this for real?
No! It's not!
It certainly isn't what
you guys are thinking of.
- This, you see...
- Yeah.
It's real.
No!
No! No!
I wandered today to the hill, Maggie.
To watch the scene below.
(Gum Jan Di means green grass)
The creek and the creaking old mill,
Maggie. Where we sat long, long ago.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I was a little dizzy.
I'm fine now.
That's a relief.
Nobody knows that I came to visit you,
so you don't have to worry.
Jan Di.
Yes?
Is it true about F4's Gu Jun Pyo?
No.
It's because we bumped into each other
accidentally. It's simply an accident.
But it seemed like he really liked you.
Hey! That doesn't make any sense.
He's just playing around and teasing me.
How could Gu Jun Pyo...
Don't you know after you
got abused by him before?
The invincible Gu Jun Pyo liking ME?
That... that is true.
Yeah.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes, I think I'm all better now.
Jan Di, should we go somewhere and play?
Just wait a little bit.
Shinhwa Kindergarten?
NO!
Why are you touching other people's stuff?
What do you think you're doing?
Sorry...
I...
I wrote weird things in here so
I don't want anyone to see it.
Sorry I got mad.
Sorry I didn't ask for permission.
You should change your clothes too.
Jun Pyo,
are you being sincere?
About what?
Geum Jan Di.
What else is there besides sincerity?
Do you even know what sincerity is to us,
to take it so lightly?
We only have freedom in dating.
The final decision is made by our parents.
You haven't forgotten that right?
Were you guys just talking
like you were real men?
What the heck?
So you've been boasting when
you weren't even real men?
What's your definition of a real man?
A man who takes responsibility
from the beginning to the end.
To the end?
Yes, to the end.
Do you want to dance?
Huh?
It's my first time at a place like this,
so I'm just going to watch.
Okay.
Then just wait here for a second.
Ow!
I'm sorry.
What?
Are you mortified?
If your face is ugly, then you
should at least dance well.
With a sad body like that, what makes you
think it's okay for you to crawl in here?
Acting ugly as you look...
Ga Eul, you're not going anywhere right?
Where would I go?
Don't go! Don't go without me!
What star is this nonsense from now?
Just go inside and make porridge.
Welcome...
Doesn't Geum Jan Di work here?
Yes.
I don't see her.
She's not working today.
And you are... Jan Di's friend?
Since when?
Since kindergarten.
Then you're best friends?
Let's go.
Huh?
Where?
See? I was right.
I'm telling you because I'm
afraid Jan Di will get hurt.
So Dear, I would like you to warn her.
Those sorts of things are important for girls.
What sort of warning?
It's not a tree she can climb,
so don't even bother?
Since she's a toy for killing time,
just accept it if you rich boys
eventually throw her away?
Hey, calm down.
It's scary to see such
a cute lady being angry.
Ga Eul, you really are Jan Di's friend.
You think, if you make that expression
with your pretty face, everyone's going to fall for it?
You tried it on the wrong person.
I'll pretend I didn't hear anything today.
Okay then.
It's making me angrier the
more I think about it.
The person who was the pursuer
is that guy, not Jan Di.
Jan Di doesn't have the faintest
notion of climbing that tree!
Yo, Yi Jung
What have you done now?
What do you mean?
There's only one reason why
girls leave here angry.
I don't know.
She's the type that I hate the most...
that kind of person.
What kind of person is that?
There's such a thing.
Whether it's comedy or melodrama,
in the end it results in a typical tragedy.
I hate dealing with unsophisticated people.
You didn't have to make such effort.
Still, it's very important.
It shouldn't fall.
Sorry about that.
It's okay.
Isn't it suffocating in here?
Thank you.
Let's go down after one more song.
[Thanks for last night.]
No!
NO WAY!
Why did you want to wear
uniforms all of a sudden?
Sometimes... it's nice to have
the atmosphere of a student.
That hair... will it really straighten out?
It's already been two hours.
You're not going to do this
every morning, are you?
A solution will come out eventually.
Straighten it out well.
Yes.
What about me do you hate so much?
What are you not satisfied with?
Your greasy face, the disgusting way you walk,
your stupid curly hair!
Everything is perfectly annoyingly.
It's such an eyesore to see
you bunch wearing street clothes.
And picking on weak kids for fun
with your red cards or whatever
with your thoughtlessness!
That's the worst!
Now, let's go!
No, it's probably not.
No, no.
How is that I can't remember anything?
Let's be calm. Let's be calm, Geum Jan Di.
If something did happen, there's no way
nothing's happening now.
Is there? Or not? Is there? Or not?
I'm going crazy.
Hey, hey!
What are you doing?
Let me go.
- Let go while I'm still nice.
- What are you doing?
Are you saying that because your
mouth is already torn open?
I can't believe this.
No matter what a hell-cat you are.
This is what's scary about people
who don't have much.
I knew you were the world's greatest skank,
but this is a little too much!
Hey! Hey!
Explain yourself in a way I can understand.
I didn't do anything to be treated this way.
Are you going to let me go?
Let go. Let go.
Let's go show her.
What's the matter? Let go! Let go!
Hurry up and go.
Let go!
You didn't do anything?
When you trick Jun Pyo,
that's like tricking all of us.
If you badmouth the F4,
that's like badmouthing all of us!
How can you, a girl like dirty mop...
Did you think we'd leave you alone
when you're dirtying Shinhwa High?
Bad girl!
What are you doing?
Who do you think you are to bother her?
Jun Pyo sunbae, don't be tricked!
Look at this and snap out of it!
No, Gu Jun Pyo. This isn't the truth.
This is wrong.
What went so wrong that a
picture like this was taken?
I don't know.
I think someone's trying to frame me.
You're worth this much?
Were you a girl only worth this much?
Even if they were framing you,
are you the type of girl to easily
fall into this sort of trap?
Gu Jun Pyo.
Even if you believe it or
not, it doesn't matter.
I don't even know why I'm
trying to defend myself
in a situation that
doesn't make any sense.
Either way,
this isn't the truth.
I... I really don't know
anything about this!
I'm just going to ask you one thing.
The girl in the picture...
Geum Jan Di, is that you?
You said it didn't matter
if I believe it or not.
Right?
Yeah, you're right.
Geum Jan Di,
From now on, I don't know who you are.
Hey! You slutty insect!
Take it off! Take it off!
Take this off. Take it off.
Take it off.
Hey, this is going too far.
At this rate, I wouldn't be
surprised if someone dies.
I think it hasn't been this bad
since Jun Hee's wedding.
Let's hurry up.
I'm sorry, but I'm not sure.
Can you just tell me once?
First things first, we should find the guy.
You said you met him at a club, right?
I went to ask but they said
they didn't know him.
Then when you opened your eyes that morning,
did you see anything in the room?
A business card or his belongings.
Ah...
He wrote a memo on the mirror.
"Thanks for last night."
In red lipstick.
Wait.
Lipstick?
Yes.
Was it yours?
No.
Then, that means it's his.
There are three people.
Stop saying nonsense and go away.
Wait, it's true.
Look.
At this angle, there's no
way he took the picture.
There was a third person in the
room that took this picture.
Then that's... the lipstick owner.
What are you doing?
It looks like a smudge but it's not erasing.
This!
Let's go.
Wait, wait.
Just leave it to us.
Thanks.
Yes...
With those looks, they must
be from Andromeda.
That's a little difficult.
I heard that guy is the number one here.
If we take your Number One,
I guess it would hurt you a bit.
Thanks for understanding.
But...
If you don't hand him over, you won't
just be hurting, you'll get closed.
Is that okay?
What?
It'll take about two weeks, right?
We have the F4 reputation.
We should finish it off in a week.
The building next to here, it's yours right?
I can probably start tomorrow.
I should loosen up and get some practice in.
It's who?
[For commoner Geum Jan Di,
Shinhwa High tomato party]
[will be held this afternoon. All are invited!!]
Jan Di. Jan Di.
I have something urgent to tend to,
so I'll be going first.
Jan Di!
Never mind.
Bye!
One, two, three!
Don't be so distressed.
For Gu Jun Pyo to act
like this over a slut...
is unbelievable.
Please snap out of it.
This isn't it.
How can Gu Jun Pyo act this way?
This is so unfair!
You...
Weren't you her friend?
Can you say that as her friend?
Because she stole you away from me.
Please don't go.
Move your hand.
What's the reason that Geum Jan Di
is okay but I'm not?
What's the reason why Jan Di is okay?!
No, Gu Jun Pyo. This isn't the truth.
This is wrong.
What went so wrong that a
picture like this was taken?
I don't know.
I think someone's trying to frame me.
Is this all you've got?
Do more! Do more!
Attack!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: Beeni, lilshinhwafreak
Spot Translator: saturn
Timer: Zealousy
Editor/QC: annchong
Final QC: melica
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
F4!
What's that?
The successor of the Shinhwa Group, Gu Jun Pyo!
- What?
- You're so noisy!
What are you doing?
From your uniform, shoes,
to your other belongings,
we've bought a new set last night.
From today on, Geum Jan Di
from grade 2 in classroom B
will officially be Gu Jun Pyo's girlfriend.
I have opposition to that decision.
Ji Hoo!
Where is this?
New Caledonia.
It's our island that only has our resort.
It's Shinhwa Group's.
Love... Love?
This is a FREE fansub! NOT for SALE!!!
Get this for FREE @ d-addicts.com