Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
Episode 10
You must be new here.
I'm...
You...
Ga Eul!
You're here to meet me?
You should've dressed up like this before!
I really didn't recognize you.
Should we...go out?
Miss Ga Eul.
Do you know him?
No, I don't know who he is.
Ga Eul!
What relationship do you have with this guy?
The person who has my heart,
and won't return it, is this person right here!
Ga Eul, please stop making me suffer and come to me.
Ga Eul!
How much luck did that chick pile up in a former life.
Even though it's just acting,
shouldn't we go through with it to the end?
Yes, yes. Thank you!
Master, one pumpkin porridge!
OK.
What is all this?
Tomorrow is Valentine's Day.
Don't you think it's a waste to not do anything?
Ooh. Who are you giving it to?
Me? Me?
Just...someone I am grateful to.
Hey Jan Di.
Aren't you giving Jun Pyo sunbae any chocolates?
Here, take this.
Why should I give him anything?
- Let me take this too.
- Hey, that's...
- This one too!
- No! You can't!
- Give me this too.
- That one you can't!
Hey! Look at the terrible state of this restaurant!
Disgraceful.
Philosophy on food.
Confidence of the Chef.
I can't find any of it at this restaurant.
How despicable.
Grandpa, our porridge is quite delicious.
*Jjajangmyun = noodle with black-bean sauce
Jjajangmyun!
Grandpa, this is a porridge restaurant.
For jjajangmyun, you've to go to a Chinese restaurant.
Jjajangmyun!
Grandpa!
Grandpa, there is a restaurant near here.
You can go there.
Tell him to wait.
- What?
We can make jjajangmyun.
How is it?
I've never tasted such terrible jjajangmyun in my life.
How can you serve this horrible food to your customers?
And you call this a restaurant.
Who ask you to order jjajangmyun at a porridge restaurant?
But Grandpa, you still have to pay for the jjajangmyun.
How much do you think we should charge?
Since it was a special order,
we should ask for at least 5,000 won.
What is this?
Payment for the jjajangmyun.
Grandpa, you have to pay with money.
Not with this!
Why should I pay you money for that crap!
Take it!
Tell him to make some catfish soup next time!
- Huh?
- You're coming back?
What kind of people work here at this dirty rotten restaurant?
Goodbye!
Master!
What's up with that old man?
Master, don't think too much about it.
I'm sure that he's just senile.
But, that over there.
Can we try some?
- Delicious!
Better than the other restaurant on our street!
He's not REALLY going to prepare catfish soup right?
Master!
Tomorrow is Valentine's Day!
Would it not be a waste to let it pass by?
Who are you going to give it to?
Just, someone I'm grateful to.
But Jan Di.
Aren't you giving Jun Pyo sunbae any chocolates?
Chocolate?
Why did she talk about giving chocolate?
Why did you want to meet at a place like this?
What a bad choice in picking a place.
I asked you nicely to come out and meet,
so can't you just go along?
It's cold!
Let's go inside somewhere in the meantime.
- Follow me!
- Where are we going?
You want to drag me somewhere,
getting me in trouble again, aren't you?
Hey!
Where are you going?
It's fun and warm right?
The drinks are free here!
It wasn't made for a cheap customer like you.
The company's owner is lacking in good customer service.
I'm worried about the future of your company.
Hey, what's that?
This?
It's nothing.
Give it to me!
This is...
These are ones I messed up making it for someone else.
It doesn't look good, right?
But it tastes good.
I'm going to try one.
Hey!
They're all mine, don't touch it!
Yes, you've all waited long for this!
It is time for the Valentine's Day event!
We are starting right now!
Will all participants, please come forward now!
Yes, they must have been anticipating it,
everyone is running forward!
Here is the prize, we're giving away today!
Last call, last couple!
Here are they.
The economy must be really bad these days.
Many of you are coming forward
as soon as we announced it.
When I call to you,
please shout "Fighting".
- Number 1.
- Fighting!
- Number 2.
- Number 3.
- Fighting!
- Number 4.
- Number 5.
- Fighting!
- Number 6.
- Number 7.
- Fighting!
- Number 8.
- Number 9.
- Fighting!
The rules are simple.
Please put down your bags and purses first.
Either man or woman is OK.
Whichever couple can hold onto your partner the longest,
will be the winner.
Looks like all our couples are ready!
Get Ready!
One!Two!Three!
Yes, please begin to carry your partner!
This guy here, you need to bend down.
You're so stiff. Your hair is all wavy.
Gently. Hang on.
Yes, that's right!
As you hang on...
Ah oh my! Just lie down already!
Couple 1 is out!
Only been 2 seconds and your face already turn red!
Now, let's start the game for real.
Wow, looking good.
Hey there, you lose.
Come out.
Uh, you lose.
Don't lift your foot until I say so.
This couple is down.
57 minutes have passed.
Two teams are left!
Who do you think will win?
How long do you think you can last?
We will last till the very end!
I see. And how long do you think you will last?
Till we win.
Until it's done?
Can you say how long you can last again?
- Till we win!
- Wow, good.
The young man is very determined.
So let's ask for an encouraging message from the girlfriend.
Ah, I see. No message,
but just that you feel good!
Hey, Dry Cleaner.
This is really embarrassing.
If they find out the president's son is doing this,
it'll be a scandal on the news tomorrow.
Hey, be quiet. You'll lose your strength!
If you need a cell phone, then tell me.
I'll buy you one!
My goal is to get it with my own ability.
It isn't your ability, but mine!
With our last two teams.
Why don't we have them do a squat. Up and down!
Up and down!
Beads of sweat are forming on the young man's forehead.
Wow, very impressive.
The last team, who shall it be?
We're anticipating...
Oh! Oh my, finally she's fallen off!
Finally, we have a winner!
Wow!
I knew this team would win from the start.
When they join in.
How do you feel?
I feel very happy about it!
I get a cell phone now!
Congratulations!
Please give them a round of applause!
Congratulations. Good job!
Let go.
Let go!
Let go, I can walk by myself!
Ga Eul, why are you here?
That is... I just...
She must've come here to give you some chocolate.
Is today Valentine's Day?
Miss, your nose is red!
You must've waited a long time!
Ga Eul, why don't you have some tea before you go.
No, it's OK!
Don't be like that and come inside.
I'll go prepare some tea.
Leave yours over there, too.
I'll leave first.
Let go of me, please.
This is why I dislike innocence like you.
Ga Eul, listen carefully to what I have to say.
Acting is just acting.
If you take it seriously, then we have a problem.
I'll hang on to this until Ga Eul meet the one destined for you.
Thanks!
Anybody called for a substitute driver?
How did you know I was here?
Like I said, I came because
someone called for a driver.
Huh?
Jun Pyo called me.
Thank you.
I'm going.
Geum Jan Di.
If something ever happens, will you tell me?
Like what kind of happening?
Well, I hope you don't have to. But...
Hopefully nothing does happen.
It's not like Gu Jun Pyo and I are serious or anything.
Drive safely.
Geum Jan Di.
Don't worry about me!
Are you taking the helmet with you?
Huh?
I was just going to give it back to you!
Here.
Goodbye.
Her father's a dry cleaner?
Mother's working at a public bath?
Yes, that is correct.
How did a girl like that get into Shinhwa High School?
Does that make sense?
Who's responsible for this?
You were the one who admitted her.
What did you say?
Do you know why the media is dangerous?
Because they are ignorant!
Once they bite into something, they won't let go.
Can't get through to them by common sense or sound judgment.
I have to bring in one of their own to calm them down.
Why didn't you tell me about this earlier.
I thought the Young Master was just bullying the Young Miss as usual.
Young Miss! Who is a Young Miss here?
I apologize.
The Young Master would like to...
Don't bother that girl.
- What did you say?
- I said don't bother her!
I don't know what your talking about right now.
Ah! Are you talking about the girl we saw at the mall?
Do you think your mother is a person of leisure?
In my position, I have no time
to be concern about such trivial stuff.
The First Lady of Shinhwa Group!
If you say so, that's fine.
Get ready to leave.
I understand.
Like a ghost, I tell you.
You, where did you get that?
Don't know.
Where do you think I got it?
Hey! Don't eat that!
Ji Hoo.
Why do I feel uneasy?
I feel like something is going to happen to her.
What scares me most,
is that something bad could happen to her
and I won't know it.
Don't worry,
Geum Jan Di, you know she's not a weakling.
Don't be afraid either.
Behind you,
there will always be us.
The president of world class hotel chain La Vindor,
Mrs. Kang Hee Soo
has been elected as the president of the International Hotel Association.
Can you share your thoughts?
Until I become the best, I will never be satisfied.
Oh my, who is that?
Is that Jun Pyo's mother?
Shinhwa Group is definitely different, just as I'd thought.
Just look at that charisma.
What a heroine, a heroine.
Until I become the best, I will never be satisfied.
How is it? Was it alike?
We can be relatives through marriage.
- There might be a chance where I'll be like her.
- Just a little alike.
A little?
Is there somebody here?
- Older brother Jun Pyo?
- Young Master Jun Pyo?
Jun Pyo Son-in-law?
Older brother Jun Pyo?
She looks like someone I've seen before.
Just a minute ago, that woman on the TV news broadcast...
Until I become the best, I will never be...
Madame President!
Is somebody here?
You must be surprised
because I came over to meet you so suddenly.
No, not at all.
Young Master Jun Pyo... No,
Ah, thanks to your son, so we're used to it.
Jun Pyo has been here before?
Yes of course.
He didn't just come over.
He also spent the night here,
made Kim Jang, went to the bath...
I'll get straight to the point.
You're a busy person, so of course you should do that.
I believe that once a person is born,
there is a separate world that each person must deal with.
Jun Pyo is a child who must endure,
not only in the Republic of Korea nor in Asia,
but the whole entire world.
Of course.
Because Shinhwa Group is global!
And as a mother, I will do everything in my power
to ensure my son will be up to the task.
And in my duty as a mother.
Yes, of course you should.
If you were to raise Jan Di well...
Yes, as a mother as well, I will try my hardest
to raise Jan Di as a good match for Jun Pyo...
That's not what I meant.
But I am talking about the grass at a golf course.
Excuse me?
Do you know what is most important
when trying to grow good grass?
Food?
It's getting rid of the weeds.
It is very important to pull out by the roots
to get rid of the nasty weeds,
so it does not survive and
grow together with the grass.
By that, you mean...?
So are you saying our Jan Di is a weed?
It is a relief that you understand my meaning.
Normally, you spray strong pesticide first to get rid of the weeds,
but this time...
Section Chief Jung.
Yes, President.
300 million won = $220K
It is 300 million won.
Hundred million?
Hundred million...
If you need more, I can give it to you.
Because it is also our fault for not raising our children properly.
- Chief Jung
- Yes.
[I pledge on February 2, 2009 that I will end my relationship with Gu Jun Pyo.
And I will not meet him than otherwise stated.]
It is a contract stating that you won't meet
Young Master Jun Pyo ever again.
All you need to do is sign.
Excuse me.
Honey!
Mom!
Get out right now!
You just made a big mistake.
Whether it be a big mistake or a small one,
It's better than calling someone's child a weed in front of her parents.
Get out right now!
Can't you hear me?
Kang San, what are you doing?
Call the police immediately.
What are you doing, honey?
Throw that money bag away right this instant!
Alright.
You won't regret it?
I'm not generous enough to offer it twice.
Meeting a woman like you twice is what I'm going to refuse.
Let's go.
Mom...
Honey.
Where did you get all that courage?
Mom, I was so moved.
I've never been more proud of you like tonight.
Your pride is more important than money.
How can you just sell it off with...
What are you talking about?
How can pride be more important than your money?
Of course your money is more important.
In a capitalist society,
first is money, second is money,
and third is money as well.
Pride my ass.
Honey.
Then why did you do that before?
That woman was telling us to get lost
for just 300 million won.
Is she joking with someone?
Even a three year old in the Republic of Korea knows Shinhwa Group,
and they're just giving us 300 million?
Then?
Imagine you do end up marrying to Young Master Jun Pyo.
No matter how much longer that woman lives,
is she going to live 1,000 years or 10,000 years?
Then the whole fortune would go to her son,
and all that becomes yours.
How dare she offer just 300 million?
Mom.
What?
You get a grip of yourself.
Our goal is Shinhwa Distribution, Shinhwa Airlines,
Shinhwa Electronics,
Cement, and Automobiles!
What else is there?
- La Vindor.
- Of Course!
Make that hotel yours too.
Mom.
What?
Who knows, 20 years later you'll be in the news!
"There is no such thing as satisfaction
until you become the greatest."
Yeah, that line!
Leave it to my mom!
Honey.
I really didn't know you had such depth.
It's enough that you know now.
Do you know what is most important
when trying to grow good grass?
It is getting rid of the weeds.
It is very important to pull out by the roots
to get rid of the nasty weeds,
so it does not survive and
grow together with the grass.
Do you have concert tickets?
What are you doing here so late?
What about you?
I didn't hear that swimming has changed to a Winter Olympics sport now.
I just...
Because you were frustrated?
If you don't have tickets,
why don't you at least turn the pages for me?
I won't wear it home today.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Just...
Because I'm amazed.
At what?
That whenever an alarm rings in my heart,
Sunbae always appears in front of me.
An alarm?
Like when there's a fire?
Yes.
Then let me do it.
Do what?
Geum Jan Di's famous firefighter.
I'm indebted to you today again.
Go safely.
[Pick up the phone!]
Yeah, Mom.
What is it?
Don't cry and tell me slowly so that I can understand.
What?
Why are they suddenly telling you
to close up the dry cleaners business?
The owner's son, who has been without a job for 7 years,
will be hired at Shinhwa Electronics.
Realtor President Yoo said no one will lease us the space in this area.
If she had something against us,
she should have just talk to us personally.
But how can she stab us in the back so cruelly
taking away the means of our livelihood and survival?
She did come and talk to us.
But you poured salt all over her and chased her out.
So what are you going to do?
What do you want me to do?
What will our family of four going to do to eat and live?
- What is this?
- This is our first day,
so our future depends on how well we do.
What are you going to do? Start!
We have hot coffee! Hot coffee! Coffee!
Dad!
Squid! Dried squid!
What is that?
Shout it loudly like you normally do.
Squid has arrived!
Make your expression brighter.
Fresh squid on a crowded highway!
- I'll do it.
- Jan Di.
Rice crackers!
Rice crackers are here! Rice crackers!
- Go up to the driver and make him roll down the windows.
- You have to say how much they are.
- You can just tell them when they ask.
Quickly, let's do a fighting.
Aja aja fighting!
Squid is here!
Rice crackers!
It's 3,000 Won!
Rice crackers are 2,000 won.
2,000 Won!
Rice crackers are here..
Rice crackers...
Mom, what are you doing?
Rice crackers? Coming!
Rice, rice crackers...
Mom, I can't hear anything!
Give it to me.
Rice crackers! Rice! Rice! Rice crackers!
Do it.
Rice crackers... rice, rice, rice.
Do it a bit louder.
Rice crackers! Rice! Rice! Rice!
I got it.
Ahjumma, give us one rice cracker.
Aren't you going to give us one?
Mom! Rice crackers!
- Yes, it's 2,000 won.
- Here you go.
Thank you.
Rice crackers!
Why do I have to go there?
Just go on your own like usual?
What a nuisance.
I'm not the successor to Shinhwa Group. You are.
Why is there such a traffic jam?
Do we have to go this way?
Section Chief Jung, let's buy one of those.
Excuse me?
What do you call those round things
they're selling on the road?
Are you talking about rice crackers?
Yes, that's it.
Are you in your right mind?
President Kang is going to buy rice crackers from the side of the road?
Are you feeling sick?
Section Chief Jung.
Yes, President.
Excuse me!
Please give us one rice cracker.
Yes!
It's 2,000 won.
Thank you.
President, what shall I do with these?
The smell and the dust.
Really, selling food in such revolting conditions is beyond understanding.
Throw it away immediately.
Yes.
Miss, one coffee!
Miss!
Noona, what are you doing?
He's asking for a can coffee!
Yes, coffee!
Rice crackers...
2,000 won.
Stop the car.
- Just keep going.
- Stop the car.
There's no need to stop the car.
Can't you hear me telling you to stop the car?!
Gu Jun Pyo.
Geum Jan Di, stay still.
Please, stay still.
You're doing well, my daughter.
Why didn't you tell me?
If I told you,
you were going to pull out of bundle of cash and asked,
"How much do you need?"
If the Dry Cleaners went broke,
you guys can just set up another one.
It's embarrassing...!
You're right.
Sure, I'm...
No, our family must be embarrassing.
But I'm not sorry for any of it.
What I mean...
You and I dating is separate from the family.
And you can't have everything your way,
just because you're my boyfriend.
Then what do you want me to do?
You just want me to watch your whole family
selling rice crackers on the street?
Yeah.
Just watch.
What?
Don't do anything, just watch,
if you want to remain my boyfriend.
Hey, Dry Cleaner.
It's been a while since I've heard that.
But what should I do?
I'm not a dry cleaner's daughter anymore.
Geum Jan Di.
I'm not trying to scare you,
nor is there a reason for you to be afraid.
Just know this.
My mom, our evil witch, is capable of doing anything, anytime.
It seemed like it.
Promise me.
What?
That if something ever happens, you'd tell me.
OK.
One more.
That no matter what,
you won't run away from me.
I don't think I can promise you that.
What?
I feel like running away several times not because of your mother,
but because of you.
Hey!
I promise.
I'll promise that I won't let your mother become the reason.
It's a relief that you're Geum Jan Di.
What?
It's a relief that the commoner gangster Geum Jan Di is my girlfriend.
That promise really sets my heart at ease.
What is that?
Is it a compliment or an insult?
Do you want to drink this?
Hello?
I heard that you were looking for an overnight part timer...
Oh, I see.
I understand.
Pumpkin porridge is ready.
Yes.
Here is the pumpkin porridge you ordered.
Enjoy your meal.
It's super hot, so blow on it as you eat.
Miss, you're very friendly.
Please come often.
Our porridge is very good.
Oh, you've a very cute face.
Are you a college student?
No, I'm a high school student.
Ah, then it'll be a bit difficult.
What will be?
Our company uses a lot of student models,
and I liked your image a lot.
I see.
I was wondering,
how much money do you pay?
Oh my. Welcome gentlemen.
What can I get you?
Canned coffee or puffed snacks?
No, that's not right.
Seeing you guys, you came for the squid.
How many do you want?
Who give you permission to operate here?
Hey, guys!
Do it right!
Yes!
Do you really think that she'd do that?
It's bothering me.
Then you can check.
Let me borrow your phone.
Phone?
Why? Yours ran out of battery?
Hello?
Hello? Yi Jung Sunbae?
Yi Jung Sunbae?
Hello? Hello?
Yes, Miss Ga Eul.
Hi.
Yeah, yeah.
Hello.
How much do you need?
Fill it up, please.
How will you be paying?
Sunbae
I was getting really sleepy.
Thank you, Sunbae.
Aren't you overdoing it a bit?
Don't you know me?
It's me, me!
Republic of Korea's commoner representative, Geum Jan Di.
If you take away health and stubbornness, I'm just a corpse.
Lies.
What?
Your body's telling you that it's a lie.
I have a lot of tissues.
My heart hurts.
If I was Jun Pyo, then my heart would hurt a lot.
Please don't tell Gu Jun Pyo.
I want to carry my own share of responsibility.
Then I'll be able to hold my head up high.
I envy Jun Pyo.
I'm off.
Hey, Geum Kang San!
You're starving because you don't have any lunch money, right?
Geum Kang San is a bottomless pit,
so what will he do when he gets hungry?
What are they...?
Let's go.
Hey, Kang San.
Are you starving yourself?
No.
Tell me quickly.
Or else I'll go and find you at your school.
I just told them I wouldn't eat lunch,
because I didn't want to spend money.
My teacher was going to pay for me,
but I don't want that either.
Why'd you say that now?
In the morning, you deliver newspapers and milk.
In the afternoon, the porridge shop.
In the evening, the gas station.
How can I tell you?
I won't die by skipping one meal.
I'm off.
Hey.
Hey, Geum...!
He's so tiny to begin with...
My heart hurts.
Sorry.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Is there anybody here?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: fangel, Beeni
Spot Translators: saturn, froglivers
Timer: Zealousy
Editor/QC: jtranla
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
In the name of F4...
- I'm sorry.
- In the name of F4...
I'm sorry.
There is something that I must reveal to all of you.
What's wrong with you?
Not yet.
Really.
Good shot!
Hit it like this.
What are you doing?
Nice shot!
Really!
You!
You really wanna die?
Since early in the morning...
How should I do?
They're so good.
I'm sorry.
Really, I'm sorry.
Hey, listen to me!
It looked like the car was moving, right?
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get this for FREE @ d-addicts.com