Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Episode 23
Are you OK?
Yeah.
Even if you weren't OK, you wouldn't say so.
I'm really OK.
Just wait a little bit.
This time, I really...
even if I have to leave home,
I'm going to take care of you.
What's that supposed to mean?
The evil witch,
it's not her personality to do nothing.
She's definitely going to do something.
I'm just saying that I'm
preparing to do what I need to do.
Don't be like that.
What?
Whatever it is, it should be for your benefit.
I don't like you taking care of me.
Why don't you like that?
You're my woman so obviously,
I should take care of you.
Someone taking care of me, watching over me.
I don't like being dependent like that.
Even now, I've already received so much from you,
F4 sunbaes and Jae Kyung unni.
It may not be much but I want us to be equals,
with me pulling my own weight.
Do you know?
What?
That you don't have any cute side in you.
Hey...
What's the matter?
Chan, what's the matter?
Little kid, what's the matter?
What?!
Is this the time to be laughing?
You... that...
Wait, you have to wait.  Come here.
Chan, what is that?
Can you see that?
You can't see it, can you?
Hyung, put me on your shoulders.
What?
Your shoulders.
Having fun?
He's gonna fall off!
I definitely won't fall off!
They're really cute.
It must now be Spring.
The weather's letting up.
It's strange.
What is?
Right now, I feel as if I'm
in a scene from a half-remembered dream.
I'm just saying.
This little kid is very heavy.
Oh, Chief Jung.
Young Master.  You should return now.
Madam President is looking for you.
Go on!
Chan...
Happy birthday to you. Happy birthday to you.
Beloved Yi Jung, happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, Yi Jung!
Hurry up.  You're supposed to
blow out the candles and make a wish.
This is your present.
"One road, one chance"?
What's it supposed to mean?
In this world, the one and only destiny.
Ga Eul!
Yi Jung sunbae, I found it.
What?
I said I finally found it.
"I love you" / "Yi Jung"
That day, the sunrise was at 7.
The moment the sun rose was
the only time you could see it...
That message.
Idiot...
Even when you knew you were being an idiot.
Even when you knew that better than anyone!
If you set me this difficult question, what am I supposed to do?
Yi Jung!
I'd like it if you came.
The wind...
Once it leaves,
it can't return to that place again, Yi Jung.
Do it again!  Do it again!
I'm telling you to do it again!
Yesterday, there were many families
out enjoying the splendid weather.
In city zoo where flowers are starting to bloom
"Splendid spring weather, many family outings"
Sir, are you truly thinking of burying it like this?
Even though they make excuse that was by an insane follower,
No matter what,
it won't bring these two back to life.
I can't show Ji Hoo that the death of his father
and mother is used as a political warfare.
Sir.
All my life, I had no fear at
what I believe that is right.
However, even that was arrogance.
I realized it after what happened to them.
Because of my fear of losing you as well,
not being able to see you was my punishment.
As if your grandfather's mistake wasn't enough,
you carried that hurt and lived on.
Now, even if I die, I have no more wishes, child.
The foundation and the clinic.
Can I entrust them to you?
To cure heart by art, illness by medicine,
that was your mother and father's desire.
Grandfather, I'm not yet...
Come on over here!
The spicy fish stew is all done!
Oh, that girl's voice is quite loud.
Because of your voice,
I think that all the fish will scatter.
Ah, this girl!
Well then.
- Is it done cooking?
- Yes.
- Here.
- Well then.
Tada!
How is it?
Oh you!  So to not let the fish go to waste,
I'll eat it.
Ji Hoo, hurry.  Try some.
It's amazing, it actually tastes like your mother's.
OK, you two!  Look over here.
One!  Two!  Three!
I have good news and bad news.
Which do you want to hear first?
Ah, I know Ga Eul's style.
The bad one first?
There's a chance that
I won't be as good as before.
This hand...
I'm not sure whether God of pot will choose me one more time or not.
No, that won't happen.  It won't be like that.
But what exactly is the good news?
That, even still, I'm gonna keep doing it.
I'm not going to avoid it anymore.
Once one gives up, how much one regrets it...
Because of someone, I came to know it well.
Sunbae...
Ga Eul, do you want to try it once?
My wanting to hear the bad news first,
how did you know that?
Because all nice girls want happy endings.
I may definitely be a cool,
but I'm not a nice guy.
Throw away the delusion that
all nice girls want nice guys.
Ah, Mom.
What?
Is that true?
I understand.
I'll be right there.
I have worked with effort on it since I built the foundation.
A lot of people worked really hard.
Jan Di, take a look around.
Yes!
It's a great scale, isn't it?
Yes, it's very wide.
Oh, what is that, Grandfather?
Those are all meeting rooms.
Just a second, just a second.
Yes, it's me.
Wait, is that true?
But who exactly?
How did this happen?
No!
No matter what happens,
we must protect the foundation!
No!
Grandfather!  Grandfather!
Grandfather!
- Oh, Grandfather!
- Grandfather!
Grandfather!
Grandfather, your medicine, your medicine!
The medicine... medic...
Grandfather!
Grandfather...
Sunbae!
Hospital!  Hospital!
I said, hospital!
He didn't want you to know.
He said that if he was careful, he'd be fine.
Let's go and get Grandfather's things.
Are the preparations going well?
Madam President.
I do not know about other things, but
the Suwon Foundation, if you could reconsider...
I'm not doing it because I'm desirable for a foundation like that.
You know better than that.
What do you intend to do?
This time, I'll have to pull out the roots.
Fortunately, that young child
cherishes something more than money.
I have a proposal.
A proposal?
The broken engagement...
I feel bad about that.
However,
it's not as if things with
JK Group are completely over.
I'll do my best to do what I can.
Trust me on this.
So?
Whether you have me followed or locked up,
I'll accept everything.
Except...
Except?
Jan Di...
leave her alone.
If I don't do anything to Geum Jan Di,
will you be satisfied?
Yeah.
Then I'll promise.
I won't lift a finger against Geum Jan Di.
In return,
don't you forget what you just said.
Don't worry.
Now is not the time to play around like that.
Grandma?
Do you still not know your mother?
It's not time to feel at ease.
You can't even protect your woman.
So how will you carry the great Shinhwa Group?
I did not raise you to be such a pathetic man.
Just because you were born male
doesn't automatically make you a man.
Becoming stronger from losing,
yielding even though it is unfair,
running away even though it is shameful,
overcoming a weak self-confidence over time.
That's how one becomes a real man.
Do you know that?
Grandma!
Thank you.
Ji Hoo - first day of kindergarten
Ji Hoo - Entrance day of elementary school
Our Ji Hoo - day he became a college student
Ga Eul.
Didn't you say that your father
worked at his company for 20 years?
And it hasn't been that long since promotion to be general manager.
How can they suddenly order
just your father to retire...
Why did that happen?
Is that true?
She gave pressure to one of Shinhwa's subcontractor to fire Ga Eul's father.
Looks like it.
After the way the wedding turned out,
I thought she was being too quiet.
So then, Ji Hoo's situation is no joke either.
What about Ji Hoo?
President Kang seems to be making
a move against Ji Hoo's foundation.
What?
The opening of new art center built in Song Do city
Then...
All this is...?
Just her way of getting rid of Geum Jan Di.
Grandfather.
Jan Di, you came just in time.
Why?
Just now, did you want to see me?
This girl, what an assumption!
Jan Di, now that you're here,
take this boy out for a bit.
This pole-length boy stays by my side and won't budge.
Well, it's frustrating.
Why aren't you two leaving?
With the long-awaited spring weather...
These pathetic young people.
Aren't you going to leave already?
Let's go.
The opening of new art center built in Song Do city
Then...
Just her way of getting rid of Geum Jan Di.
The desire to protect something...
I never thought I'd have it.
But after meeting you,
it kept coming up, over and over.
Grandfather, the clinic.
The foundation.
And...
You.
Now that Sunbae has Grandfather with him,
it's really a relief.
Sunbae, you don't know, do you?
That you were always like the sunshine to me
Goodbye, Geum Jan Di's honorary firefighter.
A dandelion lives as a dandelion.
And a forget-me-not lives as a forget-me-not.
A plantain lives as a plantain.
A plantain that lives on the
rough earth can only grow toughly,
But on an oily earth, it grows in a
different style with deep meaning and sturdiness.
No matter what, I don't lose my
identity and I continue to live as a plantain.
I learn it there.
That I have to live like myself.
Mister.
I don't think I'll be able to come here anymore.
I wanted to see you get better.
And I had a lot of books
that I wanted to read to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm good at enduring hunger.
And I'm also good at withstanding the cold.
But there is one thing
that I absolutely cannot endure.
People that I love getting hurt because of me.
It isn't something that can
be solved by me trying my hardest.
Isn't it a bit unfair this time?
Mister, I'm not running away.
You know that, right, Mister?
You must get healthy even if I'm not around, okay?
President.
Geum Jan Di is here.
She came sooner than I thought.
Let her in.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Jan Di!
Are things going well?
Why are you here?
Is it okay if you just come like this?
If I don't die, I'll just keep pushing.
Geum Jan Di, fighting!
We're always at Jan Di's side.
Hello, senior!
Welcome, miss Geum Jan Di
Why are you like this?
I'm Geum Jan Di.
Senior's apprentice.
You are this household's guest now.
But what are you here for?
I'm here for Gu Jun Pyo…
Young Master Jun Pyo…
I'm here to meet Gu Jun Pyo.
Young Master is in his room.
Yes.
Jun Pyo, let's play!
Gu Jun Pyo, let's play!
Now I'm even hearing Geum Jan Di's voice.
Hey!
What's going on?
Gu Jun Pyo, let's play.
Gu Jun Pyo…
How did you get here?
Why are you here?
Did the witch do something again?
Is that it?
Gu Jun Pyo, let's play!
Did you eat something wrong?
What's wrong with you?
Gu Jun Pyo, let's go on a picnic.
Picnic.
It's a yearning heart, It's a yearning heart
Even if you're by my side, I still miss you
Hey, my girl
Like glass, it's an uneasy heart to me
It's a yearning heart, it's a yearning heart
Even if you're by my side, i still miss you
Hey, my girl
Like this, i want to place you in my embrace
Your smile that is like the sunshine
Your fragrance that is like the wind, your warm breath
Your bright eyes.. i like it
Intoxicated in an armful of happiness
Just in case this love will become a dream, or everything will disappear
I'll tightly hold your hand next to me
Stay by my side forever
It's a yearning heart, it's a yearning heart
Even if you're by my side, i still miss you
Hey, my girl
Like glass, it's an uneasy heart to me
It's a yearning heart, it's a yearning heart
Even if you're by my side, i still miss you
Hey, my girl
Like glass, it's an uneasy heart to me
Is today some special day?
Hm?
I don't know very well,
but don't people usually say that it feels
like their birthday or having won the lottery?
Are you that happy?
Yeah.
I wish every day was like this.
Think about it.
You come to me first asking for a date,
and we haven't fought a single time all day.
Yes, we have.
Since it has come to this,
can I ask you one more thing?
What is it?
How come you don't say that you like me?
I've said it to you… multiple times.
Must you hear it in words to know?
I want to hear it.
I want to hear what kind of person I am to you.
I like you.
No matter how hard I try not to like you,
no matter how hard I try to forget you,
my efforts are so fruitless
to the extent that I get angered by it.
Haven't you come here to say something to me?
Please leave them alone.
What?
My friend's family Ga Eul's family.
And Senior Ji Hoo's alter.
Please leave them alone.
On what conditions?
What will you give to me in return?
Unless it's a credible card,
I don't want to hear it.
I'll leave.
I'll leave Gu Jun Pyo.
I'll move my school and where I live,
and I'll leave to a place where
Gu Jun Pyo will never be able to find me.
Is that okay?
If you just keep that promise.
I will keep it.
Fine.
Then it seems the transaction is complete.
I'm not losing to you.
I'm not running away from you either.
You are the worst among all people I've met.
I'm leaving because I don't want
the people I love to be entangled with you,
and I have only one regret that I couldn't
save the person I love the most from you.
Gu Jun Pyo.
Hm?
Stop here.
Here? Why?
Just stop for me.
What's that bag for?
Are you going to give me
a surprise event or something?
Gu Jun Pyo.
I'm not going to see you anymore.
What?
Tonight's the last time I'm seeing you.
Hey, Geum Jan Di.
Were you saddened because
we didn't fight once today?
Even if you're joking,
why do you joke with something like that?
I'm not joking.
What's the reason?
Did the witch do something again?
I became determined.
To take you out of my life.
Geum Jan Di.
Thanks up until this time.
Farewell.
Why are you like this?
You told me you liked me.
You said so yourself with your very
own mouth just a little while ago, but why?
It's because of the witch, right?
I'm right, right?
No, it's because of me.
What?
I realized it this time.
That you and I are from different worlds.
We met through a fantasy like fate,
but now it's time that the both
of us return to our respectable worlds.
You're lying.
You're lying to me right now.
Tell me.
I'll solve it for you.
I'll protect you.
Don't go!
You told me you liked me.
Is your love like this?
Can you end it so easily like
this after you told me you liked me?
Perhaps my love was up to this point.
No matter how much I like you,
the extent that I could endure…
was perhaps just up to this point.
Perhaps it was to this point.
Tell me.
Setting Shinhwa and me being a plutocrat aside,
have you ever considered me as just one man?
No.
No matter how much you try,
you're still Shinhwa Group's Gu Jun Pyo.
I have never forgotten that
for not even a single second.
Even though i tell it not to go,
even though i tell it to stop
My heart keeps going towards you
Stop the car!
Jan Di!
Geum Jan Di!
It doesn't wear out, it doesn't decrease
Jan Di!
Why is my love like this
I'm telling you to stop the car!
Jan Di!
One by one, i count and count the memories
My heart can't rest for even a moment
It'll just become baggage that becomes hard to control
Jan Di!
Why can't i even throw them away
After I started to like you,
I've always wished it.
Really, my heart must have done something somehow
That you were a regular man with
no relation to Shinhwa or being a plutocrat.
I must have become a fool that's blind from love
Just one place, everyday one place
I'm sorry for not being able
to keep my promise, Gu Jun Pyo.
Looking at the sad light that is you
I'm really sorry.
Even the tear glands must be broken
My tears won't stop
Just one word.. the one phrase that you love
Can't you just tell me?
Even if i hold out my hands, no matter how much i call out
You're always far from me
It'll be a love that becomes painful scars
Why can't i erase it
Really, my heart must have done something somehow
I must have become a fool that's blind from love
Just one place, everyday one place
Looking at the sad light that is you
Even the tear glands must be broken
My tears won't stop
Jan Di.
Grandpa's here. Where are you?
Where is this rascal?
I try to comfort myself with the lie that i'm happy if you just smile
Because the place you're going towards is not me
I apologize for leaving like this.
The lonely tears flow
I was indebted to your for a long time
I won't forget it
Please be healthy.
I must have gone crazy over this hard love
Can't have you, can't forget you
Waiting for you day by day
I must have gotten ill from missing you so much
From loving you too much
Just one thing.. your heart, that one thing
Can't you just share it with me
Can't you love me?
I'm telling you that it's real.
Why don't you believe me?
She's starting again.
Why are you here like this if
you have your plutocrat in-law's house?
And is it even a normal plutocrat?
Shinhwa Group!
Then my daughter in law's
Jun Sul Group's daughter.
My daughter goes to Shinhwa High School!
I even made food for Shinhwa Group's Gu Jun Pyo.
Why can't you believe me?
Okay. We understand.
Then go to your in law and
tell him to pay your debts for you.
Then no one will know what will happen to you.
Welcome.
What should I give you?
Give me one of these.
Here you go.
Who is that?
They came down around the same time you came down.
They say he's some company's president.
M…. M… anyway.
They say he went bankrupt because of being eaten by a big company.
He got divorced and got
all his children taken away.
He was crippled.
What can we do?
Seeing that he's wandering around like this,
I'm guessing that he's
being chased by loan sharks.
What a pity.
Think about yourself.
Are you in the position to worry about others?
That's true.
Isn't that Jan Di?
Oh my.
Jan Di!
Mom!
How did you get here?
I came because I wanted to see you.
Is she the daughter that you were talking about?
Yeah. She's the girl.
Wanna see?
Look at this. Look at this.
Shinhwa High School's uniform!
Oh my, oh my. It must be true
that she goes to Shinhwa High School.
Yeah!
Jan Di, let's go and talk.
Watch my shop for me.
Okay, go on.
Don't worry about it.
Watch after it for me!
How did you get here, Jan Di?
She overflows a noble figure.
What?
Dad is on a boat?
Then what can we do?
The debts keep rising.
And we need to send Kang San to school.
And it looks like we can't
even feed our family of three.
Then how come you didn't tell me?
So what if I tell you?
You'll only get upset.
I would've quit school
or gotten a job at the least.
That's why I didn't tell you
because I was afraid you'd do that.
You need to graduate from Shinhwa
High School and go to Shinhwa college,
so that you can marry Young
Master Jun Pyo or some other plutocrat,
and then we'll have a way for our family to live.
That's our lifeline.
Mom, does that make any sense at all?
Why did you come down here
all of a sudden and not go to school?
I came because I wanted to see you.
Mom, Dad, San.
Darling, our daughter Jan Di's here!
You're doing well, right?
Dad!
I'm here!
You're doing well, right?
Please take care of yourself!
Dad!
Dad…
Any news of Jan Di?
Have you heard any?
Not really.
I've searched everywhere,
and it's not easy as you think.
She hid herself somewhere.
I think it's the first time
that Jun Pyo's been down like this.
He wasn't this bad in Macao either.
You're right.
It seems like he's holding a time bomb
and teetering that I can't bear to look at him.
Ji Hoo's strange as well.
Isn't he doing well with his grandpa?
Do you think it's normal for Ji Hoo to take management lesson and commute to the clinic?
I'm more worried about the rascal that just
slept or played instruments more than Jun Pyo.
You're right.
Anyway, you're amazing Geum Jan Di.
She disappeared after plunging
the great F4 into bewilderment.
Yes, Grandpa, it's me.
Yes, I'll go get you right now.
What should I do?
Jan Di came down after such a long time,
and all I have for side dishes is this.
What about the side dishes?
I'm dying of happiness to just eat food with you.
How long are you going to stay?
I wish that you'd stay for a long time.
I'm going to stay here for a while.
Stay for a while? You have to go to school.
Don't worry about the family
and just do what you have to do.
Are you there, Kang San's family?
Who is it?
We're here.
What's going on?
She's full of a noble figure
She really must be a plutocrat's daughter in law.
They say that only wealthy
people go to Shinhwa high school.
Then you must be friends
with all those rich kids, right?
She said that she is dating
with Shinhwa group's inheritor!
I never dreamed that I would meet Shinhwa group's
in laws while living in the countryside like this.
Of course, of course.
Eat this.
And you can pay back the money slowly.
Oh my, really?
Of course.
Okay.
Accept it.
Accept this too.
This too.
There's more here.
What is all this in the middle of the night?
Oppa.
Today you ask me about my welfare as if it's so normal
I just said that i was okay
You really don't know me at all
Without you, do you really think i'd be okay?
Are you okay without me?
-You got it!
-I got it!
Got it!
Because the world without you is so hard
I resent myself who's breathing
What do i do?
Still, i live in the day that breaks apart at your one word
You said that you liked me.
Is your love like this?
Can you end it so easily like
this after you told me you liked me?
Perhaps my love was up to this point.
No matter how much I like you,
the extent that I could endure…
was perhaps just up to this point.
What on earth is he doing?
Young Master, why are you like this?
How can he mess up someone else's machine?
Don't touch me!
How come you don't say that you like me?
Must you hear it in words to know?
I want to hear it.
I want to hear what kind of person I am to you.
I like you.
No matter how hard I try not to like you,
no matter how hard I try to forget you,
my efforts are so fruitless
to the extent that I get angered by it.
Jun Pyo.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: Javafiend, Beeni
Spot Translator: saturn
Timer: julier
Editor/QC: sayroo
Lyrics Translation: crazykyootie@soompi
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
To the person you love…
Can you send her?
What are you going to send to the person you love?
I'm sorry.
Can you send her?
Hyung, stop joking around.
- Ji Hoo, kiss him!
- Go away!
I don't want to!
The shock must've been big on him.
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey Jihoo, he was hit!
Do you think that makes any sense?
The monkey that asked Jan Di to be her bridesmaid…
I'm sorry.
It keeps hitting me.
Wow!
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream
this episode using our English subtitles.
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!!!
Get it for FREE @ D-addicts.com