Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.
Episode 9
You're being so noisy!
Be quiet!
- This tastes really good.
- Just put it there.
Butler Lee...
Why is it so loud?
It's about time for him to wake up!
What do I do?
Butler Lee!
Dad!
You're being so noisy!
Be quiet!
Did you sleep well?
There's nothing much on the table,
but I hope you eat a lot, Son-in-law!
Eat quickly... while it's hot.
Honey, steamed rib.
Oh, yes, yes.
You need to eat this, too.
I cooked it for long time, so it became tender.
It tastes very good.
Why...
Are you okay?
Son-in-law, here!
Brother-in-law, can't you just live with us from now on?
This kid!
We don't even have these kinds of food on holidays!
I've never seen a food table like this in our house!
Where's Jun Pyo?
He's still sleeping.
Tell him to come down.
Leave him alone.
He was with his F4 friends until it became late.
I can't believe he's still hanging out
with those kids at this kind of time.
What's wrong with those kids?
Don't you know how great it is
that Jun Pyo has friends like them?
For a Shinhwa Group heir,
friends shouldn't be, and aren't needed.
Mom.
No one will dare to compete with him,
and he should be cold enough
to cut even his family if he needed to.
Have you still not understood that?
I think it'd be better to sleep,
instead of trying to understand that.
Are you saying that,
there are not even a few times
that I eat breakfast with you like this?
Well, is that really our fault?
Bring him here.
Never mind.
I'll go.
Gu Jun Pyo! I'm going in.
Where is this child?
I'm asking you why I don't see Jun Pyo!
Kimjang?
Kimjang means cooking a lot of kimchi for winter
You're saying the four of you are going to eat all of this?
It's not like all you eat is kimchi.
No, Hyung!
That's all we eat,kimchi!
Prices have been rising, so this is actually
less than how much we used to make before.
Come on, let's get ready.
Let's get ready!
Okay, I'm starting!
Oh, how great it feels!
Hey, is it fun?
Here, I brought it.
Honey, bring the salted seafoods too.
More, more.
Honey, is this the salted seafoods?
Yeah.
Do you want me to do it?
Here, Son-in-law!
Here, here!
Honey, we're here!
Be quiet!
Honey, our son-in-law has sensitive skin,
so you can't be too harsh on him, okay?
Don't worry!
Son-in-law!
I'll prepare a cold glass of coffee milk, okay?
Get clean!
One... two... three!
It's fish cake!
Miss, give us six!
Two for each.
Here!
It's good.
Of course it's good!
This is really good, really!
I can eat more, right?
Of course, eat as much as you want!
As much as you want, as much as you want.
What's wrong with that kid?
Did he eat something weird at Geum Jan Di's house?
Jun Pyo, did you really go to Geum Jan Di's house yesterday?
You guys, have you ever made kimchi before?
What?
No, right?
Then did you ever wash at the public bath?
What are you talking about?
You never even ate fish cakes at a food stand either, right?
Do you guys even know about life?
It was better when he used to get his sayings wrong.
I'm scared of Geum Jan Di more than tiger or smallpox.
In Korean fairy tales, tiger and smallpox are the most scary things.
Sunbae!
It seems like you have a lot of worries these days.
It is because of Jun Pyo?
You're going to catch a cold.
It's okay.
Thank you.
This is really warm.
Can I give you a piece of advice?
Huh?
Don't try to avoid.
Sunbae...
Who was it that told me that avoidance is a cowardly thing to do?
Don't avoid, but give him a chance.
Honestly, I don't like being in Gu Jun Pyo's world.
Jun Pyo's world... Jan Di's world.
There's no such thing.
Just like you and I are in the same world right now.
If you don't like his world,
then you can bring him to yours.
Isn't that Geum Jan Di's major?
I'll try to follow your advice.
Thanks, Sunbae.
See you again.
Don't be like that, and just call her first.
Think well.
You're agreeing to be her slave if you call her first.
I'm not going to call.
Just watch if I even move a finger until she says to meet first.
That's right.
Good job, Gu Jun Pyo!
That's the first amendment of the guide
to being a player, pushing and pulling.
How can you say something like that while watching him?
He's going crazy for the withdrawal symptoms of Gum Jan Di.
She's calling.
Be calm!
Act as if you don't care.
You know, right?
Hello.
Geum Jan Di?
Who's that?
That's just going a bit overboard.
A bit?
You mean a lot.
Oh! Oh, I remember!
What's up with you?
Do you think this Gu Jun Pyo is always free of time?
I'm so busy, that I didn't even know that you didn't call
for three days and thirteen hours.
Hey man... woh, woh.
It's embarrassing that he's my friend.
What?
Who do you think I am?
Why would I go anywhere with people I don't know?
I'm not going!
I'm hanging up!
Did you see that?
Did you?
You saw me yelling at her, right?
I even hung up on her first.
But why were you yelling?
She was saying to go on a double date or something like that.
Double date? With who?
You mean... Ga Eul?
That's quite a feat, for that girl.
Jun Pyo, you're not going to go?
A date is something that two people do.
How old fashioned.
She said to meet in front of a hamburger shop.
Then maybe I should go there instead.
What?
Why would you go there?
Well... I want to see how commoners date.
That sounds like fun.
Shut up!
Come to the shooting range by ten tomorrow.
You got that?
There's no way he's going to come.
He was yelling on the phone.
Then why are you waiting?
Who's waiting?
I mean, I'm just curious about your boyfriend.
That's why I'm waiting.
Hey, who's that?
Are you Geum Jan Di?
Gu Jun Pyo?
What a coincidence!
A coincidence...?
I was just passing by,
and saw an old-fashioned girl like
you shivering in the cold,
so I called your name just in case.
Oh, really?
Then just go where you were going.
I was waiting for Ga Eul's boyfriend.
Why are you waiting for someone else's boyfriend?
Just go where you were going.
Don't scratch me.
I'm done with what I was doing.
Want me to stay with you?
What?
Do you want to be the third wheel
with another couple and cause them harm?
Harm...?
I'm being nice!
I'll stay with you.
That's good, Jan Di.
For some reason, I have a bad feeling about this.
Why isn't he showing up?
He's already thirty minutes late.
His manner is...
Sorry, I'll try to call him.
Call him fast!
I lost money, and got ditched...
Gu Jun Pyo's just not a help in life.
Ah, it's cold.
If I knew it'd be like this, I would've just played squash.
How did you know that Gu Jun Pyo wouldn't come?
Today, I'm paying for everything.
Hey!
Why were you so late?
Hi!
Banga banga~
I'm Gong Su Pyo.
Hello, I'm Geum Jan Di, Ga Eul's friend.
And this is Gu Jun Pyo.
Wow, your hair!
What shop do you go to?
Your hair's just like a conch horn.
If I put this up on a blog, I think it'd be a great hit!
What?
Oppa...
Now that I look at it, Su Pyo, Jun Pyo.
It's like we're brothers!
Call me hyung.
Dongseng, let's be friends!
Dongseng means a younger brother or sister.
What kind of guy is that?
He doesn't even say sorry that he's late
and what, a conch horn...?
That kid!
Gu Jun Pyo!
Sorry...
Do you want to just... go?
We can just go if you want.
Let's just do that.
No, let's just try going on that...
commoners date, or whatever.
Do you want one?
Thank you.
Don't just get that from him!
Hey, look at this!
What kind of place is this?
Jun Pyo dongseng, is it the first time for you?
You never ate gopchang before?
Gopchang?
A cow or pig's intestines!
Intestines?!
You don't know large intestine, small intestine?
What, Jun Pyo dongseng!
You're just a boaster?
Jan Di, I think you should think again.
How are you going to trust your life
with a guy who can't even eat gopchang?
What?
Oh, that looks good!
You guys should eat a lot.
You should try some.
If you chew well, then it's pretty good.
It looks like you can't eat this.
Don't go over your limits and just quit.
We can't eat it because we can't afford it!
Who says I'm not going to eat it?
Are you okay?
What else can I be?
Are you really... okay?
I don't think so!
I'm warning you...
You better be careful.
You don't know that a fly should be scared of a snake.
What?
Jun Pyo dongseng!
Do you mean that a one-day puppy
should be scared of a tiger?
Dongseng, you're so funny!
I heard you guys go to Shinhwa High School.
I guess you really do pay to get in there.
How much does it have to be, if you're like this?
Gu Jun Pyo...
It's so pretty.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
It's my first time being at a place like this.
It feels like we're inside a fairy tale book.
Are you some Little Match Girl or something?
Why don't you have gloves on?
I do have gloves!
Come here.
Let's go together next time.
Where?
Champs Elysees
Jun Pyo dongseng.
How about we get the girls a cup of warm coffee?
It's okay for me.
Let's go.
Oh, yeah.
Me?
I'm at the ice skating rink.
I'm sorry.
Because of Su Pyo oppa...
Oh, no.
It doesn't seem like he's a bad person.
Although it feels risky, I think we fulfilled our purpose.
Right?
Purpose?
Look at Jun Pyo sunbae,
trying his best to match up to you.
I was actually touched.
It does feel like he's trying.
Yeah, I feel like I can trust him now.
But why are they taking so long?
Let's go find them.
Gu Jun Pyo!
Oppa!
What are you doing?
Why are you punching him?
What's wrong with you?!
Do I need a reason to hit someone like him?
Hey!
You.
If you're going to find a guy, get someone right.
Don't you dare go like that!
Apologize.
If you just go like this, we're done.
Jan Di...
Apologize.
Hey!
Gu Jun Pyo!
What happened?
I don't know, either!
I said let's stay friends, and he just started punching me!
If he was going to say no, he could've just said it.
This is definitely going to last eight weeks.
I'm sorry.
I'll apologize in his place.
Can we get this and that?
I can't contact him.
And he just ignores my text messages.
I'm sorry, Ga Eul.
I really have nothing to say.
I'll tell Gu Jun Pyo...
No, I don't think Jun Pyo sunbae
would've done something like that without a reason.
What do you mean?
That day, oppa made a lot of mistakes,
but Jun Pyo sunbae kept trying to keep his anger in.
There must have been a reason.
What reason?
Have you ever seen that kid act reasonably?
He always wants everything his way.
That kid, he'll do that and more.
Just wait.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to get it out of him.
An apology.
Geum Jan Di.
What are you here for?
Please tell him that I’m here
because I have something to tell him.
He’s right next to you.
That’s what she said to deliver to you.
Tell her that I don’t have anything to say,
so she can do whatever she wants.
That’s what he said to deliver to you.
Would you please ask what country’s law it is
to beat someone up for no reason and not apologize?
Hey. Did you do something big again?
She’s asking you what country’s law it is.
Tell her that it’s a waste
to even use your fist on that kind of guy.
He’s saying that it’s a waste.
Really… until when do I have to keep doing this?
Hey, what’s up with you guys?
Please deliver this very well to him
that this is my last warning.
Thanks to his high and almighty punch,
my friend is crying.
That if he doesn’t apologize, then it’s really over.
She should be thanking me
for getting rid of a piece of trash for her,
but an apology?
Tell her that I can’t do it even if I die,
so tell her to do what she wants.
Jun Pyo.
Alright, I understand Jun Pyo.
Hey, this suits you well.
It was a bit of a stretch for me to expect
that you would fit to someone’s tastes willingly.
But I don’t understand why innocent Ga Eul
needs to face the consequences of your actions.
Gu Jun Pyo, don’t act like you know me from now on.
Geum Jan Di.
Hey, why are you guys like this?
I apologize.
Goodbye.
Hey, aren’t you going to go out?
You’re going to just let her go?
What’d you do this time?
See? I told you you’d get a cold.
How did you know?
You swim when you feel distressed.
Something distressful happened.
So… she’ll be at the swimming pool.
Is it that hard?
If you’re going to talk about Gu Jun Pyo,
I’m not going to talk about it.
Did I ever say that I was going to talk about Jun Pyo?
If he did something wrong to me,
then it’s done and over with after he yells at me once,
but because of Ga Eul, I can’t.
She did it to try to help us.
We’re talking about Jun Pyo right now, right?
Can you answer me?
Anyways! I can’t forgive him easily this time.
If things end for Ga Eul,
how can I go out with Gu Jun Pyo?
You said you weren’t going to talk about him,
but you keep doing it.
I was hoping that you wouldn't need it, but you would.
If you don’t dry your hair after you swim,
you’ll catch a cold.
Someone I know is doing that every single day these days.
So…
See?
Sunbae.
Aren’t you thankful?
Then I’ll just say one thing.
A guy doesn't do anything 'just'
in front of the girl that he likes.
There is always a reason.
Huh?
I’m saying this out of experience,
so it’s okay if you believe it.
I’ll be going.
Come on.
Jan Di, I’m scared.
You’re just going to keep waiting for a guy
who hasn’t called you in several days?
Come on.
Didn’t you say that the club Kong Su Pyo
worked at was in this area?
Let’s go.
Oppa.
You know the high school chick
that I was seeing for just fun?
I went out on a double date with her,
And the guy who came out along with her
was a total plutocrat.
Plutocrat?
You should have introduced him to me.
Hey, forget it.
I think he has a lot of money,
but his taste in girls is terrible.
The girl didn’t look like a high schooler
and had the body of an elementary student.
Do you know how shabby they looked too?
They’re both waitresses.
Waitresses? Which club?
Not that, they work part time at a porridge shop.
What?
But her girlfriend is a plutocrat?
Is she that pretty?
Pretty my ass.
So when I told him that I’d introduce him to a hot girl like you,
he threw a fist out of nowhere.
Oh, hey.
Me?
I’m at the skating rink.
What do you mean, why?
I’m a little busy playing with a couple of tacky kids.
What?
Really?
Okay, I got it.
Wait for me.
Jun Pyo dongseng.
Let’s talk about this truthfully as guys.
That Jan Di or Jab Cho?
Jab Cho means weed
Isn’t she not the girl?
Is she blackmailing you or something?
What?
Maybe Miss Weed has a bit of money?
Seeing you, I think you’re more at loss.
What are you talking about?
Why don’t we finish things up here and go to a club?
If we go there, we can meet hot chicks
that don’t even compare those reeking…
What’s up with you?
If you call my girlfriend Jab Cho,
I'll make sure that you won't be able to eat intestines
with that mouth ever again.
Got it?
Is what you said right now true, Kong Su Pyo?
You guys…
I’m asking you if it’s true.
What are you going to do if it’s true?
Oppa, who are they?
Do you know them?
Do you think I’d know them at my level?
Oppa…
What is the reason why you didn’t contact Ga Eul?
Reason?
Do you guys always have to get hit
in order to know whether something is poop or bean paste?
This works out well.
Hey, tacky girl.
Send those texts reasonably.
Are you a stalker?
Because of you, my inbox is full that it’s a nuisance.
Hey!
You!
One is for Ga Eul,
and the other is for my boyfriend.
If you ever appear in front of Ga Eul, you’re dead.
Understand?
What are you?
Go home!
What kind of guy is that?
But it’s a relief.
You found out that Jun Pyo sunbae isn’t a bad person.
Ga Eul.
I’m okay.
Really.
Jan Di, go ahead.
Where?
You have to go apologize to Jun Pyo sunbae.
That… just…
Tell him you’re sorry quickly.
That way, I think I’ll feel at rest too.
You’ll be fine by yourself?
Of course.
Don’t worry about me.
Go quickly.
I’ll call you.
I’m begging you to give up now. Please.
That threat about you taking medication…
Meaning committing suicide
Am I next after father?
Your lips...
Your lipstick smudged.
Thank you.
You’re the fourth.
Excuse me?
You’re his fourth girlfriend this year.
I think you’re too beautiful to be that.
Stop the car.
Aren’t you past the age to cry in the middle of the street?
Some women are mistaken
when they think they look pretty when they cry.
But it’s really not true.
Miss Ga Eul.
It’s not me.
Miss Ga Eul!
Two pairs.
Really?
What is this?
Nothing’s working out for me.
You didn’t settle things with Jan Di yet?
Settle?
See if blink even one eye
even if she begs at my feet for four days and three nights.
Let’s just hear what happened.
I don’t think you did anything right either.
What do you mean I didn’t do anything right?
I went out on a double or triple with them,
I ate intestines or gopchang with them,
I even exterminated a guy as harmful as rice insect.
All I did were good deeds.
Then you won’t be meeting with Geum Jan Di either, then.
So I’m saying that I won’t overlook it easily this time.
I don’t think it’ll work, Geum Jan Di.
I think you’ll just have to leave.
Hey.
When did you get here?
I didn’t know that you were that mad.
I think I only thought about myself.
Sorry.
I’ll be going.
Where are you going?
If you came, you have to at least tell me why you’re here.
You think this place is a place
where you can just come and go as you wish?
Gu Jun Pyo.
Please accept my apology.
Apple and apology in hangul sound the same.
If everything is relieved just with an apology,
then why are there laws…
and why are there police.
You know very well.
So what do you want me to do?
Three wishes.
Three wishes?
If you do them for me, then I’ll accept it.
Why three-
Why do you have three wishes?
Hey guys.
Don’t you think she’s big at fault because
she can’t even see Gu Jun Pyo’s good intentions?
Pretty big.
Alright. I’ll do whatever you ask me to do.
Instead, you have to tell me all three of them in one minute.
Start!
What kind of rule is that?
It’s right here. What do you mean, "what"?
10, 11, 12, 13,
-14, 15, 16, 17, 18,
- Hey, stop that!
19. 20.
Stop!
21.
25.
Sit down for now.
26.
27.
Stop!
28, 29, 30.
Stand up.
Hey, you have one wish left.
50!
51.
52, 53.
54, 55.
Stop!
Say, "Oppa... I’m sowwy."
Didn’t you hear me?
"Oppa! I’m sowwy."
Try it.
Gu Jun Pyo.
Hey, didn’t you see Ga Eul doing it?
Now, repeat after me.
"Oppa, I’m sowwy."
I can’t do it!
I won’t do it!
You do what you want. Accept it or don’t.
I can’t do it.
Hey, Geum Jan Di!
Where are you going?!
You should’ve accepted her apology when she did.
Give it to me.
Hey!
Why are you eating this!
I accepted an apology.
That rascal looks a pretty weak, right?
It’s stronger than it looks.
How long do you think it took to make him strong like this?
It got rolled, stepped on, and cut on.
It has to endure a heat of 1300 degrees.
But that’s not the end of it.
If it doesn’t become yours even after all of that hardship,
then you have to give up on it cleanly.
Like this.
In order to get stronger,
and in order to find something that is truly yours,
I’m saying that there are steps that you must pass.
Like what you experienced today.
I think I know what you’re talking about.
Thank you.
Then shall we start going out?
Where?
I’m not having that much of a great diagnosis either.
In these types of cases,
you need to relieve it so there are no side symptoms.
Let’s go.
Who is that guy?
Oh my. It’s So Yi Jung.
F4 doesn’t come to places like this.
What’s the occasion?
He’s really glowing in real life.
F4?
What is that?
Haven’t you even heard of the pretty boy prince group F4?
Excuse me…
Me?
Yes, please talk.
May I play a song?
Play?
Please head on up.
You can play all night long if you wish.
Thank you.
There is someone who has taken away
my whole heart here tonight.
I’ll play my heart for that person.
I apologized enough already.
Why did he chase me all the way home and call me out?
That Gu Jun Pyo.
Gu Jun Pyo.
You think I’ll be like,
"Oppa, I’m sowwy" even after this?
Why would I…
You…
Again, again.
You get moved by such trivial things.
Gu Jun Pyo.
How’d you do all this?
I just decorated it using chandelier decorations.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
It’s pretty.
It’s really pretty.
It’s like Christmas.
What’s so good about Christmas?
You don’t like Christmas?
You feel happy just by thinking about it.
I don’t have any memories liking Christmas.
Why?
Look out the window,
White snow is falling.
Winter has come.
Little children riding sleds
don’t know that the sun is setting,
and they ride their sleds excitedly on the snowy hills.
The long long sunset
When the darkness comes,
Colorful and gilttering
Streets are full of Christmas spirit
I see.
Hey, Geum Jan Di.
Did the Kim Jang that I made ripen?
If someone hears, they’d probably think
that you made all of our Kim Jang.
I want to eat it.
Really?
Yeah.
I want to eat the fish that your mom picks out for me too.
The oden that your dad bought me was really good too.
I…
didn’t know what a family was,
but seeing your family,
I think I understand a little now.
Can I go over again?
Did you ever ask permission in the past?
I’m not joking.
I want to go.
In actuality...
every day.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Main Translators: xdaisiesx3, Beeni
Spot Translator: saturn
Timer: xCHELLy
Editor/QC: liezle
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Please do NOT hardsub and/or stream this
episode using our English subtitles.