Boys Before Flowers
Episode 1
Why?
Why is this so?
Why are so many things branded in school?
Why Franck Muller? Why Louis Vuitton?
Why Omega? Why Chanel?
Why is it that even the students have chauffeurs?
It's so ridiculous!
I'm tired of the seeing the same thing for past two years.
Eitoku Gakuen is a school for the rich.
A private school which provides Kindergarten...
to High School education for the rich.
Amazing!
Where did you buy this handphone accessory from?
- Vegas
Took me a lot of effort to buy it since it was only limited edition.
I wish I was there.
What a pity.
Looking at them,
I really don't know what they come to school for.
Ever since I, a commoner, entered this high school...
my life has been a very eventful one.
The Red Paper!
Kimoto Takayuki of 2A has been given the red paper!
Homeroom will now end.
We must now catch Kimoto.
Yea! Great!
Let go off me!
Sigh...
Are you Makino?
I'm not sure myself, but can we really not follow?
This transfer student who doesn't know a thing,
she will definitely regret coming to this horrible school.
What's up with everyone?
What is the "Red Paper"?
That would be F4's declaration of war.
F4?
They are 4 Year 3 students called "Flower 4",
which eventually shortened to F4.
Should anyone piss them off, that person will get the Red Paper.
And he will be completely bullied by the rest of the school.
Why does everyone listen to F4?
Those guys are the sons of extremely rich families.
Aren't everyone in this school likewise?
The difference is great.
The school gets large sums of donations from their parents,
hence even the teachers fear them,
and privately agreed to allow them a free reign in school.
It's F4!
That is why you never see them in school uniform.
F4... F4... F4...
The members of F4 are...
Mimasaka Akira...
He likes to hit on married women 10 years older than him.
His father also loves women,
and is the boss of the underground world.
Nishikado Sojiro...
He inherited the family tea business, and likes women as well.
Hanazawa Rui...
His father is the President of a huge corporation.
His constant state of depression has always been a mystery.
And finally, Domyoji Tsukasa.
The son of the world famous Domyoji plutocrat.
(Plutocrat: A wealthy class that controls a government)
He is the leader of F4, and also the dictator of this school.
Domyoji is Kimoto's friend.
Don't leave... Don't leave...
Let's play.
Go ahead!
I've said before that it will be like this.
Sigh. Didn't expect it.
Don't be a chicken and frightened.
We'd expect nothing less from Domyoji, such cool moves...
I really hate people who like to talk a lot.
This is just a waste of my time.
Alright. The match has ended.
That was great!
Have they all lost their minds? What F4?
Those crazy idiots, taking a mad game like this so far.
They're so apathetic about their own friends getting beaten up.
This is unbelievable.
This is unbelievable!!
Yes...
Only half a year to go, might as well endure it.
Sometimes I hate life.
If only this period of time would peacefully pass.
That is my only wish,
but even so...
Hana Yori Dango - The Flower Boy
Episode 1
[Character] ** [Actor]
Makino Tsukushi ** Inoue Mao
Domyoji Tsukasa ** Matsumoto Jun
Hanazawa Rui ** Oguri Shun
Nishikado Sojiro ** Matsuda Shota
Mimasaka Akira ** Abe Tsuyoshi
Eh... The Red Paper appeared again.
What on earth did that guy do wrong?
When he was eating an orange, the juice squirted out.
What?
The orange juice squirted into Domyoji's eye.
Huh?
The Flower 4 is as precious as flowers,
that is why...
No one had the guts to say anything,
so he was beaten up by the 4 of them.
From what it seems,
you might get beaten up as well if you say those things in school.
Mm.
Yuki, have this.
Why don't you eat it instead? It's almost expiring.
- It's okay.
You seem to take it very well.
But I've upset my stomach before.
I'm not talking about that.
Hmm?
Strange that you didn't do anything about those apathetic people.
When I was younger,
Tsukushi-chan would protect me if I was bullied.
Even during Kindergarten...
Primary school...
And Secondary school...
But now no one in Eitoku Gakuen knows about that side of you.
I definitely feel like brutally hitting them,
and kicking them out of Eitoku Gakuen.
But...
Mom! You put eggs in the rice cooker?
It's okay, you need the heat to cook eggs anyway.
Here you go!
Yes.
Ah. Yes. Tsukushi.
From tomorrow onwards, you will bring this lunch box set to school.
I only took it out after you graduated.
But... Using those kind of lunch boxes will be a little...
This was a gift from grandma when I got married.
Oh, what a pretty wedding dress.
Of course. I'll treat you your favourite prawns tomorrow.
Why spend so much at one go?
Hey, dinner time!
Coming.
That's about enough for today.
There's still 3 days worth left.
Dad. Didn't you agree to only drink a bottle a week?
Alright. I want to challenge myself.
A bottle in 10 days!
That's great.
Well then, I want to aim for the Middle-High School
with the lowest fees in Japan.
Great!
Well, you really don't have to go to that extent
for me to attend Eitoku Gakuen.
No. That's the fun we get out of saving money.
Everyone's so happy I was able to get into Eitoku Gakuen.
Mr. Makino. I heard that a lot of your money
is going to Eitoku Gakuen.
Well, that's...
Mrs. Makino. I heard your daughter managed to get into Eitoku Gakuen.
Makino, I heard your sister got into Eitoku Gakuen.
Well, that's...
Everyone has been working hard for me.
I simply can't tell them I want to skip school.
I should never have gone there in the first place.
Congratulations to the Year 1 and 2 students
who have made it here.
Welcome one and all to Eitoku Gakuen.
Wow. She's so beautiful. Just like a model.
Seems like the one who will be inheriting the Toudou business
is currently studying in France.
She's so rich!
Please be quiet.
I would like to say a few words to all who wish to graduate here.
Please choose your own path in life.
This way, you will have no regrets about your school life.
Wanting to become a great person like her,
I entered Eitoku Gakuen.
And I thought it would be a happy life at school.
I hate this school. I hate F4, those idiots.
I can't stand my indifferent schoolmates.
But, I hate myself the most for being so unhappy.
This can't be happening.
There's no point in packing this.
Huh?
Those are prawns?
You must be Sanjou-san, the new transfer student from Class C.
Have you started eating? Let's eat together.
I...
It's only over there, let's go.
Sanjou-san. Come, sit here.
Thanks.
No problem.
I'm not too familiar with the boys.
I also don't really like being around such people.
Hey... Maybe you're... a commoner?
My goodness, that's mouldy.
That's just seaweed.
So you actually are a rich kid.
Want to try?
Thanks, I'll eat it.
Delicious!
Really?
Yes!
Sakurako, such a nice name.
Tsukushi-chan, that's cute too.
No no, just like wild grass.
(Her first name "Makino" translates to "Pasture")
Why name myself after a type of food?
I'm sorry.
This certainly is a rare type of greeting.
Well...
I'll help pay for the cleaning fees.
Cleaning fees? You've got to be kidding me.
Now now Tsukasa... Don't bully cute girls.
What a pity, I really want to see you 10 years older.
Hey, got an elder sister?
This is cold.
What if I catch pneumonia and die?
I, Domyoji, am inheriting
the name supporting Japan's economy.
Have you ever considered Japan's future?
What exactly are you thinking? I'm asking you a question!
Stop!
Please stop...
Please forgive her.
She didn't do it on purpose.
I'm praying very hard...
Very hard...
But in the end, I've fallen into their game.
The Red Paper!
Makino Tsukushi from 2C has got the Red Paper!
Just get rid of that girl today.
This is the first time a girl has gotten the Red Paper.
Yea.
What happened?
What the hell.
Stop it you guys!
Makino-san. A lesson is in progress.
I'm sorry.
Sakurako.
Even your friend has left you.
It's because you have always been a pain in the eye.
A commoner's child, daring to study in such a school.
Hurry up and get out of here.
Slut.
Damn.
Please... stop it... alright?
Don't shout and curse here.
So it was you after all.
Huh?
Is it possible for you to stop ranting here?
You've been listening.
I'm sorry, but this emergency staircase is my place.
It's very important, I don't wish to be disturbed.
The situation must be very troubling for you now.
That girl isn't affected at all.
What's going on?
My apologies.
She says that tomorrow...
You do know the consequences of failing, I assume.
I think transferring school would be the best.
You really think that way?
Of course!
Tsukushi.
That Domyoji, he is the son of a plutocrat?
When did you start listening to us?
So it is true. And he is likely to have links to the underground.
No matter what we do, we are still at his mercy.
At his mercy?
I've met a similar man before,
always fighting with his brothers for power.
An unknowingly, he was used by them.
Wait a minute. Where exactly did you come from?
Tsukushi-chan, I advice you to be more alert.
What is it?
Hold her down!
No!
Let me go!
Stop stuggling.
What are guys doing?
Well...
Let her go.
But if this is not done, this girl will...
It's alright.
I said let her go.
The cleaning lady is...
cleaning the emergency staircase.
It was so difficult just finding a quiet place.
I never expected this.
Th... Thanks.
Don't get me wrong here.
I just hate the methods they use.
Rui?
Yes. He appeared at the last minute...
Why didn't you get rid of the girl earlier?
I'll be returning to New York, when I've finished the M&A business.
What was the response from the Manhattan bank?
No. Just stop the deal.
Maybe, we should reconsider.
- I said stop it, right now.
So you're here.
Excuse me.
Is this what you say to your son whom you've
not seen for half a year?
Please call the chef here.
Yes ma'am.
You called me, ma'am?
You don't need to be here from tomorrow onwards.
Mishida. Please employ a new chef.
Yes ma'am.
Ah! The roasted chicken skin is here.
Thank you for the food!
Wait!
Let's finish off half the rice first from the aroma alone.
Oh, so this way it'll taste better.
Yes.
Have a go...
Please stop that.
Being thrifty isn't all that fun.
Sister, what's wrong?
It must be that the stress from school is too heavy.
I'm already feeling troubled enough.
You just can't force yourself to attend Eitoku Gakuen
while relying on everyone being so thrifty.
Akira-kun, I've got a present for you.
Eh? What is it?
This way, I'll marry you when you finish schooling.
Thank you for being with me, I'm very glad.
Hang on. Akira-kun!
Get her out of here.
Wait! Akira-kun!
Ah... You really are evil.
It's still better than you who are 21 years old.
Eh? Really, Sojiro?
Men and women, need not bother about age, no?
Your skin is very smooth and tender.
Such beauty.
You're just kidding...
Yes.
Rui didn't come?
That kid just loves to hide in remote and quiet places.
But you shouldn't bother about him, Tsukasa-kun.
That is all their scheming work.
What are you getting so upset about?
If that girl is not gone, this game will never end.
("game" refers to the Red Paper incidents in school)
Don't be so serious,
you're just having some fun after all.
But one day,
you're going to be so powerful
that even that school will not be
worth talking about.
What was that for?
You really are troublesome.
What are you saying?
Ah. Just like a flower, how cute.
That kid said, it's alright to give him less,
just give more to his sis'.
I see.
I must give you a bit of this.
No it's okay, give it to Tsukushi.
But...
I'm fine, just a little will do.
Yea, don't forget to put in Tsukushi's favourite, the prawns.
Tsukushi will be very happy.
You're tired, you should go to bed.
Can I borrow a light?
Bro, a light please?
You didn't hear me?
You've got to be kidding me.
Thank you for the food.
Hmph. A commoner desperately trying to imitate the upper class.
Men like me can tell by just one look.
This is nothing but a packed lunch
made by some old woman.
Hey you, come here.
What is it?
My shoes are dirty.
Don't forget to put in Tsukushi's favourite, the prawns.
Tsukushi will be very happy.
Hold it.
Hah? What did you say?
I don't care if you're the son of a plutocrat.
Someone like you hasn't even worked hard for money.
Go to hell!
I will not run away.
I will fight you.
Come on, if you have the guts.
Tsukasa! Take this!
I've really done something big.
Once I think about the consequences,
to be honest,
I'm really very scared.
But, I will never give up,
even if I'm hit or kicked.
Because, I, Tsukushi, am like wild grass.
I have no idea what happened to you.
You should handle this more carefully.
Here.
I'm off.
Have a good day.
Ha! Which also means you like her.
I've missed you dearly.
I've missed you too.
1 hundred million.
- How am I supposed to pay you that?