Any guy who hurts Makino, will never get away from me.
You should've said that way in the beginning.
Huh?
Domyouji Tower's Heliport.
Eh?
Come right now.
If you don't, I'll half-kill you..
Papa has been laid-off!
Eh?
WHY?!?!?
Papa..
What do you mean by this?
That's what I want to know..
Umm..  This is a company owned house, right, Papa?
Being laid off... Could it be?
They said we have to leave by Christmas..
Eh?
Isn't that too soon?
D*mnit..
I'm desperate for Sake!
Wai-
Papa!
Hey, calm down!
D*mnit.  This beer has nothing but air coming out... D*mnit!
You can just look for a new job, right?
That's right!
Let's just look towards the future! This isn't like you, Papa!
Papa. Look!
Today is special!
It's okay for you to drink a new one! It's not much, but..
Papa will do his best!
Papa will definitely do his best!
That witch.
Saturn Being?
Eh, who's the Saturn Being?
Me and Makino.
Saturn.. The one with the rings, that Saturn?
I just told you that's the one!!
Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, the dotted color Saturn!
What dotted color?
That's really funny!
Anyway!
Me and Makino are both Saturn beings, that's why,
From the very beginning we are destined to be together.
Is your brain okay?
And I thought I'd go to the trouble of showing her our
Native Planet..
That peasant!  On top of ignoring me, she made me worry!
Umm, you know what, Tsukasa-kun.
We were born here on earth.. We're earthlings!!!
No one was born in Saturn you know...
Of course I know that!
Are you a baka (idiot)?
No way.. Just now..
Hanazawa Rui-san and my eyes met..
He's coming over..
Ooh, what should we do?
Hey!
- Hai (yes)!
Where's Makino?
Makino-san, she's absent it seems..
But I think she's just playing hooky~
Oh no!
Domyouji-san doing something like this!  I'm a little shocked!
Do what you want, ugly!!
Wait Tsukasa. Where are you going?
Makino didn't show up, so I'm going home!
Hai.
Is that so?
I understand.
Excuse me.
Planet fortune telling?
Yeah, this one.
Oh, so that's how it is, huh?
It says here,
both Tsukasa and Makino are Saturn Beings..
And when you told Tsukasa about it..
He was super happy!
And that's why he thought he'd show Saturn to Makino!
But..
I wonder why Makino didn't come?
It seems like she didn't even call.
Should I call Yuuki-chan?
Hello, Yuuki-chan?
But you really like these kinds of things, Rui.
Eh?
Laid off?
Hai.
Her father has just been suddenly promoted,
and the whole family were really happy..
That aside, why do you look so happy?
Uh no..
I thought I'd give Nishikado-san a call.. but..
I didn't have any courage after all.. I was feeling really down..
I didn't expect Nishikado-san to-
But, it's a real pity..
They were already that poor.. Then being laid-off..
After all, are you just playing me around, Nishikado-san?
That's Tsukasa's mom's work, isn't it?
Umm..
The same thing happened with Tsukasa's Oneesan..
Recently,
it's been really rare..
Eating here at home..
Is that suppose to be me?
Or is it you?
When are you going back?
Just go back already.
When everything goes my way..
I will immediately go back to New York.
When every piece falls into place.
5 million yen? (about $41,480)
There must've been some mistake?
This is the loan proof, Ojou-san (young lady or daughter, honorable)
Please!!
Can you just please wait a bit more?
Well, you've been laid-off, right Otochan (father)?
Huh?!
But, I'll find a job soon, and work hard..
Everyone is doing the same thing, stupid!
Even if you say "Find a job right now..".  It's..
10 days, I'll give you 10 days.
There are really some stingy people in this world..
Excuse me..
Makino Tsukushi just submitted a leave of absence!
I think she's finally not able to pay her tuition fee, right?
At this rate, she'll have to quit school for sure!
Awesome, that'll be soo great!
Are they serious?
After last night's talk with Yuuki-chan..
Dropping out of school..
It's not an impossible story, right?
It's really Tsukasa's Mother's work, after all..
Well, we don't know that yet.
What are we going to do?
On top of being laid off, we have a 5 million yen debt..
It wasn't like that at first...
I borrowed, thinking I can pay it off by my next bonus..
You say that, but you were just betting on Horse Racing, right?
I'm sorry.
Especially at times like these..
Let's combine our strengths and do our best!
Tsukushi!!
Let's look upwards and walk!
- Hanazawa Rui -
Uh.. why?
Looks like things are pretty bad..
Eh?
Yeah, but it's totally okay, you know.
I wanted to talk to you about something.
- Eh?
Right now, where are you?
Ikebukoro's West Gate Park..
'Sup! Makino,
did she come in today?
Nope.
Makino just submitted a leave of absence.
Eh?
He's late..
Whoa-
This is a good place..
- Hey. Hey. Hey.
You're an Eitoku Ojousan, right?
Looking for a part time job?
Please excuse me.
It's a really awesome part time job!
We'll just take a little picture of you in your uniform, and you'll get.
100,000 yen ($828)!
Seriously??
I was just thinking,
but I think your Mom-
-Did you hear?
Tsukushi-chan..
seems to be really in trouble..
It's really great!
Let's just take a few pictures.. a few pictures, okay?
Right here, right here..
It'll be great!
Hey you!
It's your doing again, huh?
I really don't know anything at all.
You liar!!
When things happen to Makino,
Surely you're involved in it!
I swear, this time..
Your mother has never asked me to do anything..
Huh?
You..
You've been conspiring with my "BABA" (old woman, hag)?
but..
With my own will..
I really wanted to be with you..
No!!
Will you behave?
If you just take your clothes.. You'll get 100,000.
You said it's just a picture of me in my uniform..
They say for every sweet deal, there's a back side.
Don't come!
Don't go any closer!!
The back side is the back side.  And a back side video!
Stop it!!!!
Hana Yori Dango
Episode 8
[Character] ** [Actor]
Makino Tsukushi ** Inoue Mao
Domyouji Tsukasa ** Matsumoto Jun
Hanazawa Rui ** Oguri Shun
Nishikado Soujiro ** Matsuda Shota
Mimasaka Akira ** Abe Tsuyoshi
Timing and Translation ** Backalley
Timing and Translation ** mhaellix
Editing and Release ** furransu
No!!
Stop it!!
Hey! This woman, force her down!
- Stop it!!
Stop it!!!
You guys? Whatcha doin?
Hey, don't intrude!
We're running for it!
Nee-chan.
Can you lend me your strength for a bit?
I've been..
saved by Hanazawa Rui again..
Thank you.
You didn't talk to Tsukasa,
about the situation with your dad and your leave of absence?
Yeah.
Coz' you don't want to unnecessarily let him worry?
No, that's not the reason why, or should I say...
It's possible,
that Tsukasa's mother is the one moving behind the scenes..
It can't be..
That person is an Iron Woman after all..
Even so, no matter what, that's just too-
No.
If there's something to do,
she's a person who will do it completely and thoroughly.
Don't try to shoulder everything on your own..
If something happens, you can always come to me for help.
Thank you.
Iron Woman, huh?
Could it be, that is -
Who is?
Me? I'm an Iron Woman?
Uh no.  It's not you..
Umm..
Among the men you once loved.  Was there a parent who will not
care about the means just for the sake of his beloved son?
Ahh, it's the inverse of the usual pattern..
Now that you mention, there is..
a troublesome man...
Ahh, bingo!
What kind of person was he?
Decisively, a woman of the polar!
Otsu (strange, queer)
She was a woman who raised him by herself.
And at the time that I was introduced to her..
She started getting angry, and she was like a fire...
Prepare yourself!!
But the two of us stubbornly opposed her!
And at that time, we gained our happiness!
Don't under estimate me!!!
After that..?
At the time when I wasn't aware...
I was somehow thrown out by that mother's hands..
And that was the end..
Ah, by the way!
Tsukushi-chan, I forgot..
Here, it's not much, but..
What is it?
I heard you're having quite some problems?
Uh, no.. It's fine..
It's really not much.
Uh, but..
Once your father gets a job, and everything calms down,
you can just properly pay me then..
Kami-san..
Everyone's with you, you know..
So no matter who your enemy is, don't you dare lose!
Yes..
Thank you.
Eh, is that true?
Whenever I go for interview in any company..
When my name comes up, then immediately,
the expression on the face of the person in charge changes..
and I get turned away at the door..
Mama went to find a job all day, but..
But whenever I show my resume,
they say that they've got enough people already..
Isn't it strange?
I was also turned down for Newspaper delivery and Milk Delivery.
Ittekimasu (I'm going and coming back)
Wait Papa, where are you going?
Well for now,
I'm going to a construction site that offers day-to-day employment.
We have to eat, you know.
That person..
She's an Iron Woman..
She's a person who will do something completely and thoroughly.
Our family really has to give up things like money or work..
That's not it..
Our family is not in the wrong at all.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Daihyou (Representative)
Makino Tsukushi has..
demands to meet with the Daihyou..
It's okay, let her pass.
Neechan's late..
What, Nishida?
Excuse me.
Coming all the way here,
I wonder what is it about?
I have some questions that I would like to ask.
It's exactly what you're thinking..
Everything has been schemed by me.
Your family declared a war against me.
I just took that challenge.
That's all it is.
Is that all it was?
With Tsukasa,
Or with the Domyouji House,
You shall not have any relation with them in the future.
Promise me.
If you do, I will return each and everything to the way it was before,
Ojouchan.
You must be kidding!
Are you baka?
Baka??
Influencing with the power of the money you have­
Doing whatever you want.  Is that interesting?
Being as old as you are,
doing things like that of sneaky bullying,  is it fun?
Which god do you intend to be?
Besides-
- I'm not trying to be a god!
For you I might just be a weed,
but,
I am not living a life that people have to be ashamed of.
Really?
Despising everyone but yourself, you're a detestable human being.
For a person such as yourself,
I will never do exactly as you say!!
Please excuse me!
Obochan (young master)!!
Where's Makino?
Just now..
What did that "baba" do in Makino's house?
The same thing with Tsubaki-sama's..
I will kill that "BABA"!
Please wait!
but she,
just rejected the Daihyou's proposal.
Right now, it's better if you ran after her..
Nishida..
Honestly speaking,
When I'm with the Daihyou,
there are times that even I think she's dreadful.
But that girl,
she didn't pull back against that Daihyou, not even one step.
"Because I don't want to live a life that
people have to be ashamed of.
I will never do exactly as the Daihyou says!!"
For today, I will properly explain things to the Daihyou.
Thank you.
This is bad.. I actually said that..
Makino!!!
Feels like..
it's been so long..
Yeah.. it seems..
That night before, you completely neglected me.
I waited for you over night..
Coz'..
The other day..
I wanted to show Saturn to you..
Saturn?
Yup, Saturn..
And that's why you waited over night?
Coz' me and you are Saturn Beings.
What's that supposed to mean?
If I'm not mistaken, Saturn is right in that area..
It looks like,
you've said some biting words against that "baba"..
Blood went to my head, and then I just snapped..
Are you regretting it?
I'm not-
I'm a little scared..
But,
I definitely do not want to lose.
You know what, I..
will always be your ally..
No matter what happens..
I will always protect you, Makino.
plus your family, too..
First of all, the debt, huh?
About how much is it?
It seems like it's 5 million..
Okay-
I'll pay that in advance..
Eh?
That's no good, definitely no good.
Why?
Because..
In the end, it's just like I'm getting the money
from your mother, Domyouji..
I don't think that's just right.
You may be right, but...
in the end what will you do?
I'll try my best to find another part-time job.
Rather,
Why don't we just get married?
Eh?!
Don't you think it's a nice "idol"? (He's trying to say "idea")
Wh... What are you trying to say?
That was just a slip up..
I think it should be a n-nice nice I...
I Love You?
Onee-chan!
T.O.J.?
Teen Of Japan, also known as T.O.J.
Every 3 years before Christmas...
this competition is organised to select
Japan's top high school student.
Onee-chan, as well as Shizuka, both have been past winners.
Onee-san and Shizuka-san...
You are judged on your looks, style, general knowledge ...
and some Home Making skills in this contest.
That...
That's impossible for me.
And the winner gets 5 million yen...
and can attend Eitoku for free.
5 million...
But isn't registration closed?
Don't worry.
Past winners can submit their recommendations.
Really, onee-chan?
I might as well tell you, the first winner
of this contest was our mother.
After that "baba" won, she found Dad.
That's why there's no reason for her not to accept you.
That lass wants to join T.O.J.?
It's not just to participate,
but to win this competition.
Win?
You must be kidding.
Well then, if she wins,
you'll allow her to continue her association with Tsukasa,
and you will also stop harrassing Makino.
That's not even gonna be worth gambling for.
No double dealing on this, okay, Okaasama (mother, respectful)?
There's a possibility...
for me to win?
None.
What's up with that?
But, if you seriously want to win this competition,
I will be all-out on my support for you.
Nee-san...
How 'bout it, Tsukushi-chan?
Go ahead, Makino.
Even pigs can be pearls...
I'll participate, nee-san.
I look forward to working with you.
Makino is joining T.O.J.?
Are you sure?
That's why you guys cooperate, okay?
Tsukasa, are you serious?
But, no matter what, there isn't a chance she could win.
Have you forgotten?
Makino, all by herself,
stood up against us, the F4.
Help her win,
and let my sh*tty "baba"...
No, let the whole of Japan...
accept that Makino is the greatest woman.
That's interesting.
Makino is specially training at my home.
Let's go see her now.
Let's go!
Yes!
That girl's not good at all those things.
Beauty and style, knowledge, and homemaking.
Homemaking!
Tsukasa looks like he's having fun.
Listen, the judging is split into three categories.
The first is beauty.
Beauty...
Outward appearance, of course.  But inward beauty is also important.
Tea and Flowers are standards.
Have you ever raised up Tea?
(raise up tea is to do a tea ceremony:  Tatteru)
Aaah... If it's just Tea...
You've learned it already!
Rather than saying I've learned it.
It's basically just common sense.
Ah... The tea leaf stalk is standing up!
<Tsubaki said to raise up the Tea, which is the same word as to
stand up. Tsukushi thinks that raising up Tea, is the same as
the tea leaf stalk standing upright>
Really? Really? Let's see!
But, onee-san, you don't stand the tea up, you pour it in.
Otsu (strange, queer).
Tea is from square one, huh?
Hai?
The second category is knowledge.
During our time, Liberal Education, Language Study,
and until some Specialty Fields..
A quiz that contained practically everything..
A quiz...
I think I'm pretty good with quizzes.
Next question. What bird does kogaru (High School Call Girls)
hate?
I know!
Kanariya!
<"Kanariya" is "Kanari iya : I hate canary" and
it is an expression for "I kinda hate it",
and this expression is used by Call Girls>
Ka-Na-Ri-Ya....
Correct!
I think I can do it...
And for your information, it's not a puzzle or riddle quiz.
Eh?
And the third category is your homemaking skills.
It is a little sneaky.
What kind of test did you have for the homemaking category?
Back then, we had to make okonomiyaki.
Making okonomiyaki?
There were many who have never made,
or even eaten it.
But I was very lucky. It was one of Tsukasa's favorites.
He suddenly said "I want to eat it, I want to eat it!"  So I had to remember how to cook it, and let him eat it.
Little boy, do you want some okonomiyaki?
Food that is eaten by poor people..  I don't want it!
Out of those who weren't eliminated already,
not even one could make okonomiyaki.
Then... Would say that it was the okonomiyaki
that allowed you to win?
Yeah.
In other words,
you really never know what will happen in this competition.
If you're not good at each and everything,
then there's no way to win..
There are only two weeks left before the competition.
What's next is very serious training for you.
You should prepare yourself.
After all, I..
This isn't like you at all...
Eh?
Where is the person who gave my sh*tty "baba"
a piece of her mind straight in the face?
Everyone is lending their strengths for your sake.
And...
Those are the teachers who will be instructing you.
Makino.
I'll help sharpen you.
We will all be beside you, rest assured, Makino.
I told you that if something happens,
you can always come to me for help.
Everyone...
Thank you!
Thank us when you've won the competition.
I will...
Do my best!
Raise the cup.
No! No!
Fix your posture. You mustn't raise your shoulders.
Yes!
Don't make vulgar sounds.
Take a look at Tsukasa.
What would you like to eat? (chinese)
What would you like to eat?
Peking duck.
I would please like to eat the Peking duck.
Then do it until here.
Until there, one more time.
Yes!
Nishida, please continue carrying out the contingency plan.
Ma'am, about the plan...
It's just for my concern.  So just concern yourself in it.
Understood.
Excuse me.
I've decided to enter T.O.J.
I will definitely not let Makino win this competition.
It's impossible for you.
Until now. Thank you for all your hard work.
Wait a minute, Okaa-sama.
Okaa-sama?
I've never asked you to call me okaa-sama.
Ah, hello? Ayano-chan? Domyouji speaking. How are you?
No no, wrong. Pay closer attention to your left hand.
If this goes on, you won't win, you know?
Takosuke (octopus)
Don't call me Takosuke.
I'm working very hard at this.
Come on, one more time.
She says you do not have the proper foundation.
Your posture is poor, that's why it falls off.
Hai.  Then, one more time.
What's wrong? Do you want a break?
Seriously, you're really no good at anything you do.
I've just started.
How do you expect me to be good at it?
It's useless.
If this continues, there's no way I can win.
Hello. Yuuki? What's wrong?
Why are you suddenly closing down my business?
Is there a problem with the goods that we're selling?
What is the reason?
Please tell me the reason you are doing this!
Please tell me why...
Wait!
I'm very sorry, I still have a lot of things to settle.
This isn't what we arranged the last time, right?
I beg of you, please give us some more time.
So annoying!
I can't wait on your family and just look at you forever.
Please give us 2 more days..
I beg of you... Please...
<Announcement: ... has received support
from the Domyouji representatives.>
< Critics believe that even the government
cannot stop the Domyouji Corporation from advancing further >
< Prime Minister in the shadow of the
Domyouji Corporation!! >
What's up?  Revival of your will to fight?
Clumsy and stupid and blockhead Makino-kun?
I think...
I'm quitting after all.
Huh?
My opponent is just too strong.
Even I admit raise my arms in defeat.
She has completely filled the outer moat.
(castle's moat or waterway,
she meant that she has placed the perfect barrier)
Really, everything came one after another...
This time, I've found the wrong person to fight...
I will properly apologize to Onee-san, as well as the others.
Your guts have flown away, huh?
After all, you're only a woman of that level.
Making a pathetic face.
As if you're an underdog.
What would you know?
Being this rich, living a life completely free of discomfort.
You who have never experienced hardships.
What would you know?!
How can I possibly understand the feelings of
a poor person like you?
Makino Tsukushi has to be this way.
Huh?
With that "Weed Power", you'll be alright.
For Makino, A smile suits you the best,
And maybe your angry face, too.
It's because of your mom...
that so many innocent people got involved.
If you win, everything will be alright.
But I've caused so much trouble to so many people.
I can't do this anymore..
I'm at my limit, already.
For now Rui will be doing really well about your family.
Carry this.
Plus, even if some weird guys come crashing, it'll be alright.
The SPs (Special Police; Agents) at Rui's Place will watch over.
You don't have to worry about the Confectionary shop either.
As for Soujiro, the Nishikado Ichimon will order large quantities of
confectionary to use for their Tea Parties, for now.
And that Akira, I think there's something going on with him
and that Confectionary Store's Kami-san. And so he desperately
pleaded with Soujiro's father.
Everyone is lending their strengths for your sake.
If we, the F4, are on your side.  Is there anything to be afraid of?
Just be yourself and do it.
Coz' I believe in you.
Have some confidence.
You're the woman that I have recognized after all.
Obviously, you're the best!
I...
No problem.
The Saturn beings will create a miracle at the last moment
(at the eleventh hour).
What's that all about?
You and I, from the very beginning were destined to be together.
I'll do my best.
Do your best.
Ah... F4!
But, Domyouji can really do anything, right?
It's because I was taught by my "satellite" (eisei).
Tsk.  He's really weakest in his Japanese though.
I'm telling you, there's no such thing as strong or weak in Japanese.
It's a language after all.
Are you sure you'll be alright?
There he goes again...
Alright!
Let's go!
Tsukasa!
Ayano.
It's been a while. How are you?
Hello everyone.
What are you here for?
Your mom contacted me,
"With my recommendation, can you please join T.O.J.?
That's why I rushed back here from London.
See you later.
We couldn't expect less of Tsukasa's mom.
She is an Iron Woman.
An unexpected and unbelievable bomb has been launched.
Who was that pretty girl?
Kurimaki Ayano.
The daughter of a parliamentarian.  Tsukasa's fiance.
Eh?
Excuse me.
Sakurako!
In here, we're mutual enemies,
So don't talk to me that easily.
This'll just be an extra luggage.  I don't need it.
I'm going to the toilet.
Could everyone please arrange yourselves according
to your number?
Yes!
And now, Teen Of Japan 2005.
We have the entrance of the contestants.
<Next week, the final episode will be
specially extended by 15 minutes>
Domyouji!