Everyone, take a look.
What the...
Doing this kind of things, you people want to ...
Please look at this.
It's not what you think, Domyoji.
Please believe me.
It's just like you've gotten The Red Paper again.
What kind of expression is that?
You've deceived everyone in the school.
It cannot be forgiven.
Get her!
Stop it! Let me go!
You better watch it next time.
Tsukushi-chan.
Sakurako.
You've... finally come back to school.
Don't bother about me. More importantly, are you alright?
It's nothing, just some bruises.
What's with that guy?
That kind of expression...
Please believe me.
Why... won't he believe me?
Tsukushi-chan, let's go look for Domyoji.
Huh?
Once you explain it to him, he'll understand.
Tsukushi-chan isn't that type of person to do such things.
Are you able to stand?
Thanks, Sakurako.
I'm fine.
This is really too much.
He's good.
Why is he good? I think the innocent Makino Tsukushi
being capable of such pictures, that's unheard of.
What's this guy trying to achieve by doing this?
He must be trying to give himself a challenge.
Like wanting to eat mushrooms which have not
yet been classified as poisonous or edible.
** TL's Note: The mushrooms refer to Tsukushi, the person
eating them is the guy who took slept with her **
Domyoji.
I... That guy... Nothing happened between us.
Please believe me.
With these photos around, how do you expect us to believe you?
Even I myself don't fully understand,
how such a thing can happen without my knowing.
Obviously, you went with that guy to a Hotel,
and together you took those photos.
** TL's Note: It is normal for a couple to rent a Hotel room
for a night, for the sole purpose of having it **
So I'm saying... If anything went on,
I wouldn't have known until I woke up...
Ah... That's not what I meant. That's why... In other words...
Domyoji-san. Please believe Tsukushi-chan.
Even though... From the photos, Tsukushi-chan appears to have
slept with that man in a Hotel.
The photos are undeniably true.
But, there's definitely a reason behind it.
Just shut up! I never asked you...
Hey! Sakurako is only helping me explain...
Tsukushi-chan, just keep quiet.
Eh?
Domyoji-san, he's already very hurt by what you've done.
I only hope that the two of you can make up.
You have already betrayed me.
Haven't I said this already, it's not how you think it is!
Who's betraying you? I never had a relationship
with you in the first place.
Why do you always say that we do?
Oh yea, then you don't need to be here anymore.
Yea, then I won't need to waste my time, or yours,
here clearing up this misunderstanding.
I'm leaving!
This is so troublesome.
And I thought we could have just resolved it.
Well isn't this actually better?
We now know that Makino isn't serious about
having a relationship with Tsukasa.
What was that...
Makino isn't the type of person to do those things.
It's because you are the only girl in my eyes.
He won't believe me, and yet he says those words.
Ah, it hurts...
Commoners are very used to the cold, so it's all right.
Don't look down on me, I'm just as tough as wild grass.
("Tsukushi" means "wild grass")
Hamburgers... Delicious meals... Wow, great food...
What on earth are those?
Oh! Tsukushi. These photos were taken by Papa. What do you think?
Didn't you notice that the amount has increased?
Papa is such a genius!
Really?
Well the next one, shall be our family photo!
Ah, I don't need to be in it.
Just take Mama's photo, that's all.
What are you saying? Shouldn't the four of us
be in the family photo, and not just one person?
This sort of requirement, it's a problem then.
Come on, quickly...
Everyone, smile together!
Obviously, someone has to operate it.
Oh yea...
Tsukushi, you're so smart.
I'll do it...
Really? If you don't mind then...
Come come come come... Everyone, be happy!
Yep, cheese...
There was definitely need to be another person,
who would take this photograph.
I must find the culprit. Sakurako, can you help me out?
Tsukushi-chan, are you doing this for Domyoji-san?
Eh?
Does it matter to you, how he sees you?
He doesn't understand you at all, Tsukushi-chan.
That is why you were so mistreated.
Have you forgotten?
You're right about that, but...
My apologies, if you're doing this for Domyoji, I cannot help you.
Eh?
But, no matter what happens,
I'll always be by your side supporting you.
I see, thank you.
Then, I'll contact you again some other time.
Okay, see you.
Been seeing you around here a lot.
You even doll up like this, don't be so full of yourself.
I'm sorry, it's not what you think...
Get lost, ugly witches.
It should be considered an offense to see such ugly
people like you hanging out around here.
Quickly get lost, ugly witches!
What's the matter? What happened?
Hana Yori Dango - Boys Over Flowers
Episode 5
[Character] ** [Actor]
Makino Tsukushi ** Inoue Mao
Domyoji Tsukasa ** Matsumoto Jun
Hanazawa Rui ** Oguri Shun
Nishikado Sojiro ** Matsuda Shota
Mimasaka Akira ** Abe Tsuyoshi
Timing and Translation ** Backalley
Editing ** Chibisige
Editing and Release ** furransu
QC ** mhaellix
But isn't that very dangerous,
finding the culprit yourself.
You're right about that...
What is this?
This is "Daifuku".
(A kind of snack that "commoners" eat)
Delicious.
Oh? The "mushroom" is back at work.
Mushroom?
Oh... It's nothing...
Hey... What are you guys doing?
Akira just broke up with someone's wife,
so he's feeling a bit lonely now.
It's like that for now, so we dropped by here.
But still, there's a certain girl who has had
sleazy photographs taken of her in bed,
and the most talked about subject in school
is this unfortunate girl.
We should really learn from her.
We might find ourselves feeling luckier than in her shoes.
In other words, you people are just free.
Right!
Is this yours?
No.
Ah, then whose could it be?
Alright, how about playing a detective game.
Eh? What?
Yea...
We'll help you find the culprit.
Isn't that great? Accept their request.
Anyhow, it's better than them staying in this place...
If you don't mind, please help me.
Alright! Let's start right away.
You help Makino fill in for her work.
Why me?
I beg of you, it's a crucial opportunity for Tsukushi-chan.
I'm not involved in this.
Promotion! Promotion! For each purchase,
you will get a kiss from this fine young man here.
Thank you very much. Everyone! Come on in!
I want to go with you to find the culprit.
I am not involved in that at all.
Doesn't Domyoji-san want to quickly find out
who the person behind all this is?
And whether anything really happened between
the two of them that night.
This evening, I'll wait for you at the bridge of the Harajuku Shrine.
I won't go.
What's with you, just standing there naturally,
acting as if you deserve to.
Get out.
Get out!!
Let's hope we can find some leads to the search.
Doesn't Domyoji-san want to quickly find out
who the person behind all this is?
And whether anything really happened between
the two of them that night.
Excuse me.
Didn't you go back to New York?
Were you the one who did this?
Did you order someone to take these photos?
You don't address me like that.
Don't secretly conduct your own inspections.
You are, after all, the heir to the Domyoji wealth.
How can you have a relationship with this sort of girl?
You don't look too happy about this.
Love, that useless emotion, it has no meaning at all.
Ma'am, it's about time for the scheduled flight.
Do you sell this here?
As expected of Nishikado-san,
to know that this shop that sells only one of that.
Who has bought it before?
Well, to release information about individual buyers...
How about if I open up a new shop
next to this one...
It was a host who bought it.
** TL Note: In this context, a "host" is someone who works
at a club, like the one Tsukushi met. **
That was fast...
Which club?
Well, that...
If I buy this whole place, and open
a tea restaurant, that's not a bad idea.
Hey you! Go and buy some coffee, and make it quick!
Buy it from the club called "S".
I got it.
Please send everything in this store to my house,
I'm buying it all.
Ah, so it's here. That's the club where Reiko-chan is at.
Why do even High School students know about such a place?
No way...
Tsukasa, also looking for the culprit?
You must be joking.
Then what are you two doing?
One look and you can tell... Let's go.
This is yours, thank you and have a nice day!
We're all out of food.
I'm very sorry, very very sorry.
Well, I'm done here then.
Lady Boss, I want to look for Tsukushi...
Certainly! Go with him...
Oh, I remember this girl.
Do you know where she went after she left this place?
Oh that... One look at the way she was, and you could tell...
Ah, she really was here.
Could you tell us the room she was in?
How's it going, Tsukushi?
We don't seem to have found him yet.
I'll go check if anyone recognises this ring.
So handsome...
Are you alright?
Are you hurt?
Could you get me another glass, please?
What's he up to?
Tsukushi-chan was in this room, and on that bed,
sleeping together with that other guy.
Are you alright?
I... have also been deceived by Tsukushi-chan.
I don't like that feeling.
Domyoji-san, you feel the same way, right?
Please don't look so down and sad.
I will... feel bad... too...
You better watch it.
That girl, she's been deceiving me all this while.
Tsukushi.
Anything the matter?
Yuuki, I really like Hanazawa Rui.
Mm.
So from back then till now, the person in my heart
should always be Hanazawa Rui.
Just now that guy...
Domyoji and Sakurako were walking together...
Even though they weren't close or anything,
my heart started to feel the pain,
it really hurts.
Hey, watch where you're going!
What is it?
In my opinion, love begins when you least expect,
Love?
No way... How can that guy and I be...
It's Sakurako...
Hi.
Tsukushi-chan? It's me, Sakurako.
Yea.
Right now, Domyoji asked me to give you a call.
Domyoji-san wants to make up with you, Tsukushi-chan.
Make-up? Domyoji?
Come to my place. Domyoji-san is waiting here.
Domyoji-san is waiting here.
Sorry for making you wait.
Next is me!
Hurry up and bring me what I ordered.
And my beer too...
Thank you for coming, I have something for you.
We would like to ask that you come work in this club.
Welcome!
Wait here for me, I'll be right back.
Umm... Where is Domyoji?
Let me get some tea first.
People are such hateful creatures.
They can betray your trust anytime.
The man I once loved, he had two sides of himself.
During the day, he was a hardworking, honest manager (of employees).
During the night, he was a frivilous manager (of women).
Isn't that normal?
It was then... that he cruelly deceived... the innocent me.
I have no idea what you're saying.
Ah, it's gotten dirty.
Are you alright?
Thank you.
You're such a gentleman, Akira-kun.
Who hired you to take those photos?
You bastard!
It was someone called Chiri. She paid me to do it.
Chiri?
Yea, she said that she was a rich kid studying in Eitoku Kindergarten.
Kindergarten?
Hi, yes?
Soujiro, it's the maple leaf!
NO!
I'm sorry.
F4...
This would be a photo album of them studying together
when they were young.
Domyoji-san, thank you for accompanying me today.
I didn't realise you were so easy to fool.
Huh?
You didn't notice? The people at the club, at the hotel,
they were all set up by me.
You...
Come to the canteen at Eitoku.
Your beloved Makino Tsukushi is waiting for you here.
Come alone, only you and no one else.
Hey, wait...
Let go, stop! It hurts!
Hey! Let go of me!
I'm used to this kind of reaction from you.
Why? Why are you treating me like this, Sakurako?
Weren't we friends?
Friends? Don't kid me.
The guy at the club, I paid him to do it.
He put sleeping pills in the Oolong Tea to get you
to sleep, I also arranged for that.
And I was the one who took the photos of you in the hotel room.
You've said enough!
You even betrayed your own friend, you're inhumane.
Shut up!
There is something I need to do.
No one cares about your insignificant feelings.
Domyoji and I have been together since kindergarten,
and ever since then I've always wanted my revenge on him.
Revenge?
It was because of that, that I had to use you.
Sanjyo-san. Here! Here!
Meeting you that day was a coincidence,
but knocking into Domyoji with the food was pre-planned.
Please... forgive her...
I never expected you to put up a fight for me.
A brat like you who has never worked hard for money...
Go to hell!
I will fight you.
And that was how it all began...
I really didn't expect you to do what you did.
But, what I would never expect to happen, happened...
He actually fell for you.
Just what did Domyoji do to make you react like this...?
He's been such an idiot, just like he is now,
even from the time when we were young.
I will not forgive him. Never ever!
This will be the last time you'll be of use to me.
Eh?
I want to use you to tempt Domyoji to come to this place.
Tsukasa, are you with Sanjyo Sakurako?
Nope.
You must be careful of that girl,
she's really out to get you.
Listen here, Tsukasa.
Tsukasa, where are you going?
Home.
You're lying.
Where are you going, and what has happened,
you better quickly tell us.
Don't go there, Tsukasa!
That girl is dangerous. You never know who might
be there lying in wait for you.
We've just looked through your Kindergarten photo album.
I need to go there.
Then tell us where you are going.
We'll go there with you too.
If I wait for you, I won't be able to protect Makino in time.
Domyoji won't come.
That guy... He doesn't care about me.
It's simply because he fell for you that made me so mad!
Makino!
Why...?
Why did you have to come here, stupid?
Makino, I'm sorry. I didn't believe you.
I didn't call you here to make your confessions.
You... What do you want?
I want you to show me...
How much you really love this girl...
If you retaliate one bit, I will deface her.
You underestimate me.
Makino, shut your eyes.
Eh?
Just do it, shut them.
Oh my, your sincerity has surprised me.
Stop it! Stop hitting him!
How does it feel?
You're always so high and mighty, and now
you're being beaten like this.
You're not happy about something?
If you're not happy, then fight back!
Why do you care about what harm is done to this girl's face?
Her face was originally such a mess anyway.
Is that all? It didn't hurt one bit.
Continue hitting him!
Why are you holding back? You've never been beaten before.
You're definitely able to beat all of them if you just fight back.
Why aren't you fighting back?!
She doesn't look at all like the Sanjyo Sakurako we now know.
What kind of monster is that girl?
It's a bit strange...
That's enough already, stop fighting!
Why?! Why won't you fight back?!
Is holding back for that ugly witch over there really worth it?
Why is she the only that can do this?
Why...?
And I even spent so much on making myself beautiful just for you...
Is everyone doing great?
Yes...
Well then, give what you've done to a person you like.
Tsukasa, for you.
Just take it, Tsukasa. Take it...
Get lost, you ugly...
You are "Hanapecha"
and an ugly witch... witch... witch... ugly witch...
("Hanapecha" means "Flat nose")
I became such a beauty.
I never listened once to Papa's and Mama's advice,
and I even took special leave from school.
Everything was re-made, re-did.
And still you can't accept me. Why?
Makino...
If only you would just lie,
and tell me that I was beautiful just once...
I really like you. I can't live without you.
Makino...
Why won't you ever say something nice to me?
I've had... Enough...
Domyoji.
Are you alright?
Domyoji!
No... I'm not alright.
Why? Why won't you fight back?
I won't be able to protect you, if I had fought back.
I'll make this clear,
it wasn't that I couldn't have beaten all of them.
It was just for you...
Stupid!
You're going in circles.
Really?
You knew what would happen, and yet you still came...
That's needless to say...
I like you.
I really like you.
Tsukasa was admitted to the hospital?
Yes. Makino Tsukushi is now looking after him.
That lass is still sticking close to Tsukasa.
I think so...
Hey! Feed me.
Huh? Why do I need to feed you?
You should be able to hold your chopsticks.
Why haven't you removed the sling bandage,
it's already been a week.
You're probably just trying to get the sympathy of others.
Can't you see it still hurts.
How romantic. So that's "a fight comes necessary with love".
Didn't you say the more romantic, the better a relationship will be?
Never said it.
Tsukasa, what'll we do?
What is it?
About Sanjyo Sakurako...
You come here quickly.
Move it!
You must be in here.
I found it in my cousin's house yesterday.
Such an ugly person can become so good looking,
it must not have been easy.
Witches...
Witch... witch... ugly witch...
What's wrong with that?
Don't you people also have the money to doll yourselves up?
What's wrong with using money to beautify oneself?
What's wrong?!
Huh!
Let me make this clear, this doesn't mean I've forgiven you.
Your selfish actions have made me very unhappy.
But, you once said that my mom's food was good...
Delicious...
Really?
Yes!
That should have been the only words that you truly meant.
I'm sorry.
Wonderful! I couldn't expect less out of the girl I like.
Right?
Yay!
Hey stop... Let go...
It hurts a lot! What are you doing?
You want me to break it again?
Huh?
Doesn't that mean it's healed?
Darn! She found out.
Darn?! I found out?? You...
What was that for, you bastard?
You don't have to hit me...
That was totally uncalled for...
You come here...
I'm back.
Let's have a "double date" tomorrow.
It's all the scary people.
But, haven't you remembered?
I never did that.
Makino, I...
Do you know where your real enemy is?
This isn't a game!
Here.
It's been a while,
Yomogi-chan.
I'm Tsukushi.
Racing Panda.
Raysun Panda.
Huh?
Could you be ...
Tsukasa, what are you doing in a place like this?
It's not good!
Huh?
They allowed me to stay here.
I don't ever want to see you again.