This is unbelievable!
Eitoku Gakuen, one of the most exlusive
private schools in Japan, and filled with the rich.
Leading this school would be the
most wealthy, most influential.
The band of four guys,
also known as "Flower 4", or F4.
Those who annoy them will receive The Red Paper,
and they will be ostracised
and bullied by the rest of the school populace.
I only hope to get through school
without any trouble.
The Red Paper!
Makino Tsukushi has gotten The Red Paper!
But, even if I'm hated in school,
I will not concede defeat.
I am just as tough as wild grass.
(Her first name "Makino" translates to "Pasture")
One look and I can tell that some old woman
made this low quality stuff.
Brats like you have never worked hard for money.
Go to hell!
I will not run, I will stay and fight.
My my... She got The Red Paper
and won't even come to school.
How uninteresting.
She deserves it.
She dared to offend Domyoji by doing such things.
Well, maybe she's been expelled already?
My my, how cruel of you.
Where am I?
This is a surprise.
Yea.
Well then, let's get to work.
Alright.
What's the meaning of this?
What are you trying to do?
Why dress me up like this?
Get rid of it.
What?
Didn't you want to fight me? Get rid of that idea.
You've got to be kidding.
1 hundred million.
Huh?
What you're wearing,
that's about how much it costs.
1 hundred million?!
Make-up and getting you hair done,
that's about 10 million.
The evening gown, that's another 20 million.
And there's the jewellery.
All these add up to about 1 hundred million yen.
This can't be.
Are... Are you planning on using these to buy me off?
There is no need.
I can give you anything you want.
Huh? Why would you do this?
What's so funny?
You think I'm going to like these things?
It's disgusting.
Then why are you lost for words?
You really are lost for words.
That's because...
One's heart can be easily bought with money.
You're no different. You're just a commoner.
Smile. You must be very happy
to be able to wear these
Come on, smile.
I'm asking you to smile!
Have you lost your mind? How can I smile about this?
What you've done,
I'm not the least happy about it.
There are also things in this world
which cannot be bought with money.
I will not concede defeat.
Don't treat me like any ordinary girl.
What on earth is that guy trying to do?
To think that I'll admit defeat so easily...
Speaking of which, where is my uniform?
What a beautiful person.
This isn't the time to praise other people.
My goodness, one table
is more than enough.
What a strange place.
What?? Is this Harry Potter or what?
This can't be happening.
Where on earth could my uniform be?
Er... Wait a minute...
What? What?
What are you doing? No no no no! Stop!
I will not run. I will fight you. If you have guts then come on.
Tsukasa!
Don't be so cocky about it.
There is a conference at 4pm.
And dinner is at 6pm.
My goodness, why is this house so huge?
Come to think of it,
I've made very powerful enemies.
Hana Yori Dango - The Flower Boy
Episode 2
[Character] ** [Actor]
Makino Tsukushi ** Inoue Mao
Domyoji Tsukasa ** Matsumoto Jun
Hanazawa Rui ** Oguri Shun
Nishikado Sojiro ** Matsuda Shota
Mimasaka Akira ** Abe Tsuyoshi
Timing and Translation ** Backalley
Editor ** Chibisige
Editor and Release ** Yoshitsune
I say, Makino Tsukushi should have already been
drowned at Tokyo Bay.
Of course.
She even dared to hit Domyoji in front of everyone.
She should be dead by now.
I'm still alive, dammit.
Got a problem with that?
But really, shouldn't it better to
leave this school right away for good?
Well really,
you'd only be saying such things
before you're forced to leave.
Makino Tsukushi
Slept with men 5 times,
Extremely lewd.
Who wrote this?
Writing such insulting words in a place like this.
This the first time it happened.
Really? How heartless.
Even if it was carelessly written,
I won't be able to show my face
if such things happened.
But... But... It's so heartless.
We can't compare at all.
What the hell... That bastard...
His head is full of shit.
Really,
I'm still a virgin.
Hmm. So you're still a virgin.
Hey, please don't make fun of me.
Do you know the time difference
between Japan and France?
Eh?
Time difference.
I... I don't know.
Oh.
Wait a minute,
why is Hanazawa-san and that girl together?
It's been said already,
that girl...
How hateful.
Thanks for buying.
Time difference eh...
Hmm... The time difference between
Japan and France...
Found it!
It's 8 hours.
I'll tell him tomorrow.
You seem very happy.
What?
Isn't that guy a member of F4?
He's one of those who hands out
The Red Paper.
The Red Paper,
it's probably Domyoji's doing.
I don't think Hanazawa Rui
likes doing those sort of things.
The situation must be very troubling for you now.
But he didn't stop it from happening.
That makes him guilty as well.
I don't think he's guilty.
Why are you defending him.
No particular reason.
What kind of person is he?
Well that...
I have no idea what he thinks about.
He's a bit cold.
But sometimes that's really cool.
His legs are also long and nice,
like a those of a model's.
His eyes are bright like marbles,
like there's no trace of dust at all.
He's just a bit callous.
Maybe you like him?
What's wrong with you, Yuuki?
Are you trying to flatter me?
Ah...
What was that for?
Don't tell me...
I've done it before.
Oh no,
our shop needs to be run by virgins.
What do you mean by "virgins"?
I don't know either.
You girls only appear virgins.
But in actual fact...
It must be like this.
Oh you're mistaken.
I was referring to kissing,
just kissing.
What? Just kissing.
But how I envy you.
You girls aren't that young anymore.
If you haven't kissed before,
This is why we can't sell any of our set meals.
Is there any relation at all?
Let's stop talking about women.
You two should carefully choose guys
who have not been kissed before.
What does that mean?
I've said this before,
I've known a man with a similar background.
Although he's a extremely rich guy,
you can never tell what he's thinking.
As a result,
I was dumped to this company to work.
How cruel of him.
I...
What's wrong with her?
Eh... Tsukushi.
Sakurako.
My luck is no good at all.
Don't get so worked up
during a game of Mahjong.
You must act the world famous Domyoji
you are.
Shut up.
That is mine.
(A term used in Mahjong)
I don't think it's your luck.
It's that Makino Tsukushi girl that's bothering you.
Shut up and play.
But, what does she really like?
I spent so much money on her today,
but I couldn't get her to like it.
Yea, she's so annoying,
yet so aggresive.
Sometimes, I don't feel like bullying her.
Yea. Very tenacious.
That move of hers was very nice.
Just like Tsukasa's older sister.
Indeed.
Tsukasa, don't get too cocky.
Shut up. Hurry up and play.
Tsukasa, it's your turn.
Yea, I know.
But, Tsukasa, you're really easy to understand.
Yea. All your thoughts can be easily
seen from your expressions.
Why don't you just scare her?
Ah. Game for me.
Me too.
I won't play anymore.
Where are you going?
Going to fetch that hated person.
Was he talking about Rui?
Maybe...
He's calling Rui "that hated person"?
Maybe the layman is stronger than you think.
Yea.
But I doubt he'll come.
That Rui only knows how to hide in remote places.
If you bring him here, he'll be very uneasy.
I'm very sorry. Tsukushi-chan saved me, but I...
Don't worry so much about it.
Really, if they see you here,
there's going to be a lot of trouble.
But...
You don't have to force yourself
to be friends with me in school.
If you want to talk just drop me a call.
That fella won't go to such an extent.
Alright?
I'm really sorry for everything.
Ah...
This person should be... an Eitoku graduate.
Toudou Shizuka.
Heiress to the large Toudou corporation.
Also a very famous model worldwide.
Her aspiration is to become
an internation lawyer.
You seem to know a lot.
It's because of her that I chose Eitoku Gakuen.
Please choose your path in life.
Oh I see.
Ah...
What's wrong?
It's F4's...
Hanazawa Rui.
Wait here for a while.
What are you doing here?
Oh it's you again.
I know the time difference, it's 8 hours.
Do you know someone in France?
Or you're going on a holiday?
8 hours...
Ah... If I remember correctly,
the papers said that this person was from our school.
Have you seen her in person?
I really want to become like her.
You have something on your face.
It's something like a white grain.
That must be from what I ate just now.
(Dai Fuku)
"Dai Fuku"?
Oh... it's... nothing.
I'll be off.
Let's go.
The Red Paper!
The Red Paper has appeared again!
This time, the person who got it is
Sanjou Sakurako from class 3A.
Sakurako!
Are you okay?
I'm shocked.
Oh, how pitiful.
How unfortunate.
Why don't you people stop it.
Your main target should be me.
Don't get so high and mighty.
You're just a commoner after all.
So what if one has money, dumbass?
This has absolutely nothing to do with Sakurako.
Have you...
gotten it wrong?
Eh?
It was you who wanted to fight me.
As long you suffer,
it's the same thing.
Take this!
Are you all right? Domyoji-san.
I'm going to kill you!
Stop it!
That's enough.
Lick it clean.
Huh?
Then I'll let her go.
Lick it clean... Lick it clean...
You got it all wrong.
The time difference...
The time difference.
It should be 7 hours,
because they use summer time during October.
I'm sorry.
Forget it.
Right. Disperse now.
The show's over.
What...
So what if one has money, dumbass.
It should be 7 hours,
because they use summer time during October.
Hi there. Makino.
Good luck!
Good morning, Makino.
Tsuki. It's Tsuki.
(Tsuki is a nickname for Tsukushi)
Tsuki??
That spot isn't clean yet.
Make it cleaner.
It must be clear and spotless.
Yea, yea... Hurry up.
What??
Ah... Tsuki, my apologies for yesterday.
To be honest,
I thought Domyoji-san was pushing
things a bit too far yesterday.
Things wouldn't be good if
Hanazawa-san had not turned up.
Yea...
But really, I think he's been defeated by Tsuki.
It feels good to see Domyoji lose,
doesn't it?
Yea...
Right? Tsuki.
Party?
Miss Toudou's welcoming party,
they asked if I would like to go.
Isn't that great?
Yea, I guess.
Ever since you entered Eitoku Gakuen,
have you attended such a party before?
Nope, never once.
Then go for this one! I'm happy for you.
Everyone can get to know you better.
But, what kind of people
will go to the party?
It doesn't matter.
Oh yea, won't that handsome guy
with the long slender legs
and shining eyes go as well?
If anything happens,
he'll be there to help you.
No, I can't possibly hope for such things to happen.
Oh well, you should still go.
I'll accompany you.
No need.
We're all doomed.
We should save what as far as on food,
then we can afford to buy Tsukushi a party dress.
Well, at least Tsukushi get's to
attend one of those high class parties.
Sis can finally be one of the high class ladies.
Don't exaggerate so much.
Parties are nothing but gatherings which
you can wear jeans to.
You don't need to stinge on food specially
for this party.
No... We need to.
You'd never know when you meet your Prince Charming.
You're from Eitoku Gakuen,
so you need to dress nicely.
Yep. Tsukushi you must make all the necessary preparations.
What on earth are you talking about?
Only then would losing be winning.
So you're saying admitting defeat
is gaining victory?
You can't run away,
this is a good time to find a boyfriend.
You're right.
But really, you're very lucky.
What?
I'm only going to show my face, that's all.
Let's remember the love we had at "AMANDARI"
two years ago.
Why are you sitting so far from each other?
No particular reason.
No particular reason?
Today is supposed to be a happy day.
She will be arriving shortly.
Looking forward to it?
Smile a bit more.
I bet you didn't sleep much last night.
Aww shush.
But, why is Shizuka so late?
I'm back.
Shizuka.
Haven't seen you for a while.
You've become more handsome.
I've really missed you.
Me too.
Long time no see. I'm back.
I'm back, still doing well?
Of course.
Long time no see.
How have you been?
Good, of course.
Something doesn't seem right.
Anything happened that's bothering you?
Nothing much.
Well, Shizuka has become more
of a lady now.
Gotten yourself a French man yet?
Not yet.
Rui, how bout you?
Have you got a girlfriend yet?
Nope.
That won't do. You have to experience
the love and beauty of companionship.
You really were beautiful.
You appeared in a magazine all dressed up.
Rui, Shizuka's standards are too high.
Are you being sour about that?
No such thing.
I don't think it changes anything
if she dressed up or not.
Shizuka is different from the other models.
Rui keeps praising me
I really like this kind of Rui.
Thanks
W... Wow...
Beautiful...
Makino-san, you're really late.
Why are you dressed like that?
Why didn't you wear a nightgown?
But... Didn't you say I can dress
however I like?
Oh that... We were just joking.
You even wore a flower.
Well, your clothes really aren't that important.
Cheer up.
F4 has arrived!
So handsome...
You were... Shizuka-san's high school classmate?
No... I'm...
That's... very nice, very unique.
Really?
She really is very unique.
She's famous for that in school.
And, she even slept with others
5 times.
I see...
So it was you people who wrote those words.
What are you saying?
How could you even suspect your friends?
Dissappointing.
Look who's dissapointing.
What have I done to you?
You're an eyesore.
Always staring perversely at Hanazawa.
In order to be women worthy of F4,
we had to spend large amounts of time and money.
We're not on the same level as you.
Furthermore,
how can someone like you come to our school?
If you're poor,
you should have just quit.
It doesn't concern you.
Please leave now...
If you don't want to be laughed at
by your favourite Hanazawa-san.
But I'm sure Hanazawa-san won't even
bother about girls like her.
That's because he's already...
Do you get it?
Hanazawa already has a beautiful woman...
like Todou Shizuka.
If you get it, then get out of here.
Oh I'm sorry, it slipped.
Besides, you're already such an eyesore.
This is supposed to be a happy occasion for Shizuka-san.
You still don't understand the
situation you're in.
If you don't return home soon,
you'll going to catch a cold.
Hurry up and go.
You wet... slut.
You seem a bit wet.
Don't you have a handerchief?
I don't.
My my... Makino-san can't even afford a handerchief.
Thank you.
What an interesting welcoming ceremony.
Shizuka-san.
Long time no see.
You're really beautiful today.
I really thank you for coming
to this party.
I really appreciate it.
Erm... Why did you help me?
Rui mentioned a very interesting girl.
I knew it was you the moment
I saw you.
How?
But still, I'm quite surprised.
Rui has never had any interest in a girl,
yet he offered his help to you.
Maybe, Rui has already fallen for you.
It can't be.
It'll never happen.
Because...
What do you think about this pair of shoes?
This pair must be very expensive.
I don't need it.
In Paris,
they say girls should wear shoes that...
make them feel like they're flying.
They will bring us to many wonderful places.
Don't you feel it's beautiful?
It really is beautiful.
You're very pretty.
Have you lost your mind?
How can I smile about this?
Hey,
what madness has caused you to like this girl?
This girl has gotten The Red Pape beforer.
You're still as pushy as ever.
Tsukasan-san, don't you think she's pretty?
Even if you're Shizuka,
I do not permit you to speak to me like that.
Well then I...
will not forgive those who speak to Shizuka
in that way.
Hey wait a minute!
It can't be...
Doesn't look to bad...
You still consider yourself a man?
I beg of you Shizuka-san.
Go back.
That guy really seems to
like Tsukushi-chan.
I really like you.
Bye bye... Hanazawa Rui...