Hurry up and leave...
Looks like you've gotten yourself wet...
Thank you.
You're very pretty.
What madness has caused you to like this girl?
This girl has gotten The Red Paper before.
Wait a minute!
They've kissed!
Don't say it so loudly.
Good for you, Tsukushi!
It's not good at all,
in fact it's horrible.
Don't you like him a lot?
How can I like her?
You didn't kiss Hanazawa Rui?
It was so horrible.
But then,
why would someone who considers you
his enemy, kiss you?
That's why I think you two make the perfect pair.
You've got to be kidding!
No way that's going to happen.
Then, how is it that you two kissed
when both of you fell together?
Are you saying that I originally intended
to kiss that slut?
The probability of that is high.
Hey...
How is that so?
Your first kiss is was taken by your most hated person on earth.
The two of you are fated to be together.
That can't be true...
Your first kiss was taken by the man
you hated the most,
Hang on, old lady.
and it was right in front of the person
whom you liked the most.
Why are you so interested in this?
So...
What was the feeling of your first kiss like?
It is not the first kiss.
But if I haven't gotten it wrong,
it indeed was your first kiss.
No it isn't!
As usual,
what Tsukasa does is different from other people.
You people don't completely understand me
When was it?
Eh?
If yesterday wasn't your first kiss,
then when was it?
Huh?
So that...
yesterday?
Sigh...
I can never go back to the emergency staircase.
Well I think it's a good opportunity.
Why don't you just go along with the flow?
Don't you think so?
Eh??
Even if that happened,
but I really liked you,
the only person in my heart would still be you.
What are you saying?
Firstly,
he already has Shizuka-san.
You can't just give up like this,
and not tell him what your heart says.
Why don't you tell him your true feelings for him.
Maybe there's still a chance...
You might be right there...
I had this feeling that we could be together.
You're very pretty.
Pretty...
He said I was very pretty.
Eh?
Well... Hanazawa Rui
saw my new clothes
and said I was very pretty.
You're not kidding?
Tsukushi's Prince Charming?
Hanazawa Rui really said that?
I can't just forget about what
happened with Rui.
Don't be like this.
Just forgive him this time.
If he apologises to me,
then I'll forgive him.
Well, it's clear that we all feel lonely
when Rui isn't around.
Nonsense!
It doesn't make a difference
if Rui was here or not.
Don't be so direct when you want to say something
Quickly make up with Tsukasa.
Lately,
he's been very touchy.
Perhaps he really is like that.
But what made me mad
were the rude things he said to you.
But...
You weren't very happy either
when Tsukasa and Tsukushi kissed.
Eh?
You like her a bit.
I know that.
See you.
This is like a fight where
both sides are unwilling to give in.
You guys are really stubborn.
Even I cannot compare.
Eh?
Isn't that Makino Tsukushi?
What?
We must stop here, Tsukasa.
Now's the chance...
Eh?
Stop playing a fool.
Don't stop the car.
Checkmate!
Yes!
You must treat her well.
Then I won't have any worries
about taking care of her.
How troublesome...
Eh?
You already know my true feelings
Yet you insist that I go for someone else.
Rui...
You get it, right?
What are you saying, "having no worries
about taking care of her".
I really don't get it.
Rui!
Oh dear.
Rui,
Wait a minute.
Rui!
I...
That's why I came back from France.
It's because I wanted to live
by my own means.
So I decided to come back from France.
To realise my dream of becoming
an international lawyer.
To live up to the name of Toudou.
I don't want to rely on the wealth
that I can inherit from the Toudou family.
But to live in France
as an ordinary person.
Hana Yori Dango - Boys Over Flowers
Episode 3
[Character] ** [Actor]
Makino Tsukushi ** Inoue Mao
Domyoji Tsukasa ** Matsumoto Jun
Hanazawa Rui ** Oguri Shun
Nishikado Sojiro ** Matsuda Shota
Mimasaka Akira ** Abe Tsuyoshi
Timing and Translation ** Backalley
Editor and Release ** furransu
Next is...
"Senzai ichiguu"
(A fated meeting that occurs once in a thousand years.)
Yea,
that will definitely come out in the next exam.
"Senzai ichiguu"?
I've got it!
It means, when doing the washing,
one should use one full cup of detergent.
("Sentaku" is the washing of clothes,
"Senzai" is detergent,
"Ichi" is one)
That's it, right?
Right...
Senzai... Ichi... Guu... - One cup of washing detergent
("Senzai" is detegent,
"Ichi" is one)
Wrong!
Then what's the right answer?
An opportunity that comes once
in a thousand years.
Oh that's it.
For example...
There's someone you really like
but he already has a girlfriend.
But then suddenly, he decides to break up with her,
and becomes available again.
That would be a "Senzai Ichiguu" chance.
So it's used like that.
So that's how it is.
I'm full already.
Tsukushi, why don't you eat another bowl?
Well...
My stomach is already very full.
Then, I'm done eating as well.
The dishes are still hot, why leave now?
I still feel bloated.
My stomach feels like it is inside out.
Well said, kid.
You made a joke, just like me.
Your level has just gone up.
We shouldn't joke about love relationships.
What?
She's been acting weird
ever since she came back from the party.
Maybe... She's already in a relationship
with one of those rich guys.
So it's our family status,
that causing her to be uneasy about it.
Is that for real?
That girl is really serious about
dating one of those rich guys?
Well isn't that a "Senzai ichiguu" chance?
(A fated meeting that occurs once in a thousand years.)
We're going to be rich!!
"Senzai ichiguu"...
Sanjou Sakurako doesn't even dare to come to school
You really aren't afraid of anything.
Yeaa...
Huh?
It's rumoured that she has left the school.
Eh?
It really is your fault that she became like this.
And you still dare to come to school
as if nothing happened.
They're right about me not wanting to go to school.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
No.
Tsukushi-chan,
I heard that you kissed Doumyoji at the party.
Is that true?
What kiss?
It was an accident.
Don't worry.
He won't bother you again.
Sakurako-san
I'll always be by your side.
You can always look me up
if you feel lonely or troubled.
See you.
Oh goodness.
If I don't hurry...
This is horrible.
Oh!
It's you.
What a coincidence.
If you stop the car there,
it will block the pedestrians.
I heard that you've been skipping classes.
It's none of your business.
Huh?
Aren't you skipping classes as well?
I'm going for my classes now.
Oh? Well then...
I'm going back.
Hey hey...
The last time you kissed me
be sure not to fall in love with me.
Huh??
Have you lost your mind?
I really don't get you.
Get in.
What?
I'll give you a lift to school, so get in.
W... Wait...
Let me go!
This is unbelievable!
What are you saying, you...
Stop there!!
That girl runs really fast...
Don't be such an idiot!
It can't be...
What?
Wh... What?
It hurts, sis!
Sister?
Hi there.
Why is Makino Tsukushi with Ms Tsubaki?
You can always contact me at this address.
Yes
Los Angeles??
If Tsukushi-san calls me,
I'll fly back immediately.
Fly back...
In a private jet.
You're serious about flying back.
I'm stopping over in Japan for a while.
If I have time, I'll have a meal with you.
Umm...
Why are you so nice to me?
That idiot of a brother seems to be giving you some trouble.
Then again,
Two people can really have similar tastes.
Huh?
You and I...
My my...
You're as innocent as Tsukasa.
Perhaps he really likes you, Tsukushi-chan.
Hmm?
Well then, see you. Look me up anytime.
Oh...
Okay.
Thank you very much.
So cool...
Ah! So cool!!!
Madam.
(Literally, Madam Representative)
Ms Tsubaki has returned today.
Tsubaki?
Yes, that would be the older sister.
If she has any private matters,
Nishida,
prepare his retirement grant and lump sum pay.
Yes ma'am.
Do it by today.
Madam!
Please wait a minute!!
Please wait!
Let me go!
The meeting will now begin,
for the temporary board of directors
of the Doumyoji Group.
Madam.
This concerns the remaining issues we have
regarding our restaurant.
Yes, it was caused by the English.
At the moment, the situation is under control.
If we continue this,
everyone will get wind of this.
And once the news is out,
it will have a very adverse effect on the Doumyoji Group.
**Doumyoji Group raises profits by 25% this week.**
**Issue brings about huge criticism**
She hasn't changed a bit.
Mom still does whatever she wants to do.
What!?
Don't just come in as you like.
My apologies about just now.
Why have you come back?
My husband has some things to settle here.
What problems has that fool run into now?
No one calls his brother-in-law a fool.
Why do you still stick to someone you don't like?
I'm very happy now, I've gotten used to it.
It's clear you don't want to get married.
Eh? When has it been like that?
Which means, you actually want me to leave him
and return home
Maybe you just want to live with your sis again?
Don't say such disgusting things.
Well,
how long are you staying?
About a week.
Don't look so lonely, I'll be back real soon.
It doesn't really matter if you're back or not.
Well, Tsukasa-san
Do you like that girl?
Huh?
I'm talking about that girl, Tsukushi-chan,
whom you were chasing
What are you saying all of a sudden?
It won't happen.
What?
If you're not a little more gentle to her,
she'll definitely leave you.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
It doesn't concern you anyway.
If you have any questions about relationships,
you can always ask me.
Sis.
Hey look at this.
It's Shizuka-chan.
Oh.
Eh? Shizuka-chan...
When did she start studying overseas?
Tomorrow,
I definitely want to see him.
Yes.
Why isn't he here?
I really want to meet him again!
It can't be...
Eh...
Who do you want to meet again?
Eh?
Umm.. Umm...
Oh yeah... Umm...
It's been a while.
Well... This...
Shizuka-san.
She's busy with a lot of things
before she returns to France.
She really...
wants to go back to France.
Are you alright with that?
Well I think...
She's the type that doesn't really care
about what others think.
If she wants to do something,
nothing can stop her.
But then,
if you don't do something...
we won't be able to see her again.
Want to see her?
Eh?
Do you want to see Shizuka again?
Well, no...
Just now you mentioned...
seeing Shizuka again?
Ah...
That's right.
You've said that you really admire Shizuka.
**Toudou**
Miss.
Hanazawa Rui is here to see you.
Ah!
Good evening.
She wants to thank you
about what happeend at the party.
There's no need for that.
Your mom?
She still angry?
She agreed for the time being.
But she's still reluctant to completely let go.
I see...
I'll go say "Hi" to your mom.
It's a bit messy,
but come in.
You're... Already preparing to leave.
Although there's still a week left,
it's better to prepare in advance.
A week left...?
Today, I went to school to request
for my withdrawal.
Then... You won't be coming back?
Yea.
That's what I've decided.
Can you tell?
That's F4 and I.
The one on the left,
that's Rui and I when we were young.
Isn't it cute?
That kind of smile,
I've never seen it before.
He really...
really liked her...
right from the start.
Please don't go back to France.
What are you saying?
For Hanazawa Rui,
I want you to stay in Japan.
He's always around the emergency staircase,
always hoping that Shizuka-san would return.
Everytime he talks about Shizuka-san,
his face will be lit with a warm smile.
But...
Once Shizuka-san decided to leave for France,
he's stopped going there.
He's dissappeared for a while.
And then comes back with such a sad face.
If Shizuka-san returns to France,
Hanazawa Rui will...
not be his true self.
That is why,
I'm asking that you stay in Japan.
I'm sorry,
I cannot do that.
I'm begging you Shizuka-san.
I know that by doing this, it is hard for you.
I know that what I'm doing is very foolish.
Look up at me.
Well for me,
the decisions I make
are just like when buying something overseas.
If I let the chance go and not buy it back,
I won't be able to buy it again.
People will then think
that it's a good chance to buy it,
and continue to live on.
But then,
I...
don't want to be one of those people,
even though I might have regrets later on.
I want to be myself,
living as I choose to live.
I hope you understand.
I understand.
I've said things I shouldn't have, sorry.
No not that.
I'm happy, really.
About Rui,
please take care of him.
I'm really sorry.
What are you doing?
Eh?
What was that all about just now?
Who asked you to do that?
I didn't bring you here to do that kind of thing.
Was it for me?
What difference does it make?
Mind your own business.
"Mind you own business"?
What are you thinking?
Begging in a place like that.
I...
Why are you doing that?
I really can't believe it.
You look so sad and pitiful.
You won't be able to see her again.
This is none of your business.
Go back.
Go back!
Shizuka.
About what happened at the party...
I understand.
We give you our best wishes.
I give you guys my best wishes as well.
Help me say goodbye to Rui.
See you.
Well, I'll be off.
Good luck. Have a safe trip.
Thank you.
Good bye.
Shizuka-san!
You came.
I'm very sorry I'm late.
Hanazawa Rui?
He didn't come.
He really is a small kid.
Oh yes.
Here, these are for you?
This pair really looks good on you.
But...
You must let them bring you to wonderful places.
I'll be working hard too.
See you.
See you!
Goodbye everyone.
Good luck!
Rui!
What have you been doing?
When did you arrive?
An hour ago.
Then why didn't you come here?
I've been watching you guys.
What an idiot.
Go after her!
If you like her,
you have to go after her, right?
Are you just going to be satisfied watching?
Do you still consider yourself a man?
I'll go.
Eh?
I'll be leaving for France
as well.
Rui
You kidding.
Makino.
Well I...
really like your determination.
That's what I really lack.
I finally realised that
I can't continue like this.
Thank you.
Wait a minute, Rui!
Are you really leaving?
Yes.
Why??
Why didn't you come to us to talk about it?
I'm sorry...
Haven't we been together all this while?
Why do you suddenly want to leave us?
Why??
Where did you suddenly get the idea from?
Tsukasa. About last time...
It doesn't matter any more.
Say,
do you really want to go?
Rui
Stop playing with us.
If you really are leaving,
we won't have you around anymore.
Does it really not matter to you?
Rui!
Take care,
Tsukasa.
In Paris...
If you meet any bad people in Paris
tell me immediately.
The three of us will fly there to help.
Ya...
You got it?
Thank you. I'll be off.
Tsukasa.
Take it.
Rui!
Bye bye...
Hanazawa Rui.
Rui!!
Good luck!
Rui! Take care!
Rui!
My opinion of him has changed a little.
That's the bond between men.
Well that guy is full of surprises.
Old lady...
Of all the men I've met before,
some put on a "tiger mask".
It has begun...
They appear very frightening, and violent.
But those men are actually soft-hearted.
He's actually sending whatever money they can spare
back home to help out in the finances.
Didn't you say they have "tiger masks"?
Well he...
cannot allow his true lonely self
to be seen by others.
At that time,
the only person who could understand him well
would be me alone.
I really have no idea what she's talking about.
I never got to it after all.
To Rui
How's Paris?
How are you?
Do you...
like...
Makino Tsukushi?
What are you writing?
Maybe you're writing a love letter!
Of course not!
Didn't I say not to come in as you like?
Hey wait...
"Kazu"??
(He wrote "Kazu" instead of "Rui", they look alike)
It's "Rui", idiot.
Don't tell me you can't even recognise simple Kanji.
I think it's better if I write it for you.
Why?
How do I convey my personal feelings to him if you write it?
Tsukasa,
what do you have left to say to him?
That guy...
going to France to go after Shizuka.
Oh... So that's how it was.
He's done well, that Rui.
Are you kidding?
He even left his best friends behind.
When you love, you wish to do things for it.
You wish to sacrifice for it.
You wish to serve for it.
Huh?
That's from Hemingway's short story.
(pg 72, A Farewell to Arms by Ernest Hemingway)
When you truly love someone,
you will understand what I said.
But until then, Tsukasa,
you must treasure the person
whom you really like.
You must remember,
you musn't be too fast in relationships. And...
(Tsukasa interprets what his sister says wrongly,
you'll see later)
you can't just buy a person's heart with money.
In order to be loved,
you must first give your love.
My goodness, sis.
I now...
feel like lightning has struck me.
(Tsukasa's Japanese fails)
What "lightning has struck me"?
Your choice of words is wrong again.
I need to completely change my perception.
How can perception be changed...
You really are great, sis.
Thanks a lot!
When you leave the country tomorrow,
be sure to come back safely.
What a wonderful suggestion.
The next time you come back
I'll definitely have something for you to see.
Is it okay, just leaving like this?
OK! OK!
Thank you for the food.
Such a pity that Rui-san is gone.
Shizuka-san won't be returning too.
Tsubaki-san is also leaving soon.
It seems like those who have been defending you
have all gone.
If you want to fight, go ahead.
Since when have I depended on anyone else?
Don't be so quick to say...
Ah... I've been accidentally pushed over
by Doumyoji-sama...
Shut up,
you ugly witch.
How cruel.
Yuriko...
What?
Woah...
Oh my... I must go one round.
(The Japanese words actually translate to
"I musn't be too fast")
Eh?
Sunday, 1pm at the open area
at "Ebisu Garden Place" near the clock.
Why? Why is the wealthy Doumyoji-sama
going out with a girl like her?
Even I have not heard of such a thing happening...
Which means, he wants to date her...
Umm...
Huh?
What is it?!
About just now...
What about it?
I don't know nothing, stupid.
Anyway,
Hemingway
Heming...?
You should really read more.
I think I'm a little early.
Well then, if she doesn't come 5 minutes before 1pm,
I'll show her...
Isn't it today? Are you sure it's okay to not go?
Why must I pitifully spend my Sunday
with a guy like him?
If you don't go, he might seriously take revenge.
That's true...
If you go, it's hell. If you don't go, it's still hell.
Well I'm already in a fight with him,
he can wait all he wants.
Ah... That's pretty!
Sorry.
I'm late.
I'm going to beat her up.
Thanks for the food!
Wait a minute...
How's it?
How 'bout that...
Oh, so pretty!
What kind of toy is that?
I think it should be "tiger mask".
Oh, how cute.
Oh yea, that old lady mentioned before...
Men with a "tiger mask" aren't able to show
their true, lonely, self to other people.
Rui!
I'm sorry, Yuuki.
Wait a minute! Tsukushi!
Where are you going?
Hemingway
Sunday, 1pm at the open area
at "Ebisu Garden Place" near the clock.
He wants to date me?
It can't be true.
It can never happen.
It's already so late,
he'll definitely not be there.
He won't be...
Unbelievable...
Why?
This is the girl I like.
Go check on what Tsukasa is doing.
You're pretty, let's go.
What's this about?
You must be serious about this, Tsukushi.
What are you doing?
I believed you...