Makino and I are going out.
Eh?!
There's always a limit to the extent of a joke.
She's finally starting to make her move, huh?
Here is 300 million.
With this, it's genuinely my turn now, huh?
I would like Tsukushi-san to give Tsukasa up completely.
Take your money, and please go home.
The reason why I can be here right now,
it's because of Hanazawa Rui.
Here, take it.
Tsukasa seems to be really serious about you, Tsukushi-chan.
But if there's even a bit of a chance,
I will fully support the both of you.
Let's have a double-date tomorrow.
Double-date?!
When I said I love you, I really am serious.
I will be waiting, until you can give me a definite answer.
Honestly the girl with you is a bimyou (weird, strange)?
I'll introduce you to better women.
Makino is a bimyou?
What are you doing?! Stop!
The reason you hit Nakatsuka-kun.  Explain it to me!
I'm not saying.
Yuuki is feeling really sad because of you, you know!
I wonder why I've never fallen in love with you, Makino,
until now..
Just a minute is fine.
Let me stay like this.
Oh...
So that's how it is?
Is that your answer to me?
I completely understand.
Domyouji!
He's always jumping to conclusions.
Jumping to conclusions, huh?
Wait... Hanazawa Rui!
Domyouji-san.
Tsukasa, what are you doing?
Tsukasa.
Akira... Soujiro...
From today onwards, do not speak to Rui.
What are you saying?
This guy is no longer our childhood friend or anything.
He's just a traitor.
Domyouji!
Rui.
You will no longer be part of F4.
You are no longer a friend..
Calm down.
What happened, Rui?
Wait...! Why must Rui leave?
You hit people just because your pissed.
You renounce your own friend.
I hate that part of you.
Tsukasa.
The worst.
F4 is breaking up...?
It's all because of that vulgar peasant.
What did you say?
It's okay.
I will protect you.
Please...
I cannot accept something like this.
But, I will help you.
What an untrustworthy girl.
But I love it.
Are you still concerned... regarding Tsukasa?
Concerned? I'm just pissed.
Makino.
Eh?
Shall we go somewhere? Just the two of us?
Being all serious about Makino Tsukushi, renouncing Rui..
Are you listening, Tsukasa?
Shut it, Akira.
Are you my mother-in-law?
Huh? It's for your sake that..
Tsukasa, I know what Rui did was pretty awful, but..
He also has a lot of troubles.
Okay? At least look at it.
What's with you?
I'm just asking that you consider Rui's feelings...!
Soujiro.
I can't stand this, I'm going.
Soujiro!
After that, Nakatsuka-kun never contacted me again.
I'm sorry, truly sorry.
Those monkeys kinda look like Domyouji.
Where did you go?
I'm going home!
I'm so pissed, I can't stand it!
It's my fault for bringing Domyouji with us.
Ahh... That guy really... What he did was just too much...
Plus he's trying to look as if he's the one who was hurt.
It's just sick! He's so selfish, and foolish. A weird hair...
Tsukushi's so lucky.
Eh?!
No matter where you fall, you'll always "Get" a cute guy.
That has nothing to do with Domyouji.
Nito wo ou mono itto mo ezu
(When you try to make two things yours, you
won't be able to get even one)
I got it!
The "knitted thing" is the King's, so the thread should not be burned.
("Nito": knit, "Ou Mono": The King's,
"itto": thread, "mo ezu": to burn)
Nope...
It means that you can't chase after two things,
otherwise you'll end up with nothing.
Oh, so that...
Susumu...
Wh... What?
Will you be able to rise above in society next time?
What's with you, Papa?
Tsukushi...
Yes.
Susumu...
Mama...
Yes.
You listen here... Papa... Papa...
well... has been promoted to chief clerk!
Congratulations, Papa!
Congratulations! Congratulations!
It's because I put my heart into my job, working hard at it,
and that is how I have achieved what I now am.
Is that so...!
That means, Tsukushi has finally become
a kakarichou reijou (Chief Clerk Honorable Daughter)!
There's no Japanese term like that!
This also means, your status is equal to Domyouji-san.
Tsukushi, don't look anywhere else..
Earnestly pursue Domyouji-san!
Tama No Koshi (Marrying into money)!
I'm off!
Where are you going all dolled up?
That's none of your business!
Let me pass. I'm off on a date with Hanazawa Rui.
What was that for?!
Apologise now. I'm willing to forgive you.
Huh?
What I mean, is that I'm giving you one last chance.
Stay away from Rui.
Why are you saying this to me?
Shut up! Whatever I say is ABSOLUTE!
I've had enough of being thrown around by your whims!
Hana Yori Dango - Boys Over Flowers
Episode 7
[Character] ** [Actor]
Makino Tsukushi ** Inoue Mao
Domyouji Tsukasa ** Matsumoto Jun
Hanazawa Rui ** Oguri Shun
Nishikado Soujiro ** Matsuda Shota
Mimasaka Akira ** Abe Tsuyoshi
Timing and Translation ** Backalley
Timing and Translation ** mhaellix
Editing and Release ** furransu
I've had enough of being thrown around by your whims!
Why can't you get it?
I'm so pissed..
But, meeting up in a bookstore is just like Hanazawa Rui.
<Toudou Shizuka-san is rumoured to become the bride of
future French President J.P. Maiyor>
No way...
I've never done anything for her.
Oh no. If Hanazawa Rui were to find out about this...
Sorry to have you wait.
What's wrong?
No... Nothing...
Well! Let's go?
I need to buy something.
Ah... I'm thirsty... Tea! You want tea?
Let's go... Off to drink tea...
Here, let's go in.
What about Makino Tsukushi?
Didn't she go out on a date with Hanazawa Rui?
Huh?!
Rui has completely gone out of his mind...
Makino is Makino, too.. What is she doing,
being being "fura fura" (indecisive).
Hey... please stop bad-talking Tsukushi.
Wow, you're always thinking about your friends...
I seriously can't stand this anymore.
I have a tea-ceremony. I'm going home.
Soujiro!
Yuuki, do watch out. Sometimes people just hate busybodies.
Hey!
Each and every one of them..
Akira-kun!
Hanazawa Rui, what did you order?
Ginger Ale.
Oh... Ginger Ale...
Did you know, Ginger Ale's true form is actually shouga (ginger).
I was so shocked when I found out..
It's like a vegetable.. plus it's like medicine..
Really?
Yeah... But maybe not...
You've been on a date with Tsukasa, right?
I don't think you call that a date.
Going places with him is like "Tour to Hell".
"Tour to Hell"?
I went out with him and some friends,
and he started hitting my friend's boyfriend.
On another date, we took the elevator,
and we were stuck in there until morning.
It's unbelievable.
Then that guy suddenly runs a fever and collapses..
In a place like this... What are you thinking?
To tell you the truth, nothing good happens when I'm with that guy..
Excuse me...
I'll ask them to get the menu.
Why did I suddenly remember him?
I finally get to be on a date with Hanazawa Rui.
You seem to be going through a lot of trouble.
You've gotten yourself wet.
Thank you.
Right, this should be better.
Eh?
Atleast lock the door..
YAAARGH!!
Domyouji-san! What a coincidence!
Are you out for a walk?
You... What kind of nerve do you have, talking to me and all.
I'm glad. You still remember me.
How could I forget?
Would you like to go for tea?
Don't touch me!
Are you scared of persistent women?
YOU! Don't push it...
You're a man who still has lingering affections..
Why don't you give up while it's still early?
Makino Tsukushi chose Hanazawa Rui on her own.
You...
Do you want me to completely deface you?
As you wish.
Huh?
This face was bought because of you anyway.
You can do as you wish. It's much better than
you ignoring me.
Why don't you stop crying, already?
This isn't something you should be worried about.
What part of it?!
You saw me when I was on the toilet...
what more... with my PANTIES DOWN...
You're really funny, aren't you?
It's been so long since I've laughed like this.
You...
You're pretty twisted.
The way you're looking at me, it's pretty creepy.
Sorry for making you wait.
Tsukushi-chan, you look really cute, today!
Dating someone you've always loved
Would make you give it your best!
What's up with you?
Hey, Rui!
What do you mean by this?
You know that Shizuka is getting engaged, right?
How can you say that, insensitive jerk?
How can you hurt people so easily like it's nothing to you?
I was doing it for your-
Besides, what's up with you?! Following me all the way here..
How about you? You're ambushing me everywhere I'm headed to.
Huh?! Who would want to do that?
What's up with that "hira hira"(fluttering around) skirt?
Do you think it looks good on you?
Leave me alone! I didn't wear it for you to look at!
It's sickening.
Even if I don't want to see it, it has entered my sight already.
What's with you? Which great one are you supposed to be?
"The Great I Am"
The worst!
You're the worst! You stupid sh*tty woman!
What's that?! You natural kuro kuro (curly) hair!
K-k-kuro kuro hair?!?! I'm gonna kill you!
Ah, ah, ah~
And it was such a fun date that I've been waiting for..
but thanks to you it's completely destroyed!
Let's go Hanazawa Rui.
Hmph
Are you alright?
SCRAM!
Eh?
You were purposefully following me around, right?
Hurry up and scram.
I will never give up, you know.
Someday, for sure..
I will show you that I can chase Makino Tsukushi
away from your heart.
Why..
can't he think of anyone but himself?
Selfishly causing trouble..
Letting people go round and round..
Everyone will be thankful for you..
Huh?
There once was a man that I loved..
Above everything else,
he loved to see happiness upon other people's faces..
"To bring happiness to all the children of the whole world.."
When winter comes he stuffs a white sack with presents..
Wearing a red suit and going on his journey..
Santa?
And for that man, he pulled the sleigh..
Reindeer?
Even when he's pulling such a heavy sled..
it's the man in red who always gets the leading part..
but
He who is foolishly honest about undertaking such a plain role..
For me, he's the one who shines the brightest!
Deep inside their hearts, everyone is actually thankful for those kind of men..
"I'm glad you are here with me.." Right?
[Compose a message]
Nakatsuka-kun, what happened? Please e-mail -
Everything went well.
Is that so?
Excuse me.
Nishida.
Yes.
For safety's sake..
put the contingency plan into action..
Understood.
I already knew about Shizuka.
Eh?
When I was in Paris, she was quite popular already..
I see..
Thank you.
You've always been trying to hide it from me, right?
Uh, no.. I wasn't really..
Oh man..
Huh?
That cute part of you..
Tsukasa..
noticed it far more earlier than I did..
Are you sure that you're truly choosing Hanazawa Rui?
When I was in pain,
Hanazawa Rui has always saved me..
That's why..
this time I want to be his strength..
Is that okay?
Your reason just sounds like a charity case.
It's not charity at all..
From the very beginning,
The one that I've always always loved the most..
is Hanazawa Rui.
Fine, fine..
Hey, Tsukushi.
Can you go with me somewhere?
This is where I first met Nakatsuka-kun.
Hey, you make it sound like it's a Sanctuary of Memories..
He was flirting, right?
Hey, you know what..
I don't think he deserves you-
Naka-
Sorry to keep you waiting!
She's at it again, what a drag!
What? Girlfriend?
It's not like that..
It's a stalker, just a stalker..
So stubborn..
Is that so?
Then, where are you taking me today?
For now, why don't we get something to eat, then watch a movie?
then after that...
After that?
Who is she? Someone you know?
Don't know her.
But maybe I might've seen this face before?
Yuuki!
Why don't you run after her and console her?
I will NEVER forgive you!
Yuuki-chan?
She already left for the day..
If she contacts you, please let me know immediately.
She's really the type that I'm not good at..
What's wrong?
B-b-bitter..
Isn't it?
I was still a kid the first time I drank this..
I thought this is not for human beings to drink..
but,
the truth is, this bitterness is good..
Knowing that, I walked down "The Way of Tea".
Love is the same..
With a painful.. and bitter love, people will grow.
Yuuki-chan, this time you needed this.
So next time you won't make the same mistake, right?
Yes.
Okay!
Let's go now. I'll just change, okay?
It's okay.
I can go home by myself.
That's not it.
Today, I'm really all messed up.
Eh?
What I mean is..
Vengeance game!
Vengeance?
Is it really okay if everything remains this way?
If it's meddlesome preaching, I'm not listening.
Is it really okay for the F4 to break apart this way?
Do you want me to throw you out?!
Think very well..
Yuuki..
Where are you, Yuuki?
Why don't we get something to eat, then watch a movie?
Movie, huh?
Why him?
Are you gonna beat him up?
As if.
I'm going to teach him just what a great guy really is.
No way!
It's F4's Nishikado-san!
No way..
Nishikado Soujiro?
Huh?
Who's that?
Your girlfriend is really pretty that it caught my attention.
Is that so?
What's up with you, teme (you, rude)?
Wanna go somewhere else?
Let's go.. Let's go.. Let's go!
Hey, let's go.
What's with you?
Don't get me wrong just because I was playing with you a little..
Have it your way!
My girlfriend before you was much better.
Oh, really?
Bye, bye!
Hey, where are we going?
Sorry.  Don't want to, after all.
Right now, I already have a true love.
Yuuki..
Huh?
Yuuki-chan, someone you know?
Don't know him..
But maybe I might've seen this face before.
What's going on?
If you ever make my woman cry again,
I will drag and pull out your internal organs.
Meddling, too.
It's not bad after all, huh?
Ah, you..
I get it.
It's that guy, Domyouji's harrasment, right?
I said it out of kindness.
Instead of a bimyou woman like you,
I'll introduce you to much better women.
The reason you hit Nakatsuka-kun. Explain it to me!
I'm not telling.
Can't even commit one unfaithful act. He's really a weak man.
Well, a bimyou woman like you is just perfect for him.
Wait a minute.
Huh?
I'm sorry for being a bimyou woman.
Domyouji is..
not a person that a trash like you can ever understand!!
Yes.
Akira.
I'm going to be meeting up with Rui.
He told me to go to Shizuka's billboard.
That bastard..
he's already been renounced, and he still calls me out.
Hey, Tsukasa.  Calm down!
I'm going to kill him.
Oi, Tsukasa!
Even you never cools down. What now?
Coz, who knows what Tsukasa will do to Rui.
Oh man, what an awfully busy day..
Ah!
'Sup, Rui?
How was it?
The date with Makino.
Yeah, it was fun!
Really?
That kind of commoner's date..
someone of my level will never be able to last it..
I see.
Rui had fun, huh?
That's great.
Really great!
That kind of woman. I'll attach seaweed and deliver her to you.
(Tsukasa: nori tsuke te - attach nori)
It's Noshi, you know?
(correct:  noshi wo tsukeru - make a gift out of her)
Barbequed Seafood.
Can you not refer to her like you own her?
Huh?
Whichever way you say it, she's mine, right?
Earlier, it was really bad.
Makino insisted that "I don't want to go home"
If I kiss her, I thought she'd go home, but..
On the contrary, after this and that, she started wanting more..
This and that?
Hey, Rui.
That girl,
She's usually brave and courageous..
At times like that, she acts just like a girl.
Rui, stop it!
At times like that..?
Ah-
It's alright, Tsukasa..
After all, I didn't do anything.
Coz', it's Makino, you know?
I can't do something that ridiculous.
What do you think you're doing?
You!
- Calm down.
- Shut up!
Right now, my bowels are burning.
(Tsukasa: harawata ga nikkorogatte n dayo)
It's "I'm infuriated inside"
(Correct:  harawata ga niekurikaetteru)
I'm tired of listening to a meddling bastard!
Tsukasa, stop it!
Who's fault do you think it is that I'm being meddlesome!
What's the point of you joining in?
Shut up!
Why don't you just stand back and drink tea!
Domyouji..
I'm sorry..
I was never able to understood you..
Not really knowing anything and misunderstanding..
I wounded you, Domyouji..
You were incomplex, selfish and violent but..
You were honest with me..
and you acted like I was precious..
Right now, it might be too late..
but..
Just this, I want to be able to tell you.
I'm sorry.
I was never able to notice your kindness..
Childhood friend or whatever..
Any guy who hurts Makino..
will never get away from me..
You should've said that way in the beginning.
Huh?!!
It was a lie, everything was..
Because of you, Tsukasa,
I'm not able to eat apples anymore. Revenge.
What?
Are you serious?
Rui.
Teme.
Makino's..
stories were all about you, Tsukasa.
That's great, Tsukasa.
Shut up.
You're happy, aren't you?
Here.
Akira's meddlesome action..
has finally been useful. Only once after ten years..
Shut up!
See, if you try, you can do it..
Let me just say this, but..
if something happens between you and Makino..
I will not hold back, okay?
That's fine!
What are you doing?
Nothing really.
What happened?
Hhmm..
I fell..
Eh?
Thank you for yesterday..
Me too, I had so much fun!
Let's go on a date again ,okay?
This Sunday?
Uh, I can't wait that long..
How about today? Today!
Makino.
No!
I'm sorry.
If I don't do this..
you'll never admit it to yourself..
Always needing to be looked after..
You and
Tsukasa, too.
[Ore-sama] (The Great I Am)
If you threw away that cellphone..
I was thinking "I'd kill you".
Umm..
Domyouji..
I'm sorry.
You hit Nakatsuka-kun..
because of me..
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Don't know anything about that.
Domyouji Tower's Heliport.
Come right now.
If not I'll half-kill you..
What.. He's always one-sided..
What's wrong?
Papa has...
Papa has been laid-off!
He should... have been... the chief clerk...
WHY!?
Are you baka?
Who do you think you are?
There's a Beauty Contest to determine the Best Lady in Japan.
I'm always your ally.
Wanna get married?
Eh?