Why didn't you fight back?
Isn't it obvious?
Because I love you...
I love you...
Isn't it the same with you? Your faces were all bought by money!
Buying beauty with money..
What's wrong with that?
I'm sorry..
Awesome!
As expected of my pot-bellied woman, right?  (taikobara)
Pot-bellied?
I'm home!
I'm home.
Rui.
He looks exactly like Rui.
I'm the real one.
Ah, the real one, huh?
Eh?
No way.
This can't be true.
Rui-san.
It looks like him.
They just said that.
You should've at least contacted us.
I thought I'd surprise you.
It's been awhile.
Eh?
Ah, yeah.
Doing fine?
Ah, mm.
Hhmm, looks like someone's blushing.
I'm doing fine, too, Rui!
Doing fine?
Hhmm.. Looks like someone's blushing.
I'm doing fine, too, Rui!
Super Fine!
But you're all bruised up.
Why, what happened?
Yup, that was it, Rui.
Good that you've noticed!
Anyone would've noticed.
You'll be so surprised with my Dog News!
Dog?  Isn't it big?
Why, what's up?
The truth is,
Right now.
Makino and I are going out.
Eh?
Hmph, don't joke too much.
The one who's trying to get attention is that little girl.
Whichever way it may be, Tsukasa-bocchan will... (bocchan - young master)
We're going back to Japan.
Hai.
We're leaving by my jet plane immediately.
Understood, Executive director.
Well, these wounds are our
proof of love, you might say...
Um, no, we're not going out yet or anything...
That's awesome!
Eh?
No. If it's good or not, it's quite a difficult question. Or for me
it's a Nigashibu Choice (wrong grammar)
Use either Nigai or Shibui or Kujuu. (all means bitter)
Kujuu?
Are you trying to say Kujuukuri beach?
Then,
Let's celebrate at least.
You're right!
It's been awhile since the four of us have been together.
So let's PARTY!
The F4's together again.
Yeah.
You..
Why are you worse than a stupid turtle?
Coz' you're stupid after all.
Go and take your classes..
Although, I don't want to be told, by YOU.
Then, see you later.
Why don't you girls go, too?
Eh?
Are you sure?
We'll go..
It's like a dream!
No way..
We were the only ones invited!
You must be kidding.
No way, Domyouji-sama's joke is too intense.
It's not a joke, ugly!
Yuriko!
By the way,
Here.
Take it.
Wow, this is something.
So I can always reach you.
He's totally acting like my boyfriend already.
He's totally ignoring my feelings.
Could it be, you're confused?
Huh?
Because the bead-eyed prince has returned.
I'm home!
Wha-..
What's this?
Next then!
Nure tede awa! (easy profit)
That will surely be on the next exam!
I know!
When you're washing your hand (te),
it will be filled with bubbles (awa) and your hand
will become itchy! (nure te de - wet hand)
Okay, for that, use a rubber glove
and your hand will still be okay even from bubbles!
Umm..
Then the correct answer is?
Having lots of return with very little effort,
is what Nure Tede Awa means.
Oh I see.
Umm..
Then us having all these expensive looking furniture added to us..
Eh?
Nure Tede Awa.
Ah, welcome home, Tsukushi!
Took awhile to notice.
Wait, don't tell me, all these..
were sent by..
Domyouji-san!
What was that baka (idiot) thinking?
What do you mean by Baka?
You should be thankful!
Thankful? We won't be able to live properly this way.
Well, from the very beginning..
We were never living a proper life.
I know, but..
No, that's not what I mean..
With this we won't be able to step around.
Oh yeah.
Well, Papa thought about this.
Why don't we sell everything to the recycle shop?
Huh?
Papa lost almost all of our money in the horse race.
This is not a manga, you know.
Yeah, not a manga.
I bet everything on Take, hoping to get a big comeback,
so I can feed you guys something delicious.
(Take: horse's name)
But Take Yutaka.
Ebisu's "Ao Yuzu", go there.
Not "Go there!", okay?
What were you thinking with sending all of these furniture?
Ah, it was delivered already.
Those were super top of the line, so use them with care.
How are we going to use this?
You KNEW our house was small, right?
Stop talking nonsense, and just come!
Ah, wai-
My God, we're in the middle of a problem.
You're LATE!
Don't tell me, this is Tsukasa's girlfriend?
Eh?
You can say that.
You're joking, right?
Why this pathetic looking woman?
Impossible, this practically no-style girl?
Shut it, you old ladies!
None of your business, right?
Huh?
Well said, Makino!
It's none of your business, and that's how it is,
that's why get out of here, uglies!
Ugly?
What, ugly?
Wai-
Sit!
Umm, with that, can you just take everything back?
What are you saying?
What's wrong?
Quarreling again?
Then, why don't you guys too-
Eh?
No way, kiss me, too!
Okay, okay.
Mrs. Tsubaki.
Yes?
It seems like Mrs. Kaede is going back to Japan.
Really?
I'm afraid it has something to do with Mr. Tsukasa.
Oh, well.
She's finally starting to make her move, huh?
With this, it's genuinely my turn now, huh?
Impossible.
For Hanazawa Rui to do something like that.
Totally Impossible.
It's no good.
I won't be able to look at him properly.
Haa!!
Good Morning.
'morning...
This..
Huh?
That..
Seems like you're dripping..
Could it be, from that time?
Sorry for returning it so late.
You were holding onto it for so long..
It seems like you've changed. Aura maybe?
Really?
In France, did something happen with Shizuka-san?
Makino,
Yes..?
Will you go out with me?
Yes..
Eh!!
Hana Yori Dango - Boys Over Flowers
Episode 6
[Character] ** [Actor]
Makino Tsukushi ** Inoue Mao
Domyoji Tsukasa ** Matsumoto Jun
Hanazawa Rui ** Oguri Shun
Nishikado Sojiro ** Matsuda Shota
Mimasaka Akira ** Abe Tsuyoshi
Timing and Translation ** mhaellix
Translation ** Backalley
Editing and Release ** furransu
What do you mean by this?
But, I want to go to school.
Answer my questions.
Even you can neglect work
And worry about your son?
Unfortunately, I'm more worried about
the company than you.
If I was to go out with Makino,
How in the world will that affect the company?
Are you really going out with Tsukasa?
Uh, no.. that is..
That guy just said it on his own.
You see?
The truth is, I've always been aiming for you, Makino.
Dissatisfied with me?
Uh, no..
Forget about that Tsukasa.
Go out with me.
I've fallen for Makino Tsukushi.
Is there a problem with that?
Chairman of the Domyouji Zaibatsu?
I don't care if you're just playing around.
If you're just PLAYING AROUND with that commoner girl,
I couldn't care less.
I'm not playing around!
Unfortunately, I don't remember being raised,
by someone who jokes under this circumstance.
O-bocchama! (young master)
Out of my way!!
It was a joke, a joke.
Eh?
Tsukasa is my friend, you know.
Of course it'll bad, right?
Being all serious,
You're an interesting person.
The worst!
Huh?
Could it be you're dissappointed?
Not really, I wasn't..
Then,
Wanna secretly go out with me?
Eh?
That was a joke, too, right?
Ah, that's so funny.
Then, I've properly returned the handkerchief, okay?
Oh yeah,
Makino,
You've become much cuter than before.
Yeah.
Thanks.
What was that?
What in the world was that?
What happened to you?
Hanazawa Rui.
Tsukushi-chan.
I would like to talk to you..
About what happened before, I'm really sorry.
And,
thank you very much.
After doing all those awful things to you,
and still protecting me.
I was so unbelievably happy.
-  What's wrong with that?
I'm sorry.
After transferring here, I've always been with Tsukushi-chan.
That "weed power"..
with it's power and honesty..
it seems that I've gotten a complex out of it.
It's not like that has anything to do with...
Exactly,
"It's not like that has anything to do with it."
Eh?
That's why, I will,
not give up on Domyouji-san!
Huh?
Domyouji-san is after all,
a person that I've admired since I was young.
You see, formerly I was really ugly,
But right now, I've become this cute!
There's no reason why anyone will think that I'm inferior to Tsukushi-chan. Get it?
Not at all.
That's how it is, from now on "yoroshiku" (regards)
She's too unyielding!
Your furnitures,
I've taken it back to my place.
Thanks.
If you ever need it, just let me know. 'kay?
We probably won't need it in this lifetime.
Huh?
Uh, no, it's nothing.
Oh and yeah.
Investigate the background of this Makino Tsukushi and her family.
Understood.
If you feel like there's something strange around you, contact me immediately.
Something strange?
Okay? Do you understand?
Contact me immediately.
Tsubaki-sama.
It's been awhile, Okaa-sama (Mother, respectful)
May you please approve of the relationship
between Tsukasa and her?
Just to say that,
you came back all the way to Japan?
I don't want my precious little brother,
to feel the same heart-breaking experience I had.
Be careful with your mouth.
Your convenient and comfortable happiness,
For who's sake do you think it is?
With what I did, was there something wrong with it?
Whether or not there was something wrong with it,
I lost something.
Something like that..
In life, it is not enough to just have that, right?
It's true that I'm satisfied with my current life.
Then.
don't let your words come in between this.
You're someone who has left the Domyouji family, after all.
But I still remember after all..
How vulgar!
A married person,
should not be talking in such a vulgar way.
Okaa-sama,
Are you saying that it's vulgar
to seriously love somebody?
Seriously love?
An unknown feeling like that,
will have no merit whatsoever towards the Domyouji Group.
It became quite a dangerous atmosphere, huh?
You see?
It'll be bad if something happens,
that's why he drove me all the way here.
Seriously?
But doesn't that show how serious he is for you?
Okami-san. (landlady/owner/manager)
One time, there was a man whom I loved.
He was a dangerous yakuza man...
That usual pattern has started.
In the first place, he was a man from a Dango Ya. (ya - store)
That's why I, too, have started a Dango Ya.
He's a person who collects loans, and cheats people off,
with a face that looks like a geta (wooden clogs)
Could it be, it's..
Born and bred?
Katsushita Shibamata
(google this to understand what's going on)
It's Tora-san! (It was a show)
He's a wilful, selfish and clumsy man.
but he was serious towards the woman he loved.
I think about jumping into his arms.
I can imagine just how happy I can be.
Which Madonna is Okami-san?
Umm, I don't think she came out.
He's obviously a fool, but he was trying to be cool.
Plus that guy,
had an incredible Sister Complex.
Come to think of it, the situation is kinda like Domyouji.
But you know what,
What Kami-san is saying might have a reason.
Eh?
How about you jump into Domyouji-san's arms with all your strength?
Uh, jumping into his arms is..
Or could it be, you're concerned about your bead-eyed Prince?
Wanna secretly go out with me?
Uh, no..
You know what, Yuuki..
Wow, what a gorgeous person.
What?
Akira-kun.
Akira-kun came here?
Onee-san.
It's been awhile,
Yomogi-chan. (weed)
It's Tsukushi.
I shouldn't be saying this as her daughter..
But my mother is
a bit harsh, or should I say, she has a cruel side.
Aren't you gonna eat?
Oh.. Yes
In order for things to go her way,
she doesn't care about the means at all.
That's why Domyouji said those things.
Tsukasa
seems to be really serious about you.
See, I told you.
just jump into his arms.
But.
If you can't answer Tsukasa's feelings, don't push yourself.
But if there's even a bit of a chance,
I will fully support the both of you.
Tsukasa has somehow changed, you know.
He became honest,
or should I say more mature..
I think that's because of Tsukushi-chan.
But I won't be able to compare to rich people.
I'm just a poor commoner.
But if Domyouji-san is really serious, he'll adjust to our ways.
I know!
Yuuki-chan, right?
Do you have a boyfriend?
I do. He's tall and..
Then why don't we test if he'll be able to
adjust to Tsukushi's ways.
I quit, I quit.  It's boring!!!
Crushing defeat for Tsukasa!!
When I'm playing Mahjong,
"ki ga ki ga ja ne" (the air is not the air)
"Ki ga shirenai" (Can't understand the atmosphere)
Shut it!
100, 200, 300..
What?!
Ah..
Rui, you're actually winning.
It's been awhile. (since his last win)
You must be kidding, baka!
Who was that?
Ok, let's play!
The fight is from here on!
You still want to play?
I will.
It'll be better if you stop.
If I say I'm playing, I'm playing!
I won't let you run away with the win!
What's up with the sudden good mood?
That call was Makino, right?
That baka said,
"Tomorrow, let's go on a double date."
Double Date?
"Is it possible for us to go on a commoner's date?"
As if I'd go.
That's why you're in a good mood!
Isn't that great, Tsukasa.
Not at all!
Can the heaven given, Domyouji Tsukasa-sama
ever go to something as childish as a double date?
That's why calmly declined!
Then why are you in a good mood?
We're supposed to meet in front of Ueno's Saigo-san.
No way that's possible!
Then, is it okay if I go?
Eh?
Uh, no, because,
it's THAT, you know?
We're supposed to meet in front of Ueno's Saigo-san.
(Saigo is a political figure, 1827 - 1877)
What should I do?
Tomorrow, Hanazawa Rui's going.
What's up with that?
How about Domyouji-sama?
It was impossible after all.
For him to adjust to our lifestyle.
You might be happy that your prince is coming,
But then what's the point?
Yuuki, sorry.
I have to hang up.
I'll call you back okay? Sorry.
Hello.
It's me.
Hanazawa Rui.
Eh?
Right now, I'm downstairs.
Huh??
Good evening.
Tomorrow, Tsukasa will probably go.
He'll probably contact you.
That's all.
See ya.
Ummm...
Did something happen?
Ever since you came back from France, you've been a little strange.
Is that so..
Did something happen over there?
Everyday was a day full of happiness..
Everyday, the two of us cooked food
that we weren't accustomed to,
At night we barely sleep and just talk about our childhood days.
Ah, we also talked a lot about you, Makino.
About me?
Shizuka
says that she really liked you, Makino.
But,
those days didn't last very long.
Shizuka became very busy.
I was left all alone.
I wasn't able to do anything for her sake.
I remember the first time you fought back against Tsukasa.
A brat like you who has never earned what you have,
Don't be so full of yourself!
I thought, that really was the case.
I..
can't do anything for the person I love.
Ah, I wonder why I'm telling you all these things.
That's not true.
You're not a person who can't do anything.
In school,
when everybody was putting me through some tough times,
you.. saved me..
You became my only ally.
That's why, I..
for me, atleast.. I..
have been
saved by you, a lot, a lot of times.
The reason why I can be here right now..
Is because of Hanazawa Rui.
Makino.. I..
It's from Tsukasa, right?
It's okay that I go to that commoner's double date.
That's all.
My God..
He said he's going tomorrow?
Yeah.
That's all he said, then he hung up.
My God, what's up with him?
Tsukushi!
Oh no!
I'm sorry.  Let's talk next time..
What were you doing, with this time?
Ah, sorry.
There was a cat.
A cat?
A cat, huh?
They're late..
Careless bastard..
Being just a commoner, and making the "Great Me" wait?
Don't lash out okay?
It's my precious best friend and her boyfriend, after all.
I know.
Tsukushi!
Sorry for being late!
Hey.
Nice to meet you,
I'm Makino Tsukushi.
And this is, Domyouji-san.
Nice to meet you.
- What, what?
Your name is Domyouji?
Domyouji is..
It can be.  "Dou, myou ji?"
(What do you think about my last name?)
What a name to have!
Let's hurry up and go.
What in the world was that?
Let's go and have fun, have fun..
Being late and not even a proper greeting?
Man..
Where are we going?
Huh, didn't I mention it?
Ueno Zoo.
Ueno Zoo?
Wow, it's been so long since I've gone to a zoo.
How 'bout you, Domyouji-kun?
It's my first time at a zoo.
Seriously?
So it's your first time seeing live animals?
Oh, you're afraid of animals!!
Ah, for me, my last time was during Junior High, right Yuuki?
Yeah.
If I want to see animals, I go to an African Savannah.
Ah, Savannah?
You're so lucky!
Could it be, that Domyouji-kun is an unbelievable obocchama-kun?
Obocchama-kun?
Hey, look at that, isn't it so cute?
Rather, doesn't his face look like Domyouji-kun's?
Hey you,
better be careful with your words.
Hotoke no kao mo, mitsu aru. (Even Buddha has 3 faces)
(It's supposed to be Hotoke no kao mo, san do. He read the kanji wrong.
It means "Don't try the patience of a Buddha")
Stupid!
What in the world was that?  I don't get it.
You're a funny person.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute, Nakatsuka-kun.
Those two look good together..
Is this what you call a commoner's date? Huh?!
What's up with that bastard?
Why are you getting yourself involved with that kind of trash?
That's just not possible!!
Sorry.
You're right, it's impossible...
I thought that someone who Yuuki will date, would be okay.
Hmm, shall we go home, already?
If we go home right now,
wouldn't it be bad for the two of you?
Don't worry..
I won't hit him..
But I'm extremely annoyed, okay?
Thank you.
Hey, hey!
Domyouji-kun, Domyouji-kun!
From here on, let's go separately!
Let us.
We will.
Let's do that!
Rather, that's what we'll do!
Huh, where's the cellphone I gave you?
Ah, that...
Today, I left it at home..
I see.
By the way, when I called last night, were you alone?
It's that late, you know..
I'm alone, obviously.
I see..
Hey, wait!
You wanted this, right? Take it.
Isn't it cute?
Bimyou~ (unclear, weird or strange)
Ah it's so cute!
Lesson Panda!
Huh?
It's Lesser Panda (also called Red Panda)
It's Lesson Panda!
He's a real baka..
You're the baka one...
But you know,
Us going on a date like this..
It feels like we're finally looking like a couple..
You know...
About that..
Don't worry.
I'm not wrongly assuming..
Eh?
I was saying those kinds of things in front of Rui, but..
I haven't properly heard your feelings..
But..
When I said I love you, I really am serious.
Until you've properly answered with your feelings..
I will be waiting...
Well, if you reject a perfect man, like the GREAT ME,
you will definitely regret it.
You know what they say, a fish that escapes will swim...
(He's trying to say that if you let go of an opportunity,
you'll never get it again.)
Wait a minute!
Just now, was that a gag? (joke)
Or are you a truly stupid?
What?
Wait a minute.
Could it be, you're naturally that way?
Hey, wanna buy some drinks?
I'm kinda thirsty.
Okay, then I'll go buy some drinks for everyone.
Oi, Yuuki!
Makino!
-Yes?
I'm going to take a sh*t.
Go ahead.
I'm really sorry..
I'm getting quite scared..
he can snap anytime..
He's usually not like that...
Rather,
I don't think he meant anything bad with that..
Eh? With that?
That attitude?
Look, it's like,
he's trying to make sure there are no walls between them.
If the people at Eitoku hears that kind of words towards Domyouji,
it's instant death, INSTANT DEATH!
Domyouji-kun, wait a minute.
Just now, I just received a call from a girl I know.
And because of that, wanna leave this place?
Huh?
Well, cause I told them that I was with a really good looking guy.
They're bugging me saying
"I want to meet him! Let me meet him!"
I was thinking, but..
Domyouji-kun, could it be that you're pretty stupid?
I wonder where they went?
They're a little late..
You know,
I AM going out with Yuuki, but..
It's honestly boring, or rather, bimyou..
I have no interest in whatever you're saying..
Don't try to act cool, and let's just leave this place.
Or rather,
isn't the girl with you, honestly a bimyou?
Makino is a bimyou?
That's why, I'm going to introduce you to a better woman.
Hey what was that about, you bastard!
What part of Makino is bimyou?
Her beautiful eyes are not deserving of this world, okay?
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey are you okay?
- I'm at my patience's limit already!
I'm going home!
As for you, try to find a better man to date.
Wait!
Makino!!
Me being a part of your commoner's date,
will never happen again.
Did you do something to Domyouji-san?
Like that's possible.
What's up with that guy?
I just placed my hand on his shoulder..
You just placed your hand on his shoulder?
Yeah.
Isn't he a bit strange and crazy?
Nakatsuka-kun.
Today, I made time for your sake you know!
Hey, do you understand?
Why do I have to be hit by him!
I'm very sorry.
I'm really very sorry.
Wait, where are you going?
I'm going home!!!
I'm so pissed, I can't take this anymore.
I'm sorry, Yuuki..
It's not your fault at all, Tsukushi..
I'm sure Nakatsuka-kun did something..
Even Domyouji-san wouldn't hit someone without a reason, right?
This kind of things hasn't happened lately, you know.
Today, Nakatsuka-kun has been saying some biting words..
I was kinda scared..
Ahh, shux..
I wonder if it's over..
between me and him..
If we go home right now,
wouldn't it be bad for the two of you?
Until you've properly answered with your feelings..
I will be waiting..
Which side of him should I believe in...
Tsukushi! We have a problem!
What, in the end, you ended up fighting?
I didn't fight with Makino.
Ah, the double date was a failure, huh?
Anyway, why do you know that I was with Makino?
Tsukasa..
If you don't properly take a hold of her heart..
What happened to me, will happen to you..
Huh?
Do you know where your real enemy is?
Being this late at night, sorry for visiting so suddenly.
Nishida.
Yes.
Show THAT.
Steve, Vincent.
I'll be frank with you.
I have 300 Million right here.
300 Million?
With this, I would like Tsukushi-san to give Tsukasa up completely.
Eh?
It may be discourteous,
but it seems that your family is financially in trouble.
Yes, we are greatly in trouble.
Papa!!
As you may know,
Tsukasa has a big future ahead of him..
Right now, it'll be bad if he trips upon a small stone.
Please go ahead and accept this..
Don't tell me,
You won't be saying that you're seriously inlove, right?
If you're just playing around, then it's fine.
Our Chairman is trying to say that,
your daughter is the one who will get scarred.
Okusama? (Lady of the House)
Okusama?
What are you doing?
Mama!
Take your money, and please go home.
The feeling of a parent, who's child is being
insulted right in front of her.
Does a rich person like you not understand that?
Salty.
This is really okay with you, right?
When you nameru a common person! It's salty!
(nameru: look down upon or lick)
Excuse me for coming, tonight!
Excuse us.
- Mama!!
You okay?
Mama, I've changed my opinion about you. Thank you.
I don't know about your last line.
But I was really touched!
Tsukushi,
Listen well.
- Yeah.
Make sure you get along with Domyouji-san.
No matter what happens be with him..
Make sure you take a hold of the whole Domyouji Zaibatsu's fortune!
Don't be satisfied with just a stingy 300 Million!
That is why,
make sure that you and Domyouji-san will..
Mama!!
Just kidding!
Let's eat our meal.
Uh..
Don't scare us like that.
Tomorrow, it's Yakiniku, ok? (bbq)
If you don't properly take a hold of her heart..
What happened to me, will happen to you..
Hey, help me!
Rui, what's wrong?
Rui.
Why do you..
Yesterday, I went to Makino's place.
Today, I left it at home..
It's that late, you know..
I'm alone, obviously.
When I called,
could it be, that you were together?
Yeah, we were together.
What is going on?
Tsukasa, look at this.
What do you want to talk about?
You know, I..
I can't be with you with such half-baked feelings.
Yesterday, properly explain what happened with you and Nakatsuka-kun.
By the way, you...
This..
You said you left it at home.
Why do you have...
That's what I want to know!
That doesn't matter.
Just answer my question.
Doesn't matter?
The reason why you hit Nakatsuka-kun. Explain it to me!
I don't want to say it.
So you're the type that hits people without reason?
I was pissed off that's why I hit him, that's all!
What in the world is that?
You're that kind of person after all..
You can ruin other people's happiness and still feel alright about it?
- Eh?
They broke up already.
That's great.
What are you doing?
I was pissed off that's why I hit you!
You know what..
Even if you're pissed, there are things that you can and can't do!
Yuuki is,
feeling really sad because of you, you know!
She should be thankful the "Great Me".
Are you baka?
You really haven't changed.
Red-tagging people,
and then bullying them. You are the worst kind of person.
You're a human trash!
What?
I don't ever want to see your face again!
Hey wait!
Oh, and yeah..
Yesterday,
Your mother came to our place.
Eh?
Brought a great amount of money,
And asked me to give up on you..
Tell your mother..
That I will..
no longer have anything to do with you. So don't worry.
Domyouji is a
BAKA!!!!!
But, for trusting that guy even a little bit, I'm the baka one.
Yesterday, you two had a fight?
Fight or not..
I no longer have anything to do with that guy.
I see..
That guy..
He's the worst...
Wait...
I wonder, why I've
never fallen inlove with you, Makino, until now..
Just a minute is fine..
Let me stay like this.
Did something happen?
Sorry..
Just let me stay like this..
What's this?
So that's how it is?