Don't be such an idiot!
In my ordinary life...
It hurts, onee-chan.
Nee-chan?
... yet another great person has appeared.
Hi there.
Perhaps he really likes you, Tsukushi.
What?
Thank you.
Wait a minute, Rui.
If you meet any people in Paris who are bothering you,
tell me at once,
and the three of us will fly down to help you.
I'll be off.
Rui!
Hanazawa Rui followed Shizuka-san to Paris.
You can't be too fast.
If you want someone to love you,
you must first love her.
Oh no, onee-chan.
I feel like...
I've just been struck by lightning.
Sunday, 1pm at the open area
at "Ebisu Garden Place" near the clock.
And this irritating guy actually
did something as outrageous as...
Unbelievable.
Why?
Um..
Makino!
C... C... Cold...
W... Wait a minute.
Suddenly grabbing me like that.
What on earth are you trying to do?
I'm glad that you're safe.
Eh?
I was afraid you might be in trouble.
It's okay...
Can I ask why you are so late?
Huh?
If you can't give me a reason, I'll kill you.
W... Who said I'll come?
I never even agreed to you in the first place.
Didn't I ask you?
Eh?
You were actually here long before already.
Perhaps, you've fallen for me?
Huh?
Wait... Wait...
This can't be good.
It's so cold.
Let's go and have some hot tea.
You really make people angry.
Let's go then.
Huh? Wait for me.
Wait a minute.
Let's stop here.
This building is 4 storeys high.
The Ebisu sold here is delicious and cheap.
They even sell cake here.
Are you sure, here?
Do you come here often?
Don't complain so much.
I don't like it.
Eating at low-class places like these,
my pride doesn't permit it.
"Doesn't permit it"?
Don't you think that you shouldn't always be
so concerned about your pride?
Hi there Miss.
Please take a look. We are doing a survey.
Please look carefully.
That...
It's very easy to do...
Hey.
Stop it.
Huh?
That...
Suddenly hitting that guy, what on earth were you thinking?
You can't be too nice to people who bother
the person you love.
What?
What do you mean by that?
Is the cake here really nice?
My "Bello" is very picky.
("Bello" = Stomach. Weird choice of words)
"Bello"...?
Could your Japanese be quite weak?
Does it matter if my Japanese is weak?
It's just that I'm not good with words.
He really is dumb.
Eh? It's not working.
Hey hey hey.
Don't tell me its spoilt.
It can't be...
You're joking.
Hey hey!
Anyone out there?
It can't be.
Let's call for help.
Good idea.
No reception here.
It's all your fault.
I'm sorry.
It can't be helped.
We have to go through the top.
Eh?
Get up.
Huh?
Step onto my shoulders.
You're kidding.
Step onto your shoulders?
What are you so shy about?
It's not that I'm shy about anything...
Then come on.
Hurry up.
What are you doing?
Wait... Stop!
Stop what you are doing!
It hurts.
Alright.
What's all this?
I'm scared.
Help me up.
It's so frightening.
Looks like the situation is really bad.
What to do...
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!!!!
What was that?
It's no good,
I can't hold it anymore.
Wait...
What are you doing, pervert?
I need to let go.
Look away.
Disgusting.
Help!!
What on earth are you doing?
It's so scary. So scary...
Grab this.
I'm... I'm going to fall.
Stupid,
now's not the time to be saying such things.
I'm... I'm scared.
Help me quickly!
Here...
Makino...
Huh?
What?
St... Stop.
I'll never forgive you if you do something perverted.
I...
S... Stop... Settle down.
No... No... Don't do it.
Don't come closer.
Alright, next is "Kikiippatsu".
(Lit: To hang by a stand of hair.
An extremely delicate/dangerous situation.)
Oh. This will definitely be in the next exam.
I got it.
It means that if you hit someone
with a black mustache in the stomach,
it will hurt so much that he will leave his seat.
("patsu" is to leave/depart)
Right,
let's get this guy to "Kikiippatsu".
Wrong!
Then what does it mean?
It refers to a situation which is extremely dangerous,
that's "Kikiippatsu".
I see.
Listen here, kid. Don't write the word wrongly as "hand".
("Kiki" for "te")
"Kikiipatsu"!!
Please don't say such lame things, dad.
You really are very childish.
Yea... Well then dad will only drink
a bottle of beer only next week.
Dad is in a "Kikiipatsu" (situation).
Tsukushi is so late today.
No... Doing this... What are you thinking of doing?
Stop... What are you...
Go away.
Oh my... It's hot.
Hana Yori Dango - Boys Over Flowers
Episode 4
[Character] ** [Actor]
Makino Tsukushi ** Inoue Mao
Domyoji Tsukasa ** Matsumoto Jun
Hanazawa Rui ** Oguri Shun
Nishikado Sojiro ** Matsuda Shota
Mimasaka Akira ** Abe Tsuyoshi
Timing and Translation ** Backalley
Editing and Release ** furransu
So... So cold...
You really are troublesome.
I've got it.
Open your mouth.
Eh?
What's that?
It's medicine.
Don't just give me any strange medicine.
Shut up and do what I said.
There will be people coming to get us in the morning.
Hang in there.
You...
Don't feel cold?
Commoners are used to the cold, so it's all right.
I'm as tough as wild grass.
("Tsukushi" means "wild grass")
Sorry.
Then again,
we ended up like this
because you were late in the first place.
What's so funny?
In this state, you no longer have the dignity
of a member of F4.
Shush.
The Red Paper...
I revoked it.
Perhaps it's a bit too late.
You're only kidding yourself.
You think I'll forgive you so easily?
Hey hey...
Eh?
What are you two doing?
Ah..
It hurts...
This won't do.
You can't just enter the building before it opens.
If you want to do those sort of things, go to a hotel.
Can you make it back alone?
Yea.
Makino. About that...
I'm really sorry for the mess I made.
Then let me thank you...
Eh?
Quickly apologise...
Apologise...?
Stop!
Did the two of you kiss then?
How could we?
I never intended to.
I ran before he could do anything.
Oh.
So, your family must be quite worried.
Oh no, they're the worst...
You never even came to us to discuss
what you wanted to do!
I'm sorry.
I never thought that onee-chan would resort
to doing those sort of things.
I'm sorry.
Where exactly did you go?
Dad thought you met with great trouble.
This is the result of spending the night away from home
for the very first time.
You didn't have any problems in school?
That... It created a huge fuss...
A huge fuss?
So tired...
Hmphh..
Huh?
Tsuki...
Tsuki... Tsuki... Tsuki.........
Tsuki...?
Not bad eh, Tsuki.
I'm really envious.
After that, the attitude of everyone in the school
suddenly changed?
Tsuki, let's go shopping later.
Oh yea, let's go and have lots of fun later.
Yea... I got it... OK OK
Unbelievable.
And then... Doumyoji also...
They're here.
Yo!
Hey Tsukasa. Is this true?
No... That's...
Ah, it's true.
Eh?
Hey hey. Seems like Tsukasa has become more of a man.
I guess.
Wait a minute...
Perhaps Doumyoji-san really likes you?
No way that can happen.
Ah, but he told me he revoked The Red Paper.
It's alright now.
Come back to school.
Are you sure it's really alright?
Mm.
NO!
Ah, I'm sorry.
Are you serious about Makino Tsukushi, eh Tsukasa?
I'll put this here...
I'm definitely supporting him.
But don't our girlfriends need to be
picked out and approved by our family?
Eh? It's not here?
The deeper he goes, he'll end up hurting Makino Tsukushi
even more in the end.
I won't let her get hurt by anything.
Eh?
I won't do anything to hurt Makino.
Hey hey, Tsukasa.
Are you too obsessed with her?
Now now Tsukasa.
The first thing that makes a girl happy
is the desires of her man.
How does it feel to be a bit more gentle?
I didn't do that.
We haven't got to the "dating stage" yet.
But then Tsukasa, you spent a night alone with her.
Ah. It's always best to be natural on the first.
I can't let this go on...
You've been together for a night...
No way...
I must be responsible for my actions.
What "responsible"?
Oh, yea... yea yea...
Is Tsukasa alright?
What's he going to do next?
Next time, let's have a double date.
I've said many times,
that sort of thing (dating) never happened to us.
You even said "us", that's admitting it.
No way, I'm not saying anything else.
Have mercy on me...
You're so carefree, how I envy you, Yuuki.
You get to study with people of similar tastes.
You still can't forget that "Marble Eyes"?
Eh?
Makino, I really like your determination.
Don't forget him.
Lady boss.
If you forget about a man,
another new one will appear.
There will be new hurts,
new wounds of the heart.
Oh.
I used to love this man called John.
He sounds like a foreigner.
I forgot everything when I
was in by his warm arms.
John!!! His other name was Lenon.
Eh?
In other words, John Lenon?
Rounded spectacles really looked good on him.
He was such a gentleman.
I was completely taken in...
I only needed to hear his gentle voice calling out to me...
I would forget everything else.
We had such a lovely time together
Old lady, isn't your real name Ono Yoko?
"Sengoku Sachiyo"
(Lit: A thousand generations of happiness)
Sigh... An opportunity wasted...
He was trivial like a small worm.
What a joke.
How old exactly is Lady Boss?
You can't be too fast. To be loved,
one has to first love.
Yes...
There will be new hurts,
new wounds of the heart...?
Maybe he really likes Tsukushi-chan.
No no no...
This is really unbelievable!
Why is it like this?
Why are you here? And you need to take off
your shoes before you come in.
Why?
Alright alright. Doumyoji-san is here to apologise
about what happened last night.
Why didn't you tell us earlier that
you were together with the wealthy Doumyoji-san?
Eh? But...
From today onwards, I hope that you'll take good care of
my daughter until the two of you are old.
That's how I feel as well.
Wa... Wait... What are you all doing?
Onii-sama, do you need me to get you
a bottle of beer?
Oh, if you don't mind otou-to (little brother).
No problem at all!
It's not good to drink beer!
Why are you all so nice to him?
We're all family, right?
I have something to say to you,
come here.
What?
Hurry up.
Ma'am.
I'm having my meal now, please don't bother me.
I know, but...
Is it urgent?
The piece of puzzle that we left in Tsukasa-sama room...
Is it because he ignored the puzzle,
that Tsukasa-sama has more and more conflicts with you?
Perhaps...
I've said what I shouldn't have, please forgive me.
Nishida.
Yes.
Please check on Tsukasa's activities.
I understand.
Why isn't there anyone here?
I've got this place covered.
Oh, I see.
Eh?
Didn't you say you had something to talk about?
Is that why you had this whole place emptied out?
But I'm really touched,
it's the first time I visited a commoner's house.
The way my family sees the value of things
is completely different from yours.
So please don't suddenly visit us.
You seem a bit wet.
Hey, are you listening?
Isn't that Rui's?
Eh?
You haven't returned it to him?
Yea...
You... Do you like Rui?
Eh?
Even if Rui is going after Shizuka,
do you still secretly love him?
It's not like that.
Anyway, it's none of your business.
Who says it's none of my business?
Eh?
Rui... He really likes apples.
Huh?
But he only eats shredded apples.
But I believe that it's more manly to just
eat the apple bite by bite.
Hey Rui!
Can you stop that scratching sound?
If you continue scratching, you'll become a Buddha.
(Another of Tsukasa's bad jokes.
The word to describe the scratching sound in Japanese
is likened to a Buddha.)
Don't worry. I'm Christian.
Tsukasa.
There's still a lot of apple tea left.
Soujiro, can you stop being so obsessed with tea?
Talk about something more cool.
That's not bad too, Tsukasa.
Hey Soujiro, want to try some dance moves?
I must say first that it has nothing to do with me.
That was the first time they just ignored
what I said.
Hey, you guys, look here.
This is how you eat an apple
It's much more convenient than making it
into powder.
As for me, I never learnt to eat like that.
Hang on a sec.
Hanazawa Rui really said that?
He said something like that.
In other words, you made it up (fiction).
Still, Rui eats apples like that.
And I was extremely annoyed by the way he ate it.
Rui, if you continue eating apples,
it's more easy for you to become bald.
Eh?
From then onwards, he never ate another apple
that he once loved.
I took away what Rui loved the most.
That was during early spring last year.
Umm...
But, I never thought I would say those things about
becoming bald and all.
Although I don't really know what you're talking about...
It is like that.
That's just what happened between Rui and I.
Truthfully?
It was just like that.
Oh!
Rui!
That was why at the airport...
I still don't get it.
That's why I say you still love Rui.
I...
Umm...
What if... What if I actually liked Rui?
He's still got Shizuka-san.
If you really like him, he'll definitely fall for you as well.
Eh?
I've seen many women, and they've always done it.
You're back!
Good work! Tsukushi.
You must become a modern lady, Tsukushi.
It's no longer a dream that we can all be rich and famous.
I'm going to buy lots of beer!
In the future when I have lots of money,
I'll buy many games.
Buy buy buy...
Umm...
I've thought about it.
How?
That guy really is an idiot.
Eh?
He's serious about it, Tsukushi.
It can't be.
Why hasn't Sakurako come back to school?
Hey, Tsuki. Don't forget about our outing later today.
Eh?
Didn't agree that we'll go to the Club and have lots of fun?
C... Club?
I'm sorry, I was forced to go.
I got it. I'll let the Lady Boss know.
Oh, we've got customers, bye.
Welcome.
Is Makino Tsukushi around?
I'm sorry, she didn't come for work today.
Are you on good terms with Makino?
Well, we've been friends since middle school (secondary school).
Well, then you should be Makino's good friend.
I guess...
You got some time to spare? We'd like to take you with us.
Umm... I have work now...
It's okay...
Wait... Lady Boss!
Wait a minute, what are you trying to do?
We'd like to borrow this girl for a while.
What's this all about? I'm calling the police.
Everything... I'll buy it all.
This whole place.
Have fun.
You can change so fast.
Do you accept payment by card?
Hey wait! Lady Boss!
So similar...
To a man I've met before.
They're good...
You can do that later, have a drink first.
Cheers!
Hey hey. Don't you think that guy is great?
No way, he's soooo handsome.
Don't you think, he looks a bit like Hanazawa Rui?
Eh? There is a resemblance.
He's looking here!
No way, he's coming.
He's here already.
- Hi there.
- Hi.
I'm going to the washroom.
Are you alone?
Hey, do you want to join me down here?
He really does look like Rui.
Tsukasa has fallen into the river of love
and he doesn't care about the consequences at all.
Although I feel that it's OK for
Tsukasa and Makino to be toghether.
But I don't want Tsukasa to fall too deep into this.
That's between the two of them.
I don't think we should interfere.
It's okay if they're just playing.
But what if both of them run into serious problems.
You get it?
I don't get it.
You don't understand?
I don't understand what both of you
are trying to get at.
I'll take my leave now.
Ah, wait.
Don't bother about her.
She's the type that gives me a big headache.
Sakurako?
How can it be?
Hey hey.
Here.
Eh?
For you.
Is that beer (sake)?
No, it's not. It's oolong tea.
If you don't mind.
Cheers.
What's your name?
I'm Makino Tsukushi.
Tsukushi-chan? That's a cute.
Oh... No...
Hey, why don't you follow me out?
Eh?
But...
It's nothing much... Let's go.
A dream?
Eh?
It's not a dream.
Why am I like this? Don't tell me that guy...
Oh no! What have I been doing?
I didn't do anything. Nothing at all.
And the first time always involves some bleeding...
(Hint hint)
HEY!
Woah!
It's already noon. What have you been doing?
Have you been waiting long for me?
Who says I'm waiting for you?
I just happened to be passing by.
But then you'd be going in the opposite direction
You talk too much!
Get in!
Having lunch with F4? How envious.
We can't forgive her. Definitely not.
Yuriko.
What would you like to eat?
It's okay.
You don't normally get to eat good food.
So don't worry.
But, I've got my own packed lunch.
Really, there's no need.
Don't make us men lose our dignity!
Where did you go yesterday?
We were looking for you at your working place,
but the told us you took the day off.
Ah... You went there...
I had something on yesterday...
Maybe it's another man.
Hey hey hey... Is that true?
She doesn't look like the type to do those sort of things.
I...
Makino is certainly not that type of girl!!
Even for you guys,
you will talk when your sleep.
But when you're awake and talking,
you don't call that talking in your sleep
You might say what you say in your sleep when you are awake,
but when you're awake, you don't say
what you won't say when you're asleep.
What you say when you're awake,
you say it because you're not asleep...
What the heck are you saying?
You yourself don't even know what you're talking about.
Shut up!
In other words, you should say what you would say
in your sleep, when you sleep.
I think he meant REM sleep.
(REM - Rapid Eye Movement. A sleeping disorder.)
He sleeps like a ram.
Why are we talking about goat meat?
Yes!
That guy is easily excited.
Sakurako?
Eh?
It's best if it doesn't get worse than this.
Tsukushi, nothing really happened that night?
No no no no...
Definitely not.
You better be serious about what
doing you and Doumyoji-san are doing.
What? Why arey you suddenly saying this?
If you can't take it,
or if you don't like it then just tell him straight.
But, it doesn't make a difference whether
I reject him or not.
Anyway, I don't think he truly likes me.
He does like you.
And Doumyoji's friends are truly worried about
the two of you.
But then, Yuuki,
the two of them are still rich kids.
You'd better be careful.
I don't know what those two are really like,
but I can tell they're sincere from what they said.
Doumyoji-san is actually a very lonely person.
I heard he was brought up by a mother who
is constantly unhappy about things around her.
He lived in a very harsh environment.
Perhaps that's why he's overbearing.
Actually, beyond his fierce front,
he yearns to be loved by someone.
"Yearns to be loved"...
Some outrageous things have been done to me.
I really don't get it.
Good morning.
Hey... What's wrong?
Don't act dumb, you...
You took advantage of the trust Doumyoji-san had in you.
I still can't believe you actually did such a thing.
What are you saying?
Don't spout nonsense.
Come here! Tsuki...
It hurts! What are you doing?!
Take a look!
Stop it! Let me go!
Take a good look.
What's that?
What you've done is the most demeaning thing
a woman can ever do.
No! This...
Still denying it?
Not only was it Doumyoji-san,
you deceived everyone in Eitoku Gakuen.
Even if you rely on all your previous methods,
we won't give in to you.
I suggest you prepare yourself!
What are you doing!!
What do you think you're doing...?
Please take a look at this.
It's not what you think, Doumyoji.
What's the meaning of this, Makino?
I think I was taken advantage of
by someone who really hates me.
Believe me...
I must definitely find out who did this.
Love. It happens when you least expect it.
That woman is highly dangerous.
I can't let him go.
I will kill you.